[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
K KY
key
yay look at me wow wo whoo
wo I have
upgraded
outfit wow cute Kitt we're looking even
more like the character pie
Berry thank you for the upgrade it
wasn't even necessary but now it's like
whoo oh I have to be careful not to move
around too much because otherwise you
know you'll see my naked shoulder you'll
see that I'm naked under this
no yeah today will waha Berry yes waah
Berry will play uh more of this cute
game um possibly my game of the
year quite
possibly dead beats are you still here
too thank you for the r
kaori look I look like
her hi pieber she's so cute I think last
time we played in full screen so we're
going to play again in full
screen
twins yeah yeah
my arms are so
jelly jelly as they're not jealous of
your arms no they're just jelly really
because
I I I carried a a big package of cat
sand
like felt like I carried it
from I don't know a whole pilgrimage
path okay really really jelly really my
arms are so M so nump like bringing over
my water jug was already so
painful you have become strong I don't
know maybe I've gained
some yeah some muscles from today but
they got SC that
much so like really oh my god it feels
so numb I can't grasp anything I can't
grip anything it's my I was thinking so
too it's my workout for today I wouldn't
have had time for anything else
anyway so with these weak arms I hope
that at least the controller uh I'll
have grip over it hopefully uh we what
AM we in the middle
[Music]
of maybe the journal will tell me ah we
have to find the pie maker in theak
Village I finally made it into the
village I don't like dressing like a
warrior but it's the only way to find
the pie maker I need to ask the
villagers about the village breaker talk
to humans Z other ah that Village ah I
remember now I remember remember I
remember I
remember oh Baku magic recovered
oh what was that
again is this Dark Souls yeah cute Dark
Souls talk talk to humans I'm scared
they will pberry would actually have a
reason to be scared but she's too naive
to be scared but you know because humans
don't like witches in this
game uh I think we'll just do we just go
go do we just go
I think we just
[Music]
go
oh we don't have a teleportation to go
right there but we can get close
with with the Merchants Road I
suppose not sponsored I just love this
game uh oh oh no no but I don't know if
I remember where W wo W wo wo wo oh this
is so hidden ah this
way yeah we played this for the first
time last week and I got so hooked on it
I think this way for the
village was it let me can I
uh
probably I think it was that way yeah
yeah yeah ah here we are lak
forest and
then
uh was it
uh which way which which way haha this
way maybe I think that's not the way to
the Village you won't find the pie maker
there okay that was not the
way this way
oh enter yes okay found it ah my mouse
cursor curse my mouse cursor oh I'm
wearing the
[Music]
helmet uh now we don't look so like each
other anymore
oh
man okay eight humans are you do you
[Music]
count okay I suppose that
counted oh they don't like her why she
makes great PES
[Music]
okay they don't want to talk about it
either that was Free People the other
one I I don't think I can talk to
them wait there's a weird old man over
there 3 out of 8 yeah 4 out of
8 oh that voice doesn't sound like a
child from our village oh wait he
doesn't
even it doesn't even hear me he doesn't
even perceive me oh can I enter
oh hello I'll talk to you guys inside
[Music]
then I don't have parents that's kind of
rude for you to assume that I have
parents oh wait I mean I I suppose I do
I just don't know about them why am I
wet why do I have like a wet
[Music]
effect oh you don't count oh but there's
an
item oh
berries real messed up yeah you don't
know like maybe my mom died maybe
something I don't know maybe I'll have
maybe I have two dads ever thought about
that really not sensitive of you
[Music]
did you guys
count wow wow why is she so hated must
be a
[Music]
witch was it is it how many number six
okay one more in this house I
think oh wa you got an item too that I
can
steal aged Berry
[Music]
oh how dare you put that name in your
mouth wow wow wow wow I'm shook head
okay I you think that was 7 out of
eight okay I have one more house
here oh oh oh oh you oh I can buy and
not sell only
buy oh punch red
tail Rich pudding
[Music]
juice wait who else can I talk to is
there someone over
here oh yeah oh whoo who are you
[Music]
great
David no no no don't take my helmet I
think I have to keep it
[Music]
on don't wor if it's broken I I'm not
going to use it in the battlefield or
[Music]
anything Kyla looking
different
[Music]
oh huh why are you so sensitive about it
you have to act as if you didn't hear
it come
on for that I will open your treasure
chest oh
performance enhancing equipment re
receive
recipes a small Anvil is in front of you
okay W look at the water oh I want to
swim in the
water I want to swim oh look who's there
we know her from last
[Music]
time oh she's already angry not IM for
uhoh I'm right in front of
her she doesn't know this I'm standing
literally right in front of
her oh wait that
looks yeah but that tent looks
interesting it has a like a dream
catcher thingy on it feels like a witch
could be held captive inside of it I
don't
know very nearsighted yeah she needs
glasses but she probably doesn't doesn't
want
to uh admit it seven out of
[Music]
eight last one person
do
oh cuz the children were not reacting
these people have talked to I don't
think I could talk to her them what
about up here
feel like I'm leaving the village if I
go there Farm North oh maybe it still
[Music]
counts they have a
Golem is that uh Anna on the top left of
the
screen maybe I don't know also I noticed
my hat my hat is my hat is too big let
me lower myself a little bit
[Music]
okay big
chilling Colossus
number no that's Ethan okay Ethan
wow look at his outfit he's got like the
same kind of fabric under his gloves
like Marin said by ooh spicy maybe they
went to the same shop
oh ah what a show off I was going to
take it down
[Music]
why why why are you also someone that
nobody is allowed to say their name
[Music]
on your
field they finally noticed me
the
helmet the
helmet oh that's maybe why
the the girl didn't see
me I guess that adds to you know I mean
the rest of my cloes she has seen before
but okay the helmet adds a little bit of
an element of Disguise
[Music]
he hasn't even met me before and he
knows but the other girl didn't know
even though she met me
[Music]
before what the don't expose me
like that
[Music]
oh oh you underestimate
me I make
[Music]
you in trouble well if I'm not such a
wild witch and I suppose you wouldn't
get in trouble anyway hm hm
huh so maybe you do think I'm a wild
witch after all if you think that your
hometown would be in
[Music]
trouble
mous why do you hate my mouse so much
what's your problem with my
mouse small and it's just want to watch
the stream
[Music]
okay it doesn't hurt
anybody it it it wouldn't even hurt an a
fly or an ant
[Music]
okay ah that was the name of the girl
wasn't it
[Music]
wait never mind it wasn't the
girl
[Music]
Lazy doesn't fight witches to protect
his town because he's just
lazy
wow was the girl oh oh
[Music]
well nice to meet you I
guess well how how are we going to one
one advice you could put away your staff
to be
less obviously a witch
[Music]
is
this surprisingly like female
Nam who whoa no no no no I have a really
really really bad case of helmet hair my
hair looks like because of this
helmet I I I I I would need to go to
bathroom and like fix up my hair you
know and then teleport Myself Away
secretly no please
[Music]
wow she's
panicking no don't don't you dare touch
my helmet don't you
dare what the you could have sliced
off my
head jce
Justice wow he's very aggressive he's a
h
uhoh that's my my head my staff didn't
give it
away are they
related I mean they're both blonde
[Music]
but not the same blonde
at
least he don't act that
[Music]
stupid I I'm I'm a good witch I'm just
here for some pie oh we're going to
fight okay uh let's remember how to
fight I think he won't be so strong
okay time to call some pets first of
all yeah and
[Music]
then uh I'm trying to remember something
I had a thought about pets today
huh I forgot about it okay
uh how's this work again m
we're going to go
for the four
or
no okay yeah is is HP isn't too bad
should I move myself a
[Music]
little okay he's burning nice I'm going
to try double swing cuz that's usually
pretty strong too ah only 69 total
damage I think magic is stronger
on okay okay
okay I put a lot of points into my magic
recently uh oh we can do magic
BL wait wasn't there like I yeah know
I'm thinking if there was like more
strategy to this but it was like
strategy in terms of if there's more
like smaller enemies and you kill the
small enemies and you get another turn
and another turn but not in this SP just
trying to
remember wow oh yeah waiting for the
crit ah that was a thing too like
yeah it's okay he's pretty much
dead easy
yes there's the Strategic crit that I
don't need in the end it's like whatever
because the crit comes too late
so I'm still going to go the safe route
though
for Welcome to the m thank
you oh round two
[Music]
no I don't want to run
away oh Anna is going to save me Anna is
going to save me right just going to
come out of nowhere and save me I see it
[Music]
coming free 2 one no small bomb
what where's
Anna she's coming now yes yes there she
is
[Music]
let's
go still called it
yeah just one line too
early oh she has bunny ears
too and whish hair
[Music]
too wow uh it's like college core P
Mama a comfy I love that card again
[Music]
she a she looks
fluffy hi please please please
pie wait look at her hands she's got
like a million scratches on her hands
can you
see and she's got bandages on too but
like even on her fingers she has a lot
of
scratches is is pie making that
brutal I'm going to go
here I keep on getting like kicked out
of the place I'm staying
in must be a cat owner oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe kitchen accidents I don't
know
noep for sure
[Music]
oh I guess because she can't make so
many pies if everybody knows about it
the demand would be too
[Music]
big let's
go pie time
[Music]
hope she's not bleeding into my
Pine oh thank you for the membership
gift wait that membership message is
kind of late that should be last
[Music]
time make it as usual
for
Yummy the greatest pie Anna has ever
baked
[Music]
you can taste the
fire that doesn't sound like a good
[Laughter]
taste the bird adjo
I would too I would really eat it in a
really tasty way as well please give me
one guys guys guys what do you think who
do you think that picture on on the left
over the fireplace is
from looks kind of funny but maybe it's
a her
[Music]
child could
be I see why he was saying
that maybe she is my mom because we have
the same kind of I mean her eye color is
a bit like different but we still both
have purple eyes and white hair
[Music]
so be kind of a weird way of meeting my
mom I
[Music]
think the character art where am I
supposed to go I'm big I'll just make
myself a bit
smaller and put myself here maybe
[Music]
maybe
here and the ears but I have a feeling
because the other witch that we met also
had wait she also got scratches on her
ears I guess she's just been for a lot
of
[Music]
man she must have been for a lot
I think just all wies in this game have
these ears because the other wi also had
the thank
[Music]
you okay I guess we just move in so we
can have hot pie every morning every
evening so
[Music]
are you teach me how to make
it
oh we get a shortcut to the
[Music]
pie let's
go
[Music]
for imagine a young
Anna in a more a little bit more
revealing outfit perhaps bringing fresh
hot pie to the miners who are working so
hard that is a good
[Music]
question she lost her
magic but she can still make amazing
[Music]
pie she doesn't even have like the light
in her eyes anymore she looks so dead
[Music]
what the
man that's mean she's not even a
proper witch anymore and they still are
like don't talk about her
[Music]
stupid
Pope
foree foree
[Music]
for
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
okay no I'll go deep as
[Music]
this mine I fought a mine close to
my
[Music]
home okay new mine this mind will also
be
[Music]
mine there will be we'll find a
way and I shall become God
[Music]
k
thank you for the membership
[Music]
message the way I look right now it's
almost as if I was part of the magical
girl whole life project
huh connecting the mind to the house
apparently there's a small teleportation
altar at the mine connected to Anna's
house if I activate that altar I'll be
able to come to Anna's house at any time
to eat as many p as I like let's go
worth
it yeah h witch oh yeah not magical girl
actually h witch which is more fitting
anyway I would differentiate those two
things let's go nice
be part of
it the Ian H
witches
ah cuz I would have to go here first and
then walk over to use this teleportation
device
I think there's less chos Stones here
than there should be because the knights
they gathered they're like mining them
in order to kill the witches because
they said that the chaos stones are like
poison to
witches we're using it for a different
purpose but
yeah uh the FL good painkill for Anna
since she has no magic anyway I can find
it in mine Anna's house can be reached
BL blah blue okay wait you say a good
time to save I never
save but okay I'll do it for your wait
how do you save again are you only save
in the in the in the
home so sorry no
saving spark cor oh new materials let's
go oh I do need a
[Music]
healing come on
this part is really
long isn't there auto save and if I die
I don't get uh
like I don't
get uh teleported that far back
anyway from what I
remember
other I usually nothing really happened
I just was able to redo the battle F5
yeah you are still thinking about like
Fallout safe safe safe safe K
safe yeah yeah yeah
just yeah so what's this part can I open
this oh it's locked
okay what's
this oh it's enemies
[Music]
oh kind of
cute 400
HP I don't think that's too
[Music]
bad wait can I what about
the N it doesn't really reflect off of
them Jack in the Box Jack in the Box in
the Box in the
[Music]
bo good
damage okay we
kill this one 57 should be
doable yeah okay very doable and we get
another turn so I'd like to do
uh no I'll do magic
slab one two one
two this music is so dope they
survived with 1
HP what what are the
chances
huh h oh okay at least the fire burns
them one HP and the
dream why did they survive with one HP
that see that feels like really
unlikely should I go down first or up
continue
up where am I here
ah okay
oh okay let's start with the single
enemy
first
stop new enemy
[Music]
begin what was
that sumon the second one even though
that might not even be
[Music]
necessary oh
easy
easy just one
attack defense against lightning oh you
you you
no more than me now about this game you
playing it
[Music]
I thought the lightning might reflect
off of them quite nicely but okay the
game said it
what I did not see that what the
hell speaking of not seeing maybe you
guys did not see before this stream C
was doing a
clubhouse 51
see and
I participated in
it so if you missed it you can watch the
archive I called him
twice because the first time I was like
actually I was kind of busy and uh I was
like yeah you know I went to the post
office to pick up some stuff that was
heavy uh and then I realized oh cie
Callie is still when I got home I
realized she's still waiting for someone
to
enter to play with her cuz it was a to M
but I just got home and my arms were so
jelly but I wanted to you know help out
so I called in and then I realized oh so
I have two
[Music]
Nintendo accounts that I use my main
account but then there was a problem
back in the day with my main account
remember
where I wanted to play a game that was
only available in like the US region or
so I think so I had to
switch to a different count but then I
don't know I had all kinds of problems I
don't even remember this so well
anymore so then I ended up buying a
membership and I think a
US Nintendo online
membership with the new account and on
the old account I think I wasn't able to
get a membership anymore because my
payment method was then now bound to the
US well maybe I don't know if that was
really an issue I don't remember so
anymore
oud
okay and what was
I and then yeah
basically I had to use account but I
never played Clubhouse 51 games on it
got louder by itself really I never
played it uh before can I what you
didn't hear this the
story at
all didn't really say much important
stuff but
yeah yeah the currency stuff yeah yeah
yeah because the problem also is like I
think ah I think because m
M I can't simply cancel the membership
on that account
either because there's like a remaining
balance on the US one and the US One
unlike other stores does not let
you just like get rid of that like in
the when I when I had the European
setting I think I was able to just like
say okay these 60 remaining cents that I
can't buy anything with just make them
go poof I don't care I don't need them
but you can't do that if you have a Us
store account apparently wait that was
wrong so that was my
problem anyway and then I realized
because I was recently for a while now
uh using that uh account that had the
new Nintendo the switch membership this
one looks strong
850 yeah it's
fine
uh I realized I didn't play The
Clubhouse game yet a single time there
and when I was like in cie's stream I
was trying to start the game first I was
trying to start it with the usual with
my old account and then I realized okay
no membership and then I remembered ah I
have the membership on the other
account then I open it the game in the
other account and then I realize oh
somehow all the options are gray
[Music]
out in the game like you can I can do
single player but I can't even do local
multiplayer and especially not online
and I was like
why oh he shoots twice it you have it
oh he's almost dead anyway we're good
we're
[Music]
fine and then I restarted the game
several times I was like why is this not
working and I checked my mind control
him
ah I checked
[Music]
my my subscription if it's really active
and it was really
active it took me a while to figure out
I had to Google and found out that if
you have never
played that
game uh on a Nintendo switch account
before then you have to first play solo
single player a few times before it
unlocks the online
multiplayer So eventually I came back
into C's stream and I was like okay I'm
ready let's play
now oh I wanted to heal first dude ah
you're the weak one anyway okay no need
to heal for alfredo
yeah so I just played a few games and I
I I I I took that opportunity to learn
how to play which is uh really easy
Japanese kind of Connect Four but you
connect
five it's like I would say that's pretty
much
it I know a new game now
yeah it's kind of dump but like it would
be okay maybe if they would say okay you
have to play it at least once on the
whole console not on this account in
particular but
[Music]
okay yeah yeah we can get more pie at
Anna's Place have mercy pie Berry great
witch pie
Berry Ginger
hair
interesting ranked
Clubhouse wait that's me wait wait
that's me I just realized you guys were
faster to realize or make that
connection that's
[Music]
me the voices the voices of the
characters okay I have to finish this
fight first
so anyway had some fun with CI but we
only spoke Japanese because her stream
was Japanese only
to I don't think I ever spoke this much
Japanese with C before like if we're
surrounded by other janese
members then you know we'll adjust and
also speak
Japanese so that everybody understands
but I don't think we ever had to talk
this much Japanese
together
before but I maybe I should also do a
Japanese only stream again sometime soon
because man it's gotten so Rusty
[Music]
but even within that short amount of
time talking to Carie in
Japanese it it was slowly getting back
to
me oh wait I should bring out my other
pet oopsie
[Music]
oopsie yeah I guess yeah just Japanese
maybe not Japanese only solo collab I'm
kind of uh solo collab solo stream cuz
I'm kind of worried that nobody will
show up uh like in terms of you know
Japanese
viewers
but but a collab yeah oh wait we have a
new one let's summon him can I summon
one more no okay that's
[Music]
fine but yeah uh just a collaboration I
need to do the Shark Tank Japanese shark
tank with via
[Music]
strong that felt kind of
strong M
[Music]
wait G G I think my suggestion to her
you guys are probably thinking of that
my suggestion was an off
collab so I have to go to Japan first ah
speaking of going to
Japan
ah oh wait I thought I was going to get
an another turn damn it did you see my
tweet about the quas quas
[Music]
my favorite qu Place cafe in Japan s
Maru Cafe St Mark Cafe they have like
different kind of
quasons all the time they have their
basic quasons and then they have their
like time limited qu and sometimes they
have collaboration qu
and now they have collaboration pule
with a Japanese chocolate bar that is
super cheap but super popular called
Black
Thunder it's so cheap really and it's
actually pretty tasty it's one of the
few chocolates that I actually like and
it's so cheap though Black Thunder and I
saw actually when I was in Japan last
time Black Thunder was having
collaborations in uh what
one of the convenience stores uh and
they had like a ton of interesting
desserts and products in the convenience
store with black Thunder as well which
is super
cool oh can you turn the game up yep yep
yep yep yep yep yep turning it
up cool name for candy bar
mhm yeah but now it's
loud Mama
Mia now I don't know what I was going to
say anymore where I was going with my
black Thunder and cuaso
speech but yeah I think I was just going
to say I'm going to miss out on trying
the quas but then already some people
some Japanese people Bros who saw my
tweet they already went to some maruku
and they ate the Black Thunder quo and
they said it's really good and the only
reason I even know about this
collaboration was because Japan eat
uploaded a a short of him eating all of
the Black Thunder products at the cafe
it's not only the quasa it's a paa and a
smoothie like a chocolate smoothie and
he tried it all and he said the quasa
was really good man damn
it how dare you make it that I'm kind of
interested man but like the the time
limited ones are sometimes hit or miss
man freezing I was thinking of that I
think you can freeze them
decently I was considering it I think I
might have done that
before and then just warm them up in the
oven again but I don't know if it's
going to work so well with the Black
Thunder qule because it kind of has like
a a weird crust but your diet my diet is
going to go into the trash can when I'm
in Japan probably how can I not eat all
the yummy food
I don't think I can control my diet when
I'm in
[Music]
Japan anyway Ginger girl is
here let's
go it's it possible yeah I'll be dancing
yeah yeah yeah yeah I think I'll be
burning plenty of calories
a
Kate is she a witch no right because she
doesn't have ears I mean she has human
ears probably
but not quite the right
ears oh my God that reminds me I think I
had oh I had a dream last night where uh
it was kind of it was oh it was
definitely only a nightmare wow wow wow
wow wow wow W it was quite the nightmare
but I was using magic powers I was
trying to I I was supposed to be able to
use like fire magic but like when it
comes to it you know you're never able
to really bring it out and you you like
really try to go
like and then nothing comes out and it's
really embarrassing cuz you're in a life
threatening situation but then one time
uh I found a coin on the floor and
I picked up the coin and I did like a
mikoa Mika m m what the was the
name again it's always confusing me from
rail gun I did a rail gun move
in my dream I rail
gun mik yeah okay I had
[Music]
it and then actually Loki worked so that
was quite exciting I was like oh my God
wait this works
IRL what the hell rail gun if I pick up
a coin like it was a dream but I was
thinking oh my God this works IRL I
thought this was just an
anime what's the move you have to watch
ra
gun nightmare Corner oh yeah I should
have a nightmare
Corner definitely
[Music]
um kind of low on
HP I can use the shield right and
then it will take MP inste of HP
although I won't have that much anymore
oh
well ah
[Music]
n just MP down to zero
okay rail gun was added to Blue archive
what they have a collaboration you
mean oh is it great time
this turn is
crit oh
wait 4 no 700 wow h no we we need
something that gives me MP as well right
that would be
[Music]
good this is weak but we have so many of
them I'll take this
so is this a crit turn Ark Knights
KFC where where not in Japan
[Music]
right probably not in Japan right I
would assume it is in Japan no
way get out of here until when
[Music]
how
long ah are they reusing those skins
because those are not new the because
they did KFC collabs before I like those
skins they were so
cute isn't it the same art
[Music]
too the KC skin
K side
too yeah it's a ring
[Music]
run their Skins are like carrying
buckets oh wait okay I'll look into this
[Music]
afterwards that's fun um
I wonder if this is a crit no wait it's
not a crit turn what does the sign mean
again uh when the staff is
likey and the whole uh square is uh
yellow next turn is
[Music]
um next turn is the crit that's for
sure okay here we go okay I did that
good I got rid with a with a small h I
got rid of the low HP dude that ah the
special skill being ready
[Music]
ah didn't kill him four let's go ends
this
now this ends now
actually reminds me of did you see on
Twitter I upload a picture I made my I
made a shrine I made a
shrine tells of arise and berseria and
ceria Shrine yeah I finally I had like a
couple of things packed because I wasn't
sure if I wanted to unpack it or not but
um I thought cuz I was like cleaning my
apartment uh place yesterday
uh wait oh God I'm still used to living
in apartment's
house uh I was cleaning it and then I
thought okay you know what ever since I
moved my shelf was so
unorganized even my mom pointed it out
so I thought you know what I'll organize
it now and then I uh decided I'll make
it a tastes of AR rise short short
showcase thingy although normally don't
like
to have a lot of merchandise like anime
style merchandise now because I want
everything to look relatively mature and
not cluttered ideally not cluttered so I
like to keep it at a minimum but I think
it looks quite nice and it's only in my
office so yeah I think it looks okay
I'll keep it like that DVD case what
filia no I don't think I have
maybe but I don't have anything special
uh for the other games I just have maybe
the PS4 PS3
cases but no merchandise but I got like
so much special merchandise the chess
the chest is so special I so funny so
cute because I opened it for the first
time um yesterday and I was wondering oh
what is this chest set going to look
like and I open it and I realize
oh that is
smart a very smart thing an original
thing to do with small acrylic
[Music]
stands I thought it was going to be
actual figures but once I saw the
acrylic stands I was like okay yeah
makes sense because it would be probably
very expensive to make figures properly
for a chess
set but how did we in Hol never think of
this maybe because chess isn't a big
thing in Japan but
these tiny acrylic stands you know we
don't like seeing acrylic stands anymore
in whole life English right when we
announce acrylic stands for merchandise
everybody's
[Music]
like but on on the chest set it's such a
great idea such a cute
idea we should make a whole life English
or whole life in general chess set
totally or you can make your own
actually if you have enough acrylic
stands you like acrylic stance a okay
well then you'll you will like the idea
of a chess set with acrylic stance even
more it's actually genius but then I was
putting it together and I realized some
of them are really really loose in their
stance so I would maybe have to glue it
if you want to play chess properly with
it but it's just being showcased now so
it's all good but it's so cute it's so
smart
[Music]
does she not have character art for sure
she does come on show
[Music]
me she has she has
freckles she has freckles
metal animal
[Music]
pins oh you wanted to save your
bro
[Music]
for and I'll find your brother
too don't worry I'll find
[Music]
him so he's either dead or he's not a
human or he's too deep
[Music]
oh he's a witch
okay we will do that we'll find Kate's
sibling while looking for the cha Stone
yeah speaking of merch
yesterday I put together
uh the plan for my anniversary merch
because okay my birthday merch is
already decided so I had to work on my
anniversary merch wait does it continue
there oh yeah it
does but wasn't there another path I
wanted to check out anyway I think it it
will be again very
very practical things useful things I
had some cute ideas since a while ago
that I wanted to realize I hope they
will the merch department will accept my
ideas okay I think I've seen it all okay
okay okay the ideas you would like them
and then actually for my birthday
Set uh birthday merchandise I decided
for the first time in a while to do a
voice pack
again uh because okay maybe you would
think first time in a while you've done
voice packs recently have I have I but I
mean for anniversary and birthday the
previous ones I've skipped doing a voice
pack um
but actually I need to heal right
now I'll get it
afterwards uh start
com yeah this time I was like well I
guess I'll make
voice pack again but well uh so if it's
not anniversary or birthday voice packs
I've had usually I've had or I think
always I've had the staff write the
scripts I've just left it up to them but
remember my first
birthday uh merchandise had a voice pack
where I wrote the script right or two of
them two right I made two where in both
cases I wrote the script one was a get
well soon voice
pack and another
one was the animal zoo we're going to
the zoo voice pack where I made the
animal noises too and I wrote those uh
and anyway because it was the first time
in a while that I would be doing a voice
pack in my anniversary SL birthday meriz
I thought okay I'll ride it this time
but I totally forgot about it that the
deadline was coming up and uh Jenna
reminded me once a while ago but then
she also forgot to remind me again it
seems
and then I yesterday I realized cuz I
was I was looking at my to-do list and I
realized
y the recording deadline is very soon
this week in a few
days
and and I have to give them my script
first to check it and the script
deadline is actually
over already passed so I was like ah I
got to write a script but I have no idea
I didn't even decide on the theme or
anything I did not have a script no not
at all I didn't even have a direction of
what I wanted to
do so yesterday I
spontaneously uh took the time to write
the script
and I think it went quite well I think
um I think I like the idea and I
think it's a good
script but you know they're usually not
very
long so it's going to be
probably between 5 and 10 minutes but
that's pretty common I just feel kind of
weird that it's so short but it's hard
to come up with
more it's got to be like a bigger story
if I want to have it be
[Music]
longer but it's really cute I think the
theme is nice it's not cringe
either that's what worries me when I
write the script myself like oh my God
will this be
cringe but I think it's pretty good
[Music]
so look forward to voice back I hope you
guys will buy it because I wrote the
script this
[Music]
time and I think it will speak to you
personally personally individually in a
personal
[Music]
way I wrote it down just for you maok
Kiwa yes I am Mao
Kiwa wait which way should I go oh wait
this was a dead end right okay okay okay
dead end
dearu let's get these
boys
yeah hand with an autograph uh this time
for the birthday one I've said no
because it's too stressful but I'm going
to do it for iversary or was it the
other way around I think it I think ah
it was the other way around
maybe yeah I'm just doing it for one of
them because they're so close together
and I remember last year after hours and
hours and days and days of signing one
Set uh like a few one or two weeks later
I got the ones for the anniversary and I
had to sign those next and it was really
[Music]
stressful yeah
yeah my wrist was suffering I had so
much to sign and this summer I'm so busy
too I
think got to keep that in mind
[Music]
yesterday I had big tummy H and I feel
like it came from the fruit that I
cooked but I I didn't eat yesterday and
the day before yesterday I ate the food
the the chicken
dish that was not past its due date okay
the chicken itself but the day before
yesterday I cooked something it was just
rice with uh chicken and
zucchini and terak
sauce and I ate it the day before
yesterday in the evening and then the
following day yesterday I had big tummy
hordes right but I also cooked another
dish that I will eat
today with a chicken that was one day
passes two days right so you would think
my tummy Hort came from that but
no I ate the zucchini stuff again and in
the night I had big tummy hord again
so kind of
sussy but I don't think it was
anything
weird but because of the big tummy H
yesterday I took a long long
nap hoping that it will
pass I
slumbered for a long time oo we're
playing this kind of game
oh uhhuh
oh it let me release go go go
interesting
interesting can't be pushed right ah can
I guess towards
me
mhm is that closed
oh uh well let let's push this
back guys wa wa
wa you have to play this game it's so
cute it's so adorable and it's so fun
big
recommend if you want to become a
witch I'll take a look it's not that
long either so you can probably do it in
three streams or so if you if they're a
little bit on the longer side
wait what is
that
uh what is this switch
for aha uh oh
wait bring it
back damn we're having a lot of anime
talk today and I didn't even get to the
point where I was freaking
shook that kawori is also a bakali fan
wait do you like P
too I am
shook shook to the
core
uh why why did we turn that
thing what
four just to get
up I guess so oh wait there's another
one and now it opens okay I'm not sure
what the purpose was
yet she hasn't watched it
yet oh it has so many seasons you know
and they uh just announced a while ago
finally for the first time in many years
they announced in two new seasons for
this summer
so I really recommend this anime it's
one of the few animes that I say I would
still watch these
days
um not a whole can I push these
too but if you want to get into it you
should probably like start now and you
should watch it in the release order
because that's a big thing like there's
a a chronological order and then there's
a release order cuz they released it
like you know all over the place you
should if you want to watch it you
should watch it in the release
[Music]
order never chronological yeah I mean
there's a reason why they release it
like that right so oh wait does this
turn wait I get it now
oh when it shows you okay it shows you
that there's that it will push the other
mine
carts yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah finally hey don't dot dot dot me
like that I was talking well doing this
my focus is not 100% on the game right
now oh
e wait that's her brother isn't it but
like okay it's not listen listen it's
her brother but somebody um a witch
perhaps uh cast a spell on
him to turn into a
rat and that's why we couldn't smell him
what the I jump or
what this is complete luck isn't
it there's no way I would
know oh my
God ghost of
mint 100 copies sold
yay I hope they sell
more it wait why
both wait after jump on this one is
there a chance that the left one is
suddenly not broken oh no I can't go
right left I tried both of them what do
you want is it different each
time H it is different each time the rat
is a hint the rat is a hint
okay I'm watching its movement but I
don't I don't I didn't get anything from
that movement the button the
button the
button no she keeps on going there wait
what ah what
button
what restart the
hint wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait huh
the rat is not the brother is what
you're
saying go down oh I can go down wait I
can shoot
it was I supposed to do
that huh maybe I can jump on there now I
don't
know no I should
not wait use mine rat
ah who whoa who W that was so fast what
the can I use it again I think here
was
[Music]
diagonal I had to shoot it to make it
mine oh oh no more was the last one
right or
left uh I think
right ah
should have waited for you
guys wait
rat oh my God no more
rat but is it the same path oh
God a
I could probably leave the area and
shoot the red
again no what four
four one 2 3 4 5 now right now maybe
okay and then front
[Music]
no okay one two oh no I think it changed
right see it definitely changes still
because now both of them were broken
the order changes let me go back
and get a rat again ah it's there again
Hallelujah
okay I didn't want to use it right away
because I thought I will forget
anyway okay go
I think I got
it the last one is right the last one
but now I'm like wait I can use it one
more
time left left right okay thank you
rat sorry I don't know why I thought you
were the brother oh maybe maybe it is
the
brother maybe it
is there's still a chance
M let's leave it there for now what does
this do ah okay uh no no no undo I want
to undo
it red
MVP let's bring it to the
end ah and then I need to move the other
one so I can get behind it to push it
from right to left okay okay okay okay
no problem I like this kind of
riddle yeah I brought up Bak so randomly
with
K wow I didn't think she actually would
say yes she likes it and then she said
she likes nadle the most as well I'm
like what the before I even said it
she's like yeah
not
oopsie I'm like e no way we like the
same girl because like I feel
like so many people we talked about this
too no we never talked about Bak but I
mean we in the chat we talked about it
before you guys didn't like ntico that
much you guys were like oh she's
crazy
a we never talked about it because I
didn't think she would you know be
interested in bakat and also because it
just wasn't relevant at the
time because there just hasn't been a
season for so long and I haven't been
watching anime for so long so I don't
really talk about anime when it's not
relevant she gets she likes n the most
she also likes
insane well part of it okay I feel like
because she likes like
smaller people and she likes to Yeet
small people haty cie would be kind of
closer
to her likings I would say very eatable
very
small but NAD was also pretty
small somewhat eatable and very
very men head off
[Music]
oh is my bore not out interesting why
that's fine
[Music]
though oh that hits everyone I think
let's
try
wow good damage holy
they are ganging up on me
[Music]
the rest of
myth I would doubt Ena probably watched
it I would
[Music]
think I would believe so
nice oh
[Music]
nice I don't even know when Ena finds
the time to watch
things but she
[Music]
does good
fight um
[Music]
that's a lot might want to heal before I
go into that
[Music]
fight just a small one dried pie where
did I get dried pie
from she probably does well working on
stuff I tried
like watching so to say watching things
while uh
[Music]
also doing something like making my
schedule or so it doesn't work I
can't cannot divide
my
[Music]
attention even listening to music is
distracting for
me then get
good you just have nothing on at all
yeah nothing a lot of time it's just
[Music]
nothing no I'm not a multitasker and i'
I've heard that multitasking is a myth
[Music]
anyway so
a h
on all T
[Music]
tack we don't see that often
enough yeah I think I want to do it over
here there's the most
HP Collective HP in this area nice
so
oh they get no chance to fight back
anymore yeah see there is no
multitasking your brain just jumps in
between those things yeah why have we
not after all these millions of years
how how come you know our brains have
not developed to be able to do that
though like we've developed in so many
ways but if you think about about it if
we developed to do that that would be so
op that would be really op kind of
crazy I want all the EXP so I'm going to
do that fight
[Music]
twoo playing a game and talking to chat
while mul that's
oneing but I'm always like when I'm when
I'm tanging when I'm doing a proper
tangent
I I I'm I'm
constantly on the edge of losing my
train of
thought
[Music]
yeah so
difficult I mean I could play really
mindlessly just pressing whatever but I
also want to not do that I want to I
don't want to play mindlessly
[Music]
cuz that would be
stupid singing when I work or drive D is
I
guess surprisingly manageable I have I
don't drive cars I don't know how but
seems like that is fairly
manageable
but yeah I because driving is not that
difficult
then but don't underestimate it just
because you
think you're doing well with
[Music]
it wait let
me kick that one's ass real quick then I
get another
turn different parts of the brain really
[Music]
you often forget what you're doing you
mean in terms of
driving you don't know what you're doing
in terms of
driving that's not good that's not good
at
[Music]
all you just go on auto but you know I
guess you you just follow the GPS like
like a zombie without thinking much I
guess would you say so you don't really
think about oh I'm going right now I
have to go left now you just like
mindlessly numbly follow the GPS I
[Music]
suppose you don't use
GPS weird flex but okay
oh we're so close to the level
up let's
go oh there's a heal over there that I
don't really
[Music]
need I could already go to the next area
but I want to get these
[Music]
exp yeah something becoming muscle
memory definitely can be a bad thing
don't rely too much on that
[Music]
friends ah oops see I wish I could
summon them
[Music]
automatically I feel like this didn't do
that much damage on them did
it now maybe it would have been around
the same with the Thunder
[Music]
let me try
it oh okay actually Thunder was better
Thunder actually did
more might want to upgrade spells staff
but then I probably have to go home for
that
[Music]
nice worth
it
perhaps oh
did you see that guys that's not a
normal enemy am I at a boss fight
already but what about this other path
did I come from
here no
this is
different
right this is different this next to the
The Riddles over
there treasure path seems like
it this looks like a lot of mobs oh dear
oh
dear yeah that is a lot uh
[Music]
um might want
to go straight into Magic
[Music]
Shield and then yeah with with this
attack I could potentially get every
single one of them right
[Music]
no maybe not all but it's too
complicated I'm just going to go with
this should get everybody but one oh
everybody but two
okay
wa
H wo whoo whoo whoo Who whoo whoo whoo
whoo whoo whoo okay Magic Shield was
smart but I'm not going to give
[Music]
up not going to give up I think it's
manageable especially after I survived
the first big
attack just got to do it again
probably and now there will be less
attacks so it won't be as strong and I
can uh get rid of one more with an extra
turn getting my extra turn so there's
two left
[Music]
now oh we already have magic blast now
all right all right all right magic
blast
easy you just have to survive the first
turn you should not underestimate the
damage they do even with the Magic
Shield I almost died
so all
right
strategically very smart of me
[Music]
oh we're so close to the level
up we're so close to
it one more fight maybe or after that
big fight High elasticity spring plus 20
scrap iron ingredient
oh it did look like we're going to be
doing some blacksmithing because no
I was able to interact with the
iron kind of maybe we'll be doing that
at some
point
[Music]
okay I don't know if I want to go
back I feel like I'll be
fine will
I
no go
away I think I can take the boss
if there's more after that then it's a
bit rough
but used to have a time
limit well I think so too but actually
maybe I do want to go
back
um we go to the ENT where do we go
entrance and then there's a big
teleporter I could totally do
it
but let's go back
anyway get G because we have three of
the training thingies I don't want
to you know I want to use them
now
um okay what do we want to train um
maybe magic power
M an overall
[Music]
one and this
one let's
go something oh we H we had this one
before uh it's just like turning turning
turning
[Music]
easy
clockwise well I almost missed that one
actually I pressed a different button
together with X but they didn't count it
let's
[Music]
go e physical attack crit chance 10% wow
wow wow wow new
skill overload strike one momentarily
overloads the body's abilities in order
to deliver a fierce
blow what is this a physical attack what
triple swing oh the double swing already
was so
good strength charge charges strength
while defending death will be slightly
lower than your base defense rate and
your strength will be temporarily
temporarily increased when your next
turn
arrives uh
okay uh what else do I usually do some
crafting
right we got a new book was it
this
[Music]
whoo the art for it looks
so strong ah this one could be we could
make it if we go back and farm some of
those crabs
[Music]
this one I don't know where you get that
little
[Music]
Shard small dark magic
Stone it's a shield it's an owl Shield
wait that's so
cool it looks so
cool
what sheh look at that design
was there something new
here not
[Music]
really
no um maybe ah we need a
few of n not these the temporary
ones these ones I'm running out of
them slow slow sticky bump
oh white fox marble
oh yeah I can only make these
[Music]
two oops
oopsie and then this one just checking
if there's anything new
no yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay
oh weapon Evolution oh can we do that
again I don't remember essential ah
we're missing those ingredients okay
[Music]
all right
ah right we have to find out what they
like to
eat okay here we go let's try
everything we've tried a bunch of it
before on this one
[Music]
what what did I just was I ruin it or
what was it a flower is bloomed on all
enemies planted with a seed Bloom flower
leeches life from the enemy life Leach I
saw someone in the chat say life Leach
is op in this game and a portion of the
energy absorbed from enemy is returned
to the Caster
MP available free turns after combat
starts wait will it use it on its own or
wait did I learn
bloom or did the pet learn
blue so Dwarf Gold goem Essence is the
one what do you
need pet okay how do I make it use the
[Music]
skill I'm sure this one wants a blue
item right one of these
no ah sparer okay well it is from the
the area that it's from I
think lightning ball it will
automatically oh okay good okay okay
spit out a bolt of electrical energy
that forms into a ball and flies away
wow okay looks like it could be strong
let's get another one in and another one
and we have reached Max Affinity wait
what was that uh dwarf Golem Essence
thingy can we make more
no I
need what was it what is it what is that
again Dwarf Gold where do I get that I
want to go get some really quickly I
know we had a lot of it
before somewhere in the beginning
right the cave near home okay the cute
plant pot gos oh okay okay okay let's go
go check him
out y I never did that
[Music]
before still even these ingredients like
the rabbit meat are I think still worth
getting is this the right
cave pudding cave
nah what you go
now I still want the materials
it's worth it for these items that I
need to
craft other Cape
okay but still let me kill one they
might have something cool drop me some
[Music]
items let's try these new attacks
overload strike
[Music]
one that looked strong
wait did it drop
something a quick hunt quick hunt skips
combat completes battles quickly
triggered by sword or magic attack in
conditions only enemies appearing reply
on the field can be okay let's
try
[Music]
um do
it okay it gives me
items that move hurts me
oh well it's
[Music]
okay in in a fight like that we can
afford to use
it
[Music]
so nope over there
any help of getting the pets oh I'm fine
at the
moment that did not drop
anything this dropped me some stuff
nice oh maybe oh yeah yeah yeah okay
okay
okay these ones I have to fight properly
[Music]
for craftables optional bosses D is
there one in here do you mean one we
fought before
[Music]
or never seen it before it's so cute
apparently this is a series that existed
since a long time but it was also for me
the first time that I really heard about
it thanks to the recent releases
should we fight the giant Golem in here
[Music]
again I wouldn't
mind for some crafting stuff cuz I'm
guessing that the the stuff that they
drop now will be useful for
us
crafting backtracking and like crafting
with the stuff that they drop seems
pretty important
behind a DPS check door oh
okay it needs to be unlocked first oh I
can't do
[Music]
it I want to do it though
I've got enough grass yeah but maybe I I
need I think I would need two more
Essences because the other um the other
one also took three items in
total and we only
gave that flower
thingy one so I think I would need
to you probably dropped something
else ooh
you think it would be
enough just you know just in case we
might need it for something else too and
these ones as
well these ones
[Music]
too because they dropped the purple
shards right I think
[Music]
we need a lot of them to make the the
purple I said I mean pink make the pink
ball or maybe even something else I
don't
know I don't
[Music]
know I thought my PC was like lagging
for a
moment wait did it drop something please
drop me something good
please these aren't even that
underleveled now even even
[Music]
now yeah right that was a little lag
morning
[Music]
actually I don't want to use this now
because I'm like wasting the the turn
based MP
heel Min
maxing like crazy
[Music]
I know generally yeah it's
definitely not
lagging no problem
here okay now I would like to have one
of these thank you
[Music]
yeah the Bonks are good too now that we
got new Bonks
[Music]
especially I'm already out of MP again
wow
wow I use I like to use the magic anyway
because I can hit many of them
X once in one turn turn bonus
y okay ooh Fox marble Shard let's
go and my mp is full
[Music]
again oh yeah right wait I remember they
steal my
mp I just now noticed I'm like why is my
mp empty again
ah they eat it up these little
shits
[Music]
quz can't even cast
them how dare you
[Music]
run out of magic but not of options well
said well
[Music]
said all right I have no MP thanks
turn bonus oh can we do special skill
let's
[Music]
go this ends
now what is this game about well there's
this girl pie Berry that we're playing
she's a witch she loves pie she lives
alone in a little Forest uh because the
world hates witches so she's kind of
like
isolated um but uh you know she kind of
keeps on getting visits from knights who
want to kill her and then she realizes
oh they all have great pie maybe if I go
where they came from they'll have even
more pie I know this sounds kind of
childish now but maybe it is but that's
what makes her so cute and the search of
pie leads us through the world
and H and more and more we learn about
people and we learn about pie and people
who make
pie maybe we will also be able to say
the full numbers of piie one
day the or the square root of Pi I don't
know
um this game is about pies no it's it's
a
metaphor it seems to be leading us to a
metaphor it will probably be about her
connection with her mom I think because
she she loves these pies because she
remembers them from eating
them uh from the hands of her
[Music]
mommy maybe the real pie will be the
friends and the family that we make
along the
way
right I think my explanation was pretty
good
huh one of the best explanations of a
game story that I have
ever uh explained
[Music]
before tar
I
cooked different one this time
[Music]
which to
PIR so
[Music]
pie can we take this one down with a
double swing yes
turn
bonus you are next oh that was the wrong
one y it I got the wrong one
ah
oopsie oh she
strong the board is not so strong
anymore strategic
crit wasted
[Music]
okay so what's up with you
again
nothing should I keep those shards for
something
special
or should I make you know there was this
uh recipe
for where was it this
one the white fox marble seems to be an
item to use in the beginning of a fight
but that's what I was thinking but is
there something to like awaken that fox
over
there there's a better Mana is there
something else where you use that
the
no ah in this one ah this is the one you
meant to enhance my
own
MP permanently oh that's pretty sick too
this one actually just needs
one uh of these shards per
item get the
marble this one but
it's just one for 12
that's like
insane uh grinding that I'll have to do
like if I ever want to use it again
feels like uh okay I crafted once it was
such a pain in the ass kind of thing
I'll never do it
again I feel like the marble is
connected to the Statue okay I'll make
it and then I'll go to the Statue and
see if it
reacts but yeah the permanent MP
increase of course course sounds a bit
more
[Music]
tasty okay I think I'm going to leave
soon
though this cave I
[Music]
mean but maybe before the next uh
which spring our stream I
can do some of
this uh res materials
grinding I was Wonder like if I can do
anything off screen but I didn't think
about uh the fact that I could do all of
this grinding might prove useful didn't
realize even these I can quick hunt even
though there's so many nice the crabs
yeah I want to grind the crabs too but
should I do it before the next stream or
should I do a little bit today maybe I
think those are so high level we still
have to fight them I don't think we can
quick hunt
them but I really need their
materials uh I can fight the goat statue
again does this make sense to
do Thunder
crab should I
okay do you drop something nice
[Music]
though you like pretty colors is that
what you see in this game when I play
it pretty colors wow chicken gets
excited about pretty colors
[Music]
nice good
damage by the way I was really happy
that people really liked my Fallout
stream even though I felt like kind of
like I wasn't at my best in terms of
entertainment but people really seem to
like
[Music]
it my
V went v v Watchers
fruit who
oh I I got a message right away from one
of my closest
friends messaging me like about my
Fallout bot like normally my friends my
IRL friends they don't
really talk about my no two of them they
don't watch every stream but two of them
keep like a a a a rough uh eye on what I
do pizza friends and BFF specifically
but my other close
friend did I tell you it's it's the same
dude where I told you before I think I
told
you
uh wait was I ever ever able to go this
path before what the I told you
something before where I told him
something and he was like uh
I think oh I think I asked him to like
if he wants to watch my the the concert
if if he wants a code and he seemed so
disinterested so I was like uh okay yeah
I thought so um so he definitely doesn't
watch my streams at all doesn't seem so
interested but somehow he caught wind of
my Fallout stream and wrote me a long
message about like I don't know why you
played why why you chose to play New
Vegas I feel like Fallout 4 would have
been better if you wanted to you know
get more references from the show and
blah blah blah but yeah they're all good
anyway you should do this and that they
gave me some advice and some tips and
tricks um I was like well you know it
was only chosen because of a poll I
think I did a poll where it was more
popular yeah but I I I was kind of happy
to
see so like that my Fallout stream must
have sparked some
interest
uh oh okay we've not been here
before I think I'll stay away I I'll go
back
now but that means when I go back I have
to kill the boss
again I don't think we killed the boss
before m
yeah it was an
overwhelmingly convincing vote people
really wanted New Vegas but now that I
play New Vegas a lot of people are like
oh you should have played Fallout 4 or
whatever it's like
whatever you
know I think it's whatever either
way either
way should I go over there once
oh you guys
[Music]
you should still check out four later
was
foures does does four did it get
released after New Vegas is it like
newer so to
say yeah okay well I think it's good
that I start with New Vegas because then
the graphics from Fallout 4
will make make me happy I don't have a
problem with the graphics from New Vegas
but if I played it the other way around
then maybe I would be like ew towards
New
Vegas for Super
pretty you make me
curious okay Blue Crabs I I just quickly
want to go on a trip to the Blue
Crabs then we'll go back to the main
thing
super pretty is overselling
it oh you can wear the tank
armor okay let's see can we do a quick
hunt
[Music]
no it's no Skyrim but it looks good no
sky Skyrim are you saying SC Skyrim is
[Music]
beautiful Skyrim
beautiful well when I think of Skyrim I
guess I think of Oblivion and I probably
shouldn't think of
[Music]
Oblivion Skyrim is very pretty Skyrim is
pretty is it prettier than me
sheesh that
damage from my pet is kind of
crazy never nothing is greater than
you
stop wow
[Music]
he did AOE my pet did some AOE that's
the special attack I guess that it
learned
[Music]
wow wow wow wow
wow I think we're like close to being
able to quick hunt
[Music]
these close
maybe with heavy modding uhhuh it'll be
pretty with heavy
[Music]
modding I found a funny comment on the
VOD of my follow
stream I was like you can't be serious
can I walk over there there's mops over
there um what was it again someone was
like uh like you in order to play this
game properly I'm not trying to tell you
what you have to do but you there's the
only thing that you have to do you have
to do this you have to is get 100 what
was it
Charisma and uh what's the
word like go through all of the dialogue
options like don't skip any any
anything like if there is five questions
I can ask I have to ask all of them and
it would be rude not to or like like I
would be playing it the wrong way or so
or like in any case I would surely be
disappointing that uh
person is there something
here why did I not look last time I
should have totally checked last
[Music]
time yeah I'm like I mean you you lost
me at listening to every every single
piece of every conversation like the
hund Charisma I was actually still like
H
okay but nah bro I'm I'm choosing the
conversation options that I think sound
interesting and that's
it something that I feel like will bring
me forward and help
me I mean
maybe if I would play this outside of a
stream like on my own time maybe then I
would
like what was the word like what what
was the
word that he
used in in terms of using all using up
all of the dialogue options uh
forgot but like I'm considering
also the fact how much time exhaust yeah
that's it how much time everything
takes so a lot of people just say ah it
doesn't matter just you know do it
anyway
but I am also thinking about my
[Music]
time and I don't think I don't think I
listened to so little dialogues
I don't think it
was that
little I think it was plenty he's
probably one of the dialogue
writers I mean I'm so sorry I have to
disappoint you but I'm not going to do
that if that's if that's the point where
you say this stream sucks and this let's
play sucks and the way you're doing it
is the wrong way then so it may
be but I it was quite extreme you know
there's always people who backseat and
who are like you should do this you
should do that but that was pretty
extreme and like um very demanding you
know I'm like nah sorry
buddy but it made me
laugh made me laugh for sure
you think it's a community's Insider
joke the comment seemed very serious
about
it yeah that was
[Music]
funny I guess the blue crabs are all
outside
[Music]
I just want to see how you play it I did
get a lot of comments that were like oh
it's like so interesting to see someone
play it for the first
time I guess it's like one of those
games where everybody has played it
before uh and the people who did play it
they just they have played it for like
hundreds of hours so seeing someone
experience it from
the POV of a new an absolute newcomer
didn't even play other uh Fallout games
seems very refreshing I get that I I can
see that
y ouch oh I have to
restart I almost had
it now go go go go go go
go you okay okay
okay so far I always did it without
bonking against
them it's fun to see new takes on
different people thank you I I saw some
people say that you know other Fallout
games would have been maybe easier to
get into as a first timer because this
one kind of expects you to already know
everything and they were praising me for
picking it up so well
I was happy to hear
that can I not go home by just walking
through
here n
do head PS thank
you but also
shittier got to hang out the pit boy
mechanic yeah yeah yeah that one's you
know a little bit they don't they don't
explain a lot of things do
they like the pit boy may be still
somewhat explained but other things are
like find it out yourself have
fun oh I can train again two
[Music]
times this
one and oh more magic only
magic never did that one before I think
oh we get to do that one magic practice
ooh first time is always oh wait no it's
this one
a oh no oh
oh
oh wait last time I missed like every
single one and now I'm hitting every
single one how did I do
it how did I do
it I swear I missed every single one
like as if I was
purposefully
aiming like away from
them I used
vs oh my God so can I make that thing
already no oh see after all of that
we're still missing half of it all right
I'll go there again
sometime
um what did I need those ah for the
armor
right ah I need a few more of those too
I want to go back one more time just one
more time just one more time so we can
make the armor that will be so worth it
trust
me
uh here this one
I would hope they have respawned oh wait
no they're still wait maybe at least
outside come
on
respawn was there any other place where
they
spawn
nice you wake up the turtle no ah look
at them they're
[Music]
here yes I was hoping for that turn
bonus I think good would love this game
this game h
yesterday she played some kind of weird
medieval
game I was quite surprised about her
game Choice then I had to look it up
because you know I love medieval
but it doesn't seem to be I thought
because it said Henry I thought it was
about Henry the e but no how
disappointing give me a game about Henry
the eth come
on but yeah it seems like Kingdom Come
has quite the big uh following
[Music]
you made don't all that's it only two
spawns that's it oh man they're kind of
rare is this game available on Steam yes
it is and I'm not sponsored but I am
hereby promoting it to
you uh it's on Steam and on switch too
now H I think
yeah but yeah get it on Steam if you
[Music]
want across the
island how do I get
there oh well um let's sleep once and go
back
to what does sleeping sleeping should re
spawn
them right
[Music]
yeah I was making materials I got to
make the material remind me you can
bring me money
heo bring me
this
[Music]
and more of
this and this and this
it won't fast forward
time oh
man okay it's okay I want to craft uh
the what was it the this one this one
that's what we went out for
originally let's uh what does this do
anyway 80% MP
recovery I'll make a
two it's like we went on a t
in
game we totally
did uh was it for you no
was I was for her oh yeah we are pretty
much full oh wow oopsie ah
uh uh there you
go increase skill power in battle
y okay
M I slept so let's go back I slept and I
wept in my bed about the
pie let's go to where are we going U
teleport um M
entrance yeah the armor I think I'm
still missing some a few more of those
crab
shells it's okay we're surely strong
enough um that wasn't really the con
concern
anyway but we got level UPS so it was
worth going back
oh
[Music]
okay next Farm run yeah by the next time
we go there should be uh enough to do
what we want to
[Music]
do B damage
yeah it was a huge huge
[Music]
boost
electrocute I'm so
cute that it electrifies
you it's not electri cute it's Electro
cute cute
wow wow wow
[Music]
wow nice it's like I'm playing the game
oh I don't get another turn okay then
I'm not playing the game
of the boxes
that I played with
Cy
wack my pun game has been
strong
really people always laughed about my
puns in a bad way like oh she
sucks now you guys praising me wow it's
like a leveled up
[Music]
looks so funny when their heads go up
one
down and maybe 3 20 is probably too much
but I'll give it a
try oh
[Applause]
wow I
underestimated
myself
damn triple swing
strong sheesh okay
I guess I'll absorb it let's
go what the is this magical girl
robot what is
this looks like
[Music]
me hi
oh so that it does more damage to
witches I
suppose got to be careful let's use a
agility cuz I have so
many unless I thought of it first wow
okay
strict
[Music]
worse oh okay this is
nice
sick
oh that was nothing
electrocute wait I don't think I can
ever see that bird in its original way
ever
again it electrocute
electrocute it just looks like
electrocute to me
[Music]
now cannot go back anymore
magic blast is
ready I wonder if the the one that is in
the middle of it gets more damage than
the
others then I would like this one to
take more damage obviously but I want
all of them to be
hit oh no looks wow 1,900 99 damage in
total anyway that looks pretty
even strategic crit time
[Music]
baby kind of want to try to Triple
swing and we electrocuted
him well it was a pretty cute Golem
robot thingy so A fitting fit
finishing is this the
[Music]
brother is this a
powered by steam just like this
game cuz I'm playing it
on nice joke
[Music]
controlling
robots probably not the first time in
his
No you little thanks for the
membership did you join because of the
joke just
now oh
this the
brother
and I miss your sound for I don't know
why just have it routed wrong I
[Music]
guess Chang
something well he is the brother very
much
likely this looks so cute definitely if
I were to get into the robot this would
be the robot of my
choice get get in the into the robot pie
Berry get into the
[Music]
robot oh why can't I push
this oh to protect my I see what's
happening I
think maybe those monsters are over
there and not to be fought normally but
uh I have to protect myself with the
mine
cart so it goes off PE PE PE
yeah so
this okay I didn't think it would go
after me
there come on
come
on come on okay can probably leave it
there already but I'll bring it to the
end activate
it
not just seeing if there's smaller
fights first then I would go back and
heal but no we're getting right into
[Music]
it hasn't slept in three weeks
captain Oh Captain My
Captain is he strong wrong fre
80 what
yasi he's not even worth using any of
these oh he's got bombs though
okay uh let's see how many more bombs he
will
spawn if it's just the one then it's
like whatever but maybe every turn he
spawns a new
one who
knows but I mean how long can this take
with 380
[Music]
HP do you realize the monsters that I
met before you were stronger
is that a
captain
incoming cute
[Music]
I
love oh my God cute
[Music]
no let's be
friends she's so
[Music]
cute I might like her more than pie
Berry wait her HP is also so
low there must be a catch right nanika
everybody brings out a
bomb
weak but I've noticed she's a witch but
she doesn't have the
ears but maybe every witch has like this
kind of skin tone though maybe that's
how you can tell because so far all the
witches we've met had like a darker skin
tone than the
others she has the ears I can't
tell
[Music]
where that's her Cape
no I don't see the ears anyway yeah so
white hair also wait did the did the
girl have white hair the the witch that
we the first other witch that we met I
think she didn't have white hair maybe
white hair is not a most does she have
white
[Music]
hair oh she
did yeah the ice one she did okay
okay
anyway let me
think can I
wait can I have
them oh I can have free now I didn't
realize let's focus on the
K
[Music]
uh
t
t nice died from
fire easy easy
tle coughing baby
what uh no I mean with I mean within
this game maybe in other games they're
not uh dark
skinned but in in this game it seems
like they're all darker skinned it's a
meme okay
okay haha
[Music]
funny why is this so easy you guys are
so weak you're not a challenge to me
oh she lost what but she was using
magic maybe she has a way to hide
it to con conceal
it or or she's a fake
witch but but I recognize her as a witch
maybe I just recognize her as a witch
uh like visually but she says she can't
sense the magic so
told you she has no
ears
don't tracking the bomb witch I met
another witch called Kaa but she doesn't
use magic only bombs yeah I think she
yeah she doesn't have magic anymore did
the Pope take away her powers like he
did to Anna I need to go deeper into the
M although she didn't seem so dead like
I feel like Anna why why are they called
so similarly Anna looked so dead
probably because she lost her
magic
but Kaa doesn't look so dead so I feel
like maybe she still has her
magic or I don't know I'm confused
it's conflicting hey yo what the
what is
that I want to fight that
open seems like for another
time he y another big boy
hey am I supposed to fight this now did
I go the wrong
way you need to use the C oh this is
optional oh let me check the cuz it
warns me anyway right before I go into
the
fight so nice
3,800 is that for
us a tough fight
[Music]
I think we can do
it I can tame this big boy what does
does it surely get sized down
right I think I can do
[Music]
it oh
yeah
[Music]
easy summon all my pets
summon the small version of what we're
fighting
too oh yeah okay so as long as we don't
use
[Music]
Thunder it for sure gets sized down at
least uh half off while still looking
bigger than the other one hey yo that
was big damage okay okay wait it gets
another turn wait it gets another turn y
y y y y y oh no that's my
own right that was my own
[Music]
okay 100 400
50 I'll eat that for the next turn I'll
take a Magic
Shield I wonder physical attack would be
good not
bad ah easy it's down in two turns by
the latest I think
I
think cuz I'm
getting the big magic attack
now
[Music]
uh wondering if I should heal one more
time does it if I can't heal for the
bird does it take up a
[Music]
turn or I just do Magic Shield and Magic
blast together
oh but wait then I do I have enough oh
we'll do it we'll
see oh mind control time oh yeah B don't
kill it
then okay okay okay
okay don't kill it no B you can't do 300
damage we're good we're good oh but ah
it's his turn ah
ah well
well we can try
again at some
point so ah
ah oh oh we're going to blast through
ah we do get to fight this one yeah ah
I'm interested has an interesting
design oh oh they're
dead time to save
[Music]
them uh pberry let me tell you about the
cycle of life
friendship
[Music]
has to go on diet
okay oh 1,800 that's way less than the
one we just fought no tool
[Music]
okay going to get my whole party out
though
[Music]
strong optional
monster strong you call that
strong all was in in one turn it did
pretty decent damage and then the next
turn it didn't so that was kind of
confusing
[Music]
wait the chests are opened what behind
it are unopened
chests can we use this for
[Music]
crafting wait in one of the crafting
recipes they had like smaller dark magic
Stones I think so if we yeah make it
split yeah yeah yeah there we go yeah
that's what I was expecting now getting
the small pieces for
crafting a stone that controls the
reasoning of those who touch it fueling
the desire for
[Music]
power I like her voice actress sounds
cute
for yes I
[Music]
did sure you could have mhm
mhm what makes you think you could have
done
that it's
him
[Music]
for she followed
evil
Kate she used
us that's why she doesn't have character
art are can't be evil oh yes they cane
[Music]
the why does she know
magic did she use the dark magic
[Music]
Stone they still Magic from the witches
and then they give it to
humans to fight more witches but then
don't you just have more witches you
made humans
witches what's the
point I guess to have the power on your
side and you
control she's
SM she's SM
no not the
BS Bros of
Cananda thank you fro of Cananda where
is Cananda
[Music]
no thank you go from Canada Oh Canada Oh
Canada how beautiful are your maple
trees they make us good yummy syrup that
we pour over pancakes Oh Canada Oh
Canada how beautiful are your maple
trees you bumping too one and apologize
he apologizes back oh what a surprise Oh
Canada Oh Canada the land of
politeness pleasantries oh wow
wow
[Music]
wow W that thing in the back is like a
uh robot they didn't use for a million
years or what cute can we activate
[Music]
him
no not the cramps you're getting old
black Joe just like
[Music]
me she overlapped with herself kind of
almost
L the Sky City yeah yeah it looks like
it could be from
[Music]
that I had no idea Kate was so dangerous
I'm out of the mind but ended up
somewhere strange I didn't even find any
chaos Stone I should look around a bit
Matt's Garden are you Matt
Bro look at the cannon on top of the
house sheesh the house looks interesting
too looks like it's made out of just
like cardboard pretty much I like
[Music]
it
nah oh is there sleeping is there
someone sleeping
[Music]
no become a pilot for
it no it's not the
popes wait why did he why did he
just in between after saying he has
never seen it before he like coughed in
a way like he was concealing something
[Music]
oh Jay I thought you were
Matt
just black Joe is
[Music]
evil how is that hair growing out of
your
head don't tell me you made made a hole
for that little piece of hair in your
[Music]
hat so Dum but I like
it
[Music]
for oh thanks bro
one of the girls in this game is the
same VA as
[Music]
riseo damn they they had some budget huh
H comes full circle well the voice
actress must have been thinking that for
sure oh
another cute crafting game let's go
[Music]
I don't want to go
Y no I don't want to go I want to
[Applause]
stay I want to
stay okay
[Music]
bye chainsaw man really
oh we're all the way back here luckily
K's companion shared some cha stones
with me I need to hurry and take it to
Anna Anna's house can be reached here
this m what if Anna's dead
now why do I have this feeling that we
go back and Anna's
dead damn it
W Doom
[Music]
posting just want to kill a few of these
monsters because I need their tails
they're fluffy tails
okay we go in here and then we teleport
to the home of Anna who is now
dead uh was it the small one no it was
the big one
right no was a small one why why not
just use the big
one wait no it wasn't
the wait what small I guess it was the
desolate Hill oh yeah yeah yeah it
didn't say anything about Anna so I was
confused I was just looking for Anna in
the
[Music]
text what is this space
for this
space Hidden Treasure Chest no
[Music]
why I'm sorry I'm so curious oh there's
something here for
sure for sure not go to
sure I'm clicking I'm clicking looking
but there's
[Music]
nothing
really
[Music]
okay
H oh she's
alive oh I like how her bed fits
perfectly into that little
Nook I mean you know you probably
normally IRL you you wouldn't place it
like that because you can't really stand
next to it but I like that I kind of
like it just got to leave or enter your
bed um at the end of
it just like you know also I think
there's like maybe like 10 cm of space
um where it's not right next to the wall
like at the tip of the end of the bed
basically you can scooch in through
[Music]
there you used to have a bed in like
that no pies what the
[Music]
hard to make you bed who the
makes their bed I never make make my
bed no need to make your
bed for
reasons
why but see I kind of thought that we
end up using the K stones for ourself
for crafting
[Music]
yeah crafting yeah yeah I knew it I knew
why did I know that we would use it for
ourselves
[Music]
a s forier not to make you
bed it was unhealthy to make you
[Music]
bed sharing the most random knowledge
here
[Music]
fore
ohe
[Music]
fore oh oh oh for
what do you mean so far he's been
stripping people and just letting them
go anyway
[Music]
he's
he's making up some
[Music]
aimim say that to me when I play Fallout
again this
week
for
[Music]
Fore
spee fore
[Music]
a hard is a try
hard believe
[Music]
me sorry me a banana
banana banana
[Music]
[Laughter]
fore
[Music]
that's fine I was looking for a
challenge
I need to go to idle
meeting so please wait a moment
[Music]
don't let the bladder control
you but it's part of my
system I'm not going to for wa on the
ground because it's part of my
[Music]
system don't say it like that what the
don't throw it on the ground and also
don't be on the ground I'll be RV
he
it's soft movie
spee foreign spee
[Music]
oh I think oh that's
interesting what that smoothie press on
my
keyboard what you didn't hear
me
somebody think it was motion or so in
the chat who said I pissed away my voice
so
dumb I know but I think smoothie pressed
on something maybe I don't know what the
I was unmuted but it still was gone
anyway okay you didn't hear me the
hell you heard me talking too smoothie
though right so I unmuted myself and I I
did she I did see her pressing something
on my keyboard that must have been it
H okay we are so back guys we're going
to put on those earrings that they
really want me to wear apparently ooh 8%
magic
attack
sheesh anything
else that's
new oh I think the iron armor was the
best one yeah
okay also we should switch outfits again
we have you been using the normal one
for a while let's switch again
to this
one yay I look like a vampire
witch okay here we
go oh
wow oh wow oh it's the other one too
it's like several of them
oh don't
worry yeah your worries are so
useless in these cases you need a witch
you should be thankful for the witch's
existance
[Music]
oh she tries but she
fails would you guys like to receive
help from me
poor
girl
okay
par
literally oh that's
R oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah she does
sound like her
Olivia it's a loser Big L
[Music]
moment okay two of the Big Friend shaped
ones and one very interesting
snake with pigtails twintails
M well we have so many of these might as
well use
them all the ones in the front actually
have more HP than the ones the one in
the back what's the
catch what is the
catch I have a feeling if we take out
these ones first he will spawn more of
them so the fire demon maybe had I don't
know could be must not be necessarily
true yeah yeah you say you say I should
Target the one in the back to that's
what I was thinking he looks like he's
going to spawn more and he has lower HP
so I can just focus on him
first he'll be down in an instant
thanks for the membership welcome oh
it's a
jailbird judging by the picture oh you
were here since before that was just a
renewal thank you
[Music]
again yeah oh
done I'm too strong guys I think I'm
overleveled we might actually really be
overleveled
these ones are more
[Music]
buff we get another set of turns let's
go oh
special magic blast school
[Music]
time cute
dance counter attack let's
go oh and another turn and another turn
and another turn and another turn and
another turn and another
turn agility going
strong
I I'm the hero who saves the
[Music]
day yeah I don't mind being a little bit
overleveled we can
go for everything more comfortably
but I didn't really try to be
overleveled
Alfredo shut up and go make some chicken
alfredo
Alfredo you be more useful in the
kitchen yeah at least he is Brave
[Music]
bra give me that
stone slap
he was just Fanning the
demon
girl
fore fore
[Music]
speech mhm
foree
fore
[Music]
fore can
you
[Music]
for entrance on top of the
room witches protect witches after
all the bomb
[Music]
what the what kind of treatment is
this
hey she says while strong to
[Music]
foree
for what you going to
[Music]
do whip me watch me whip watch me nigh
neigh
he wants to whip whip he wants to neigh
oh it's
spider it's kind of
cute it's kind of adorable and freaking
e go away you sound like a
cream oh that really creeps me out what
a
[Music]
creep what spider
cute
foree
[Music]
foree spee fore
funny
exchange you should apologize for what
because you broke my robot oh okay sorry
that's not enough what what should I do
uh become part of our team
no wow nice
[Music]
no it's
not
[Music]
Alchemy
no I don't believe it
[Music]
there was too much liquid for it to be
makeup where sharing Anna if exur the
devil the devil the evil demons the
devil from theak Village Anna must be
very worried I should let her know I'm
safe Anna Anna Anna
Anna I'm
coming I know
way let me just pick up some
items oh they haven't even where are the
enemies oh here maybe I should fight
[Music]
some it's all Tona and makeup remover
that could be but still no I don't think
so it's some nice ingredients for
crafting I would
assume did the big guy spawn where
exactly was
he if we would use a teleporter we'
probably get him
easier somewhere at the end
right we can give it another
try to get the big
boy zone four
is this where he
is this is the
puzzle now this
was
oh oh did I go too far next
one oh yeah maybe he didn't respawn
though ah here and then left
I still
respawning takes them a while
sheesh oh but we can take some stuff
wait we never got to open the chest
because we were ped it out weren't we or
did I just walk out forgetting the
treasure
chest it was
the bulb BB bulb of slightly larger
explosion radius
oh bump BP jnel that was forced out
let's go worth going
back
nice
by that's me
[Music]
finally a real athl
[Laughter]
game
[Music]
for understandable
she seemed so nice in the
[Music]
beginning bet hp's only triple digits
the
[Music]
roast no I think she would have four
digits Maybe
not maybe now she would but by the time
we fight her she would be leveled so
high she would have for dig
[Music]
a here I I think the um developers are
watching here there's a type of grammar
mistake I don't mind but you know might
as well take a note there's a demon
ceiling Stone in the mine there we
go write it down write it down
I'm a game
[Music]
tester
for yes just leave me in charge of
[Music]
it but it's fun
AE a
[Music]
pie let's go it's pie time
baby thanks for the pinky thank you ni
[Music]
s I'm reading one
message oh wa wa W to me way
W oh
oh yes wa after my
[Music]
stream okay way way a key from David for
unlocking the iron gate at the entrance
to the lak
[Music]
ahy saky sneaking like your snake
Furrow exorcism I need to take care of
the small demons remaining in the mine I
if I left them unchecked they'll grow
into larger demons and reappear in the
[Music]
village oh tip try getting a new weapon
how about enchant staff stage two try
creating a magic circle how about four
Fork like I already did that did I not
four Fork lightning Circle I already
have but a new staff will would be
nice well organized collection of
restorative recipes let's go pie is
there a
pie would be nice if there was
pie let's go to the mine
entrance then we go wait oh was it this
what they mean what the key is for
ah okay I'll come back
eventually the hotel's cookie recipe but
I didn't steal that one they share it
[Music]
publicly okay let's see what we can do
in terms of crafting and getting even
more
overpowered oh staff weapon of
Evolution yeah where the do I get
the flame frog fire pouch is that even
accessible to
[Music]
me flame FL flame flog flame flog
fire the dwarf Golem Essence see there's
another uh reason why I need more of
them I can make more of them but in the
swamp flame flow fly fl FL flame FL
in the
swamp flame
flock flame flog uh
flog yeah so here right right
[Music]
here wait I thought I could walk
over oh wait I need I need to I need to
be on my on my board or so right I was
wondering why I couldn't go over there
last time t
[Music]
flame vog I'm coming for the flame
flog flame
flog quick
handt frog
spawn frog
[Music]
spawn didn't they have like some really
dangerous enemies here we were like
let's try again some other time maybe we
can try it this
time flame flog flame flog oh wait this
is not flame flog where is the flame
flock the the flowers yeah
they're over
here those shitty flowers let's give it
a
try although my mp I'd like to heal the
MP is there a heal here flame block not
flame CL
[Music]
oh shortcut back because that's good
because I want to
heal you think I can stomp them this
time H let's see I would not
underestimate them although oh okay they
have 4 it was the damage that they did
not the HP I think that worried me
oh wow wow
[Music]
wow
okay yeah it's no
[Music]
worries
probably
[Music]
right a little bit worried
oh sheesh I should have put that in the
middle
[Music]
maybe I should have summoned them from
the
[Music]
beginning what what status of oh I die
in four turns or
[Music]
so don't worry it won't take that
long but that might be what it is just
ignore
[Music]
it are they fly they they fly they die
by the fire anyway why am I even
bothering with them
huh oh
[Music]
well goodbye it was lovely to host you
all in my late night RPG show today
thank you soon and goodbye
off to the flame
flogs I wonder what did they drop did
they drop something
[Music]
cool crispy flowers for dinner now I'm
actually having like a chicken salad
with
M it wasn't cuscus what do you call the
small round noodles that are bigger than
couscous
they're actual
noodles what what was it
[Music]
again oro
oro oro did I make Oro they're really
small but I made like a noodle salad
with uh cucumber tomato and chicken and
it was seasoned uh with a lot of parsley
[Music]
and a lot of parsley and like a a
apricot is
[Music]
dressing very interesting I'm excited to
eat it today oh and it also has another
dip even though it already has dressing
for some reason it comes with a dip a
yogurt garlic
dip oh interesting this one we also
stayed away from I guess actually all of
these we stayed away from did we yeah
cuz we still earn combat exp from
this Oro pastina was not pastina I think
cuz I've never heard that
before glad you have a healthy
meal it's pretty healthy H I had three
chicken dishes because those are just
the lowest
calories and has protein and stuff
next time I'd like to have some fish too
it's kind of boring just having chicken
and also the problem is that it was like
three times like separately packaged
chicken stuff right but the their uh off
date is the same for every single one of
them
so normally I can like plan it out
better to because I have us usually I
have some dishes that are um that don't
even have meat or it has like beef or or
pork pork goes pretty
long yeah usually the chicken or the
fish I have to cook pretty
early Taste of chicken gets old what you
think
so I think I still like it I like
chicken a lot anyway
yeah the date is just really close
already by the time I receive it it's
like fre days until it goes off but it's
supposed to cover the whole week right
so I'm
[Music]
like I have to
hurry and I don't want to of course I
could cook all of it in one day but a
lot of the things they just taste better
when they're fresh so ideally I don't
want to cook all of it in one day and
that would take up too much time anyway
so that sucks I don't want to cook
everything in one day I don't want to
have to do
that giant wamp Leaf w
w oh oh they're all relatively strong
450 on each of them
she that looks like we're dying in four
turns
again or or not maybe not maybe that's
not one of is who
knows meal prep save you lots of time uh
I kind of did meal prep by cooking what
I'm eating today already
yesterday ah no not this ah
oh well I have enough
um summon cost for
it ah
[Music]
he what is this what are you doing stop
stop hurting me
[Music]
yeah I think I need a bit more
HP maybe the 100 is fine
but I don't want to go Overkill you know
with 700 when our HP right now is 282
why can't we even make
this this seems so overkill for early
game we've had that early on already
[Music]
that one's
fine
[Music]
and cure poison oh did I cure
that yeah we we're F oh does it like it
now the number went up again and when it
hits me I wonder what it means maybe
they do more damage to me the higher the
count is or so no wait now okay 41 I
guess they're just renewing their dot
damage cuz it just took 41 HP from
me just like stacking
[Music]
restacking finish it SE Spirit
nice w we got some cool
items maybe they're going to be useful
in
crafting e
item where are the flyer logs what fly
logs what the is that there's a
puzzle oh there's panas or
so let me go back what is this thing oh
fro Stone oh oh I see I throw it like
over there and then
I and didn't they didn't react to the
stone yet I
guess but I probably don't have to go
here do I he wait it didn't
[Music]
fall am I doing it
wrong it's just lands over
here ah is this bugged
let me try one more
time I need to mount and wait for fish
to go to the Rock okay I need to be
mounted
oh but I have this feeling I don't even
I shouldn't be here this is not where
the flame blogs are I think wait
okay ah now it's Landing
there oh my God
chill should I've waited
longer I'll need more
Stones well now what I'm out of stones
oh I kind of made it what the
go go over to this side get stuck
over there and run run
run hey yo what the water balloon
frog I have this feeling I shouldn't be
here
[Music]
though
7,000 finally a challenge
it that's 7,000 is a bit
[Music]
rough
oh wait we have a few of these permanent
things I forgot
ooh do I need these for crafting should
I use them now this one for
sure this one no this one I don't know
some of these you still use for crafting
so
h
no I'm about to get even more
overleveled
yeah oh we should use some of these
bombs maybe in this fight if it gets
tough this one I used several times
already I don't think it but
[Music]
okay here we go and give this a
try I think we can do it maybe agility
or
strength maybe
[Music]
agility at least he has no
minions from
me love some
frog unless it's
frog what if I can do you guys think I
can summon
him this big
boy he looks like the trees cute
[Music]
friend of 66
is this might be
[Music]
tough already need to heal
oh this one's good
[Music]
too well once we get you know magic
blast and stuff it'll be pretty
good I'll have to heal like every turn
and then every other turn I'll do Magic
Shield guala
oh gree's
[Music]
back did it say that it
was immune to
[Music]
something I hope
not 536 that's
good that's good okay his turn is next
please be
nice
he yo yo yo yo that's
big that's a big win then I don't have
to heal I wouldn't be able to heal now
anyway all
right yeah and he doesn't get another we
get two two turns all of us get two
turns before he attacks again
okay lucky
he gets the the fancy attack let's
go why is the boar so weak man we need
to replace them crit
time can you crit on the aru's Arrow I
haven't used this in a long
[Music]
time does not consume a turn
Doo pretty
six 1,100 damage
and we get another hit because that
didn't consume a turn W
Pyle I got this in the back now we got
so lucky with that counter ooh this also
gets a
crit
[Music]
nice no problem I get another heal from
my bird my
bird let's
go no luck oh skill that thing nah it
did stand a chance hey yo wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
he gets
[Music]
a the moment he gets two turns without
me going in between it's over
[Music]
what I'll try one more
time bird was stunned couldn't he I
didn't even get a turn
[Music]
though cute Alex cute
maybe I don't mind healing in the coming
turn but I I could Shield it in theory
but I don't mind healing in the next
turn as long as I have the bird it's
[Music]
fine let's use the stronger one this
time
time 600 damage just got to get him down
faster I could even go for the Thousand
damage
[Music]
one super cute at least you know it it's
good that you know it no need to deny
it okay he's probably not going to miss
this time
[Music]
right which means that a lot of
things up I can shield and then magic
blast though and heal next
turn I got it under control
[Music]
I got it under control
still until he gets a double
turn strategic crit arua Arrow
[Music]
ready and we got to
heal and now sh again if I can can I I
think I can
[Music]
uh
ohs yeah I
can and fire so if he hits me now I'll
be
fine I'll be
fine this is exciting
actually I want to win I want to
win oh oh oh see he gets another turn
but I might survive it my
HP I wait do I still have the shield
actually does it continue until it's my
turn
again it does doesn't
it I didn't realize that let's go I
survived I survived
okay but I I have to heal but he's
almost dead um n
1,000 what if I don't
heal and I pray that my attack in
combination with the others will kill
him don't chance it yeah the bomb could
also be quite good another another bomb
like this one is certain death for him
this one
in combination with the
others
maybe I don't want to waste this one
it's like one of a
[Music]
kind play it safe but what if he gets a
double turn after that again I can't see
that oh but wait what what if I what am
I thinking why don't I just
[Music]
uh Magic shielded
but I'm running out of uh MP
though then then I'll do a triple
swing oh but but ah wait wait wait wait
wait wait but if there's no MP for him
to
[Music]
take oh I survived
the Magic Shield saved me oh he's dead
[Applause]
yay oh I got an achievement for that
let's
go oh I did it wait did I get something
cool I I never
catch
wherever I got a cool item or
not okay okay
friends m
M oh I can go like really
far they're already reacting to
it com back to
[Music]
me do I have to like wait longer or what
am I doing wrong I yes I am running away
too fast but I have enough Stones it's
okay I have enough
Stones I can just keep on running
actually why am I stopping on one
[Music]
stone they they they re re respawn
to fight these
no no I have to
[Music]
heal wow
now that we killed someone like that
Bron I will forever be super confident
about
anything nothing can get us
[Music]
down oh
wa My Pet's attack is
crazy also he just dropped
one of
these
damn they dropped that just like it's
candy flyer log what the f I'm wrong
here where where's the fly a flog fly it
gets worse and worse fly a flog where is
did I go the wrong path somewhere
there wait have I never fought the fly
of logs before
cuz I don't think I've ever been here
before I don't remember the
piranas wait oh I forgot to
mount damn it can we do it n i I'll go
back in yeah I never came here
before
so for some reason I thought we fought
flyer blogs
before flyer blogs
[Music]
they do come back really
fast go
away what there he is oh it's another
big boy I wonder if he's weaker than the
other
one dear Lord uh
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
3,400 I'm not even going to use one of
my Buffs for
that we'll bring my pets still because I
bring them everywhere I go
[Music]
hey Playstation release date not out yet
for
this go get it on
Steam I'm playing on
Steam don't you have a
computer feel like steam is like the
easiest solution
[Music]
hey you need a 4090 for this not a good
one oh I guess I mean you don't need a
490 for sure but oh
counter but some a decent PC I guess is
necessary potato laptop potato
potato but hey potatoes are awesome I
love potatoes we all love potatoes
you should appreciate your potato lap
you could fry it if you wanted
to Flame FL
flyou oh I got an achievement for this
one
too FL FL flame flog fly a
[Music]
flouch okay now we can craft the new
stuffff
am I doing this okay let me just once
wait a little bit
longer no they do I waited and they
still come right
away bye-bye
suckers hope you choke on those
stones why you life
again you respond too fast my
friend it'd be better for your own Goods
to just stop respawning cuz I'm spawn
camping
you okay we can go
home I
suppose I suppose hi
oh let me get
that for some reason I thought we i f we
fought fire frogs before like small
ones but all of that
was not what I
expected or did we fight fir flogs like
in the lava is cave
[Music]
before how do we get this one it's time
to get it I need a replacement for my
stupid
[Music]
boar an itemp to wake it
up eat an AG bar next to it
okay
interesting is that it better be it if
that's not
it oh
oh I didn't need it I threw it on it how
do you get the idea for this what the
1,800 weak we might kill it
[Music]
accidentally you
cheated how do you get this idea don't
how don't kill
it be
nice be
[Music]
nice I'll remove it next turn
no that's really like having to remove
your pet so that it doesn't kill what
the one you're trying to capture is Big
pal World
Vibes same problem
there you searched a lot for the
[Music]
answer yeah don't kill
it it doesn't do anything it doesn't
even attack me
[Music]
bad
yeah why won't you be mind
controlled sp sp top of the house come
on yes I flipped it
no is to stimulate its sense of smell n
do hold
[Music]
okay then let's make a weapon and also
check what we need to bef friend the
turtle shall we
wow it looks beautiful looks like
there's mountains on top of
it this is the only way to find out what
it
likes I might not have it though I don't
know maybe it wants another aged
Berry oh I don't have it
wait was there more below oh there
was well whatever it is I don't have
it oh wait uh we have to
make uh one dwarf Golem
Essence coming right
up see it's good that I got
extra it's good that I brought more with
[Music]
me
a oh wao I want to make that but we need
the crab stuff for other
things I can make five or flame Circle
thingy oh but that uses up
[Music]
the I got to kill that frog another
time lesser booster Circle oh I made
this before
yeah just checking just checking bombs
Nar do wait can I make the uh no
thousand damage bomb yet an a spell
book meat pie whyn't she share the the
the berry pie recipe with
me but okay it's actually a good uh
recovery
item I have the things it needs to I'll
make them I'll make them I'll make
them got a piria feeli
do annoying
but it's
okay lightning yeah did this I need more
of
[Music]
these see I want to make this I need two
more we need to go to the Blue Crabs
again and then we can make this crabber
armor I just realized it sound it it's
called crabber and high
crabber oh for the high crabber you need
the normal crabber oh and the other
piece of armor oh it builds upon on each
other
n then Evolution finally stronger
[Music]
staff magic super explosion
W that was already overpowered let's
nourish it with h
[Music]
yay already
full next we need rage horn and again
dwarf Golem
[Music]
Essence looking forward to seeing it off
my Expo I'm nervous I'm nervous about it
I I might have to use my own
program where the movement looks really
weird because I I still don't have like
the the model and the
program from go
sta I don't know I I I'll try asking one
more time but recently they haven't
replied uh what's next
what's this
I yeah well at least even if it looks
scuffed at least I I can make 3D work
somehow I might just not dance that uh
like with 100% because you won't see it
properly anyway I might just like dance
a little bit but not properly
[Music]
I don't know if I even remember my own
coros that
well it's been a
while um what are we doing a let's go to
the
crabs and save once just
[Music]
once no
M I'll will come back to you actually
not I'll actually have to practice
[Music]
and I need some time for
that these are the wrong crabs but we're
going to fight them
[Music]
anyway if they want to see 100% that ing
yeah they should come and watch our
concerts or my music videos or my
shorts my YouTube
shorts there's currently two more that I
have on my mind I just don't have time
for it right now but I'm going
to make I still want to do the mikoi
dance and another one the one from
canatan
Oru uru is also one I want to do
I really like
the the moves from that
one maybe next week I can make
them p
p i I already did forget about the
canata dance that I wanted to do it but
then she was really late in replying to
me but she did reply to me today
yesterday is and then I was like ah yeah
right I wanted to dance
that thanks for the
reminder she didn't really remind me but
just her existence reminded me 20 days
later qub
there's more crabs there
[Music]
too my turtle pet can swim here oh then
I'll get a couple more of these then
[Music]
cute okay
uh let's give it a
[Music]
try it's so
slow but I guess it will be really fast
in the water come here come here you
slow as
[Music]
Turtle where are we going with
this zoom zoom
zoom over
there is there more Islands let me can I
see
it a closer
view don't
know immediately Dismount that
wow there they are this is like
the the Farming Farming
Islands let's go to Aloha region yeah
[Music]
Aloha oh strong
ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow they don't want to be built into
armor they
refuse but you have
[Music]
to I do be tanking
nice
six
six loots noise is there more come over
here not SM small to of the house slow
slow SL SL T the
house where is the invisible
[Music]
wall I came back
home
[Music]
ah oh
oh
uhuh Ah that's where I I am right
now I want to see is there something
else
[Music]
here suddenly
sh oh wait right I can make this bigger
I forgot
ah swirly thingies I guess are the end
of the
[Music]
map can we even go into the
ship I know they talked about it when we
first start and I just didn't
acknowledge it and didn't go
[Music]
in
oh what the where the am I
[Music]
I'm I came to Southeast
Asia oh found an
island he yo he yo should I be
here oh I guess we'll have something
never
mind South Coast abandoned mine
how strong are oh what this looks
like my pet has been recalled
treasure
woohoo that is what you are
Woo you're my golden star W make my
wish if you love me
treasure
you if you let me treasure you you
y what am I
doing you are my
treasure you are my
treasure you are my treasure you you you
you
are you are my child
treas you are my
treasure you are my
[Music]
treasure actually I guess it's got to go
a little bit forward
first now
you you are my
tal wait no is it what doesn't this just
open it oh it was that
easy but I got to bring it back in order
to pass by okay so no this was
necessary wow there's a treasure chest
in this cave there's several
unless unless there's some mimics
trusting by the condition of the chest
it seems to have been put here recently
no one can get here by land are these
Pirates it's the treasures from the
pirates that they're just storing
here well we'll have to put these items
to good
use I hope they're not strong they don't
look
strong you're human right why am I
talking
okay wow Ninja pberry
[Music]
Thomas oh it's not ours it's
his
treasure he's old he can't speak
properly
anymore oh pberry he got no mercy
holy
how can we morally excuse burning the
guy who got I guess because he's a
pirate and stole
it but now we're stilling but now we're
stealing it I don't think this is
morally
excusable she is
evil wow 2,000 gold and I don't know
where to use my gold though five out
holy
St what
what am I going to do with all this gold
so far I've had no use for
it
what
5,000 what
15,000 or 100,000 do you say
1,5 what
15,000 what hey
what hey
[Music]
yo what I with all this
money eventually they will give us a
reason to use our money
right
eventually pull down bed and roll around
it hell
yeah that is a good
idea
oh that's the that's the pirate ship oh
no it's the Royal Palace world Warrior
ship never mind it seems to have been
deployed to hunt down the pirat on
around here let's not go this way
okay yeah oh what's that over
[Music]
there sh oh
it's try
me
[Music]
for going to have a ocean fight
now no not really
[Laughter]
[Music]
girl you stole their Loot and you're
like oh man these are so annoying she's
like Savage sometimes oh my God like
this belongs to
[Music]
her funny girl
man hey grabs I'm back
I see what this
um what this uh turtle is for now it's
really not for anything but swimming and
it's for getting these
trashes I like
[Music]
it it's pie B's world we just live in it
so true so true hey I wonder if I was
dodging the the Sharks but I wonder if I
were to kind
of um not Dodge them
if we had a
chance to just not get
bunked anyway then I think I'm ready to
teleport
home now the hole can I go into the hole
maybe from the
[Music]
water switch our PC game
both um
what was I going to do a uh I was going
to make some
[Music]
armor okay now we got 22
she let's
go did you beat the hermit
crab yeah I guess not is that where this
item comes from
probably wait hermit crab where was that
hermit
[Music]
crab I mean we don't need to be that
overpowered now do
[Music]
we we can make a few of the shield
stones again but not really
necessary this one increases HP and
death I want to make a few of these cuz
unless we need it for something else
the the
t t
t
no no no
okay then I can make a couple of
these w w I'm going to buff myself so
hard I can upgrade my lightning to four
or
really oh oh it wasn't already oh it oh
yeah I guess it
wasn't
ah ah
[Music]
nice wait I was going to make this
one should I just make it
all yeah
clearly overpowered CH maybe I'll make
one of these
[Music]
too Max HP + 5 and then tutu tutu Tut
tutu Tut
Tut H maybe even throw one of these
in another
one we can afford it cuz we just added
so much
[Music]
HP to so
cute okay we can train we have two
training
sessions
um what what could we need maybe more
HP I don't know we're so
strong we're so
strong we're already so
strong maybe this and this
[Music]
I want my bongs to be strong too so
we're going to hit some
rocks oh no how does this
work oh
[Music]
wait I thought I had to mash
it no
oopsie next
time charges magic while
defending oh the defense will be
slightly low
than okay H sleepy
[Music]
time get this maybe
M
[Music]
okay we go by Vibes
exactly we learn by doing not by reading
okay what was next in our
general furo exorcism investigate
landlock mind ah okay
okay let me save
though I need to switch my armor
too uh
[Music]
here
yay follow me kfp we'll go even deeper
than ever before even deeper than any
human has ever gone before well why
because we're Wich he yo demon demon
H found you
cute looks like that helmet might be a
little bit heavy for you let me take it
off oh there's
more
600 W who who oh okay I thought they
were keeping the the small ones too no
it's just one big one okay
okay oops no not this
[Music]
Miss wait I didn't I didn't put the the
Thunder cycle thingy on can I do that
while I'm on the
road for sure right I can do it
sure I can can
[Music]
I wow it was already 900 damage now
sheesh ah there's more
[Music]
oh no I could have done it
easily it's turn number two it has bunny
ears she that gun
[Music]
did you see my
Firepower here we go 2,800
let's
go let's make quick
pieces with his
[Music]
bombs why do they want so to fight so
bad well it is a RPG
game everybody wants to
fight me too me included
[Music]
uh kind of looks like she could be a
vtuber that design looks like a vtuber
design I like it
[Music]
oh nice
explosion yeah 900
damage
wow either or from
[Music]
a more V me
Get
[Music]
Wrecked I look like a terap character I
do also when I wear my black
armor but it's kind of different style
pberry
Savage I like this rivalry it's kind of
cute can we get much deeper
[Music]
is this some too song what I'm thinking
of right
[Music]
nowon that's some T
song I should tell
Anna go to Anna's house didn't they say
I should go deeper are you
[Music]
not too but Japanese meme song but it's
a meme song yeah but it's also too no
was it not was that on
mut I thought that was to
though oh what did too just make a video
to it though like not too themselves but
yeah cuz I know the
video two different songs yeah maybe
we're thinking of two different
songs Silver Forest yeah it's from
Silver
[Music]
Forest is she dying is she okay
what my do post was
[Music]
true
what what the
why maybe the
[Music]
boy you don't really seem to have a
reason for it
[Music]
I'm hungry
guys
[Music]
hungry alred
f is keep doing ew stalker
[Music]
creep would have to be a big
snack just going to eat dinner
soon 900 p.m.
[Music]
they look like lell which is funny
because this place is called
[Music]
lak today today I only had breakfast and
a banana during the
stream cuz I had breakfast and then I
went to get my uh package and I came
back I played a little bit with CI and
then I started my stream so I didn't
have time to have like my
sandwich or
whatever so I'm more hungry than usual I
[Music]
suppose I am
hungry CH some nuts
pistachio woohoo let's go I wish they
were salted
[Music]
though oh my
God stos are so good even when
they're not
salted put your own salt I feel like it
won't stick to it
[Music]
sh can chicken eat
pistachos are they not toxic or so got
to make sure I wouldn't want to risk
[Music]
it
nuts check on Google you check on Google
[Music]
feed one of us and wait who wants to be
the test
[Music]
subject no why did you do that what the
hell in the
forest for up
there
oh you say you're not kfp the fact that
you're here in one of my long RPG
streams means you are kfp trust
me doesn't matter if you have a
membership or not you are kfp
[Music]
why am I taking my time to summon all
these mobs pets when this fight is over
in an
instant yes you are
chicken everybody here except me as a
chicken
is this That Way
Northeast oh they want me to go
Southeast though again southeast Asia
but what's here I'm curious what cute
what is this
monkey I think I need his horns these
horns look like the ones I might need
how much xp do you have an
AO what was this
again oh let's
go
3,200 i f way stronger Buffalo gorilla
hey let's go I think I need it for
something cool either it was either for
armor or for the
[Music]
weapon let's
go zaku
monkey oh it's cute how he's so like
fluffy with the feather uh not feathers
the leaves
[Music]
oh
okay looks like me in the
morning
hugable very hugable
[Music]
oh she does life
life
sucking oh nice oh that was fast I got
the Buffalo gorilla horn and I got an
achievement so was it for
[Music]
now I think it
was for the weapon but I don't think I
can check it
here I feel like it was for the weapon
which would be crazy I could already
upgrade it I
think no way guys guys do you
know do you
know yeah the lightning
[Music]
uh I have to uh replace this
right I think I have to go
home how do you do this again I think I
have to go go home
[Music]
H then we can check the staff thing
too if we can upgrade the staff already
that would be crazy we just upgraded it
now a moment
ago my Liv staff with the horn huh yeah
yeah I think I remember seeing this kind
of horn
there wait I can just tell I forget I
forget I don't have to go to a Teleport
Stone if I want to teleport home
not get harit oh
dear poor poor gorilla poor
monkey oh no it's a rorn it's a
different horn yeah that would have been
too easy then what is this horn good
for okay uh how do we do this again
[Music]
oh what I don't
remember
h
ah there we go this one Center magic
circle
is has to be exchanged right
[Music]
yeah this is the is it the right one no
I I put flame and this
one
and yeah we don't have anything better
for this one yet maybe we can make
one wait you can double
this heck did I do that for the others I
didn't but it will just get more
expensive which is okay at this point I
think
oh was just
double Merchant request also needs the
horn Merchant request
ah Merchant
request
[Music]
n
oh look at
that there's you're showing me what like
is currently
respawning Jee maybe talk to RAF he has
optional Quest RAF is has some Quest
Ralph
Toco who's Ralph
again Ralph
Ralph Ralph was Ralph the dude with the
pie like one of the D with the pie yeah
re R the Coronet look like where is he
though where do I find
him I guess in that fork uh of the the
puff Fork Fork
[Music]
puff Merchant's Road maybe around
there okay okay
okay bro give me something to do with my
money
[Music]
oh 5,000 gold for these
700 increase Max by 15 by seven by
three is that all I'll ever be using my
gold
[Music]
for wait I have uh one of these
I wonder if I need to craft something
out of it this this feels
[Music]
like scroll down there's more oh just
one this looks like Maple cats
balls sorry I think a lot about Maple
cats balls
H
anyway I can sell too
[Music]
forgot ah he wants
it
huh I get a ring for it all right you
going to have it
h
dooo oh
[Music]
need a few more of these I had a lot of
them before and these are always in
[Music]
demand damn all that money
okay somebody who played this game here
has to tell me if these are used for
crafting something the crest
leaves or if it's safe for me to just uh
eat them
now
no not that you
remember okay okay
if they are I never used them okay M M M
M plus free
m
yummy power is
mine
okay by the way what's over
[Music]
here ah the boar plane oh didn't this
place also have something over
powered don't
[Music]
remember sorry I'm just running
around trying to see if I can find
another big boss monster that I missed
out
on can we tame aor senior I think we
fought them before and it wasn't the an
option ah yeah didn't we have problems
with these
Knights did
[Music]
we yeah we never fought them we can
still get exp from them that's for sure
but they're weak
now what do they drop I'm curious tell
me give me
[Music]
is it just not going to hit all of them
but it goes back to one oh
well oh the Ring The Ring the the ring I
got from the quest I got earrings from a
quest but yeah the things he just gave
me
oh yeah I should check those
[Music]
out oh I got a warrior sword
uh I can carry it oh for stronger bnks
but we're focusing on Magic it's
interesting though that we can use that
why but it's like it's Canon that we
would use a witch staff why would we put
a warrior sword
on is she okay
Alex okay what was this this uh we just
[Music]
okay maybe I can switch this out if this
is good
oo oo this one's good Enchanted
[Music]
ring this is not much we can replace
this one too with
that I like those
Rings this one I'll keep for
[Music]
now I'm talking to you
guys guys if I wasn't talking to you
what would be the point you're going to
give me an existential crisis please
[Music]
don't ooh
wow they're even on the
[Music]
tower why is the reach so low I feel
like in the past it reached
further oh oh well we can get up there
[Music]
too
sure wa even the tower was
shaking the higher they climb the harder
they fall wow you sound like you're full
of
wisdom
Al ow wait why am I so low hey hey hey K
me they're hurting
me oh look there's treasure over there
okay okay okay got to focus on killing
them protect yeah what do you got
shields for I gave you
shields in the chat only to use in the
chat not outside of
it m
M damn they're actually kind of strong
these dudes their armor must make them
really
defensive oh oh you're asking for a
counter attack
this swords you can use outside of J no
no it's an emote in chat only the only
thing you can use outside is whatever
you use in the kfp
[Music]
kitchen
wow hey wait do they even get
damage I feel like I
[Music]
don't what's happening maybe I have to
burn them I don't know
[Music]
they do the building with fall
okay to has its own HP bar I don't see
it is it just not shown to me oh
counter they're
strong I am
impressed as we say in
[Music]
German let me snipe them
really
[Music]
brutally this should do the
trick he's still standing ah there we go
it's like it had one more
HP back
a okay let's see what they have in their
Treasure
Chest
money
5,000 and 10,000
wo this is where it's at and another
10,000 oh my God okay all right I can
buy more stuff at the merchant if I want
to
oh secret little path for another th000
gold oh and wait there's another
path wait that respawns you could like
Farm
gold we can buy the merchant no no no we
don't do that here I only buy
chickens into my service no I don't buy
them you guys just choose to be
here oh there's more there too oh this
is a money
Farm money may not be growing on trees
but it's growing on the ground
[Music]
Oh Let's do let's let's give them a
quick
death cuz we're nice like that
[Music]
the other one go further and what what
what what
decides how far it
[Music]
goes is it just because there are more
buff or
so invisible AO
oh but I feel like the free Fork went F
[Music]
further so I must depend on the enemy
too for
[Music]
it's about hitting chain for power
hit
a
[Music]
n okay I think we can go
home maybe I'll go to the merchant again
sometime to buy more stuff good night
test
people h oh what I need to find out
where the hell is the southeast
Forest bottom bom right
from should I go from the
mine
[Music]
entrance and then
here
perhaps no okay this was the entrance to
the
Village then it must be down south
east here but wait
what no oh wait they have treasure too
but it's probably not wor it
[Music]
I didn't heal
myself oh he was only I was thinking so
like Alfredo doesn't really have a good
reason to steal that like what's his
agenda but okay he was asked to do
it by her that makes a lot more sense
how
[Music]
cute the Doles Canute
it looks a little bit
like a certain someone's arm
style sounds like
no have you guys been watching like the
little dances and stuff that NOA puts
out
[Music]
she hiding her true
power it's
cute like she she puts up videos like
from BB DEA for example where she sings
and dances
it her singing is pretty
cute Who whoo
whoo casual outfit warn in the vilia
village worn mostly by young children of
noble families not suitable for combat
okay but does it
change what wait notable for
comat wait a
[Music]
second has anybody ever
has has anybody ever invited itan or NOA
in 3D for a birthday SL aniversary
life I can't remember that if that ever
happened ah s Senai I guess yeah she
would have invited a probably but I
don't think anybody invited no before
I'm getting
ideas I mean I kind of already have
things planned out so it wouldn't happen
for the upcoming one I can't make
changes now
really
H that would be
funny it's just like I think she only
has one outfit so she couldn't be
wearing like an idle outfit or so
there's not much variety to it only has
that like business outfit for
[Music]
M I wonder if they would like be up for
it even learning a whole Coro not just
like a
chorus would be funny I don't know if I
can promise anything but it's in my head
now it's become a brain warm for
me wow
[Music]
yeah
pajamas it does look cute the icon
looked
cute good brain War
[Music]
dance shorts with her I don't I don't
think I would normally get the chance
because I don't get access to the studio
unless unless you know uh a more than 6
months in advance planned uh birthday
life
uh and then it's like really tight
schedule so not much freedom for stuff
like that just saying well you know I
can bring my accent suit to Japan but
then you know I only have one so it's
like how are they going to we could
record separately I could give it to
them and then record separately but
that's a lot of
effort making that work too
[Music]
looks like Alchemy to
me
[Music]
disgu did Ka
um cuz she doesn't
have ears and we don't think she's a
witch
um um I'm I'm not going to say it but
there's no way right
[Music]
it's she's going to get cancelled by
Twitter no way
no okay yeah you can reverse it too by
yeah making me
look no
way who is
this where did I put my ears
[Music]
well it's a disguise wait she looks so
cute in that outfit though oh I'm not
wearing it now no I got some pretty
clothes from Sarah they won't be any
good in combat but they're perfect for
disguising me as a human to enter the
village I should show Anna my new
clothes and return Moo's
headband
uh what post about eating in McDonald's
what
huh okay now we go to
Anna where are we right now is this a
dead end I remember we've been here
before
actually yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah can you change no it's equipment
the equipment doesn't change the looks
shouldn't be changing
anything cuz it's here right oh it's not
even
here oh
here
what noncombat outfits only apply in oh
okay okay okay I have it on but you
can't see it now until I
enter the village or
[Music]
so uh uh yeah
right let me get
that
and
cute outfit so
cute and she looks good without her hat
too surprise
surprise oh oh yeah that's right that's
the actual reason we're coming here
man can't she like put that pie away
it's like my eyes I can't
focus Anna will be like uh K my eyes are
up here pberry my eyes are up here stop
looking at the
pie I can collect it what
really no
way oh is that
like I can like ah collect it and it
respawns or so because I can always go
here to get pie
[Music]
right
oh
[Music]
Mommy I like the bun I like the jacket I
like the reow
[Music]
cute but this way she finally won't be
judged anymore by
everybody and pushed away and attacked
[Music]
do we really get pie are you just saying
that
[Music]
oh it's more like he became the backpack
rather than he is the
backpack
oh cute yeah I just wait he's also there
though
you how did we so quickly make a black
Joe backpack if that's not actually him
and it's just a
backpack so adorable though that is so
cute that is so
[Music]
cute going to
explode let me in let me
in we just a normal little girl
wow don't say that so
[Music]
loudly that does seem like he's supposed
to be
like not a backpack but it's him
although he doesn't blink but the fact
that they put the camera on the
backpack well it is a backpack but he's
also inside of it while the outside of
it also looks like him you know what I
mean like he's wearing his own
skin does he already never
blink even outside of the backpack
we all wearing own skin yeah but I
thought I think like maybe he's wearing
a double now he doesn't look
alive the spring war is that like spring
break in this world
or God the water looks so close
I love the
water that
[Music]
water that makes me want to go
hiking and look
for like a a a river like that
sheesh you still can't hear
me pberry asked about Anna's p
[Music]
stop questioning me
always
[Music]
for
dump they're still like not really
helpful
okay thanks for nothing
[Music]
I have this feeling that I
Amo but let's just ignore this hch that
I
[Laughter]
have are you calling me crazy chat HH
[Music]
States helped a bit for now don't worry
Anna thre her daughter into the forest
below the Merchants
[Music]
Road before she got caught before the
child got or after
[Music]
I thought before yeah cuz she did get
caught right if it was after then I was
like I was going to be like oh 100%
that's
me hey yo
I have to ask seven people okay two
[Music]
more what if m is your
mother I think then Anna would be even
older hey do you want to tell me about
Anna and her
child doesn't seem like
[Music]
it
for that's
[Music]
me oh that didn't count just now he yo
uh was there someone down
here who
could help
me
oh the blacksmith oh yeah hey yo what's
up I think I got iron or
[Music]
so angry on his
own we're flexing our
iron what are you going to use it
[Music]
for yes yes yes yes yes
yes how much just
one got to help each other in these
trying times
right 10,000
gold I want of those you want more
oh yes you're teaching me let's
go what happened to your
[Music]
son though
he's I am interested I'm dropping by
right
now weapon enhance let's
go oh
done would you like to learn it
done let's
[Music]
go let's give it a
try enhancing requires a certain amount
of iron metal depending on the selected
equipment as enhancement rate increases
the following enhancement will require
more iron materials materials the more
evenly you hit all areas of the equip oh
it's like a game the higher it's
uniformity the higher the uniformity the
higher the effectiveness of the
enhancement uh banging the hammer will
consume stamina when all the stamina is
used up the enhancement will
end but I'm not wearing either of
these H can I not enhance the other
[Music]
one I'll try though maybe do I just use
one o I use a couple I got to use a
couple useful later ah you you think if
I take it
off yeah maybe for
later I don't think it's about taking it
off that would be weird
right also he did not tell me about Anna
or her
child who could we
ask guess we got to go up where did we
enter all the houses
this one
[Music]
here all right
you're you're one of those
[Music]
people I'm going buy just a
few was I here before ah this one's
new I think yeah
[Music]
of course of
course I thought so that counted okay
children usually don't count for these
things I've
noticed oh he calls me is into me I'm
too old for you even though I'm also
young little boys having little
[Music]
crashes a yeah there could be someone
here also I feel like I got kicked out
of this place last time
too carrots
[Music]
there's no one
here there's no one
here I W I think I was in
here oh was I I
wasn't yes
[Music]
for is iric because she's powerless now
don't be afraid of
[Music]
her being canceled by The
Village no
[Music]
way yeah
but a lot of them have the same voice
though still it's cool
[Music]
might be my
mommy she's not going to say it but if
she was really thinking it I think she
would be more like oh my God oh my
[Music]
God I didn't
realize nah he just wants to protect you
it's going to eat you back to the forest
oh that's his way of protecting me I
suppose
oh
whoa who
that is
true is it
me who who
who is it the
pulp no way the p would actually lift
his finger
right W
oh is so
[Music]
powerful
was must be
arredo Alfredo finally regained his real
power
no no no no no no
[Music]
way he was like trying
to
yeah yeah
maybe that would be too
smart whoa whoa hey hey what the
did you kill him
who the are
you
Crown
what how do you know I'm a
human he I
did when did I use my
stuff oh we can oh we can fight
4,500 man
[Music]
ible
okay here we
go I'm going to go all out
[Music]
anyway his sword looks so cool his whole
design is pretty dope I like the armor
Des
design what do you think could be good
I'll go for the ther
1,200
W
strong but I'm
stronger shielding myself how much is
this in
total okay so fer is stronger
my
Pokemon
attack what do you call that water
cannon move from water
Pokemons ah no
MP good to have you
here
hydrum Turtle Chan hydrop pump let's go
[Music]
crit that was
actually crazy smooth of a fight for
4,500 if is real power is around like
four or five times this then I can still
handle
it okay maybe not five
[Music]
times I think I am
midle I'm pretty sure that's
me it just makes sense with the
pie the pie
connection Yeah Anna is my mommy she
looks a little bit different you know
but once she has the light in her eyes
again I'm sure she'll look more like my
mommy
hi bye bye I'm out of here
[Music]
I wasn't worried at all
I'm so addicted to Anna and her
[Music]
she gets it she's thinking the
same yeah because the pie tastes like
the pie her mom made
SM not dump like other
[Music]
characters but the
fact the fact that she brings this up
now on her own so earlyish makes me
think maybe there's a Twist and she's
not our mom h
but I
mean it's got to be her right but that
would be too easy now that we would meet
her so early and that she wouldn't
recognize us she would totally recognize
us why wouldn't she say anything I mean
maybe there's a reason for that too
but we'll find out more on this in the
next no just kidding a bit more
[Music]
may she scared to
stay we were
[Music]
aband fore
you think the very
suspicious there was one thing that he
said I was also suspicious and he's also
really trying to block her right now
[Music]
the bird must be
good he must be
good or he's a spy from the
[Music]
pope is he your dad
wait what if the what if the pope is my
dad cuz I got to have a dad somewhere
right not saying the bird is my dad but
the
[Music]
pop or the night that we just
thought maybe it was the night and when
he said he was looking for me he meant
to like why you're my daughter and then
I suddenly attack him so we have to
fight but
M or like yeah maybe maybe they also
have bad intentions my my my
father I don't know I don't
know maybe the
Golem well it could be the Golem of
course it could be like his soul was
like captured within the Golem and he
can't get out you know that kind of
magical
Theory h
but no I wouldn't believe that a very
strong Warrior has appeared in the
village who's my dad but I'm going to go
back anyway if Anna's really my mother
she might accept me if I can recover my
memories maybe if I go to the great
Gates of the arura temple I can see
something people who played the game how
far am I in the game question mark
percentage wise
roughly question mark
not even halfway
AO maybe
halfway not
halfway oh it's longer than I
[Music]
thought but I think this is a good point
to end it today
[Music]
cuz it's been 6 hours pretty
much yay I got a chance at this again I
kind of want wanted to do that again
okay okay okay okay I'm going to get a
perfect score
now
[Music]
I forgot that I have to keep on
pushing I thought I just push it once
and then I wait and
then and then I push it again ah it says
hold the button Wawa read the text
man oh well at least we got a normal
success did you just say com
pickle com
[Music]
pickle sounded like it to
me
uh stop crying about it
[Music]
go get me some
money
[Music]
nice
okay
maybe I can Farm some resources even
though I don't really think it's that
necessary if there's another secret boss
or not secret but like hidden boss that
I haven't fought yet that you guys can
think of if you played the game let me
know I could do it off
stream just to you know get some stuff
done some homework so to
[Music]
say meow meow
meow
request no
but I had a lot of fun today again love
this
game you could make a separate safe and
search no no no no
no definitely want to pick it up someday
yay you should or is there a crap boss
on the
islands if you guys can tell me that in
the kfp hashtag with like the name of
the boss and the location that would be
amazing
[Music]
K oh mommy is on my roof that says it
all but if we're only 20% through the
game or let's say let's say 30 I'm just
going to Proclaim that then I feel like
it's too early to know but she's on my
roof she's on my roof and this is a all
kind of dark dark because she lost her
magic she needs the The Magic In Her
Eyes again and then she look like
us she looks already pretty much like us
just not not that
obviously more like
40 mom on roof that's at least
25 that's how it is in RPG games if the
mom is on the Roof then you're like 25
minimum that has to mean something yeah
her being on there
M would they like reveal that to me so
early in the
game takes a lot to climb up there yeah
that's a lot of effort if especially if
you don't have magic
anymore she's not pie B's mom I do think
it's a little bit like too easy like it
feels too
easy
yeah yeah the way she kicks her feet is
so cute she's such a little
Savage Savage Berry
is Mama on your roof yes everybody's
mom's is on their roof don't you know
look why don't you never check your roof
check your roof for sake don't
you care about your
mom check your
roof I'm going to read super chats while
staying here because it's nice and cozy
but I'm going to make myself bigger at
least
ha I am which spring are just got to
cover her up then it looks
like it's me the protagonist of the game
I have taken the place of
[Music]
pberry this is my game my screen go away
pberry
[Music]
here
screenshot W I got a new job it's witch
spring R we got to turn it into witch
spring W or
[Music]
k would you look for quo instead of
Pies no
actually I think I'll continue to search
for
pies although quas could be a
[Music]
DLC which bring our ambassador to the
English region self
proclaimed okay I
[Music]
for how while I feeling kind of
tired didn't have a nap today and had to
carry some heavy but my arms don't
feel so jelly anymore they recovered a
little bit throughout the
stream have bad
sleep tonight will will be better for
sure well there's so many tiny super
chats oh my God what's with all the pie
super chats super stickers did you guys
send that before the stream
[Laughter]
started cute I guess got to make use of
the pie stickers if there are
[Music]
some okay super raining
time does time usually fly this much
honestly surprisingly with this game I
feel like time goes by a little bit
slower than usual for
me but I'm enjoying my time so that's
fine does it feel fast for you
[Music]
guys it does feel
slower even though it's not like
it's like slow paced or anything I feel
like it's pretty well paced the game
itself h
although now that you tell me I'm not
even halfway
through that shocks me but uh it still
feels normal paced well paced it's just
longer than I thought and cuz I'm I'm
doing like a lot of uh like sidetracking
too I've
noticed running back to get some
mats but I know it's worth it I get
stronger stream went Zoom I feel the
game is doing a good job but yeah it
doesn't rush
[Music]
anything it was faster for you really
well time is an
individual feeling I
[Music]
suppose players are supposed to GA lots
of mats it feels like it like the ones
that I felt like I had to GA it felt
like I had
to makes sense
huh time is an illusion
time is a social
construct okay are you ready to
[Music]
rumble
h77 tiny
delun unnown Cru
J space water for D
Els thank
[Music]
you
birthday 29th May is my birthday oh
tomorrow for me but now already in Japan
27 years old I'm glad I met Kiana and
spend precious time with you I hope we
continue to have lots of fun times
together sorry for my English no that
was really
[Music]
good my lovely sister
foree
[Music]
birthday
birthday Jones D ghost of mint thank you
for the red super chat finding out
you're starting uh you started playing
wi spring R right when kiwi walks
announced 100K uh copy sold what a
timing thank you for helping spread
brand awareness of such a beautiful game
have fun thank you I'm glad if I can you
know promote it a little bit because
it's a really cute game it seems to have
its own little cult following um but I
didn't know about it at all and that
means to me that a lot of other people
didn't know about it
yet so especially on my channel where we
play a lot of jrpgs I think it's the
right place to promote it a little bit
yeah and they really did a great job I
think cuz it is it is an indie company
right but the game feels so high budget
it's really good
so I don't know I really like it the
only thing really is a few
translation uh grammar mistakes but
that's about it they have like two two
voice overs they have so many NPC's
voice they have beautiful character art
for everything the world is really
pretty the battles are fun like it's a
really good game
[Music]
it's really damp Pack full of things and
really cute and interesting yeah really
I'm glad I gave it a
try because like the Lesser well known
the game is the
lesser the worse it will do as a as a
project on my channel but um like I'm
having a great time and this game
definitely deserves a lot of love
[Music]
so I want to give it the love it's kind
of like with
tunic like in for different different
genre you know but for what it is it was
incredibly incredibly amazing and
underappreciated and not as known as it
should be and I'm giving it the love
that it
deserves feel like I found another gem
yeah underrated Indies yeah
I got to give everyone wish spring R for
Christmas no no no maybe somebody who's
interested in it
but just can't get over it's so cute
right it's got upgraded again why so
cute I want a girly outfit like
[Music]
this and ever since we saw it at the
steam gift stream that's where we saw it
oh and I I think I was like instantly oh
my God I need
[Music]
this well waya might be interested cuz
she seemed a bit interested today
but waya plays long series
to but does she play like jpg like this
I wouldn't really like put Persona into
the same bracket to be honest
tunic is free on ps+ this month hey yo
wow it may be a JPG but like it's not as
cutesy as this I feel like for something
as cutesy as this even if you like RPGs
like it's a big difference for example
this and Final
Fantasy you got to be into the cuteness
and I think waya is into cute stuff
so no she likes stuff more maybe but
cute too I'm sure she
[Music]
does but it's up to you know themselves
if they want to play it or not but
anyway ghost of men thank you and it's
nice to have another person here who
knows the game well seemingly so feel
free to come by
again you want
[Music]
D oh nice thank you Alex D it is 10 pm.
Alex clond
Saloon John EEG
D Cananda t d also from
Cananda this the next huge meme from 10
years excuse
[Music]
me oh because I mentioned the sister
I'm not part of the
system here come the flush
Jets reer Dan Slavic fell Dan ntp Dan
enime kid Dan Alexa Dan you went crazy
today
[Music]
Alex
no froggy waa she thinks she's so strong
but she's such a weakling
she would get eaten by that big ass frog
that we
fought
Al Alex Alex Alex Alex
Alex and another one Alex Danish oh
don't don't marry your mom that's weird
she would probably refuse
anyway flame flyer
flog and space waterful than thank
you yeah we'll find out more soon for
sure if Anna is really the mom or not if
crown is that I I feel
like even the pope or or that Knight
might be or they just go with no dad at
all throughout the whole
story just joint nice hat thank you
we're reading super chat now cuz we
played for 6 hours so feel free to watch
the VOD I would appreciate it very much
and death Rex St are you guys trying to
extend my Super Chat reading
time uh while having my eyes blasted
with dozens of partical effects playing
modered risk of rain 2 at 4 in the
morning sheesh it's time to go to sleep
death Rex how can you even play that
game with those tiny hands h chck monkey
than soon
Cananda Cananda
sounds real to
me hey it doesn't refresh
[Music]
properly there we go map in
a ah yeah world of Final Fantasy well I
think I've seen
that ah yeah wait that's just Kingdom
Hearts wait that looks exactly like
kingdom is that not Kingdom
Hearts what
that's like 100% Kingdom Hearts
[Music]
though it's Pokemon Final Fantasy oh can
you catch and like fight with animals
like
that we mean it's not of course it is
even the logo the Maxima that makes it
it it also kind of looks with the logo
and the picture it looks like Digimon
[Music]
you capture men monsters and fight with
them oh I'm sure it's a great game just
looks like Kingdom Hearts like I mean
come on you can't you can't deny that
that looks very much like Kingdom Hearts
the hairstyle the style the
eyes it's very
[Music]
Disney uh not bad though just looks
exactly like it looks separate to you
the
no
same the what the world of Final Fantasy
dude looks exactly like that what's his
name Sora the guy with the
key looks exactly like even the
direction of the hair is like the
[Music]
same open your eyes
chickens open your eyes
God keep on keep on coping I
guess roxus it's
roxes who
Rox
roxes
roxes is I thought that was the same
person when Rock that's a different
person
[Applause]
that's his
counterpart ah an evil counterpart I
guess he's like more blonde than brown
[Music]
haired so it's complicated oie doie I
think it's just him same person that's
my guess okay moving
onar thanks for the red ofar
[Music]
thank you for extending my Super Chat
reading time so that I can spend more
time with
you
y the D dougle Jones thanks for the
pinky
maybe so clingy my fluffy chickens sappy
Cy oh is that what you're doing now what
no way you're not doing all of that at
once Alexa d
yeah why I wonder why she says your name
all the time HH huh made
[Music]
it strangers of
paradise what the what is that
never heard of it I I I would probably
just enjoy a normal Final
Fantasy it doesn't have to be one of
these Niche
ones M uction Kingdom Hearts I don't
think we're going to be ever able to
play Kingdom Hearts sorry mfin a that's
[Music]
unrealistic I doubt it wait how are my
Stella blade perms looking let me
check also curious about my dualingo
perms Cella blade looking the
same oh do lingo perms get to there all
right dingo has been
[Music]
approved and hold Japan play it
really Kingdom
Hearts which
one let me
check Kingdom Hearts oh I don't even see
it in our
list uh wait no never
[Music]
mind no Grand
Kingdom no no no m
no no at least it's not in the list but
maybe sometimes things are not in our
list and they're still somehow
permitted Japan
[Music]
only that would be weird I don't I don't
know I'm not really interested anyway in
general would be cool if we had perms I
would like think about it
but no perms no think to be done I'm not
going to waste a think I have limited
thinks per
day
uh you
guys I would have already finished yeah
yeah she's into it isn't
she space water for Dan soon one two
three four five Mississippi and motion d
okay I'm done I'm going to go eat my
dinner
[Music]
now
okay thank
you thank
you chicken salad yeah chicken salad
basically not really there's no leaves
in it but it's basically a chicken salad
with noodles motion D YouTube censors
you what the are you that
[Music]
scandalous you eating chicken salad too
a
[Music]
yo
what yeah I'm caught on to supers are
you guys like should I get U behind
again would you prefer
that you stri
D you saw a lion joined for no reason oh
I y
classy Seas line that's like feels like
um that's a Japanese
thing I noticed that with Japan eat he I
think he mentioned that before you see a
line like you see restaurants in Tokyo
with a long line and you just like
decide to stand in it just because
there's already a line you're like m h
they must know they must know that it's
good so I'm going to line up
too I don't know or they just all no
they just all exchange all the good
knowledge cuz when I went to places
where there were lines it usually was
really good but then also places that
have no lines at all are also really
good pretty much
same I'm rarely disappointed in food in
Japan h
[Music]
the line was so huge the tone got the
place well that store that restaurant is
really small and I told you guys to not
go in big groups and you did it
anyway
yeah when I went it was also pretty full
I was kind of Lucky uh we only needed
two seats so we got in relatively fast
but yeah that place is pretty tiny for
how popular it is so yeah you got to
wait a little
bit got to drive so early oh
[Music]
byebye food there is all amazing yeah
even conven nexts yeah
man now it's okay I'm sure my dinner
will be yummy
too orata I have to make orata sometime
I need to do cooking stream anyway at
some point before I go to Japan ideally
because I want to show you guys my k
kitchen I mean I can't like really like
you know show you everything and andh
whoosh the camera around to give you a
big overall look that would go too
far I probably couldn't really show you
much but I want to talk about it anyway
my kitchen is so
sick yeah I just need to think about
what the do I do I you know I have
this really really
amazing uh
e just a a crunchy Leaf salad crunchy uh
cabbage not cabbage the ice back salad
two Cas just a
salad what was I going to say oh yeah so
the one solution to
reflective uh cooking stoves would
be um you know those um like not built
in
uh external cooking store
I see Japanese members use it a lot for
their streams too when they do cooking
streams cuz they can put it next to
their PC I guess um portable
basically um
but I have this really sick uh stove
that I paid a lot of money for it's um a
special one with the sucking of the air
it goes into the middle of the stove
it's it was really
expensive yeah
[Music]
suck the vented ones yeah is is a really
good one and I paid extra to have it
even with the counter evened
out it doesn't stick
out but I've noticed because it's so
smooth and beautiful it gets dirty dir
so fast I have to wipe it after every
time I
cook yeah so it's so reflective though I
have to test it
out otherwise worst case I guess I'll
get one of those portable ones that they
come in like um matte
non-reflective uh form
but I love my kitchen I want to use it
way it
[Music]
is induction stove tops to be like that
but I love it it's so
[Music]
beautiful wear a mask no even then like
you can
see and if I wear a mask then my face
tracking won't work and and
I still I don't think if you see my
reflection with a mask that would not be
preferred from the management just no
reflection reflection at all cuz you can
probably see my eyes really clearly I
took a picture of my own reflection and
I was like yeah
B
B I just have to angle the camera in a
way that it won't catch the reflection I
think and just not get too close but
normally I don't don't like look deep
into the pots or whatever so should be
fine I don't look deep into the pot
because I'm straight
[Music]
edge pix pixelite
pre-recorded it's got to be in
[Music]
stream okay wait you guys sent like two
or free more
yri
Al TR
okay now I go I'm going to I'm going to
teleport
[Music]
okay just like pberry so that I prove to
you that I am
pberry
[Music]
okay now I'm on the roof see me see me
there that's
me bye-bye I in German we
[Music]
say w b no no not the bird
all coefficient waa cosplay stream in 30
minutes
oh interesting
[Music]
yeah you can go watch more Wawa by
watching coefficient same
[Music]
thing oh wait he does have a a YouTube
reservation I thought it would be
Twitter Hey does he always stream on
YouTube I thought it was at Twitter I
mean
twitch that's
tomorrow
what I it says 24
hours ah he changed it he chickened
[Music]
out all right bye