questions
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
uh bonjour
hello everybody
Welcome to it's been a while
welcome to uh snack World worldwide
International snack Box review so
so why I'm so loud
[Music]
uh
um
a boy
[Music]
okay okay
yes I am Madame thank you
hello I have a beautiful uh Beret I have
which is made by elmy the baguette as
well all the baguettes many baguettes
the uh mustache I think was from Skye
and the little scarf is by yours truly
[Music]
more
yes
yeah you like it
thank you sir no not yet excellent
excellent pardon
very fasting oh thank you I think today
we can make fetch a thing
magnafique
[Music]
writing that down for another one
apparently Kiki in French is kokoriko
oh I see him
very distinguished mustache oh thank you
it's
I can use this mustache from my Mario's
dreams as well
but I actually I really love Berets in
general so it's my [\h__\h] pleasure to
wear this one
um
[Music]
pardon my French
my my stash is
what do you mean it's behind it's
perfect the way it is the problem is if
I want to move it now uh
it's hard to reach right now
it's complicated I will have to re-align
everything that is above that layer
which means I have to realign my scarf
and my and my bucket and I'm not in the
mood for that
yeah it's okay in the way it is
so oh [\h__\h] I forgot my water oh well I
have some tea no that should get I
forgot I forgot let me let me fetch you
know these snack boxes they usually come
with a drink and the drink that came
with this one I left it in the fridge
oh oh
[Music]
um
huh
[Music]
Allah voila that's French too right
that's French right well that's French
you know in my head I mixed a lot of
Italian and French words so I have to
think twice of Thrice or Force the force
shall be with you okay I got my drink
um and the tea and like a few drops of
water
so uh
yeah okay
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
come over
how you doing ah it's just Sava I heard
that one before and I know Japanese idol
group that I know they once released a
song that's called saba and they keep on
singing
or is it Java
Zava
that's a short way of saying how are you
I suppose all right guys all right all
right all right we are once again doing
the snack Box review and to all of your
surprise this is not the snack box
unfortunately I would be happy with that
many many bucket
uh but no no no no my dear my dear view
is from everywhere especially my beloved
French people
um it's my pleasure to have you thank
you for being here today I'm sure
there's also some people who don't watch
me regularly right
right
well well well I'm
in the same time zone you should be
watching me more often mm-hmm
but anyway
screen please uh bring down that's crazy
yes
birthday
Simple Plan
[Music]
magnetic okay
ah
this is a French Learning stream now
I'm scared oh there it is
voila oh
voila
excellent okay
don't I look
I look Flawless now today huh
I'm so happy with what I look like I
feel like oh my god I've never looked
better before and yes white gloves yes
[Music]
I need better gloves that don't make my
fingers look so
sausage
[Music]
I don't have sausage fingers to be true
okay
just letting you know also this is
birthday merchandise beautiful birthday
merchandise for my first birthday
yes
so
sweet
oh
where are we going today everybody where
are we going we're going to a party or
France
I have been to Paris Paris before yeah a
couple times
um but it wasn't until last year uh I
reported about this in a stream so if
you missed it you have to watch it oh
but last year was the first time where I
really like properly went sightseeing in
Paris
um
and it was really really nice before
that I just went for Japan Expo and it
was like I was I was in Paris but not
really like I was kind of on the
outskirts of Paris because for the
people who know they know Japan Expo it
might be officially in Paris but it's
like really on the outskirts
and yeah it takes a long time to get
back into the city
um so I never really took the
opportunity back then yeah Philippines
uh yes I was there twice
wow how was it this year
how was it this year
I wonder I wonder if I should have gone
it was very full well it always is isn't
it the cool thing about Japan Expo is if
you're into that kind of stuff it's not
only all about anime and stuff like that
there is also like pretty empty when I
was there pretty empty Halls where
um there's like more like normal stuff
uh that has to do with with Japan like
like novels and like it's like when I
was there it was in different halls and
it was like like as if I was in a
different event because those Halls were
like so much more empty than the main
hallway all the cosplayers were and the
anime blue blood blue
um
I don't know maybe it's not it's like
that anymore but it seemed like the
really unpopular area but there were a
lot of like
um yeah I don't know like I don't know
just not like anime kind of content
stuff was there
um
yeah yeah yeah but when I was there oh
my God I heard they had the best [\h__\h]
guests ever because they brought in
Japanese Idols like um ladies colorful
and cute and then in in later years even
though I wasn't the fan they they
brought in
um not akb48 what was it again 46 and I
met them
hmm I met like I was oh man I think I
told this story before did I I was um
sitting
somewhere alone
in in the venue did I ever tell the
story
I'll tell him again in any case seems
like not everybody knows it so I was
sitting I was sitting in um in the venue
somewhere in the hall where many people
were passing through one of the main
halls and that was just I don't know I
was alone I had I don't know I guess I
didn't really have any friends or many
friends that were there like some
acquaintances but in that moment I was
alone and I was kind of like sad I
remember so I was sitting
in
Perhaps Perhaps Perhaps dressed up maybe
I mean it's in Japan Expo maybe who
knows uh somewhere okay on the one
against the wall and then I was just you
know being my Coco broken espresso
depresso kind of self
um I was also much younger at that
moment and then suddenly
I see it a group of girls Japanese girls
in school uniforms
on the way passing through the hallway
where I was sitting in but with a camera
team
and
I was like oh yo these are not normal
people these are not cosplayers I know
these girls I know them I know them
[Laughter]
[Music]
when I say I'm not a fan the thing is um
you know the the Iowa groups that I'm a
fan or was a fan of
were big rivals of those Idols you know
AKB 48 groups versus hello project
groups and I was born the whole project
sign way more so anyway but they were
coming up to me and
um the the main girl that was back in
this that was in the center back then
the the most popular girl
and a couple of other girls from the
group they were like looking at me and
waving at me and then I was like okay I
I waved back and I'm like oh I know you
girls and they're like what really you
know us they were like really surprised
about it
and I'm like oh
[\h__\h] what am I getting myself I'm
getting myself into a conversation why
am I doing this I'm not even
so
direct all their attention at me the
whole group looking at me circling
around me me the small little girl in in
the corner being sad about them being
alone
and there they start talking to me and I
tell them
a story of why I know them
uh-huh
all right let's let's tell the story
because it's interesting
[Music]
um
back in the day I really wanted to be an
idol you know because she loved Idols so
much
um she wanted to join in hello project
ideally oh but it was was not was not
was not possible
[Music]
b48 group and kiwama things interesting
don't like it could be but
maybe I try to audition so I fill out my
audition form online at this point I was
living in Austria you know but I wrote
down
uh yes hello
um I I want to be an idol I'm a big fan
of hello project which I know are your
Rivals but I think that is especially
that exactly is the reason why
you would want me
[Laughter]
and I'm not a fan of your company is
exactly exactly the reason why you want
me listen to me
I think my my reasoning what I wrote
down was something along the lines of
this feeling of
um
what is it
rivalry or so
is is
um
is a strength and I'm very motivated and
I want to
um you know be number one top Idol so
please please please take me
I don't know I don't quite remember that
well anymore but it was at least I was
not sucking up to them you know I was a
complete opposite I didn't say I like
you guys I'm a fan so please let me
Joanna said no I don't actually like you
I like the other company but but
um well I just really really want to be
an island and you know I think I could
bring a lot of good stuff to you uh very
talented skillful yes yes yes yes yes
anyway so I filled that out and I sent
it in
and I passed
I passed but
I never went to the
second audition partially because I was
not interested probably maybe and the
other reason was because I kind of like
lost interest I was like I know actually
I don't really wanna I mean this is I
don't like this company
I don't like I want to join Hello
friends
so I didn't answer anymore after I got
the answer from him so I told the girls
that story I said I passed the audition
for the group that you're in right now
but then I didn't go
[Laughter]
um
they probably thought I was a fan I
couldn't like straight up tell them
directly in their face that I don't
actually like them and I don't actually
listen to the music
I didn't say that they probably thought
I was a fan I'm so sorry
uh wanna Flex hmm
I mean it wasn't really supposed to be a
flag but they were really excited to
talk to me yeah
it's a crazy story huh yeah yeah
well anyway I mean the girls are cute
okay I just I when in terms of music I
used to prefer hella project nowadays I
don't listen to Hell project either to
be honest oh well anyway so we a puppy
that happened at Japan Expo yeah
so first of all I got a big sorry note
saying that this was supposed to be the
June box and sorry for
you know not making moves
but it's it's partially their fault and
partially my fault so we're not
completely
um I I think I think it's part it could
be partially my fault so I'm not I'm not
not blaming them or so at least it's
here
like it um
I think yeah it arrived once at my place
already delayed uh but at that time I
was in August in Korea so at that point
it was obviously already too late right
and then when I arrived back home they
already sent it back
so then they were kind enough to send it
back to me
so all is good
but yeah um to start it off with let's
do it as we usually do
okay at the top it says bonjour
oh
interesting okay now that's kind of
spoiled but let's let's look at this
here there's this stuff okay
in German
Paris is the capital French is the
language uh people live in French
accumulate to
67 million people
um they use Euro and typical French they
say is baguette
lavender oh love lavender
Eiffel Tower macadon and wine oh
I have had all of these before I've had
baguette before I'm using the lavender
uh every once in a while for all kinds
of things
I've been to the Eiffel Tower I've been
to the top
very scary I've eaten many macarons and
I've tasted wine before but I hate wine
so that's really unfortunate
um
I want to visit the south of France
someday which is really beautiful when I
went to Paris but it was really nice a
joke before I know
so
okay next page it says
France is not only
the biggest country in Europe but also
an important
hmm what does this mean
which I think means something like a
country that produces a lot of things
yeah two-thirds of the country I'm I'm
translating this as I'm reading it in
German so please bear with me two-thirds
of the country are being used land via
chaplage uh agricultural I think
in the south is the province with its
big Lavender Fields mm-hmm
yeah for perfumes and stuff mm-hmm
oh oh the center of the French perfume
uh uh
um construction no what's the word
creation uh I can't find the word
project production
um is the city
I don't know how to say it
in France there are many Specialties for
example the famous fish soup
boiler brass I don't know how to say it
bread and more bread and baked goods and
cheese
French people take a lot of time to eat
so uh sometimes it takes over two hours
it says well that's normal though I feel
like
but here is a funny fun fact
people have not even
oh oh [\h__\h] we're gonna get into a fight
here oh oh oh oh can I say oh oh dear oh
no
France France please don't kill me this
is what it states here they say French
people haven't even come up with the
cool song the ones who invented it were
uh the V Viennese in Austria
I'm sorry that's what they say oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] this is probably another one of
those discussions
[Laughter]
you know it oh my God We're not gonna
have a fight over it let's go but there
was another thing
another thing where
I think Austria is like we made it but
then uh I think other people say no
turkey came up with it or so I'm not
sure what that was about I forgot
I forgot what that was about but you
know we in Europe we have a lot of
fights about that
maybe that was the coastal
we might have invented it but we
perfected it
I just have to say
you can get great croissants in Austria
and you can get marvelous
in France honestly when it comes to
bread and baked goods I think all over
Europe you can get good stuff while when
I leave Europe I have troubles finding a
good course off often so yeah was that
coffee I I have a feeling that was
coffee yeah
but in general there's probably many
such things yeah all right
um then there's a page where they uh
wants to explore
France number one Paris
yeah yeah yeah of course
not only the one of the most important
big cities in Europe but also the
capital Paris belongs to the cities that
you can easily get get to with a train
so for example from Germany Munich you
take a train and take seven hours okay
who the [\h__\h] takes the train for that
long nowadays
um people who like museums should go to
the Louvre a fashionista should go to uh
shops boutiques and [\h__\h]
yes and then chill at a cafe blah blah
blah blah the other cities they
mentioned are bulldog
do you see this are you seeing this [\h__\h]
campy
I won't focus Province and Marcel
or something like that I'm not gonna
read all of that because I want to get
started I've already touched it it's
already half an hour
so we're gonna get started let's see how
disappointing this one will be or if it
will be decent
um first of all if this is your first
snack Box review stream
please do not get your hopes up my dear
French people there is a high chance
that these are not very much
representative of the snacks in your
country okay
but don't don't take it like you know
let me change the position of my uh
camera there we go and we're gonna get
started with a drink
okay
also let me take a sip from my tea if
it's ready to drink
yeah just don't expect too much and then
you're good so first of all
right
so what could oh I probably sound
distance sorry I have to turn away from
the microphone what could the drink that
they sent for me be
um no they don't send alcohol so it
can't be oh the camera stopped
can't be alone
it can't be wine why
probably moved something a tiny bit and
then it's like no
no no Dad you suck
[Music]
let me try the
fix it
grape juice
bucket juice non-alcoholic wine no they
normally don't do that either
oh
I did oh there it is oh
do you see my hands because I don't see
it
it activated itself again but
there
all right of course you're done
um
[Music]
why it was working until a second ago
and then I moved my tea and suddenly
it's not working
this is so annoying
okay hurry re redids the thing
plugged it back in again
come on you can do it camera
oh
[Music]
try to
change the outlet if it reaches no that
doesn't look like
it won't reach
one one minute
what was that oh
I heard Windows oh ah what do you mean
[Music]
it's not recognize
please windows don't be such a [\h__\h]
why
did you [\h__\h] sometimes it was just
wearing it
oh does not recognize why you were just
recognizing it a second ago
why are you so weird
how about this one you recognize it now
oh it's it's a
it should be working now no
well it's weird because you know I have
the camera attached to one of those USB
um Outlets like like but that one is
also attached to a USB outlet so it's
like a more like a splitter
and that one seems to be working because
it's lighting up it's lighting up it
worked before
give me a second here
maybe if I switch
laughs
no
I have many USB hubs so many yes
[Music]
um
no no no no no no no I don't know what
it is
[Music]
hey what couldn't be I'm reconnecting in
a different Hub again
but see when I when I reconnect and
disconnect on the extra Hub it doesn't
make those windows sounds ah
probably reactivated because this cable
on the top is new I moved that but then
immediately it stopped
so this is basically a freeze frozen
screen
hello
[Music]
it's frozen
come back
I'm changing some settings
hoping it will do something
[Music]
I'm a raccoon hello VOD launchers please
please skip this
I don't know how much you have to skip
but a little bit at least
ah
how stressful
directly yeah when I want to plug it
directly it's too short
that's why I have it on the Hub
okay
how
how why
why why why why
dude
reconnecting again
[Music]
I hope
why why are you such a [\h__\h] it's not
like this camera is so old or did that
much with it wow
I didn't use it so much that the USB
cable would suddenly be broken makes no
sense
ah
if you drop the baguette you can use
your hands instead of fixing your feet
I what if my feet are also just hands
[Music]
at least the music is nice I wanna do my
French things review
let me do it worst case I just take
pictures of everything but it's nicer
with the camera
also it finds the device
in OBS it's there if it wouldn't like
recognize it it wouldn't be even showing
it but right now it's showing it
it's just being a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] about it
[Music]
one more time reconnecting
hello
okay reconnecting this here again
look The Hub
hub goes here how about now how you like
that you don't like that huh you don't
like to be on the 3.0
but you wear the three point s too
before
and you worked
can I put you back on the 2.0 you don't
like the 2.0 yeah you do seem to like to
2.0
[Music]
okay okay I will
carefully move my computer while it's on
so hopefully reach
PC
let's go hey boo
yeah sweetie
how far oh this will be tough
let's see let's move move move
more more careful okay all good all good
is it okay to move a PC while it's on
I'm just like pushing it though
okay
ah wait that was three points now
no man whatever both are weird
okay connecting
connecting to the PC directly
nothing happens
oh
[\h__\h] I swear to God nothing makes
any sense at all nothing sometimes it
works sometimes it doesn't it's always
the same with this [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay
okay let's try not to move anything
anymore
sorry for the wait
[Music]
okay stop the drink
is Seven Up
Citron vert
and Mente Mentos
mojito
have you ever drank this before guys why
I don't think seven Up is French
but also mojito is mojito French I don't
think it's bread
that doesn't seem very French
[Music]
right
hahaha
no it's seven of friends hey mojito is
Cuban
that's not very French
not very French of you
okay nothing about this is French but it
might just be a special version of 7Up
that only
um really exists in France because this
is also the thing of these items often
there's Limited Editions
that are only from specific countries so
opening up come on yeah
I have never drunken drunk a Mojito
before
[Music]
oh salute
oh
[Music]
a yummy
oh that's really good of course it's
good without without alcohol of course
it's good
um yeah I can imagine I could already
imagine before and then this one would
be good
hold up thumb oh
ah what's that that thing in in the
Mojito
the the green leaf thingy
what's that again
because that oh it's really
it's really coming through mint oh yeah
mint it's really coming through
damn this is good very good stuff
um
like it's like a
the main taste is still
like uh
lemon
lime kind of taste but then in the back
you will get a a big hint
of
mint yes very good
um
definitely something
or like definitely a
a
drink dead
I have rarely tasted before
so that's something new and exciting all
right now let's start with some snacks
let me check the expiration date
okay it's uh uh January 2023 I think so
all is good
we have
Oreos
which are probably also not French but
it's okay this this specific version of
it might be French or you can even see
my camera in the reflection
it's a marshmallow
filling with like soft pie uh
surroundings and covered in a layer of
chocolate
which is an Oreo that I've never seen
anywhere before we never saw this
oh no oh yes I am a camera sounds like
diabetes
yes
a little little chocolate pie with Oreo
flavor and marshmallow filling
you have those in an a
h
those those
let's give it a secret okay
let's not make a big deal out of it uh
I'm having troubles opening up this
thing oh there we go
[Music]
oh yeah it looks looks proper
and I'm gonna dig into this
ah
[Music]
so hmm
I don't really taste much of the Oreo
it's just any kind of chocolate
not the best chocolate though
um
at the marshmallow like when you bite
into it in the middle you
you meet something that's like
marshmallowy indeed
I'm not a big fan of marshmallows but in
combination with like a
pie texture like this and chocolate is
fine
yeah yeah okay uh I'll take another bite
otherwise I don't know what to to rate
this one
hmm
uh-huh
the marshmallow gives you this
bounciness when you when you bite inside
um
that's pretty good
all right I will give this
um
it looks like chocolate pie but the
middle is marshmallow
I don't give this
uh
what should I give this
5 out of ten we're not starting good
today I'm not impressed
it's not bad but I'm not impressed and
I'm I'm I'm I guess in a mean mood today
okay we got a Cheesy snack
what could this be
[Music]
Berlin
did I say all right I wonder
this is with a cheese called emmental we
have that one indeed amentala
I like that cheese that's the yummy
cheese
so this is oh with corn corn and cheese
all right this is France oh you guys
know these ones
yeah yeah finally the first thing that
you guys really recognize
oh okay I I've said this many times
before in these streams
um I'm not a huge fan kind of like
cheese snacks but I do like cheese in
general I don't dislike it but when it
comes to snacks that are like solely
focused on Being Cheesy it's not my
favorite thing but these should be good
okay
so I open
not too much open
so these are like little warming wormy
things ah you're still there
you want one you like cheese
let's give this a try
ah
um
okay they taste like these cheese balls
that everybody probably has tasted
before
I'm your bgm let's go
I missed cheese what you can have cheese
everywhere
did cheese leave you alone yes homage
you can leave cheese everywhere I mean
okay the best cheese maybe is in Europe
but diet and what did
you want to talk
if you miss it you should give up on
other things that make you
more puffy than this one
cheese cheese is good okay
how can it be bad
it's just milk
old milk old milk solidified
what you can't eat bread even what the
[\h__\h]
I can't get this streaming right now
you're seeing bucket and cheese baguette
and fromage
and you can you look at it and you're
probably crying oh no oh no take it away
from Cali
okay the bread I mean I guess I
understand because
well I don't I mean I've heard that
bread can be bad for
you know the figure
I haven't heard it before about cheese
though
but I trust you
I guess yeah bread is carbs
uh low fat aha low carbs low fat okay
there's so many diets out there I don't
know
anything about these kind of things I
don't know what is what and what does
what what has what effect and what's bad
for your body
um
ah well maybe maybe
has a cheat day coming up and she can
cheat on that one day and eat match much
much much cheese
we're looking forward to that day so I
will get this a
pretend
we're good
very good cheese snack
absolutely no problem with it it's yummy
yeah that's good I'll probably eat a
couple more of those
[Music]
okay
next door
I'm gonna go faster now oh my God
what's gonna say I'm going fast because
I already tags with it so much but look
at this
there's a roasted chicken on there
oh there's a French flag on it too so
this must be uh French chips yeah
uh pulley
so I'm guessing this is
um roasted chicken chips
foreign
chips
I like those too I like all kinds of
chips though but normally when I go get
myself some chips
I usually go for
um just simple salt flavor chips I know
that's I guess boring but
yeah I I just always feel like I I like
to just go for something simple not too
overwhelming
and a safe choice
best oh thank you same oh really
oh so it's a pretty small bag there's
not much inside really it really looks
like barely anything but it's a small
bag to begin with it's just um how many
grams is this
25 gram that's tiny
25 gram is like nothing wow
okay so a chip ah
oh wow
[Music]
whoa
that tastes like
you know the best part of a roasted
chicken is the skin
it tastes exactly like the skin
shop
foreign
that's yeah it is really good wow
what what it's not really what I am
um desire in potato chips but the flavor
is on point
um
wow
damn
oh wow okay that's pretty good holy [\h__\h]
wow
roasted chicken for dinner
and this is
I mean The Taste is on the point but
it's very strong too
and it makes you want to eat a real
roasted chicken it makes you wonder why
the [\h__\h] am I eating chips and not real
roasted chicken
it makes you question your life choices
it's like you you're coping this is your
copium for not being able to eat a real
proper roast chicken
I'll give it a
8 out of ten because it makes me
question my life choices
okay
let me sip my Seven Up
oh I should also drink my tea before it
gets cold never mind
[Music]
but thankfully my tea is in the minute
cup so it
um stays warmer longer
um
[Music]
see I can finally show you I never
showed you before I think
[Music]
it is it's like firmness inside
yeah yeah it's like Sakura design from
Starbucks yeah
I got two of those from Nana too before
um
foreign
and
it is fine okay what about this one the
new one that I'm picking up
oh [\h__\h] expiration date Halloween
2022.
oh yeah
this is something sweet what do we have
next seems like something that you guys
would know if you're from France
[Music]
the original
two of those apparently
pretending yeah
so it says here foreign
[Music]
I can't read French I'm so sorry I don't
know how to pronounced words
I love these very good good snack oh
oh there's a strawberry version is there
but these are just this is chocolate at
the end it seems like a like a cake with
some sprinkles
wow oh good good Focus good job camera
[Music]
let's eat this
look
if I could open it but I'm having issues
oh done
[Music]
okay they're they're packaged
separately
and then you get like one of these
uh-huh
I'm curious
uh how how well they
um
have gotten through the travel
because they they have been delivered
twice
but okay looks fine so far so you open
it and you see oh there's some sprinkles
on the bottom
oh it looks it looks exactly like the
package
[Music]
beautiful
looks exactly like the packaging so it's
not
not like um lifting your expectations
and then disappointing you like many
many other snacks do
I like that I like what it's true to his
packaging often
anything like that okay I'm digging in
looks very spongy yeah indeed
[Music]
um
yeah it's good oh
[Music]
uh-huh
yeah I can see myself like
just buying this next time when I go to
France when I need a little snack
um
foreign
[Music]
it's a bit simple The Taste is a bit
simple but the sponge like it doesn't
all of this I would have expected it to
taste a little bit more artificial but
it doesn't
so the chocolate is also
pretty good but not overwhelming
no no I won't give
[Music]
out of 10.
eight out of 10.
yes I'm I'm back to being nice
yeah yeah wow approved
it's a good writing good rating
oh
oh can we try something now that I can
put it back into the refrigerator the
following thing was not in the snack box
however it was a gift that my best
friend gave to me when she uh was in
France
oh recently
and I have not had the chance to eat it
yet but it's something special that's
not part of the snack box and I was like
wait a second French feelings now I have
something in the fridge don't I
um
she gifted me
um jam
uh which I I'm not gonna taste test here
because it's uh just a raspberry jam
which I know what it tastes like
but the other thing I haven't tried yet
it's a focus
huh huh hello
the other thing is
um a cream that's kind of like a jam I
guess from
my my Maroney
[Music]
uh uh
it's from France
special special thing so at your
Chestnut how how would you guys eat this
on bread because is it like a is it like
a bread spread or do you put it on
Crepes or so
where would you how would you eat it
is it like Nutella but a bit more nutty
Maybe
it's like Nutella oh it's pretty small I
will be done with that immediately if I
eat that on bread crabs too ah perfect
recently I'm eating breakfast crepes
every day
so maybe tomorrow I can put it on my
crap but I wanted to take like a little
spoon now to taste it
oh
good that I have a spoon
from my teeth and I have never
eaten chestnuts before chestnuts are
really um popular here in Austria two in
the winter there's like vendors outside
um that sell fresh roasted chestnuts
Maroney
well I've never tried them before I like
almonds and all that but I've never
tried chestnuts before
because I'm worried that I wouldn't like
them
so I
I chestnuts are supposed to taste like
this
is
[Music]
nice
better than almonds well I mean that
isn't that like
an individual kind of thing
well okay let's try that so this will
probably make a nice plop sand so I put
it to the microphone I'll bring it to
the microphone
let me turn take off my my glove at
least one of them
should make a nice pop sound ah
I want to take off the other glove
if I need a grip okay don't judge me
[Music]
sometimes you have to smack it a little
bit
against something hard for surface
pull up excuse me it's not pop it's plop
okay p-l-o-p that sound was obviously a
plop
can you guys not differentiate
it was a plot not a pop
very different
all right okay plop yes so
this is what it looks like what it's so
shiny
oh shiny shiny
mm-hmm
I'm not sure about the smell it's very
mild I and I don't know what this is
supposed to be
let's see I'll take a a little Spoonful
oh it's like gel jelly the consistency
is like texture is like jelly
uh
[Music]
uh-huh
oh it's like a sweet it has a sweet
nutty taste
sweet and nutty
maybe tomorrow it's right on the crap
yeah
it's not bad
I don't like it as much as almonds but
or pistachios or so but it was yummy
not bad maybe in this winter I can try
some real roasted fresh
Mahoney chestnuts
okay that was
a little extra that wasn't in the snack
box let's go back to the snack box
okay next stop
next we have
okay next we have some some sugary jelly
is there a baguette no
it's right in front of me
the bucket I see I'm cuddling what's up
again
oh we we bug it oh we we
sorry I'm getting a little bit
Intoxicated by the baguette but no in
these snack boxes they they can't put in
stuff like that that's like too fresh it
will die in the snack box before it
arrives at my place but we're gonna eat
this now
crocodiles
jelly crocodiles from a brand called
Finney
that seems like it could be a a French
company because I've never seen this
brand before this company
uh investigators ah it's cheap as hell
oh well I mean
I mean
don't hate on it
it's maybe not well known but that's
okay the other things
things the things you don't know when
things you know and yeah it doesn't mean
it's bad yeah
yeah another jelly snacks I feel like
they're generally very
um cheap always
low cost French brand not too funny
Maybe
[Music]
um
the smell is
oh
trivia tilapia smells good
here you see them you see them there and
there whoa
whoa
Peak peekaboo
let me try one I'll go for the orange
one
oh it's a cute little crocodile oh it's
so glowy ah
oh oh this one tastes like orange juice
oh
no it tastes not like orange juice it
tastes like
[Music]
um
not orange but
no
Tangerine Tangerine tangerines
tangerines
clementines yeah
hmm
oh very yummy it's not really sour even
though it looks sour
at all actually
mmm
yeah it's really yummy
I like these
hmm
[Music]
um
I will give them
eight out of ten
oh
I don't think I normally rate um
jelly snacks that highly
but this one I like
oh
I'm gonna try the other colors all right
which one should I try there's a blue
one a green one a red one
and the orange one and I think there's a
it's not the same I think it's also a
yellow one but yeah the blue one looks
interesting
like green could be apple red could be a
strawberry but for blue I'm like what
the hell is blue maybe blueberry
balloon
ah
you like my mustache thank you
[Music]
oh oh it's a berry took me a while to
figure out what it is but
there's some kind of berry
um
we're good
I don't know which Berry definitely not
a strawberry though
[Music]
very good
yeah
um
[Music]
stuff is here
my hellofresh stuff just arrived oh
all right okay this is French this is
fledge
next up we have
made it yeah
[Music]
the classic the good old the typical
very simple but yummy
like a
um it's kind of like a cake without
anything on it
just the biscuit
texture of a simple
simple and soft
cake
oh this brand apparently is also very
well known and well love it
someone said it's a really good one
good only the best for takanashi kiwawa
now we're talking all right all right
I think he would ring again they want me
to open the [\h__\h] boat why BRB
BRB normally let's just leave it there
[Music]
foreign
okay
was because they couldn't get in but
I think when they are up then they
shouldn't be needing to
bring again
or they might ring again but they might
not need me to open up wait where did I
leave my
my gloves
let's keep it
an ear open in case
in case they have a fresh Deliverance
rings the bell again
looking at the bread
it's so gorgeous
BRB
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
might
um have to get up one more time
depends I'm back again I'm back again
all right let's eat these
um um
[Music]
okay it sounds kind of similar to the
German pronunciation what's the English
pronunciation madelines madelines
Madeleine okay Madeline okay that helps
me a lot thank you all the different
pronunciations of these words
I'm very confusing in my brain
getting good exercise
yeah yeah I've been doing some stuff
today I also cleaned vacuum cleaned my
whole apartment is quite a lot of square
meters so
it's quite exhausting actually
having to vacuum clean the whole
apartment
um
good okay
just I mean no that should be fine I
shouldn't need to open up anymore
just leave it in front of the [\h__\h]
door
ah
[Music]
okay it's Madeline time
just putting back my putting back mine
gloves by the way did I put them on the
wrong way no
no no no no
no no no
[Music]
wait wait okay got it let's see
very good pronunciation
[Music]
you're lying anyway we opened it up and
are they again separately past the
package or
oh no wait oh God what's the respiration
date
let me just check because this makes me
worry
what is the expiration date
where is it
[Music]
oh
these are expired
for 10 days
if it was chocolate I would still eat it
but I don't know about this kind of
stuff
is the the first of October
I mean they look normal
and there there's eggs right I don't
know that's where they eat it
smell is I think okay
there's a lot of sugar on them
10 days is nothing 10 days not a big
deal okay okay okay I'll eat it if I'm
sick tomorrow well it's my day off
tomorrow so I guess it doesn't matter
let's go expired Madeleine
it's beautiful the shape is beautiful
I've only eaten the ones that are like
shaped like an eye kind of
okay itadakimasu oh
yummy
remember good
bon appetit
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum
very good
they taste like as if I just bought them
from
the bakery I don't know
[Music]
um
I give this
dead
foreign
[Music]
I wonder how it would be to combine
the
chestnut spread with the madeleines but
I think typically you would just eat the
mudlands plainly right without anything
additionally is it a crime is it a crime
to eat them with something
try it is it not a crime
I wanna hear from the God no where where
are the French people
are they saying it's okay
[Laughter]
no that would be absolutely delicious I
know that
I eat them with milk oh you dip them
into milk
it's okay
where do I I need to put this somewhere
here
I need to open it up again okay
let's try
I feel like there's cat hairs on this
from the from the glove so [\h__\h]
I only take a small bite because the the
back is definitely of cat hair is
infested
um okay Flavor Boost I don't know about
that so I'm pudding
a tiny bit of the chestnut spread
on here
arranging my mudlin
ah
mm-hmm
I mean why not
perfectly fine
this is perfectly fine yeah
and there's no surprise either like it
tastes like these two separate things
are coming together
no no particularly surprising taste
isn't it
um
do you know now
20 to 10 I guess so no way then it would
be 18 out of 10 or so no how much did I
give the the the the spread how much did
I give that
yeah a plus b is a b
that's exactly it
oh yeah my my combination choices this
this wasn't too weird I think
wasn't too weird
um
ah okay next stop
I'm glad we had something really classic
like obviously you can't really put in
cheese or baguette or so or croissant
whatever macaron's also difficult
because Michael wants me to be chilled
and cooled um so you obviously can't put
that in a snack box like this
so I'm glad we still were able to have
something that's very typical yeah
but I've had macarons before so I even
from France directly so I don't need to
test them to know how they taste I
for macarons it really depends how I
would rate them depending on which
flavor I think that's the same for
everyone like the flavor
can be so different
really really good ones I like
strawberry I like vanilla like pistachio
I like chocolate
many many actually my friends who
brought me the the spread she also
brought me some fresh macarons from
France as well
so the two spreads so the jam and the
chestnuts spread and the macarons and oh
those macarons are really good really
yummy and she brought them from one of
those famous stores that they have in
Paris I don't know which one I don't
remember but it was a famous store
where everyone buys oh yeah I think that
one actually I think I've been to
Switzerland before and I think I went to
LA durre in Switzerland as well
I think I feel like I did I feel like
that was the same place
if that exists in Switzerland I might be
wrong I don't know but I feel like it
was the same
yeah most famous macaron's door yeah
yeah yeah
sorry I always say in Japanese
pronunciation I don't really know what
is actually pronounced like let me look
it up my God
macaron
macaroon
it's pretty similar
you get what I'm saying
what is it in English
macaroon macaroon no thank you I say
McDonald's
and next up
surprisingly I didn't know Pokemon was
French
is at least the company behind it French
foreign
[Laughter]
French I would say and it's just a
collaboration they have
probably it's um yeah just some soft
jelly kind of stuff
yeah
I kind of don't want to open these I
feel like
I don't wait inside is like this
oh the shapes are
shapes like one of them is that's a
thunder I don't know about the others I
I know he don't want to open these I
want to give it to someone
[Music]
I want to look at the other ones but
I kind of don't want to open them
I feel like okay there's a there's a
relaxer that's what we call it in
in German
I think that's okay if I don't open this
I feel like I'm gonna just waste it I'm
not gonna eat all of it immediately so
then they're gonna get hard and stiff
and then I wasted them I prefer to just
eat it either at some point later or or
I give it to a friend maybe because it's
something special as Pokemon
is it okay
I want yeah I mean yeah it probably just
tastes like all the other jelly
things
yeah those really don't taste different
depending on the country I can imagine
what this tastes like you guys can
probably imagine too but the shapes are
the shapes are special the only ones I
can make out is the Pikachu and the
Thunder but I wonder I wonder what this
red one is maybe a Pokeball
but it's the back side well if I ever
get to open it I will tell you guys the
exploration is fine and so one more year
over a year
pop oh maybe it's Jigglypuff oh curious
France loves Pokemon because Pokemon is
French
no no no I guess not okay what is this
you [\h__\h] with me now this is
not from
[Music]
this is not this is not from France
that's it
what
um what I have to mention I guess is
somewhere in there
they said
um
there's one surprise product in the Box
to apologize for the delay so maybe this
is it I don't know what maybe
whatever is not on the official list
there isn't there is an official list oh
no this is this is in there this is
supposed to be in there I guess okay I
wonder which one is the surprise gift
um the Pokemon is also on the list the
drink the mudlin the crocodiles chicken
the nail polish and everything so far
oh I don't maybe they forgot my special
gift
no no wait maybe it's the Oreo
right it might be the Oreo
I don't see it on here
it's the Oreo
it seems to be the Oreo that's why
everybody was like ah this is not
particularly French
okay next we have
this snap and Crackle
I was confused because all of the
packaging on top is English but I guess
I saw some French
Maybe
but is this really
a French thing
it doesn't really look like it belongs
into this box even though this looks
like a different country country's flag
it's not French huh
yeah I don't I don't know but
it says in the back made in the UK
[Laughter]
yeah in
okay this this is from the UK guys
what is going on see this is why I
canceled my snack box subscription this
is one of the last boxes I got
it's not very French at all is it
how did this one sneak in I don't know I
thought maybe this would be the the
surprise gift because
it doesn't seem like it belongs in here
but it's it is like
right there
on the official list
explain yourself
so it says snap and crackle am I
supposed to
snap it
snapping snapping
[Music]
okay what what is this it's like weird
and I'm sticky
uh-huh
[Music]
um
the texture is like
my worms that's at least the name for
the product that we have here
The Taste is
I don't know what that is
it's not bad though
um
[Music]
it's so sticky
I know this I guess it's pretty good
um
[Music]
but the more I eat of it the more it
tastes like mallames
yeah
mm-hmm
but
my throat
[Music]
um
it's yummy
it's very very sweet tasting very sugary
um
problem with this one
honestly honestly I give it a
an 8 out of 10. surprisingly even though
I didn't I know I didn't sound so
impressed but
okay seven out of ten never mind it's
not so special but it's not bad it's
actually actually pretty good I like the
taste the more I eat of it the more I
like to taste
foreign
out of ten not very French though not
very French at all
[Music]
we have two more things
okay
the next thing also does not look very
French to me but maybe you guys will
tell me otherwise maybe you tell me that
this is the national snack in France and
Everybody Eats every morning
crunch
from Nestle
is this French yes yes
oh
okay
I mean the company Nestle is not French
but but but this thing apparently is
very popular in France
finally
Hallelujah
yeah
and the expiration date is fine
okay all right so it's like a like a
waiver wait wait wait waivers with some
puffy rice covered in chocolate
so the bottom is like this and the top
is like these
all right
itadakimasu
bon appetit
mhm
yes
yes oh it's different from the US
version there you go yeah that's often
like that with products like that
hmm
okay very good
10 out of 10 already I just took a small
bite but I'm giving it a 10 out of 10.
because
this chocolate flavor
is very good it doesn't taste like too
artificial this is the kind of chocolate
flavor that I like
the crunchiness is good it's like a
combination it reminds me of um our
Austrian manner uh waffles
and combined with poppy rice crackers
rice puffy crackler thingies
yummy huh
you almost have it camera
no
yes very good
um very crunchy yum yum
[Music]
okay
and
one more thing what is there something
my French kfp think that is so missing
and I really hope you're gonna say
something that I have right in front of
me
why is this not in here something that
could be realistically in here
[Music]
we already had mudlands
uh nougat oh that's too expensive they
only put like
cheap [\h__\h] in here
I would say no that is probably too
expensive
petite Prince
mm-hmm
[Music]
uh-huh
I wonder what that is petite prince
prince
petite Lou
Lou
this is this is not it right this is not
what you're talking about is it
I have something
that looks like it's well known it looks
like it's well known
is this what you mean
it's Lulu
is that petite Prince or something else
it looks like something else or is this
bear a prince is he a prince
what has strawberry
and his buckets almost bucket almost the
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh
it's not but it's still from Little aha
so this company makes a lot of French
snacks I guess
oh oh that's the kitty ones oh they
often put like kid snacks in here
the same company oh okay
yeah I love strawberries y'all I I
wonder this looks kind of like it's a
Madeline with some strawberry jelly on
it but I guess it's not a what is a
bucket La bucket
it's not bucket what's is this not on my
land
something similar in the USA often given
to young children
ah
[Music]
yeah I guess it looks somehow with a lot
of
fantasy it looks like a boat
okay this is a big package well well
ah
are these like different products they
make
[Music]
oh they say
um combine it with milk or
uh
uh what's that again
a peach
Peach a peach
[Music]
and then you have the perfect
combination I don't have I don't I don't
have a peach with me now
wait how do you lie have you combined it
with a peach
peach juice or apricot apricot juice or
or apricot slices
that sounds weird
eat it together
uh-huh oh ah maybe maybe it's not that
it's like such a such a Godly
collaboration it's just the fact that
it's a okay a balancing okay yeah I was
just gonna say that they're just trying
to make it a healthy snack for children
for maybe in their school school
um
Bento
okay so it comes like this in like
smaller packages
let's see what this tastes like oh oh
there's so many inside oh there's like
it's in one package
hmm
all right I'll give it a try it's very
thin
oh
[Music]
that tastes like
nothing
absolutely nothing
however oh oh wait this this um this
tastes like without the jelly it tastes
like the thing you put uh on when you
make a Tiramisu
the the those fingers shaped thingies
tastes like term and then you put them
as a base and in between for a Tiramisu
what are they called
lady fingers later fingers yeah and it's
so expired but it just tastes like
nothing
uh
man
the jelly also
even with jelly
it tastes like nothing
that's the player with the delay no no
no
the expiration date is on the
um on the end of March 2023
it's way way before the expiration date
at least it's not disgusting I guess
yeah artificial strawberry flavor is
just disappointing like even the smell
when I opened it I was like ah
they should taste something
[Music]
yeah
I mean
it's a it's a very
Bland
flavor it's not very strong at all it's
very weak there is a flavor but it's
just really really weak
uh
hmm very sugary sweet you remember that
but when when's the last time you ate
that because as a I think as a kid
you eat this and it tastes stronger to
you than when you eat it 10 years later
as an adult I think or 20 years later
um
[Music]
that's why we need the pizza with our
milk yeah
oh yeah maybe maybe the recipe also
changed but I do think yeah your your
taste buds change and then your
perception of uh you know strong sugar
taste 10 years 20 years later won't
taste as strong anymore
um
yeah I mean they're not bad but again
yeah
this is the that was the last snack so
here it is that was the French snack box
but wait
it's not over yet
It's Not Over You know what comes at the
end of my snack box streams
you know it
let me move my phone back into the right
position
[Music]
I look so cute today don't I I'm so
happy with my outfit today
[Music]
I could look at myself forever
cute I'm so cute maybe even outside of
my French snack box stream every once in
a while maybe I'll show up like this
would you like that
cute I'm so French
Sasuke
yeah yeah
the Hat I love Berets yeah I mean my my
main outfit already has some kind of a
beret but here I got a new one with a
little French flag on it and oh I
actually I wanted to show you something
so maybe for that we can move over to
the screen without the screen
um let me bring the baguette with me
would you care to join me because I
decorated the office
for you guys
I want to show you
[Music]
yeah okay
come with me too
hey Halloween office
2022 version it's been updated spooky
let's go
huh
oh whoa spooky oh no it's so spooky let
me fix the chat with my dad
oh spider webs and thunder oh I think
the pumpkin is new the weather the rain
I think that's all new oh you see the
raindrops on the window oh and the
Thunder I think that was new I don't
think we had it before there's more
pumpkins than before probably as well
mm-hmm
and there's oh yeah there's a new
Post-it on the menu ideas
oh Casper was always there and live my
love to see Cats bringing hi guys what
are you doing oh you decided to stay Oh
no you're leaving again I thought you
were staying longer this time
yeah welcome to the October
Studio the Halloween studio uh
office once again it's nice to be back
here I'm excited to finally bring out a
new version
for the office again I feel like you
know
um last year we went from Summer to
October version then to Winter version
and then to Spring version and then back
to summer so it felt like it was
changing so often but throughout after
after Springtime until October it was
like the longest time without any
changes
yeah but then starting from October it's
like
so often changing
um
right now
who knows what I will do with Reina
who's in the window
okay so there's a crow oh my
oh my God wait was that always there or
does it disappear after the Thunder let
me let's see oh no it's still there I
guess the Thunder doesn't get that
bright I didn't notice the Krill until
now
you're seeing it up there there oh it's
still there it's just chilling there
wow
crony what you doing she's watching me
Everyone's Watching Me Not That Thing
behind me the logo is also
very very scary
ah
but yeah I think the songs got updated
and for the whole talk thing I think we
might have run out of space because uh
do you guys see I'm is there on top
right there's I am a senpai
but I don't know how how we're gonna do
this from now on like this already looks
really squeezed
we need to put it in another shelf maybe
on on the top right over there on the
actual right side
after October we can
put um replace the the pumpkin with some
more tapes I guess I guess
gotta start converting into DVDs yeah I
don't know why the [\h__\h] I'm using this
old tape version
no it's it's like it gives you it gives
you those vibes you know
those vibes also I'm gonna adjust myself
to look a little bit
darker according to the atmosphere in
here
um
[Music]
well that's too dark oh baklad
oh no my baguette is burnt
[Music]
oh that's so difficult
um
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
I yell
it's so difficult to figure out
I don't know man
oh
well now it looks so [\h__\h] bright this
is original
holy [\h__\h] less less
well this is more or less contrast
well this just cause I guess
[Music]
I know
maybe maybe
it's fine without
[Music]
it works not bad
oh but I just realized it does adjust
the the pngs that I attached to myself
so wow actually I'm surprised that it's
doing that what wow
oh
uh-huh
there we go oh yeah this this baby is
pretty good
I mean the baguette looks really dark
but besides that
[Music]
there's no
um
low high mid and all that and shadows
and brightness and all that and then I
can adjust
um there's only a gamma contrast
brightness saturation and stuff like
that you know it's within OBS so I can't
do everything like I can do an OB in
Photoshop
but yeah I think this looks fine
although
the picky wait we need to
people are you guys so
I'm so sorry I'm wasting too much time
here
I need to do the quiz with you guys
okay okay it's time for the quiz
questions
oh yeah
yeah wait you know how they always have
a recipe at the back and I have yet to
try a single one of those recipes but
this time the recipe is for cream
in my crabs see
let's see what they do different
one teaspoon butter or tablespoon table
tea table tablespoon 250 milliliters
milk 160 gram
uh vites and mail
well don't forget what's that again
wheat wheat
powder
um
float floor of flour with flour floor I
don't know
some sugar some salt two eggs
um maybe perhaps
uh cinnamon sugar and jam
and then yeah it's just you know how the
typical typical way of making crabs I
know how to make that
but in Austria we make the the crabs
thicker
way way way way thicker and it's a bit
easier than Crepes
um
but here I at least finally have an
official recipe
for craps maybe I'll try this one out I
need to buy myself like a crap thingy
crap crap making
thingy you know what I mean all right
it's quiz time I need I need everyone to
put their heads together
and put their thinking Berets on
we're starting with the first question
oh this is
oh wait never mind it's not too easy it
could be
could be it
B or C I guess
it's probably B all right oh but done
don't take me
don't take my word for you know certain
which
building
what's bad saying
English landmark
is the
Landmark on Paris yeah okay [\h__\h] this we
don't need this question
the options are the building center
the Eiffel Tower and Notre Dame well I
mean it's uh okay it is Eiffel Tower yes
okay let's skip this question let's go
to the next one
which
well oh thanks
huh
we learned the answer already which of
these dishes is not from France they're
just like
trying really hard
to to
um make sure you understood this one
[Laughter]
okay let's let's ask you guys
is it a galette B club or c
croissant
have we learned something today if
you're watching since the beginning of
the Stream
then you probably know the answer did
you pay attention
ah
crap so Japanese no but Japanese people
definitely have their own version of
crabs
which I would say is almost a different
dish in itself because Japanese crabs
are like way more plastered with tons of
extra stuff on top of it while French
crepes are usually very simple
crap sounds Belgian to me well the
answer is
into the class in the beginning of the
stream we found out that croissants are
actually from Austria which I'm very
proud of and very happy about because I
[\h__\h] love Christmas it's my favorite
thing to eat in the morning besides
crabs
croissant is the winner
oh
hey
[Music]
all right next question
ah
which one
I want I won't say the question until
you guys see it
um
[Music]
need to look up the English version
there you go
and one more is
um
[Music]
fancy names
okay which one
of these islands
is belongs indeed
to France
oh
[Music]
we have a Sicily B Corsica or a c
suppress
Cypress Cyprus Cypress
pen
well of course the French people know it
very well but the non-french people
might be struggling with this question
especially people who don't know Europe
so well
what ah you guys seem to be very sure
about Corsica
I'm assuming that's correct yeah it is
[Music]
[Laughter]
geography class
indeed all right we have three more
questions
uh no
like last time we had these snack boxes
the questions were more difficult and
I'm gonna skip the next question because
it's literally what is the capital of
France
it's one of the most well-known capitals
in the whole wide world
how could anyone not know this
no [\h__\h] way I'm not asking you guys
these questions
okay
this is difficult the next one is
difficult
unless you're from Europe but even if
you're from Europe you might not notice
which one
of these
[Music]
it was so specific too
does not
um
is not at the border of France that's so
specific
uh oh God I need to translate again
[Music]
and
third option is
[Music]
okay I hope these are the right
translations Google spits them out for
me so the question is which one of these
Mountain groups does not
it's not it's not at the border of
France hey the Alps B
the pirate Pirates
Pyrenees
or C the or oral mountains
wait
oh I guess oral mountains are
completely somewhere else
[Music]
oh okay
I'm pretty sure about this one too okay
so yes uh it's so mountains
[Music]
yes not not not
on the border to France yes yes yes we
have many many mountains going for
Europe as well
the Alps also go through Austria mm-hmm
okay okay
how do you say that
Euro Mountain URL okay I guess that was
not so difficult all right last question
oh or interesting
France is the
origin of
interesting
I know they're focused on B but who says
that this is where
uh where it came from originally
but okay France is the origin of a
quack and food no a Comics B red wine
see movies
now you might want to say wine right
because they're like focused on on wine
they say oh why in this wine that
but how can
surprisingly guys
um the answer is surprising surprisingly
it's surprising surprise me too just now
I looked at I looked at the
answer
it's movies
foreign
movies are from France let's look that
up
where movies invented in France France
can with some justification claim to
have invented the whole concept of
Cinema film historians called the
arrival of a train at La chiotat station
the 52nd film by the Lumia brothers
first screened in 1895 the birth of the
medium
hey y'all that was surprising I
I was like when I saw the answer movies
I was like what no way like what
[Laughter]
[Music]
I want to read more about that
oh my God so many movies
so that's impressive cool
but they came up with the concept but
that they also come up with like all the
I don't know the things you need to
create to make a movie
the things you need to create a movie
like I don't know camera no they didn't
come up with how to make a film camera
probably today
[Music]
huh
Francis isn't actually
what
who invented the
camera
[Music]
oh French inventor Louis the
Prince yes
oh my God
[Music]
well
whoa
uh-huh
I learned about that thing in school I
think
I remember that thing
oh oh
I'm Googling but hey one thing
a a German person also Johan San he
invented also some some kind of camera
thing but mostly it seems to be the
French people
wow
wow benefit oh my God Magnifique
I've been Justified for too long we're
no longer surrounding the type of
Revolution you mean kfb can't be it's
time to revolutionize the world through
kfp
hey
so the friends are indirectly
responsible for the cats movie oh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh no
wow
that is
something to be grateful for something
to be thankful for isn't it
okay guys I'm gonna read some super
chats um I'm really tired for some
reason
snack box streams always Tire me out and
kill my throat and tire me although I'm
just generally tired these days no
matter
how much or how little I sleep huh
but yes Echo stream is at this point
done thank you for joining me there
should be one more snack box coming
relatively soon but I hope it wasn't too
disappointing I mean some of these
things were good actually I mean in
terms of
um you guys said these are pretty French
so not so disappointing
some questionable things in here but not
so disappointing mostly I would say
yeah and honestly France is so close to
me if I want more and I just I fly over
to you guys
I say bonjour
and I said you give me the goods give me
the good stuff but no frog legs please
but I might be turning into a frog next
week so if you want to see froggy Wawa
next week is
is the day where the week was happening
finally
oh yeah I have
time for a replacement so if there's any
snack box company that sends to Europe
to Austria that is really good that you
recommend it has like monthly different
countries let me know I'm open to
suggestions let me know on Twitter
perhaps afterwards
please come to Japan expo well I've been
there two times and I don't know if I
want to go again
but I want to go to France again that's
for sure
[Music]
texture is same as chicken no thank you
anyway
my food to be green just kidding I like
salad salad and broccoli but but still
I'm not gonna eat a frog no no
but I need to travel Europe somewhere
actually I talked a bit more of this
mysterious whole life member who is very
serious about visiting me in Austria
um early next year hopefully if
schedules align
[Music]
well she was very
various when I told her we don't have to
just be in Austria and we can very
quickly jump in an airplane takes two to
three hours to go literally anywhere
France Spain Italy Switzerland
Deutschland
we can go anywhere in a really short
amount of time and she was like yo
a yo for real oh my God that's so cool
I'm like just posted my smoke Kiara
emoji
yeah baby
who couldn't be
yeah that's quite the flex European Flex
man so many countries so many beautiful
sceneries and cultures all within two to
three hours
flying distance
um
it was originally in France in fact it
tastes pretty good if it originated in
France why is it such a German name
that is not a French name
what is this
oh
it's a long hope uh-huh
I may have
it's with raisins huh I may have eaten
it before but I'm not a big fan of
raisins
what looks relatively familiar
Lang hope
Lang means long and it is indeed a long
long brioche why is it German
why did German
[Music]
ah
ah that place where it was invented
belonged to Germany before huh
all right all right
all right let's read some super chats uh
where do I have to continue I wonder I
wonder I wonder
I said [\h__\h]
ah it switched from Germany to France
for quite quite a few times
history lessons oh by the way I'm
watching a movie about French history
right now a movie uh serious actually
yeah
um
I told you guys before
it's about that
Italian Medici coming to France and
marrying uh Prince Francis I think it
was Francis yeah
and then they become king and queen
bleep drama drama drama
big drama
no no the empress is the Austrian one no
no no I also just started that one but
I'm not very far at all yet I'm still
I'm at the end of the first episode I
kind of got distracted and then did
something else but yeah
foreign
from Vienna
that's what you call that in French oh
that's funny
you were all acknowledge it in the words
while finally croissant how we call it
here it's such a French word why don't
we have a German word
um something else after all
but anyway uh yeah yeah yeah yeah
I like
me like uh European medieval history
very very much yeah yeah
although yeah the empress is not
medieval anymore
and by the way I was surprised to see
that actually the original language for
that series is indeed German because I
was gonna go like for watching it in
English because I was guessing even
though it's about Austrian history it's
probably filmed in the UK or wherever
and then I turned on English language
and I noticed this shitty really shitty
lip syncing I'm like what the [\h__\h] is
this
so I switched to the original language
German
which feels so weird to watch something
in German I usually never do that and it
feels kind of cringe when they talk in
such dramatic
language
but in German it feels it felt so try
hard but besides that I guess it's
pretty good so far the visuals are
beautiful the actors are decent
so if you guys want to watch a series
about a famous Empress from Austria aka
me uh just kidding [\h__\h]
um really famous there's a museum that I
took Cali to
uh that was about
her
um
uh and now there's a Netflix show so
it's on Netflix I think you guys should
be able to see it
[Music]
yes sister
she's really well known here
no it was not about Kelly I took Kelly
with me to the museum
[Music]
and stopped down in here here in Canada
oh wow
you should watch it in German with
English subtitles finally you get that
kind of experience where a show you're
watching is not an English huh I mean I
guess that's the thing with anime but
but besides anime
everything I watched besides anime is
usually in English like original
language always English
so weird watching something in German
so awkward a little bit cringe but
that's probably just because it's my own
language
thank you for the membership thank you
aside from all the animals
I don't mind watching subtitles shows
it's not bad
um
it's on Netflix in Ireland too it seems
to be International
foreign
okay I said I was going to read super
chats but I did not see your answers
what am I supposed to read
where where am I supposed to continue
do you guys know
oh by the way starting from today Japan
has opened its borders
I'm not there
but
and and I think in December end of the
year
I'll be going
wait now now I spammed with that I spent
the way your actual answers to my
question let me scroll back up I keep on
changing the topic and then the comments
changed before the karaoke Mario Kart
well including Mario Kart or did I read
Mario Kart
karaoke okay okay okay
I got you I got you I got you I got you
okay oh wait ah ah oh they were oh oh oh
I can't read them in Hawaii sir
to go to Studio although I can probably
copy the link and put it in there real
time that worked before
uh I've heard of a couple of other
a whole lot of English members who are
planning to go to Japan around the same
time as me roughly
some overlapping is happening so there
should be some offline of guys happening
but I obviously like mainly want to meet
Japanese members or or hollowayan
members who have have not met before
because you know if I only stay for like
one or two weeks
that much time I can't meet everyone
I'll prioritize people who I have not
met before except for an energy of
course because I love energy and Subaru
again
[Music]
but hopefully it will meet some new
people hopefully hopefully hopefully
[Music]
you know
so basically
it was
instead of archive I type in real time
and then I insert
the URL here I think oh
this should work it works
[Music]
um
okay
rebroadcasting
either next week or the week after or
next week I'm actually like pretty I
think the week is pretty packed so
it's not really necessary like I like
filling up empty days with with these
rebroadcasts but I don't really have so
much emptiness in my schedule next week
but who knows what I'll think about when
it's good
[Music]
all right because next week is frog wink
and frog week not good to be interrupted
by non froggy Wawa no no only for Guyana
welcome
I only want to see froggy Wella
nothing else
but we may have to make an exception
um
all right so
um thank you soon for the red super
chant well how many super chats are
these oh dear that's quite a bunch
on yesterday's stream you said you
wanted to watch a Bond movie well I just
want to say it has to be golden eye
sure the original is a classic and most
people might say Casino Royale or is
that the first one
but really it has to be GoldenEye for
watching along I think I understand I
mean GoldenEye I've heard many times
it's the classic it's uh the one go-to
Bond movie
understandable
[Music]
ah first Daniel Craig because Casino
Royale I know I know I know Daniel Craig
is a famous blonde actor and then I know
something
[Music]
oh it revived Bond oh
could kind of gave it the the life it
desperately needed again
I like Goldfinger more uh-huh
golden eye golden finger golden nose
golden butt golden egg golden booba
and those old Bond movies so I didn't
just came up with new titles for future
Bond movies
why is everything so golden
hmm
Golden Chicken
[Music]
oh those are all real Bond movies okay
they're even already existing or I
predicted the next 10 Bond movies
oh no I'm gonna get I'm gonna get
silenced for
speaking the truth and revealing secrets
for future blunt movies oh no I'm gonna
get silent what should I do I need a
safe house so I need to disappear for a
while so that people can't find me I'm
it I'm scared
Where'd I go
where should I go
maybe to Japan
don't go a bit faster a bit quicker
I'm gonna go right now
go ahead with Ina oh that's a good idea
too
James Bonk
all right thank you imaginate I will
consider it uh as a movie watch along in
the future
thank you very much
Jacob 47 I'll thank you for the pinky
congrats is a big one million on do you
and what a better way to celebrate it
then with some singing looking forward
to this thank you yes one million thank
you everybody for watching do you
streaming do you please continue alright
thank you for the support very much
appreciated
let me take a pair of candy it really
[\h__\h] hurts
[Music]
thank you guys
um
okay dial thank you for the red super
chat shamelessly bragging here but I
passed oh wait did I forget the kiss for
the muffin muffin muffin come here what
all right uh so shamelessly bragging
here but I passed an eight hour
post-grad engineering license exam and
got promoted oh
eight hour exam
your Bots have been a great way to
de-stress while working towards my goals
thank you for helping to keep people
like me from burning out as expected
from a phoenix
yeah I'll do all the burning out for you
all the burning out that everybody
should be doing I take it all in I suck
it all into my body
and I burn forever so thus I I burn I
never burn out because I burn forever
from all the burning you guys should be
doing
but eight hours what the [\h__\h] is that
normal
for like the final exam I guess
saying that's so long like how can you
even like focus and concentrate for so
long
I hope there were like proper breaks in
between like long breaks like an hour or
two
[Music]
um
oh
welcome to the membership
oh wow wow wow wow wow wow well
congratulations very proud of you I hope
that from now on your future in that job
will be very bright and that you're
gonna have
lots of success and fun and feel
enlightened by it I wish you all the
best thank you
mwah thank you for the support
had their birthday you happy belated
birthday congratulations
[Music]
and thank you for two years of
membership as well I don't know if
you're here right now
well thank you so much
I hope you had a lovely birthday
so you made excess comments and do you
reaching 1 million
thank you for releasing such a
bangasanki and for setting up the dance
challenge I haven't followed a Korean or
even danced apart from DDR for almost 10
years and I forgot how fun it can be ah
yeah yes right I mean while you're
learning a new choreo I totally
understand the feeling of being like
absolutely overwhelmed and and being
like oh I can't do this and oh no I'm
trying but I don't think I can probably
learn this and so on but you keep you're
gonna keep on going and going and then
once you've got it in because you will
eventually you will eventually be able
to somewhat remember to choreo it may
take a while but you'll be able to do it
and then you'll feel so accomplished and
you'll feel so proud of yourself
and then you can always
flex your moves whenever that song comes
on
and show off
your choreography hmm
yeah yeah yeah yeah
me too sometimes when I start learning a
new choreo
you know I just brute force it but then
I I also have moments in the beginning
in the first couple hours where I'm like
oh [\h__\h] hell I'll never [\h__\h] get
this right but at some point he's
keep on banging it into your head and
eventually
actually we'll figure it out you have to
just brute force it really that's all
there is to it
if you're learning by looking at a video
only all there is to it is brute forcing
if you don't have a teacher teaching you
step by step
um
yeah yeah
thank you you meetings
oh you're practicing in front of a
mirror oh
I don't even really do that most of the
time
but it's good to see yourself because
sometimes you move completely
differently from
like what do you think you're doing like
you look at the video and you you don't
know your body so well if you're not
like an experienced dancer so you think
you're copying the moves exactly but
then you look at yourself in the mirror
and you realize oh my arm is not
straight at all or my my leg should be
tilted or whatever
um
if you don't have much experience then
that's very noticeable in your dance
style
and it can look very clumsy and very
um unclean
[Music]
very messed up
um
yeah no one can suddenly learn a
choreography and suddenly make it look
absolutely perfect that honestly needs
needs much much much much practice
regular practice or or practice over
years
end up spreading my ankle oh no
no
oh
how did you do that well I hope I hope
it's better by now
be more careful you have to stretch
if you suddenly dance and you normally
never move your body then you you have
to stretch
en
type and thank you for the words of a
chat congratulations on do you blaze
into one million the song is so fire
it's almost as hot as you
and now that I finally burnt out of my
pocket I can join my flaming tasty
brothers and saying thank you for being
amazing and can't wait for the whole
talk Resurrection too
oh
thank you so much typhen off the past
Kiwa of the future thanks you with this
baguette thank you soon
thank you so much for your kind words
yeah many exciting things happen I'm
glad I finally got these things done the
music videos out whole talk happened
finally
hmm
getting some things ticked off my list
and I am sorry to announce that I'm
already having trouble
scheduling the next guest again but it's
not gonna happen next week anyway
because next week
is frog week and there's something else
happening but um I'm hoping for the the
week after that like the 29th or the
30th I'm hoping to get someone
I'm hoping
but don't get your hopes up guys
but it's really once we're over that
hurdle
that we're going for right now
[Music]
then we shouldn't you know
we should be able to
get back to normal
at least it won't be a seven month break
anymore I swear I swear
Jennifer
we're basically done with Gen 3 besides
peculus and by Gen 4 Gen 5
Gen 6 I don't want to interview
honestly before they reached
at least one and a half years if not two
years
um
because I just don't think it makes
sense
[Music]
but who knows
because I can do I can do en
before I do
um
the 6th gen
need some history yeah yeah
has been around way longer so if
anything I'll go for Ian first and ID as
well
on en I know I could just simply
interview them in fully English but my
plan is to translate it to Japanese yeah
reverse Holo talk
so probably I'll go fourth ten fifth gen
IV en 6th gen
that's probably the order
[Music]
yeah something like that
but when I say ID I mean first gen and
when I say Ian I mean first gen
and then and then okay so id1 en1
then maybe id2
then 6th gen
and then maybe en2
Maybe
something like that or was Ian too what
answer was before 6th gen wasn't it
[Music]
yeah yeah the best would be Chronicle W
order um
Iris Iris too but I'm kind of counting
Iris into en2 whenever I talk about
and two and I don't mention Iris so Iris
could be before Ian to
um
[Music]
the same right yeah me too
because it's so weird to have a
one-person
um
generation for me it's like
it's just en2 en1 and en2 Iris belongs
to Ian too
and now to be honest
[Music]
I feel like she she
completes
en2 anyway
now they're not five anymore I'm not
saying it's just replacing Sana but
she's at least
you know filling the Gap a little bit
hmm
yeah
because they're all I've always been
doing a lot of stuff together with with
um Iris and Council
they seem to be like an item as they say
in English don't you guys say that it's
the first time I said it like that
they're an item oh my God
oh my
[Music]
yeah an honorary sixth member yeah yeah
even though she was there before maybe
maybe maybe maybe Council are honorary
second third fourth fifth and sixth
members of Hope
[Music]
[Laughter]
they're like delayed hope members
maybe Hope Was supposed to be six
members but then although some delay
happened and then they kind of became
their own oh my God I'm creating
different narratives don't don't believe
me don't listen to anything I'm saying
Penny ran out of Hope oh no no Iris
already delivered enough hope
for one generation they didn't need
these other five girls who give more
help it was hope overload
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay let me let me let me write this
about it yeah
[Music]
thank you
I'm so excited for frock week you
wouldn't believe it
[Music]
thank you for your words of a chat there
have been many times where I had a hard
time with work these days I left your
stream when on when I got home from work
I feel better thanks to your Lively
voice I can't watch a live stream it was
nice to hear your voice in the archive
thank you Kiana you're welcome
I will be
rebroadcasting I hope you can catch it
at that time are you
foreign
[Music]
me
ah [\h__\h]
oh there we go well the color is [\h__\h]
up and now I have many hands
[Music]
there you go
[Laughter]
in his little color adjustment on that
one
but it's it's the thought that counts
mm-hmm
I haven't used that chicken in a while
it was on this obs scene so I was like
all right it's time to use that again I
guess
you're welcome
[Music]
hard worker fighting fighting
but please also remember to take a rest
okay
don't work too much don't do the work
yourself
um
thank you for your support
thank you
Mr big thank you quit Sperry's fiery
thank you the certified
Lou plays thank you for the pinky I
needed this after really bad football
loss also I love your streams being a
football football fan sucks
[Music]
oh this person is really really
upset about losing a game huh
oh no
I can absolutely not relate to that
I do not give a [\h__\h] about any any
sports teams out there
sorry I can't relate but uh good luck
surely at some point you will win again
or your team will win again at some
point
[Music]
it will happen
well thank you for watching my stream
um see kfp and Chihuahua is always
winning so if your [\h__\h] football team
is always losing then maybe you should
consider focusing more on me I'm always
winning I'll make you happy
that was really harsh wasn't it
I'm not always winning though today when
I woke up I checked Discord and I had
one really unfortunate
notice
from management
ah I can't talk about it now but I'll
eventually probably be able to talk
about it next year sometime next year
and yeah
it was really unfortunate really unhappy
about it to be honest but you gotta
you're gonna deal with whatever life or
cover froze at you
no it's not it's not free to you related
or anything but
I was very sad
um
no
you'll see it hopefully
in Spring maybe hopefully huh
[Music]
yeah
no it's not really covers
I don't know I'm not sure whose fault it
is
yeah oh well
[Music]
um
you'll see
oh wow not always winning but mostly
winning Cuba mostly winning so find your
happiness at kfp
it's back in time for the pinky and Kiki
yes I will completely ignore the way you
wrote there because there's only one and
only true kikiriki and that is kikiriki
thank you though
not acceptable though next time
you better write it correctly
otherwise otherwise
[Laughter]
don't work completely else
[Music]
okay
oh man
you understand now don't you I made it
visual like a PowerPoint presentation so
there's no doubt that what I wanted to
tell you has been received properly
[Music]
Rachel vermillions
fwlt
duncano Rodriguez
[Music]
Jones
bring to the Stream
how you doing
thank you taji even though it was
extremely late for you
really awkward time slot for you thank
you that you came nonetheless
I appreciate it
we had some yummy snacks what
I did
yeah
oh camera travels though so you might
want to skip that part was like 10
minutes or so
yeah I'm using the devices again you
can't stop me
[Music]
yeah
temporary
[Music]
how do I read this
Toshi
they're around Duncan
Robert Carney thank you for the right
Super Chat thanks for blessing my ears
with your singing just made a stressful
week better
this week has just started I hope this
one is better for you Robert Robert
um
I wish you all the best thank you for
listening to my singing I'm glad it kind
of helped
I'm honored you're saying that might
feel honor thank you so much
[Music]
tiny Delta thank you for the pinky
because suffering from tangents oh
ah the pool tangent
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah I've heard of them are Idols but I
understand your point about being a
part-time Idol where is the line drawn
you went from idle to part-time Idol or
from Idol to not idle
I mean it depends really on what kind of
idol we're talking about because
nowadays the word Idol I feel like is
being used for a lot of different kinds
of things
but uh like in my
that's right in my head the traditional
Idol
so it's a traditional sense of idol is
you know like those Japanese idol groups
yeah like Betty's covel and morning
musliment they can be and whatever
yeah
um
oh yeah cool
November 10th interesting
I don't know about permissions but
I'll look into that that sounds exciting
[Music]
the lion it's difficult uh just the
concept of idol is like generally
someone who performs
but
um the difference is to being a singer
for example would be
many Idols are not necessarily the best
singers or so because they're more like
they come in a whole package
they are supposed to be okay at least
okay-ish singers
and good dancers and good entertainers
and normally
they keep a pretty
um
innocent say so
image
to you know
I don't know that's an idol you know
they and I don't they're supposed to you
know I don't know they're not gonna sing
songs about doing drugs and drinking
alcohol and [\h__\h] like that no
at least not in the traditional sense
in the original sense and that that's
what makes them say so on their
usually encouraged by their company to
not have a partner so that's also a
thing to keep them focused on work I
suppose
um yeah this is just idle things you
know but yeah for me it's like
someone who definitely like focuses on
performing they don't need to be like
really good at singing or so but it's
the focus is on performing
and making music
you were in a group or solo but most of
them are usually in some kind of group
many group idols
no I I before said in an interview that
I don't agree with this whole
idea of us in whole life being I don't
see if anything were part-time Idol so I
set up before and I stand by that
um opinion because I'm a huge fan of you
know the traditional
um Idol type from Japan
and if we wanted this to be called
all-time full-time proper Idol then I
feel like there's a lot more live
performing necessary like I don't see
streamers as Idols you know
that's not an idol to me
I mean if you called it an idol and
everything is an idol at that point
YouTube Idol
bucket Idol
I don't know flight attendant Idol
anything could be an idol then
we are going to shambles I'm sorry I
mean the moment where we're on stage
okay that's very out of the like
you could I guess you could call us
Idols then but when we're streaming you
know since that's our main focus
whatever your main focus is if it's not
being if it's not performing then I
don't see that as an idol advocacy
Sapphire for Apple she's more focused on
on like making music and Performing so
yeah so let's say bye too
those particular members who are focused
on that
I can see them
being called considered an idol yeah
yeah but a whole life English no
Cali is not not much of an idol she's a
rapper she's a musician the difference I
see a difference there too she's a
musician to me
as I just talked about you know singers
are not necessarily idols and Idols or
not necessarily uh singers
hmm
yeah she spit spies she's a rapper she's
a musician
I don't know about being an idol
oh my God are you guys gonna
what about this person I wanna buy this
person do I have some Mission everything
God you know what I mean don't be like
that you know what I mean where
but in the end
even like you know
these members in whole life that are
very focused on music maybe I would call
them virtual Idol and not actually only
an idol
and finally think about it also look at
hello project that's that's how it is
I'm sorry
I'm sorry if that is not like
didn't you probably don't understand if
the people in my chat who like Idol uh
culture as much as I do
they probably
noodles I I am just explaining what it
is and if you don't if you're not
familiar with that kind of culture then
it's very understandable that you're
thinking and trying to gay keep
something I guess but it's really not
that it's that says if I say a baguette
cannot be a cool song
because it's a fact baguette is a
baguette and the Crystal is a croissant
in the end they're both like some kind
of bread thing okay
but there's different categories and me
saying
a baguette is not a croissant it's not
me saying [\h__\h] that I'm gatekeeping this
[\h__\h] I just don't hey you were to see me
I don't want you and I'm going to stop
you from being Christian no no it's just
it's different things
ah
[Music]
oh no it's not that difficult
it's not that much of a drama either
like there's nothing dramatic about it
I've shown you guys many times the items
that I like and I've sang songs of them
many times
I followed them in their like 10 years
of activities
and I've studied them and I've observed
them and I've supported them for like 10
years
I
I think I know a thing or two about
idols
so
yeah
it do be like that
[Music]
what
no it's not gatekeeping
it's not gatekeeping
oh
oh my God
[Music]
maybe maybe a little bit easier to
understand if I say I don't this is an
anime but if I say love love I didn't
even watch it but it's about Idols so
maybe maybe some of you guys saw love
life and couldn't can't understand it a
bit better if I give that uh example
and there's some things that are
overlapping maybe in terms of activities
from what we do
and what a typical Idol would do
we'll go once Loveline you fools now if
you're gonna watch anything then watch I
don't master
or or watch actual like hell projects
is it understandable now or are we still
not agreeing with one another
[Music]
I I I'm trying to make it like
understandable
don't agree why do you not agree
[Music]
okay most of you guys seem to agree
prefer horse girls
I see um
you might leave away
yeah okay see as I said before there's
so many different types of Idols like
but I the whole time I said I'm talking
about the traditional
kind of Idol
the Japanese
pop Idol whatever
but of course there's different aisles
like you know American Idol
or Disney Idol
yeah K-pop Idol
um
and I can see how
there's like streamer Idols like I see
how you could Define me as a streamer
Idol
but that's like so far from from the
original meaning that I have in my head
what an idol is to me that's a different
yeah that's Idol that's a different it's
just a different thing it's a different
thing it has the same same word word in
it but it's a different thing
in terms of activities yeah
can we change the topic
it's like talking to a [\h__\h] wall most
of you guys are understanding thankfully
but I feel like there's definitely some
people who are like
something oh no she's calling this
person none I know how disrespectful
[\h__\h] you are you even listening to me if
you if you're trying to make an argument
and listen to my whole reasoning and
then inform yourself about what Idols
are and then then we can continue
talking
oh
just thinking about it makes me mad
it's not that come
that cuddle it really is not that
controversial
um
yeah
let's change it
[Music]
Lord and Savior hello project this is my
Lord and Savior
[Music]
a tradition I don't know man
I don't think that's it
yeah yeah
wants to be even a full-time Islander I
wanted to do that
and
I don't think it's like
undesirable I think it's very desirable
it's a really really really really
really really really really rough job
though
[Music]
depending on
what company you're under you have
different things you suffer with if
you're on the big company then lots of
pressure about
rivalry and
um the more popular the more famous you
get the more work you get so your
schedule is absolutely overloaded and
then even though even though you're
doing all that a lot of vitals are still
like [\h__\h] broke as well
and um are living on on just eating a
bowl of rice per day or even less who
knows
and oh my God there's so much [\h__\h] that
comes with it and then if you're if
you're in a small company
if you're like a really small Idol then
no one knows then you're in that endless
Circle Loop hell of performing in a tiny
venue with no one watching you and you
try so hard to suck up to everyone to
get some fans every [\h__\h] day and it's
just endless and also again you're broke
but yeah then you have to try to balance
this thing while doing your best to try
to become famous while doing that
balance it with a side job part-time job
and bouncing with school
uh it's a [\h__\h] rough job
and that's why I have so much respect
for it and that's why I I don't want
this these terms to be mixed up too much
you know
[Music]
so
much more to it
okay let's [\h__\h] continue
yeah
you get it now okay
okay
let me drink my mojito
[Music]
I'm just I'm just checking
if I have to put any more more feet down
or if one foot down is enough now
checking how we're doing
foreign
screw yeah yeah we know what's gonna
happen we know exactly what's gonna
happen
[Music]
how many feet you got well I have four
hands you saw that
who knows about my feet
[Music]
are my feet an eyeful
hello
[Music]
we just agree to disagree all right I
guess I guess we're speaking different
languages whatever
your idol is a different Idol than my
idol okay
[Music]
ah
bye-bye
don't cry don't cry if anything crying
the usual room I don't want to see it
here
you're nice though you're not not trying
to make me angry so it's okay
it's okay you're nice
we're happy we're happy people
moving on yet I don't know I feel like
I'm stuck I can't [\h__\h] move on
I felt like this for 10 minutes
someone
get me out of here I'm just stuck
[Music]
but Thanksgiving special uh
today is in Canada Thanksgiving isn't it
it's not kind of Thanksgiving
was it yesterday
oh yesterday I read it somewhere
Oh Canada how was it are there any
Canadians or more goose
[Music]
um
I'm having my turkey today oh here I'm
Canadian sadly why sadly
be proud of it
Canadian here oh okay here oh visiting
family oh
[Music]
no replace it for funeral that's sad
I was at work oh what the [\h__\h] they did
not give you a day off what the [\h__\h]
how about we talking about even being a
part-time Warren said you wanna you
wanna know the line the line of being a
a warrior to not being a warrior
let's open it
uh I guess if it's whatever or not you
slay some dragons or not I guess I've
I've played uh Orcs and dragons and uh
dinosaurs if you don't do that
yeah you know I guess I mean you can't
just say you're worrying if all you have
is a sword made out of wood and all you
fight is your inner demons that's a
different kind of warrior that's like
the 21st century kind of
um Millennial Warrior okay but
we're talking this is actually this is a
really good example we're talking about
different kinds of words I'm talking
about wars in a traditional [\h__\h] kind
of sense where you find some [\h__\h]
dragons like in [\h__\h] Lord of the
Rings man the little Orcs you know or
exploding the Rings or or even fight
[\h__\h] sour I know what I don't know I
don't [\h__\h] know you you have Arena
you have to hold on don't you throw it
into the [\h__\h] lava cause that's what
you gotta do cause your [\h__\h] Warrior
or something similar to that I mean I
wouldn't say in a Frodo was a warrior
but in a bigger sense in a bigger
meaning something like that
uh English
hahaha
let's stop it
yeah yeah yeah yeah people love people
was an idiot
um
dear Lord
MK what the [\h__\h] did you get me into MK
Broken Man
thank you for the pinky I am now broken
woman
ah you know
my my
you know how my family was like and me
as well we're more into medieval uh
festivals
um we would go to Joe's and then at the
same time another thing that my brother
and my at the time Mother's boyfriend
partner were into was making these these
swords
um
not wooden swords but like out of some
kind of foam or so
and make it look like swords and so on
and they were like
doing stuff with that
I tried a few times but I was not much
of a warrior back then ironically
uh yeah I think LARP swords yeah
I guess yeah
[Laughter]
they were making those yeah we had a
couple at home we also had a real sword
at home that's obviously my sword that
was me getting into the warriorism
um I wouldn't play with [\h__\h] large
swords only play with real swords
huh
yeah me too oh yeah let's go are you a
fellow Warrior
[Music]
my mom my mom was some kind of a warrior
I guess yeah because the sword actually
was from her and
um she also at some point she was doing
uh bow and arrow shooting
archery archery Archer archery
um I'm a Kiara Ward keyboard Warrior at
best well at least you're honest and
true to yourself
yeah yeah she had that as a hobby for a
while
um
she doesn't do it anymore
it was her hobby is temporary
temporarily yeah
his mama told me one of the Fellowship
of the Ring I can't say
I'm under an NDA I'm not allowed to say
okay I think we have all calmed down
what people have been on swords with my
other job like you would abandon animals
at the shelter
why would they come to you like what job
is that I ended up taking one home and
it's been with me ever since
what what where where do you work where
would people go and just abandon their
swords
what kind of place would I abandon my
sword at
game store
why why don't they just take it to the
trash
what I don't understand
[Music]
if I had to abandon a sword
the first spot that would come to mind
is
put it in the
trash
I mean I wouldn't be sure about it
because I'm like is this okay to go into
the trash
oh baby bring it to
um uh bring it to
uh not what's it called like those big
markets where people bring like their
own things
and sell it
like a like a garage sale but not in a
garage
a flea market thank you flea market
or a pawn shop yeah whatever
why the [\h__\h] would you bring it to a
game shop
anyway broken man thing even the pinky
oh it says you don't have to read this I
love you I'll read it silently
ah
comes Anita
but as you have heard I'm already broke
until I'm like
um I feel so connected to you now broken
man I'm a broken woman
I'm Rogan Phoenix they've [\h__\h] broken
me
I'm broken
I will heal
I will heal tomorrow
yes
I'll say one thing one more thing about
the topic in some way it's I guess a
compliment people insisting on the fact
that we are idols
thank you very much
all right uh Jacob 47 outline
spanking time thank you for the recipe
chat thank you
thank you so much for the karaoke feels
like it's been 84 years oh that's a very
specific number
and since I've been able to watch live
due to work such bangers you sing them
all incredible
thank God there's a good job too no that
was a good karaoke
solution
thank you very much I'm glad you enjoyed
it I'm glad you got a chance to watch
your life yeah finally finally it was
about time
it's more
special when you can watch it live after
all thank you spanking high
thank you I hope there was a song or two
that you like very much originally
already
and thank you for the recipe chat thank
you my beloved chicken for the recipe
chat as always I love your singing I'm
finally able to see you live oh since my
two-year-old member anniversary of super
chats oh it was replaced at work for the
job I've done for the past years
I hope that my original job will let me
work from home more and once you let
life more again
wait
wait I'm confused when you say original
job do you mean kfp
so you were you were recently replaced
at your other job that's not kfp
that you've been doing for the past few
years but now
you you know you say I hope that my
original job will let me work from home
more and once you let no
yeah I'm confused I have five jobs oh
what the [\h__\h] is one of them kfp
so one of the jobs you lost and one of
the other ones you're hoping that you
can just work from home or all right
holy [\h__\h] why why so many jobs what the
[\h__\h]
oh my God
[Music]
well I think four four is four is fine
one less means you can watch me more
it is factors at the same company
it's like
running a supermarket all on your own
you're the cashier
you're the bagger
you're the the meat person you're the
stalker restocker
your little boss
of the the branch
huh
okay let's not ask too much
it's private information but I wish you
all the best
and I hope for improvement
um hopefully you can watch from home
I'll work from home that's honestly the
most ideal thing I I you know
so many people were complaining during
the sea thing
that they have to work from home and I
guess I partially understand but their
reasonings but like I'm so used to
working from home and I love it I
[\h__\h] love it but okay some people
just are so used to being out there and
and interacting with people they're so
social they love interact with people I
guess they just really need it but I I'm
so happy
about it like I wouldn't want it any
other way
um some of you guys seem to be the same
way
and I guess I understand other people
needing
you know that Rhythm for example or
there's any other reason why they don't
want to work at home like maybe there's
a baby at home that's [\h__\h] noisy or
whatever they see there's some kind of
escape from their wife or whatever I
don't [\h__\h] know
but
I I'm I just feel like working from home
is the most comfy thing you don't have
to feel pressured about looking good at
work especially if you're a woman then
you know I I felt that pressure all the
time I had to do my [\h__\h] makeup every
morning because I just wouldn't feel
comfortable I would feel ashamed if I
had if I were to go to work without
makeup and then you have to wear heels
and and and tights and all that [\h__\h] but
oh [\h__\h] oh sure
yeah so anyway I think it takes off so
much pressure from you
know and it saves you time because you
don't have to go to work so many people
have to commute to work like for an hour
or so who knows
depending on where you're going
I didn't I didn't have to wear heels but
in many jobs
um
women have to wear heels at least like
from
not maybe not in every country and not
in every job but I've seen
[Music]
women complaining about that because
it's part of the work uniform yeah
wasn't the case for me but yeah
[Music]
if once you're used to heels then
there's heels that are relatively
comfortable but not not when you wear
them for eight hours yeah
[Music]
okay with the bus is so bad
yeah
and I feel like the the hat is sitting
on my head so
so well isn't it it's moving along
pretty nicely too
now with like the feature that I can
stick it onto very specific layers of my
body is like really helpful
um it doesn't wobble around so weirdly
oh yeah it's connected nicely it's
pretty natural yeah yeah
[Music]
I kind of want like a short haircut for
chihuahua because
um the thing with like if I want to put
some some clove pngs on myself clothing
pngs then it's weird because it would
cut off the braids or whatever long hair
I have that's like overlapping in the
front
it only really works well with short
hair
um
yeah
then it doesn't look so weird
oh yeah hair tied up yeah with the
dandel for example
it could work
decently
um
[Music]
foreign
yes new background you just noticed it
wait how you've been in here for a while
how did you just noticed it
it's my new October background
um some things changed from last year
I'm 100 sure which things but I've
noticed some things
it's been a while since the last time
I've seen it
but changes have been made
did you notice your visitor yet you mean
Casper or the crow
what do you mean something else
[Music]
what do you mean
not
um
you mean my frog
[Music]
the flash on the right window right
what the [\h__\h]
the time for you guys were just joking
in the chat what the [\h__\h] was that
kiss
ES
[Music]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] horrifying
that's [\h__\h] terrifying
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] eat an exile where the
[\h__\h] are you I'm gonna Exile you into
the usual room you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
someone behind you I thought you meant
like I don't know nothing I thought you
wanted to just spook me made me look at
something make me get get me paranoid
herself
oh it's so scary
I want to be in here anymore he's an
exile No you little [\h__\h] sorry it's not
gonna do it well you should have warned
me
um
I'm spooked
I don't like this
[Music]
hope you like this night with banging
your liked them sorry I'm
just book right now
I like them but you know I just want to
go back to France and eat fresh food
yeah no snake snacks is just you know
they're just snacks
nothing better than a fresh dinner and a
nice restaurant
all right um I think yeah this this
counts as the butts
no one can ever I mean you already
stopped benching it anyway but no one
can mention the bats the game anymore
can you I just spooked myself here this
is this is my homework for Halloween all
the all the horror that I needed to do
to meet my Halloween quota of horror
stuff
is done
it's done I did it myself
I don't care what you think
let me continue
thank you good
I'm not a cheater chef
shut up I'm scared I'm crying and I'm
scared and I'm shivering and you're
calling me a cheater and being mean to
me how dare you
I'm gonna get my mustache wet from the
tears
so funny to you
protect me thank you
[Music]
it's not supposed to get wet
and we'll fall off
the stickiness will
it will disappear
and Dominique
is
hitting one million control
Masterpiece definitely deserved at least
100 million indeed even after listening
to it one non-stop everyday since
released I still can't get enough of it
it's just too amazing I keep streaming
forever and ever thank you
thank you
I believe you I can always count on you
[Music]
thank you
really enjoy it's the best words can
describe how much I love your voice
she's seriously so beautiful and always
be one of my favorite things ever please
do cat Okay more often if you can
I just want to listen
to using forever thank you
um that's sweet
thank you
mm-hmm I don't want to do it too often
though because then it won't be special
anymore
um
ideally every stream would be cut out in
my mind
space wonderful language
[Music]
I'm gonna hide behind my bucket
foreign
[Music]
what's happening
I'm gonna hit you with my baguette if
you come and spook me
[Music]
this baguette is three weeks old so it's
pretty stale
pretty stiff it's quite the bunk get
bunket
[Music]
it's not fresh anymore no no
oh my God okay let's put it back where
it belongs
oh why is it so weird now no
no I misplaced it
I'll just try to stay still
um thank you Jason wishes thank you one
week your singing is so nice to listen
to yours don't do sweeter I love you
don't look at my arm don't look at my
arm
look at me neither
don't I'm not a raven
no no I don't want to be Rayman looks so
painful
[Laughter]
no thank you James wattpark
this is Halloween this is Halloween
interesting it will always be music to
my ears
[Music]
looking forward to more content
intentions for me and my OC
are you sweet
love love love love love thank you
thank you
I'll do my best
please support
thank you for the pinky thanks for the
amazing karaoke you're singing It's just
divide and exquisite our family recall
for the next four days uh it's that time
of the year I have to leave for a
quarterly camp program
I'll slowly miss you for the coming four
days
I promise to keep up with the Vlogs is
it four days because you have the number
four so often in there to replace words
but
are you saying it's gonna you're gonna
be gone for four days GD are you here
are you here
where are you Daddy are you already gone
I'm hitting myself
today are you already gone if it's only
four days at least you'll be back soon
[Music]
um
stop it
out
oh
I went away
it's threatening me
[Music]
that bucket
okay bucket
it's a love story
oh my God
yeah I'll put the comments on this
screen this is better yeah that's better
okay
thank you Didi
I'm awaiting your arrival
please come back soon otherwise I will
die
soon
Optimus Prime Duncan Jolly rainfall
thank you for the pinky appreciation
thank you
I'm glad you enjoyed the karaoke stream
thank you for being there
you sound like a first time super
channel to me thank you so much
ah for the pinky you could have learned
us that we're gonna experience audible
Perfection then again that had to be
accepted about wonderful thank you but I
was not expecting such levels of jazz
um do you like to ask
do you
thank you I'm glad you enjoyed it it
wasn't like completely Jazz but it was
an attempt
I I tried to
getting a little bit Jazzy try my best
thank you for listening
um
thank you for the pinky saying amazing
no you no you thank you bye Ghana
thank you
[Music]
Jacob 47 outdoches
you gave us inspirational power so I
give you this thank you for the heart
thank you soon sorry guys my throat
really hard
because I haven't been drinking normal
water I suppose
trying to
get through this with the Seven Up
now I'm gonna get through it Phoenix two
six one two and I'm going to enjoy the
rainfall language
[Music]
so damn fun great setlist amazing
singing much love Buzz thank you I try
to make them
um entertaining and trying to put in
songs that you guys know
and there's always gonna be songs that
some people don't know but I feel like
I'm I'm mostly choosing songs that
people know
I'll try my best you know
it's not like I really am
know that that many like underground
unknown
songs anyway I've been listening to a
lot of mainstream
music and the course of my life
yeah so
that's just what I grew up with
as my library my music library
hey Kyra
hi one one
what's up it's my business so I just
wanted to say it was a birthday
saying you and your dog streams make
every day more fun
thanks for being you you nerd uh-huh
oops oh that wasn't on purpose I thought
you did it on purpose
[Music]
also I'd like to get my favorite little
Devil's number
huh
10 583 is my kfb ID number please
also great Carol can you sing me never
disappoint
you want a uh no one has even gone to
four digits and you suddenly want a five
digit number
I know you'll have to be nice to me for
a week
for me to allow you having a five digit
number
and you know that's really hard for you
probably because you're a tsundere
if you're nice to me for a week then you
can apply for that number again
a week
I want to see compliments genuine
compliments and no mean words can you do
it okay oh wow
foreign
okay
let's see how you're gonna do
[Music]
I'm you know even in the chat like for a
five hour stream or so I don't want to
see a single sassy baka
common okay
see you even if I don't read it out loud
I often see you being a Little Bit Sassy
so I have to
even be nice there when you think I
don't see it
[Laughter]
was [\h__\h] okay let's see guys I want you
to be my my second set of eyes okay if
you see it one one over
um being a little little mini beanie
let me know
okay all right it failed no no way
where
I don't see anything
[Laughter]
we got our eyes on you
preach out yeah
otherwise it would just be fake
that should be everywhere has to be
genuine I said it's not genuine if it's
only in certain situations
[Music]
all right it's a deal you you get the
kids too when the one week is over
um
thank you for the red super chat
yeah I'm holding the kids songs that
this is exactly what I'm doing
yeah Chris Ransom
gives give some one one over even more
reason to take it seriously I'm a
celebration one million music it's my
favorite song now in my lifeline doing
work really awesome week two weeks ago I
celebrated my second birthday
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
you probably don't understand what I'm
saying
hey I'm not moving why the [\h__\h] am I not
moving
[Music]
oh my phone um is oh no the app is
refreshing all right here we go
you're here
little baby
I don't see I don't see them
[Music]
don't curse in front of the baby and
then take the baby away
I'm stuck here
ah barely in life when I'm here how are
you barely alive you look the way you
were just born two years ago
how's that possible
[Music]
how how are you are you um a queen bee
it was queen bee is uh lifespan three
years then you're pretty close to that I
guess
then I guess you are barely alive
well things happening to you guys yeah I
mean
damn I guess it's rough 42 year old
okay I'm bullying you Google and it's
just like so sleep deprived apparently
yes I saw a b video what the [\h__\h] why do
we all get the same videos recommended
did you also get the video recommended
from a Japanese idol or crying in her
stream and then wanting to eat chocolate
and and have a pool in her house
did you get that too today
oh my God
I can't [\h__\h] take it that that was
partially my my inspiration for today's
rant about being [\h__\h] broke as an
idol I
got a famous couple of recommendation
that's nice
it's stalking me no I'm not stalking you
it's because we're the same [\h__\h]
recommend it's not my fault
it's not my fault
are you okay you're like so
unemotional
where is the Emoji
I can't write a message like that say
good night without an emoji that seems
like you're going to bed while being
angry at me
you can't leave me like that did I'm
you're not like the bubble bubble thing
I'm sorry
we can't end it like that
yeah you have to you know I think no you
make me think you're angry
[Music]
or like not even an exclamation mark an
exclamation mark would help
me on the rough right no
I'm sorry okay I'm gonna stop
here's a kiss
I'm sorry
[Music]
I'm level happy happy birthday
are they gone did I was I doing
to mean
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday do you know
oh there you are and we're funny
I thought you were angry at me and left
sadly
okay happy happy
[Music]
sorry for saying you're only two years
old sorry I didn't mean it like that
[Music]
um
me
fries
oh man this Super Chat reading I am
I have so many regrets
uh I feel traumatized by the Super Chat
reading
um
finished now
um don't look at me
don't I don't want to be looked at right
now
oh look at me
[Music]
I have to go cook something now it's
like midnight but I have to cook
something
I've got some pizza frozen pizza in the
in the freezer but I feel like I don't
deserve it
it has been rough mentally it was really
nice to hear you even if I couldn't hear
to be here the whole stream oh then you
gotta catch up
I I told a funny story in the beginning
that's worth catching up on the VOD
floor yeah
I'm going to be I don't deserve it no
[Music]
no don't just try with the pizza
eat the pizza or else
you bake the pizza
I want to check if my cats used the new
toilet they probably didn't they like it
they
I want to talk about it the day after
tomorrow perhaps in the GTA stream but I
think that's a GTA stream but yeah they
don't have a problem with it
[Music]
but I don't think they used it yet but
there's a there's an application
um
where you can check when's the last time
it moved and it only moves after a cat
entered but
uh last time
last time it didn't move when I put one
of my cats inside
I guess it didn't it didn't acknowledge
my cat
and then other times when I put them
inside
it they did get acknowledged sometimes I
don't get acknowledged I guess I don't
know why
but it's it's
um like detecting the weight changes in
the toilet and then it knows oh there's
a cat in here right now and then when it
leaves it goes back to the original way
so then it's like okay I'm gonna start
cycling now whoosh whoosh
it didn't do that the previous time when
I put the last time when I put my cat in
but I think generally it works
and it's honestly it's fine if it
doesn't do it and every time I think
because
that's fine
one little piece of poop
staying until the next
cat enters is fine as long as it at
least Cycles every second poop action
but yeah I I'm gonna talk more about
this toilet once I have more more
um
experiments behind me
hopefully no failures but yeah as I
wrote on on Twitter this movie was like
the first to check it out and like I
built the toilet and then I I found
smoothie in the living room and I was
nice moving
let's go and I pick her up and she says
purring purring purring because she's in
a prairie mood and in a happy mood
so she was like really cuddly and then I
bring this purines movie into the toilet
and put her inside and she's like
so happy
and then she just stays in there for
like
so it felt like 10 minutes and she was
like sniffing sniffing and pairing and
pairing and she was like kind of laying
down low-key
she was not sitting she was actually on
all her tummy
getting really comfortable
I'm like at least she likes it I don't
know if she's like she understands that
this is a toilet but it's the same
toilet sand that I use in the other
toilet so she should recognize that
was really cute
and I think the fact because chunkers
entered
um the room
well smoothie was purring inside the
toilet and I think that kind of let
junkers know that this thing is safe and
okay
but then
I did and did an oopsie so I waited
until smoothie wait a left the toilet
okay
[Music]
and the thing is like there's like
buttons that glow up on the side of the
toilet
[Music]
um let's tell you that it's about to
cycle or that it's ready for a cat to
enter and so on and then when this movie
left
the the button
that would say that it's about to cycle
sometime soon was on
so then chonkers enters out of you know
curiosity
and I'm like [\h__\h] what if it starts
turning
while she's inside
because one cat entered too fast after
the other I think there's they probably
wouldn't
do it but I got kind of worried about it
so I was like okay you know what I'm
just gonna turn off the toilets for now
while chungus is inside just to make
sure that her first experience with the
toilet is not a scary one and that she
that doesn't start turning or or making
noises while she's inside so I I push
the button to turn it off but I didn't
know that
the toilet as a mechanism that when you
turn it off that it Cycles one more time
so while chokers are inside exactly the
thing that I tried to prevent happens
and it starts turning and she's like
what the [\h__\h]
she of course immediately jumped it
doesn't start turning fast it goes
really slowly and carefully but it also
makes a loud sound so then she backs up
like beep beep beep
beep beep and I'm like chocolate
[Music]
look look it's fun it's fun and I waited
until the
I waited until the toilet was fat um
finished with the cycle
and I tried to
you know one more time familiarize her
with the toilet
uh which was fine like I I I I like got
her to purr inside the toilet too by
aggressively petting her
[Laughter]
she was
seemingly comfortable inside the toilet
as well but
I don't know if they understand what
it's for
but at least shunkis does not seem to be
scared of the the noise that the toilet
makes you know she's usually very very
spooked out by like the vacuum cleaner
and so on and also the hair dryer but
um when the sound
of the toilet you know when it's cycling
what's happening she was in the same
room and she seemed totally fine and
unbothered by it
yeah so that's fine and normally I mean
that shouldn't really happen while she's
closer toilet anyway
because normally she goes in she does
her thing she leaves the room and then
it starts cycling
if it would work like that but
the food that I was
like I guess I really wanted to tell you
the story about me freaking out jonkers
unintentionally okay I'm gonna go now my
throat hurts bye bye I love you guys
enjoy myself videos and see you on the
day after tomorrow I'm probably gonna
upload a clip on the German Channel
tomorrow
or also maybe maybe even also a clip on
this channel tomorrow who knows
ah goodbye thank you merci beaucoup for
watching them
um
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]