[Applause]
[Music]
key
feet
[Music]
i have to say i'm a gamer who doesn't
really get aggressive
jump no no
i stay positive
maybe i get a little bit loud but i
don't get aggressive
this is wonderful i really enjoy this
just such a nice weather
and
my um said aim for the sun
well then i'll do it do i trust my papa
i trust him
i love him so much she can't be lying to
me
i believe in you papa
[Music]
[Applause]
now what about me i would say i'm very
pure and very intelligent
now hold on a minute hold on i wanted to
bring something up real quick
but when you say that you're very pure i
would like to remind you of the many
times you have come into my house
and said to me hey when are we going to
have a sleepover
we are back and in the meantime i have
seen
a comment in the chat from my papa my
fuki papa
and my papa says i belong in the bottom
left i don't know
i think so your papa and i are on the
same wavelength it would seem
about words it's not a bad thing i don't
know don't you think i have kind of
proven
that i am quite the idol
my arm and
yeah big chest just like
callie
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
by the way i do not know how to put
items on my ass
if i gotta use this item which i get the
whole time
then i will put it on my ass and stick
it up
all the way in there and then it is
where it belongs
okay i don't think i should stick this
up my ass
i am single-handedly
going to kill you mario
i will kill you and your family
will kill you and luigi and pete
and daisy and pull
every single one of them i will kill
them
ah no who loves that fire
fired who the [\h__\h] did that
you're all fired you guys don't
understand these days
it's hard to get a job you really want
to lose your job
are you sure about that yeah i already
hey it was nice knowing you all
bye-bye alligator
fireworks i'm standing uh
wait the task should be here so oh no
no no i didn't want to do that
i didn't see that did you
sorry what hello
i'm going to marry petra
because she reminds me of cali and i
like her
she's very very friendly and open
she told me she will take off her
clothes in front of me
i like her vibes
she's straight there's people who are
straight and not
you can't tell me she's straight
she she's at least
come on
you can't fool me
it's [\h__\h] okay okay one more one
more one more
one more open your mouth open your
goddamn mouth it's feeding time
i don't have milk but i got some water
for you
i drank all the milk already it's very
delicious cali's milk
okay look at this now you won't be able
to look
at the road anymore
it was at this moment he [\h__\h] up
oh
okay
chill concentration everyone chat not
only me but you must also concentrate
okay concentration
nice job well done nice distraction
tactics ted who's ted no one
who is telling you wanna tell me
something
i don't know it's head wanna tell me
about ted huh
what i don't know only you and me and
vincent i mean yeah
yeah is it that from the ted talk who we
went to see together
what when was that i have no memory of
this a few years ago we went to
a ted talk and ted was talking to us
i don't think that the people there are
named ted kiara
i don't think they all have different
their know there is
one dude and he told
don't forget kelly who's kelly
oh anyway um
[Music]
how can someone be confident
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
mb 737.00
a red super chat with no words what
pool mb737
please next time write something please
please please please and thank you for
your support for your
you get some i can give you some blows
[Music]
wait that's [\h__\h] weird oh my god i
take it back
yoshi
okay
oh yeah i want to collab with whole live
japanese especially of course back when
i'm saying
there's so many senpais that i really
like so
uh it would be really cool especially
since i speak fluent japanese i think
that you can easily
collab with me i would be really happy
i'm scared to ask but yeah
we'll see what happens
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
that's not the problem you can eat as
much chicken as you want but um
i've been worried about your everyday uh
foods taken that one i'm getting
really healthy oh
look at the gyoza
[Music]
i'm going to ask her to do something i
wonder if she'll she'll be able to
reactive because she
she's really good at um
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
oh
okay
[Applause]
three two three cheese
[Music]
thank you so much for collabing with me
today
[Music]
i hope i can do that i think i can do it
i wonder if he'll say um
he always writes to everyone it's like
and i want to be successful but for that
i need everyone's help
[Music]
all whole ivn members have reached
100k either during the stream or shortly
after
let's say congratulations
[Music]
300k
thank you so much for subscribing
everyone
thank you congratulations 600k thank you
thank you oh thank you thank you so much
thank you and when i release original
music eventually
i really like singing i'm not i'm really
not a good singer i've realized
that i've come to that realization but i
really am
enjoy singing and i hope others will
enjoy
presents to you her first original song
[Music]
thank you
one million is such a such a surreal
number
insane number
thank one i love you all so much you are
the best people i could ever ask for
the best employees i could ever ask for
i'm glad to have the people who are with
me now
because i think everyone who is here now
has a good heart and i just
i just feel like these are the good
people
it's been a long time since i was able
to
focus on one thing so much and
put so much effort into it without
forcing myself but actually having
motivation for it too
it's been a long time since i
was able to put so much in so much heart
and so much soul and so much power
energy into something
without it being painful for myself
but i think that is because of you guys
because you show me
you guys show me that it's worth it
without you guys in the chat
you know my twitter timeline and
everywhere
then i would not be able to do it and
this is so true
i would not be motivated to do any of
this
i was so i actually already gave up
i i was already okay i'm done
i'm done with dreaming i was i was so
done
there is literally no better fan base
than the kfp fan base
there's no one better than you guys out
there
all of you are just so goddamn kind i
don't know what to do
i just want to do my thing and i'm happy
with what i got already
but of course we gotta keep on growing
cannot stop that was
2020 for like the last three two four
months of it i guess
we did so much in such a short time that
it does feel like a whole year somehow
and you all stayed by my side and
supported me through it
even when sometimes i had doubts about
myself and others maybe had those two
i think i found my way and i will
continue doing my best in a chiata-ish
way
so thank you for a roller coaster of
emotions and for teaching me things
making me laugh making me cry in a
positive way
and letting me know how much you guys
love me i love you all very much too
see you in 2021 auf wiedersehen