[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
the power of professional studio yes we
are in the studio today thank you staff
for help thank you thank you very much
response microphones five cameras well
there's one PC that I'm controlling but
besides that everything is five times
yeah so I wanted to do a little off
collab uh you know to do something of a
something like a game show with you
girls and now this is maybe inspired by
an already existing show
me I yeah I'm probably gonna be good at
that she probably was a guest at that
show before
she was in Disguise
well to explain a little bit what it is
for the people who don't know what this
is inspired by because I'm not gonna
mention it
um well so everybody prepared Eva one
true and two lies or two truths and one
lie because I didn't want everybody to
have the same amount because then you
could maybe
um guess which one is one
so we don't know that except well I I
kind of know who prepared true or two
but I'm not I'm not even sure if that
sounds familiar yeah
I couldn't get around it but um you know
it's still difficult because when I read
those prompts I was like I really don't
know which one of these is true which
one is false so I hope everybody is good
at gaslighting because that will be your
job today
so if you win today are you actually
winning or is that a sign
you win a red flag
permanent red flag taped on your
forehead well I would say what that
would mean is also just that your
stories are unbelievably
so we're kind of on a tight schedule
um but don't worry guys this will not be
just one hour well we probably do two
hours if everything goes away so
who should start who should start
I'm gonna start I guess from the left
side which left your left the screen
left I'm gonna start with Ina and you
will not know which one comes first
okay okay explain like they're all true
all right okay I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm
gonna do the opposite of Poker Face I'm
gonna be
um the hint I'm gonna be the hint the
right way to do this by the way is just
like don't give out too much right away
let them like pull it out of you like us
interrogate yes okay okay Inna please
read your prompt uh I wanna spread water
on a classmate's face when I had my
mouth full of water
all right
um I kind of believe that was it out of
surprise or was it because you wanted to
spray water on her face or did they tell
you something funny yeah
um yeah yeah yeah somewhere along that
line
what did they say what was the joke they
said hi
what were they wearing
I don't know how many questions can we
ask each I know that at any end is as
many as you want were you laughing at
how they looked
um did they have a funny nose no they
had a very normal nose so what was so
funny about it yeah it was the situation
what was the situation so you know
back in class like I um you know you
always have to like interrupt the entire
class to go like get a drink or go to
the bathroom
and so I didn't like standing out in
class but doing that so you didn't want
to stand out yeah so during recess like
I went to get some water from the
fountain I had a mouthful of water from
there and the bell rang so I was like
rushing back to my classroom oh and then
just as I entered the doorway when my
classmate stepped in the doorway oh I
said hi
[Music]
detective what questions could you have
to you know I feel like catcher all
grounds have been covered really be like
why didn't you drink the water how long
was the walk back to class I mean you
would have already drank it at that
point yeah I believe the fountain was
like pretty close ish but then like it
wasn't like super far where I could like
you know
run and drink at the same time what was
your friend's reaction yeah
I just remember them just being stunned
but like
I think I like try to like kind of hide
that from my memory like back in the day
because it was kind of traumatic I was
like I'm so sorry I mean can brains are
mushy inside so I guess yeah it makes
sense it's like your memory is like a
film oh and it's like a thing it's just
like the scratch Cuts right there what
what which school year was that
um I believe it was when I was in grade
three
is that Junior
school elementary school elementary
school yeah Elementary okay yeah yeah
after second grade yeah
okay well if you guys are already ready
if you already have made up your minds
um or does anybody have a question left
tell me is it true or false what do you
think
false okay
um Gemma writing them down
Kelly what do you think false false um I
think I think it's false too good on you
true
curveball we used to do that too like on
the spot like you just like you're just
like oh my God I have to rush back so
yeah like I can see baby Ina doing that
yeah I can no no
it's we're not believing it but what if
it is just unbelievably believable
exactly okay
left we have made up our mind all right
all right okay thank you for the first
prompt then we will uh go on to the next
one next is gura
tell us a story
please read
I could where's the rest of it oh I cut
a skirt shorter and shorter until it
became a belt because it had holes it
continuously was getting holes uh-huh so
I cut it shorter
wear and tear what learn one time I was
in the grocery store and it caught on
the The Wire baskets that hold the bread
oh Mr really loved that skirt yes what
kind of skirt was it what did it look
like it was pink and I had it was like
corduroy pink and it was rather long and
it had it was like a hem at the very
bottom to make it uh wavy flowy I told
you guys she's girly
I was wearing pink yeah she was wearing
pink and she was like the cutest hats oh
we have matching hats
when you when you cut the skirt
did you also like
the Hem yeah did you do that yes I
rolled it under and hemmed it I didn't
leave a ride how old were you how old
was I I was probably
oh
[Music]
what would you rate your sewing skills
from one to ten one being bad ten being
excellent
ah two a two is really bad oh
why didn't you get like your mom to help
you then if it was really bad because
she said this is something that you
should learn uh when you're older so you
can fix your clothing on your own which
is true why didn't you just buy a new
skirt
plus it's like when you're young and you
have a favorite article of something
you're gonna wear it until it literally
is falling apart what was the original
length it was long it was long
it could possibly drag on the floor if
you weren't wearing like a uh-huh so
what was the shortest that you wore it
that was after yeah
what stage it does a skirt become a belt
you know the finger test yeah nothing
finger test I don't know if everybody
else knows with the finger test is when
you put your hands down oh and if the
skirt the skirt has to go past your
fingertips right yeah it no longer went
past my fingertips it was up quite a few
inches I didn't like I didn't wear it to
like school or anything but yeah that's
fine that sounds fun but it's just I
don't know it's but there's like you
said one instance of how it got hold but
how can you have how can you
continuously get so many holes I've
never gotten like a whole okay maybe
once in my clothes after wearing it a
million times
what's another instance that made it get
another hole when you squat down the
wrong way but it's a skirt yes it's not
pants which she said it's like a long
skirt so it's kind of like a pencil
hem's kind of and it's curly which is a
pretty stiff fabric
now but then you have to see like she
was like nine thousand ten nine thousand
thirteen so like I could totally see you
like tripping and like you know also
like getting holes by that you know
being clumsy
bad stitching shorts why didn't you just
buy a new one
because I was a kid and I loved it I
liked it
how dirty was it when it became a belt I
watched it disgusting
fabric does get worn down a little right
oh I have a question oh yeah uh what
like how old were you when you first got
it
ten nine thousand ten oh okay
so for three years yep was it real
stinky no
it meant the laundry detergent somewhat
frequently needed a hole for your tail
huh oh yeah that could have been in my
tail hole it's like having three legs
if you got it at 9010 then I would say
you were probably still growing yeah
exactly well why aren't you growing out
of the skirt then I could have been hmm
could have been so are you sure it still
fits at 9014. you don't have clothes
that used to fit you as a kid
is
from like like 10 years ago I still say
I don't think three years is necessarily
unless puberty really hits you like yeah
so you say a word you know you cut it
until it was as long as you know the
fingertipsy thingy but that doesn't
really fit the description you said it
became a belt yeah you said it became a
belt that's not a belt at all look at my
skirts that's good I guess that is
basically a belt with like you know the
little stats inside that's like your
real clothing and then you got the
orange belt yeah yeah exactly exactly
well anyways have you made up our mind I
think I did I really don't know okay
well we will we will have to know so
please uh give me your impressions
[Music]
okay uh what about Cali uh I think it's
true okay uh you know I think it's true
I feel like girl is the type to like
really keep things like like dear to her
you know sentimental yeah she's she'll
like keep you like you know yes like
that paper bag that you're still going
to get back
okay they're getting them back no matter
what yeah what about amen I say false
I'm saying false too
oh it's a split I've seen uh skirts as
short as belts before so that seemed
like um she was caught in a lie there
okay well I think that has been noted
down
oh okay okay he's very good record
I totally see you're getting like
scissors
you should have seen what I did to my
old toys oh my goodness yeah
do you still have like Sid from Toy
Story do you still have toys from your
childhood oh yeah yeah yeah like what
um I have like a like a cat he's like a
he's like a alley cat toy and he got a
hole I don't know if he got a hole or if
I cut it purposely so that I could show
him back up
um put it some lime green there's many
holes in your story aren't there many
holes
wow see see chat they do like like jokes
and puns
that just sounded kind of unbelievably
unbelievable but okay
okay we will go on with
one of my problems
okay reset and Stato
when living in Japan I befriended
somebody
to hang with their cash she might be
faking true you know she loves cats all
right
psychology where'd you meet him uh at
work when I had a side job uh in while
it was not the working holiday time
where I was living in Japan it was
before that so I had a little side job
and she was working there what type of
cat was it it was a Maine [\h__\h] it was
Maine [\h__\h] let's show you pictures uh
she actually had a picture of the cat on
her work desk was it a male or a female
cat what kind of work was it I think it
was a female cat
the work oh I think I shouldn't be
saying
um but yeah so I saw the picture what
color eyes did the cat have I think it
was yellow Maine Coon's kid have yellow
eyes
[Applause]
but did you become friends with her in
the end
well I mean foreign
but like I mean I first tried to become
friends like
well really because I knew she had a cat
but I guess she was nice so
why would you want to become real
friends with her yeah then you can see
that you're so friendly you always want
to be friends with everyone she wasn't
that interesting as a person
I can say that now because I don't think
she's watching but yeah so like
how many toes did the cat have
was the tail really fluffy I thought
that there's like six-toed cats
very big very fluffy what color was the
cat it was like brownish with uh I guess
some some dark brown with blue black a
little bit did it
yes what did the meow sound like
ah okay my cones have a very distinct
meow I don't think she meowed a lot she
was more of a quieter okay did she know
tricks no Maine Coons
I didn't see any tricks at least
I don't know you don't I don't normally
teach my cats tricks either I don't
think people teach their cats tricks my
cat used to know again
it was on so some cats no tricks
I'm hungry button
do they really know what they're doing
what was your favorite game to play with
the cat yeah uh we're not
really the type of person to even play
games with my own cats I had a question
like what is your logic behind friending
someone like just to see their cat like
you were planning to just go to their
house and like hang out at their house
or my logical my tactic yeah like like
uh like you were planning to go to their
house hopefully right in the end yeah
well we first like went to karaoke and I
didn't go to her place at that point I
was just like warming up to each other
getting to know each other uh and then
the second meeting I already went to her
place because we wanted to watch anime
what anime did you watch we watched
working do you know working Yamada yeah
yeah I don't know which season but
they're only the first I'm using
I don't know anymore because I think
there was three seasons was there I
thought that was two no business with
every season there was another
exclamation Oh yeah because the three
was like a different kind of story I
remember now a different title because
it's been almost one exclamation second
was two two third one had like a
different title I guess so yeah um
so the cat was yellow eyes with brown
and black fur did you notice anything
else like specific about the cat
[Music]
not that much
I feel like I can't get adult cats to
like me much
um unless I spend a lot of time with
them and I didn't get to spend that much
time did you bring did you bring this
friend a gift when you first went to
their house no that's unusual because
you always bring gifts to everybody
was it a Japanese friend yes
are they speak in English no last book
Japanese already so she always gives
gifts she's even given me gifts when she
first got here you gave me a gift last
time you always give gifts especially if
it's a cat you would have brought
something give me a gift like last like
look the last he gave me something
recently you gave me sweets yeah but I
think this is kind of something I
started doing in the past ah okay since
I joined the whole life I think because
I I don't think I was a big Gift Giver
before that because I had less money too
I was very broke and um
[Music]
I really I don't think that I've been
doing that for a long time I guess I've
been like you know bringing souvenirs
for all the Japanese members and so on
too but just because I won yeah I want
to leave a good impression for them but
it was quite expensive to get presents
for all the Japanese members for every
single one that I met so yeah I don't
think I could have done that in the past
all right cat question how many times
did you hang out with a cat oh two times
two times yeah because I I quit the job
pretty
you didn't stay friends after that no
I'm like I
I don't really I don't know I'm actually
surprised but I guess it's because you
know I'm still doing this job so I'm
still staying in touch with everybody I
don't know like once you're done with
some like
part of your life and you go move on to
the next one often you just like yeah
that's true which is okay so you said
your people drifting you know with the
cats twice oh and you went they're the
first time to watch anime what was the
second time what'd you guys do continued
watching working
so there's a only a little bit of time
between the two times you met the cat
the coaster each other did you live in
an apartment no was it nice was it cute
inside yeah it was I guess as girly as
you can make it but it's like a typical
one man one room okay
smaller than ours this show was good yes
but we really have to cut now
the cat's eyes were green you said right
yellow
okay
you can't get me there in game so let's
get some answers I mean what do you
think true
Callie what do you think
false oh excuse me
I have to say true the only thing that's
weird is the gift thing because I think
regardless you would have made a massive
effort to give something because that's
just how you are but I'm gonna say true
okay I I I I I feel happy that you have
that impression for me with the gifts
because I guess that makes me seem
welcome what do you call that sweet
I say true you know what about you I'm
gonna say true because I know how much
you miss your cats yeah
it was in Japan right we probably
haven't like seen your cats in like a
lot like a time frame like if you even
have oh that's true I should have asked
at that point I only had a family cat
but still you had a family cat so you
missed the cats I would understand if
you want to you know
okay so uh I think that was written down
by General thank you okay all right
thank you deadbeats from every story
that I say I want you to say oh I
remember hearing that
yeah yeah well and generally I wrote it
already in the pinned comment but guys
if you're in the chat no something is
true for a fact or you know for a fact
it was wrong for some reason please
don't like write it as that in the chat
you can like guess along but don't you
know you know don't ruin it okay reset
and Cali's first prom right
please read it all right so I played
drums in a contest with no experience
and saved the song single-handedly
what kind of I don't know about this was
it it was a battle of the bands at a
summer camp uh-huh yeah I watched you
play Groove coaster oh
all right
no no don't get me wrong the song was
still bad but if we didn't have drums it
would have been worse which song was it
yeah it was a cover song that we made up
okay yeah we had one rehearsal for it
and it went something like da da da
that was literally it and and we wrote
lyrics during our one rehearsal and I
was supposed to say it but I said guys
this sounds like ass without drums
because there's no rhythm and look with
the other instruments there was a violin
she wanted to join in and she's a
violinist and she was like well I can
play the violin maybe we could do that
so it was a violinist and then there was
a bass guitarist who played a little bit
of bass there was a male singer there
was me on the truck what were you
originally supposed to be because you
said the song originally didn't have
drums yeah that was supposed to be the
female singer and a female singer
but if they were originally not supposed
to be drums in that song anyway then why
was there a drum set because they just
had one there they had one prepared for
anyone in the bit in the background
bands that wanted to go and do their
thing did this drum set have a cowbell
attached to it no that is
did you not fix drunk it did you guys
end up winning no absolutely not there
was there was a voting system there were
only two other bands that entered so it
was us and two other bands and the other
bands were really good like they were a
legitimate bands that third
yeah because everyone came up to me
afterward and said thank God you were
there do your shoulders hurt dude you
carried that song
who are the other like people in the
band like did you were friends or what
yeah I had a female friend who played
the violin I kind of lost touch with her
a little while ago but she was really
cool she like got me into the the
deviantART thing oh the furry
commissions
yeah and then um there was a guy he was
the the singer the male singer Kelly
Kelly just one thing you do understand
that in case this is true you do want to
make us think it's a lie yeah okay
also with her gestures it sounds like
she's telling the truth okay like when
was it like how old were you like how
many death years
High School death High School okay
you have no experience with drums
otherwise this was the first time you
ever sat down no I just know what a
rhythm is maybe I'm not the best at
Groove coaster
oh
the mama that is that's all you did how
you calf muscles
how does it work how do you do the thing
how explain to us how you play a drum
can you do a paradiddle
okay
take a drumstick go boom boom and then
hit the the symbol is it a crash symbol
no
I was in the crowd I remember that I
found that
okay you remember Sushi man Chad
[Music]
any more questions this is tricky I'm
trying but it's like I
she was she's so excited telling the
story so it feels true I mean even the
deadbeats are saying it's true
and what happened so you signed up to be
like a band there right yeah afterwards
as you continue being a band no it was
just because we were friends and wanted
to be what a surprise yes good surprise
for first place no prize it was just
like this Glory so you dedicated your
time with no prize no it wasn't a little
summer camp I mean I mean it was like
one of those School summer camps it's
not like a camp in the woods is it like
a Bible Camp no no no no no like all the
school
oh my God it was Camp Rock
oh my gosh
oh thank you wait what we're the Jonas
Brothers there too
Yes actually oh my God yeah
[Music]
okay should we vote yeah sure okay well
it's not from Ina
gonna say this is false my gut feeling
is somehow telling me
story might be a little different from
what actually happened I don't know why
but it's just a taco senses okay it
might be wrong it might be off today but
okay yeah
CLC false then okay I'll say true
because I know you have the personality
of like [\h__\h] it yeah let's do it
what if like she was on something
different and she's telling a story
about something else that happened I I'm
changing things up I don't know that's
not allowed I'm still gonna say you're
not allowed I mean I mean yeah if it was
a true story you're not you're supposed
to tell the true story
around it was like I actually was the
violinist that would be stupid yeah
okay wait so good at saying true I'll
say true okay
I say it
true because you didn't you didn't
actually win anyway so
um right if it was if it was a lie I
should win like we went first place
and everybody collapsed
it was amazing okay not that that that's
like
movie in a plot
what makes you think false uh I don't
know it's weird that there's no prize
it's kind of weird that there's no prize
true also true no that's true I guess if
it's like a summer camp they use smaller
prizes like incentive yeah and a gold
sticker stuff yeah she said just the
glory yeah okay that's kind of cheap but
I love his kids like school kids they
just maybe they just want to prove it
usually a five dollar gift card yeah
like Battle of the fans usually they
have like you know first prize gets you
know extra like snacks or something even
like the smallest it wasn't in the
budget
Cali's making funny faces now okay
[Music]
um concluded we will go with the first
I'm a story okay when I it read all
those prompts I honestly was like what
the [\h__\h]
I'm not hearing you know stories that
almond tells of like her childhood yeah
it's like some of them are unbelievable
already
I'm curious okay first I'm a prompt
please read it I almost got struck by
lightning when my foot got stuck in a
pool
I used to live really close to like a
community pool and they let me like when
I asked my family I was like can I go
swimming it's really hot so I went
swimming in the pool I mean it's like
right next to the house so it wasn't
that far away but I wasn't really being
supervised and so like in the pool you
know how there's like a metal ladder
sometimes like sometimes have that I was
like swimming I was doing like flips
around the metal ladder under the water
like swimming through it and then
because you know as a kid you're like
swimming's fruit but isn't it like
really close to the wall it wasn't that
close to the wall oh okay
um and then it started to rain and then
it started to pour and my foot ended up
getting stuck like because it is pretty
small but like I I was I would try to
squeeze through
and so yeah it started to rain and there
was lightning that struck really really
close by holy [\h__\h] and I don't know if
you guys have ever like felt lightning
yeah like you can feel like the
electricity in the air you kind of feel
like your hair all like yeah
all of you
yeah scary I haven't experienced it but
I've read about it oh your hair stands
up and you can smell it yeah it feels
like like Goosebumps kind of what time
what time were you swimming at this pool
I think it was like towards the
afternoon probably yeah okay and was
there no lifeguard on duty then no the
no the community pools didn't have life
well you're the only one there I was the
only one there yeah did nobody help you
um
how did you get stuck wouldn't that also
be like a legal issue like if you have a
public place of swimming for a community
you would think that there would be
somebody there watching especially if
there's children it was like a you know
apartment complex sort of thing and
apartments
no I've lived at many apartment
complexes I have never seen a lifeguard
at any of them I've ever lived in an
apartment with the pool yeah I don't
think they necessarily come with
lifeguards yeah our cameras or locks on
the doors or anything to keep I don't
have cameras they might have had cameras
back then but you know usually pools
they like lock after a certain time and
then or if bad weather is coming or
maybe I'm thinking of hotels maybe no
was it on on the ground on on the roof
or so is on the ground above ground pool
or below ground wait what is oh it's a
below ground I guess yeah like it goes
it dips into the ground okay indoor pool
yeah it was raining we started raining
when it
when it started raining because it was
cloudy that day but it was like it was
hot anyways and then I decided let's go
for a swim were you scared I was scared
well I wasn't scared at first because I
was just you know like oh I'm doing
flips you know and the thingy and it's
normal because I go swimming a lot as a
kid but then when you know there's
thunder or lightning that's really scary
how long was the whole weather thingy
how long was it uh well I don't know
because then I went back inside after I
was able to get my foot unstuck
thankfully and so I don't remember how
long it lasted did you tell your family
what happened no
[Applause]
how deep was the water I think pools
like go maximum like seven feet or
something no like like when your foot
got stuck like it was at the deep end
yeah you're not supposed to we're trying
to climb out
was I trying to climb out yeah when I
got stuck no I was just uh I think I got
nervous it was I was like looking around
and for some reason my foot like slipped
in a really skinny part of the bar like
towards the bottom it got wedged there
okay how did you not drown first
how long were you holding your breath
underwater huh how long were you holding
your breath I told my breath for a good
amount of time are you under the water
fully submerged if it was the deep end
no not fully submerged okay but the
ladders don't go all the way down to the
Deep yeah they like they're pretty
I have a real question what swimsuit
where you work
first question how old were you
that's true that's true it's a good
question I was like around 10 I think
okay yeah
question rejected
question rejected what color was it I
used to wear like a like a hot pink
swimsuit I think what thing yeah because
you know I didn't buy my own clothes
one piece or two Piece One Piece okay
okay
I believe the part about the swimsuit I
don't think I believe the rest of the
story no I don't know like usually okay
let's vote then do the deep end of the
pools usually have a letter yeah yeah
they really do
okay really so Cali's going for Falls
I'm gonna say nah I'm gonna call you out
on this one
you know goes for
I'm gonna say true true
because I just feel like from the
previous you know links lots of dumb
stories that she's told like the amount
of times she like gotten away with like
yeah almost hit by lightning yeah but I
believe that okay
I don't know there's just something
about it like there's not enough
to it or something something not like
it's almost too believable like it's so
much I don't want to say it's mundane
but it's almost like two it's
unbelievable
wait what did everybody else say is that
true I've never truth is
I have no idea I'm gonna say
fault okay
I will say
true true okay okay okay okay okay okay
we're usually like split half half
it's so interesting yeah yeah that's the
way you win is just by saying false
every time yes it's like when you guess
in a multiple times yes I'll go for like
C and then you realize there's only two
options for all the questions
no not yet not yet not yet we're gonna
tell all the stars first okay okay this
is uh now I guess round two because
everybody told the story once right yeah
right yeah okay
let's Gaslight even more then in a
second story
[Music]
please read I borrowed and renewed a
single book from the library for over a
year I believe that false right away
which book which you wouldn't remember
to return it
you wouldn't have remembered to return
he would have kept it until you were
like oh I need to return that no I used
to go to the library a lot when I was in
like Junior High High School oh okay
yeah because I live really close to like
the the local library and it was um it
was like one of those rare well back in
the day it was pretty rare to have like
the digital illustration like like book
right that's like one of the first I
mean that's the book that I like um
first saw a crew watch Papa's already
okay and then like I didn't I want to
keep like looking at the art inside of
it because it's right there was that in
your library
yeah they have it it's called like um
Japanese comic girls too I'm sure some
some people in chat will know it's like
it has like how like Pro illustrators
like like their uh painting processes
and stuff I just like happened to find
it like near all the mangas and stuff
was it a school like no it was a public
library
um
it's like translated to English because
it's like localized for here wow all I
had was like Curious George books
yeah
but it was a really tiny section and
they wouldn't have something so specific
no they had it
but would Ina ever lie about
Kruger
yeah but like it's like
I'm looking at because that's like
around the time I really you know start
a digital drawing cute did you have to
pay a fine
um no because I could renew the book
like before after I return it I asked
them to renew like my little boring like
time oh yeah you can renew like how how
much longer you can was there a charge
anyway though it was free yeah oh
because it's not Public Library as long
as you have the library card you can go
and like they go Peep and then your
library card cost something oh I don't
know because I was like still in like
junior high or something so my family
all went to make a library card together
junior high is that when she started a
digital drawing
[Music]
I don't know when it came out but yeah
the book itself already had like a bit
of you know you can see that people have
read it a couple times okay you know
again yeah this time for you if you're
telling a True Story You're supposed to
make those fingers a lot
just so you know just just you make all
of them seem like they're super true
just because you want us to think the
wrong thing
we're right now
Public Library do you have to you said
you paid to renew it no you didn't pay
to read it no okay
I think I don't know if there's like a
deposit for the library courses because
I haven't gone to the library in a while
like recently did you just read you
would not return it because you wanted
to continuously read it over and over
and over again even though it was just
illustrations but or did you just forget
it no because it's like no I didn't
forget if I forget I would get fine
because you know if I return they'll be
like oh you're overdue but if you renew
it you're allowed to you know borrow it
again for like yeah but why did you not
just give it back you wanted to keep it
forever
in the book
Junior High what is it
in high school no Junior High no she
said high school she said Junior High
High School junior high school maybe
she's not lying what is Junior High
maybe she's not lying
so you were you just why did you keep it
because that was around the time I got I
was really interested
as a reference basically because it
showed like how they went step by step
I was like you know figuring out how to
do it myself and I was just looking at
the book all the time okay I've read
that book actually and that's not what
is in the book what is it
trying to trip her up and I can't do
that so how many chapters is in it I
don't remember how many people are in
there though of course how many pages I
don't know
I read that book
it's actually not that much
[Laughter]
gaslighting Kelly
it's actually I'm gonna watch how long
she aren't you Cali doubt myself that's
right
have we got what we need I think so okay
I think well
uh Anna what do you think
uh false okay I'm gonna say true true I
will say also true
Papa was in this book yeah it's like
true she would never lie about that if
she did she'd feel pretty bad she would
feel very bad okay
we have made our decisions we're moving
on to the second story from goodbye
[Music]
I can tear an apple and have with just
my bare hands oh it's not actually that
hard
like if you press it in a certain angles
anyone can do it technically okay but
girls are awake
how do you hold it yeah
okay no no
it's false
she doesn't know maybe she's trying to
twist you can twist I'm sure you've seen
a video
how many times have you done this
[Music]
[Applause]
I've done it
12 times 12 or 13. that's so specific
yeah that's so specific yeah
I can see girl completely like fumbling
around with the apple and not being able
to do it maybe something she can test
her grip strength on your your arm do we
have an apple oh my God they brought in
an apple
how did that come to you know happen the
first time don't remember I think I I
think I saw
I think I saw a did you know I was like
there's no way that can be true oh you
know like life hacks that I learned that
changed my life forever kind of thing oh
life hacks I'm not really called
breaking an apple life hands more like a
party trick
if you have no knives exactly and you
don't know you don't want to bite it
because it's a life like a life hack it
would be like a way to eat the apple
without like leaving the core
degradable you don't gotta worry about
that these shitty life hacks that you
can't even pull a life hack but they
call it live so I do believe it might
have been in the video trendy is there
something that you do to prepare the
Apple like maybe use your fingernail to
like bash it against the side of
something oh okay
and you could use like a corner of a
table in does somebody have money here
have an experience breaking an apple
like that no I remember seeing a video
on it though
they're pretty easy to smash though I
mean if I were to have an apple I want
to eat it I'll just eat it like without
cutting it my teeth are sensitive though
if it's cold and then I don't want to
like I don't know biting into a whole
Apple it overwhelms my mouth so I'd
rather have it broken so well if this
ends up being true after the stream
maybe we will really have to get an
Apple yeah and you will prove us if your
claim was easy
easy
we'll have proof
what are we gonna do are we do we need
more questions or I don't know I feel
like
I feel like my mind's made up have you
ever showed the trick to somebody like
in real life um like a family if someone
we can call who can say
mom is that you I could Rock I told my
mom about it oh she was like I don't
believe you oh which I don't know and
you should I agree with you no you
didn't show her I know I told her it was
possible I was like did you know you can
you can oh
tear an apple apart I guess she never
made you prove it
okay
okay well let's vote
[Music]
how old around like what age you know
were you when you tried to do this
um
if it was like one of those trendy
hashtag trendy videos it's probably
fairly fairly recent barely okay
recently hashtag whatever the little
shorts or whatever within the last five
years
I don't know yeah
oh my Instagram algorithm has been so
good to me lately that's where I found
that Lord of the Rings
she sent me a lot of the Rings meme last
night that's so proud I'm so happy
sometimes it's good sometimes it's good
okay
all right let's vote I think it's true
you think it's true Kelly thinks it's
true
false you know thinks it's false
I
I want to see it
you want to believe it's true I don't I
will say it's false until proven true
that's such a thing that girl would like
like these muscles
when she like if she were to prove it to
us later on she'll be like if it didn't
work she'll like blame it on the Apple
you better say that girl's gaming grip
ain't strong enough but have you seen
her Play Rhythm games oh those fingers
are strong
her ring fit ring fit uh what's your
weak in the ring fit I didn't she's I
think powerful good stamina but um
well okay I made up my mind though I'll
say it's false
okay
let me check up if everything's okay
with janma
Gemma you believe me right
she's nodding I can I can feel it well
well thank you I can feel that oh No
Just chuckling okay next kiwawa story do
you want one what's up I know okay
[Music]
my family was robbed on my birthday
because I thought it was my brother what
what's up
story
all right context to explain
from where
so you let the Intruder in like you let
the Intruder in
I mean I guess there's a way uh I could
have maybe prevented it but maybe I
would have been
attacked in that case what were you
doing when the events were unfolding I
was sleeping we were all sleeping it was
at night
um the night oh it doesn't yeah I'm on
my birthday night on my of my birthday
my 15th birthday
and we were uh my family we were in a
building everybody was sleeping at night
okay what was stolen
money I think only money because yeah my
mom like checked uh in the morning like
so we woke up
I mean we we woke up in the morning and
I I was the first one to wake up I think
uh it was getting bright and I saw even
a cat
passing through
and I was like why is there a cat here
and then my mom came up
and we were like that's when we realized
why are the cloves everywhere on the
ground
and then my mom checked her like
wherever the money would be and there
was no money left why was there a cat
was the cat from outside because the the
robber opened up the doors and kept and
the Stray Cat just came in yeah
I think that she's pretending to not
have her story straight I think that
this is amazing no it's just something
to be a bad liar tell me one question
you thought it was your brother so you
saw this person you weren't sleeping you
woke up to them uh I woke up several
times at night because I heard noises
and I thought it came from my brother
because uh I heard like doors
like somebody trying to open a door what
that's what was what my interpretation
was but I thought they weren't trying to
open the entrance door to me it just
sounded like my brother was probably
trying to open the toilet door whatever
he was stuck in the toilet in the night
did you hear footsteps
no footsteps were they heavy footsteps
no no no footsteps at all no footsteps
so this person took their shoes off they
followed the Europeans they gotta be
quiet in the night they're trying to be
quiet so this Rob this thief took took
their shoes off to tiptoe around the
house and left them at the door where
was your room
um relative to the front door
um so this was like a narrow tall
building kind of like Japanese style you
know and
um
where my room was I was not sleeping in
my room
but my brother was sleeping in the room
where I was supposed to be in but I was
not in that room where were you I was in
the living room why were you sleeping in
the living room because the bed was
really uncomfortable so you heard
dorsling which you didn't hear footsteps
they would have had yeah
sleeping most of the time the sounds
that woke me up were the the toilet door
sounds which I guess in the end wasn't
the toilet
so you sleep on your couch every night
because your bed is uncomfortable
there you go it was not at home
what what
it was a vacation
home vacation place vacation house what
was it what did it look like on the
inside
it looked like I don't know how to
describe that uh like a carpet on the
floor
the carpets on the floor for sure it's
uh it was uh I guess like
how to describe that
it's like it was in Morocco so oh what
was it in the city or in the countryside
City oh okay that I mean that makes
sense
[Music]
why are you in Morocco because my mom
wanted to go to Morocco even though I
didn't want to go that would make sense
if they only stole the money because you
know not really any valuables in a rent
a home or would there be because if
you're going you're going on a vacation
you're probably gonna go out to dinner
you're gonna bring like nice jewelry or
a nice dress that's a good point a nice
watch
I'm sure you brought your like phones
and maybe laptops uh yeah so your mom
wanted to travel for your birthday yes
no not for my birthday it just happened
to be on my birthday
hmm
everyone's family's different so I don't
know about it I think you're pretending
to be a bad liar so I think this is true
I think the story is true
because
okay any more questions I'm telling this
with a lot less confidence I don't know
the footsteps thing makes me question
too because I would think if I was if I
was going to be a thief I wouldn't think
to take my shoes off to well she said
that there are carpets so it's likely I
mean quietly with shoes on carpet was it
carpeted floor like completely wall to
wall or was it a carpet on a hardwood
floor or a tile floor it was not a full
carpet no no it was just Carpets on a
normal floor also yeah Kiara is very
picky about where she sleeps she needs
to sleep on a nice comfy place
yeah that's so true
I just I couldn't sleep well so I
changed to the living room and
film
then where was the money being kept I
think well
I'm not sure where my mom kept the money
because I didn't have any money so it
was only my mom's money that was stolen
um I think probably in her wallet that
was baby in her
when they're back probably not bad what
about your brother's money he ain't no
money either I don't think we brought
any money because we were the kids we
were pretty young I guess the stream
just couldn't we're back
again curse throughout the studio not
our fault that was a problem YouTube
it was kind of funny yesterday because I
went to Lonnie's place yesterday for off
club and then like we had everything set
up like 40 minutes before the stream
started as soon as we were trying to
like hit the go live button like that
you know the YouTube slide button it has
to like turn red yeah
red or blue something like that to for
you to like press it and then you go
left in turn that's a lie you said red
but it turns blue I don't know I don't
really like it it's blue and then it
turns red okay no that but that's not
the story
I was like oh no
well I believe I believe yeah your story
you believe it's truth yeah I say true I
say songs
false Ina says
it's rough I'm thinking
thinking time move
I'm gonna say
[Music]
false okay free pause one true okay okay
next story Gemma has written the donut
thing yes okay next story from Cali
uh please read it all right so me and my
sister were scouted as child actors but
it was a scam oh
how old were you this time gosh we were
probably Junior High ish yeah it was one
of those things where like they were
looking for kids at the mall and they
give them like a liar yeah like you
could be a star you look like you could
be a child actor yeah right what kind of
like you said flyer but uh was there
people who came up to you and gave you
the flyer or was it I don't know it was
my sister that got scouted to be honest
but then we called them and they said
that I could come too because of course
it was a skip but how did you find out
it was a scam no we went we went did the
whole song and dance so
So eventually you know we looked at the
flyer and whatnot and we had Mama more
you drive us we couldn't find where it
was because the address was ridiculous
but it was in some creepy like Warehouse
district and we go in there and all
these kids and their families are
gathered in this point but they're
showing like a video on the screen where
they like they had an actor from like a
child one of the like Disney one of the
Disney Channel shows I'm not gonna say
who it is what but that sounds like a
summer camp I know right if they had
someone like that it was it was on a
screen it was on a screen oh so they
just stole something they just paid him
money to like you know advertise their
thing and like show up at their summer
camp but that was about the extent of it
um and then eventually you know we got
called into the back and they're like
here are all of our plans you get access
to our website and we lose jobs oh no
child actors and my sister and I really
wanted it so it's so close and poor Mama
Maury is just looking at us and she
loves us so much she says all right well
let's try it it was on Godly expensive
and Mama Mori was not making a lot of
money back then you would have to pay
for your child to yeah yeah to access
like the website or whatever for jobs
listing it's like yes yeah just for the
chance of getting a job and so she wrote
a check and then we went home to try and
like figure out the site and it didn't
work and so we tried to cancel the check
right but eventually you know they
called us back and said no no it's fine
we'll get it to work for you and then
they eventually got it to work but it
just turned out the site really just
didn't get any jobs posted on it at all
eventually just made it away
[Music]
yeah I'm gonna pay back Mama Mori for
that
um
wow how much was it can you say yeah it
was about well she got she gave in to
the cheapest plan it was about
it was about 1 500 per kid what was the
highest yeah five grand per kid good
yeah it broke my heart as I grew up and
even on that day even as like a young
kid I like got sick to my stomach I like
thought I was gonna throw up because I
was so upset
because my mommy oh what I think we all
met your mommy yeah yeah she's very nice
very supportive
she's incredibly supportive no it's fine
now because I've definitely paid her
back she's with my assistant now that's
her job okay happy ending yeah many
years later
many more questions
no I think that's I mean I can believe
it because I remember being in a mall
and they have like they do modeling too
yeah oh my God you're so cute you're so
cute Mommy Daddy can come you know you
just take those pamphlet and whatever
child models I've never had that happen
in Austria but I've had that happen in
Japan on the streets there's like in
Harajuku especially there's like Scouts
who are like oh you want to be a model
or like a singer or whatever actor or
whatever yeah but it's it's usually not
a big place that does that they wouldn't
have much money
[Music]
I don't know about how it is in America
so but it seems to be a thing you know
yes I guess yeah
[Music]
okay should we vote I don't think I
can't think of any questions
[Music]
I'll say true true I'll say true too
yeah that's it true okay I don't think
she would lie about me yeah don't say
true okay what
we'll find out later if that was really
true but you're definitely convinced us
all damn
okay okay next I'm a prompt is oh yes
yeah I almost got lost at sea on a big
floaty with my friend
how did what do you mean you almost got
lost at sea uh well the we were on a
floaty on the beach like at the beach in
the water and we kind of just weren't
paying attention and it drifted pretty
far oh like pretty far how far
while the people on the shore they look
like really small like ants so I don't
know maybe
uh I mean as a kid it seems pretty far
like okay probably less than half a mile
though but it seems pretty far how'd you
make it back
we started swimming we got out and we
paddled with our legs you know started
kicking
where were your parents in this where
are the lighthouse I don't know they
were not watching us that's for sure
again she's rapping watched in the water
maybe we shouldn't let her into the
water anymore how high were the whips
how wavy was it I don't think it was
that high it was not a very choppy day
okay
where in the world were you where in the
world yeah like were you in America I
was in America yeah South uh the west
coast East Coast the East Coast just
chilling yeah which season like which
month was this
you remember maybe summer probably
summer
was there like animals in the water not
that I remember nobody how old were you
um probably like eight or seven that
young and nobody was anybody else in the
world you paddled back to the beach
and nobody saw two little people I guess
not maybe they didn't see us but what'd
you do it's a floaty what do you mean
did you drag it behind you or did you
just let it oh we were kicking behind it
like you know pushing it up well then if
there's a current I don't know if young
people would have had the Plus usually
Beaches they have like a little border
for like the safe area
well I've noticed that and depending on
the beach sometimes the border is just
kind of like on the water so you can
accidentally swim over it that's true
but still is it a busy Beach it was
really busy yeah it was really busy uh
was there so there should have been a
lifeguard yeah probably I think there
probably was but I don't know maybe they
didn't care or
um what color were the floaties uh it
was just like a big floaty and it was
blue so it was like the same colors what
shape was it I think it was Square maybe
probably Square yeah Square floating I
mean there are many shapes of floaties
but you have a square foot she says big
floaty and a lot of big floaties are a
square shape yeah is it the type that
has a hole or the type that you lay on
top of
uh no no hole
uh what color was it yellow blue
both of them there's only one it's like
a big one oh not like floaties like arm
floaties like uh like the ones a pattern
on it
so I mean there was like a pattern from
like it had like a little cushion marks
I think yeah and and you say it's square
but was it like shaped like a square
with like a unicorn on top no nothing
just hot Square no how big was it like
size wise probably as tall as I am today
I would say like lengths okay so it was
a little raft yeah yeah but it was
inflatable
so were you a sufficient efficient at
swimming what's the word ah fishing did
swimming I mean I used to swim a lot as
a kid so yeah I guess so only a friend
yeah she's pretty good whose raft was it
your rafter your friend's raft uh
mine so you bought the raft or your
family bought the wrap yeah family
proficient
so you didn't rent the raft no okay
I don't know I have a hard time
imagining that nobody would have noticed
two kids floating out that far that's
really dangerous because even even
though sometimes like older people that
float out pretty far and if they notice
any kids they'll when you notice you
were so far away were you not scared as
a child scream hey I guess it was more
like oh [\h__\h]
um
that's really young though seven that's
I didn't try to get help just out of
kindergarten I I think I might have
tried to get help yeah but I realized
that it was like too far and I couldn't
tell I have bad eyes right now so I
think my eyesight was pretty bad then
too
let's mulch already okay unless somebody
else to ask questions
I think it's a lie oh
okay Kelly thinks it's still alive
[Music]
I feel like it is false as well okay
something something something just
I'm trying to figure out if there was a
difference from the way she told the
story previously like the last story she
was definitely more broad punctual about
the last story yeah I feel and this one
is more like it
yeah true so the same time like I've
swam in the sea a lot and
imagining like two you know kids it's
like seven eight like swimming
and the ocean with like the ties Plus
what's a pretty big floaty too like
people will think it's easier to swim
with the big floaty but if there's like
waves and stuff
like even as an adult so if she like
drifted that four I don't know if she
could have made it was there no like
were there no uh you guys were the only
ones there wasn't like any older
siblings or friends or kids I mean we we
both had brothers that were the same age
so were they swimming I don't remember
if they were swimming so your family
didn't say Hey Big Brothers Go and Keep
eyes on the little ones they probably
did but you know as kids they just do
whatever which swimsuit were you wearing
then
was it the same or I think it was a
different one hmm which color was that
one
um maybe black I don't remember
that's true I don't remember my shirt I
wouldn't have remembered how do you look
at like pictures or something to be
honest I would never remember yeah okay
well so Ino said what
true or false false Buddha says
[Music]
um am I the last one to go or can I go
last
I can't remember what I said last time
I I guess I'll say
it's generally a believable like a thing
that could definitely happen
and I'm a
H I'll say
[Music]
ah okay let's say true
I mean if she wasn't able to swim back
like that distance I'd be amazed like a
seven year old a mile no I said I said
less probably less than half a mile less
than a half but it seems a lot like a
lot as a kid I don't know when you're
like seven or eight like in the middle
like the ocean may look calm from far
away but the waves are still pretty were
you scolded after that I guess we're
done with questioning
I don't think so God damn it this girl
did you have parents uh
this is sort of
okay well I guess what Donald question
even um
but I think like if she said it was calm
so if if the waves are really strong
then I think it would have been very
difficult for a child to get back yeah
but since it was calmer
it was cold but the ocean even if it
looks kind of like how did you get back
how did you swim back yeah uh well I
didn't know you guys already answered
right yeah
well I didn't know uh I didn't know this
at the time but you're supposed to swim
diagonally to the current but because
like of the wind or the waves that day
we'd actually drifted diagonally anyway
so we were like Sideways from the people
on the beach like where our people were
so we had to actually swim diagonal and
that I think that really helped us
unintentionally it was windy so there
would it would have been choppy I mean
that I mean the water has a current and
you know Echoes but you said it was calm
and if there was wind there was enough
wind there's like a little bit of wind
because it's the ocean the ocean's never
calm it looks calm but there's always
there's some glasses
ocean was incredibly calm at all times
no matter how far you went out
especially if near the beaches though
there's always waves because it always
goes like that so there's gonna be
always a little bit of I don't know
about American beaches but Maldives was
calm everywhere
maybe because uh yeah I think depending
on the difference yeah it will be
different yeah
um what were your recordings
one last question that doesn't I will
not change my answer but I just want to
know after all these like traumatic
water experiences I always I'm not like
traumatized by now do you go into the
water without but I have something I
have like nightmares waves like crashing
on me like a lot it happens really often
but uh I don't mind going into the water
even now that's a scary dream I would
like to say it has nothing to do with
the insurance
also I had nothing to do with this
okay okay now we're going to the third
round which is
Nina's last story is
[Music]
the chorus while only attending a single
lecture during the entire semester nope
what course
it was a
Photoshop Digital Arts course oh okay
Photoshop Digital Arts course yeah I
believe you could answer that yes by
being a good artist
I've been to one of those classes before
and they're not very in-depth like it's
just stuff you can learn pretty easily
so this was like University oh what were
you majoring okay yeah
classified
I know
um
I had because
um I took
like was it five or six courses per
semester in my first three-ish years and
I kind of want to take it easy because I
kind of was really sick of school but
they really like what I was studying
so I was like I'll take it easy but then
in order to be a full student you had to
take at least
three courses per semester or something
like that so I had
specific
major courses I have to take for my
degree but you also have to fill in
the semester to be a full-time student
so that I can get a discounted train
pass for the year that was your reason
oh yeah I see
um
assume since you aced it does that mean
at the end there was like some kind of
test
it was an assignment-based class that
makes sense yeah oh okay so it was like
per project yeah and that's that's it
uh-huh
and so you didn't get marked absent if
you missed a lecture you only intended
was this so you could did you take it
like online or you just didn't go at all
no it was in in school class like you
turned to one I went to the very first
one I realized
I don't really need to be here to learn
Photoshop that's very easy yeah but then
I did the assignment because I saw to
pass the course yeah okay where'd you
see the assignments online there's like
a web portal for each class
some some classes uses some classes
don't so
you could just choose not to go to
English I mean it wasn't really
attendance like
Paul said we don't mark down attendance
for this class was the professor female
or male it's a male Professor was he old
no middle age I think what was his hair
color
I guess because you only went once yeah
does that make sense
um
so how many assignments did you do
roughly roughly
um
it was like five or six during the
semester all right what kind of give me
an example of what one of the
assignments would have been a bit well
the assignment was we would take a
normal like you know Disney coloring
book like the lines coloring book and
you know how the coloring books only
have like lines right we would think
that in Photoshop
not just we're not filling in the lines
we're imitating like a famous artist
Style on Photoshop like painting
Photoshop classes teach you more about
like the using Photoshop just more no it
was like a Digital Arts
um media course so use Photoshop to to
pick all the assignment was like getting
two animals uh-huh like pictures of
animals and we're merging it so it looks
believable were there any logo
assignments
no it was not a graphics design class
okay okay
did you learn how to use the mesh tool
she would have already known again yeah
I already knew how to use all the food
it was it was a Photoshop class yeah
it's like a kind of like using you know
digital software for like media and
painting and stuff for painting mainly
okay those technical cost of as an art
class but like more on the digital side
than the traditional side well what
other stuff did they make you draw
um I don't think there was that many
drawing ones it was a lot of like more
like photo manipulation and stuff like
adjusting like the levels and huge
saturation to make like matching
pictures together to make it look like
it was like just one picture when all
the different items were from different
pictures that's not painting though yeah
it's not a painting course it's like a
digital art yeah Digital Arts course
like not going to the lecture though
wait how long did you use Photoshop
before that
so since like Junior High because that's
when I started learning digital art So I
self-taught myself Photoshop yeah not
anything else she already knew
everything all of like the Digital Arts
programs and stuff and like I knew what
I had to do something you were paying a
Photoshop did for how long has Photoshop
have the our adobe's how long have they
had the monthly fee because you have to
pay monthly was it if you're going to
school they'll cover that for you no but
if she knew about it if she's had she's
known Photoshop for so long and there
was no you had the money to pay the
monthly fee unless the monthly fee was
recently there was no monthly fee back
in the day yeah it was it one time it
was a one-time program I've used very
expensive Adobe CS2 for many years many
many years until I started paying the
monthly fee
I believe it I say true all right I'll
say true and I said false the other one
but I actually think maybe the first one
was true
going back and thinking but I can't
change my answer so I'll say for this
one yeah all true or they all false uh
now there has to be one true one right
here okay at least one Cali says I think
it's true okay I think
I feel like hmm
is it Ina like to not go to school yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I mean with college courses you don't
have to be there they don't you already
paid for it maybe so as long as you do
you're wasting your money I guess but if
you are if you already know how to do it
yeah and I took a class that was just
like that where you just had to do the
assignments pretty much and that was
like the whole class wait why would you
sign up for the class so if you're any
new Photoshop if you have to fill an
elective easy grades
no no if I had to keep the course like
like any course in there I would put one
where I can get easy grades what was the
previous story
in someone's face Library
okay
I think I said the library one was true
okay I will say this one's false like
don't you guys do that too like
if you have to choose an option class
you would always take the one that you
can you know
not have to do much work
is do you have to pay for University so
wouldn't you want to get the most out of
it by taking something that you're
actually where you learn learn something
from it you're just trying to get it if
I'm just trying to fill in the space
[Music]
this one
oh I once used a body massager and my
finger to whip my eggs true oh
girl cool
that's the wrong one
it's one of those uh gun massagers and
it's got like the different attachments
on the end I can't believe it with the
juice
I don't think it really matters because
you don't need an attachment was it
round or it came with a round one so you
used it without an attachment uh I mean
you don't have to I probably used one
that was like easy to clean so one of
the either the bullet shaped one or the
where was your whisk
dirty that's why that's the rest of it
uh I was too lazy I was too lazy to wash
the Whisk so you just so I had a finger
but didn't you wash the body massager
did you keep it easy no I didn't touch
the eggs
also she used her fingers yeah
if you ended up just leaving the
massager in the in the sink after all
you have done the same with the Whisk
you don't get the the massager icky
[Music]
oh okay well that's not that bad you
could do that with your hand again
because when you say whip eggs that's
like you know making fluffy eggs they
cut it down by quite a bit I had this
was a pretty long one so yeah I was
making an omelette
why did you not just uh because I know
when I'm just making an omelette I can
just whip the eggs to the fork yeah why
did you not just use it how old were you
okay this is racing because I saw it I
died on the internet and I said wow that
look cool don't always follow the [\h__\h]
on the internet
[Music]
why not
I mean it works doesn't it
didn't work doesn't it whose body
massager was it uh mine
you don't have one with the icky I have
one that you can put like there's like
sleeves and then there's like this whole
thing you put it uh you put your arms
through and then it massages the back
but
you know they have ones that are like
which which brand is that body massager
I couldn't tell you uh-huh
uh-huh
what round is yours
what how did you buy it where did you
buy it I like Amazon probably like
Target I don't know how to remember
how recent though do you remember where
you bought that jacket you're wearing
yes you do yes yes I do remember oh well
when I came back from Indonesia
doing sick
I still believe it you do believe it
yeah I don't think we need to think too
hard about it wait what was what was
girl's second question again
uh she had the skirt and then the album
the Apple okay okay I'll say True to
this one because I think I said falls to
the other one yeah I think I said false
to the apples this seems true this is
like something you'll be like
just try like randomly
does gouda cook though
absolutely she cooks yeah right she told
me yesterday that she cooks yeah she was
gas loving yesterday
oh how do you like your eggs I guess
scrambled that's how you prefer them
I'm not picky she was making no you're
not picky as long as they're cooked how
many eggs was it
um one that's really you do one egg and
one egg white
yeah it's a one egg no one egg one whole
egg with a yolk and then one egg white
so two eggs but then only one
put in your sink yeah yeah down the
drain
I'm very particular I like my miracles
how did you season it
salt
it's very normal what kind of stuff do
you have
I don't know if this is it again
classified I classified salt
salt is that salt yeah was that it just
the eggs no like veggies or protein
powder protein powder powder
have we heard of her doing stuff like
that with protein powder yeah I believe
it
Apple
she needs those games for the Apple okay
let's vote
let's start from right now I think the
first one was a lot oh man I was like
true because they said falls for the
other ones true
okay I don't believe the body massager
part
which is the main part it looks like I'm
gonna have to show you
guys I mean yeah I'm gonna beat your
eggs making your breakfast tomorrow
breakfast eggs with my body's massager
seasoned egg omelette for breakfast I
want flavor they finger flavored with a
shark fingers it said good what do you
say about your own story do you believe
it my own story
I forgot about it up until now
you know I said it's true true yeah okay
oh next is me all right last QRS story
I almost got into a famous Japanese idol
group but rejected them why'd you reject
them
um because I lost interest
in being an idol or in the group
in being an idol at this group okay did
it become famous afterward the group
yeah the group was uh it was a new group
but they
um the
they come from a very famous big
conglomerate is that a one yeah yeah of
uh Idols AKB
48.
yes
so why'd you decline
uh same question I guess
um
why did I decline because I lost
interest
um
I guess when I originally auditioned
I I guess I never was really that
um motivated to begin with
I mean I really wanted to become an idol
but not in this Idol group
did they just not fit your your personal
image
yeah yeah were there a ton of girls yes
oh like a bunch of girls yeah I see
that's it could be groups for you 48
groups
[Music]
I believe it like 48 girls
no no they they don't uh that's just
maybe they started out with 48 but uh
uh they it doesn't necessarily have to
be 48 girls
questions
you said you weren't motivated to be an
idol at this point you were no longer
motivated no I really wanted to become
an idol
but not at this group
so your will to become one was strong
but not strong enough to join this group
yeah because I like yeah I have strong
opinions
I can kind of Envision that yeah why did
you try out then
because
I wasn't so sure at that point
and I also thought that even though I
don't like them that's that's exactly
why I can improve them
because I see it from a different point
of view
and yeah like a brain but couldn't you
have joined it and then you could have
left it if you didn't like it like I
feel like you would have been the type
of person to give it a shot anyway I
feel like it would have been contract
difficult yeah we was there like a uh if
you can say I I don't know about that
part like there were several rounds and
I rejected before the last round
but I was able to move on but I didn't
want to move on so I don't know like you
know I I wouldn't want to have join and
then left because that would have been
like a big commitment I'm like I guess I
got a little bit of cold feed maybe to
understand you said you got to the last
round not the last round there's several
rounds I don't know how many rounds
there were in total but I see so almost
got into a famous uh yes
um yes so you didn't really like quite
get in just yet yeah and just decided to
stop before you got to the final round
yes
I don't know
feel like you would have seen it through
all the way and then decided I don't
know it just
from what I know about you I don't know
if you would have ducked out beforehand
no I would believe it though yeah if I
was in this situation I would say true I
believe it
because you know I don't know if I've
ever said this on stream I almost said
that with the Hall of Edition you like
yeah you must say no I oh I was like I
was like am I okay how about you almost
say no when the crew
like I don't know okay I wouldn't know
yeah yeah so I was like
I was like can I can I really do this
like I started like that myself a lot
okay like right before I got you know
you got in message I was like I was like
do I send this like I don't think I can
do it anymore
do you still have a draft in your emails
I don't know if I do but oh it'd be
interesting really but like it was
really scary because I was literally
like writing the email and yeah
I got it so I was just like I guess it's
kind of too late have we all shared the
story when we got the the email sorry
this is like taking away and I'm just
curious now about everybody yeah where
was everyone when they got the email or
should we I would check every day yeah I
was I was crying alone in my apartment
and then I saw the email I was like yeah
I was teaching my last class of the day
and I just sat down at my desk and I was
really tired and I checked and it said
we need to talk to you in like 30
minutes
[Music]
they were like they didn't even tell us
over the email I think they were just
like we need to talk like oh yeah oh
yeah yeah can we have a meeting with you
like today yeah um
I remember because I was like wrapped in
my blankets like not being well quote
unquote napping but I was just looking
at my phone like in the dark with just
like the phone like on the side I was
just like man do it do I do this or not
and then like it got the message I was
like Wow fake the best yeah
mine will try it out yeah oh I think I
was uh I think it was it's probably like
the day that you know the day like this
isn't happening oh this isn't happening
whatever and then it was that day where
it came in
see it was in the kitchen or something
it is like the rough like time of like
oh we'll get back to you like within
the end of that so we're just like it
was so much emotion I got this I don't
got this I don't know this maybe today
to me we'll get back to you in a month
and then they messaged me that two days
later uh let's talk now you're in let's
go yeah okay anyways yeah yes yes I say
true yeah I say true yeah everybody says
it's true
[Music]
okay
I don't know anymore
okay next one is Kelly with her last
story
[Music]
set three pigs free at high school all
right I know it sounds unbelievable but
this is an actual thing you could do in
my school so we really like we're into
the school pranks the seniors always did
a high school prank all right so usually
it was like one homeroom class would be
like we want to do it and like nobody
had done one the previous year right and
I was like that's so boring like we were
waiting for like what are the seniors
gonna do and so I was like all right I
volunteered to do the prank and so my
whole homeroom class got involved I
wasn't really really good friends with
everyone but everybody got into it they
were like oh yeah let's do it and so I
like didn't know what to do so I went on
the internet and I searched up
high school high school senior pranks
and one of them came up where you're
supposed to set three pigs free in
school and you oh sorry Mike you type um
you tape the number number card to each
Pig right there's one two and four I
don't know what free is exactly
good right well that's really cool we'll
also be wondering where the two is
oh
I'm never gonna live that guy
ever never ever
just the way you said it okay
there are a lot of questions you can ask
about this so ask away so where are the
pigs from all right so
I live in Texas or I come from Texas
so my uncle and his family have a farm
about
50 miles north of my city and it's they
have pigs they have cows horses and pigs
and also chickens and so they happen to
have exactly three pigs she's telling
this with such an excited face man it is
crazy so I didn't tell we didn't tell my
uncle but I texted my cousin and I said
hey this is what I want the senior prank
to be what do you think and he was like
let's go he was like 18 at the time he's
not really rambunctious we were like
about is it not I mean zero I'm zero
years old and whatever but
zero plus 18. right I'm no years old no
plus 18. Reaper Farms are pretty pretty
crazy they're pretty much the same as
human Farms though so so my cousin was
like all right I'll drive him over in
the truck and so he just told he made up
some [\h__\h] story to tell his dad and
was just like all right you know we'll
bring the pigs over and the thing is
maybe this makes it less exciting but at
my school because senior pranks are a
big thing you you do tell the staff
about it so like someone has to know
right yeah yeah yeah so you tell the
school that you want to do a senior
prank and you like pitch the idea to
them right and at first they said no and
I had to make an appeal to go in and be
like please let me do this prank it's
super funny I had to give them all the
information about my cousin's Farm Etc
um and so you know we did that and so
you know they they gave my cousin a call
because of course I wasn't gonna give
him my uncle's number right so I gave
him my cousin's phone number and he was
like oh yeah you know we we have this
one use info on our farm and whatever
and so he brought over the pigs like
right before first period and of course
we had like one of the staff like one of
like what is it like
one of the counselors yeah come to the
back and like lead the pigs enemies set
them free and they were super hungry oh
so they were looking for food they
weren't like evil evil Hungry Pigs okay
you know sometimes you see like evil
hungry but these were like regular
regular pigs they weren't too
rambunctious but like they were still
looking for food did they poop on the
floor yes and I had to clean it up
to the cafeteria yeah they obviously
stopped the cafeteria it was not very
funny what does it look like like little
Pebbles or a big you know like a
steaming dump bro okay they say pig poop
smells closest to human which is why it
smells worse than any other animal poop
just if you're wondering
so people were like where's the third
one and like some of the students
actually like got together and like
tried together like Wrangle the pigs
we have to stop this the school like
people thought it was funny but like
then a bunch of like kids tried to be
Vigilantes or heroes or whatever and try
to write I will shave you my princess I
picks dangerous though like I feel like
that could have potentially ended up
being dangerous
if it's a stressed out animal though and
I'm surrounded by a lot of people in an
enclosed area yeah but these were like
kind of small pigs like these weren't
like really big ones and like they were
maybe it was kind of mean to do I feel
bad about it now I don't know I didn't
mean it like that I just meant like uh
they weren't dangerous dangerous to the
to the to the people like I don't know
if I don't know yeah I mean if you see a
bunch of movies with like you know
people getting tortured by being thrown
into the pig pin and the pigs like tear
them apart away right flesh eating pigs
they must have been starving because
Pixley anything yeah yeah I mean they
were generally hungry but they weren't
starving so like they weren't going
after like the kids or anything like
that one of a smaller domestic Pig yeah
I was a domestic Pig it wasn't like a
like a a meat farm or anything like that
no no no no no they just they just
wanted pigs they're just pet pigs yeah
Pet Farm pigs yeah they weren't gonna
like they're only three of them no you
don't only have three pigs
there was no plan to butcher using them
for food no oh but I mean they still
weren't gonna keep them in the house
what were their names am I allowed to
well well you're probably dead by now
did you bathe them before because
I'm trying to remember if like there's
anything on the website about their
names and stuff because they had a
website where they like showcased all
the animals
[Music]
were they dirty when you let them lose
no
no because I was covered in
[Music]
they're always covered pigs are yeah I
mean like they stop around in their own
forehead I'm trying to drink here they
were kind of nasty it's like what what
to when would you
tidied them up because would they have
let them run the lights
confirmed or assumed
they didn't look very dirty
I mean they were kind of dirty by the
end of the day though because one of
them rolled in their own [\h__\h] that's
what they do that's what they do what
other like pranks were there from the
other people like roughly their classes
just tell me roughly let me think I'm
trying to there was one no that'll
that'll box where it is
hold on uh let me think because a lot of
them involved
things that are kind of kind of doxy
there were multiple in the same year not
in the same year there's always just one
just along the year before me nobody did
anything which I thought was boring oh
yeah
[Music]
well how did you how did you attach the
signs to the to the pig just tape
it stayed on just tea what did you touch
them you touched them right wrong tape
yeah how does their texture feel of a
pig not like fluffy but like they have
little fur on them like peach fuzz if
someone ever touched a pig before yeah
um it has yeah what does it feel like
the hair is coarse usually yeah
I don't know if tape would have stuck
though wouldn't that hurt if you're like
I mean it was a pretty strong tape it
wasn't just like duct tape or anything
but it didn't hurt the pigs either okay
it all worked out somehow
okay okay I say files oh
I say true I could totally just like see
it play out it's a huge prick yo you
know it's a good brand it's a funny one
yeah I could totally like
see you really get into it and doing it
so I don't know honestly true because
someone in chat said Cali can't stand
boredom
I'll say true true I
generally I would have said this was
wrong but the way she told the story so
excitedly
yeah something fun but you did that with
all her stories
lastly true
true
maybe it's true and if it is true then
she's definitely you the best yeah
okay last but not least the last Amish
story bring it on baby this is just
ridiculous
my friends mom saved us from an agitated
alligator with the wooden's food
[Laughter]
terrifying can you explain the whole
situation a little bit Yeah so it was my
friend and her mom and we went out to
have like a picnic and like where we
used to live you know there may have
been alligators and a lot of bodies of
water so
it was by a lake you know
um I guess it's more closer to like a
pond size but uh yeah it was pretty big
and then we were poking at stuff with a
stick as kids do
um poking around in the grass and stuff
and we saw something I remember it
looked like
um like a bag a plastic bag filled with
like marbles it looked like it was
filled with something but it was like
floating on the water and so we tried
poking at it of course because you know
we're curious kids and we're like oh
what is this what is that and the stick
actually like hit it it didn't go
through like a bag of wood and then it
turned out it was actually a gator and a
gator in the back stuck or no it looks
like it looks like a bag yeah because
it's like marbles in it of the skin yeah
because it only has like a little bit
like of its nose like peeking out of the
water so usually just like the eyes yeah
yeah they're really hard to spot yeah I
think that would have looked like a bag
though no I could totally see it I can't
did you did it not like react when you
got closer to it uh not not no it didn't
react when we got closer to it but when
we poked it with a stick it like put its
snout up and it was like
is angry and then it started to come out
of the water and so we ran and but it
was a small one and it did come out
fully out of the water but thankfully
her mom
um She Was preparing the food uh for our
picnic and she it was a small Gator and
of course she was like worried for her
kids you know how like if a mom's kid is
in danger they like it mommy yeah super
powers she had a a pretty big spoon and
she smacked it and it just it turned
around and left because he's like I
think she got it like right above the
eye
yeah I mean we were pretty close by like
it was uh we were at you know a park
together
once you have a wooden spoon at the park
just setting up like food like I think
she was setting up a salad or something
she's trying to get us thousand how
close to the water was this
thing to get bag the bag it was like in
the like towards the shallow ends of the
water but like hidden among some grass
like stocks or plants or alligators
common there yeah they're pretty cool
why did your mom her dad mom let you
guys play were those alligators well you
don't know like you don't know they can
be anywhere it's just like any other
wild animal yeah exactly I think yeah
there's an Austria so I can't relate I
would like to think that if you live in
an area that has Gators dinosaurs that I
would think that was there a sign
I said caution their humans really are
like some signs but honestly like Gators
can just cross the street and go like
wherever right across the street our
gators like generally aggressive they
can't be usually aggressive but like if
you [\h__\h] with them like yeah
yeah they get fast too
quick do they on their own they don't
attack humans on their own do they yeah
they do if you bother yeah like if you
get too close very terrifying and
they're territorial too that seems
really dangerous to let your child out
even if it's common exactly because it
is common you shouldn't let your child
play in that area away from the water
yeah somehow
sit out there I don't be surprised I
believe I believe generally that
somebody would let kids play by yeah I
just don't know that I believe the part
about the mom using this yes
[Music]
skaters run like they're super fast so
why would you stick your hand flights
not if you have to reach out into the
water
yeah you said it was chasing us oh my
God so now I was chasing you because you
that's what I said you said you said the
snout came up yeah it came up and then
it turned around and it started chasing
us out you wouldn't have outrun a gator
if it was chasing you well that's right
I don't think he would have outrun again
sounds like the water boy really I don't
know did I get that first you can well
when we saw it move initially we started
running and then it was behind us I've
seen one video of a man a little
different out uh I don't think he ran
away he didn't run away from it but a
gator was propped up in his offensive
position
and he whacked it with a pan and that
made it turn around but it was I don't
believe it was moving I believe it was
standing there small Gator like as a kid
you know it seems really big but looking
back it was pretty small oh my God if it
was out lunging though and chasing like
you said you would not I don't think you
would have been able to outrun that
distance like how long how much did you
run how far well it was like maybe
I don't want I don't maybe like 30 or 40
feet away from where her mom was but uh
we started making our way over there
okay I don't know how much are those in
meters it doesn't sound because if you
were reaching out there and poking with
a stick in your child your arm's not
that long that Gator is pretty close
baby arm child arm with a stick I mean
it's pretty big Stakes pretty long if a
gator lunges it like it didn't it didn't
lunge like when we poked it with the
stick it just like you know shook its
head like really angrily
yeah yeah yeah yeah get a fight on and
then of course we start making loud
noises as kids so then I guess it felt
threatened and it started to come after
us it did have to get out of the water
and we already had started running
I don't know like Mom reflexes is this
is pretty exactly pretty amazing like if
they're kids in danger yeah I don't know
if that hurt stories or like my mom like
she's she like saw the corner of her
eyes while she was doing dishes like my
sister when she was little she was like
running around and she kind of like had
the spider senses she was like she's
gonna trip so she like put on her feet
because she was doing the dishes and she
caught my sister and she was falling
like behind her back like they have some
like superhuman cute to senses like when
their kid is in danger you know I would
be surprised if she suddenly got like
okay was this the same friend that you
were on the on the raft with same
friends so they said this same mother
let you float out to sea without paying
any attention but somehow turned into
Spider-Man when there was a gator
present 30 40 feet away that she
couldn't sleep
we're at the B
was there because they were friends with
my brother we will have to vote now
foreign
maybe it's just because I'm Austrian but
she gets into so much trouble and I
think it's just like look at the look at
the text up there
that sounds so ridiculous well that's
you know unbelievably
but if it is true I really really
worry about like your childhoods
stories like her life
back and forth I was looking forward to
your stars I uh we'll say this
this is false okay we'll see we'll see
Buddha says I'm trying to remember what
I said for the other ones
must say fault okay okay yes we have
been through all the stories
so here are her prompts oh yeah
and please tell me the first one read it
again and tell me if it was true or
false I almost got struck by lightning
when my foot got stuck in a pool was
false
[Music]
uh yeah okay I just want to say before
this I did not read what you sent me I
thought it was two lies and one truth so
I only have one truth because I thought
that was the I didn't know you could
change it I didn't know that you would
give me a different prompt so I just saw
two one so that's true okay this was
false everybody uh who voted on the wait
where's the first one I'm a story one uh
the people said false originally will
get a port that was gouda and Cali yeah
so did I get all the wrong
[Music]
next story was please read it I almost
got lost at Sienna big floaty with my
friend this one is true
out of these ones this is the most
realistic one yeah
I just feel it
[Laughter]
I can see my friend's mom says from an
agitated alligator with wooden spoon oh
my God okay
for the Second Story the people who said
true were uh only gouda
gets a point and up to two leading now
the last story was false and everybody
who said false was
me okay
[Music]
go to sleep you know her too well
okay the next one let's look at Cali's
story all right
uh so let's read the first one all right
I played drums in a contest with no
experience to save the song
single-handedly this is true
it's a true story yep God damn it okay
everybody who said true then let me
scroll Scrolls
the first Cali story true
[Music]
up to two
okay second one please me and my sister
were scouted as child actors but it was
a scam this is this is
true
[Music]
which means the pig story is false
I'm so excited about it it's too excited
someone okay so that prank actually was
done at my school but it was done before
I entered the high school
but for your second story everybody said
it was true so everybody gets a point
here
it's not that Mama Mori wasn't smart
enough for it it's that she loved me and
my sister so much and seeing our faces
get so excited she just wanted to make
us happy I just always remember that
okay uh let's see if who voted for falls
for the last one
up to two all right there's still
everything in there you can still change
it up now to my stories
[Music]
this one has to be true which one the
first one the first one when living in
Japan I befriended someone only to hang
with their cat
false
no I will say that when I uh recently in
my most recent stay in Japan the one
Year's Day I I was like hoping for
like I was thinking like maybe I should
make friends with people who have cats
specifically but I never actually like
ended up doing that but man it's
definitely a believable story well with
how much you love cats so first kiwawa
story who said uh Falls uh Callie yup
wow I knew it I knew the cat thing was a
curveball oh she tricked us two parts in
total now okay the second start my
family was robbed on my birthday because
I thought it was my brother
this is true
this is true and
um there's I feel like there was a
little bit um more to it but yeah if you
want to hear the full story there's a
clip about it
you look up uh robbed
birthday then you will find the full
story I was kind of like scared of the
dark after this for a while yeah I even
remember that the person was standing
right next to me in the night like I
woke up like half it was dark like
exactly that's what I found that weird
because like I was like if you're
sleeping in the living room and they
were like digging around yeah yeah they
were around me I just thought it was my
brother because I only saw like the
silhouette of some legs right next to me
they map that he might have smacked
that's true yeah
okay so everybody who said true for this
one is
oh my God
okay and the last story was uh I almost
got into a famous Japan Japanese idol
group but it rejected them this is also
true
I got all of them right for Amit I got
all of them she knows
yeah there's also more to this there's
also a clip for that so please look it
up the people who said true for this
with everybody everybody
clappy clip Watcher or clappy just
Hastings
did you know any of these stories no not
a single one I mean she gets the second
one with you not wanting to sleep like
uncomfortably yeah
Okay let's listen to uh story
where are they oh my God I'm getting
confused with all these layers
[Music]
first one please
I can tear an apple in half of my bare
hands is this Canyon is this true false
this is true
all right
you put the meat of your thumb right
this part I can't really describe it and
you put that on the top
you went like because I had to figure
out how to fake it because I do know you
take it you tuck your fingers oh I
should have I should have seen through
that leave it to us guys we will test
this out later yeah yeah I'll prove I'll
prove it okay
to Cali for this one because she was the
only one guessing that right
uh next store please I cut a skirt
shorter and shorter until it became a
belt because it had holes what about
that one that's faults
I'll get a point for that
good job us yeah
yeah
okay and the fruit star Blues I want to
use a body massager and my finger to
whip eggs
this is false
[Music]
I was trying to make it sound like
evolved you know
three people got points for that okay
that was uh uh good at stories last but
not least we have
you know stories let's find out which
one is true here please read the first
one I want spread water on a classmate's
face when I have my mouth full of water
it is true yeah I said false but
afterwards I was like that's probably
true it's very true
I'm pretty sure I remember they said hi
I kind of also wanted to say hi back but
I realized my mouth was full of Wars I
was like why did you not swallow because
I was in her to get
okay the people who said this was true
it was only gouda
here yeah oh seven
and then the second Story the board
renewed a single book from the library
for over a year this was false
okay uh everybody knows
I bought the book afterwards because
they wouldn't lie the book yeah I have
it because I asked you why didn't you
buy the book you're like back then I
couldn't buy the book so I try to you
know return it and as soon as they
return it to the chef I'll borrow it
again but I wasn't renewing it over and
over for a year I was like discrepancy I
see there were times I didn't have it
because someone else borrowed it but
like I kept going back to library over
and over
last one
I aced the course for only attending a
single lecture during an entire semester
it's true
because I only ask the ass actually
asked her from one Trail oh really yeah
you I said if you want to do it more
feel free to add more
oh
damn respect yeah it was an easy
Photoshop course
okay this one was true so Kelly and I'm
gonna get a point
what does this mean
we might have a tie which we might oh
oh
[Music]
what do we do about this
I guess it's just a tie is a tie looks
like we're gonna have to duplicate your
detective license I'll be taking my
coffee
just yes
fun I learned some things about you guys
too
yeah
needs to not be deceived so easily or or
to distrust you guys
I learned something if you set if you
tell a slightly dramatic story most
everyone will believe it you
I know right
one it's pretty good because everybody
was just like oh like seriously
listening yeah I believe it yeah but did
you even have like uh like friends uncle
with pigs was that also non-existent no
no no nothing no pigs no no have you
ever touched a pig no damn it okay let's
do it yeah he said it was soft his pigs
are very rough so we tape what is stuck
that's true
well that concludes the show
[Applause]
[Music]
that was unbelievably believable thank
you for the wonderful stories yeah thank
you for listening chat and uh if you
want to hear like more explanations
about these true crazy stories that the
girls have maybe you can ask them to
follow up on it in the future in their
streams yeah
all your true stories have you ever
mentioned them on stream I think of mine
did I think I did before I must have
mentioned breaking an apple maybe not me
personally but like did you know oh I'm
drumming what I did you did I do believe
so some true some some stories have been
told before but maybe also some new ones
yeah yeah okay so that was our stream
for today yeah now it's uh Ira's
birthday time yeah
[Music]
let's go watch her yeah let's go to
Irish history
[Music]
my dances okay I'll see you guys soon
and in German we say
um
[Music]
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]
foreign