what's
me
[Music]
oh
hey
[Music]
m
oh um
[Music]
tell me
hi
[Music]
i promise
i will
find you
doing the aftermath
this is what this part is called
sounds like a friend maybe it is
she said the valkyrie connecting no no
it's the other way around it's the other
way around no no no no no i said that he
don't do anything
oh
let's go
yeah who's back few hours back with a
new song yeah that's dad oh my god
hello
hello you know what i should i should um
i should be in like this actually
yeah unrealistic man
unrealistic you're not that tall
hello oh what's that what's that behind
me what what what what
what is that oh it's the it's a jacket
for
the well it's only a digital release so
i mean yeah you know but digital release
jacket for a song which will be out on
everybody's
music thingies like spotify apple music
itunes from amazon music and so on
uh
starting at midnight at your time zone
so if you look at it now you might if
you like in america or whatever then it
might not be there just yet but please
be patient and then stream it so that i
can continue making music and my but my
budget doesn't go um so solo that i have
to visit kelly in the underworld
please
i have make me taller
if i'm if i'm taller than one day i'll
be taller than you dinner don't you is
that okay for you
um
i'll i will i will exceed your tallness
oh let me play the instrumental in the
back i think
i think the instrumental is being
distributed uh as well
with the song on the music services
and
um
it's pretty damn good yo the
instrumental on its own like you know
with my with my other songs i feel like
the instrumental on its own
is like you know missing the lyrics
that's that's the feeling that i get but
in this case
i don't think so at all like like i
listen to the instrumental before the
stream and i'm like this is just like
so chill to listen to
on its own
yeah you guys maybe and didn't listen to
the instrumental on its own yet so it's
perfectly understandable if you don't
get what i'm saying but if you get the
chance to listen to the instrumental on
its own please do
when is it releasing on digital i just
said it midnight in every
person's time zone i mean if you have a
vpn i don't know you might be able to uh
i don't know go on spotify and hear it a
little bit early i don't know how that
works but
um
uh yes yes it's a good really good bgm
yeah
yeah it's it's really really really
really good um
to just listen to like that especially
if you like the genre scent flake oh
uh
did you really have a flip phone
uh i did never have a flip phone in
austria
also i was not um
let's say i was not alive in this
dimension during the 80s
so it has been pointed out to me that
flip phones were not
a thing yet until
later
um but anyway you know we're just trying
to get a nostalgic vibe going so don't
point out all the little details okay
you picky picky nitpicky
this breaks
that um so what i'm trying to say is
i had
i did have a
a flip phone when i lived in japan when
i was younger because like even to this
day flip phones are so
popular in japan
and uh the first time i moved to japan
when i was still a young young teenager
i i needed some
prepaid phone
uh
and uh yeah the the cheapest one from
softbank was a white flip phone that i
absolutely adored
yeah and i had like a [\h__\h] ton of like
accessories dangling on it flip phones
are so fetch
i love that you're trying to make it a
thing
let's make it a thing
i'm not going to stop you
yeah they're they still are very popular
and honestly they're coming back in
fashion okay because i saw
that certain phone companies are trying
to make them come back
by making like a modern version of it
uh you know how you can like um
[Music]
uh okay i saw that one from samsung
which you can
um fold but not quite like a flip phone
but i also saw flip phones being like
made modern again
and uh i must say
i don't like it
i don't like it the folding screens are
freaking me out it's weird to me
uh but to each other and maybe someone
likes it do you guys like it i saw my my
dentist was using it
and i'm like
isn't that weird do you like using that
but yeah apparently he likes it sound to
me today around hmm floating screens
scratched so easily really is it
different from other screens
really
feels weird yeah i don't know it's just
weird but i mean it's cool though that
they made that possible having folding
screens um
yeah they're softer yeah they must be
softer
it's
miraculous that you can fold them like
that
you must be wondering why i have the
screen out huh and uh the flags up there
do you guys remember these flags does
anyone remember these flags because
they're [\h__\h] nostalgic just like the
song
i mean the song is new but this it
sounds nostalgic you guys remember those
fans fans flags
i said fans because in german we say fun
and not auf wiedersehen
um
yeah yeah they're from my old gaming
screen uh
you know back in the day i i was like yo
i need to we're celebrating so i need i
need some flags and i remembered i still
have a folder with my old gaming layout
here it is wow
and ah [\h__\h] i just deleted no it's just
doing it oh [\h__\h] let me bring it back
quickly
i deleted it not only from obs but also
from my pc just now that was an oopsy
um
no no open the open the trash can
don't throw that away that's precious i
keep these things you know why i keep
these things like these gaming screens
and other i i still have my debut stream
materials guess why
i always think of the possibility that i
might need to do another re-debut stream
and that it's easier for me to
work with it if i have it there yeah
you got it
yeah i have those backups uh where the
[\h__\h] did it go oh found it back okay
there it is
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah there it is
no i don't need it on obvious you can
let it go now but anyway i used to have
these these flags up all the time
um i'm a hoarder no i'm actually not a
hoarder okay
no i'm not
uh
did you ask mama tony to advise on the
outfit design no
um but we'll talk about this
i guess now i i have some things to show
you
and so we'll do like an hour of talking
about the song
and uh also singing the song once or
twice
um and then i'll read super chats while
still talking about the song
because i need to
obviously also read the ones from this
stream because you guys are very very
kind thank you so much for being so um
generous danke soon it helps me create
more songs it's been
a while since the last one
um the last time was sparks
uh i don't
know or i do know
um i partially know why
it took me so long like first it took me
a long time to get back my motivation to
make music again
i knew i still wanted to make music but
maybe you guys remember there were some
some
reasons that i may also not have
explained very clearly because you know
it's you know
uh adult stuff
as we like to say in japanese
it sounds different in english
but yeah there was some
complications that made me lose my
motivation um for creating music
and um
yeah i think um
if if you're in holo
and then making music is
not
and one has to realize this making music
unless you're one of the lucky
exceptions making music is more
something um for
seeing it as an achievement for yourself
and also as a way to
use it for
you know stuff like concerts and all
that and then birthday concerts and just
like
um
you know
just for the sake of making music but
not so much for making money
uh
yeah because yeah music is just like uh
in order to really
you know make
a lot of profit from that
it takes uh
a lot more
but
that's okay
i
eventually got back my motivation but
that wasn't that wasn't why i lost my
motivation anyway but i got back my
motivation and then i was like
uh you know it was around the time where
hinotori the remixes came out
and you just heard one of the remixes
um from the one year anniversary of
hinotori during the loading screen
and that was the astrophysics
hinodori remix back then i chose three
different
remixers
to make a completely different version
of hinotori for me for my one year
anniversary
and one of them was astrophysics and i
knew his remixes from before a while
before because you know you i think a
lot of you guys know his name too
because he has a lot of popular remixes
out there um that are like synthwave
vaporwave and so on
and he's really good in that genre and
uh yeah when i heard you know tony like
that i was like
i guess at some point the
inspiration
struck me almost said stroke me
struck me
and i was like wouldn't it be cool to
have like an original song
like that maybe maybe it's worth a try
um
yeah i like how steins gate um remix
yeah yeah and some others uh
what's your bear
what no that wasn't your bear
god why is it so hot in my room
why is it always still hot why not
always
it's probably the pajama pants they're
too long
they need to be shorter
we're just gone
yeah hacking to the gate
which is amazing
and there's many many others so uh if
you don't know about him you should
check him out astro physics
he has really a lot of really really
really cool remixes he's been doing it
for a while and he kind of specializes
in that um genre so i don't know at some
point i was like let's let's uh let's
maybe try that genre and i asked him do
you feel up to the challenge of making
the whole original song and are there
like any
samples of
of like full originals and so on so we
started talking and honestly it was
quite a while ago this is the song that
i've been
um working on for the longest now or had
it on
on the back
bone
what's the word
i have it somewhere there in the back
for a long long long long time
i said this yesterday or when did i say
this i don't know but i said that
uh
i didn't give myself a clear deadline i
just wanted to
not stress myself and and astrophysics
too much so
yeah we didn't i didn't give us a
deadline so that that resulted in
us taking a little bit too much time
with the whole production
um
yeah
yeah yeah but at one point i was like
[\h__\h] you know and you really need to get
this song out now so let's [\h__\h] get
it done
and then finally you know i got the
relex done and and for the lyrics i was
also
for a long time thinking
who
to
ask for because i don't feel ready to
write my own lyrics
um
and uh i wanted it to be english you
know cause uh
yeah
i i love i enjoy singing japanese
but
i do realize that you guys really really
want english songs
the request the demand for it is so
strong i cannot resist so
yeah
and after a while i realized you know
what
i could ask
i could ask pinky
and
now our lyric is yes pinky
maybe some of you looked her up she
specializes in a very specific
genre currently as well she's a singer
a songwriter she produces a lot of her
own songs she's very active she makes a
lot of tracks but she's more like of a
rapper like a cute uh otaku style um
rapper
idol otaku j-pop style she mixes a lot
of genres
and she's so talented i've known her for
a long time actually and i'm really
really really really happy that i could
choose her um to work with me and
basically also support her work through
that
yes yes yes
she's also such a great singer like she
raps a lot but she's such a good singer
she um after she wrote the lyrics she
sang
um
like a demo for me
um so i know you know how how
the words are supposed to go to like um
how the words are supposed to stick to
the
melody that that astrophysics created
and uh release the pink i wish i i
should i want to but i didn't ask like
you know ah it's very nazi releases
because then you guys are gonna be like
oh she sounds better than you
uh which she does but yeah she obviously
yeah there's always guide vocals usually
yeah and her guide vocals were so pretty
i fell in love
i was like yo we should just release it
like this to be honest i love your
singing so much i really love her
singing
and uh yeah she has a very sweet
sounding voice so partially like i took
inspiration from her and tried to
like recreate the way she sang it here
and there
um
yeah can never reach her levels but
she's great but i am i i guess maybe i
don't know
i hope i did it justice
one thing she's
um also really good
good at is harmonizing and i always like
was wondering like how she does it
because um
like
i
i know a lot of people who can like
hear a song even though the first time
they hear it
they can automatically out of nowhere
naturally come up with harmonies to the
song
out of nowhere and she's one of those
people
i always love listening to her harmonies
it's like oh it just feels so good so i
also requested her to create me some
harmonies and she was like yeah showing
the problem
and then she sent me some beautiful
harmonies and now
uh whenever i try to sing
um fever night
i slip into the harmony so often you
might
hear it um afterwards when i try to sing
it again
yeah
um feels good to be harmonizing i wish i
could do it myself but when i try to
come up with harmonies by myself i don't
know i can't i can't like not nope not
proper harmonies just changing the key
okay whatever anyone can do that but
proper harmonies is difficult i feel
like some people have a talent like a
musical talent for it and some people
learn how to do it and i think pinkie is
like she just has a natural talent for
it and also like you know very skilled
but she also has a talent talent and
skill yo i love her she's so good
yeah uh
did this song take some inspiration from
madonna or other pop singers from the
time
um
now that is something that you would
have to ask
astrophysics because like partially i
gave some
references of what i wanted it to
resemble
and sound like take inspiration from
um but i don't know if he took any more
other inspiration from somewhere
um i
did throw some k-pop at him
no koi no dance queen was not one of the
references i basically told him i want
synthwave but then give it a k-pop sound
as well
and then like an 80s k-pop song
um
[Music]
but also like maybe a little bit of a
modern sound too
like uh an 80s song that was created
now like you know what i mean
a song
purposefully a song that
sounds like the 80s maybe
but only if maybe you weren't born or
living in the 80s you just feel like
that was what the songs back then maybe
sounded like
so fake retro but on purpose
on purpose so that's totally on purpose
you know he definitely was able to
get the the combination of vibes that i
was asking for um
yeah and also some people have been
saying city pop no it's not city pub i
feel like city pop is completely
different what are you talking about and
vaporwave like i i will be honest like i
didn't notice until
today uh the difference but if i
understand correctly then vaporwave is
like
you know
covers
remixed into that style
and
synthwave
is originals created in the style is
that correct
maybe it's [\h__\h]
i don't know let me no vaporwave
honestly i thought rainbow wave was the
style the aesthetic style and stiff wave
was the music but then
i heard other things too now how about
with google vapor
maybe maybe astrophysics is watching
this and he's probably face palming
right now like this [\h__\h] doesn't know
what she's talking about
slow down all the music really vapor
wave but i can't even say the word
vaporwave is a micro genre micro
that's so mean that it's like what was
that
pluto was it pluto the planet who was
like called so small that he then wasn't
even acknowledges the planet anymore
this this feels like the same way
looking rude you know it's so micro that
soon enough vaporwave will not be even
considered a genre anymore it's gonna be
smaller and smaller and smaller that's
so mean
okay vaporwave is a micro genre of
electronic music visual art style okay
so it is also the art style
because that's what i thought it was
just the aesthetics an internet meme
that emerged in the early 2010s it is
defined partly by its slowed down
chopped and screwed samples of smooth
jets ah you like jazz
elevator what
r b and lounge music from the 1980s and
1990s
okay
so it is not what i said what i thought
what i found out it was so it's you know
then what is the difference
rapier wave synth wave i guess i simply
maybe because it uses all these synth
sounds
difference here there you go
um
[Music]
sim wave is the original synthesizer
heavy music style popular in the 80s and
retro wave i didn't ask about retro wave
oh [\h__\h] you
there's so many oh my god there's also
chill wave
what's outrun that's also a thing
okay whatever there's so many genres man
yeah i guess they just use different
instruments but what we have here is
synth life okay same wave 80s retro
synthwave
that's that's what we're working with
okay
now uh
please support and check out
astrophysics channel if you liked this
song then you'll like the rest on his
channel too i think
um
yeah simpson wave what the [\h__\h] is that
the simpsons
what is that
no
yes he makes bangers
[Music]
ah stop singing okay um so
what do you want first talk about the
music video we'll talk about the art
we'll talk about both eventually but
what do you want to see first
[Music]
[Applause]
so this time
once again
i
this is the third time
for
okay i have four original songs and now
three out of the four original songs
are being tantowed
by mamaloni san
once again now
it is true
i may feel a certain sense of
um
security and
what's the right word
um safeness safety
[Music]
yes when working with mamaloni
comfort yes
i know i can rely on her and you know
by now i've been working with many
music creators
um
creators graphic designers artists and
here and there
there are creators who
don't
go well with deadlines and just
you start working with them and then
you're you have high hopes and then they
suddenly disappear or or they just need
a lot of time blue blah blue and you
know that happens but with mama looney i
know i know she will deliver
when she says yes i'll do it then she'll
deliver
and it's just
i know
when i work with her that i'll get great
quality
and
i'll get it fast she works so fast
yeah um legit for all of the art i think
she took
one to two weeks
which is insane
um
so uh i have some things to show to you
but uh
oh yeah i want to say one more thing
when i thought about
who to go for
i did also consider a different
candidate uh who had like this
this classic old um sailor moon-esque um
anime style art style you know like
really old shojo
sailor moon art style
um
also like it was recommended to me by
one of the management people who are
like how about you go for this kind of
um artist and i'm like yeah okay
i guess
i guess that fits the retro theme
but
i thought it doesn't quite fit the kpop
theme
um
and
also
i don't know i besides me going for
mamadoni because she's reliable and and
safe to go with the safe choice and fast
and
other reasons
maybe budget reasons
she's also like i think her art style
i might be biased but i really do think
that her art style was perfect for this
because her art style also kind of has
something retro-ish to it like a low-key
retro shojo style
do you agree with me
or am i going crazy because i think it
fits a lot yeah it fits right and then
there was another thing that um
where i was like yo it must fit every
time she draws me
she always draws me with very fluffy
hair and it made me think
uh maybe like think of the the fluffy
fluffy hair from the 80s 70s 80s maybe
um and i was like i wrote to her i'm
like mama noni you know how you always
draw me with fluffy hair i love that
now
let's
um
do even more of that let's make my hair
even fluffier and then i think we will
nail the hair of the 80s
yeah make it even fluffier oh my god
it's so fluffy yeah
big big big fluffy
um
yeah fluffy wavy curly hair maximum
fluff
because i really love how fluffy she
always draws my hair
yeah makes me think of the 80s even
though i wasn't around
but yeah so let's start i will show you
some
of the rough designs or actually the
the
design ideas for outfits i
gave her
um a [\h__\h] ton of references
of what i want
uh
like references from
70s 80s
mixed
of like casual and dance outfits disco
outfits and also workout outfits
and mama only said that she never
drew
something from this style before but she
had a lot of fun with it so let's look
at the number one
now
uh apparently this was dfg
uh
i think this was like you know supposed
to be
one of the dance outfits but i liked d
and g both so much they were also so
different
uh that i ended up putting both of them
requesting both of them and putting both
of them in the music video
mm-hmm really cute right so
i did send her some references with uh
like very very shiny
um pants like shiny golden
pants that were really tight
those were long on the reference but she
made them short which i like
and you know neon colors
and high waisted skirts
and then really
wide big belts
and contrast colors
you know stuff like that
was implemented perfectly here yeah um i
mean f was fine too but i guess f was
like you know kind of simple in this
case so i did go for
the left one and the right one
it's so good yo the g is so
mmm
yeah it ended up being the main outfit
that's also on the uh cover art and the
thumbnail
yes yes gold gold and neon colors is
kind of what um i i told her to focus on
bright neon colors
so cute man so cute
and now we have
i requested okay there's a lot to look
at here i requested let's first look at
the outfits
i requested um after giving her some
references
uh this kind of like you know workout
outfit i don't know if this is 70s or
80s or both
but i just love this so much
the high-waisted uh body suits with the
colored tights underneath and then the
loose socks at the bottom and the
sneakers and then
sometimes a
a wide
hoodie on top of it
uh
that oozes 1985 80s 80s okay good good
good so we got that one right
um
but i was like who goes like this into
the disco huh so i had her um
draw this
in like uh at home setting as if this
was casual room wear for kiwawa in the
80s
so we went for the left one because i
like that one a little bit more it's
very cute also a high ponytail with the
fluffy hair so cute
and then you see some
some scenes i did uh ask for specific
scenes
in specific situations like in the
beginning you know the lyrics are like
uh i'm tired of the same song
i'm bored basically i don't know
so i asked her to draw me being bored in
my room with some
retro items in the background and me
holding my phone and so we have like a a
a
a retro tv that's really cute really
damn cute in the background
um
also yeah no background for this one
because i was hoping for
a 3d background to be created
and then uh
we see for example the number two we see
me in the taxi i was um planning on for
the bridge having me go
um to the disco on the way to the disco
in a taxi because you know kibaba needs
a change
uh
in her daily life obviously she's bored
but she doesn't want to drink alcohol so
then we have her
in the bar uh on the counter yes yes
we're gonna stay in character we all
know chihuahua no drinking alcohol no no
straight ass idol
yeah
it says all straight edge no alcohol
everything is a mocktail that you see in
this music video
yeah i also told this to
pinky uh who wrote the lyrics i mean she
knows i don't drink alcohol
i told her i kind of want you know like
a
um
relatively i guess this is also
important to say um i did want the
lyrics to be more generic than my
previous songs i did not want like any
junior references like phoenix and
i don't know
whatever i don't i didn't want any of
that i wanted it to be more generic so
that people who are also not from kfp
and not from whole live or not from the
youtuber fandom can enjoy it and
connect with it and feel like that's a
pop you know
so it was on purpose to have
it sound more generic which is not a bad
thing to me
um yeah i just didn't think that
forcing in
the whole phoenix theme in every single
of my songs would would be good i think
that gets boring and and yeah
just i don't know i want something
different i don't want everything to
forcefully be
in character you know i don't care about
that
i feel like that's just um
um doesn't help my creativity either and
just keeps me in like some sort of cage
um
yeah why is my throat so [\h__\h] recently
ever since i came back from the maldives
i it hurts i talk too much man
fruit candy let's go
[Music]
myself where was i here okay
so the bar counter yeah um um there was
like um a line in the lyrics that's like
uh
someone's like walking up to me or
something like that
so i asked also for a different
expression where it's like oh
um i noticed you hello
hello nice to see you
let's get this party started
okay
these were i asked her some dance poses
to use in the chorus
so these were like some post suggestions
and they were already perfect so
no change is necessary absolutely nailed
it as always
she knows what i want um
oh man i loved i loved just all of the
outfit suggestions says she gave me i
did like the green one too
um i love the two colors
you know
but the black one was just ah
yeah so
hot man
spicy
yeah it's
[Music]
originally i think i was gonna like
choose like
one casual and one
um
like stage outfit but then they were all
so good and i couldn't choose so i just
went for
several ones
yeah i i like the black one
i like the others too the black one
with the sheer fabric and the ruffles
and i love the flare uh pants
and it's like you know the whole thing
is like a one piece so that's that's
i don't know very 80s too in my opinion
um one piece um pant pants thingies
very 80s in my opinion
yeah very cute
black is perfect this one is so perfect
right you own the floor with that outfit
right thank you
it's just yeah it's so spicy
so those were some of the
um
design ideas from mama luni
thank you so much mama luna for your
hard work i love you
that is
[Music]
i i told her that and then she was like
paper lonely no no
god loney kami can be gold and paper but
in this case god got luni
but uh don't call her that okay let's
just call him a maloney she's she's
gonna
maybe um not like it
i will call her camiloni you will call
her mama looney okay
oh yeah it could also be hair yeah
she's yeah a goddess drawing hair as
well
now let's talk a little bit about the
the music video um because
uh this time
uh i chose
a new
like for me new
uh music video creator who i haven't
worked with before uh their name is ere
which i wonder if they're aware that
that is a german word
uh for like
not respect wait what
honor yes honor that's the right word
i wonder if they know that
it is
yeah so for the music video
um i was hoping
to
capture obviously the vibes like 80s
vibes and also the synthwave vibes
um
and then
you know the atmosphere was very
important and i did give kind of a
storyboard
uh
like a storyline as well
um following the lyrics
and
yeah i needed all that gorgeous art to
be implemented and we were kind of like
working at the music vid
music video and the art at the same time
so
uh era kind of started working on the
music video and creating some 3d assets
while mama looney was working on the art
at the same time and then you know we
got the art finished and then finally we
could like continue the music video but
let me show you some of the
notes that era took
because we have something special here
now this is japanese but let me try to
translate it for you guys
uh fever night concept spoiler alert not
a spoiler for you guys because you guys
already saw the music video right
yes yes yes several times thank you
please stream it please please please
watch it many times and then stream it
on the music devices please please
please
so uh the first thing that i was asked
uh
was these
cassettes cassettes
the tapes the tapes
wait you guys don't sing
cassettes in english do you do you say
tape circusets
because like in german we say
this cassette cassette
you say both
okay
okay so um there's like four cassettes
because i have four original songs now
and i was asked to draw to to to write
the
titles of them
by hand on it so i did that actually
pretty late but uh it made it into him
and besides that what does it say oh
yeah this is at the very beginning of
the song
um
where you know before it starts with um
16 to 9
uh aspect
but then it switches very fast to for
free which is on purpose to give it a
bit more of a retro style
and obviously the cassettes are also
kind of retro who uses cassettes
nowadays no one i used to
i used to have some cassettes when i was
younger but they were [\h__\h] annoying
because of the
the weird paper thingies that you could
pull out and then once you pull them out
you will literally never be able to fix
it ever again
yeah that was um terrible
and
yeah so people night um
yes yes and then there's like this first
you see the the first three songs and
then wow
the new one
[Music]
next up we have the
vaporwave
inspirations
in the very beginning you see the logo
in like a very very vaporwavish
environment
and
i think the the phoenix the way it's
like
modeled is also
kind of vaporwavish i guess
and retrowish
the cg
are supposed to
look very retro-ish here and they do
and also he tried to
the way that the the logo
um
transitions into the screen he tried to
make it look like uh like the television
shows and tel aviv
television shows i'm really
reading the japanese things here um from
the 70s where like
in in the television shows
they would like
make the logo come up on the screen like
that a lot like really big and like
swashbam
i don't know if you guys understand but
um yes
i think i get what he was uh going for
hmm
tally shows yeah
next up we have the credits
for the credits it was purposefully i
don't know if you noticed but purposely
made so that the the people who are
related to the music were shown on the
screen with the
the walkman
and then the ones that were related to
like graphic design where on the screen
with the paper and depends
the music video creator on tv
and me
obviously the dancing silhouette yes yes
did you guys notice on this screen on
the left side there were um
more tapes with uh
my my songs on the left side and on the
right side
i didn't notice until
later on but uh
there's
one tape that says interacto fantasia
which is the third gen's original song
and then there's edo start oh no and you
started
um
which is mummy's song now you may wonder
why
it is because
eva made the music videos for both of
those songs
and i remember reacting to interacto
fantasia for the first time on my stream
together with you guys
and i was like really really really
really like shook off
by
how
incredible that music video was like
there was so much to take in
it was like
overwhelming
the first time i watched it it still is
but i actually i forgot
i think i kind of forgot that era was
the one behind it when i uh asked him to
make my music video i was mostly aware
of
anustart let's go and start
because that was more recent and um
yeah mummy's music video for in the
start was really really really really
well done as well
um
so yeah that's kind of why i
had era in mind
i wanted
to
[Music]
have like partially in 3d music video to
give it more oomph
yeah
so that's why i requested air summer and
then you put those references in there
nicer
an easter egg yeah 10 of the 10 easter
eggs not many people noticed i think mmm
this nesu now here's my room apparently
this is what my room looks like 100
accurate
and so
mamaloni actually for this artwork she
drew some extra um
furniture but originally
era didn't know that there would be
furniture so he modeled
i suppose he modeled this by himself
because that's what it says here
i think
um but yeah he modeled some furniture in
here
and it's not only furniture but also
maybe some of you guys notice the ones
who who stop at every frame to try to
find the easter eggs may have noticed
um that for example
this is uh the the neon light here is a
reference to one of my song covers uh
there's a glue gun on the floor here as
a reference to my glue gun stream the
glass shoes are a reference to my
um
to my cinderella cover and then the skis
are also a reference to my skiing trip
so there are some references there
indeed on purpose yes yes yes yes
the glue gun
now i really need to
get that new glue gun and do the stream
that i promised you guys you know
that was supposed to happen previously
yeah these details it's kind of dark in
this room so it's uh hard to miss
yeah they also write that there's um
quite a strong blur on this frame
so it's difficult to notice maybe unless
you really pause every scene
yeah but now you know
can you zoom in
okay there we go
and now we have the disco hall
i love
like the lightning in this scene so much
oh the warm lightning oh my god it's so
pretty
and it has your chickens here and there
and so this says yeah um
when when you think about a disco you
think about strongly flickering stage
lights and
strong
uh
floor lights like these these flickering
floor lights
and crazy
dancing
people
and
the disco ball that i don't see here but
there was definitely a disco ball
somewhere
and
then we had your chicken chimkins
here and there dancing and cheering and
djing for me thank you very much for
being part of the music video i see a
lot of you guys in the chat here
there's no pay obviously but i
appreciate you guys doing it for free
thanks for volunteering
and they were modeled after the dakuma
design
so
they look um a lot like the dhaka my
chickens i think which are the best
chickens i love the document chickens
tackle my chickens forever
yeah
your love is our pay
that's a good answer
that's the best answer that's how it
should be
um
[Music]
i love this yeah the lights are so
beautiful and the big big disco floor i
did ask for a disco floor and may
i may have given
um
a yakuza reference for the disco floor
just because when i looked up
images for disco
like floors and and
um discard rooms i just didn't find
something that looked like how i wanted
it to look like so i may have given like
maybe one yakuza reference
from a certain yakuza game that we
played recently um
i think i don't actually no i when i say
i may have i really don't remember but i
think i may have yes
i'm saying it because i really have
a blurry memory but i think i may have
um
that's red
[Music]
then we have the taxi scene
for most of the artworks i asked mama
leonie to um draw them with uh with no
background and make it transparent but
for this one um i asked her to kind of
draw me in inside of a taxi looking
outside
at the scenery and looking kind of sad
or bored as well
and so that's
what
she did and then
uh the air ever made it like move
outside so that's
actually perfect and then
of course when we have the inside of the
taxi we also must have the answer of the
taxi
this taxi looks so cool doesn't it
yo
the way it's driving and during doing
okay it's not really drifting maybe it
should be oh maybe we should have it
drifting we should have had it drifting
maybe damn it damn it i missed that
opportunity no don't leave
just looking at those images alone
not only but
yeah
um
that was perfect
and
uh
[Music]
purposefully made it look like a taxi
from the 80s
i don't know if this is what taxis
looked like back then but looks legit to
me
then we have the wrap part originally
i
didn't request
any art for the wrap part but then last
minute um after
we already started working on the music
video and already after
the other art was finished i was like yo
mama donnie i'm so sorry but i feel like
we need one more piece of art
and do you think you can do it in like
a few more days
and she was like yes of course i'll do
it
yeah
and i gave her like a rough sketch of
how i wanted it to look like basically
me
on the floor and with my arms up
and i want a different
mouth movements so that we could
um have the mouth move along the wrap
pipe yeah
so you were probably able to see
[Music]
to notice that during the red part
spicy floor yes very spicy but cute and
it's in the room where because i noticed
that the room where only shows up in the
beginning
um in the artwork that i wanted for the
beginning so i was like maybe we should
use a little bit more often
and then it was implemented here again
and we have some more of you guys
viving to the music oh right now there's
the wrap again in the instrumental as
well
yeah
spicy
uh
yeah
and then we have the concert hall
so originally in the first chorus we're
dancing in the disco
and then later on we're dancing in a big
concert hall that also looks very 80s
you know instead of a big like uh
um screen in the background there's just
like the big logo
um
in the back so i do like that it looks
like something like a set that would be
used to record uh like a concert for a
tv show
in the 80s
you have a good sense for directing yeah
you know i shouldn't only
credit myself as a singer in my music
videos i should i was thinking this
today i should uh credit myself as a
director because that's literally what
i'm doing yo
yeah i'm directing these music videos i
i did direct this one pretty pretty
intensely
i'm directing
again i love the the filter the light
that is on top of the colors that is on
top of the art here
it makes everything go so smoothly
together so i was a bit worried about
you know
combining 3d backgrounds with
um 2d art again we did that before for
heart challenger
um so i guess there was no need to worry
about it but it ended up like really
really going so well together um
thanks
thanks to the light i would say
a lot
because it makes everything blend
in the end um color grading yeah so
important
uh and uh era
notes here that it's like
um the thought behind it was that
it's like
a
singer that has become famous
ends up in like bigger and bigger venues
so in this case from the disco hall to
the concert hall
nice
go famous let's go
and also more
more people in the audience
and
yeah a big big logo in the background
and me dancing in front of it
yes
the success story of takanashi kiwawa
then we have some extra
instincts for example the tvs which are
on my screen
on my office screen as well
the four screens
yeah
all right here
you know you see them on the on the left
side of course you know where they are
then oh yeah the the number plate
on the back of the taxi is tk 2022
live
[Music]
yeah i love that scene too with the
phoenix flying on top for the intro and
the outro i really like that this is the
end of that thank you so much edgar for
providing this mood board and like um
storyboard thank you
[Music]
i think
i think that's it for the things that i
wanted to show you
perfect it's been an hour now i will
sing the song
do you want to hear it do you want to
hear the first
live version
of favorite night
my voice
feels a bit [\h__\h] but
we will roll with it
i can do it i can do it
should we go to my stage or something
i don't know what my stage looks like
right now though
uh but let's it might be a mess but
please bear with me
um
oh i can i can uh fix some things in
studio mode right now then then it won't
be so much of a shock
for all of us
uh
okay i think i think it might look okay
let's go to the stage
where am i where am i down oh sheesh
here i am
[Music]
it's looking good here
chickens are already ready to vibe i see
already in position
thank you thank you
wow
no let's do it like this okay
okay
the first time the first live version of
favorite night
um i might as i said sing the harmonies
here and there because i just feel like
it
and don't mind me when i do that
you guys maybe don't even know the
difference
but
i don't know enjoy singing those
harmonies
let me get the
lyrics lauren drink some more water and
sit straight for once
um
mic check
my check
one two
yeah i'll increase it of course it's
just bgm right now that's on purpose
okay
let's
sing
favorite night
[Music]
i'm tired of the same song
every day like it's on repeat i need a
risky breakdown
oh honey
the night is calling don't need a steady
simple melody
can you make it original
take me away
like it's just the two of us i'm ready
do you feel the music baby
make me underneath the stroke i'd call
my life move my feet to something you i
don't need no drinks tonight give me
that beat
and sing feel it rash through me let
this new sound take over me
intoxicating dj keep playing
wow
lately i'm dancing alone
so orthotics so emotionless
but then i see you across the dance
floor so now honey
follow me i need a frilling red hot
melody something to keep me up all night
don't look away now it's just the two of
us i'm ready
do you feel the music
baby underneath
[Music]
moving you've got the shining glowing
like a prism that this gorbal makes me
wild don't care who's watching a soul
baby
meet me underneath the strobe light come
alive
moving my feet to something so new i
don't need no drinks tonight give me
that speed get me dancing feel it rush
through me i don't need no drinks
tonight give me that beep get me down
baby
can we dance until the day like crazy
about this song i'm making with you
[Music]
huh
yay
[Music]
let's go
especially in the chorus i fell into the
harmony so often did you notice did you
notice it's like the higher harmony
mm-hmm
yeah i'm i'm so used to it i keep on
doing it now i can't go to the old
version anymore
i can't go to the original anymore i
didn't you need to compare it it's just
so natural at this point that even to
you you don't notice it yo that's a good
thing
i enjoy singing the harmony
um i don't think i can try to sing the
original anymore
one more should we sing the same one
again or a different one i can oh you
know what because we're here for
for uh an astrophysics song i could sing
hinotori
astrophysics version i think i have the
instrumental here right here
we can do that yeah uh hinotoni lyrics
[Music]
let's [\h__\h] go let's [\h__\h] go
i'm cool
[Music]
the remix version of the one-year
anniversary remix version of hino20 by
astrophysics the same person who made um
fifa night
let's go oh this one has a long intro
though
well let's vibe to it let's go
so
[Music]
tell me i can hear it clearly tell
me
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
is
[Music]
me
is
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray
if i go wrong what awaits me in the dog
could you tell me please
[Music]
tell me i can hear it clearly tell me
me
[Music]
[Applause]
let's get down
i love this outro
[Music]
bye bye
one more i'm gonna sing one more can't
stop me
can't stop me now because cali is here
we're gonna sing fever night again let's
go
[Music]
dance version
i'm tired of the same song
every day like it's on repeat i need a
risky breakdown
oh honey
the night is calling don't need steady
simple melody
can you make it original
take me away like it's just the two of
us i'm ready
do you feel the music baby
make me
underneath my feet to something new i
don't need no drinks tonight give me
that beep get me don't sing feel it rash
bro me let this new sound take over me
intoxicating did they keep playing
wow
daily i'm dancing alone
so robotics so emotionless
but then i see you
across the dance floor so now honey
follow me i need a feeling red hot
melody oh something to keep me up all
night
don't look away now it's just the two of
us i'm ready
do you feel the music baby
make me underneath the straw
something new i don't need no drinks
tonight give me that beat cut me down
sing feel it rash for me
[Music]
i'm in the chance of the way that you're
moving you got me shining glowing like a
prism that this gumball makes me wild
don't care who's watching us so baby
leave me underneath
[Music]
i don't need no drinks tonight give me
that
baby
can we dance until the day like crazy
about the sun i'm making a view
oh wow
[Music]
hell yeah
hello yeah
thank you
don gato that was fun
that was fun and i'm sweating
my hands i sweaty spaghetti because you
got me all nervous guys you got me so
nervous man
how dare you
how dare you make me nervous
uh
i'm going to drift to that oh please be
careful please be careful
well i want to see that yo if you drift
to that i want a video of that
love the part where she sings
wait which part
[Music]
no need to be nervous you're nailing it
thank you
it's fun it's fun it's fun to sing i've
had this as i told you guys man we've
been working on this for so long but
when did we start like usually
production for my original songs is like
two to three months
but this was
we started last year
like
a million [\h__\h] years ago
let me look it up
yeah okay i guess we started like um
it started started like i think in
december
yo
so long
so long farewell
saying goodbye
yeah normally it doesn't take so long
but as i said i didn't give us a
deadline until much later because i
didn't know like when i wanted to
release it i didn't have a particular
day in mind so far i've always been
releasing my songs on like special
days like valentine's day thanksgiving
and my birthday so yeah but this time i
didn't have that i just wanted to bring
it out eventually without putting too
much stress on all the involved people
although at the very end
it ended up being a little bit stressful
the music video made it a little bit
goody goody but
now everything's fine everything's
released and looking good so i'm really
happy about that um
yeah yeah yeah
thanks even if you give yourself so much
time in the end things always end up
being
last minute it's just the way things are
it's just this is how things are
supposed to be it's normal
um i'm not gonna sing it no i'm just
gonna play it in the background
yes
and you guys are welcome to stay and
keep me company while i uh
discuss more about the song while
discussing your super chattels
[Music]
the effort shows thank you
i've seen many people um say that this
is their favorite song of mine now which
i'm so happy to hear because i was
after working on it for so long and
hearing it so often
i wasn't sure anymore like it is
it what what do i think about this i
don't know i got so used to it and i was
getting really worried and
self-conscious about it
uh
yeah and i know you know
it's
it's a different genre so i totally also
understand if you guys like are like ah
safeway without my thing like that's
okay
um but i personally just wanted to mix
it up a little bit um the next song will
probably be
a little bit more
normal whatever normal is
again um
but yeah this is i think refreshing um
to have in my discography
and i i don't know when i heard all
those synthwave songs
and the retro
some retro songs and and you know what i
do i do also like me some 70s and 80s
songs
so i just felt like
i'm creating something similar to that
all four of your originals are different
genres
[Music]
uh
i would say you could put them roughly
into the same genre
except you know heart challenger and
uh him tony is j-pop and then sparks is
like
not j-pop because it's not japanese but
it's like
um kpop but with english language
yeah but i feel like they're all very
poppy so
they're similar in style although sparks
definitely stands out against the other
two in style yeah but when i say normal
i mean like more
mainstreamish pop music
although j-pop is not really mainstream
i guess
well i i
i do have
a very basic [\h__\h] taste in music i
guess as people like to say
and i just want to say shut up
but
because of that but not only because of
that also just because it's i think
smart to appeal to a broader audience
so my next song will probably be
um
back to back to the usual menu or um
back to the usual but even more improved
a lot a lot more proof because like i
already have the i already have the um
demo tape for the upcoming next song a
little bit early because i have to wear
girly on it for making a
choreography i'll dance choreography
uh for it to hopefully perform it during
my birthday concert in street 3d yeah so
be there or be square
or be four four
four two four free for two free aspect
let's go to my office um
oh where the [\h__\h] are we
uh
there we are
um
yeah uh
be square or or
be not so square
a little bit more
wide than square but almost square
uh
thank you guys for listening we're still
gonna stream continue streaming so
you're welcome to stay stay stay stay
you're not allowed to leave don't leave
don't leave don't go
yes stay with me otherwise i'm gonna be
lonely and cry okay
stay
rectangle
um
oh this schedule is now blip almost
uh
if you are going to docomi and you
applied for the meet and greet then you
might want to check your email inbox
because the
um participants haven't chosen and the
emails are out now
and i wish i could um i have had all of
you participate but you know we have to
limit it
um i'm doing uh
no actually i'm doing 51
participants i think it ended up being
51 for whatever reason
um
yeah
i wish i could tell all of you i'm sorry
um but i was so happy to have a lot of
lot of lot of lot of lot of um
people signing up for it
and um yeah i really appreciate it i'm
sorry for the people who didn't make it
but it do be like that sometimes
yeah um originally
uh it was supposed to be way less but i
doubled it because i said whatever i
want to do at least
two sessions
um because i know that this year there's
so many more kf people
coming to dokomi to see me and i wanted
to give as many of you as possible
um this chance
and you know what i feel like even
though it's just this is just how things
are i feel so bad for the people who
didn't make it um so i want to ask
um
if maybe at least i can sign
cards for everybody maybe and and maybe
they can be given out to the um people
who signed up but they were chosen as
well i will ask but i can't i can't
guarantee but i want to give you guys
something
um
yeah we'll ask
i don't mind signing hundreds of cards
that's no problem
yeah yeah
but i don't know if we do it how we will
give it to the people who signed up i
don't want to give it to everyone you
know just to the people who signed up
originally
um for the meet and greet
um
yeah but we'll try we'll try to i will
try to organize something
okay yeah yeah
yeah
so uh
check your emails and uh
make sure to be there on time and
although i don't know what time because
we're separating it in two sessions uh
be there on whatever time
they tell you to be there
yeah okay
now
super chapters
where do i even start i have to read
others first um
can we just read uh
the ones from this week and everything
from before we'll just act and that we
are we will act as if i already read
those
uh because i think there was one one
vi stream
um
that
i was supposed to still read but can i
can i read them um
on my own
please thank you i love you guys thank
you thank you
um
okay okay
then we will read the
collab vacation recap super chats
and then wind waker and then the ones
from today i suppose i suppose
i'm scrolling already i'm scrolling
scrolling scrolling
scrolling
scrolling scrolling still scrolling
scrolling for years
holy [\h__\h] this is uh i it's weird like
um i've i've heard this song for the
first time like what half a year ago
and i feel like now that it's finally
finished and
all out there i like it even more
than two months ago or five months ago
yeah that's weird it's grown really
really
dear to me
maybe you guys will have the same
sensation but i i was really happy to
see so many of you guys liked it from
the get-go
thank
[Music]
oh you that was not my idea that was
astro
i think it's funny
uh wait did i say recap from
the collab one i i need to read two
right yeah yeah
okay almost there ah i'm there
there i found it
so this one
yeah i'll try to
get through all of them
today which is maybe a little bit
actually unrealistic but we still have
tomorrow wind waker i can read more
tomorrow yeah okay okay but why is my
photo so that i should make some tea
honestly
honestly honest tea
but i feel like if i leave you guys are
gonna leave too
the moment i leave the screen
you guys are gonna leave too i know you
i know there's some
weirdos out there who just wait for that
moment
and i'll leave the screen for like a few
minutes and you guys leave
maybe maybe i can make it for a little
bit without a team
i still have water
well let me try to get through it for a
while
i don't need no drinks tonight give me
that so that for example was the harmony
that was not the original key that was
the harmony did you did you notice i
like singing it hi
[Music]
thank you soon pepsi thank you for the
pinky duncan hi boss patrick here
reporting that i've safely arrived in
europe oh wait you came pretty early
what the hell i'll do my best to enjoy
my trip to the fullest ah
wait so are you already in germany or
somewhere else
there's so much i want to do and so many
things to eat i tried tuna pizza
yesterday but did you go to a proper
place like a proper italian no place
because like
in in
europe as well depending on where you go
you can get some
not so italian pizza too
and then that will make a big difference
i mean i like i like any kind of tuna
pizza but you're in switzerland right
that's so cool i want to go to
switzerland
you're you're obviously
not vacationing though right you're
working at the switzerland kfp right now
right
you're not vacationing because i didn't
give you any permission to vacation
it is closed yes what's on this
oh one of my neighbors no
i could go
nice damn so you're making the most out
of it i'm happy about that
checking that they're working hard no no
no you shouldn't just be supervising you
should be working yourself
yeah use your use your wings
and your feetsies and your beak
everything
wow waiting for the dokomi booth
well that's actually like real work wow
thank you so much foxy
oh make nice memories please
dominique
isn't
tiara
today marks one year since the move
breakers characters were created time
sure flies oh
i see
one year wow
wow emif breakers
needs an ending huh
well he left you guys
on
not quite a cliffhanger but definitely
an open ending oh tiara my beloved yeah
tiara
my dream of white silver hair
when will it when will it ever be true
um
it's been a year hmm
[Music]
cocoon dankeshen felix sal thank you for
the red super mwah
thank you very very much
no message with it
but hope you're doing well thank you for
the support as always
um would you be interested in playing
any other ttrt in the future
um
generally yes but maybe like
uh
when i have more time
and
maybe privately instead
because i did feel a lot of pressure
always in every episode um
i don't know it always felt like i i
didn't know what i was doing and i
i felt like so pressured and criticized
and
i don't know
um
i don't know it wasn't
even though i like ttrpgs
because like i was really looking
forward to it because it was the first
time after
um a long long long time i only played a
ttrpg once in my life with my family
when i was like a lot younger and still
lived with my mommy
we played it as a family
and yeah since then i always hoped to
maybe try it again sometime
yeah um
[Music]
maybe maybe one day privately
when
when i don't feel the pressure
[Music]
and more regularly
thank you
very much
[Music]
in
yeah the commercials holy [\h__\h] they suck
i'm glad some people
uh were molding together with me about
the emirates
um commercial that was not even the one
i posted on twitter wasn't even the
safety instructions but that was just a
commercial that they play immediately
after the safety instructions
about the
um
in-flight entertainment
yeah and that was already so [\h__\h]
annoying
so unnecessary man usually
other flights they just play the safety
instruction and that's it but in every
raids plays the safety instructions
depending on what country you're flying
to three times or two times
and they're really long and then they'll
play that stupid
in in-flight entertainment
thingy commercial extra
it's just like 40 minutes of trying to
ignore it but it's literally playing on
every [\h__\h] screen in the whole
airplane and on speakers and in the
headphones so you can't turn it off
so
obnoxious yeah like the saved
instructions i i can ignore it but then
the entertainment thing is like what's
it i'm on a 10-hour flight do you really
think i'm not going to check out the
entertainment you don't need to
advertise it to me just just leave me
alone
[Music]
ah
optimus prime fashion the coral kiana
stepped on duncan
[Music]
in
thank you guys very sweet
then petal of dankeshin i really trained
you guys to
say bless you in german so perfectly
it must be scary to be in a place of a
gang problem you could be walking around
and then someone shows up and forces you
to do a sub story quest
when i first started reading it i
thought it was a serious um
super chat and then i saw
the joke
i love that
you're so funny
terrifying those sub stories man you
just wanna do the main quest but they
keep on talking to you at every corner
looking very suspicious in their outfits
standing out
and having that that aura around them
and they're like talk to me
i need you to do my side quest
uh
did you ever see the reward for bowling
yes i did
i did i did i don't remember anymore
what it was but i remember watching it
uh thanks for the report part one the
rumors of your vacation the maldives
have been around for a long time
yes we talked about it for a long time
i'm glad it finally happened sounds like
you both have a lot of vivid memories
hope you'll continue to keep in
touch papanashi is so special thank you
yeah um we are like definitely closer
than before
um
and i'm i'm really happy about it i feel
like
um
and
when i say this um i don't mean it too
negatively or so but i feel like a lot
of um most
relationships
uh
between her life members
at least it feels that way to me are
very
superficial because we're co-workers and
we're all busy and
it just feels like
um
like that to me but with reyna i feel
like we reached a point where it's
definitely not just superficial we care
for each other and we enjoy each other's
we enjoy each other's company and yeah
reyna is so supportive of
my stuff like i always see her
liking and retweeting my tweets like no
one else honestly she and ollie
reyna and ollie are the ones who like
and re tweet my stuff the most and i
love them so much for it oh i just
noticed this
um yeah
and i say that and i i remember that you
know
it's so sweet and yeah
i love reina
she was also
she messaged me before the stream about
my song she was like holy [\h__\h] it's so
good such a banger i love it the music
video is so good yo let's go
and i have to tell her again thank you
for being so supportive like it means so
much to me
yeah i saw sana and bae as well they
also
listened to it
and ame ami too
i wonder what anna thinks of the song
well you know
as i said i don't mean it too negatively
actually you know keeping things mostly
superficial and
like you know
co-worker
kind of
relationship
is
when dealing with so many girls
you know mostly women or like only women
in a company
um you know i feel like if we're all
weren't so much like professional and
and in a co-worker kind of relationship
then there could be a lot of [\h__\h]
fights you know what i mean
um and like
i don't know i'm actually
yeah
glad partially that it's like this
um
cat fights [\h__\h] fights and like
bitching and gossiping
behind each other's backs and all that
see this is this doesn't exist and i'm
really happy about that yeah
what do you mean
honesty and all that it's just
but
i'm just saying it
i'm just saying it's good
that's the way it is yeah you know you
know obviously some girls are closer
with one another but
just judging by
the workplaces i've been in before
like there's always like
there's always like i don't know
co-workers gossiping about other
co-workers
like in in my previous workplace
now that was definitely a thing i don't
know about your guys's workplaces but
you would think that adults don't have
that
but adults are surprisingly childish
it's like you're in school man
it's like you're in freaking school
it's so sad that adults can't just
behave and respect one another
um
i'm saying something good yo i'm saying
that whole life doesn't have that
problem and that's a good thing there's
nothing to
worry about
serious clip no i don't think you can
twist this oh try try maybe make it a
challenge try twisting one no don't do
it
you guys understand me
no but that's that's not a reason i
appreciate the
professionalism especially from the
whole live uh japan members because like
i feel like japanese people with their
work ethic they have
they have this professionalism to them
um
so
it's really good working with them
yeah
i'm joking i'm joking
[Music]
professionalism that's a word right
gossip to me about a lot is the reverse
of what i usually experience oh
yeah
yes okay
uh
elias e1
or elias
oh
we're done with the maldives recap
hallelujah
okay
so we're gonna read these potatoes yeah
i like the thumbs now
thank you guys for appreciating my
efforts that i put into the thumbnails
yes
oh [\h__\h] i need to make the thumbnail for
tomorrow afterwards
oh what to do next
i know that there's still like a a
bunky bunk hammer
and uh
a bomb
i can use those items
hmm although maybe i can think of
something with the
what the
sword still
oh yeah shield as well
[Music]
no i mean like perhaps that people
already made into
um
like images for me to use
and
doctor duncan hold on thank you for the
razor
and i
am become deaf destroyer of the worlds
what's happening my soul been forged and
body tempered by hellish ah one year
hellish flames of the usual room i
witnessed many chickens come and go from
this god forsaken place all of them
oh wait no you left the usual room i
love them broken beyond redemption yet i
stood strong and none shall stop me now
or in other words my usual room sentence
of one year
finally ended and i'm free i
i forgot
ages ago probably one day after i put
you into into the usual room i forgot
that i gave you a one year sentence
oh
oh dear
just in time for documenting a new song
release oh as if i planned it
oh my god uh what now i kind of forgot
what i'm supposed to do in kfb outside
of the year
should i put you back maybe you'll feel
more comfortable
oh my god
oh [\h__\h]
one year i'm i'm kind of low-key sorry
but now i shouldn't be sorry i'm your
boss
you should be thankful
you should be grateful
one year aren't you gonna miss it
you're probably gonna ask for it again
very soon
you should at least try to stay outside
until after document
holy [\h__\h] i totally forgot
welcome back to the real world i guess
and i guess here's a kiss for you
[Music]
don't get used to it there's no cases in
the usual room
[Music]
uh at least you didn't try to escape did
you you were a good good chicken
and followed my orders right
stayed until the very end
as you're supposed to
got used to eating stale pop tarts ew
were you
you
[Music]
no you didn't get a kiss for surviving
and then you are you got a kiss for a
red super tattoo
you can escape no you can't but even if
you try i take that as an insult to
me
and disrespect
because you're not supposed to even try
to escape
it's a usual room sentence and you
deserve it and you're supposed to
reflect on your actions
i was patiently waiting okay very good
that's what i like to see
he became used to the lego phone and he
probably even became one with the lego
floor
um
as sora's keyblade thank you
it's morphing time danke shin you just
want me to say that right
big wind wake up burp that is it hello
big wind wagon verb packaging duck hood
thank you thank you for watching
hey boss can i dedicate an inspiring
kiss to oprah ah oh
[Music]
yeah i love the art you're doing
especially the one you're working on
right now the valkyrie connector i'm so
happy that people draw the valkyrie
connect outfit even though it's just a
collaboration outfit
um from their side
i'm i'm really happy to see some fan art
of it thank you very much
for dancing
why are you doing that
why are you sending a five dollar super
chat every hour
no not sometimes even twice
until the stream started why did you do
that
were you that excited understandable
understandable thank you
uh it's such a good design yeah it's a
really cool design i like you know that
kind of fantasy
um jrpg art style
uh design style i really like it
there's like three
free super chats from the teaser okano
mike dan questions
thanks to the pinky danger
you're welcome
yo i saw some of you guys be like
wait that's it
when that's it
i'm like yo
i gave you a taser that's better than
nothing shut up will ya
be grateful
hey where's your shirt wait
yeah
i'm gonna try to do teasers again in the
future
yeah up until now it was like i always
forgot about like asking about it and
then
yeah
then it was always too late or like i i
didn't know if like the mv maker would
maybe be up for it um
yeah
hippo fans are used to teases yeah
that's that's why i wanted to do them
because i like the k-pop teasers
it's
uh
you know
when i can't use when i can't use 3d
freely then it's a bit difficult because
like i want to do stuff like they do in
the
in the k-pop teasers and also for the
k-pop teasers they often use like kind
of altered instrumentals
um and for that you know i would also
ask the whoever's making a song
to
make that for me this time i had
astrophysics quickly whip up a version
of the intro where it ends at a certain
beat
um maybe next time i can plan it ahead a
bit more and then
have an even more intricate altered
instrumental if you know what i mean
i think the person that i'm working with
next is up for it
the cut was clean yes
[Music]
thank you
i like that you're not complaining i
like people who don't complain
who don't nitpick about every little
piece of
detail
thank you for the membership message
thank you
phoenix are you living in phoenix
that's cool
i know i've heard people told me before
that phoenix is
not that special of a place but just
because it's called phoenix i do want to
go there one day
not cool it's hot yeah
i guess so
but what did you expect that's probably
why it's called phoenix
it's very hot that's okay
i guess oh by the way the bubbles are
gone my bubbles are gone i am now
losing my skin everywhere
and i'm planning to put him up for
auction on yahoo auctions
i'm putting up my gamer skin
i sure
here i'm pulling it off right now fresh
fresh from the phoenix
no i didn't rip them off i don't know
they disappeared
after one night i don't know if there
were even you know those bubbles with
something inside i wasn't sure
but on the next day they were already
gone
it was just you know yesterday i noticed
down like really tiny bubbles
but then today they're already gone it's
like as if they're never they never were
there in the first place i didn't do
anything you
hmm
but that's definitely
a very special sunburn that i had this
time with a lot of
a lot of issues
yeah
i
i will
be more careful
next time
[Music]
can't wait to move out to the new song
you guys
you guys really like the shiny new memes
right
if you guys keep on saying these words
i'm gonna pick them up and then i can't
stop saying them either you know i'm
like that i'm like a baby you guys teach
me the words and i can't stop using them
don't i already saw it was like trending
on twitter and all that
why is it even
that big now
what
why i don't get it
i don't
and would be not fetch yeah
oh no
she moving
don't lie
shut up
you guys are so stupid
oh yeah ahmed ahmed was playing with it
huh
maybe i should ask her what what is it
what is it all about
oh
this is spirit snare watching right now
spirits there made the logo
for fibonite
someone mentioned
something in the comments and it
reminded me um
i might show
something
[Music]
um
yeah 10 out of 10 as usual
i'm just gonna show it
remember when i told you guys that the
um
that the letters for my song as a teaser
i told you it's f right and then you
guys were like oh friday night or
whatever you guys kept on trying to
figure it out fried uh
whatever
whatever it was what was it friday
fried nuggets
and then there was one
yeah there's a new parody logo yes
there was one comment that stood out to
spirit snare i think
because he made this
[Laughter]
a different version
yeah um fortnite my new song please
listen to it on your music services
whatever spotify whatever
please
uh starting from midnight
fortnite will be available
on your spotify apple music amazon music
whatever itunes
and please watch the music video
fortnite let's go stream fortnite oh no
oh no oh no
oh no
[Music]
baby
let me to your xbox to play for night
nice lyrics you got there
oh [\h__\h] my super chats scrolled all the
way back up on y'all
i think i can find it where i was
right at the teaser there it is all
right um
don't
unfortunately i have to go to work oh no
yeah i guess i started in
like
morning time for pst
we'll vote later boss said enjoy the 17
hour for chad and i did
wait but did you
you can't schedule super chat did you
you stay awake or did you wake up for
some of these
now that i
think about it
you're crazy
i hope you got some sleep oh my god
an alarm every hour
you interrupted your sleep so many times
dedication
dedication be like you didn't have to do
that
yeah
i hope you got a good sleep on the
following day
oh man
[Music]
i need a massage again
ah
commitment
and sheer [\h__\h] will
across the dance
[Music]
indeed
i'm tired again guys i'm tired once
again oh guys i i wanted for lunch i
wanted to use up my my parmesan chicken
yeah
um that wasn't supposed to be chicken
parmesan but somebody mentioned chicken
parmesan so i was like hey i still got
bolognese sauce in my in my freezer so
let's use it up so i wanted to do that
for late lunch
and
so i made the noodles and i warmed up
the the boneless sauce in the in the
microwave and i put the chicken parmesan
thingy
in the oven and i tried to make it
crispy again and then i used a mold of
my oven that i usually don't use
and then i left for like
five minutes
and i go back
and see
my chicken parmesan started morphing
ah
everything
like the the paper the baking paper
around it was completely black and my
chicken parmesan was partially black and
the moment i opened the oven yeah i
turned on grill mold and i forgot i i
didn't forget but i underestimated how
strong the grill mold is
and i opened it and all the [\h__\h] uh
fog
came out and holy [\h__\h] it was so
stinky i had to open up the
door
uh and the windows
[Music]
so
what did i eat i just ate pasta
bolognese
instead i wanted to put my chicken on
top of it
now it ended up just being normal
volunteers that was boring
that was boring i'm getting so tired ah
quinoa
can't stay up late anymore i need energy
drinks what happened normally normally
i'm still awake at this time mom i'm too
healthy now
tired kiwawa once again today i woke up
before 10 a.m once again who is this
give me back old kiwawa
get me back
bring me back uh
oh so i'm feeling too hot
um
freedom
freedom okay
okay
i will not say
why i'm feeling freed now but
a part of my body feels less hot
um where was i level
dedication
posting a super chat every freaking hour
thank you so much
don't do this again okay you need your
sleep you're interrupting your sleep
like that not good
unless you can easily fall asleep again
in like five minutes but still
your boy stephen adams thank you for the
red super chat this is my first red
super chat i've given you this may be a
silly question but if you're excited for
pokemon scarlet or violet which starter
would you choose first of all thank you
for your first red super chat hold on
cushion very very generous and kind of
you wow
[Music]
i do like
the starters
[Music]
i like i like the apple
um
dinosaur or what was it
dino or
um
crocodile
or whatever that was supposed to be
but i also like the cats and i also like
the shabbat
i like them all
but
i think they still didn't put out the
the
um
evolutions right
so i think i have to judge by the
evolutions because i like their starter
forms all of them very much
i think i'll judge after seeing the
evolutions
[Music]
yeah they've been radio silent yeah
no i you know what i hope though i hope
they changed the style of the characters
though
the 3d models
for the characters the style
to me looks like um a game on a ds
where
it's for girls only girls are supposed
to play it and you're supposed to i
don't know um
you raise a horse or something
yeah
that's that's what it looks like a ds
game for girls
where you
raise a horse take care of a horse
they're barbie vibes yes
yeah i don't like it it doesn't look
like um the pokemon style
like the artwork the design concept
looks fine but then the way they made
that into 3d
looks
questionable although the artwork now
that i look at it again well while i'm
discussing this
um it looks like
the original pokemon style mixed with
uh ghibli style
yeah very much actually
but it doesn't translate well in 3d
and
they already showed the trailer so i
doubt they'll make such a big change
but i wish they did i wish they did
because i think i'm not the only one who
dislikes it yeah
i saw i saw a lot of you guys agreeing
to me
um
thank you
mm-hmm yeah we agree
pokemon plus
ghibli is barbie no i don't think that's
correct like that
something happened when putting when
when turning it into a 3d something
happened there the artwork was okay
no
the ninokuni rpg game yeah i feel like i
even played it privately before hollow
live
cocoon dancing lord eric dangashin
skydankashin the gimmick and ultra noob
is
[Music]
pink super chat from a korean kfp
this is for new cable mater k will be
with you thank you
thank you thank you much
i went out to buy a new cable
um and therefore had to delay the stream
i'm so sorry guys again so stupid i'm so
stupid
i'm sorry um but i didn't feel like
playing something else
in that moment
um
yeah i wanted to play something long and
and i wanted to play wind waker i was so
so
um determined on that one
so i know i could have just stayed at
home and played something else but
you guys were
expecting wind waker and i know you
would have been fine of something else
but you were expecting it and i was
expecting it and i wanted to do it i was
in the mood for wind windwanker
but then yeah
i wanted to be fast so
uh
i stressed myself
i'm sorry i'm sorry for the delay man
that was a long delay it's not normal
here but sometimes
sometimes also the the
oversleeping a little bit that's also
unlike me but i guess
once a year it can happen okay
i will say that you may
shake your heads
at the moment when it happens and be
like ah okay
but
i want to hear
how many
how often you guys always sleep for work
in a year
okay
it can happen sometimes
wow
okay you guys are so sweet i love you
guys i love you guys
and i also never over sleep
i really don't
but okay i did i did the other day
thank you for the pinky oh boy
thank you
[Music]
spicy
just fine always we are keanus chicken
[Music]
you i'm so glad i have my kind
kind-hearted audience
here for me always supporting me thank
you
[Music]
you're so sweet
foreign
thanks for all the work you put in keanu
i respect the hustle right back to work
after vacation you're a great example to
us all no more of the self-deprecating
humor okay please what did they say
you're great things happen somebody's
gonna deal with it who you're gonna call
camp it
oh i suppose about you know the whole
cable thing mm-hmm
thank you
for being so sweet
uh
yeah but to be honest you praised me for
being right back to work
but
i
i want to go back to vacation
ah
i feel
uh
i feel the presto espresso
and i don't know i feel
weaker than before
i don't know why
i have no energy
and i have
i don't know
issues
staying awake now
and i feel hot and my throat feels
[\h__\h]
even more than before
[Music]
it's weird
but i started taking
vitamin d again from today it probably
won't show much um results that soon but
yeah
i gotta
take vitamin d properly
sunburn i don't know i don't think
moving to sunburn had that much of a big
effect
maybe in
the first
day or second day or so but um
uh
i think it's just general
exhaustion
and also now i'm kind of used to
going to sleep earlier so maybe it is
partially the jet lag but also like
yesterday when we played the wind waker
uh
we started at 4 pm my time
and
i was already tired at the beginning of
it
but that was okay i guess because i
i ran in the heat outside to get that
stupid cable
but generally i feel like
i can't take long hours of streaming
anymore it's weird
maybe i need to start drinking coffee
maybe i need coffee man but i don't like
the taste of coffee
did the vacation do nothing for you
it did it did a lot
i don't know i think
oh no it's something else
he has caffeine see i believe you and i
do i
i did try out different teas before and
see how
they work on me and i i noticed that
green tea especially
made me awake when i was working early
shifts uh let's start at six a.m
um
not as strong as coffee does i would say
but yeah i don't know
maybe i should try green tea again
[Music]
i streamed six salads yesterday yeah but
compare that to me back in the day
like last year
um
yeah i feel like last year i didn't have
to force myself
that much just to stay
high energy energy high energy i can't
speak anymore oh my god
back in the day
i would recommend green tea over coffee
hmm
yeah i definitely prefer to taste
as well
yeah life is also very stressful right
now so that's the thing too
um
yeah
well thank you anyway dr tag so nice to
have you around thank you for your sweet
words
i'm going to continue
with the hustle yeah
she saw the gondra thank you you need to
chat thanks for the pinky yeah don't
worry too much look at how you went out
of your way to save the zelda stream and
got it working yeah you didn't cancel or
swap it to some random other game or
anything you made it happen you're
committed on the resource phone thank
you oh
how sweet
yeah i didn't feel like streaming
something else so
that was just my personal vaga mama
maybe
um
yeah
thank you thank you
and you know how to cheer me up huh
thank you
devil
[Music]
thank you for the double red super chat
what a chat cause you just leave that
there and say nothing
thank you
[Music]
wow mysterious super chatter
i appreciate your support thank you
get right to you obliterating me
what what what
movie thank you soon
oh thank you
[Music]
what's it this time
i was scrolling down twitter when i got
a notification of your new tweet i
called my poker friends to check it and
when i opened the tweet there was a
model covered in oil and skimpy bikini
and my friends all laughed and looked at
me like
slow
a model covered in oil and a skimpy
bikini what is he talking
about yeah did i retweet something
[Laughter]
wow
wow you remember that
slowpoke
why are you crying slowpoke
didn't you appreciate my retweet
oh yeah i cannot retweet i know that was
also spicy but i have to retweet good
art how can i not
hm
are there any german speaking viewers
here right now by the way
i mean i know there's at least
two
anymore
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah oh
hey
[Music]
look magnet magnesium
really
okay cool
uh
nice good to know
um
[Music]
robot
yeah
okay
let's look to english
when i speak german so suddenly i speak
like a robot
klingstein
no song
and your boss
okay
okay let's go back to english i just
wanted to
see how many german-speaking people are
here
so
where was i
but it's cool to see you branch out to
other genres any
genres any chance you'd consider a
eurobeat song
um
if anything has a remix version but
probably not as a single
yeah
i like your repeat but not so much that
i would release a whole single
like that yeah freak video gamer duncan
randy rj
i think these are flush chats so i'm
going to skip this scoop
para's toy goddamn kitchen
yeah that's true
thank you for the thinking
yo tantra so excited to hear your new
song i'm sure it will be a banger i just
got my wisdom tube removed today oh no
so it was actually quite lucky it got
moved to tomorrow ah
speaking of which may i receive some
kind words from my egg and gums oh man
were you kind of like high when you
wrote that i wonder
did you get like some
something injected so that you
dream of rainbows and unicorns
because your your super chat sounded
very normal
uh
and the steve said yeah yeah that's what
i mean
i hope it was okay
i hope it was i don't know that sounds
really scary
wisdom too removal
but i hope your gums are feeling better
now
[Music]
i will blow on them to make them feel
better okay
open your mouth
don't make this into something weird
okay now your gums feel better right
don't
i'm i'm doing something nice
like a mommy okay
hmm
you have an ouchy did your mommy never
blow on it
be honest
no shut up that's i don't believe it
you just don't remember it or you don't
want to remember it because you're
embarrassed
my mom never did she told me to man up
wow she kissed it okay see that's
comparable
that's cute
are you drinking tea no i'm going to get
tea yes
uh
blub baby duncan happy
birthday
related but still happy birthday
julio paso stanky should
i think i'm all
i'm i'm at the end almost oh my god
speed
is this uh
thank you soon
still very happy to still see you around
thank you miss fizz thank you so much
you know what i'm gonna read the ones
from the music video
and then i might stop and read the ones
from this stream tomorrow i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry but then tomorrow i'll try
to
end it a bit earlier or we might even
start an hour early
maybe how about that
maybe we'll start an hour earlier would
you guys mind
i know a lot of you guys live in like
estpsd
[Music]
old time sounds currently
i'm an eu so it's fine yeah and it's a
sunday so
maybe you guys can adjust to me please
[Music]
it's not like a
whole life member to sleep at midnight
that's just it's
wrong
is there any other hall life member who
sleeps at like before midnight
i don't believe it you have to prove it
to me
it's too healthy something like that
doesn't exist hover really
thomas has a healthy sleep schedule
sleeping before midnight are you kidding
me ready where do you know that from
ena no no no no i know for a fact that
ina
has
like a twisted
twisted sleep schedule
don't you dare lie to me you're just
randomly throwing names at me now
cola has been kind of bad recently
[Music]
yep maybe she seems like someone who
would um have a healthy sleep schedule
it's just she's so say so that even her
sleep schedule must be safer
can't really imagine soros and by
staying up until 4am right
that's weird
when even the sleep schedulers say so
thank you
for the smackdown
foreign
this this genre
people have been saying that i'm the
first one in her life to touch this
genre
it's a cool genre
[Music]
oh
yes that can be cool too but honestly i
wanted to be
how to stay
a little bit
uh at least like in the singing style i
i tried and probably didn't succeed too
much but i wanted to be a little bit
sultry is that the right word
i tried but you guys probably don't hear
a difference
[Music]
no not salty
sultry yo
a little bit
okay
you definitely were at some point all
right that's good enough for me
[Music]
by the way before
um
before like
deciding on
the final mix i sent it to gooda because
i wanted someone else's opinion because
i already like listened to it like a
million times
and i wasn't sure anymore if what i was
what like i was hearing was really good
or if it's just me being used to it i
sent it to buddha and i was like yogurt
can you like give me
some input do you think this is like too
much reverb and so on
and then
the only thing
she said to
me um
was
wait where was it
she said she like she liked a lot how i
sang crazy for your rhythm wow
so she really liked the song but i
didn't get any like
um feedback if something sounds off so i
guess it was okay
i think she forgot about the fact that i
wanted some
some uh feedback about the mix but
yeah basically
the
feedback was
wow amazing well 10 out of 10.
yeah she was just vibing she sent me
like a a gift gift i will say it both
ways so that you guys don't get mad i
give gif of uh like a vaporwave
background
yeah she was vibing to it
yeah i would hope so that she would have
said something if something was off
maybe it was just that perfect
[Music]
i didn't want to share it with too many
people because i wanted it to be a
surprise
no
but i'm hoping that the other whole life
members
like it too and that they give it a
listen
i did send the instrumental out to the
whole live english members and todayna
and gave them the lyrics too and i said
yo
if you want to sing this feel free i
would be happy
i sent them the instrumental
oh
[Music]
i think i think there's a chance that
they might sing it because um it's an
english song
that you can sing in an archived stream
now we don't have much
of that sword
you guys can sing it too of course of
course please do
wayne will 100 sure yeah i think so he
she then finally has
more kiwawa songs to sing
yeah
can't wait to hear this orange
instantly killed by boss's cute 80s
fashion trip yeah since i'm dead boss
can i pass my kids to dominick oh okay
dom's been doing great work helping us
that can't go to document send your love
and messages thank them oh
yeah and i've heard i've heard
organizing like some uh kfb fan booth so
that's very sweet thank you for the hard
work indeed mwah
yes yes and also yeah i freaking love
the
outfit so much it's one of my favorite
things about the whole song is
the chance to get to do these super cute
outfits
soon
i was saying oh [\h__\h]
um soon
how long is it again two months three
months three months i think in three
months
many of you
will reach their two years anniversary
of membership
because that's when i opened the
membership two years ago the four maps
okay
and i was like [\h__\h] wait what that's
like so soon like oh i remember when i
was setting up the memberships
i was like oh one year that's so far and
then two years holy [\h__\h] two years
that's never gonna happen wait what the
[\h__\h] wait what we actually gonna reach
two years what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
and then i was saying like
because i added the two-year membership
emote later on not emoto the badge
um
and made it into
a
revived chicken
i said that oh [\h__\h] i
i didn't actually think
that
this that you guys would stay that long
and then i would really need all these
phoenix dance to revive every single one
of you so now i'm a little bit [\h__\h]
where do i get all these phoenix dance
from now yeah
another thing to stress out about great
i don't know where to get them from yeah
we have two the ones in my ears
i will
maybe buy them from the
um
the secret market
i'll buy them from them
uh it's called black market
and in germany we say black market
phoenix black market
[Music]
buy them from screens this is probably
really expensive
the spicy market same in english okay
for the pinky you got not time to do the
lyrics for you okay now i'm even more
excited can't wait to hear your new song
also the art is amazing can't look away
anyway hype yeah the art mamaloni always
delivers
yeah
oh i'm so so so happy to work with her i
know like
you guys made me want to see like
different artists too and i agree like i
want to see like different artists too
in theory but then mama looney is so
easy to work with like ah
and easy on my budget
and i just love her she's so vast and i
love the way she draws me so
much and yeah
a lot
but for the next song i'm aiming it to
be a 3d music video so
there probably won't be any art at all
just the music video and the 3d
me and 3d with my default outfit because
yeah getting a different outfit
won't make it in time and i don't think
the default output fits the next song
but we'll have to deal with it
we'll have to make it fit
um
a musical video
we'll make it in time but there will be
no no that's not really what i mean
if i ever do a concert then yes for a
concert i would um
try to get
myself a different outfit for 3d like a
cute idolish
performance stage outfit
can you edit the color oh
interesting
thought
that's
interesting let me write that down write
that down kfb i
i'll will ask
don't have to write it down that was a
joke i'm just going to ask myself
hey
idea
um
[Music]
i might not
next don't get your hopes up it might
not be
possible
because like default outfits shouldn't
really be
changed usually but i'll ask
yeah
anyway continuing and the game recruit
duncan can you stand standard from
suzuki
and afternoon
krt
thanks for the pinky thank you
but i have been double jumped in for the
pinky love
[Music]
where are we going to the dance floor
let's go let's go this little party
party
good i can go red sometimes yeah that's
true that's okay cause like she's doing
it on her own
um i guess but
yeah um
like for example i asked if i can have
um
like a different hairstyle additionally
for my default outfit and i was told no
but for my other outfits maybe
yeah but not for the default
so like because changes cannot be made
to the default
just so you know
yeah
what the [\h__\h] you got into an accident
are you okay
i wish you the best
don't worry what the hell
don't worry about me
you can't go bald and deep
now that that's what you're talking
about you're talking about you know
those moments when cali goes bald in 3d
yeah i can do that too in theory
i guess but no then it's more like a bug
than
intentionally
i don't want to see bulky
[Music]
now
where was i
morgan shendon thank you thank you for
thank you
so so so so so so so generous thank you
way to kind thank you thank you thank
you
lazarus
um
[Music]
humidifier again maybe
in the next like tomorrow remind me
tomorrow if i forget remind me to turn
on my humidifier please
maybe it will help a little bit do you
do you hear it
because i definitely
notice a difference
i see my voice i feel like is [\h__\h]
maybe you guys don't hear so much
different
no no i mean on my voice and
yeah
raspy
no
i tried to
i tried to like
um
make it sound normal but
it's it's a little bit tough
oh and i'm so tired right now i can
barely keep my eyes open
oh man i need to you know i
uh
i wanted i i thought when i planned out
this week
um
that was on sunday when i came back from
the maldives okay
and i was like
as as far as i know myself
i may have a healthy sleep schedule
right now when i came back from the
maldives but i know i will ruin it
immediately and go back to staying up
until 4am anyway
so that's why i put
streams at this late time
into my schedule because i expected to
[\h__\h] it up again but here i am still
having a healthy sleep schedule and
being very very tired right before
midnight i did not expect myself to keep
this up for so long
and i don't think you expected it either
oh man so maybe next week
uh the few streams that we are having
are going to be a little bit early maybe
s-e-a time zone is going to be happy
all right so what happened
[Music]
hi i'm
i know right you guys always always
always say ash your baby has to have a
sleep schedule for one day but you'll
[\h__\h] it up again tomorrow
surprise i didn't
ah
i'm so tired
i'm so sorry
why am i so tired
i'm so tired chunky chunk thank you for
the red super chat
indeed fever i feel favorable i don't
have a fever but this is how i feel when
i have a favor
risai thank you
for thank you for the of a chat i come
down with a favor this night because
that song was saying
thank you
how do i
how do i make you
be healthy again i don't want you to be
sick
[Music]
efo you can't be sick you're still
working on something for me
gumbagafo deadline coming up soon
bye top
everyone support fo fo is working for
someone something for me
etho by the way
elsie love and donkey soon why did i
give you a kiss at all
i don't go i forgot
thank you thanks for laughing i'm glad
you liked it
thank you for the pinky well the bob
such a classic feeling while giving us
that rare low tone keep our list yeah
actually that
original
was so low that i really had some
trouble singing that line
um
now just now i sang it higher than it's
supposed to be
ah
some some parts were
mostly only those parts
with original
that one was really difficult
somehow hypnotic perhaps for the mv2 i
really love the low poly graphics ah the
low poly phoenix
yeah yeah yeah yeah
the mv is really really great
i told ere that he really captured what
i wanted
very very well
even though you know
when i was
making
the storyboard and like decided on like
what i want and all that
to be honest like i know the 80s only
very superficially obviously and i
couldn't think of much that was
80s and 70s to me
so
i think i didn't really provide that
much
material
in terms of what i wanted in the video i
basically you know i said this girl
um old tv
old phone
uh taxi
um
yeah um
yeah no put myself no no
yeah but he still did a great job
putting it all together and yeah i know
no flip phones but whatever it's okay i
i i want that to be in there i feel like
it fits the mood
the phone was a bit too modern yeah
that's true
yeah
maybe it was a
a fake one like you know a toy flip
phone that's not working
that could have already existed maybe
you know those that the children play
with that don't work
mary pippin's bangs on the
pinky i already read that one thank you
secondhand thank you for the red super
chat wow love love pure fire loved every
second of that thank you
i'm glad you like it please continue
listening to it a lot so
that
uh
that the music department sees some
results
[Laughter]
uh real talk
uh yeah
i can listen to it forever though so i
think you guys can listen to it forever
too or at least as long as you
stay alive as a chimpkin
wow yes dream favorite night forever i
like that
stream favorite not forever make it even
longer than it needs to be
it's so catchy thank you
it's almost 100k
thank you
jay swagman friends with a pinky and
this is great super unique song and so
much detail in the music video thank you
yes it is definitely unique
yeah
i'm glad that i could impress you guys
with a synthwave song yeah yeah yeah
so many of you guys expected different
genres
not really
a lot of people guessed it to be
synthwave
hey
surprise bamboozle can i still steam
stream love conquer
what the [\h__\h] is love cooker
well yes you're welcome to stream heart
challenges like love conquer is like
some secret code to describe heart
challenger
stream love conqueror
i love that
tracy um for the pinky favorite night is
so awesome kiwawa you totally rocked it
on the vocals and the music is so cool
as well thank you
the mv itself was just so high quality
too
absolutely love it i'm totally going to
be streaming it like crazy once it comes
out here thank you yeah it's still gonna
be a couple of hours
what time is it in the u.s i mean i know
you have more than one time zone but
whatever tell me
4 p.m
6 p.m 3 p.m
okay that's still quite some time until
midnight but
you know what to do
at midnight right you know what to do
also
five minutes until midnight in my time
zone
so my dear european friends you also
know what to do right right right right
right
yoroshiku onegaishimasu
yeah
what
please uh stream my song
stream favorite nine stream fifa night
forever
stream favorite night
buying it from itunes the moment
midnight hits thank you
thank you
and evansell thank you for the pinky i'm
genuinely just surprised it was
expecting a mess on but no i'm actually
jamming to this
why'd you expect a mer song hello we're
talking about takanashi kiwawa
nice going kiana and team i'll be
looping this i guess
[\h__\h] sunday
i have confidence in me yeah
if i can't have confidence in myself you
guys need to be confident in me
yeah there's no man in kiwawa world i'm
just being honest okay is it because you
just don't like the genre in general but
then this one actually
was um
something you liked
then i guess i get it
i guess
because it's a new genre for me oh but
well i mean i'm working with someone
experienced so obviously it's gonna be
good
okay i'm dying here here's the last
super chatter
and now i'm gonna fall asleep and
lose my voice
oh
flip phones were in star trek in the 70s
apparently so
duh
they had a vision
okay guys i will um read the rest
tomorrow
i guess we'll just um play the game a
little bit less and we'll start an hour
early um
okay i'm falling asleep
and in german myself
and i love you guys
i wanna be i wanna be hyper because of
the song release but
i was already tired at the beginning of
this thing
oh why am i so tired
uh i'm turning into a
sloth slopjol
i'm sloth
[Music]
okay guys
uh something's wrong with me
i don't know i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry
i feel like i'm not at my
um full
potential i'm not at my best
[Music]
i'm
gonna try to
fix it i don't know how but i'll try to
fix it
um
keep up on your service
yes
indeed
i wouldn't mind going to sleep now with
my quitocatos
okay
and in german yourself with us in
tomorrow wind wake i'm excited for that
more wind wake up more wind waka let's
go let's go let's go let's go let's go
more wind waker
um
yeah i love you guys
thank you the reception on the song
was so so good thank you very much i'm
very happy about it
and i hope you guys will continue
listening to it and not eventually end
up like the first line in the song
i'm tired of
fever night
every day like it's on repeat
it's literally like spoiler in the
future you after listening to it for 100
times
that's that's what you're gonna be like
yeah
but then i'm gonna be like continue
streaming it and you're gonna be like
okay attention
that's all
[Music]
reservation right after the stream ends
so free feel free to
look at pre-chat while you're streaming
remember you have to stay in the window
when you're streaming my song on the
music video on youtube you have to stay
in the video otherwise otherwise the
view doesn't count as we learned
yesterday
and good night everybody
just came out on spotify in italy oh
yeah it's midnight
gmt plus two check your spotifys or
whatever you're using
bye-bye
bye bye
and no tabbing out no no
bye
[Music]
stream favorite night stream favorite
night
[Music]
stream favorite night
you can play fortnite while streaming
fever night
it's your funky nuggets
oh that's a cute title
[Music]
spanx and heart
love conquer
oh man
[Music]
fried nutella
no
[Music]
ah