a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
d
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
K good
morning good
day good
night to all of
y'all
hello oh my
God we are early today haven't streamed
at this time in a while I think we are
are going to play Minecraft wait I
forgot to do a tweet let me do a
tweet chunky wonky staring at
me and she looks like a freaking
Dorito she looks like a
Doro okay starting
[Music]
now because of her shape the triangle
shape
hi Shas opening quite early what you
think
so quite normal I would
say oh
sure okay it's been uh also a while
since I played
Minecraft uh was this Minecraft was okay
just like this right not not window
capture
right okay okay ah it needs to
be
longer
no like
this free mods I have threee mods loaded
really I thought I just have one
okay
ah it's 11 a.m. for me yeah it might be
a really shitty time for Ena
though ah I think today there's going to
be a lot of action I'm joining today for
the first time but I saw there's a bunch
of new Japanese members joining today
just for one day uh they're on a mission
of helping everybody with tasks that
seem very dangerous so that they can die
without worrying like they're going to
do some dangerous things apparently four
people are on that mission as far as I
know as far as I
know the FAA get okay I got FAA into the
server yeah and uh and P Senai also
thanked me for my heroic
[Music]
actions okay oh okay I think you can
hear the game maybe I'm like it a little
bit
louder okay uh uh uh my voice seems to
[Music]
work I
am on the server let's go there's
already so much stuff I think
uh are these are the are these
the these are the missions as far as I
know oh oh for example there's a mission
where you get two diamonds if you get
Neza
[Music]
wart oh you get 10 diamonds if you go
get uh um frog eggs with someone you
have never like did anything before like
I couldn't get this with Ena hi Ollie I
know you have a diamond armor for me
right uh you get five diamonds for
destroying a GH go ghost GH G NE s oh if
you get Soul Sand and never you get free
diamonds so today is the day where they
open the never glow stone uh getting
glowstone brings you free
diamonds I feel like a lot of the others
already have a bunch of diamonds but I
have nothing wa this one gives you 30
diamonds
I'm not sure what this means called non
non
n but this means if you're the first
person to discover the never
itself
Sanai 30 Diamonds oh The Fortress ah oh
yeah that makes sense 30 diamonds that's
a lot man but I don't know I think today
I I I will probably go into The Nether
but that's not really my priority what
this a yeah I think so I need to take my
head right this is my
head and then put it on the wall I
think I
think oh
okay it's been a while no wait what how
does it work how do they put it on
there is it left click or so no BM yeah
oh I probably should put bring some bgm
ah how do I put it
shift oh
okay my head is so fre
so and is there anything else here to
do oh okay uh wait
bgm I'm not going to die like even in in
my recent like not recent but the the
last Minecraft streams that I had like I
generally don't die anymore but that's
because like everything's so safe I have
armor I have weapons you know so okay
there's definitely higher chances of me
dying
now let's
see what's this okay for now I know it's
a little bit mind breaking but for now
we're going to play this bgm are you
hearing it it's really
quiet I just don't want to
drown out people's voices
later but here well maybe a little bit
louder
that lava lava
no mind breaking yay uh
uh there's a there's a
locker for survivors for exist
yeah is there anything else I need to do
in the
beginning about missions
doing
missions these are just general messages
yeah okay and inside
here ah yeah I need to H but I don't I
think I only need to take a diary at the
end of the day and then I Rite it and I
get uh one diamond for it I
think I think I know where all's home is
is is is K Senai really not speaking or
am I do I have the wrong Senai
[Music]
Senai
foree okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay so yeah I actually I watched a few
streams in preparation in the past days
uh I watched a bit of P streams a bit of
Ena streams a bit of uh Ollie streams a
little bit of
everything so
I I know that this is Ollie's house I
know that this is ena's house oh shesh
what what did did she make over
there and I I know my way around a
little
bit oh wasn't this path originally a one
block
path or maybe not but uh I think it was
like kind of dangerous to be up
here do you still remember how to play
Minecraft
M yeah partially ah paa fixed it so it
was really only one One path one block
right m
so this is PA's house I know I can get a
bed for free here and free torches let's
go take free bed take free Gohan okay I
take blue
bed yeah I say I take a blue bed and I
take a white bed uh okay um maybe I
don't know uh I don't want to take all
of this maybe let's take some cooked
mutton gold boots ah for the ne I will
need this and I'll take this free
pickaxe let's go free Farm
F what this is this what farm is this
what farm is
this can you guys recognize what this is
oh maybe it it's for these things to
harvest oh it's a cooking
station oh it did cook the Cod I guess
you put anything up here and it Cooks
it oh o okay I
think I think I have what I need I know
that this uh uh all the Sakura Tre is
there from vat Senai I think because vat
Senai it was vat Senpai right she went
out to find
uh she went out to find the Sakura biom
me and yeah then planted Sakura here and
there
uh wait so I got lost wait
where's oh yeah over there then I don't
know I guess I'll uh try to make
something next to them although I need
some blocks to build anything
really but first and foremost I hope I
don't lose it
but this is Ollie's house and she loves
me therefore she said I can take her
diamond
armor uh do I take this with right click
or left click
guys I don't know help me out she's such
an angel Senai
text was that her DM
yeah empty hand ah ah oh okay right
click and
uh I I'm sure there's a button where you
can then automatically put it on but
look I'm I'm wearing my I should
actually but I don't feel so op yet
that's why I'm in my Farmer
outfit but in reality I feel like one
day one day I'll become a
warrior
again
fies yeah I I
I still know how to play Minecraft but
there's uh certain things that you know
maybe maybe for now I'll move in with
Ollie well
it yeah I don't know why I would be
sleeping why can't you even sleep at
during the daytime why I thought that
wasn't
impossible okay oh wait it is it is an
evening oh it just started to become
evening
now I think Ena should be streaming now
too right did she not start yet cuz
she's not locked in at least there's CL
[Music]
Kyla did she like has she been streaming
for like 24 hours or
what oh oh she on
flowers Ena whose house is this
no
bed subu Senai join the game but I think
superu Senai has been playing already
for a while like generally she's not one
of the
four uh people who
will uh sacrifice themselves okay I'm
going to I know I'm not ready to go to
the de I need weapons and stuff oh
like is there any like free stuff to
take any more than this
like it would be nice to get some
iron or I guess like I can just get some
stone for now Stone stuff ah man I don't
remember how to start from
zero
uh there's there's there's something
there's an iron form
somewhere need gold yeah I have the gold
boots at least
near nearby do you need to go H I don't
know I mean I don't have to but they're
opening it up uh
soon near the spawn you don't have
Senpai Senpai Senpai
Senpai Ma
oh yeah with Co COI I was basically just
saying hello and saying oh
yeah uh oh is that
free uh yeah I'm joining today Euro
school is that house
free does this belong to someone this
looks like it was a villager area this
this all of this I feel like this was a
villager
area this looks like nobody's using it
right anyway I know that this is the
court that thing over
there uh an iron is this the iron
[Music]
trap that's a oh no it's
raining the whole area yeah that's what
I thought the whole area was a village
so we can take these houses as a base to
build something out of it
oh God oh God it surely horse it surely
will not count right if I die now like
early the first
[Music]
hour oh she's swimming she's doing a
swim my my
uh my distance is like can I change
that there's nothing about distance I
think damn it cuz I want to hear
everybody from F
away okay this looks like
it
okay oh this is scary ah what people
already built stuff like this this is
from Kyla or so because I saw her
dealing with villagers in her stream
they are still working on
this this is the This what I think it is
this this looks like it could be
a an iron
[Applause]
trap now this just says if you have any
problems with this uh like if it's not
working let's eat
H where's where do I get the iron oh
right that h
Y how do I get down safely how do I how
do I how do
I I don't know how to go down on a
ladder uh uh
uh uh uh stay close to the
ladder no okay okay okay
okay truly a cat
moment and I don't see even any Treasure
Chest to like take oh wait maybe with
with the
[Music]
train for
nice nice
nice
[Music]
hi okay so loud making me nervous
uh okay how do I I don't know if I need
that much but okay okay wao so many
recipes let's go but we got the shield
we just need a
sword I think this is a good starting
point there was no sword in here right
no but an axe is something to fight with
at
least okay and then I wonder if there
there's any more like free
blocks I'm so late to the party you
know okay
equip I got the shield okay okay okay
okay nice probably need some wood oh
yeah can I chop these
trees are these special trees I don't
they're they're kind of nicely
lined in a line
replant I don't want to
replant okay let's see if I get some
saplings I'll
replant I think maybe fauna will also
join
today speaking of saplings I told her
don't worry fauna you're not the only
one that's late I'm also late and then
she was like oh that's really indeed a
relief
yeah okay
okay I told her if there's anything you
don't understand in the server in the
Discord server because like a lot of
things are only Japanese let me
know yeah so it's going to be all right
I
think
yeah okay where are the saplings come
on come
on fall down give me saplings
oh there we
go
got don't know if anybody made this or
if this is natural
trees but I'm trying to
replant I feel like since this is
Hardcore Minecraft oh look at that since
this is Hardcore Minecraft this is like
for me I can see this as a roleplay
opportunity like this could be Fallout
this is this is Fallout this is the
apocalypse we're all short on everything
we have to repopulate that's there was
nobody here before now we have to
repopulate you know it's a dire
situation but we have to work hard
together but who knows if we all really
are good people maybe we're not
okay this is
good repopulate how well by joining the
server okay don't get it twisted I am
repopulating the World by joining the
server right now I am from another Vault
I was a vault dweller once the Vault was
called H life englishan
server nice okay I think I got all these
trees e this n so Eno over
there let's say hi
to byebye
[Music]
W what's
up wait oh I guess you got you got the
pick Pi a stone gear from from Ollie uh
yeah I got it from Ollie yeah oh my God
my connection is so bad is it like what
do you hear me like a
robot no no okay
oh oh I don't have it right now
oh oh well uh maybe my bed okay run car
run
okay yeah B uh coote also sounded a
little bit like a robot to me a moment
ago yeah my bed is in ol's house
okay ah there's a bed
here
hi it should really it should go for the
night now right yeah yeah okay
yeah all right uh I'm going to I'm going
to check the missions and stuff
okay I'll use this
house I'll use this
house I'm just going to use it it's my
house now Kiana don't eat
it
this what is that can't
see I don't have optify or anything on
right now so I can't zoom I wish I could
zoom wait I need to get my
bed from Ollie house I built
[Music]
this small small house small small T of
house man I'm I'm nervous about
this
you oh house take bed my bed I mean what
does she
have no no ooh
what why does she have oh yeah Cobble
deep slet is from from like down not the
nether anywhere it's just from really
low low low low low underground
right fancy
I mean what does she need it for maybe I
could take it and build a proper house
with
that oh yeah I think
banai is one of
the people who are offering their
services I
think okay I got these saplings might
might as well plant
them it's my tree
now uh okay and then uh you make uh a a
box oh wait okay first I guess I
can do this oh so many so many
planks how does this work
again yeah that's what I
fought crafting table and then we can
make oh why can it not type
in ah
ah check
CH and a sword would be
uh why I write it like
Japanese cuz there's no like when you
write sword in Japanese you write
sword
like
sword iron sword
yay uh a
shovel iron shovel
uh that's it I think iron pickaxe iron
axe shovel sword am I missing
something shears I don't need oh bow and
arrow would be nice but like I don't
think I although I saw a lot of feathers
at uh paa's
Farm a bucket would probably be
good oh oh a sign to put my name
[Music]
there does it have a
door
yeah water bucket always good to have a
water
bucket
oh kiar
house but this might not stay in my
house forever who knows uh uh sorry I
keep on pressing tab for some reason
must be some other game that's confusing
me ah wait is it sor St Valley where you
open the inventory with a
tab
house no that's e h i wonder what it was
with with uh that
button uh okay let's put down the chest
where though let's get rid of this here
yeah need more
space maybe even a second
one chest was this a boat what what the
was that other
one I'm
[Music]
waiting bamboo
raft what the
what heo
what
happened no not the pink B there's a
bamboo raft he
cool um damn
it okay I think so I can I I can put
this here I can put this
away yeah maybe all of them put this
away okay what now what now I need to so
the end goal is to for everybody to
survive and kill the
and a dragon I wish there were some
missions that were easy to achieve for a
newcomer like
[Music]
me didn't see her coming oh why should I
maybe re rejoin maybe then the VC will
be fixed let me
[Music]
rejoin she was floating right yeah okay
H here's someone
digging so let's look at the missions
again where are the missions again here
yeah okay is there anything as simple I
can do I think these are all pretty
much yeah not all of them but it's kind
of difficult there's one for like most
of them are for the never but this one
is for killing uh free
skeletons I couldn't FY do that I mean I
can also just do some stuff in never
this should be easy
like although not the gastal I don't
want to try killing the
gastal glow stone glowstone wait
glowstone is only in the nether right
yeah maybe I'll find it accidentally
[Music]
yeah skeletons are fine but those only
appear in the night really oh and do
they wait do they appear in the ne cuz
in the night the thing is and for Senai
brought this up uh in the our Discord
the thing is like
um oh I in the caves too yeah like if
you're hunting for something that only
appears in the night then you're going
to have problems cuz everybody skips the
night why you so careful why you so
careful W yeah what
happened it was not you it was not you
what what what happen why are you so
depressed no no you gave her a chw and
she didn't chew you back no no I thought
I thought she said chew so I was like
chw but then she was like oh not chew me
too I was like oh oh me me too oh oh
it's okay you can have my
too I got to
do did you build a house yet uh I just
like took one of the broken villager
houses for now oh you too
yeah you want to see my house I I
already saw it in your stream but
yeah
okay I saw you made some additions some
nice improvements pretend you didn't see
yet okay this is my green corn doog you
might have remembered from the uh Ian
server back in the day green corn
hog green dog corn dog corn dog cor dog
M
yummy yeah this is my
house ena's
house yeah I got blown up by a creeper
yesterday I fixed it oh if I ever need
like some dirt or some Cobble deep slate
can I take it from you yeah yeah of
course of course oh you have some broken
bows did you go fishing or what yeah I
did I have a pretty good fishing fishing
rod so oh that's my goal to fix it today
to bring it to the nether what do you
think I should do like I I finished my
house and I made uh some weapons I have
weapons and I have armor and yeah um I
mean I think oh are you are you going to
plan to go to the nether today I guess
so yeah cuz most of the missions today
are for the nether yeah so I think if
you want to go for the go for the
missions then you should just prepare
for the nether cuz it's opening like in
a bit right yeah or gu a bow and arrows
would be nice yeah and I have I I have
the list for today it's like prepare
enough food
prepare extra gear like Shield weapons
and then bring enough building blocks
enchant gear if
possible um all right blocks will nice
for yeah and then last thing very
important bring Kyla bring KY yeah
should we just stay with
KY maybe that's my plan nice okay I'll
get some food then and I try to get
arrows in a bow maybe yeah okay bye-bye
bye don't I need a string though well
wait can you can I take one of
bows um I think there's
only uh cuz I'm going to be merging two
of them and then keeping one as like a
backup bow but Kyla definitely has um
string too so okay she has like a spider
fall apparently okay sleep first yeah we
can talk again okay okay she's got to
show me where Kyla is or I'll I'll just
Rite Kyla don't
try fishing I don't have a
rod I don't have
anything
okay um let me see uh tea
[Music]
KY can I come visit you
yeah the diamond armor is a good start
right it's a really good start thank god
let's see if Kyla also sounds like a
robot to me where are
you I am at ol
house let's go to
Indonesia H am I am I troubling her is
she like is she doing something
important but she says all wolf of
course
so I can compare y y is she coming with
with a boat like imagine if she just
pulls up here with her boat and I just
start hearing GTA
music I'm imagining the the the music
that you hear with like missions oh
what's up hello I'm also one to be
picked up by Kyla oh well I don't know
if there's more than one space in her
boat if she comes with
boat I don't think she's on a boat I
have a feeling she's coming on the boat
you know I can swim he can swim I can
swim oh well well we could let's see how
she arrives do you think she oh I was
going to say she might already have
wings but we didn't go to oh yeah no
it's not possible I mean she she might
at the end of all this
yeah
oh Kyla do Kyla what do you want from
from Kyla
some string too
ah we want the same thing it
seems yeah but I want an already
finished bow because I have nothing to
work with right now oh I have uh yeah I
just want to make bow so I can repair my
bows
yeah
yeah are you going to play for long
today what do you think cuz it's like
are you not tired are you okay I'm
exhausted but at least 3 hours hopefully
around there okay okay at least want to
you know drop out the ne yeah yeah yeah
we should kill a gas
together oh yeah we can but do do we get
each one of us gets those diamonds or do
they get split then if we kill it
together that's true maybe we can kill
two then yeah yeah is just somebody I
guess we just need the achievement to
kill
one maybe and then each one of us needs
a last hit I don't know if if they look
at the achievements but I don't think
it's the last kid but okay we just
killed two yeah minimum two we need to
free the ne of the
casts but there does you know their
voices yeah it's like it's like one of
the developers cat for oh yeah yeah I
know I heard that yeah you know the
random knowledge I already know that one
oh I should replace the gas's uh voices
with my own cat's voices that be cute
that cool that be
[Music]
cute W doio doio I'm so lost right
now it's okay steady steady steps
okay do you have do you know if there's
a way to like extend the rad ra ra
radius rad do you say that in English
the the distance of when you can hear uh
people I think that's server side oh
okay okay yeah the it's the only R Us
okay radi oh did you know there's
apparently there's a a court meeting
happening did you ever uh uh Join one
yet or is it your first one no I don't I
don't think I think they haven't done a
one year yet because no one really died
until now M I think yesterday they did
one for Rica though oh
Kyla
hello
[Music]
hello H we GRE the goddess of Minecraft
oh Kawa hi I Kawa I just joined today
and I was hoping you could maybe be so
sweet to maybe if you have one if you
can give me a bow and maybe some arrows
oh um wait um any it doesn't have to be
enchanted yeah I think we can craft it
like let's go at my okay I'll follow you
probably okay and Ena needs a string I
think just a string yeah not just I just
need to make some bows yeah string bow
is wait um feather yeah um I should have
I just need the string cuz I don't want
to farm the
spiders how long have you been
streaming I'm not streaming right now
oh yeah I'm not streaming how long have
you been
awake
I yeah that's not a question you ask the
cont of Minecraft I mean I I mean I
slept a lot in Minecraft though yeah wow
because I dinner last night I saw you
you you were streaming already for like
7 hours and now I see you when I wake up
and I'm like confused oh yeah i' I've
been doing um 12 hours back to back oh
my God but yeah I'm I mean I'm still
playing even though I'm not streaming so
oh yeah
she she this is her life she takes it
very seriously the no log out rule she
takes it very seriously
only sleep in
Minecraft in a bed don't log
out
Kyla you're so fast oh I guess I got to
jump yeah you got to jump is that is
that your house no that's the village my
house is just no my my house is just
dirt house oh oh okay oh we got to be
efficient oh well Ena said she would
swim it's okay uh you no it's okay swi I
I can't there's two oh let's go wait oh
okay
okay let's go why did this
happen
oh
shotgun what you trying to do right now
in a pie what are you trying to do right
now oh I'm trying to fix some bows that
I fished up they're pretty good bows ah
and
then see I hear Kyla
normally ah I have my own trading Hall
just in case if you need like um yeah I
heard you had like Unbreaking three and
oh yeah so if you need like books
maybe Kyla's so calm
oh does KY here that's a good question
it's on ena's end okay okay we need to
walk a
bit Kyla do you hear Ena like completely
normally or is she a little bit robotic
to you oh completely normal though oh
okay youa say something
again hello hello okay you're still
robotic to me but KY is normal to me
weird maybe it's like the location
would you like me to now you it on
purpose this you see that one you see
that one the the dirt oh with the tree
on top square dirt with a tree yeah
that's my house
ah oh don't ask me if I live like that
yes I live like that
[Music]
this is fine this is
fine oh is that pumpkins let's
go I have pumpkin but ah pumpkin as a
food item is like annoying cuz it needs
to be pumpkin soup in a bowl right no
yeah cats objective Alpha
[Music]
for Fortune mending Ming let's go
looting Unbreaking fed falling sharpness
flame silk touch you have silk touch
let's
go oh my God I think I P needs I don't
know if she got it already but like she
was saying she needs silk touch a while
ago
wow
Shar
she mending let's go
but that's for the for the for the wings
eventually nice Kyla nice freaking
nice think for your bow is infinity is
better oh for for fighting the Ender
Dragon later on yeah
POS get some oh actually yeah Infinity
would be amazing I I would love some
Infinity
do do you have um Iron Ingot with you
right now I have
uh I got 44
iron all of this guys is for um
emeralds eaing oh I guess we need to
sleep wait I'm so scared wait I'm so
scared I don't want to like be killed by
an iron golem we can sleep here or if
you have another bed maybe okay yeah I'm
so scared sleep I can't sleep next to
the Iron Golems scare me please hold my
hand it's
okay they want to kill me don't hit the
Golem don't hit the
Golem don't hit the Golem don't touch
the
Golem too many traumatic
experiences don't hit anything
yeah good
morning
okay okay uh wait so are they going to
come up the do do you trade from here
tra yeah trade from up here okay he I'm
so scared okay sorry sorry sorry
sorry what
a our 11 emeralds enough to buy the you
want to buy what what Infinity what's oh
Infinity is I need a book too right the
book is free here you can here n nice
you are
God nah
Infinity 18 I need a few more I don't
have any more iron with me I have 11 uh
how many oh seven emeralds I need
[Music]
seven thank
you remember where her house fin yeah
remember where her house is
okay okay okay no just just to come back
to get get all the stuff I just need to
get my Emerald I mean okay since since
you have uh since you have a lava farm
right maybe if you pass by here or I I
need the lava bucket for my friend here
okay maybe you can you you can drop you
can just drop it in this one or this one
or you can just put I I'll bring some
over yeah thank you
okay I'll be
back see um do you
want I I could use a I could use a boat
where'd he go where'd he go wasn't there
a villager in here I I I just killed it
when you called me what by accident but
but no evidence no evidence it's okay
what villager the POR villager because
because I found the cheaper one oh wow
okay what vill Kiara I don't see any
[Music]
V okay can we make nothing nothing
happened and one Arrow okay okay uh so
bow right uh come here come here and
then I I need to enchant it I forgot how
to enchant things
uh
en en I I think she went to get the
emeralds and the bucket oh okay we can
just take it for her I guess
L I don't know okay let's just go okay
what are all these
messages by the way do you want to do
the
skeleton wait skeleton no I don't oh
yeah I might need a higher level to
enchant maybe you can enchant it for me
I gave you the book oh I I used up all
of my exp too but I
think uh what's the level I
want I think I
can um cuz I'm level five now can oh I
don't think you need that much though oh
oh in 6 minutes the trial is
starting trials yeah the trial for like
Revival Reviving um ah okay some members
[Music]
some people
died yeah make sure you don't
die make sure you stay alive well I I'll
try or I'll be sad you'll be sad really
wait this is I have I I going to finish
this zombie exp Farm today o but it's
actually here
oh
mhm
nice I'll remember that
yeah but this one is not finished yet
I'll open
um proper entrance later on after I
finish because I need to go to the
nether to get the Soul Sand oh okay yeah
uh wait this don't get lost KY n we go
negative X okay this way there's already
a monster tower for exp and items oh
made by who I'm sure Kyla still likes to
make her own things she also made her
own like a villager farm even though
there's already also a different one
yeah jumping make you faster oh yeah so
sorry sorry yeah it's okay it's
okay n now you're really fast W what the
sheh it's okay ignore that it's
fine it's so
pretty a bunny pickle pickle pickle
pickle pickle pickle pickle pickle
pickle
Pi spider farm okay but it's not
finished too because I need the
soul Pi Pi Pi
Pi Pi Pi pickle pickle pickle hold on
hold on kill it kill it kill it with
fire you don't want to kill it oh oh is
it the farm oh okay
yeah but just be careful oh my God it's
so scary I'm so SC I mean you have
diamond armor it's okay but it's not
safe where are they even I don't see
they're like up there I
just
wait because sorry because the farm is
not finished yet oh string
ah I can't get the one that's up there
yeah I think I need to remove that dirt
first
oh
wait they're all they're they're up
there they're friendly it's okay oh just
like spiders I didn't know Minecraft
spiders could be on the
ceiling yeah they're going to stuck in
in the sail
[Music]
so
no torch Toco I think it's supposed to
be dark
yeah it's supposed to be dark or else
it's not going to spawn
right why are they on the
ceiling yall are they bugging there
because they're not coming down
either I think it's because it's not
nighttime oh so they're not like being a
grassing oh really so I'm being cruel
right
now is there baby spy
okay is that what you
need yeah I guess so I I guess I guess
so I don't know I guess I need uh yeah
the string and but I'll I'll kill it
I'll take it for
you get thank you I'm level
six okay I'll I'll uh should we I I will
I think I'll go to the
trial oh okay okay we need to go back
yeah please lead me otherwise I'll
probably get
lost yeah we don't have to go to the
trial uh P said but if you want to go we
can go I'll
go let's go Kyla probably busy doing
stuff yeah I still need to continue
working on
stuff they haven't announced the nether
portal yet right uh I think they said
they want to build it after the uh trial
oh okay
so very soon I need to get the Soul Sand
yay why do you why do you need
it she she can't hear me I'm too far
this is already too
far up
oh
okay oh maybe e is back
now oh she must be like where where did
they go
where did I
go a for water elevators ah makes
sense Ena is she here oh no Ena water
did she go straight to the trial maybe
all right I'm going to go to the trial I
can bring you back yes please
let's let's go I think I have enough
string for Ena
to if she needs it from me uh you don't
want to just make the bow right now it's
okay I'll make it after the trial I'll
try
why get the cords oh
uh okay guys remember the cords
[Music]
should okay
okay Jo the
[Music]
game where am I Asia Anda
Bros in the chat what's up
[Music]
here here whoa s EA e s EA let's go
what's
up nice
see yum yum yum oh it's getting night
time oh
no it's okay
[Music]
this okay I think I want to go there I
know which house it is oh God oh God
it's so dark sleep sleep uh is there
beds
here you know where to go uh I think so
yeah I think I think somewhere here
is oh I think that
one here I can take it there
okay oh yeah I see it all right yep nice
are you going to
[Music]
go no I'll I'll go back to my place it's
okay come
byebye let's
see what's happening in here
[Music]
yeah hi a lawyer
[Laughter]
[Music]
hi
okay I'll try to
translate so there's two cases and
it'll probably be no problem to revive
her oh she she watched the video
[Music]
she's staying
the she's asking her to explain what
happened someone's
snacking they were going to
[Music]
they wanted to make an automatic
well she's yapping a lot
[Music]
okay yeah yeah she got caught in in the
fishing
machine she didn't know she didn't know
how to use it
[Music]
she asking if it's
an yeah she's saying that she was trying
to save her it was her fault
[Music]
she's saying what happened in the video
that was just laughing
[Music]
she's talking in lawyer Japanese
she's read going to read some evidence
[Music]
repeating what
happened they don't they don't hear me
right
now I'm mut
[Music]
oh she's she
wants questioning maybe she wasn't
trying to save her but leave her
behind want to check just to make
sure the is
[Music]
but the no is supposed to
be to turn on my Japanese
[Music]
[Laughter]
man she already died twice
[Music]
ni she
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
second case is
aqua she's looking for a lawyer
[Music]
oh there she's asking if anybody has
been uh troubled by by
[Music]
oh as she fell from the TT Tower
that's
[Music]
it she s
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh they were working together on it but
I didn't see
it and then just suddenly noticed that
she was dead
[Music]
is like roasting her all you have to do
is bread chip to not fall down
[Music]
oh she's asking if anybody was treated
badly by her because P also said like
some
some crime or was put onto her by
aqu but okay these people have been
harmed by
[Music]
over yeah I guess I burned you sorry
was pushed into a
[Music]
[Laughter]
whole cour
[Music]
she's like you've harmed many people
so oh she's defending her saying the ti
Tower could have been could not have
been made without AKA
so please consider
[Music]
that hold up no no no never mind
burnt because of that without thinking
twice which is I think supposed to be
defending her I think
[Music]
I mean they can't say no right I don't
think they'll ever say no
[Music]
I I when I just came I didn't make any
memories of her I'd like to make some
[Music]
oh B says we have Red Bull connection so
yes she's getting she's getting revived
but she's
[Music]
um well you know punishment
yeah she has to help P Senai with
whatever she asks for
[Music]
and must daily help others repay their
[Applause]
[Music]
kindness community service
okay they're going to make the gate now
for the never but I got to make my boat
so I'll make that
first that was
[Music]
funny okay I'm going to make my bow I'll
be back uh where's oh
yeah are you're welcome
whispering to her viewers wait where is
uh where is the path over there
okay that was that was interesting I
hope that will never happen to me but
surely everybody will be kind enough to
revive me I just got to not die that's
all I got to
do I think by the way
um like I just have to write it in my
diary what I did and then I'll be
rewarded like if I say I I killed a gas
I think I could just write it in my
diary and uh it will count they'll just
believe me I
think but then generally even if we go
to the ne besides like just fulfilling
the missions is there anything I really
want to get from the never in order to
in order
to like do good in
the in
the uh uh and end fight
blaze
[Music]
rods blaze rods what do I need blaze
rods
for I just want to participate by like
shooting the
dragon but okay I'll just try to do the
mission so like just just to like you
know uh okay
bow I need ah okay sticks I have some
sticks from the
trees B and then let me go to Poco Farm
to get the feathers so I can make one
single Arrow hopefully we we'll be able
to put Infinity on
it and I uh I don't know I hope Ena
doesn't I hope they don't all just like
cuz they're going to build the portal
right but I think they want to not just
build the portal but make it look a
little bit nice I think that's the
intention but I I want to know before
they all go can you guys like if
anybody's like having two windows open
uh can you tell me when they're going
in if anybody has an eye on that let me
know I don't I don't want to like end up
lagging behind and being all alone on
that I want to attach myself to somebody
oh I probably Kyla will go I'll just go
with
Kyla uh do I need torches maybe I'll
need torches just generally also for the
uh
never uh okay I saw feathers
somewhere wait weren't there feathers
somewhere pretty sure it's saw feathers
maybe somebody took them I just need one
I think for an
arrow I can like kill these I think like
one
I CH I check oh Ena Hi H do you need the
string I have a string for you I think
oh where did it go oh really oh never
mind it actually took three strings to
make one bowl oh yeah oh but then yeah
just go back to Kyla place and she will
go back anyways cuz of uh yeah okay I
need to get one
feather I'll
just no not the SP oh okay I got the
feather one feather is enough right
probably wait Ena wait wait
Ena
wait the young
LS oh
f p is writing like please pay up uh at
the chest for their revivals but like I
don't have a diamond like who's who who
has to pay who um responsibility is that
yeah they volunteers okay tax the rich
exactly tax the
rich I don't have
nothing
Arrow oh
Flint where the do I get flint
again I I'm just going to go back to
Kyla she probably has flint and then
I'll enchant does she have an enchanting
table she probably does right oh wait do
you even need an
enchant huh I don't remember how it
works if you already have the book do
you need the enchanting
table cuz the enchanting table you can
use without a book right and just get
something random too Anvil ah Anvil okay
so I think uh she was somewhere over
there
right M this
Direction Just Anvil okay
[Music]
okay thank
you I just told her her new outfit looks
really cool where am I going
it ah
okay yeah I saw her Play Bunny Garden
yesterday with that new outfit I think
she was maybe waiting to play bunny
Garden until she has an outfit so that
she looks like
cool cuz now it's really
fitting yeah and did you guys see SAA
sire's new frie outfit like I mean she's
always frie but you know she had a 3D
stream of it and oh my
God she looks so pretty she's got like
another like idolish outfit looks so
nice she's like pass to this right who's
living here cuz this doesn't look like
how efficient these villagers would
normally
work
what is this
natural okay L's diamonds have
[Music]
been uh acknowledged
this is
normal sheesh okay where the hi
dude can you lead Point me the way dude
to Kaa yeah I'm
lost ah I don't see the
place I know we passed here kind of but
not really I think we swam
by oh damn it KLA
I am lost when I tried to get to you I
got lost but
whatever H is this the wrong vill you
have a quartz yeah but I got to open up
the should I give her my co quarts
oopsie
uh where am I where are my cords H minus
191 minus
191 uh something what was the second one
I can't see and
then - 217 what's the second one let
just
okay
ah V villager place
already they already turned on the never
portal
[Music]
what okay I'll tell Kyla cuz she
probably doesn't know that they just did
that too I'll tell her and then we can
go ah
ky
[Music]
ky hello I I I made a bow um and I have
a feather and I I have a stick I think
but I need do you have Flint I needed to
make one arrow and then I was going to
level up to make the infinity at your
place and and then if you want we can go
to the nether cuz they're just going to
the nether
now oh um but you don't want to
go this is my dinner time I need to go
oh okay dinner Oh I thought you would
like rush to be the first one in than
never I thought you really wanted to go
dinner is like my top priority a that's
nice that's sweet like you game all day
all night but the one thing you will not
like Let Go is the family dinner that's
that's what Papa I always say that
that's important that's sweet I like
that good mentality
mhm Papa my dad always ask us like the
family together for like 2 hours every
single day oh wow yeah we we we going to
talk about like the whole day thing so
when is that starting do you still have
a little little bit of time like 5
minutes yeah yeah yeah it's fine it's
fine okay so uh do you have
Flint yeah uh let's see that is really
sweet
damn how many do you need again I think
just one because I'll have Infinity so
I'll just need one Arrow
anyway here ah oh oh thank you
nice and then the crafting table is here
uh uh Arrow okay I made oh four arrows
okay and okay uh there's an anvil down
here right Anvil Anvil is here just
right beside oh my God I'm
blind it's okay I'm blind too let's see
what I need Infinity uh oh I can do
it cost cost all only
four nice H should I put anything else
on my bow maybe Flame or so yeah you
have uh Power five maybe power five
power five oh the best one is actually
Infinity Unbreaking at least the
Unbreaking you need the Unbreaking
because you can men it right oh yeah oh
yeah Unbreaking the Unbreaking is here
here this one oh wait I have the free
Unbreaking
here cuz I'm out of emeralds here ooh oh
number level
three yeah okay I probably need more
levels yeah let's see
Bowl Unbreaking okay I need two more
levels should be
easy uh and
then I think you can just level up but
hold on
I think I
can enchant it for you oh really okay uh
there and
there oh okay okay do I have an extra
bed we need to sleep it's yeah it's okay
you can just use that one
[Music]
okay P says Aqua there's currently
nothing you have to help me with so you
can live freely I will call you if I
need you oh oh yeah so I I'll tell you
what happened in court uh Rika was like
revived with no problem pretty much but
then akan they were like bringing up all
the crimes she has done to others how
she burned others with lava magma and
like yeah done some bad things so she
was revived but only under the condition
that she's going to be serving the
community AKA Us by helping everybody
and especially P Senai so she's like
yeah doing community service she's safe
right she's safe yeah she was revived
but she's she's basically P's slave now
oh no oh no yeah thank you so much for
helping
me wait you don't want to get the
P oh can I put a third one on it the
power oh yeah for
sure wait I thought this was Max maimum
power power where's the
power finally actual made oh yeah did I
really lost the power no wait wait wait
wait maybe it's in one of the free books
the the free one in the other
chest where was that
chest here
[Music]
power oh there's looting and Power in
here H
may I would be fine with like fire or so
too are you are you going to do like
mining uh yeah probably eventually but I
only have this iron pickaxe so I don't
think I would enchant the iron
pickaxe I'll just get like diamonds
first actually uh if you go to the
trading Hall the AOH house one they
actually have the the the what's that uh
not the tool Smith I think they have
like the blacksmith one so that you can
just oh I'll check it out and then buy
yeah and then you can have this Fortune
maybe you just take like wait I going to
buy it for
you K
[Music]
[Laughter]
mommy no Mommy here this one oh thank
you yeah and then enchant it later
on the bow you mean uh on the no on the
P whenever you want to go my name okay
all right thank you I'll go do my own
thing now have fun with the dinner are
you coming back to Minecraft after
dinner yeah after dinner I'll start the
stream after dinner oh okay have a good
dinner bye-bye thank you byebye if you
if you come back after dinner and you
start your stream are you then going to
the
nether I think so I think so yeah can
can I go with you yeah of
course then hit me up you to stream that
long tonight today uh I mean
possibly okay okay I'll see you around
bye-bye yay byebye thank
you yeah I mean if she's going to dinner
like very soon and that takes 2 hours
and then she's coming back does she have
her stream reservation
up it's not that long if it's like about
2 hours or 3 hours from now I'm still
here where am
iuck it's this
way yeah she's probably doing another 12
hours stream oh my god when is she
sleeping uh I want to stream relatively
long too but I have one concern that I
might get really hungry after 2 hours or
so cuz I woke up and I had had uh
basically one banana and I will admit I
I was going to kind of cheat for my
breakfast because I would I wanted to
there's like some leftover uh like
chocolate e
cereal and I tried it but it was
actually disgusting so I only had like
five bites or so of the chocolate cereal
and one banana
so
yeah I think it's this way
maybe so I'm probably going to get
hungry don't worry it doesn't count as a
cheat because I didn't really eat much
of
it is it this way guess I could try to
go towards
zero this way then I think it's going
towards zero
it's the intention no I just wanted to
eat leftovers and I I also genuinely I
thought it would be a faster breakfast
because okay I got up at like
10:30 and I was like cooking the egg
will take a
while like not long but it it's faster
to make the cereal but then then I
realized oh the milk that I have smells
kind of weird but I always think that
it's probably never not edible but I
always do you guys have that too like
you open a new milk and then it's fine
right you use it for like two or 3 days
and then on the four fifth day or so you
smell it it's like not much left in
there but you smell it and you're like M
that smells weird but like it always
smells weird but at this point I'm
getting like really sussy about it like
does it really should it smell like
this I always doubt
it wait I need to get iron did they have
here is
this uh iron was at paa's place
right seems like not everybody is going
straight into The Nether oh s but she's
one of the ones who are going to be
sacrificing
themselves I don't know I want to I want
to do the
thing you know like going but but frogs
eggs
is I want to do
that for
[Music]
ah
okay yes yes
yes Japanese G oh
no gamble oh no Japanese G
okay okay okay yeah she started talking
to me saying oh K you need anything I'll
do anything for you I'm like I thought
she was like she really she meant it is
she talking to oh no
yeah she's like oh do you want me to do
something for you but I thought she
meant like for real but no oh she wants
diamonds in exchange so when I asked for
like diamond pickaxe uh she was like oh
well I do need diamonds so that's not
going to
work not a hold uh what did I come here
for ah
iron yeah yeah
yeah I'll have to go into the M me yeah
I might go mining maybe it's kind of
boring but oh maybe although I was
thinking get the iron get some emeralds
with the uh with the iron and then get
some diamonds with the
emeralds I don't think I ever talked
with like not properly right with
our son
wait where's the iron ah did I get it
wrong where did I get iron before was it
not
here yeah in the hard Challenger stream
yeah but that was just a little bit I
wonder what the like how serious it is
meant to like do something with someone
you haven't done anything before if it
just means like within Minecraft or like
in the recently or never
ever there's a farm somewhere
[Music]
under
for okay
[Music]
I can't hear hi hi
hi okay
[Music]
I I asked her if just for showing me
this if I have to give her a diamond
she's like
w well it would be nice if you would
maybe you know
[Music]
wowe
for
for so so so soe
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay okay okay
that was funny she was going to give it
to me like she gave it to me like
immediately but turns out she did need
it herself um so I gave it back but she
was so surprised that I had like a bow
and diamond stuff and I was like why do
you have all this even though you
started today and I'm like well I am a
senpai of many people and they're just
being you know nice to me helping me out
you know yeah uh
but well then she was like she took it
wrong I I didn't mean it like I'm a
Senai therefore I help no no I meant I'm
a Senai therefore kis helped me but she
misunderstood and thought I would help
her but no no no no that was not what I
meant but
she I felt sorry for her cuz she wanted
to her goal for today was like getting
diamond armor I guess strong armor and
she need she wanted to do the same thing
as me like get the uh get the iron then
get the emeralds then get the diamonds
yeah so I gave her back the the iron uh
and said I'll just I I'll have to do
some things myself I'll just go digging
is what I said but I realized um
I might have needed like maybe two irons
at least because what if this one breaks
soon but it's okay I'm going to put this
away um going to fill this with water
I'm going to put this away this away
this away this away this away ah I need
more food though that's one thing I
should get if I'm going to go down
yeah Stone Pi pickaxes are fine too I
guess we'll just start a little bit and
then we might already also get some iron
early
on um let's say okay we can dig for like
2 hours until uh Kyla comes
back and then we go to the
nether at to Tom I'm just going to PCO
for
food oh God there's so now now I'm like
realizing there's a lot to do p
okay
[Laughter]
so noisy here hey yo what's this
eggs okay food let's take a potatoes
potato potato
potato told her it's so freaking noisy
here what's Ena doing guys do you
know also where should I dig should I
continue digging from one of the holes
or just make a completely new one
get extra bed too oh should I uh to
sleep when the others are
sleeping you mean
underground she was killing spiders
using spider F oh KY spider
farm
oh oh just dig straight down no I'm not
going to dig straight
down I know that's a no no thing
we're doing well oh the never is right
at the cour
house
Oh I thought they were going to make
something like really special I feel
like they said something like that in
the Discord but it's just a normal
portal
now oh okay um what was I what was I
doing
[Music]
uh PE Nora wants to do the same just
dig okay I'm I have
water water is good water is good
especially also if we find lava then we
can get rid of it like
that torch okay you think I need even
more torches
but I don't know I think this is enough
cuz I can always
leave uh I'll need that for
shooting uh yeah the only thing I don't
really need is the
axe but I can still bring it I guess in
case my sword breaks or
so the feathers actually don't really
need because my bow has
Infinity yeah
okay I'm scared what if I
die well my argument will be it's it was
my first day please revive me okay
I'll just I'll just uh dig somewhere but
ow I want to go a little bit away so
that I don't like bump into other
uh uh uh underground
spaces bring wood why
why why would I need
wood just for crafting something in just
in case
[Music]
or I have torches I have plenty of
torches craft ah a for pickaxes yeah
[Music]
okay right these trees seem
natural dig under your house
I don't know about
that
okay spare pick
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
okay ni
ni nice sometime during the day I think
I might have to go to the door to
receive my
hello order
I think it's coming
today which is perfect because just
yesterday I ate the last of my
meals
yeah I ate the pizza the peepy pizza
this time with the salad the peep
Pizza what a
deal okay it's getting late
I'm I'm scared but it's going to be fine
I just got to be
careful but digging is always kind of
scary
man
digging like I can just suddenly be met
with just random
lava
right okay should we just start here
where am I let start
here actually this place looks
interesting wonder if somebody went
there
before okay here we
go this is how it works right
uh here we go we're digging let's
go let's try to be efficient
I'll I'll figure it out how to be
efficient if you're in danger just
disconnect yeah I I I tend to do that
when I panic
anyway
uh by the way I think that was the first
time I I really talked
toim uh okay
maybe we talked like one word or so
exchanged the word in the sports
event but I don't know it's been too
long and now wouldn't really have been
significant okay am I doing this
right she likes my music oh no there's
water Ah that's not really
good uh maybe I shouldn't have
right next to water should I go this
way who doesn't like my music huh I
think my music is generally like
something that is popular with these
kind of
girls this is It's mainstream friendly
and uh like I think Japanese girls they
like kind of they they they don't really
make this kind of music on their own but
they look up to it I think you know
western music
K-pop a yeah likes to dance yeah I heard
that
too why is this why does this look so
funny never mind doesn't look funny it
was the
darkness
yeah I'm looking forward when she
becomes 3D to see her
[Music]
dance I hear water I think or did I hear
something
else oh that's a skeleton I think I
heard a
skeleton oh oh I definitely hear
skeleton oh maybe I can kill free
skeletons get those
diamonds there must be like a cave
system here oh I hear them I hear them
SK I am not
scared of
skeletons what's the current level for
finding
diamonds the uh how low do I have to get
where are we
now
33 is that the
depth minus 50 4
53 I have a shield but I have to carry
the
Torches I don't I don't hear the
skeletons
anymore too
bad go under 50 but it's why right
yeah
I
uh ief
preer not to go
[Music]
there why not
because I I just kind of want to safely
mine for
now let's try to distance ourselves from
that
going in the circle
oopsie okay that's that's at least on my
level but is it's lit
[Music]
up he can't go here
he's gone no he's going to jump
scare
me yada I'm wearing diamond armor yeah
but like if you get blown up by a
creeper it's just not
good it but it's lit
up someone's been here
right sorry
sorry sorry
[Music]
what do I
do I I think the creeper saw
me oh he saw
[Music]
me oh oh that broke
go no
[Music]
no oh thank God oh he's so good at
climbing stairs what the
okay
okay I could have closed it off or
something too but oh God my heart my
heart my
[Music]
heart oh
God okay we're
good I still hear
skeletons maybe that light is lava I
don't know or someone's been
here oh that place looks isn't that uh
iron or is that
copper
uh what's the
light is it what's this
light what's the
light Swit it up oh yeah
uh oh
[Music]
yeah
man iron right that's
iron is it
yeah and copper I don't know do I even
need copper or
something got to keep my eye out for
sudden creepers walking up to me for
real for real
there was
more
so nice
nice o my pickaxe almost like dead
already
[Music]
I heard
bones
okay no so
scared exophone
intensifies exophone suddenly turns into
battle
music B ble music with silophone I want
to hear
that it's a
skeleton it said free skeletons to get
some
Diamonds oh
oh
oh thank God I have an
Infinity oh
one one
skel nice nice nice nice nice no more
bone
noises it does like no damage oh yeah I
guess that's right but I'm scared you
know I got to be careful it's better to
be
careful uh exoy can I mine that coal do
you do you mind if I
M do do you
mind so so so so so so sorry
Tob your
PE so sorry sorry sorry sorry Sor
sorry don't don't hurt me it will be the
end of
me
please I'm friends not
full
okay the to the h
[Music]
w yay coal is also good to have not
really what I was looking for originally
but uh should be good oh
sleeping can I sleep
here
ah ah a monsters they call you a
monster Mr
Enderman can you believe
it you're just a nice guy I know
it I would not call you that put your
shield in a hot bar so you can use f to
Quick swap oh F to Quick
swap
Nar I didn't know
[Music]
that are you going to sleep are we going
to sleep
oh please quickly I don't want to die by
a
[Music]
creeper come on two space tunnels safe
from Andy oh yeah true but not safe from
creepers or anything else
really oh 9 out of 11 okay we should be
sleeping
now I heard
another uh scary
Noise Okay so you
said
this
perhaps here also um it's time soon for
another
pickaxe so let's make uh
[Music]
no a working table there you go crafting
table I'll will put
it like in
here safe
space my mouse is like doing weird
things doesn't
move and okay we have iron
now but uh in this form I can't use it
right I have to like burn
it into actual iron right doesn't work
like this oh man need a furnace for that
okay okay so for now we got to do stone
stuff uh Stone
uh
okay stone
pickaxe I
am a little bit on
edge did you hear the
[Laughter]
train uh
oh
man the mice or the bats or whatever
that is also freaks me
out I hear I hear
something did you invite a friend huh
don't don't get so close to
me
what
what okay uh wait
there's so much hair in my mouth not in
my mouth this time just in my
mouse what do I do should I continue
mining or explore this I think
I'll uh continue
mining okay like just like straight from
or down can we go down now I think cuz
there was water right so or no I was
getting away from a vein we can continue
here
maybe copper so what do I actually make
with
copper close off the cave you think I
should close it
off
H
okay okay so the creepers don't okay
surprise me
what the
oh there's another cave here
damn I want to mine
efficiently go away noises go away
[Music]
I lost my pickaxe there why
oh oh that's
[Laughter]
[Music]
me is that him no what am I seeing
where he go come
back okay
that's fine
then okay I'll
continue even though there's iron there
kind of want
it there's surely one there right no
okay okay
it y it it y it quick quick quick quick
get the iron get the iron get the
iron how much how much raw iron for one
iron is it just one iron one raw iron
for one
iron I don't wanted to
break one one oh okay nice
[Music]
nice this really was not a good place to
mine okay well this is lit up maybe it's
fine actually no no no it's not
[Music]
fine
sealed okay can I go down though you
have to explore caves to get any decent
number of ores well we still too high
though as well and no I don't need caves
I don't need
caves
ah there it goes my iron pickaxe
goodbye where are we
now 23 still way up too high what I'm
looking for is diamonds and iron
both is fine the iron I can also use to
get
emeralds so either way is fine feel like
I have tangents but just I'm just like
brain empty right now let me let me
check my my phone diamonds are deep
yeah but I'll get
them one way or another
uh I don't know my tangents currently
might not be so interesting but
uh
um man that's that's no that's so not
interesting wait
[Music]
a oh wait my phone's actually dying it's
on
5% uh can I get a cable really quick
without
dying okay okay don't die don't die
okay okay
okay don't want my phone to
die
okay yeah here we
go no already 4% no slow charging for
faster charging use a supported charger
wow that's all I got
really ask the trial to revive your
phone oh yeah what happens if my phone
dies do I need diamonds to revive it
too yeah okay I have just like small
smaller smaller baby tangents on my
phone did I tell you when I was in
Thailand I brought some
souvenirs and this time I
brought like I okay before um there's
several things that I might bring as a
souvenir um several times to like
members I brought them the sakur cakes
like I buy them in the dutyfree place
little small sakur cakes they're really
good um they're like in the small form
like a cube really good
stuff but those are a little bit
expensive especially if I need to give
it to a lot of
people and then uh another time I was
bringing Manor schnit this is also an
Austrian snack back which as a child I
didn't really like it much because it's
really just underwhelming it's not sweet
enough as a child the oh no got to
go straight a little bit it's not sweet
enough as a child in my opinion I think
many children don't really like it
much cuz it's just
boring oh there's so much iron there but
H um do you guys know
man I want to show you yeah those are
like the the waiver
cookies with like
hazelnut in between each like really
thin layers of hazelnut uh spread or
whatever cream really thin everything's
thin the waiver thin the hazelnuts thin
but the more older I get the more I
appreciate it at least like every once
in a while like if it's just offered to
me I like to eat
it and it's pretty cheap I think
compared to the sakur
cakes oh oh pora Senai wants to stay
awake next night
okay because she wants to kill
skeletons did I kill one or two by
now two all right I think I was was free
right
me oh my
God
sheesh uh yeah
[Music]
okay just let it
fall just going to
[Music]
continue
walking
uh okay Redstone I don't care about even
though it looks so
fancy
oh it takes a
while even if I find diamonds it's going
to take a while to mine them
huh oh wait I don't get
it is it because it's
Stone I don't even get
it
[Music]
je I feel like I'm not going to get much
out of this mining trip in 2 hours
because I'll have to go back and make my
iron into iron make new tools and then
probably there's not much left for
spending it for emeralds oh well
okay back to the uh omag souvenir
story eh okay so mannit is what I would
bring recently why not make a furnace I
guess I don't know I guess I could make
it
now my my crafting table is kind of far
now oh my bed I forgot the bed
too why don't make a smell the tear H
okay okay let me go back to to the
crafting table at
least and yeah man I was bringing man
and before that I would sometimes bring
uh Mozart
balls yeah but I'm personally not a fan
of mozard
balls there's um maip pan in there which
you may have heard about it but some
people never heard about it before I
find it really interesting it's like
more common in certain places very
common in
Austria and usually it's like marod and
dark chocolate dark chocolate also I'm
not really a big fan of you know so I
wouldn't want to give it
to uh people when I don't really like it
much
either right so considerate also cuz a
lot of people that like even a lot of
austrians don't like it it's not just me
moart balls they're just nah they're you
know moart balls so it's like a great
souvenir if you think about it they're
also like in a fancy package with
Mozart's face and
everything so you think that
that's you
know it looks like a nice souvenir but
then you bite into it and then you Pro
especially cuz like when I give it to
someone from a different continent their
chocolate tastes different on it like in
itself already so when I eat like
American or Japanese chocolate I don't
really like it and I imagine like that's
going to add to the already not so
tastiness of mad balls um just the fact
that our chocolate is different they
might not be used to it and then they
don't like it just because of the
chocolate
taste yeah but uh for Thailand I brought
some more mzad balls because I just
bought several you know you know they're
small I can buy big packages and give
them out uh Solo or just like smaller
smaller packages with free individual
moad balls or so and they look cute you
know why am I taking all this just leave
it oh can't leave it
anymore I'm a pickax
again uh maybe I should make a chest
over there
[Music]
though yeah and so I was giving it out
to people in in Thailand and I
was I was already feeling so insecure
about the chocolate that I was like
warning everybody I said I so this is
like the most popular souvenir chocolate
in Austria but just so you know it's not
really good so you
know I'm giving you the souvenir
but it's not good so don't get your
don't have high expectations and please
don't think that this is how all
chocolate in Austria is our chocolate is
actually better than this a lot better
but it is what it is you
know I was warning everybody yeah just
lowering their
expectations cuz I feel bad but at the
same time I thought it's just just it
looks cute you know and Mozart his name
is in there don't you want to eat
Mozart's balls who doesn't want to eat
Mozart's balls the
right so would you be happy if I
gave you moart balls but at the same
time warn you that they're not good
I mean maybe you like it some people
might like it I feel like uh cie I gave
her mot balls before I think and she
said she liked
it I don't know if she really meant it
though give them packs of RP minis M
that's good chocolate but it's like
that's German mad balls are Austrian
so giving German chocolate is not so
special I'm going straight right now
right because this is uh the dead end no
not the dead end but underneath is the
big uh vein
right I'm more of a Boven
person what that should just have better
balls oh come on his balls are fine
yeah but people were still happy about
receiving it although I should have
given it to them like earlier I gave it
to them like a few days in of us being
like uh around each other and then they
were kind of like melted but then I
waited for the them to be hard
again but when chocolate melts it like
affects the taste a little bit right so
that might have made it even worse I
don't know I didn't get their
reaction I didn't get their reaction I
hope it was
fine yeah Mozart's balls have gotten
soft Mo's balls are always soft
okay no they're supposed to be generally
MOA balls are generally
hard
okay you guys are making me think of
Fallout again
oh man I'm really enjoying the show I
don't know which episode I'm at like 6
or 7 or so maybe I hope there's still a
bunch
more I have to think of
[Music]
Maximus eight is the last no I'm close
to the finale no are they already
working on a new season please say yes
they are already confirmed but are they
okay confirmed that there will be a new
season but did they confirm that they're
working on
it already deep slate
I akis Senai also joined aisai is also
one of the ones who just here to help
for one
day a few days ago oh okay H they
haven't filmed it yet but Amazon has
ordered okay but some people are saying
they're already filming they better
be damn the more I watch the more I'm
like the Lucy or should I should I say
GL
gles Goosey gooes Goosey facial features
are so mesmerizing holy her
eyes are so big that I was really
thinking maybe did they like make her
eyes bigger in post it's crazy
where are we we're at
one her eyes just be like that yeah
crazy her eyes are so big they pop out
like but they're so pretty so
pretty is that
iron that's
iron like
Golem oh yeah uh there's also news about
some
new uh oh no not again the
new
uh uh yeah a Golem
movie first I make a Golem game and
absolutely fail at it surely the Golem
movie will be good right no my iron
I thought we're not
sleeping is this the night or did we
already get past the night of not
sleeping I I can't
tell I'm on the ground
people copy struck a 15-year-old fan
film on YouTube Just because it had the
same name what golum they're probably
just going to name it golum right
no oh is
back I'm not going to follow the trend
and press t
no this is not good guys
guys I'm not mining efficiently at least
I got iron
though that's good maybe if I get back
to the farm they already have produced
more
iron do it
no
no this summer is going to be so
exciting there's going to be a lot of
shows coming back
so excited to watch everything man cuz
I'm going to finish Fallout like this
week
probably and then what and then
what ah wait I still needed to watch
um I think there was this show on Disney
that you guys uh the the some uh Samurai
show or so that you guys recommended to
me
uh Shogun yeah okay I'll I have that to
watch it's it's uh in Japan right it
plays in Japan right it's about is it
about
Samurai there is a event starting at I
think half an
hour some kind of
uh probably some fighting event should
probably spawn
something she going to spawn
[Music]
something I don't know if I want to join
it maybe
not ah maybe I don't
know Shogun is excellent so wait does it
play it's a remake of a classical Series
in a novel technically not a samurai
show but golden has two shins and gy
members
what oh
you're talking about a never
show could go watch the event I kind of
do stuff though I I'm
uh depends if there's diamonds that to
be won by the
event H doesn't
mention doesn't mention if there's a
reward
maybe she's going to spawn
skeletons because of the
skeleton Mission the
oops oh my God it's going to break in a
moment ah don't break I will never give
up train passing
[Music]
through this tunnel is cursed this not
normal right I just shows a really bad
area it's probably because of the
mountain maybe I'm right under the
mountain right
now it's hard to get
through what's the point well today's my
first day I got to like you know no I
can't only be getting free stuff from
everybody I got to gather some of my own
stuff too I need iron and stuff but I'm
going to go into The
Nether with
everybody like Kyla and Ena probably I
don't know if Ena is Ena in the nether
right
now curious did she
go no okay what does she she doing
what's she up to yeah don't discourage
me from doing some of my own stuff ena's
just fishing she's cutting
grass fishing alone you should help help
with fishing how do I help with fishing
do I stand behind her and and hover my
arms over
her over her arms like a hug from behind
and then hold the rod together with her
act as a bait oh because I'm the
masturbator is that
why emotional
support oh okay apparently said we can
sleep now is it night oh it seems to
be
oh time to go back to get a new axe I
guess
maybe here
okay
[Music]
baiting take down G no I want to take
down I'm trying
to but I'm meaning this these dangerous
predicaments
yeah that was fast I guess in one night
she got all the skeletons she
needed damn I mean what I'm doing is
multitasking okay oh wait I wanted to go
back cuz I can get the skeletons here I
can get diamonds I can get
iron just general
materials I can get exp possibly maybe
not though not
really take down waterful just don't
drun I don't think I would drown but
first of all I don't know how to
efficiently put a water ball so that it
stays there I don't know and also I'm
just scared to like suddenly be in a big
space where enemies can get me from all
over but okay maybe I'll try if I find a
a
goodlooking
uh a
goodlooking situation
hey now I don't have to take Cobble
Slate from others cuz I have my own I
only got two more raw iron ah look at
this this is like barely
anything
man oh there's a few more here
[Music]
though pickaxe
iron uh oh it would be nice to get like
a few diamonds
just a
few just just a
few because I want to make myself
diamond tools at least a diamond pickaxe
would be nice
pen
[Music]
p no I'm not in the right depth yet
H wait we'll see I'll check what depth
I'm in make
more I guess I should be making
more just by
training you think you think this amount
of iron is enough minus it's okay it's
okay it's okay we'll we'll think a
little bit
more it's okay it's okay it's
okay let's see we are at - 11 okay I I
think I was uh trying to get past
something but are we past it
yet I wi
[Music]
iron is
good is there only one iron farm there
should be a second one would be would be
actually amazing to have a second one if
I knew how to build one I would do
it but that would actually help seems
like I'm not the only one who wants iron
[Music]
who built the one that's there uh uh she
said they like okay you know how kind of
but they built it together with v and
others
oh okay so maybe I'll go down there but
I don't know how to go down I
can't yay Studio Rob thank
[Music]
you okay first of
all let's get a bigger view of what's
down there
gold I have struck gold
okay give me give
me it almost feels better than
diamonds okay it's probably going to go
down here oh not
yet oh oh oh
oh okay now I don't see or hear any
enemies that's good they want to sleep
chut them up
there Kon that I'm going to make a I
think I can make some stairs
[Music]
maybe can't build
underneath what's search protector
achievement huh something in the nether
lightning rods oh wow they're already
getting lightning rods
[Music]
okay out of
copper you can make him out of
copper
oh seems like they
need like
like 80% of people to sleep something
like
that
uh pong thank you oh you had dinner with
fell CP what in
Korea come Sita for the
[Music]
pinky how to I can't
reach I see I see
nothing oh he's in
Japan so cautious of course I am
cautious I don't really know how to do
the W water bucket thing I'm not good
with water buckets
[Music]
man how do I place it on this block
just pass mine pass it no it's okay I'm
going to go
down on the side on this this side
here I'm
scared don't look with
it that
works lower
[Music]
y y y
y okay nothing
nothing don't go away ah the water's the
water is protecting me
this area is generally just cursed oh
God can he come up
no like everything about my mining uh My
Chosen mining area is
cursed no no no I don't want to I don't
want to I don't want to go down I don't
want to go I don't want to go I don't
want to
gold where am
I minus 30 we're pretty
close should I try to go down
here well the water shows me the path to
go back so the water and the light can I
take like water back oopsie ah uh
no okay okay have have this
ready wait wait
wait stop pushing
me ah oh
ah yay
that's that's a pretty good spot to go
digging I want to I want to close some
things
off okay I'm going to
close this area off I think oh God
faster
faster is that a good
idea kind
of what's wrong with
it kind oh they're going for the
frogs are they going for the frogs I I I
want to do that mission too
but I don't know who to ask to go with
me okay I think uh close it off quite
well
frogs people don't realize what kind of
danger they're getting them into by
going after
frogs I know I know how dangerous it is
oops
see okay
beautiful beautiful I feel so
safe uh wait how do I
place there we go
[Music]
Ana an's not here right now oh she is he
did she just log in oh she did
[Music]
Ana well Ana would not be a candidate
for frogging because um it's got to be
someone that I don't really have a
connection well I've never collabed
one-onone with Anya maybe it
counts I would have to kind of ask like
P Senai do they mean never ever having
talked with one another or just like not
much of a
[Music]
connection is I see diamonds
okay I'll try to
ask oh let me ask
in no I can't
[Music]
type you
probably probably well I don't know I I
I I feel like I just answer my own
question I feel like I feel like like
everybody would have uh talked to
everybody at least a little a little bit
but just someone you don't really have a
connection with
[Laughter]
relatable if prise we don't even have to
do it there's so many missions I can't
do all the missions probably I just just
do some
Mission wouldn't alome be perfect I feel
like Al probably already going maybe you
know what later a little bit later I'll
I'll just ask in chat hey is anybody
here who didn't go for the frogs yet who
wants to do it with
[Music]
me
bat Get
Wrecked
oopsie how do you stop aiming without
throwing the
[Music]
bow makes sense right yeah we'll just
wait a little bit cuz now I'm busy
am I busy or am I just trying to avoid
interactions
well what the is
that what the was that oh what oh
it's a bat oh looked weird to me
okay that should be uh okay that should
be
good where are we at Min is
50 yeah that's why diamonds are here
nice I hear
lava I think yeah yeah I hear it I hear
it
okay got some gold let's get the
diamonds
safely oh it's like a circle
here
oh oh oh
oh the thing at uh 900 p.m. with the
like event is happening right
now and and uh they're asking for
help you little
die and the dragon
practice no they're already going to
help
uh there's so many of
them go
away okay
okay okay okay my first
[Music]
diamond
what uh what
what diamonds only
one Pillager is a Pillager
radiant something about seven waves
hardcore
dig around it was not connected to
anything but I'll
try oh they say it's really
y really
son shop will be destroyed
from okay uh if I okay I guess
all
right it might take a while until I'm
back up there do something here yes it's
okay the hero the hero is coming I'm on
my
way okay they're
sleeping right now okay okay okay
I'm
running can we even
sleep they're passing for the night
right okay okay oh what did I need
all people
now do I get a reward for
saving
Humanity come on come
on I do have a cool bull I think I have
strong bll I don't know how much other
people Enchanted their things yet but
Infinity is kind of freaking
broken Ena is AFK
what oh that's why she's not seeing the
messages but she's still streaming right
did she just get a snack or
something I've never tried like to
protect people from a villager raid
before Oh God let me put the diamond
away
though
okay okay here we
Go's vill
save I have no idea what's going on I
don't know if it's even pillagers
equ
Shield
do uh where
do is it the
where where
though
oh now I know I know where it is it's
close to the you know the courthouse is
close to my digging place but wherever
Villages are take cours it's okay
[Music]
uh - 94 62 -
12us minus 94 minus 94 maybe she's going
that way is that question by going that
way
this
way-- 94 minus something else I think
this is the right
[Music]
way are they not going are they not
going is it over
[Music]
what in three minutes oh okay okay I'm
not
late yeah you're not late thank you very
much for coming it should be very very
dangerous and is it going to
[Music]
be enemy it's okay it's okay we'll
protect each other
please do not die uh okay same to you I
don't know if they will grant you a
second Revival if you die
again no actually says no more oh only
once
[Music]
okay oh we can kill him with the
lava is she like
is Pai like activating that on her own
cuz if she knows it's coming she's
probably activating it herself
right build
archers smart as I only have eight
blocks though oh ah oopsie
oh
[Music]
sorry oh why is that so smart fill the
water bucket yeah to get
[Music]
down all right all right e
IDE but I could also just get up here
right I don't know if they're going to
be up here
too but what I'm scared what if somebody
shoots me down oh they're also trying to
snipe from
there
[Music]
oh yeah I was thinking just around here
I don't have much time though oh okay
this should be
good I hope I'm not too far from
everything make it
bigger P just can shoot
too started going to get sniped off for
real make a platform a yeah okay so it's
not just one block
okay let's
[Music]
just
okay is this too high I
wonder I can't hear the other people
talking
is this is this
good two killer
Ki and
Senai yeah the killers of all killers
[Music]
do you
know know t t
yes
yes make
walls we don't need
walls Ena also built
[Music]
[Laughter]
something oh no
come over
here they're probably coming from other
I
see okay okay okay
hey I want that gold too I want to be
hired help
[Music]
come
on come
on oh they're planting flowers a n
planting
flowers
oyy not much of a raid they kind of
exaggerated how bad it would be oh she
went
down well I got to I got to get that
achievement
though come
on ra
Doo I'm abandoning my
tower seems like it's pretty safe
there's so many people shooting but they
might shoot me by accident
H what about being up here good
view they came from here
right but soon it's night so there will
be other enemies perhaps
[Applause]
is it over antil climatic for
real
oh what does the bar mean when it's
going up like that oh there's more
people coming
[Music]
okay what the
did I did I drop
something do you have a flame up
there oh
[Music]
y I helped I
helped oh oh let's
go
a now we're
[Music]
[Laughter]
I barely
hit so good I
love I love doing nothing Your Existence
is is enough you're like one of the
targets who could pull the aggro so it
would be nice if you pulled oh God be
careful though are you telling me that I
need to be baited yeah be bait be the
master
[Music]
bit yeah go get him go get
him don't
shoot get away from
En what what the
what the
what is that is that from them
us what the
well that felt kind of
uh is that someone's
stuffy can I get them
totem
[Music]
died but she died in a way like a hero
right
Ana dying on the battle field is the way
to go
down no okay is it over then I think
it's over can't he us yeah I think it's
over okay no I wanted to land hit
to I was I I I was useless but that's
fine did you not get the achievement on
no cuz I didn't land a hit at the boss
what does the buff
do yeah you can get stuff for cheaper at
the train let's
go kind of want to ah damn see now it
would be good if I had a lot of
iron oh they protected them like this
a h how long does the buff hold on
but yeah I'm false on you to explain
valala I feel like they might know
generally it's not just Valhalla it's
just a general medieval thing from
Kings you can check the duration in your
inventory oh
38 I I need iron and stuff to use the
buff
well where was the
where was the farm again I'm probably
not the only one thinking about
this um is this is this where it
was was it here was it somewhere
else to the left
it doesn't take if you're outside The
Village's radius oh for
real oh it's taking now
though they already made a they making a
gravestone is wait is this it
yes please please please please please
have some
stuff oh a little bit a little bit a
little
[Music]
bit
oopsie okay so with this and uh if I
finish
um my
other uh iron
melting then I could
go exchange a little bit even
[Music]
did KY have a villager that trades maybe
not I'll just go to that place again and
trade the iron for emeralds ASAP so that
I can wait maybe I'll need this this is
a good
find
oops I'm happy I could help happy I
wasn't late you guys made me think I was
late
this is good to give me that
[Music]
coal yeah was exciting too first I was
scared but like going down for me was
the right choice not super safe but
exciting more
[Music]
exciting
yeah oh they they took a photo right are
they done with it
well I'm probably not the only one who
ran away
right photoshoop me in there please and
hey I got to talk a little bit for I
tried to stay cool I think I managed to
stay
cool very cool
yeah we were just like discussing battle
strats nice
iron
okay saying oh since you guys had such
an easy time next time I will not like
announce that it's happening I'll just
spawn it
[Music]
randomly where is the question
mark hey yo
no don't
Co is like bringing up the fact that
somebody died so it's not really like
sure somebody died okay somebody died
and you want to make
it who needs to be in court actually
maybe not us maybe the
real person to go to court is you
yeah that's right Co she's like what do
you you're like treating her sacrifice
so oh I found it so
[Music]
lightly war criminal
yeah h
[Music]
H yeah P died so naturally I feel like
you know of course for the sake of you
know everybody being able to play
however much they want it's nice that
everybody seems to be able to revive at
least once but then again just for the
sake of like lore and and like building
a story line within this Hardcore
Minecraft I feel
like it it would also be like in in a
case like this where somebody doesn't
die by an accident but somebody dies in
a in an important challenge of like
protecting an important building and you
know a real war like having someone just
like stay dead there it would like add
to the seriousness and like the I don't
know how to say like it makes it more
dramatic
yeah but no
P if she wants to be revived she should
be
revived yeah she would be like she would
we should build a statue of her she
would go down in
[Music]
history but no um I'm sure she wants to
stay the Boromir of the story yeah it
would be
impactful but no no no no no we should
revive her anyway they built her a grave
yeah but she's going to want to come
back I
[Music]
think oh are they like actually
considering not having her come back to
life
Messi does she mean Messiah or what
[Music]
Mesi okay this is not that much Iron
Man kind of
sad 29 30 30 iron is all I got
how many emeralds do I
get I have to do the gold
[Music]
too or I should just take this with me I
don't know if I'm going to come back oh
well for now I'm leaving
it 20 iron in the chest it oh the I was
looking at the raw iron now there was
some more iron okay okay okay okay and
the diamond let's bring it
[Music]
home spectate as a ghost I honestly
don't know what happens when you die or
if you just get logged out or if you can
spectate I don't know is if Pai is
streaming you can probably see it on her
side I would assume that she's
[Music]
streaming oh audio
so she can type
also oh you do become a
[Music]
spectator you're going to spectator mod
no no no okay
okay that's good I I didn't know what
would
[Music]
happen kind of want to walk in and see
what what's there
just for a
moment no maybe not let's wait until
Kyla is there we'll go in
together honestly with Kaa I mean we had
that one time in Minecraft you know
where we did a lot of stuff together but
I I didn't do much with her until now
either oh this is so
[Music]
cute uh where am I I'm going home right
Kyla is coming she's not online now
right thank you very
for you welcome it was
fun
cute
cute in 12 minutes
oh oh oh wait I subconsciously went here
uh actually I was thinking I was going
home but that was the wrong bridge this
is perfect though um
for oh I'll take it what not
the
what
what did I do
that did more die did they all die
[Music]
I got the iron out of
it okay uh can I see it
sir free okay is this the only one free
iron for One ammo worldd oh wow let me
see three iron for one Emerald why
sleeping why are he
sleeping I guess that's probably the
cheapest oh wait I can ask him
to okay I got 18 ammo
walls is she going to do it
again like when she says she should do
it again without warning does she mean
like right away
maybe that's is
that I'm ready I'm
here in case it happens all
right
um do I want to buy tools with my
emeralds straight from them
should wait it's so expensive I can't
even afford this
one
man a this one I don't need
oh that one's pretty
good I'm missing one
ammo this I think I'll just get
diamonds and make my own
right is that best
hello
[Music]
hello I have one
Diamond one
diamond oh that's selling oh
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
for
spe
for okay let me try to lead her
uh was it which way which way was it
this way
[Laughter]
way yes yes yes yes yes
coordinator uh 140 420
really wrong way
one minus 140
[Music]
okay okay okay is it a
perent
for let's go
[Music]
[Laughter]
says she's going to lose her hip with
this
information uh it was somewhere behind
here
right okay
[Music]
just pass the village wait
but she's so excited about this nobody
really knows yet that K is giving so
much free stuff
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
spe
[Music]
oh Ena getting
naked oh she's
snacking she's still snacking oh
[Music]
oh
Al
a nice
no no no no noing
genius time to make profits yeah as long
as people don't
know what was I doing oh yeah I was
going
[Music]
to 20 more minutes
[Laughter]
she's so
excited it's like
unbelievable wait what do I do with my
emeralds
now what do I
do I guess I should just exchange it for
some pickaxe
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
now I'm following
her okay
he going in a
circle okay okay
what's return to
cender yeah yeah
yeah the
Torches gas
[Music]
fore oh nice
fore
fore oh coming
okay we got some more she said she got
it from TT anyway so she has a lot left
over
so I can exchange some
more but he's like
immediately out of emeralds
[Music]
man it
fore
fore fore
[Laughter]
okay for
[Music]
I even have
Infinity
sorry because Ollie loves me and gave me
a full uh diamond armor
I
see
[Music]
so for
bugging
[Music]
get this one
I still improve it
[Music]
right
nice this one looks really good too but
the axe is not so necessary oh hi Ana
you're still here behind me oh yeah um I
was adjusting your volume oh
Ana I need to get morning Jo because the
the yapping just now I was like what the
are they talking
about um it's like um they were
referring to uh to a Japanese meme damn
it's so over for me yeah
Dam
[Laughter]
we got left out um oh actually it's
okay because I I kind of promised Kyla
that I will go with her to the nether I
mean I'll just be oh you're not going
with us I mean I I I I I I I could but I
don't know I guess I don't understand
what everybody's saying in Japanese
so I mean it's okay I can always
translate for
you I wonder if it's okay for me to join
I guess I I that would be fun okay yeah
okay I'll join you guys I'm ready
whenever yeah okay are they coming back
here um yeah hold on what am I going to
do I a sword I want to a sword I need a
sword diamond sword do you have one a
good
one sharpness to sweeping Edge
too that's good sharpness Edge sweeping
sweeping Edge
too do you have a sword
no rip Kyla well she can like first of
all I'll probably just be like dragging
her down if I go with
her and uh I guess I'll
she can join our group I think this is
good can I get this get that sword
okay y diamond
sword y I have diamond sword and diamond
pickaxe nice enchant it let's go
Enchanted how do you enchant stals I'm
so I'm so blind about Minecraft you are
a Minecraft Noob sheesh I you either get
them already Enchanted or or you enchant
them yourself with like books and
stuff but I have no idea there's a meta
there's some good books and some good
enchantments so there's meta so you need
books yeah they also sell books over
here and there's some free books at
Kyla's place for specific
things but
oh
[Music]
oh okay let's go
I saw Ena over there I was I was about
to invite her but she's gone you know
normally I would probably stick to like
Kyla or in know but I think it's good
for myself because I've become so shy
that I should I should stick to people
like you guys that I don't do much with
right yeah
I'll be
back I'll put my things away I don't
know why she needs a
diamond I'm going to put my my things
away and then I'm ready to go don't
forget you go boots oh yeah I think
they're in my house too
I don't really ever do anything with so
I think even though it might be very
Japanese heavy I feel like in order to
you know make this whole uh Adventure
make some sense I should I feel like I
should go you know for for the sake of
bonding and interacting with some people
[Music]
right ominous Banner damn I got a
crossbow too
cool but I'm quite happy with what I got
damn I'm like damn everybody's like K
why do you have so much
stuff
well well well w w
connections was that
Ena okay
water bucket
[Music]
maybe
okay where's my food ah where's my food
oh it's in my right
hand okay
nice could you say I'm Decked
Out is that do you say that about
people bring
dirt I feel like we'll pick up enough
materials in the next but
okay yes okay I'm
out I only I feel like I only heard that
about cars or so I don't
know pretty stacked now yeah for real
thanks Big thanks to ollie for real for
real and Kyla of
course I Alon also in the group right
[Music]
I
invited oh okay
[Music]
can I put something in
here keeping
they put journals in
here she shaved her
head
[Music]
for
for how they find that
[Laughter]
[Music]
you have to take the hat off
too like your
helmet take off the
hat now you did it you did
it look so
[Laughter]
shaped her head out of Shame
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay
uh F4 F5 uh you change the angle with F5
and then you take a screenshot with F2
[Music]
y
go write this down
guys one guys
[Music]
yeah
transl she thinks if we all find the
Fortress together at the same time maybe
we'll all get it
[Music]
what is in Minecraft
lingo I I picked up someone
[Music]
did i k fre skeletons guys
I killed two damn I kill another one
eventually before the day
ends
what oh my goodness what have I done
still from her grave what what have I
done
[Music]
let's
go
[Music]
the I didn't do
anything at me I'm I'm you you need to
join
us I
[Music]
have um set go to settings and skin
custom ization and then head
off take off take off your take off your
yeah helmet whatever yeah
helmet
that I wanted to get water
[Music]
forgot there you go okay
I'm
so I'm shy I'm shy I'm trying though I'm
trying
guys wait when water in the nether why
oh it doesn't work in the nether oh
forgot oh well still nice to have it
right as long as I don't place my bed
right the bed the bed explodes right
[Music]
should I leave the bed
behind I don't accidentally use it you
think I'll accidentally use it
[Music]
we going
thank you thank
[Music]
you
st yeah yeah I got some
Stones let's
go
[Music]
foree
for let's
go go
[Music]
already
gone let's go let's go let's go let's go
go
[Music]
oh that's
do we need
boats we need
boats you
can if you
fall like right in the boat you don't
take
damage
really I'm going to have one just in
case I'm going to have one just in Cas
we're going all together so it's like
whatever
[Music]
I don't see front of me
[Laughter]
let's kill the
guest you're telling me that's a cat
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh I hear
lava all the sounds all the scary sounds
[Music]
feels like a
schol
why
okay go sh let's go sh let's
go oh okay okay shift Buton
okay they're building probably a one
block
path danger danger danger it's okay okay
okay okay
okay my goodness not dangerous
[Music]
pink
okay
ble big hole big hole big hole Yeah
that's good maybe good let's go let's go
let's go shift let's go shift let's go
[Music]
okay I feel like I'm just
observing you know when you're just like
standing outside of
a group
observing seeing them have
fun go
away nice big
hole
nice nice
[Music]
does not
work let's go let's
go what
[Music]
did oh is this the thing we're looking
for
[Music]
this
this I thought we were looking
for what do they look like there's a G
app oh wait that part that part
[Laughter]
the G that we saw for the for the
mission oh it's not the gas it's the
Bastion I think oh yeah this this
building thing the gas is the flying
[Music]
yes
for entertainment purposes she should
let go of shift
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe so I'm really scared
my pinky my
[Music]
pinky no
pushing no
pushing okay
[Music]
oh we need the mushroom
a
okay okay okay okay
okay how
oh my pickaxe is too
strong they went
up but if we just make a block like this
to go up how do we go down
afterwards how do we go down afterwards
if this is how we're going
up um yeah that's good question um
that's why they're that's why they're
like getting
blocks ler
[Music]
I got a glow stone out of
that I'm so scared have
aouch there's more
there oh there's so much here I don't
want to take it by
[Music]
accident okay I could go up oh they're
like oh they went up to take the glow
St yeah task done
[Music]
happy the teamwork
[Applause]
[Music]
speee foree
[Laughter]
[Music]
go next go next let's go
we're going to go that
[Music]
way
okay what sound is that oh there the
garbage truck hold on oh oh oh this
place is safe
but this is not the right one
right which one is that Crimson fungus
that's probably the oh but this
one warp fungus that's the one
right it's the green
one so is there's something that I need
D it watch out
for
[Music]
oh standing
out the green one yeah one
there I see another one behind it
[Music]
Ford
for
oh you good
[Laughter]
adding adding more to her that was laggy
adding more to her
crimes it did look
[Music]
laggy she looks laggy overall with her
VC cuz the others are fine to me
oh it died right it's
gone is it safe down
there is it safea
[Music]
oh did we Skip
[Applause]
[Music]
One like someone's going to
die someone will
die oh that looks dope from the outside
this pattern looks cool so are bastions
and Fortress uh a different thing right
and this is a Bastion right cuz like I
was thinking about a
fortress I haven't seen many
bastions yeah
okay
for still thinking whether or not
killing one with everybody will count
[Music]
ah this path is not
good okay
okay oh thank you thank you
okay okay okay although I'm behind
everybody so it makes no sense oh Ena is
still there okay
good okay okay okay appreciate the
[Music]
effort we're getting lost too
we going to be able to find our way
back she's taking her life to light just
because she saw a
mushroom this is not how you live in the
Never
[Music]
for don't jump I see one there but
that's so far she going there
oh oh there's one I think I think I
think I think she's trying to go
there I'm the cameraman cameraman Never
Dies this is
so you want to go up
oh I can shoot
too I don't I don't have kind of
far nice
[Music]
she getting more for everybody sweet Ena
you got
yours mushroom yeah I have two okay if
anyone need it I got
one let's wait for her
there's another one across the magma too
yeah I feel like we'll soon we'll soon
have them all
anyway oh
oh yeah let's go moving on uh
okay let's make this a double pth
don't
[Music]
[Laughter]
die do we still need more
[Music]
it's over here
oh yeah there's a lot there's a
lot there's so much La down
[Music]
there we have extra ones though know has
an extra one there's a pig on
the bridge Pig on the bridge
[Laughter]
Fork I did it alone so
strong she probably wasn't even panicked
was it just
one I have gold what do you
mean oh how getting so
much have to go
back maybe I'll need
more do I need stuff for for water
elevators right but I don't think I'll
be building
[Music]
any
okay what are you doing
here I'm come up come up come up mining
they're moving on
[Laughter]
did they go that way oh
[Music]
it's very
orange yeah I wouldn't mind get it
to but I think she's going to the never
[Music]
anyway
for
foree
[Music]
for
for my fault she didn't get the emeralds
and she doesn't have to buff
anymore but I gave her a diamond and she
was H happy about
[Music]
that oh they're actually so smart to put
down torches I was going to say like how
are we going to find a way back but they
put
torches so
smart Okay
Okay P's still busy with her extortion
okay then I don't feel so
bad cuz if I wouldn't go with this group
I would probably not be doing anything
right now
careful
[Music]
careful too
much
for
Fore
speee oh
show so much
courage doesn't want to be the first
anymore
[Music]
spee fore speee
apparently it's scary up there
[Music]
is she getting mushrooms for like
everybody who's not in the never know
yeah all of us no no no all of us all of
us oh but I already have onea has one
has
two so one person one person
one one for each person
where
did I see
it I
[Music]
challenged okay
[Applause]
okay it's so dramatic when someone dies
let's
go let's
[Music]
go only pick it up with right
I don't want I don't want to hit
[Music]
anybody there more
are you good up there oh you need
[Music]
help how do I say I have Infinity bow
Infinity Japanese I know it's like Al
but what's the buff
[Music]
called
for oh no better go
here she's sticking again
alone
for danger danger
[Applause]
where came
from danger
danger nice nice nice
[Music]
wish we could do that everywhere
though eventually
[Music]
I got of gold from that let's
go go go straight to the Gest
[Music]
mysterious
sounds stop
[Laughter]
[Music]
stop foree
red Forest
fore oh
[Music]
is asking her do you want to be
revived
she doesn't want her wife to be um
Widow in the
[Laughter]
chat
[Music]
for fore
[Laughter]
[Music]
spee
[Laughter]
[Music]
we're going to take the Miko PA
is giving coyot hard
time a hard time for her uh
yeah for her
death she needs to get s diamonds on her
own I think without getting them from
others
[Music]
they're talking about maybe ending it
for
[Music]
today thank you thank
oh thank you
what the are these sounds Somebody
went
like oh nice what a beautiful
path where are they I think they're
actually logging out right now
that's why they're not coming some of
them are logging
out is like if you're not back in 30
minutes it's over
to
KI what she has she has to get seven
diamonds on her own in 30 minutes
they're also getting excited about
something
[Music]
we found
something oh it's um they reported the
Bastion but we found the first but did
we have to find the Fortress or the
Bastion BAS
I don't
know are the other group found
[Music]
those were the days is that
uh achievement
[Music]
where are we
going entering bathroom oh we should
have entered it to get the achievement
oh we also took a picture
what's
[Laughter]
[Music]
it I don't think I would have been
pressing shift if I was in her situation
I would have died it
[Music]
n one single
hole dangerous
[Music]
yeah we should go up up
up we just went the path it 22
okay and should we make a path towards
up yeah while she's gone just like from
here
maybe is this
dangerous should be fine right might be
danger we can we can probably dig a
little up just have to be careful of
like like my pocket lava pocket yeah
your pickaxe stares me it's strong it's
so strong cuz it it will it will just
pop yeah I mean you're welcome to
dig okay I'll leave it to you then I'm
just scared it's just going to you know
go and get a indeed well Y is Diamond
too yeah
Taco
Taco oh G I hear G I hear G yeah it's
not visible
though must be up there then yeah yeah
we got to go up let's
go I will catch you if you fall down
from the
magma Forest wait I hear I think I hear
Hain
or have to be careful
of what the oh G is attacking us oh
okay
gas it's cute should we should we try I
think we should wait should wait for
them
also
GTO no let's close this off just in case
uh a pig yeah do you get an achievement
for killing a guest probably
right but does only the person who did
the last hit get
the the kill the achievement is what I
wonder I don't think I can get back to
sender with um with this pain
there's achieve I know there's an
achievement you can get for rebounding
the fire ballet shoots at you
oh it might leave if we don't kill it
y was it close I mean it sa us right
away
right where is it oh
uh must be a little below here
yeah oh is it gone be gone yeah be
no G come back Pig oh there's a big pig
and it didn't see me yet a small Pig
small Pig smaller smaller pig big big
pig a little dangerous here damn it's
gone it saw us and left must have thing
gone oh no I hear
it
oil
o oh it's oh it's there it's below us
basically all right close yeah like
straight over there oh okay the baby
look it's it's around here it'll maybe
stay for a
while I see it I don't know should we
should wait
right they should be on their way right
no ah so is saying we can do things
separately like probably because mikoi
can't find them
what's
this can I rebound the
fireball
yeah it's chilling
there I didn't even see it I just heard
it shooting
[Music]
no she's just explaining where we are
where we
went oh oh
[Music]
no ah oh but sub Senai said uh there's a
gas over at their area too so oh okay
yeah oh I heard the just defe
just a
[Music]
picture there's
two too lazy to switch to Japanese
keyboard
okay let's let's see I asked her if if
we should wait for her or
not there another h
I would like that leather is it is the
guy still there I don't hear
him I don't know
[Music]
gone wait maybe over
there no did we miss our chance
okay now I'm scared everybody's gone I'm
scared G is
gone
okay do they come down here oh my God
is I don't hear her but she's not
dead oh you know you okay okay because I
just I went back and there's wait don't
go up there there's like two big pigs
there's two big pigs don't okay I just
thought they ate
you oh
no don't die Ina don't
die don't worry don't
worry it's
on Miki said she's on her way but I
don't know if she's on her way to subu
sire or if she's on her way to us
there's another one
question
baby oh no it's not really it's it's
pretty far
anyway the baby on they run
[Music]
away help
oh it's is it okay it it stopped is it a
baby one no I think a big
one oh g g is back yay yay we're so
happy to have you back should we just
kill it I don't know if cuz she has her
uh sakuro also says Sako that she also
has a
gust okay I'm just yeah where did it go
now
oh wait let's kill the pig first before
it uh pushes us
down oh it just ignores
me okay good yeah it's far enough okay
come back come back we're ready to
fight oh there's another
mushroom this is kind of scaring me I
thought these mushrooms are Clos to
SC it's close
there it
is that was one
hit I didn't even shoot I don't think
that counts for
me no it's okay like somebody must have
already shot it or was the bow too
strong I don't know doesn't it take more
hits
normally I mean I do have a power four
bow oh me
too h M maybe never one spawns I don't
know if that counts I I mean I don't
know if picai really like checks what
every everyone did but feel like I need
to kill another one you you kind of with
me kind
of
kind they always one hit gas don't have
much HP oh really a m CH should we go
back then cuz yeah we should go back
let's try to find her
damn that was that was kind of funny
we're like we're we're scared and I was
like oh in
one where where is iess we were kind
ofp might not be us do you think maybe
they were hitting the same gas from
below oh maybe cuz we keep on going in
circles
oh 301
35 I mean wait was
that North First negative that was n
right that would be too
crazy
oops we were with
but separated
now to find
Mei all we see is tunnel see walls
Ena I see Ena which is also
a
[Laughter]
uh no no no no no I I
[Music]
uh good
timing
[Music]
[Laughter]
fore one
for okay okay
[Music]
we got back together
with okay yeah where are the
pigs
okay nice
[Music]
yes
English
English yeah root
M straight straight go
go go to meet friend
[Music]
foree
for two different
paths don't they connect we saw this one
before but the other
[Laughter]
[Music]
one
for where did they
[Music]
go not our path
that's so nice
convenient
what
[Music]
what wait how did we get
back no
[Music]
portal
[Laughter]
oh oh they're going back
[Music]
did we use this path I think
so t
[Music]
we going to go look for more
guests oh okay okay okay
okay just updating Ana so Ana can tell
them cuz Ana is with them with
them yes yes
yes yeah yes
yes hi
careful says we can
go but we want the guest
[Music]
wait they all get those achievements I
need one too I don't know if just seeing
one counts it we got to go in maybe
is that a pig or Ena oh it's
Ena the golden helmet made it look like
she's a
[Music]
pig oh
you know guys that's not what I meant
[Music]
I feel like it was above
us oh a several Enderman okay
okay yeah Green Forest is the Ender area
so m
[Music]
fore okay
if we get caught by the gas up there
we're so
effed
okay no yeah
oh I'll be on I'll be on
Bo oh God God I gas I'm shooting oh God
oh God oh God oh God my pinky is
weak I have a weak pinky I don't know
how Miki does it she must have a really
buff
pinky oh God I know I can there I can't
tell uh
eventually eventually for
sure
tle God feel like I'm slipping out of
out of it oh god oh she's making
okay wait we're going back maybe oh oh
my God they're
here finally
[Music]
dangerous I was jumping from happiness
oh
[Music]
St
okay that's all I got at least I think
oh wait I got
more at least we found each other
[Music]
[Applause]
no I
[Music]
[Applause]
no no this is the second time so she's
probably not getting revived di
before no
it should have been me it should have
been Me No it should have been me it
should have been me I know she's going
to rived cuz this is her second time
ding
really when did she die
before
yesterday there was a lot of Stu
happening oh no no not
so but then that's good because she has
been relieved from her 120 Diamond
depth now she's asking it
now
poor
[Music]
no oh pig pig danger Pig
thank
you I don't have a bow I'm so useless
[Music]
here it's my window
are we giving up are we going
[Music]
back is asking to return the
money in different
ways said let's let's talk about it
later o
hey that's damn that's so sad like we
were a
[Music]
team our our
friend our or
Senpai oh there so far you know let's
go yeah it's it's got to happen it adds
to the
drama
okay I don't see it
a lot of
[Music]
HP just hug the wall or hug the you know
why thank God Ena uh uh Miki
[Music]
came okay okay
okay oh yeah I would have gone that
[Music]
way no
[Laughter]
says bye-bye a star
bye-bye she right
there
[Music]
damn I got some Crimson Roots maybe
that'll help
[Laughter]
foree
speech
fore okay
I also got this one there we
go just
like it's like she's burning
[Music]
[Laughter]
make it a bit more fancy
my
[Music]
not listen
if you light the nether it will burn
forever oh
[Music]
wearing a
swimsuit where did it go
does it count does it count that I got
one I wonder
I can still go back like I think a lot
of them are logging out but I could
still go back I might die
but I think the still counts as
[Applause]
mine
okay oh
damn
it no we fight
nice I got
one oh there can I
have
one okay okay
okay yeah I killed one I got one too one
mem brain one member's brain is it two's
brain we'll never know we got two
ye okay
okay I still want to kill one gas and
one skeleton but I'll do that uh later
[Music]
bye okay
oh
potion oh potion
[Music]
machine I can even make a new one
for speech fore fore fore speech
what is this actually for for the diary
right I'll find my first Diary
today oh it's been already five and a
half hours
uge
[Music]
I'll fix those later
ni
nice for
[Music]
thank I'll
continue me too me
too you want to
continue yeah I think so we want to go
back and get a
gas
together yeah I mean I mean one one clap
one one collab one onone
collab that would be crazy what if I
invite
Miki oh she is she not quitting too
[Music]
okay let's go t let's
go then I'll put back my bed
[Music]
okay oneone collab again yeah damn it
will it will never happen Ana cuz I hate
you we're never going to be beating
the
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
for
[Laughter]
[Music]
fore
for
speech
speech spee foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
we keep on talking for the fence
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
oh my bed is gone I put back
I can't assert
dominance okay Ana surprisingly social
[Music]
where's where did she
go gone
sleep yeah um I know she went to sleep
then she'll come back I'm
sure okay
[Music]
okay are you are you
okay hey what time is it for you right
now
[Music]
4m. watch skit she's she's uh lifting
recently
[Music]
she just lost weight instead of
gaining
[Music]
foree okay
K's ready to go oh she should come now
then she can join the group
[Music]
speech speech
is not coming
[Music]
back fore
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'll tell
them nice nice
come
[Music]
[Laughter]
on let's go we're going to TT first KY
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go
all
right Kyle just so you know we're going
to TT
first okay but then we can go do all the
missions if you want let's
go this way this way
[Music]
go I wonder how far it
is for
[Music]
[Laughter]
close the door close the door oh close
the door okay
[Music]
already reached
it okay
okay let me go with you
Anya
oh
jungle oh the bamboo is
here all right I don't really know what
I need uh uh exp for
but let's go get it oh there's mushroom
world
too
damn oh oh my God can you imagine if I
would find a trident here can you
imagine damn that would be sick what do
you do in a t game H you get
exp don't know if you can hear me
probably not
I'm I ran out of water I got to go get
water while everybody's doing stuff
there I kind of want to go to idle
meeting I need
to I need to exchange my
oils
no I'm not a
robot I don't know what I I meant
because uh water goes then and water
goes out and I called it oil instead um
I don't know I I don't even don't no
let's change the topic can mikoi come
suddenly again so I can change the topic
naturally for
[Music]
yeah K you still have uh uh the the
what's it called Infinity
enchantments yeah but I don't bring it
oh no
problem but they're saying they want it
to have it okay but I told them just
come to
my
[Music]
for thank you this okay yeah I I look
this
wow I
oh
oh oh nice the skeleton mission
then I guess I did that too
[Music]
nice they're
doing taking commemoration
[Music]
pictures at the death bed of Aqua Seno
for can I go now is it
[Music]
same
fore
[Music]
for Fore
okay
[Music]
they want to make bows talking about how
to get
bows I already have mine te
[Music]
spee
Kyla what what what did you have for
dinner oh uh wait what
is I think I forgot
already I thought it was an important
time for
you yeah but it's it's the topic of the
conversation not the food
right but the food is connected to
it yeah well yeah well mhm what was it
I think I think wait wait wait oh let me
try to remember because I think my brain
and my soul already left my body I think
wait Nas Padang I think I don't know if
you know Nas Padang or but yeah I
heard n is like spicy
food that's
it yeah
okay what did you talk
about wow
tell me where'd you
going
you I don't know why mcft is like
that okay Minecraft very weird oh yeah
yeah yeah
mm
yeah she wants the
infinity stuff we got to go to Infinity
my house kind of house yeah my house at
home at home
[Music]
yay okay we they want to go
now house go now yeah they seems like
they want to go
okay okay let's go let's go that was a
short trip to
the emerald we
have
Emerald
wo wow
[Music]
wow oh they're blue wow
schol this intrusive thoughts
sorry thisin
[Music]
wo oh okay there they go help me dolphin
help me catch up why am I floating Oho
[Music]
[Laughter]
foree t t house
K hi I'm making a small small T the
house oh okay okay okay t house okay
okay T the house small smaller t house
smaller
[Music]
Y no they're like oh we feel sorry for
it no you don't get it it's not prison
it's small small t house
it's I love small small P house nice
not n no
fight I love gasto the family restaurant
in Japan very
recommendable yeah it's a quot
understand by meme they'll never
understand they don't get it they don't
get it it's
okay no one knows
oh yeah gust developer of
[Music]
aier that would be
proud ah the graves of our friends but
Co doesn't need a grave yet she's still
alive or alive again
way Emerald okay
oh I think they all have I think she
thinks that because some books you had
on in we we need to we need do we need
Emerald I don't really have the stock we
need to buy how manyal
[Music]
okay she's going to go get her emeralds
okay oh how much do you need how much do
you
need 20 maybe oh
20 you you can you can have like iron
ingot uh for for four iron ingot you get
one emerald in my place should I give it
a third enchantment so if you have like
fire Ingot you can trade it there my in
my house fire inot I I don't think
wait maybe we can check the iron farm
first hold on I don't know if they have
it
[Music]
okay yes yes
yes yes yes yes
in
house I'm having some unusual
interactions today M Senpai suicide
Senpai pretty
unusual oh they went down there for iron
they're probably going to take it all so
I'm good I don't need any I already have
my
stuff you know my right
hand you know the mouse hand the bottom
right of my hand is like really bruised
now I don't know today the table is just
harder than usual I have the gamer
bruise it
hurts no it's not about the crouching
it's about my mouse
hand booby Mouse bed I used to try them
but I feel like they're in the way I
prefer not having anything
there I'm not gripping so
hard oh I think I left my
bed damn it I I just thought we're going
to stay in the nether yet here we are
where did they go wait I'm I'm
lost oh no never mind we are at the
normal
Farm to
exchange
I what
what
lo oh not
here you're not here right because of
your bed or what what the you you won
the the the the no um the individual the
individual yeah the individual Locker
here here here it's here okay okay okay
ah okay okay okay I don't know where did
they go everyone is
like they're scattered it's fine I'm
going back to her
house why do I have a crafting table
[Laughter]
for one moment cuz I want to see it do I
still have
emeralds probably not
right cuz I was thinking maybe I could
get uh some enchantment for my sword
like a third one but I feel like at the
moment I'm strong enough for what I'm
doing I have
18 wait I wanted to I could put silk
touch and mending on this pickaxe no I
forgot about doing that now I have the
levels for it that's all I need right my
levels and the book and the
pickaxe mending and silk touch should I
put no don't put sick
touch well I can get another maybe
another
pickaxe oh speeder speeder speeder
speeder uh Fortune B than silk touch
yeah I mean if you think about it when
am I going to need silk touch when this
game ends in a few days what would I be
needing it for what do I want to
mine zombie oh they want to fight
[Music]
zombies
M okay then let's put s touch away but I
can put mending on it
no
maybe maybe I can get afford to
Fortune Oho okay
yeah
okay because there's the the dragons in
the air we should sleep this night oh
somebody passed
by that sounded like
coyote s touch just for a few BL
fortunes for everything
oh yeah but some things need Tok touch
but it's okay
I don't know what I would need it for I
can make two different ones so one silk
touch uh if I can afford it but the
other one I put mending on the current
one will end Fortune
right Sushi Sashi me
[Music]
where Are My
People my starting
point okay okay let's go let's go nice
[Music]
what the there's so many right
now the
I know the way I'm going to go that
way but the thing is I don't think we
can exchange the iron at
uh her uh
at her place it's this way
right it's this way yeah oh there's my
tunnel is this my people
[Music]
no I thought I knew the way turns out I
don't know the way
but it's somewhere this way
maybe yeah the village but no I feel
like if if I don't see the village yet
at this point then it's not
[Music]
here
sh why did
I why oh God
[Music]
creeper and I don't even remember
remember after several times of going
that
way but it was
somewhere um m is 140 right ah okay now
there it is there it is there's the
village and then past that
is deep deep deep
deep Ana was worried about
me swim
faster Ana thinks about me even though
she hates
me what an angel oh someone
here oh
[Music]
no not this is too good to be true
right so so
so they thought that the village was her
home yeah I know right I know that they
going to think the village is my home
but it's not oh this is more impressive
don't
worry C water why C
water yeah yeah
yeah thank
you okay can I buy something what did we
say I want fortune right
can't afford maybe
later maybe later maybe
later oh wait you guys don't
no in your hands K you need you need to
have a an iron Exchange wait do I do I
give is this one oh yeah right they do
have a too
oh do I do I give do I give them no no
uh uh right PL right PL the person yeah
yeah yeah I'm I can afford it
[Music]
how many four three what three I
think all
right she replaced this one right to
efficiency 5 damn she finally found what
she
wanted all
right uh
wow
wax wow wax W wax mine why so
good je wait you need the book the book
is here oh yeah I have the book I have
the oh you have the book okay I have the
book
what do I buy y y y
y nice good use of my
emeralds w
[Music]
yummy water I'm getting hungry though
got to go back to the nether soon I hope
we're going back soon and then get a
guas and then I'm pretty happy with my
achievements today but damn so many so
many missions today's missions were
really like a lot of work but you don't
have to do all of them obviously
it's all right I
guess llama's over there a where's the
owner you have an owner can I be your
owner I'm a I'm an alpaka collector you
know an avid fan of you guys yeah yep
you that's right I got blankets made out
of you guys too yeah yeah yeah very very
comfy but they seem so precious to me
that I don't use it the alpaka things
so in the end it's
useless
yeah made out of the wool
obviously I didn't kill an alpaka to get
a
blanket wo wo wo wo
[Music]
oh oh she really wants
the wait oh
no they're leaving no go back go back
[Music]
what do I do with this we might get
another addition to our
[Music]
group go down go
down what you going to
do sleepy time protect your villagers go
now
is actually sleeping
[Music]
time we're doing great yeah can't hit
them by
accident
uhoh worried about me have the bow what
do you need to make the B wait I think I
can make it for you hold on hold on
but do you have the infinity book
already yeah I do I have come here come
here
[Music]
all these bows that they're making now
will also be very helpful for the dragon
butt yeah yeah yeah
yeah Infinity is
best I already have mine so I'm just
waiting waiting waiting waiting
[Music]
oh they don't want to
sleep power on my bow I don't have the
emeralds for it now and I don't have the
iron for it
either it's okay I'll don't need it
right now for the for the ender dragon
fight yeah I'll get some
stronger o oh
[Music]
no did
I it
y sounds like a trident to
me first try and tole
could be so sick I would be the only one
to have a
trident imagine imagine at the end of
fight somebody uses a trident and
they're like who the is using this
trident I'm like it's me it's just me
yeah
yeah can you enchant of course you can
right yeah yeah yeah
I should go and get a trident on my own
and then keep it a secret until the
end that would be such a
flex sheesh
[Music]
sheesh joined the party so late but
shows up with a freaking trid
End oh I'm helping the gold
Golems ah he doesn't know what's hitting
him oh we sleeping
now are we oh they're still running
there oh yeah I think now we are
sleeping just saw her go to
bed building a drown Farm is not very
hard well well you don't know the story
of takanasi ki's first
Trident okay granted I shouldn't be
sleeping
there I don't need a trident V to get a
trident no
no why were they hunting zombies by the
way what's that
for do I need zombies
you had to be there alive for
[Music]
real oh there we go oh
I'm going to Dr
[Laughter]
myself okay again and again and again
Unbreaking
Unbreaking hey it's here where's the UN
Unbreaking oh okay thank it's your Old
Farm it's 11 you don't have 11 no no
more inot uh wait let me
see I'm
four how many ingots do you
need um 11 apparently
you 11 take it's just 10 though uh this
one this one wait where is it this
one
oh oh this one oh you got it oh hold on
hold on hold on hold on I have do
manyu it's okay okay okay okay I can
take that for you thank you like go back
to the Anvil yeah
Anvil
okay um so the oh and then the this do
you have enough level for that you need
the level oh yeah I I think so I take
it y thank
you thank
you nice
[Music]
I
think she needs a bow too need
[Music]
a thank
you
you coming
no no no
go not caring not caring thank you very
much you me yay
[Music]
get that should be our introduction when
we do a collab you for
[Music]
cominging the Villager
follow yeah it's okay it's fine
nice I wonder if she'll ever notice
it wait
what
hey read it out
loud oh she you're not seeing it K look
here I'm not a Kiara I'm Kaa I'm not a k
I'm kaha yeah that would be my part
oh you know what that is
referencing yeah I know B right okay try
again try again first first take first
take you start okay I'm not K I'm K and
I'm not a Kyla I'm
[Music]
K oh the Villager wants to did it we did
it okay maybe we could
be nice
CH and but you know why I wrote this
because subu Senai called me Kaa several
times today oh
really she did she should know who I am
she
did I
see I think she was confused because I
was leading her to Kyla's house so she
was also calling me
Kyla
she I didn't kill her she died on her
[Music]
own you murder no I didn't do it I
didn't do
it
no why do she keep on leaving the
game Arrow okay oh arrows arrows Arrow
I I I gave the arrows
already what's what's the what's arrows
in you explain AR Arrow
yeah thank you very much
[Music]
I should go to pick the others
upbe no no
[Music]
no
grou my name
[Music]
isce my name is not can I'm no no
that's come here come here
[Music]
now everybody knows now everybody's
finding out about ky's free
[Laughter]
[Music]
stuff I had a feeling that throughout
the
day more and more people will figure it
out what you wanted to monopolize it no
no no because like well yeah kind of but
no but today you know I found it because
I just was asking for help and then I
told S stand by at that point nobody
knew yet and now everybody
knows so kylo's going to get real busy
everybody wants something
[Music]
kylo she can't go to the nether because
she has to make bows for
everybody so
sad theand is
high when can we go I want to go back
[Music]
okay okay the pig will not be forgiven
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
[Music]
somebody will
die it's okay it's
[Music]
okay is worried that somebody will die
with these am this amount of
people no no please don't see that
no stop take down arrow be
friendly I'm just repeating my memes
that nobody else
knows but you guys know that's all that
counts what me the first expedition went
okay you're saying that but s
died
hi didn't go well at all someone died
for God sake
[Music]
what did you say you guys wouldn't
understand you guys wouldn't get
it no okay I'll tell you Ana I'll tell
only
you okay so okay first of all you
remember when I was building the turtle
house yes that's a cal meme
actually oh yeah I don't get it yeah
because like in a I think in a Super
Mario uh playthrough that you know
there's a turtle and she was like ah
turtle is so small smart smallart t
house smartart t house and she was
laughing at the turtle which was funny
so I was making a smaller smaller t
house yeah and just now when Miki and uh
Kyla when they were fighting I made a
refence reference to um a that's like
from three years ago um when P Senai
said basically take
down be friendly to me and MAA Senai
because we were
fighting so that's also a
reference Sun versus Moon
fight guys
guys I I don't think they know the way
we we we go to the wait we went to a
different village yeah they they just go
further and further oh uh I don't even
see them anymore
[Music]
yeah I think they just got into the
mountain I don't know
okay she she
noticed should we should we should we
wait them or should we just go wait for
them they went that way right yeah they
they went to that um Mountain they went
to the Village I think the village they
think that's the other Village that we
went through I guess yeah I think
yeah she thought that
was go to this Village oh yeah yeah
there there went to that Village come
back
hello what's happening here why is
there does the Alpa own
house it's like greeting the
others we're never going to get to the
never at this
[Music]
I want to eat snacks
[Laughter]
[Music]
where's
where she at spawn okay we we have to
start leaving people behind
because we can't keep on stopping
no I think I think mik Miki led the way
and
then uh Kori P got to meet Luna said so
she stops a bit there I think yeah yeah
yeah it to be like that at the spawn
point okay
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
you think there'll be many
Clips well the subu thing definitely
becoming a
clip and maybe me and Ena talking me
saying she's a she's also a
wall probably yeah oh and now I have two
beds
oopsie well well
well wait for me okay okay
[Music]
T but you got the tetu from me right you
still have my t
[Music]
yeah you don't need glow
stone
okay come
[Music]
on there's that a gift right of a cat I
think doing the pop po pop pop oh it was
you oh you heard my pop
[Laughter]
pop you know the song Ana I know I love
that song Let's
[Music]
Go Ana you speak Japanese so well what
about learning
Korean oh I am really bad at Korean me
too did oneing stream and that's it I
need to learn Korean to Lear I took
lessons from a IRL teacher privately
oneon-one for half a year last
year uhhuh but then I forgot
everything oh no yeah I think I should I
shall start from the from
memorizing fore
[Music]
[Applause]
we don't want to go in a circle again
let's go this way
[Music]
g g g
[Laughter]
[Music]
g too slow too slow
what's wrong what's
wrong are you
good yeah yeah yeah you want we probably
already have a lot of things that you
don't have yet so just feel free to you
know what you're so quiet I can't hear
you
yeah are you trying to say something
what I can only slightly hear you
where's the
guest where did Miko go the way okay we
going to make a path here
[Music]
she just goes next
door maybe it was on
purpose what you mean on purpose because
she's only uh participating for one day
and maybe she's just like all right
I'mma end it in a dramatic
[Music]
way very
nice I'll do it
[Music]
she returns to the star maybe when she
dies
[Music]
wait wait wait
okay
okay she
lives
y oh Kyla is fixing it nice fix it's
okay it's okay is it really
though yeah it's okay it's okay maybe
should go
first I I I think Kyla would would be
chill in every
situation I think I would have just
ran oh wait I forgot the
Torches oh
[Music]
spee
is this a flag for magma
[Music]
okay oh it'll be faster with this she
maybe too
fast maybe too
fast oh God
[Music]
okay kylo thank you Ka thank you
ka thank you ka God I could not
[Laughter]
react okay it's
okay it's
okay what's that path be careful
[Music]
dancing oh
God yeah yeah yeah nice nice nice
nice where are we going to go just going
to go straight or can I can I have some
blocks please yeah um how do I throw you
a whole block again
here I'll throw you another one if you
want
okay let's go
oh nice
stay down stay
down I could make the sides
but what is this you guys know who built
that where leads
[Music]
[Laughter]
there's AAS oh God oh God uh we should
we should reach uh a
ground uh
now oh
God
okay KY just kills it
casually K you got a kill for the gas
Mission yeah for the mission right
complete yeah mission complete
nice oh God I just walked through the
fire nice
okay okay well the other side is
dangerous I leave I leave
torches oh
God what is
this wait I didn't read if you guys
answered but did you say I'm scrolling
[Music]
I think that's a path to a fortress but
not but it's like not naturally
generated
right that looks human
made
yeah you're in the way
Pig oh the others made
fore
speee where did you go
like me and Ana are miki's
assistants and Kyla is a separate entity
because she's too powerful
[Music]
me me too I want to kill
too just baiting it I'm the masturbator
how many guests that we need
again um one person one oh okay we we
can just do it together we can just do
it together as a
team I'm I'm I'm baiting
it baby no no no no not baby
[Music]
where did mikoi
go I forgot the uh I can't take the gold
close to them oh
nice a few more
[Music]
please I would tape my shift button
okay okay okay Kyla still needs a lot of
things that we already have
oh wait yeah that's the sound of a ghost
right uh
[Music]
ghost yeah it's probably
above ni
path
W oh it sounds so close it sounds so
close yeah the gas
right maybe we'll just go straight again
back to where we
began H oh
felt an
earthquake here's glowstone for kylo
maybe if she didn't get it
already bgm doesn't fit
here
yeah damn the atmosphere is so cool
though what if this was just a way back
back this is just the way back I think
this is like the T way right
May uh don't know what this
is where does it
continue this is not the
yeah it's not what about
this that one see this one yeah oh yeah
I
know this one be
careful are you okay yeah probably not
oh my God
[Music]
she lives she no um no yeah uh I saw
that coming I was about to close it off
[Music]
[Laughter]
she was too
curious
yeah I really was about to close it
off
man you saw me put those uh blocks in my
hand
[Music]
damn for
could have almost it could have been me
can always be
me can be
anyone don't
panic should I should I kill it for
them okay
let's go let's go let's
go kiaha Kawa
teamwork those cubes are vicious they
didn't seem to want to attack me though
maybe cuz
I'm kind of my element is fire so they
like me I don't know maybe I smell like
fire so they like me
ohe oh
[Music]
okay
me I am not
I everyone
is yeah
[Music]
I'm glad I went with this group now
yeah it's a reference to Dragon Ball
apparently the amount of
diamonds
interesting night
dangerous
like be careful
night uh I'm going to run out of
blocks
oh oh so hat also has to go to solo
server and uh get uh seven diamonds on
her own in 30
minutes
oh that system yeah yeah kyi also had to
do it
okay
[Music]
it's time to watch Indiana
Jones it's pretty
funny of
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
hold on hold on you fix it you fix it
Kyla you're the
fixer nice nice
nice when they hear my scream they know
what
to don't
die it's
okay but doesn't
work she was burning it's fine
[Music]
yeah KY you you you do some of the path
please
yeah
nice together strong
thank you
yeah
isad her she reacts so much better than
me she's so chill
she's so
good she's so
good I can't stay so
[Music]
calm so
calm damn
[Music]
that's how a professional
Works never is a true home I can I can
feel that call for oh what oh
yeah should we still go straight I think
maybe yes
[Music]
okay to use
cobblestones yeah it's fine yeah
anything except don't place a bed in the
nether never place a bed in the
nether yeah I I know that much
okay oh thanks for the raid thank you
for the
ra she's so good she's so good it's okay
it's
okay
oh it's better if I don't build here uh
if I'm not digging there's so much
magma
for
nice so much m
is isun to high in the
[Music]
never
High it's so
close yeah it's like let me out let me
out you want to go
left I don't know we probably still it
sounds so close I want to take a
look I don't I think it's on the left
yeah it's kind of on the left but I
don't
know oh mcky now it's right
thing yeah what oh this it's right there
it's right there oh is it can you see it
there there there there it's so close
it's so close I'll kill it I'll kill it
dangerous
dangerous beer be safe safe thank
you I see
[Music]
it let me kill it oh sorry sorry
no it's gone it's gone
I
nice
no come
back come back
no oh my
God
back afraid if they die come come come
[Music]
no who was that we both both of us I
think we can both have the
achievement we both did it nice yeah we
both did
it it doesn't say so we both did
it we did it together nice
[Music]
okay we can continue
Kyla thank you for leading us what what
should we do now uh we we have to dig
more I guess we we continue we
continue okay Fortress
[Music]
what is
this it's
[Music]
chill I think we're looking for Fortress
and the these people uh looking for oh
actually is gone so it's
only and KY I think need all kinds of
[Music]
things I
think KY you still need like everything
right like the or are you trying to do
the missions or do you want to ignore
the missions the missions the missions
just a glow stone yeah and a a a green
mushroom mushroom green Soul Sand you
got to get Soul Sand oh Soul Sand it's
the oh yeah War fungus it's a warp the
oh the
[Music]
warp we did it it's appar down here
me
not really is she says it's down there
[Music]
foress wa we actually found it
M I have to make a
[Music]
path
Yuki she wants to fall down with a boat
down
uh I think it's too dangerous if you
want to go down KY do you want to
something hold on will you make
Bridge can can you can you try make
[Music]
something I can't tell oh is it is it
this no wa what n n oh where is it
where is
[Music]
it where is
it she is it is it where is
it where did it shoot from
yeah I don't know I don't see
[Music]
it oh it's this
PA it's
okay nice one nice one oh it's there oh
yeah yeah yeah
oh they're playing
tennis I thought I thought Canada was
going to try kill
[Music]
it
uh don't die
people does she have the bow now
are are we all fine
yeah okay oh
oh still
there it's done it's done okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
down here right
[Music]
fried
potato fried
potato but that one is very
aggressive that one was aggressive yeah
that one very is very
aggressive SK SK
[Music]
okaye
fried
potato
[Music]
skato they're
shooting that one that one guas guess
that one
[Music]
I'm land uh Canada my bow
first okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay it no no no no no no no no no no no
I don't have Arrow now uh so if she dies
[Music]
now panic panic
okay
nice nice okay okay
nice it came right to
us
[Music]
nice here here this way this way that
way oh that way
right oh they went down here oh but this
one is down down here too oh okay
um how far did she
get H they're making two BS uh like
pretty close already this
one okay okay but miki's path looks
safer don't fall okay don't fall don't
fall
oh your path looks kind of dangerous
there let me get some blocks when I was
digging all the blocks were picked up by
the people behind me so I have like
nothing please no
nothing this is
me she she's somewhere she didn't
die yeah she she didn't die I think I
think is she at the bridge the other uh
stairs oh god oh yeah
there there is a
communication yes uh they're they're
here they're all on the other side we're
making like two paths now down
now wait what there's two paths
now which way I don't know they're
they're making a nicer looking one
this one's safer
[Music]
who's going to be faster oh just
protect
M
prot are they there
[Music]
later
okay thank
you than they don't attack me I'm too
far oh there's so
many got to make the path
safe oh
[Music]
oh nice
this reminds me didn't I go with fauna
into a
[Music]
fortress that's the wrong one unless
they have a green
one why is the why are they here
oh yes
I you want skeletons to summon oh right
they drop something sometimes
right was it their head or what are they
dropping they dropped their head if
you're lucky okay
[Music]
okay I want to see the
connection oh what's
[Music]
this oh
oh the blaze I hear them
[Music]
yeah
the oh that one be careful be careful
it's coming it's coming oh my goodness R
I don't want to shoot the pig fine run
run just run
run what do we do that we we catch
it no we kill we kill it all right if
you if if but it
burns I killed it nice and then take the
drop take the drop oh I didn't drop
anything nothing
sad it's okay next
one maybe there's one
here oh
here little bit of so
exploration this closed off do we go
here do we go
here uh I know thank
you I feel so comfortable now like this
isn't even Hardcore Minecraft I'm just
chilling
oh never W that was also a
mission there's never
one I think it
was cuz now we already had it Anya I
think from the previous trip oh really
okay where did KY
go oh what
is there nothing
behind I think here's dead
end this is a dead end okay you need
them for
Missions I'll take oh now it's
gone
oh need to find the others
again where did they go
a normal
skeleton I'm
fine
D I wonder when for maybe during her
usual streaming time she's going to
join she's also got a lot to do hey yo
mine mine
yeah I got a place
[Music]
R got
it what what's
scary maybe there's more where that came
from
okay oh it's fine I killed
it thank you thank you thank you no
Blaze Rod this
time but there's more NE
wart if it's necessary for potions I'll
take
it oh yeah I need I need to do the
potions too the
potion go get it
yeah looks like another dead
end
okay H we can go down from
here but I think we were here too
all I think this yeah we were here
before wait isn't that
literally never mind
okay oh
Kyla yeah uh I already killed like two
blazes and I got one Blaze
Rod nice so if you go that way I don't
think there's anything but
ni
[Music]
okay oh
I want to kill a skeleton too oh do you
still have the mission open you still
have you don't have free yet um yeah I
need to kill two more skeletons oh okay
well they're everywhere they're also at
the TTT
so I wonder if the skeletons at T
I kill a bunch of
them I don't know if that counts or
not is that why
we they're downstairs are
they do wa there skeletons pretty huge
area yeah so I don't know oh oh that's
normal
pig make got
ah I think I
see so maybe Miki is close oh
[Music]
wait so we're all together except for
mikoi
[Music]
Senai yeah
really my eyes are
blind okay then maybe we need to go down
way
where over there over there let's go
let's
go over there what are you
seeing
ah
T maybe how did she get there oh this
way
a this way this way this way but she's
up now it's up there how did she get
there hey yo hey yo hello
hello uh I'm cursed what do I do now oh
God oh God I might die I'm going to die
I'm going to die no I don't want to die
I don't want to
[Music]
die I was so CL close to dying I was so
close to dying I was so close what were
are you doing I had three more Hearts
left I had three more hearts
I underestimated the
curse the the curse that you get from
the Wither Skeleton so
[Music]
strong I thought it was over for
me I like this feeling oh my
goodness oh good you're living on the
edge I still see her now should we just
dig up about the edge should we dig
up cuz I'm a weapon
there is no way that there is anything
where is she though is she in the
Fortress though
[Music]
almost
di
go I'll hide
don't die don't
die it's
[Music]
okay that's a play spawner
oh my shield my shield doesn't exist you
know I like to ignore my shield
he's friend
shaped
[Music]
oh oh that's a spawner
n exciting
[Music]
why am I burning again
oh who shot me
[Music]
hot hot hot hot
hot yeah there's two spawners
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't die Kyla don't die don't oh don't
die it's
fine okay
chill someone's shooting
[Music]
oh oh she's gone how do I get at the
Rocks when there's so much
[Music]
spawning that looks
yummy um what the
[Music]
okay how do we get them wrong
oh who who W oh they're in the back
there
too hi
guys you breathing kind of
loud I want the rods
it's so over it's so
over well until we have a good solution
for getting the
r it's not worth killing them
[Music]
hey yo hey yo hey
yo
[Music]
for don't come out don't come
out stay
[Music]
okay okay my shield I don't
even doesn't exist to
me I don't it's been so long you know of
me playing Minecraft that I it's just
not up in
my like not natural actions choice of
actions okay there's one here too is
there a spawner there
too probably
not
oh I think she Googling goog s
[Music]
H
Blaze how
tutorial oh
[Music]
does anybody need the
kill too
far what you going to do about it what
you going to
do oh I think she found
it
oh I will have her back I'll try
[Music]
no
no K Kyla do you know how to build it so
that you can get the
drops oh it's it's uh they're like
specific build do you know how to build
it I can help to do it but maybe
[Music]
not yeah later I I can do it off stream
though oh okay yeah I think she wants to
build it
now oh you want to she she wants to
build it now
yeah we don't really have to oh but no
she's saying we might go back yeah
[Music]
maybe it's
[Laughter]
okay now I don't would I have needed it
now
okay I think we might be going back it's
not recommended to build in hardcore
well we have no
[Music]
choice k
how to
get I don't know you want
[Music]
to
okay
oh
[Music]
oh will be fine right
but she'll need a
bow
sorry sorry
sorry uh got it got it got it oh it
dropped the rod it dropped the rod it's
right there the rods the rods just gone
it's fine it's on it's on the
ground if only alun was here he would go
there immediately
[Music]
potato not worth
it Al yeah he would be he would jump
down right
away oh God what's wrong with
me wow because I think it's because of
the kunon
ending wow the C like okay it's used
sometimes for girls but mostly for boys
so it's like making everything confused
in my
brain
she I didn't realize at
all
[Music]
damn oh
don't don't touch
me uh no it was unintentional of
course I'm
sorry you hit
me oh no problem I we all know that we
hate each
other I mean that's true yeah that's
true
Which
Way um I don't know I'm I'm just going
to be following
KY she know the way is this the
way what is this
path it's interesting
yeah the question is now how do we find
I don't even know like we entered so in
such a weird way like it would be hard
to find that exit again or the
entrance into the Fortress once we have
that we might be
fine oh the those torches probably mean
that's the way to the spawner
hey I hope it counts for the whole group
that we found it or is that I'm still
confused which one's the achievement
because we acted like the Bastion was
the
achievement left or right I got to check
the missions
again I think
is
somewhere got to check the missions but
I hope I hope we all got it yeah it's
probably not that strict right we were a
group so we all get the Fortress I don't
know is it Fortress of
Bastion we go that way we want to go
back cuz we also took a picture of the
Bastion together
[Music]
and does she have the curse
yeah
same same
problem is this where we came
from hm
oh this way we're making two paths
[Music]
again has to be towards a CLI wall
yeah yeah this feels like we came from
there
danger dangerous dangerous dangerous
dangerous dangerous danger dangerous
dangerous
danger
wait you're sweeping the the ground
under my feet close don't get close
is that
love don't get
close don't get
[Music]
closeth isn't that what you say when
you're in love or when someone's really
magnificent beautiful oh yeah don't get
you sweep the floor under their feet or
so what was it
sweep them off their feet
[Music]
a you went up a
level yep it's okay
you know if you don't have blocks I
still have
some should go to
die God I'm so scared to now
my
pinky is under
pressure I don't want to bother you guys
I'll yeah no
[Music]
worries laying out the red or dark brown
carpet for the
Senai I need blocks ah I got you
what did she fall
down oh she left the game I have wait I
have uh let me give
you thank
you she just disappeared so I thought
she fell down
he disconnected that was scary like okay
we that close that was
scary
uh nice slide
Panic oh yeah B oh portal we have portal
here really right there
[Music]
is it the right one which one is
it what not not not not not our portal
but it's the other
portal
can the dri
one should we use
it no I don't think so because it's so
close I think it's too close it's too
close to the city one it's going to
break the
[Music]
city
true go up I'll be I I'll go up
later Kyla's chat be like can we get
much
higher can you get much much higher so
high okay
one
okay don't fall
down fall down
we got
our what do you call it
the what do you call it
when we fulfilled the quota we already
fulfilled the quota of people to die in
a trip
[Music]
wait
wait let's let's go
[Music]
back one person per
trip seems to be the
quota I wonder if she made it because
the 30 minutes are over
[Music]
wait wait wait
wait
[Music]
to yeah seven diamonds in a Solo
World hey
okaya always so
thankful oh seven no seven blocks is I
think unrealistic that's a different
thing the
blocks when you die you have
to get in 30 minutes in a Solo world
seven blocks on your own H not blocks
normal
[Music]
diamonds don't know how she did
it she said she did it let me ask
[Music]
she found 13 in 27 minutes she was just
digging so it's not impossible 13 in 27
minutes and I found like nothing
no she said she even found it before
reaching the right level for
[Music]
diamonds No More Death what do you mean
I never Di Happy Happy Happy Meal happy
meal
McDonald's oh Ana you're making it
now
[Music]
thank get some food what I'm full I'm
full for
[Music]
all you can eat on cake Bing
spe
[Music]
you good I can I can make it too Anya if
you're tired yeah um I ran
[Music]
out who saved my life
okay
ol what a nice
VI I feel like that was a
song
Danger there's like no way dangerous D
and and we are actually running out of
blocks I still have lots of
[Music]
blocks I
give thank you
[Music]
just go up or just go up
okay it's already 700 p.m. she
right those eight hours went by so
fast are you stream for 8 hours
yeah but that's nothing for you
so close to
12 you want me to go to 12 I don't know
I want to
[Music]
eat I want to eat food
yeah we achieved accomplished a lot
today I don't even know what I want to
eat I should eat my diet food
[Music]
KY you good Kyla
are you
okay I can't
hear
oh oh there we go you
okay were you
lagging yeah I I was like why everyone
stops talking is this the Indonesian
internet no I think it's the Minecraft
oh yeah they said those really I think
it's my Minecraft my Minecraft just had
enough I
[Music]
guess what's with
your oh my
goodness
nice oh my
goodness what
[Music]
that could have pushed me into that lava
but could I have gotten
[Music]
out she thank God that there was a like
a yeah not like immediate death right
there
jeez depends how
deep if it was two blanks deep you'd
have to swim up
hot tourist
destinations
what what does it mean
nice is it the
green this is officially the best St
ever
[Music]
oh very successful tour
I indeed nice feels good
man Tour by yeah I think in Japanese
they say
B very nice
tour no I didn't pronounce it correctly
I pronounce is in
[Music]
Katakana oh this is the mushroom biome
well maybe we can get a mushroom for you
and Canada you still need a green one I
think
KY or does it not grow
[Music]
here eat the green mushroom
right the blue green
one there's here here
here over
here here here here here
[Music]
yeah
yeah there were several
just there's one more here K just need
one right over down here there's another
one we just need one right yeah just
one okay I think everybody got
it
[Music]
okay okay
musom I can do it KY you just built the
ground damn you're that close already
okay
okay I do have some experience with this
in the end as well well so yeah it's
been a while though building paths like
this very
nice
okay
okay just go lower a bit it's fine you
go down yep bit
[Music]
n still thinking about Subaru
Senai oh yeah I ran out of
foress what happened actually yeah she
was with us in the group on our first
never trip and yeah she fell I think she
fell into the lava but because of in the
yeah but because of a pig yeah yeah the
ne because of the what the pig like it
attacked us and getting attacked by the
never mind she's
gone oh welcome back that's very
unfortunate
[Music]
yeah you're being bullied Kyla I don't
know Minecraft bulli me so hard yeah why
why Minecraft asked me to stop yeah I
think they're trying to Nerf you it's
not
nice I think in Japanese they also say
na yeah they say that
what it I I'll put I'll put time
Tok I have a few
[Music]
more y teamwork
teamwork
teamw and every single time the let
down give
me weird feeling yeah does scare
you does it give you a nervous
feeling yeah because I never
forch uh the way in Nether and every
single time the nether got a little bit
brighter it means lava oh oh
oh yeah so it it's like tangle me every
time you put the torch it's like my auto
it's my outdoor reaction towards
lava
lava I get it makes
sense it's
okay I can I can say before I place it I
can say torch it's fine it's fine
wait we need to go up again
[Music]
okay that was indeed
lava that is not my
torch y yeah right you know what I mean
right mhm if it lights up the same
[Music]
way but don't worry if it's it's not in
front of your eyes then it's all
good oh but that was kind of in front of
her eyes
[Music]
okay come on come on
Pinky wa that could almost sound like I
was saying that to mik
to build the bridge with me come on
Pinky cuz she's
pink okay hold
on it's
okay my Pickle's too strong I don't want
to do it Pinky and the Brain Brain Brain
Brain oh
I don't I don't have a weaker one
though it's okay they're doing it
more
carefully wait how does she know
where we even took a curve how does she
know do you have the coordinates Kyla
yeah damn so reliable
it's just it's just how I
[Music]
survive so
good seems like we traveled far
out but now we're
making a path specifically for the
Fortress to reach it easier that's also
it's there we
ar or so it
[Music]
seems she'll do anything for you says
mik oh
[Music]
how did they get where did they
go oh I didn't see oh okay
okay
yeah I don't have
one M we should put it there yeah so
people know where it
leads
[Music]
nice still streaming yeah good
morning good
morning good yeah
yeah okay
[Music]
in Minecraft just feels right yeah
that's right feels nostalgic like I
don't think even when Minecraft was more
popular that I ever went around with
such a big group before except with
maybe the ender dragon fight in the EM
this is really rare I was mostly
alone playing alone
[Music]
nice
yeah it's raining man
what the
[Music]
hell it feels like we've been in the
nether like forever then we go it's been
years oh my God we in the N for 100
years maybe for tomorrow event or and
then we we come
back and while everyone watching
it what happened here maybe tomorrow we
have to fight to death in
here wow go still
building spoiler
spoiler close D
event wait cuz I still don't have the
names on I was like why doesn't show the
name
[Music]
thank you very much very very very much
thank you thank you
[Music]
for
us who going to write it
uh okay thank you
[Music]
okay
okay no diamonds for
Fortress damn so it was only the Bastion
I know I think I think it's going to be
defied if I remember correctly but just
said there's no reward for the Fortress
only for the
Bastion oh yeah the Bastion
yes oh
Bastion I thought I don't know I thought
the Bastion is like for one one person
who sees it first
I yeah IR there's a ice paath for uh
another a second ah was just asking for
it hours
ago showing her the there's another iron
trap over
there there's another
one
nice free iron armor are they playing uh
Junkin B what's
this what is this way hey another
another iron farm the second one in case
this one's empty oh really mm okay wow
wait hold on I'm I'm going to write
[Music]
English
nice trap
[Music]
too it is Fortress well whatever I saw
both so
uh it's right there oh shees you're so
low come here come
here ticklish I'm ticklish
stop they do so little
damage give me the membrane
stole my
kill wait
[Music]
B There we
go it's okay I'm not mad not at all
really really
don't just having fun killing some mobs
is there a bed in here
I need to find the locker where I put
all my stuff I it's over
there yeah I don't know why they were so
low they were constantly so
low normally they're only low for like a
little
bit
hello sleepy time
[Music]
this sleepy
time oh
okay time to clean up
[Music]
everything I'll put this here as
proof H now I'll be
back ah it's free right now so let me
[Music]
I'm going to write something in it right
now oopsy oh okay really quickly
upss how do you make a potion no idea
you you need the you need the materials
what what what kind of potion is
different is different any potion it
only says potion in the mission um a uh
you need to have
the the what's that the potion maker
kind of
and pretty sure I don't have any yeah
the Brewing sand yeah that's the word I
I have it uh I have it in my
house yeah M um I got Nether
wart um nether W yeah oh another what
this oh it just ends there uh wait let
me check understand
okay
uh anything extra did the skeletons and
the GH GH maybe the blaz powder I can
still do the the powder the what powder
and then oh we need the bottle of water
if you guys are making a potion I want
to join can go to my house
actually do you have a potion maker Kyla
yeah I have
the can I go and make
okay let's go then I have another
mission The Fortress I'm not
sure here is this for Bastion but I saw
both I'll just ride it yeah oh no but I
think um K is writing it for all of us
this one
[Music]
automatic potion
machine
oh that
one but how do I use
it but
[Music]
you you just need to put the the the the
the what the
the the ingredients the ingredients oh
really oh this one I think it's missing
the
[Music]
the I I can I can I can take it for her
oh thank you okay okay wait wait okay
thank you
oh oh oh think she's going to her
[Music]
home more diamonds
should we not just
[Music]
wait
yeah I think I'll go to my home
once guys
I'm I did not think that this is how
today would
go in the beginning I was so super
anxious and
like I thought if anything it would be
the safest choice to just stick with
Kyla in the end I was with Kyla a little
bit
but actually most of the time I went
with like you know people that I didn't
expect to go with
today especially mey I'm so happy that
we got closer like really I think today
the
biggest friendship so to say Improvement
that I had was with mik
Zai which I didn't expect but we worked
so closely together and I went on both
of her never
trips
so what do I need for potions is there
anything I need like it doesn't matter
which one we make so I really don't care
but I just want to bring the right
thing do I need like bones or anything
or never warts right people were saying
never warts
yeah Ana to lots of Ana to Ana made me
feel more like comfortable too around
everybody else in the beginning I felt
like oh as long as Ana is there I feel
good uh
so no idea what I need
guys I'll just bring the ne W the thing
is close anyway the machine
so what then another ingredient what
could it be like what an
apple an apple or what
chicken spider ey oh okay what does that
make the Magma Cream what am I making
with the spider eye
[Music]
yeah fore
monke monkey
monkey
[Music]
[Laughter]
monke how to you
[Music]
well she's growing it here
nice thank
you
[Music]
for
okay or where she go oh
[Music]
not sure what we're
making move the Redstone and the M move
move what do you mean move like to the
middle one Magma Cream enough to brew on
right but qu simpa was saying like maybe
we'll make it for everybody oh isn't it
because there's something missing here
the glass is missing
I don't have a class oh s by a Kyla yo
what's
up hello we are
uh trying to make
something yeah good luck not sure
how it's just that the the bottle is
missing I guess
or what happened it's not working I I
don't know know how it's supposed to
work cuz I didn't build it but I put in
the never
warts supposed to be
like oh it needs to be the blaze powder
you need
to to you okay I got it I got
it yeah I that's my single only um BL
yeah what are we making
now it's
working nice
[Music]
nice not again not now okay it's already
and then
you need everyone
sleeping okay okay sleep sleep
[Music]
okay take the Redstone out
uh-huh does is that what makes it
mundane first one I don't know how this
works I didn't make it
[Music]
it's useless but it is a
potion better than
nothing hello
oh you need to add more stuff so it's
like we can work from this as a base
right oh no no
oh need to
get the the nether word in the red stone
right and then after that we
go red stone after that to make it 8
minutes
this is this is like this is like wrong
order we shouldn't get the mundane
potion I wrong one so instead of
[Music]
here how do I make how do I make potion
hold on wait you already made a mundane
potion at
least mundane potion is the wrong
one any potion you
need no no no it's it's different
M so so so you need to take the
bottle no taking out the Redstone filled
it with the ne W yeah and then you need
to the munde potion first and you need
to fill it with the water
bottle okay it should be correct right
now
yeah
this this is not
savable I guess I can drink it and it's
empty awkward potions
okay yeah this one is correct this one
is correct okay and then after this you
put a red
stone to increase the time okay the
duration make red okay this one is 3
minutes one right I put it in I put it
in
yeah do you need
the yeah you need the Redstone D you
make a red
stone uh no you you mine it but I can
just give you um there's there's there
50 Redstone Dust
above okay than you nice you can take it
yay
GG take it take uh uh not do I make red
stone with this and then we
can do I do I make red stone with the
dust no no you just need the dust I just
need the Dust
[Music]
put it there we need one more
here wait you you you click the this one
this
thing thank you thewing
stand brewing stand what do I do with
the Brewing brewing stand and then hold
on okay oh okay okay and
you need to put
the wait I'll
I'll M first wasn't it warts wart wart
the nether no no no not that one I I I
oh no no no hold on no that one that one
oh the wart oh the W the W first is this
is this automatic okay okay I put it in
there personally oh okay okay wait also
put it in there
it's not
automatic no is this Magma Cream yours
yeah I put it there I I took the magma I
took the Magma Cream didn't we already
wait it's a water bottle now wait I took
the MMA W First Ward first and then the
cream and then
Redstone work first okay wait now work
okay MMA and
then red stone red stone red stone and
then red stone dust yeah the last one
I'm out of redstone you got to put it in
there okay the me Redstone Dust yeah and
then after this is the product you can
just take it
[Music]
yeah oh do we have to make it on your
own or you can just have a
potion there's so many potions
Now is it going to be automatically you
need like a button to send the signal to
the droppers
not much yeah but I gave him my NE ws
and I gave him my Blaze Rod
so I contributed yeah then I can now add
another
achievement let's
go
M let me make some space
[Music]
keyboard
thank
okay now I need to figure out
the way she appears
[Music]
Ana yes you did you write your diary
yesterday um yes I did uh what exactly
am I supposed to write just what I
did um anything right whatever like
anything anything you experience just
make it as kiaha Journal like K's diary
anything but it's unlike this Mission
book so it's not like I need to write
exactly all the missions I did and stuff
it's no the the the mission you just
need to put to write on this this book
not in on your diary okay diary is the
personal thing and do you know where I
get the diary is it just uh over there
right here no no it's not it's
[Music]
here yay
W and then after you write later you put
it here okay and then
tomorrow
tomorrow after the peora
news you peora going to uh put it
here ah into the locker yeah your locker
okay I'mma write something then
okay let's write in my house
so yeah I think she took longer but
maybe she's been done for a while we
just haven't heard about
it okay damn yeah I did a lot sheesh
today was so so
eventful day one
[Music]
uhai needs to read it so I have to write
it in
Japanese I'm writing the
date today is my day one my personal day
one day
one
and ah the Frog thing though man forget
the Frog thing we did so many other
things h
yeah
[Music]
okay my life in hardcore my hardcore
life starting today is what I wrote
[Music]
where's where's my writing what the
ohuh ohuh
H how do I
write broke it do I have to switch page
already page one is title
page can I not write more on this
one oh I was like who who wrote it this
before but it's an
example ah
okay ah
[Music]
then
no your
word 20
why we also think
about can I delete this
yeah uh Phoenix
story
okay ah
[Music]
or
no
diamond
[Music]
no okay I wrote I'm I I thought I
wouldn't Uh Oh I thought I wouldn't
perform well because I'm late
but uh only prepared
Diamond uh armor for me so I started off
really
strong now I'm going to
write
and after that
I uh I thought the smartest thing to do
is to go to Kyla and get some starting
help from her too
so I gathered
materials
for uh and help for a bow and already
made and super strong
[Music]
bow yeah something like that going to
write the whole story no I think I
should write it like shortened because
otherwise I'm wasting P's
time sleep
I can already eat dinner after this it's
8:00 p.m. almost what the but
tomorrow I think tomorrow is the the
stream that I'm going to start later
right at 5:00 p.m. my
time I I actually wanted to write some
more before this part so that's why I
was writing here so
no CL
[Music]
sucks
it
okay someone's burning
sounds like Golem throwing up honestly
if the gas sound is the Creator's cat
honestly that just to me sounded like it
could also be a cat throwing up
[Music]
uh the Pillager event what was that
again in
Japanese Pillager
[Music]
okay uh I
okay so I wrote after the after digging
for a while not finding anything really
I participated in the event and I was
able to fight hand in hand with suici
stand by a little bit and I realized oh
I'm
actually pretty
uh no I'm actually not alone and I I I
might be having fun right now also
should I write the thing about subai
leading that's going to be a lot it's
it's a bit too much to write about
leading sub Senpai to the uh stuff I
don't think it's necessary I
guess
sonato sonato okay how do I write
about um
[Music]
Senai
Al
uh who else was with us in that that
first
group what the
just for a bit I mean like in the
never oh yeah well she yeah she
separated like halfway through Aqua
Senai yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah the
old Squad Squad
true
[Music]
you here here here here here here
Senai Senai oh there's a different CI
for that that keeps on popping up S
[Music]
go and she's dead forever she's not
coming back okay so I we we really
nervously and acly went into The Nether
and uh I think we cleared pretty much
probably all of the missions but Subaru
senar died I'm so sad
is this too
[Music]
long is everybody writing this long
stuff but I've did so much man
now I'm writing after we came back uh me
and me Ana and mikai we still didn't
realize we still didn't kill the G and
we wanted to go back after like leaving
everybody
behind and so we decided to go back
again but uh we happened to
again uh form a big
group
mik uh
[Music]
uh
Shin I think shinin newcomer as a new to
the
group but K is also new to the group but
she's God and then Coan I feel like I I
might put it put her as newcomer too but
not really M also
[Music]
right that's that was our
group yeah
Drama Oh yeah guys what what you are you
guys worried about how long I streamed
I'm fine I remember recently I did like
Yakuza Natalie really long actually I
feel really
comfortable I'm fine okay so I wrote the
group people I wrote leader mikoi and as
I said while we were digging it felt
like me and Ana were Miko's assistants
because we also came from the previous
group and we were like already
close-knit and then the god Kyla who
saved us in many ways and then uh the
newcomers new group members and kind of
like especially hat and Canada they they
acted uh like they um were very
[Music]
like naive towards the
never yeah kind was looking at
everything like whoa oh
wow
yeah
okay
RP uh
uh H I still don't know
Fortress you
[Music]
one Japanese bro is saying the Fortress
Is Your
Side well then what was the Bastion
because I think we were thinking when we
saw the Bastion we took that picture as
a
proof that that was the
Bastion I'll just write then
okay I wrote we found this time in the
ne we actually found the Fortress I
guess red
yosai basan is Ian
[Music]
isi but is it is that what the word they
use within Minecraft
though yeah they are similar I built
them the same way I am a poet after
all T to
oh too
similar oh okay
[Music]
okay oh okay the first one was to not
yosai but everybody was saying oh we saw
the yosai in the beginning right like
what oh well okay so I what we we uh
killed many blazes we met many magmas or
lavas lava spots and I killed many
skeletons I was very active
[Music]
ch
how do I write that the wait I think I
know
the small and no
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay I will uh everybody who I like uh
worked with today I felt like we got a
lot closer and I have so much gratitude
and and emotion in me I I had a lot of
fun yeah
[Music]
hopefully my Japanese is improving again
too do we sleep it's night time should I
sleep
oo now never for real like in the
first hours first two hours or
so like okay I was digging and I was
alone I don't mean that time like even
when I was around people sometimes I
felt like I I don't know if I can in um
like make myself part of that I don't
know how to include or merge myself into
that how to
how but
then it it became better and better I
just yeah you know I felt a little bit
bad because I didn't want to cancel on
Kyla because I told her oh yeah I'll
let's go together because I just thought
that was safest option but
then then I just joined the Ana
Group which
was good choice good
choice I didn't know if I would be
welcome but I just forced myself into
it and it worked yeah
yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh where did they go weren't they
just ah they're still making potions
oh weren't there more people just
now oh well oh someone's
there who is that
I'm
[Music]
curious feel like I saw like a bunch
more people there okay they went to
pora's
farm for food ah yeah I think I used a
lot of food today as well
[Music]
oh how many pages oh one two three four
five so
[Music]
okay
okay I wrote too
much I want to read it
read
it said I can read
it Miki also had her first day
today it was also our first day I
thought it
wasn't a talking about getting
[Music]
bald
oh talking about the depths being gone
for sub Senpai cuz I guess sub
Senpai no I think it's the other way
around not
sure she's riding so so much like a like
a
offer like a proper offer damn she she
only how can she write it in threeee
pages I was not able to do
that damn how did she do it I wrote
right to detailed
so I want too
much I want too
much it's okay I guess does p Senai
really read all of this today there were
like so many people who joined for the
first
time a lot of death
todaya had more than 10 p Pages sheesh
should we read ena's I'm curious you
guys probably were watching her stream
too so you guys probably know what she
wrote 14 pages for one day but she's she
was writing like English and Japanese
right so it takes more
pages
wait okay
is this it
no
okay you know of the wat
Tower
yeah but her Japanese uh sentences are a
bit
shorter oh yeah the
raid
uh with my gear blessed and enhanced by
the goddess of Minecraft I finished
preparations for the battle of the
underworld oh remember great party
members who joined me on my Quest we oh
there she mentions me in
Japanese we tried a long dangerous paths
to venture into the
underworld not
all however on our MCH back to our
hometown the bravest hero super of the
sun fell upon the hands of the enemy
into the Lake of Fire
no we have returned to safety but at
what
cost I swear upon my tuyyo bow hey
mine's tuyyo too I called mine tuyoo as
well
that I will go back to avenge her death
one day until then sleep well
hero
nice we both have too too
bow all
right all right then
shees
she what a long day I don't know
tomorrow I'm starting like pretty late I
might be missing out on some fun things
that everybody's
doing but I just thought because Ena
wasn't playing wasn't going to be
playing supposedly according to her
schedule that I I'll just start later
and I think I think I'll I'll need I'll
need that tomorrow because when I woke
up today I was
[Music]
like I just want to not stream today
just because I I didn't I already felt
like exhausted cuz Monday
the day off I was constantly recording
motion and stuff didn't really feel like
a day
off so tomorrow we start later I mean
maybe
maybe depends I think when I wake up
I'll see what's happening what's the
challenge of the day Etc I'll see what
everybody's up to if I feel like I might
even be able to miss the Day Without
Regrets then I might can't cancel the
stream but otherwise if I feel like oh
there's a lot of exciting stuff going on
I have to be there then I'll
stream I'll be
flexible what do you mean I'm recording
one of my fans
oh
ah yeah yeah yeah yeah hey I got this
this potion for the Ender Fred let's go
I have to clean up this too and oh
I could make
a oh
it seems like I bought an extra Fortune
free
book
oops okay maybe I can put Fortune free
and silk touch on one pickaxe
too and bending I
suppose just same pickaxe but instead of
efficiency silk axe a silk touch if we
need it I don't even know if we need
it gift to fauna yeah yeah I don't know
is she going to play today does she have
a stream reservation up cuz like she
might be alone unless maybe Kyla is
going to still be online but she has to
sleep at some
[Music]
point uh fortune and Sil clut are not
allowed oh man okay that's fine I was
just hoping to still use it but if I
can't then it's
okay
[Music]
M well well well
so yeah tomorrow late start but possibly
also no
start depends on how things are looking
I don't want to miss out on you know
like an experience like today bonding
but I think today was a very special day
because the never opening is just super
special on its own oh
[Music]
yah she sounded like she's really tired
is she
streaming me and my
little 4 square meter
Hut IED stream a while so she was like
in like tired off stream mode
probably yeah okay yeah I'm going to go
think about what to do about food now
cuz it's already dinner time pretty much
H yeah I made lots of memories I didn't
die although one time I got kind of
close to it when I had the curse on me I
was really scared I didn't want to no I
didn't want to
die having to
get seven diamonds in 30 minutes in a
Solo World on my own sounds like
hell damn
but it's okay it seems like even if I
die at least once I'll surely be able to
revive um through the court well I don't
understand like haa was it also her
second time to die because why was she
given the challenge I understand why COI
was given the challenge because although
COI wait COI died once or twice
now did she not I don't I'm not sure is
the court never going to happen again or
is the court only the first time or they
changed the rules
again no more court or what only going
to solo world to get seven diamonds
now court is over I wonder if they left
a message in the chat about that let me
[Music]
see oh oh they posted proof about the
uh
Diamond
challenges okay but
nothing about court not happening
anymore Court was fun though today I
didn't even mention Court in the in the
uh diary she announced it in her stream
oh okay
the only except exception was n she died
three times also normally three times is
not okay only two deaths but Suba had
two deaths so on the on the second death
it's over you're only allowed to die
once
then they all went so easy Ona how they
were so harsh to no but for real like
from what they said Aqua Senpai was like
trying to burn a lot of
people which of course is all jokes and
you know fun but she had more reason to
be
objected okay guys I'll leave it at that
we had a long stream 9 hours I swear
like I feel really comfortable if it
wasn't for being kind of hungry not even
that much actually not so
bad it didn't feel like 9 hours that's
for sure for
me yeah so maybe I'll see you tomorrow
maybe not I'll try though if I feel fine
you know if I feel motivated going to
read super no it's so late it's like 8
800 p.m. I need to do something about
[Music]
food yeah damn damn crazy crazy crazy
crazy crazy crazy I had fun though
[Music]
yeah I'm I'm glad I participated I was
so nervous though so
[Music]
nerve-wracking
maybe if there's some time where there's
no like events and whatever going on
maybe I can build a better house but in
the end I mean the on the on the first
or second second day I think they had a
challenge where maybe you guys saw the
the nicest house gets like 10 diamonds
or so so everybody was trying hard to
build a nice house but now that the
challenge is not happening anymore
obviously it only happens once it's not
really any point in making a nice place
maybe a bit more spacious so that I can
put more uh
chests but it doesn't have to look nice
and it doesn't have to be much prettier
than this at
all yeah if I was like active on that
day I would have really tried to make
something cool
[Music]
to yeah L can yeah Lou no not simp L
also died right so I wonder if she's
coming
back sah Vibes in for days
exactly I don't know though if the last
day is Sunday or Monday because they
said one
week and it started on a Monday I
think so I'm not sure what is the actual
last day but I think with everyone's
power together it will be
easy although we didn't get uh any
wither heads right damn got to go back
to collect wither hats because killing
the Wither is also a goal
H oh yeah R was only playing today I I
was a one time only thing all right all
right then yeah then it doesn't
matter yeah super Senpai has a great
Dynamic with everybody and she's very
energetic so it is pretty sad in terms
of like
streaming and interaction and content
and entertainment that she's
gone damn shees Maybe she'll come back
as a
ghost maybe on the last
day yeah that's hardcore I mean if we
could all always revive then there's no
no
point
okay
W and in German we
say I had fun thank you for coming
I'll decide when I wake up if I do it or
not as I told you and then the rest of
the week is also
Minecraft more Minecraft more Minecraft
I'm going to go stronger get stronger
and
stronger thank you for uh chilling with
me hanging out with me I tried to
translate our conversations uh that we
had you know I think well one thing that
was good about the second
group I think but generally like Ana
being there I think prompted us to speak
a little bit more English because me and
Ana speaking English like to each other
obviously but then KY being there who
obviously don't who doesn't understand
Japanese prompted us to speak more
English too so I think that was good for
you guys it's good to have
a few more non-japanese speaking people
in the group so that it doesn't turn
into a completely Japanese speaking
group you know what I
mean I do it for you guys I do it for
you yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah good yeah I
think it was good balance very good
balance anyway I said a in so I got to
go otherwise I'm going to be going to be
pictured as a liar ah bye-bye
[Music]
also big a to if there's any na people
who stayed through the whole stream you
crazy people why did you do it
why
why any oh 6 hours that's also crazy
thank you because yes did you actually
5:00 a.m. to 2:00 p.m. oh my God please
go to sleep let's all go to sleep
[Music]
bye-bye oh but first I got to eat