foreign
[Applause]
this is
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
please
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
ah
Kiki
wait
forgot
hello hello
I wonder
and change window size oh
you see that
[Music]
konichiwa
hello I'm wearing my glasses
because today I need to be smart
[Music]
um
I don't think it will help
cause I saw a little bit of gura why is
my mouth always just like d Big D what
why ah
why why
[Music]
okay sometimes it pisses me off
ah hello every word I say it looks like
this yeah
[Music]
okay
uh funky funky mood today
Funky Monkey
ah
turned off canceling
uh
huh
there's a weird sound yeah it's my my
fan behind me
because it's weirdly hot in my room
it's a it's a fan
gonna die from a heat overheating
if I don't have it on you won't hear it
much once the bgm is on okay okay
[Music]
oh my God OBS I can't believe you accept
webp images I don't think it did that
before
did it get updated so now it accepts web
peace because everything you save on the
internet now comes out as a web P most
of the time
amazing
Dot webp
yeah yeah when I save something on
from Google nowadays often it just comes
out as a web p
and then I couldn't use it on OBS most
of the time on Photoshop it worked
though
um
okay
it's a new format from Google [\h__\h]
Google why why make things worse when
they are working huh
why
we will never know
Rush okay
uh it saves bandwidth
as if they don't have enough money to
get a good amount of bandwidth
or is it is it our bandwidth that they
want to save I don't know
[Laughter]
maybe it's our money our bandwidth
um is there both ah
as a web as a website designer I depend
on webp sorry okay
okay I forgive I accept my destiny
ah I guess it's all right I mean if it's
you then okay
especially you
my chat is weird let me
let me get
let me get it not from YouTube Studio
but get it from
the normal one hi kiwawa
wait let me
how are you
our how are you oh thank you I'm good uh
and how are you and how are you uh uh
yeah I don't know I had a good nap after
that stream that was early in the
morning
um in the morning
um good dreams and but this movie was
annoying good dreams and but this movie
was annoying right yes movie's such a
little [\h__\h] right right yes moving such
a little [\h__\h] right
so true sis so true so true sis so true
she gets it
[Music]
okay
I am crazy
December December while coming back
everything
[Music]
my ears what about my ears
you always worry about your own ears
what about my ears
this oh this interface looks like
I think the Wario game interface is what
it reminds me of
so let's start Hajime
[Music]
looks like Mario wet right right it
looks like WarioWare right yeah why do
you know
everything must be quiet so that I can
focus
[Music]
I haven't done two streams in one day in
a while guys
old old school Chihuahua is back no more
Grand monkey Wawa who cannot take two
streams in one day
this is this is old Wawa which is the
new Wawa no old Wawa doesn't mean that
she is the old the new Wawa is the old
guava basically but the old Wawa is the
the the Vino the old new wow the fresher
wow what the older Wawa is actually the
the you know
it's older than the old lava but
shut up
uh oh by the way if you haven't seen
this stream
uh earlier in the day here
did you do you remember when watching
the collab at some point we were like oh
hello Tony dance hello dance
we were hinting at the title in some way
um but we are releasing our first ever
original song uh I just want to say this
again I'll say it again at the end of
the stream because I'm [\h__\h] proud
because this is my my doing basically by
pushing this group endlessly uh since
the beginning creating this group and I
want to say a big thanks to Ian
management especially for helping me
push this project
[Music]
um that's why it's on the whole live
English Channel it's going to be on the
whole loving this channel yeah thank you
thank you Ian management for believing
in May and Horror Story I'm excited uh
the also the the shorts that is coming I
don't even remember what we did for the
holograph
I don't remember but the relay the
YouTube relay dance short that was an
idea that I I always wanted to do like
alone I can't really do a dancer like
you know those I I
when when it comes to K-pop you know
K-pop groups they like to do dance
relays when they have a new song they
stand in like one line and then they
dance a little bit and then they switch
they go back to the back and then the
person behind them continues the dance
and so on
um but like even then it's kind of
coordinated they have like you know some
probably choreographers who help them
make it even more interesting even when
it's just one line of people but anyway
I kept on watching those and I always
wanted to do it myself but if I bring
out Solo Songs then obviously I can't
really do it that much because I mean
I'm just one person but for holotori
like I I suggested to uh en management
that maybe we can do this uh you know in
the free time in the studio if we have
some free time and
um yeah I I wanted to do this and I
forced everybody to do it
please
um and and first first everybody was
like yeah what the what what and then at
the end I think everybody had fun
um and was quite delighted
[Music]
uh so
um I'm I'm excited so please check out
the music video that is coming out
um and just so you know in the the
credits I guess it already says so so I
can say it but remember that holotori
uh
opening that I also showed in the
beginning of the collab that I also
showed several times before when we did
hola Tony collaborations yeah ilios made
that cheeky Breaky
that was so funny that you know people
really liked and so for the music video
of Whole30 dance
we got Alias on board uh yeah the azoken
op parody I don't know I don't even know
that but you know yeah
so we got Elios on board so you know
it's gonna be fun animations
um
really cute it's a really cute MV it's
their birthday today
what what a [\h__\h] coincidence
what the [\h__\h]
what
it's your birthday
[\h__\h]
what a coincidence
you're welcome
happy birthday you're welcome for giving
you a birthday present
AKA we gave you work congratulations
we we gladly make you work yourself to
the Bone
for a great music video
yeah no that's so cool man I think you
know
um it was a great choice to go with Laos
because uh yeah it's like we have this
you know history right with politolian
Elios creating that uh legendary
video mm-hmm
so I didn't drink Red Bull no I still
didn't touch those red bulls that I
bought a while ago
and maybe I should have but maybe I
shouldn't have and so I didn't um but
yeah anyway so Holiday Dance is the name
of the song and it's gonna be out on
streaming services and it's gonna be
with the music video on YouTube and you
have to watch it and you have to support
it because because because
I I I I I'm actually really happy that
management is supporting this because
then I don't have to pay for it yeah
yeah
and and we can put lots of resources
into it uh so this is a good thing a
really good thing
yeah and the fact that en management is
mostly in charge of this is also you
know good thing because I can I can
communicate well and I feel like they
they have a similar sense of uh what we
want you know mm-hmm
yeah yeah
but obviously stuff like this is a
reason why we can't just suddenly accept
another auditory member and thus nerissa
will stay an intern
for now for now mm-hmm
and yeah I I agree it's like a little
bit announced too early because it's
like four days but uh as you know we
were literally incapable of finding any
other day and any other time where this
could have worked and even then we were
time pressured
by Louis not Senpai having something
coming up afterwards
[Music]
we're like you know we work so well in
in terms of personalities and all that
but we we don't work well at all in
terms of time schedules [\h__\h]
I'm actually like it's actually quite
lucky that movie is in Japan right now
because at least then we had no n a
time zone to deal with yeah
and now we can wait four days
I I really don't remember what the [\h__\h]
did I record for it's been a long time
all of these things have been done a
while ago I've this has been in the
works for a while
[Music]
um
so yeah
I'm so glad I wanted to exists because I
love every member of it yay
yeah International Group is difficult
but it's worth worth a try
um was so fun right I know
I know
did you record it in Japan yes I mean
not the song the song I recorded at home
sometime but the relay the dance were
like um
yes yes yes yes yes yes
it's ready to show us bird bread
okay
en Tori subdivision
well maybe in the future I don't know
but for now she's in my intern okay so
that's what it is
that's what it is okay what is this we
have ad games that you keep on seeing
everywhere and that you hate to see
games that look like why would anyone
buy and play this so thankfully somebody
made it into a package
remade the game
um so that hopefully this person won't
get in copyright trouble
but it's called yeah you want those
games right so here you go now let's try
to clear them uh is that what it says
let's see you clear them and I think
maybe it's made by the Japanese person
because the title alone gives me
Japanese light double uh Vibes and humor
of Japanese people
yeah uh
I can't believe the games weren't real
yeah what do you mean I've seen this one
before 100 I've seen this one before but
you know they're like remade obviously
uh some of these I haven't seen I think
but the this one definitely this one
definitely
what do you mean the ads are fake
[Music]
what are they what are they advertising
but I never click on it obviously
because why the [\h__\h] would I click on it
so I don't know
viruses
the games are real but the ads are fake
what
false gameplay
[Music]
so the actual game doesn't look like
this
[Music]
there are nothing like the ads
oh what
he adds don't actually represents game
[Music]
I didn't know that like how do you guys
know that did you click on it you idiot
idiot why would you click on it why
would you even be interested in this
just ignore it why are you not ignoring
it why did you click it if you guys
click on it
why would you look at it they look fun
[Music]
like this what
well that's a interesting start
what about it huh
says the One streaming it well because
this is a fun compilation that makes fun
of those stupid games kind of and makes
them better maybe
it was super obvious and dramatic no
it's but the visuals it didn't even look
excellent game
okay what should we start with
um some of these are very math heavy I'm
scared of them I I don't know let's
let's start with this one this looks
looks easy oh YouTube YouTube hates me
these days
gameplay shown is so bad that makes you
blah blah blah blah
the gameplay shown is so bad that makes
you try to do it to the the right way
but at the end the actual gameplay is
nothing like that
there's some weird signature where the
company that makes the ads do not care
about the game they just want the clicks
[Music]
usually been like this for multiple
people okay at least if it's not just me
let's try this
why is there so many
I saw like a little snippet of goodest
stream do they have 50 missions for
every single of these games
I know
we don't need so many
okay what do you want me to fill up
bread with red okay wow sugoi
oh I know it will get more difficult but
this is this really what you're making
me start with
uh we'll only move to other tubes when
the colors match
that was tricky free stuff oh I get
coins for this what do I do with the
coins
gotcha unlocked in the gotcha not gotcha
is it maybe a typo
okay wow I'm a scientist now
I didn't want to read that because I
don't need to
because I'm assuming it was just easy
information stick on be careful ones and
you can't move a color when the tube is
full
make sure not to spill anything or
you're fired
what do you mean I can't move it when
it's full these are full
well I have to I have to move them
okay
easy
see I'm moving them though
or do they mean don't add anything onto
another already full
Cube that's probably what they mean
ass baby okay okay nice good so far good
good good good good now bring on the
more challenging ones i i q free
[Laughter]
yeah bye don't fail don't fail Lala
uh-huh
no this is still fine
is this really accurate though in terms
of IQ
is this representative of the IQ no ah
damn it I would have liked in the Q test
like this
um
yeah are you proud of me guys right now
I'm proud of me look at that
look at how fast I solved this
yeah
genius
mm-hmm
no tricky yeah
we'll have to do some Maneuvers here
ah
Aya look at me look at me solving this
like a genius whoa whoa okay
okay no I don't want hot pets I hate
head pets no thank you
Gene look at me guys
why only two stars [\h__\h] you
I would say we started with this
and then maybe we could put one color
to the side for now huh what
huh why can't I put it in there
um
it's not too much I only want the blue
stuff to go in there
and I just want to put it on the side
okay it has to match
hmm well it has so much to color that is
at the very top what
ah you can only follow the same
[Music]
I didn't hit my limit run up
start with something else then
the game already know that I've failed
what let me let me return it then
does this also make me fail
no oh wait then I think I'm on the right
track now yeah okay look look look I
just I just needed a moment okay see I'm
fine I'm fine
I'm fine
easy easy freestides please
yeah see there you go still got three
stars
look that is not brute forced
mods Ben Ben
okay I think I'll go here and then here
and then here and then here
and then here oh look I'm doing it I'm
doing it you can't call me stupid look
how I did that smooth
seamlessly
um yeah plus one IQ
all right all right all right
I will start with red because I see two
Reds at the top then I will mix this
over here on the blue on the blue and
the green on the back on the green and
then the red on the garage see
you little shit's making fun of me at
any possible chance you get
but now you're believing in me again
aren't you aren't you and level 10 speed
run
I would say red and then blue and then
we have an empty one that should work
and then we add the green on here and
the blue one here and the red on here
this red on here and of course finishing
the green sit
no problem for me
though I don't think you guys can even
catch up with what I'm doing right it's
too fast it's all happening too fast for
you guys
it's okay maybe watch My Stream in slow
motion you can you can turn down the the
stream speed so that you can actually
understand what's happening with this
big brain that is exploding literally
yeah oh interesting
oh I mean how about we just make use of
this make that the blue one
move the green over here
apparently that simple
you can learn from me
learn from Wawa freestyles let's go
let's go okay
okay
I might do the same thing again maybe
um blue here blue here and then red it
will be the second one
finishing the red one
and then the green onto the green add
the blue one to the blue I got it down
yeah
what's that
somebody doubt me here you you have me
at 0.25 speed you can't keep up oh no
oh
I know what will help you wear glasses
like me
wear glasses it should easily help you
with your problems
this is fun so far
but I think I'm running into a problem
right now
um it's okay we just have to
change things up a little this is
it works it works
German always works
Works never doubted you not in for years
thank you
the trick you're in a more satisfying
yeah yeah
I oh a new car
this is nothing for color blind people
no no no no no hey hey hey hey uh
uh okay no no no issue no issue I
understand we first get rid of the Reds
then we fill up the yellow then we fill
up the green
then moment
hair yeah momentarily we do this
and then we bring the blue over here
what part of my brain am I using right
now guys what what thinking what what
kind of thinking am I using for this
all of it
um we have green green
as the majority so I would say
that we filled the the LA the yeah that
one with green first then we can finish
the red one already we can bring all the
blue over here wow wow
how how did I even
manage to fail School a few times how
how
maybe I was too smart for them I
thinking was just next level for them
probably what is this it this is like
way easier than the other things I've
done so far
this is easier than before
this was easier than the others
if they were teaching this at school
yeah then I would have had no issues
school too stupid for me exactly
yellow okay I see I see we fill up the
yellow first then we bring over the blue
I I I know what I'm doing I know what
I'm doing we can just get rid of all the
blue here just dump it
then we can get rid of the yellow I I
didn't just
almost messed it up there no no
I know what I'm doing I know what I'm
doing
yeah this is PhD level chemistry I have
a friend who's uh you know very very
good with chemistry so
I I you know you just kind of
kind of uh
here you know some just catch you just
catch a few things you know when you
when you communicate with each other
yeah yeah just you just naturally pick
it up you know easy
foreign
no I mean I mean an actual real person
what who is this who is that person and
you guys are mentioning I don't even
know them I'm too smart for them this
might be a mistake
oh [\h__\h] yeah
uh yeah it must be blue I think it must
be blue because blue is the majority
that was at the top it's just my I think
that's uh that's generally uh
a thing
[Music]
yeah
smart me whatever you see as the
majority
filling up the containers you should
probably get rid of first um
you know what I mean
what
beep ah Breaking Bad ah is this another
I really need to watch Breaking Bad If
you oh see my majority green
if if you guys keep on making Breaking
Bad references I need to watch Breaking
Bad
breaking
bad
breaking things is bad don't break
things
so Elon just break Twitter
[Music]
have you not learned he must have also
not watched Breaking Bad
[Music]
free stuff
okay we we cleared can we clear them all
I'm not sure but we cleared two rows on
already
oh okay
foreign
[Music]
I'll just empty the green one
flip over the Reds
this is actually fun
bring the blue bring the green this is
actually fun
[Music]
I'm enjoying this
satisfying I mean I don't know if I
would want to like download this and
play it on the phone because games like
this would always have a million ads on
the phone and it's just kind of lame
like I don't like phone games in general
anyway like when I'm outside and I need
to kill time I just endlessly scroll
down my social media and I'm happy with
that
that's all I need
this will be the blue one yellow is
finished
green
play it offline so there is no ad
well that still show up don't they
endless scroll and the endless endless
refreshing
yeah Doom scroller that's me but as I
said like yesterday or so it's my it's
literally my job so I have a good excuse
for it don't die
I think so
um
I'm gonna try
bringing the yellow here
oh wait and the blue will be there
yellow finishes over here green goes
here
yellow goes here green goes here easy
this is fun
gotta keep up with the pace of the
social stuff mm-hmm
helps to keep up on date what's going on
too yeah and you know what I found out
keeping up to date
you know when you I think that maybe
this is only for smartphones when but
when you go to the left
like oh it's like next to your main page
to the left there's like like Google
news or whatever
and somehow it's reading my mind and
always keep showing me stuff that is
relatively interesting to me
and I saw I saw huh you know what I saw
I saw
just the thing that I was asking
yesterday is is this new information why
did nobody tell me yesterday
um because I was asking about new season
of uh Wheel of Time
and apparently Wheel of Time new season
is finally coming out on the 1st of
September
yeah obviously my phone is listening to
me I know I know it's [\h__\h] scary but
yeah we love Time new season finally
[Music]
it's about time they actually from what
I read the original plan for it to come
out was way way way
earlier than that months earlier
but they got delayed quite a bit
um
I mean I like the scariest scary City
that eats people ah you mean that I
think I know what you mean yeah
that city was indeed scary it reminded
me a little bit of
I think something in The Hobbit also I'm
not sure I might be imagining things but
why wasn't that canceled why because the
show wasn't good I mean yeah I've I've
heard from book readers it's not so good
and honestly even watching it without
knowing the book
I can see why some things are you know
questionable but it's still you know
better than watching some other trash so
it reminded me of Cali Titi RPG the mind
that eats people oh
it's made but I rather have a Mitchell
then exactly that's my fault exactly oh
new color
rabba have a mid-show doesn't no show at
all
foreign
can I just warn everybody
I want everybody to be warned to never
try
this one certain thing in their whole
life I just want to make sure because
maybe there's some young people
in in the chat I honestly don't think
anyone would really attempt this but you
never know some people have apparently
some people apparently do attempt this
so I want to I want to make sure
that you guys are safe
please never attempt
to become a stowaway in an airplane okay
I've watched a video about stowaways
people actually attempted
and pretty much like 80 of them die
or 90 and even the ones that do survive
end up with long lasting
um problems
because you are almost certain to to get
like hypo what's it called hypo
something something
yeah because when people try uh yeah
they even get crushed by the wheels
because the the place that you can
apparently hypothermia the one place
that you can maybe get into is the part
where the wheels go in and the however
that space is like made to really mostly
only fit the wheels
yeah it's not really built for you to be
in there but that's pretty much the only
space that you will be able of getting
into
and then and then you have to you know
be able to yeah
fall out for example one day in the air
after however many hours uh bring out
the wheels again yeah also the the cabin
is pressurized but the wheel part isn't
so that's also a huge problem anyway so
it's just not a good idea so please
nobody do it
nobody ever attempted I I thought it I
don't know I mean honestly I would have
never tried it myself obviously but but
um in and you would think that other
people would be smart enough too but
there's actually a lot of people who
even attempted now like in these these
days
so especially young people who just
don't know how it works you know they
don't realize that there's maybe like
like it's really [\h__\h] cold and you
will die from the cold
they just don't get it
um yeah I just wanted to make sure
everybody here is uh
aware of this no don't
don't do it
laughs
[Music]
Hollow airport not secure enough yeah
usually they are but uh yeah some some
few people
make it by not even going through the
airport security of course but just like
somehow getting over the fences and all
that I guess and just jumping straight
onto the runway
um
gotta be really really lucky not to get
caught
and then not falling out at the time
when the
the wheel goes in but also not falling
out at the time when the wheel goes back
out and then in the damn it's just crazy
it's just crazy man what people do
man
[Music]
I want to visit Japan and flight to my
hero it's so expensive
hey I mean
they I will tell you they are I I've
been flying to Japan since like
how many years ago 13
years ago
and prices are definitely lower now than
they were back then even though you
would think there's inflation but simply
because there's more choice of
connections I suppose
and more choices of airlines that fly
there they compete with each other and
the flights are way way cheaper yeah
they're lower because I remember like
flying to Japan on uh it wasn't even a
direct flight on the connection flight
13 years ago it was like
over maybe thousand three hundred four
hundred euros or so I don't know and now
I can fly in on a direct flight premium
economy with that money to Japan
um but I could go cheaper if I want to
fly economy in a connected flight I can
probably find a flight for 900 I've seen
that before 900 under a thousand
um
just gotta find the right connection
Europe especially has so many
connections I don't know about like n a
but Europe has so many connections you
can just like start and whatever uh
Dusseldorf in Germany and then maybe
although this would have already had so
many direct flights but then maybe make
a stop in I don't know France or or uh
Dubai or turkey and those those
connection sites are really cheap
um
hmm might as well walk in swim to Japan
um yeah good luck with that
flight to Japan was coming up to 1 400.
hey I'm talking round trip yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
I don't know it's not that it's not that
crazy like it was really more expensive
I can tell you that
back in the day
prices have become cheaper
now what
yeah I don't know man I don't know
I am but up until then it was correct so
let me do my thinking let me put my
thinking cap on
so we're back to the same spot
apparently it's ah wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait yeah yeah no
here now we are at the same spot yeah
whoa
should I attempt it differently Maybe
let's try it differently
let me bring the yellow here but then uh
is this a certified a moment no not yet
wait wait wait wait wait wait now now I
think I got it I think I got it now
[Laughter]
but I think that was better
than before
I'm trying to recreate what I did and
then
okay
is this what where I went wrong
no not yet I think not yet because I can
bring the green here right and then but
then
um
that's this is where it's like eh
yeah okay okay okay
no okay I'll try it completely
differently then I'll do it completely
different how about
I don't like this
since since yeah
[Music]
yeah the start is important
I want to try that again though
foreign
[Music]
yeah
Yeah
well yeah
[Music]
yeah okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
I want to say that this was fine
doesn't this seem like a logical way of
doing it
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
I know I know I know I know I know I
need to I need to make one empty first
so that I can move the big amount of
blue because if that's so much
suddenly difficulty Spike what the hell
what have I not tried yet green
I don't really believe in green right
now but
I will
no this is stupid no I knew that it
wouldn't work
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
should I try blue
yeah that could work
yeah
and this goes here and this goes here
okay I was I was trying every color
besides blue
I'm not cooking I'm I'm chemistrying
hey okay I was a little bit stressed
okay but sometimes I'm allowed to get
stuck to every genius get stuck
sometimes and then comes back even
stronger
like now
I'm just gonna get rid of all the blue
first
and then I can bring the red over here
and empty that one so that will be
helpful
and we already have this going for us
see see
why when did anybody doubt me why did
anybody think that this is the end of my
genius streak
is still going
[Music]
oh see
yeah I just I don't know I was just
weirdly stuck on the other one but I'm
fine I'm fine look my EQ is now
officially 30.
yeah
bring it on baby show me what you got we
got two empty ones that is very very
nice of them
do I want to go for green or for blue I
would say blue because then I can switch
over the pink in theory
oh ah maybe a mistake no no maybe not
mistake because now I get another empty
one
I'm just gonna bring the pink over here
and bring the green over here
can we get free stars please yeah bye by
the time
[Music]
yeah but that's just a theory now it's
reality it's not a game theory
it's me just being smart for real for
real
and that again two tubes really you want
to be so gracious to me
that's just making it too easy
is it look at that look at that
beautiful
this is a good game for OCD people
they're my love Kiara's voice oh my God
thank you I rarely get told that thank
you
the number Tower yeah the number Tower I
cannot promise you to be smart at the
number Tower okay
please do not even expect anything from
me I will not pretend that I am smart
enough for number Tower okay
um I'm scared already
hey I don't I'm not looking forward to
it okay
um
okay
no worries no worries I got this
Guy dog
[Music]
it was always bring back
I can even less than half a second
[Music]
and it almost broke fauna eh
okay okay it's probably it could
probably break every single en member
not just me
hmm
okay red is finished
I'm gonna bring yellow over here so that
I can bring this one over here too
to top up the pink
uh empty the yellow bring the rest over
here make this the blue one
finish the green
and finish the pink three stars
which Ian remember do you think is the
smartest
hmm
[Music]
I mean
probably someone who stayed in school
the longest
and now we got new members and I don't
know how smart they are honestly but I
think
surprisingly Bales might be pretty smart
[Laughter]
yeah I said it's an amazing before
didn't I
uh
surprisingly
I don't know we gotta test it
we we would have to test that okay maybe
I should have started with blue oh yeah
a new color too
sorry sorry
I didn't even notice the new color
blue
we finished blue we finished green
we almost finished yellow we finished
pink okay okay
ah no problem
hesitated for a moment but it's okay
it's okay
oh three stars
[Music]
these will be cutie at Escape simulator
what does escape simulator save oh I
guess because it has riddles
I forgot it had riddles right like uh
[Music]
what kind of riddles does it have
puzzles
I never played that before I wanna play
that is that fun to watch
as a viewer
important question
oh
I suppose
what am I doing
Buddha was really good at it
no no to be honest yeah
not fun to watch
um
I think it's important to choose games
that are fun to watch Mostly
but sometimes you know I also think it
can be even if the gamer itself is not
so fun to watch as long as the streamers
are enjoying it I think it can still be
you know saved by the sheer joy of the
streamers
um
yeah and if you stream full time
for years and years then I think
sometimes you we streamers we need to
choose games that are
you know for us you know
not always for the viewer just so that
we stay sane
just something that's really uh you know
just for us to enjoy and also like I
think uh for whole life members it's
important
to play games where we can Bond and
um you know get to know each other so
sometimes we just gotta prioritize that
why did I do that
[Music]
like Mario Party
there's always fun stuff happening I
don't understand what is your problem
with Mario Party
Mario Party is fun promo party was also
really funny because there's it's
literally Mario Party with violence
I love funnel party honestly I don't
know why why why I haven't played it
more often until now this was only the
second time in three years
thanks for reminding me of its existence
[Music]
because I'm so [\h__\h] grateful that
it's um it's really Mario party for more
than four people that's that's so that
is so valuable
you don't even understand
[Music]
I've waited for that for so long and I
always had it in the in my in my steam
library and I didn't realize huh
realize it's
watching people suffer for 50 turns is
still a good time
almost died at that point body no no
no no
thank you for enjoying the violence a
bit too much no that is impossible
party streams are great right
new color again
[\h__\h]
um
okay let's start with pink because pink
is the most and I can finish up a whole
a whole
yeah
that's
ah let's go with this one
then I can finish this one
priorities
uh I I I saw that coming the moment I
touched the vessel
but I think up until then it was good
uh subscribe
[Music]
I guess let's pull it up here first
uh then we make the yellow one then we
fill up the blue one as much as we can
this dark green one
and the red one
three stars
[Music]
stay back she's thinking
[Laughter]
all right
[Music]
I think I want to make them
yellow and red
I think I regret what I just did oh my
oh
foreign
could work still
no no okay
um
this is a lot of
a lot of containers
how about
green
and then
we could put this here for now
um
mom maybe
I'll put this here
I don't know ah but it's okay
oh wait wasn't that here before yeah
ah okay okay a little bit stuck again
but it's fine
how about even though this is the
minority
I start with that one
so that I can get rid of all of this
but all the blues are at the very bottom
that was a mistake too
I mean I want to figure this out
I'm going to
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay
did I start with
pink I think so I started with pink and
red before I want to try it again
I wanna try it again
oh no wait wait can I restart I want to
try with yellow and red ah I can't
restart I think
yeah have I done this the same way
before I think so
God damn it
ah
Oh wait we're not she's not giving up
yet oh I thought she was gonna give me
an a any time now
but wait wait mother
oh
wait wait
oh yeah oh yeah oh chat YouTube
[Music]
hey
you didn't see my genius moments
are you seeing this did you see it at
the end
[Music]
I figured it out I didn't even believe
in it while I was doing it but I figured
it out anyway
okay IQ 40. you saw the end
I was like really waiting for the ear
from the lady from the scientist but she
just let me keep on cooking and she
believed in me
interestingly
okay
I would do blue first because I can
literally fill up a complete blue
and then
let me try red so that I can bring the
yellow here
and the pinks here
the Reds here
[Music]
almost full with the red
and
okay we get another empty one nice
figured it out guys I figured it out
thank you for the gesundheits
close one ah she loves me she loves me
the scientist loves me she's so happy to
have me help her at work
[Music]
all right this is literally asking me to
finish it thank you
I would then
either go for blue or yellow
or buff basically
um
[Music]
I'm not sure yet what I'm doing
okay
it's working
oh
look at this oh yeah
let's just bring the light yellow a
light green here
oh my God oh my God
see I'm so much better at this than I am
at what was the game Q
this is the kind of IQ game that I like
okay
did you say cute um on its steam page
is using my stream uh but it's it's uh
with um
is this the same color is this a
different color
is it yeah it is
uh yeah so the advertisement it's it's
it's with
um
permission they asked if they could do
that what the [\h__\h] is this
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah they of course asked
for permission
to use our streams as advertisement like
that on the steam page
of course no problemo
mother
uh
Auto auto
promote Tony
no we didn't get sponsored by kill but I
guess they liked the stream so much and
then like whole life I guess
um
have I not tried this before
[Music]
have I tried this before
have I how have I not seen that before
eh
that easy
how did I not see that before okay but
now
these two we gotta do a switcheroo
[Music]
is that gonna be possible
yeah it has to be yeah yeah
[Music]
wait which one was this
can we beat this game
and show him who is the smartest
YouTuber in the world
mirror mirror on the wall who is the
smartest of them all and why is it
takanasikiara just because
it is
who else would it be
what do you mean air
have patience lady let me cook
I know what I'm doing
100 percent
I always know what I'm doing I will do
it the same way as I just did because it
has to work
it has to work
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what's the matter with her man
what's that about her
[Music]
ah
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
ah
interest ah I think I see it
I think
if I do this and then bring see I'm
thinking ahead
because
I've got a huge head
and I have to think about it
otherwise big problemo
[Music]
no my head isn't even as big as good as
head
when we like look at our 3DS or even no
2DS also but in 3D I feel like it's even
more noticeable
when she like at the official stream for
example when she stood next to all of us
and we looked at the screen like wait
very funny looking
you look funny gouda your head
so big
[Laughter]
ah
I got it
says
she knows she's just coping she knows
that too
big head but you know
[Music]
she's surely hiding something in that
big head and she's just not telling us
one day she will reveal it and we will
all be
shook head
and we will think we knew the world but
we were so wrong about everything
our whole image of the world will change
I don't know if I'm doing this right
right now maybe not
um
I love this right now my favorite new
game Game of the Year award goes to this
game
imagine if this got like nominated for a
indie game of the year
just kidding laughs
going from tunic to this
besides Zelda I did see like a tweet or
something
that was talking about how game of the
year
next time will be really freaking
difficult to decide on because I mean I
personally didn't play most of those
that were mentioned in that post
but
wait let me think
yeah okay no problem I got it I got it
but yeah there were like really a lot of
good picks like I think it was a list of
like 10 games or so that were genuinely
really
good though
for even from like without playing it I
know they were good what's going on here
let me Focus let me Focus
here this one
yeah
okay okay I was talking let me Focus
um
Final Fantasy was also one of the games
I think and Baldur's Gate tears of the
kingdom of course
I don't remember most of them ah they
also put like Spider-Man in there I
don't really know if Spider-Man really
deserves it
what do you say guys
the Spiderman deserve came of the year
was it that good yeah no
oh yeah
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's not out yet okay then how can you
even put it on there on their list man
biased as [\h__\h]
um
I mean we are on the last row of IQ it
has to be a little bit challenging
let me do it a little bit differently
how about I bring over the pink here for
now
just gotta
gotta try things a little bit
differently sometimes but
I didn't see that
blind troll strikes again ah
[Applause]
okay I want to do that again I want to
do that again I started with pink did I
did I
did I do it like this
um I think I'm I'm not doing it the same
way I did it before man
or is it maybe it's the same way
yeah okay I think I'm back
to where I was and then I'm just not
supposed to do the blue one
I think I see why
yeah that's fine that should work
[Music]
Street Fighter 6 is definitely I think
that game was also on there maybe but
Street 26 is the okay we'll do here hmm
well I guess if you really like that
genre then
I suppose yeah
I can see why it would
choose it what's everybody's Game of the
Year take your time think about it think
about it for two minutes okay
think about it
don't get over eager I because I can't
read it right now I have to focus
sure
no eh
don't say pizza teller what Baldur's
Gate I see a lot of you already got to
play a lot of other skate huh you like
it that much yeah
armored Core wait what kind of game was
armored Core
can I redo I've been looking at the chat
I don't want to lose my timing
Resident Evil
Pizza shut up about Pizza Dallas
America
do you say Mecca or Mitchell I think
Mecca right
[Music]
I wanna redo it I already lost so much
time I don't want to make it
um
um but maybe I'll do it by accident
again
because I'm just picking random tubes
right now
uh
okay I guess I'm doing it
gotta switch these around
and then this girl's here and we'll top
up the pink one okay oh well
[Music]
song of stars that I'm really excited
for that I want to be my game of the
year a jrpg called song of stars only
two left
[Music]
[Applause]
y the superior color obviously we have
to start with it right no
Stars okay
deceived me they tried to
they tried to distract me by making me
really happy about the pink
man what's going on okay uh
hahaha
nanny
um
did I do this before
you would think so wouldn't you
yeah I think I did
[Music]
okay we have two finished ones
but apparently this is where I went from
before I think
but how else could I do it besides
putting red on red oh yeah because the
pink is too much to put on there
isn't this my only choice and then it
goes a
h no not yet okay but uh but then then
it goes yeah
I think
but I still have no way I think I've
gotten this far wait no okay wait
it's fun it might actually be fine
I feel like this is the same way I did
it before though what the hell
[Music]
all right then I'll take my win
laughs
cooking Chong why last one
oh
the final It's the final
chemistry
[Music]
I hope I started with the right one but
it feels right so far uh I don't think
I'm
I don't think I'm wrong
finish the green finish the yellow
bring the pink
[Music]
dark green
no
oh three stars wow
oh my God I finished this game I'm a
color lab expert yeah
the game called
end let's go they are so correct they
are very right good assessment
wow what can I even do with all these
coins now let me let me find out
oh okay the gotcha is the gacha is that
a mistranslation what do you get from
this
I don't know daily gotcha spin
what do you get
a title
great
I mean is that all I can use my money
for
title rankings I don't give a [\h__\h]
okay uh what game
should we try next don't say number
Tower
because I'm not gonna be good at it
uh parking lot okay I want to try that
what is this all about oh it doesn't
even have 50 levels only 25.
two all 24 or 25 already until IQ 24
okay speed it up speed it up thank you
seems like it I've proved myself enough
what is this about
getting them out of the parking lot okay
but I don't know much about
driving but I mean
this is like the game the The Thinking
game that you sometimes you know hear
about the two people get into the bus
next station one gets off or whatever
you know maybe it's like that
[Music]
something like that
how do you feel about driving on the
left side of the road honestly recently
I've been between Japan and Austria and
London and Japan and Austria so many
times that
I even stopped like noticing I should
have noticed it even stronger the
difference but
I actually didn't notice anymore like oh
now I'm in the country where they drive
on this side and now in the country
where they drive on the sun I actually
just
didn't realize it anymore at all like my
friend who was with me in London had to
point it out to me and I'm like oh yeah
right I guess like I got used to it so
much it's like so normal for me and my
brain automatically adjusts to it
wherever I am with my brain however
doesn't adjust till immediately what I
always forget is when I arrive I arrive
in Tokyo
and uh escalator
which side to stand on because in
Austria everybody just stands wherever
they want but in Tokyo they stand on a
certain side in Japan generally they
stand on a certain side but depending on
the city you're in they might stand on a
different side like Osaka and Tokyo is
opposite
and uh yeah and because I lived a while
in Osaka and I lived a while in Tokyo
whenever I come back to Tokyo it I
always end up standing on the wrong side
in the first moment and then jenma is
like kiwawa wrong side
[Music]
is
um
yeah yeah and keep on forgetting
it has a casino
okay let's see how is this game gonna
get difficult
because I don't see any problems so far
what is where's the problem
should I just go straight to a difficult
one
[\h__\h]
is it telling me to start with that one
hey wait it's telling me to start with
certain ones
how do these even I don't know parking
things how do these even get out
oh no it's just okay it's not really
telling me to do that
thank you
I mean
can we crash oh oh you can just go
straight I guess okay I don't like the
way you parked there though that's
really [\h__\h] stupid who Parks like
that
who the [\h__\h] Parks like that even I I
don't have a license I don't know which
[\h__\h] about driving and even I know
that's not how you park
or there's a person at wig you're not
allowed to
eh
[\h__\h] you get out of the way what do you
what are you doing now what's up
little [\h__\h]
yeah
get out of the way
[Music]
I am what do you call this job traffic
no parking parking spot
uh control agent what do you call it
just drive you know in a curve I guess
they can only drive straight on the
parking lot
until they are on the street okay at
least I didn't get a failure
parking attendant
[Music]
I've never actually seen someone have a
job like that before I think
it's not common here
okay
yeah no problem I think we just we can
just do the last couple ones because
otherwise I mean
[Music]
foreign
I don't like the controls here just let
me immediately drag it please
okay we can get rid of the
this bottom Lane
instantly there we go
uh what do we do about this one if it
can't do a curve
can it drive through there
oh it can okay it looks really close to
me
but there was not enough space should I
use arrow keys I'm currently just
relying on my mouse completely
[Music]
surprised that that didn't crash okay
okay okay
uh what
[Music]
how
is it okay to sometimes crash for the
sake of for example
doing this is that acceptable I guess
it's acceptable
all right okay
I thought I shouldn't
dance
but as long as it's not a failure and as
long as I don't get sued for bumping
your car this but a scratch
they were in the car door I'm surprised
they didn't complain about it obviously
they were in the car everybody's in the
car because they're all ready to drive
hey
don't
funny was already passed
uh go go go go go go
no time to lose
I need to get smarter
not Hotel
what a weird car is this a muscle car
it's a muscle car
it's a muscle car guys
it's very wide unusually wide
oh
I love this game it's so cute
you should honestly let children play
these games
I think it's good to train their uh
uh brains
collateral damage
don't you think okay what now
uh I think get rid of all of these
how often can I crash them oh [\h__\h]
that's not enough to get let the yellow
one through actually ah unless I bring
this one up first and then
and then you can go
but this one can go through
and then this one can go through too and
this one
and then this one and then this one and
then this one this is like a puzzle
[Music]
one of those puzzles where uh you have
like a square thingy with like thingies
that you move around like uh plates that
you move around to make a picture and
one is empty and you will move them
around until you have the right
the right picture yeah yeah
I understand though
Sliding Puzzle yeah
I hate I hated sliding puzzles as a kid
I hated it go go go go go
go go go
[Music]
oh
um
can you go back no
something in the way there
how about you you know
[Music]
um
I think we moved this
wait for the person
yo
it almost
here but it was forgivable they were a
little bit upset about it though okay
sorry
hmm
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
one red car
how about no
um
but it has to be
one that's facing
probably down
or up and it's not in the like in the
path of one of these cones
[Music]
oh wait this one can go
okay oh
[\h__\h] I wasn't patient enough okay okay
I'm sorry
[Music]
I'll I'll be more careful and patient
let this one go let this one go
and let this one go
this one
Zoom
do you guys also have a culture where
when you see a yellow car you hit the
person next to you
on their like upper arm with your fist
it's a stupid culture yes yay yay
there's some people what is that where
did that even come from why why did
people start that violence
this is this is where all the violence
in humanity stems from
laughs
punch buggy
I think it's just like because yellow
cars are kind of rare I guess and then
in like traffic jams people were
thinking of games to pass the time
probably
and so they thought yeah how about we
punch each other when we see a yellow
car because it's the rarest thing to see
you do it with Volkswagen bugs ah you do
it why are they also rare
is that why you do it
bad look at
those going
and I think I can let this one go
beautiful
all right
we shot
[Music]
I hate the way it moves ah the yellow
one can't get through
okay but it eventually will have to
somewhere or another
um
I think
I think I I I just realized something
like a general
a general General thing you want to
accomplish in this game
the way that they're the patent the
direction they're looking at
you want to
line them up
that way even if they're not ready to go
yet
I don't know I don't know I know
that's what my brain's telling me
let me cook
Yahoo
all right now we're cooking
and let's now we can get rid of the
yellow one here nice
um I'm gonna get rid of this one and
this one
go go go go go
go go go you can you go no
um okay but no wait oh wait
no that's just me
[Music]
all over
okay okay
I will try my best to be efficient and
Speedy
[Music]
even using my arrow keys now it's not
too hard is this because of those stupid
people walking around there like they
got nothing better to do what are they
even here for
we're just waiting to steal a car or
give me like a
a side citation what do you call it
[Music]
you could go but wait
patiently
ready
okay
um
ouch
ing citation yeah
sidewalk yeah but they're like they're
doing this on
some bullying traffic bullying
[Music]
um
wow chill music though
okay I might wanna get all of these to
the side
so we can get the yellow oh this one can
leave oh my god I didn't even pay
attention to that okay let's go
let's go okay
I don't think I was able to set that one
free before
noise
um
good for you
so proud of you
how far would this one
oh
look at him
go
oh
[Music]
mm-hmm it's cleaning up it's we're
getting somewhere oh my God this feels
like untangling Christmas lights
the most fun things about holidays
wait wait wait wait wait
what can I do
ah me uh wait I can no it's still too is
that wait I don't know we're too fat
this one might be able to go to
all right and then this one
all right and if we move this one out of
the way then we can move this one out of
the way and then we're gonna move this
one out
I'm gonna do that
here he goes and now here we gotta be
careful it's really scary
this can like mess up everything
wow
okay oh God
[Music]
oh this one go
if I mess it up again because I drive
over one of these guys I I think I I
don't want to waste my time anymore with
it
oh okay
sorry
I'm just moving it out of the way for
now
because I mean I understand it you know
and I I can solve it we we saw that
right
baby now yes okay I got another one
coming Mr John would you please quietly
thank you
okay
oh this one maybe next
once he's over that line it's safe to go
[Music]
you go bring
Pringle
mm-hmm
does this one pass through of course it
does okay
bunk sorry it's for the greater good
[Music]
nice
sorry wrong direction does this work
yeah
we're cleaning up Ohio
by the way just a reminder I know my
schedule uh says something else but
tomorrow
let me just for safety stop this car
here
tomorrow I'm not streaming unfortunately
yeah
I know what's in the schedule but Wawa
Wawa cannot stream tomorrow I'm so sorry
I have to cancel the Korean study stream
and the member stream but they will
happen next week
how am I ever gonna pass the yellow car
through here you crazy
[Music]
well that will have to go last I think
because what the [\h__\h] maybe if he's like
here then I sent the car then he should
be here by the time it arrives Maybe
this yellow car has to go through here
do you have something in mind for
members not really no not yet nothing
specific I think
because I also I don't think I can
really stop it this time like I did
before
yeah but I think I have to go with this
one now
I think I don't even have a choice okay
let's go let's go
[Music]
that was a close one buddy be careful
just because you're walking on the
sidewalk doesn't mean you can just walk
without looking around your surroundings
okay
doesn't mean you're you have a license
to be ignorant of your surroundings and
that you're you know allowed to do
anything whatever and get those all
those drivers in trouble you know
mm-hmm
yo they give you so much time for this
though huh I'm still
in terms of stars if I was a little bit
faster I could have gotten two stars
not so bad
oh there's another one of those
coins
and the timing okay when he's like here
maybe
[Music]
or earlier
now yeah it should work yeah okay
I think we got it
nice that took a long time but it's
totally manageable
please let's go let's go one star only
but I mean
do you guys want to see the last one or
should I go to a different game I think
everybody wants me to go through
different games
what is this stack your cash to get over
the obstacles okay how is that like
logical thinking
let's start at 21.
oh maybe I should have started with the
first one though what what is this what
is this how what do I do wait wait let
me let me look at the first one
so you collect money
and
that was too easy I didn't even do
anything
ah and it has to be enough money to
reach the house I guess okay
[Music]
okay but what's the catch how do I
what's what's with the obstacles
what's the catch
here it is obstacles what what
oh
no ah no no no no no no no
I if I click with my mouse it makes this
aha it makes me some stairs okay
all right and then I understand oops
Yeah Tapped Out shitty house
this looks like the house that I lived
in in Japan
at the beginning of my time
okay is that enough knowledge for me to
do this already
[Music]
okay the stairs disappear or like more
like I'm always walking so uh I gotta be
constantly making stairs
[Music]
are we still good
Alicia
what the [\h__\h] Casino what what are those
well it goes robbery I robbed the bat I
didn't even look at the writing
I'm a celebrity though and I'm [\h__\h]
Rich eh free stars what the [\h__\h]
wait easy
crime
what
what two ladies I have two ladies even
so I said that is my ideal dream life
what
what's this
crime always face is that what I'm
supposed to learn from that
how was I able to clear the oh God these
spikes look deadly
what what let me redo
wait those spikes look deadly
do I even have enough money to survive
that
I guess I do
oh
God
wow
that's cool close I ran out of money
there I was trying to save it
only like little two baby steps
it's like a rhythm game
what's good at doing good at this
because I saw she played this one too
I can't make it about that um
she had a rocky start
really maybe that means
after okay just
after a rocky start maybe I'll figure it
out too
I mean I understand it you know it's
just
quite difficult let me die I would die
once you mess it up there I think it's
already over
waste
[Music]
this is how you teach children how to
spend their money I guess in life
okay what what do you mean I was already
on there
that is rigged come on you saw it guys
right you are my witness
[\h__\h]
I missed it
don't hit walls while bridging with
money over so wait I thought it was
actual advice but you're just saying
you're just making a joke [\h__\h] hell
yeah
we are
why does why is it so painful to run
against the wall I'm not even running
I'm like walking against it it shouldn't
be that painful
we can still do it we can still do it
[Music]
what a stupid game
why
what
a stupid [\h__\h] game
I don't want to be in their
advertisement no
unless they pay me lots of money
[Music]
I run out of bunny there I guess okay
I'm the ad guy I'm Not Dead
I'm smarter than the ad guy was the ad
guy not doing well
vaccine or virus what do you mean what
the [\h__\h] why would I choose the virus
but I get money for it or what well
obviously obviously I would go for that
okay okay okay
I may not be as rich as before but
that's good enough
I lose money when I when I get the
vaccine but then I might is the chance
that I'll I'll die because is there a
random chance that I'll die from the
virus or what
still got the maidens
okay oh my God we get the option again
I'll take the vaccine
and I'll take the vaccine again
Triple Threat baby I don't need my my
third vaccine please
ah
hey what I don't understand what is that
bloodbath that's toxic what the [\h__\h]
okay enough good enough
good enough vaccines make you rich yeah
when you're on the side of the people
who make and sell the drug the vaccine
yeah oh my God look at those ladies I
even have a child and a limousine now
let's go
wait I don't want so many ladies it's
hard to take care of so many ladies
I I don't want the whole harem
let's let's rob a bank ah look at that
GTA paying off
now I go to work
not risking it again
you guys are jealous aren't you for me
having such an easy life with robbery
well well well
practice makes perfect and I had a lot
of practice on GTA
okay I respect the hustle thanks bro oh
whoa
whoa I was ready to go up to the heavens
man
can literally pay to win to get into
heaven after my life ends
wouldn't that be great if you could like
pay your way into heaven
I wonder if you can
I mean I honestly I don't really I
personally don't have like no
I personally don't really have like an
opinion about
that unless we win again
what happens like after
life
I think like uh it's interesting though
to consider
many
options for sure I'm gorgeous thank you
you too game
the Catholic Catholic Church is
interested in your idea
a bit of deep talk for this game what do
you mean high IQ means I gotta do deep
talk
you could find a way into heaven in the
Middle Ages true true I guess so yeah I
mean at least you you thought you could
all right
I'm actually pretty good and fun game
too actually parking lot is kind of lame
it's fun too if you have a lot of time
and if you're really bored
should we try this but
I don't know man
[Music]
um what
do I just have to have a higher number
than the enemy yeah
[Music]
okay
I don't know how far I'll get
I don't want to immediately go to the
last levels for this one let's let's
look at the second one maybe it explains
another you know simple mechanic 10-5
can I
just go here and then like
aha
again the five okay okay as long as
we're just using addition addition then
I I can handle it but later I will have
to use
um other things
I I hate it uh what do you call it uh
dvdn what's that in English
um dividing in a math class back in the
day I hated that so much division okay
I think we have to go step by step for
this one
so
we start maybe maybe this is what I
needed back in school days maybe a game
like this would have helped me
understand everything
[Music]
better
honestly maybe it would have
um
I learned the vision from a video game I
mean yeah
I'm sure it can help you with that
foreign
uh-huh 19.
you can already strike this one
I hope we don't get crushed by the house
noise
oh and then
well that was easy
[Music]
could we have gone straight to that that
one and we could have skipped the others
or
yeah because we got like a little bit
too strong for that you know what let me
go to 11.
okay okay
um let's go here
150s
what do you mean 150
what
did we both have 18
does that mean when you both have 18 I
die first why who decide that also Chat
is dead I guess then at least you can't
laugh about me right now
oh times two the sword gives me times
too
but wait
is it smarter to get times two after I
kill this one because then I get
from 81 times 2 instead of
41 does that come out as the same I
don't even
if I would think about it for a little
bit maybe I would know but I think this
is the smartest way to do it
Chad cannot tell me what's right and
what's wrong right now there
are you laughing stop laughing
laughing okay here you are welcome back
was it smart of me to do
the one first or does it come out the
same way
no yes yes
yay yay
it's not the same see you know I thought
so I thought so
let's skip a few again oh no division
um I gotta do this one first then
[Music]
because
um 14
would be so is it yeah yeah we're still
we're still
strong enough
simple division
Rusty sword will divide your current
numbers and make sure to get it at the
right time
okay
[Music]
oh
well this one's just 10 but I can't go
straight to him
okay interesting Chat is dead again then
I am once again on my own no
yeah I mean
yes
[Music]
can we go back to 10
yeah man doesn't really matter news Plus
10.
no I feel like the order didn't really
matter for this one
mostly
poison restaurant and other items can be
dangerous but you're just going to have
to find a way to use them okay I guess
it was just really a really
introductionary I I see the icons thanks
guys thank you thank you
thank you oh [\h__\h] oh that was by
accident why is this one so
ironically dancing
oh God
okay
Plus 10.
then we take on the 18.
and then the 32
okay
now
we hmm
times five is
350.
take care of this one then half it not
half divided by three I it will be
enough it has to be enough
it is enough
yeah it had to be enough I didn't even
have to think about it it had to be
enough logically thinking because
otherwise they wouldn't do it like that
[Music]
oh
come I always got the worst grades in
math huh how how
okay
10 plus 50.
and then the 54.
add that to my score got the 102.
welcome back now are you willing to stay
for once
or are you
do you need to go somewhere else
I think you should stay
um
[Music]
two two thousand
uh okay
should I divide early but first time let
me I think it's smart to take down one
of these oh God they're all around 300
but
I wonder if it matters like if the small
numbers matter
[Music]
hey is it good to divide early
so maybe now
okay that's still enough
okay
[Music]
and then
take the multiplication at the very end
whoa whoa and we're we're not quite
ready for the top yet but easy
I'm looking at how much it adds up to at
the end seems like I could have chosen
almost any of the enemies before first
no
or maybe not I don't I actually don't
know
but we kill
devil
the devil is himself
okay that wasn't so difficult still
I can handle that let's go to 36.
[Music]
um
13 is not an issue how about with divide
wait let's do minus six first
and then divide
to so that we get to 32.
do you guys think that was smart yeah
okay
now we can take care of this one
[Applause]
oh
thank you thank you thank you
I don't even think that far ahead
but uh it seems to have worked 170 is
what we're dealing with okay
um maybe minus 30 maybe the same way
first the minus standard divided
because we want to divide the the
smallest amount possible Right
probably
right yeah same logic okay
wow
wow not so stupid Wawa after all
oh
[Laughter]
I feel very
good with this game
I like it okay here's some big ass
numbers oh I start with 246 okay well
then obviously I gotta take this one
first
[Music]
whoa and then this one obviously I mean
just gotta build up some numbers first
and then we got 1200 and then a divided
by three divided by 2 and 838
wow
but we want to divide early on
I think
wait I could take the devil right now
even
actually
maybe I do that first because I don't
know if I'll still have enough
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay okay
I didn't look closely so I didn't
realize I had enough to catch the devil
but maybe now I should divide
so
half of two thousand
500 is like one thousand
250 right
so that's still enough
should I divide by three
okay
okay that is very close
um
and then for two
okay we have to end up with 636 at least
647 I guess
um
just these ones
yeah dissolve each other
we have times two minus five uh not mine
divided by five
but maybe I'll do this one first
and then take the poison
so that's out of the way because maybe I
wouldn't be strong enough afterwards
oh yeah I think this could work I don't
I don't really know how much it will be
but yes it's enough it's enough it's
enough and then I I
I multiply myself again
and I'm back in the game baby
oh yeah
yeah okay okay
[Music]
hey noise
hey this is no match for me I'm I'm
smarter than you guys and me fault
all right
level 45
we start with ten
[Music]
um
I kind of want to just straight up go
for him and then go for him and then
think about everything else
because I could I could
but I have to think about the later
stages too
try it
could we just see what happens
it's probably not gonna work
[Music]
it's not gonna be that easy
uh
let's do minus 12.
divided
by two
and then times ten is that okay
no rip really
can I not fix it
um
I mean it's it's
it could still work uh
we got two minus tens
ah wait if I got two minus tens and I'm
down to 100
and times fifteen
is like a good amount
more than enough no
should I multiply first or kill
everything first
is this gonna bite me in the ass now but
because so far I'm still good
or is it just really forgiving
what's this Super Chat what's this nice
man saying
but fever night has become my go-to song
at the gym
wow thank you
some levels are more forgiving than
others
I made a big mistake in not killing
first a man really
ah math is so boring I'm sorry for all
the math fans out there but math is so
boring man
and what do I do I need to still have
enough for this one afterwards
and there's
um
[Music]
do I fight first or do I take the
multiplication first well it's already
over
it might be audio
[Music]
it's already over
no wait wait
what
it might be but I don't want to give up
yet
here
[Music]
um
yeah okay
yeah I get it ah
ah clothes no
no
I failed it it's over
yeah I don't want to redry it
okay what um
what what do we do
can you go into the
okay we cannot go into the minusk
um
what did I do first was it even right
yeah I know first I did fight first uh
let's not fight first let's multiply
first
ah [\h__\h] maybe I should have
taken the poison first
before multiplying
well yeah no
I see you
there
restart
don't say that
it shouldn't already mess it up in the
beginning
there should still be a chance for me to
fix it
um
[Music]
um I don't wanna I can't I I don't want
to look at this my brain is like Zone
phasing out zoning out everything I
can't see the numbers I I can't let me
out I wanna I Wanna Get Out kill me
kill me I don't want to do this I don't
want to do this I don't know this I
don't like it it's traumatizing
I don't wanna I don't wanna let's just
look at the final one
maybe I can
get it through sheer luck what do you
think
[Music]
I think this is okay okay no
no
see I have doesn't this look so right to
have just about enough to kill this
Goblin doesn't that sound right to you
I mean why are you already have you
played it already yet
and you remember
so well because you haven't even seen
the end
how can you be sure
that is already over
it seems like we're not compatible guys
you and me I fought kfb and me I thought
we were so compatible but I think I was
wrong
it seems that you guys see things that I
don't see
let me just kill myself really quickly I
don't want this anymore I don't want to
find out that we are not compatible guys
I want to live in the ignorant Bliss
that I lived in before
yeah
kill me yeah
I want to continue thinking that we were
maybe somewhat compatible as viewers and
streamers
yeah so I can't play this game let's
play this
remove pins to clear the missions
all right how does this work
aha
as long as no math is involved I think I
have a chance
[Music]
if this treasure Stickman will find it
if you remove the pin Block in the way
be careful not to collapse from
exhaustion if the pressure is still
blocked
collapse from exhaustion
okay
you just don't don't let the rock Fall
Down rocks will break apart and
disappear they fall on things other than
pins ah Stickman can get hurt by them so
use them only to hit enemies ah but if
they if they fall on the ground
then they just break and fall apart or
oh wait there's there's a hundred of
these
oh okay then let's go make it more
difficult it is a bomb what the [\h__\h]
do the dogs eat me
do they eat each other
what happens with the dogs
eh I honestly don't know what is this
he kills the dogs
wait here's another one for you
it works okay the dynamite kills both
the dude and the dog so
[Music]
it worked
first thing forcing it learning by doing
guys learning by doing all right let's
skip ahead to Freddy free
oh is that lava
just make sure that I don't step on it
right
[Music]
oh
I think
oh I got it what do you mean wrong move
I made it in the end
[Music]
you guys
believe in me why don't you trust me
and but wait how do I I can't ah at the
end maybe I add the water
wait this is so easy though
all right that was really easy I feel
like maybe I can go up to a hundreds
I have faith in you for this game thank
you because you failed us with math but
this has nothing to do with math
trust me on this one okay we have a big
golem whatever and goblins
and stone oh and uh catapult
interesting
should we just let set them free for
what do they fight each other oh
they do
wait where's the treasure I don't even
see the treasure does he leave me the
treasure
[Music]
the treasure on this one just have to
kill the ogre
[Music]
okay well that was very easy
and now there's treasure again and some
lava well
well well well well
[Music]
he gets rid of the doggo but
um
let's do this
is that a mistake
come on go to the dongle come on go to
the dog I know you want to go to the
doctor maybe I messed it up
are they gonna take the treasure away
from me
no
it's activated
[Music]
I finally just activates on its own when
it like drops on the ground and then has
just like AOE damage
okay uh
[Music]
then let's get rid of this dog first and
then
[Music]
huh
ah
I think I understand I want to get rid
of the floor so the doggo falls into the
lava but don't let go of the water yet
yeah that kills that dog
[Music]
um
then
we can let the wizard or whatever that
is go but then he still doesn't really
feel compelled
to go over to the last dog
huh
well okay almost
[Music]
One Step Closer
um
maybe I shouldn't drop this one right
away but I mean it's in the perfect
position to kill this dog but maybe I'll
do it later on let me see what I can do
first
um
let's try to get this one going early on
and I guess if the TNT is in the way he
will not go to the dog
eh what about now he still doesn't want
to go to the dog
why not
what
I mean he's slowly slowly slipping down
thinking
lure him to the dogs
huh
[Music]
I don't know
no I need oh I need something to kill
the dogs
[Music]
ah
laughs
yeah that's that's not it either ah
[Music]
he needs to kill the dogs
I need the wizard to kill the dogs
ah wait I start with this
I got it I got it oh he's very angry he
really really doesn't like dogs why I
don't understand I personally also don't
care much but I would never hurt them I
would never hit them
I would never try to hurt them
but I think still same problem
[Music]
because yeah
this is so not ideal I can kill the
wizard but I can't kill the last dog
[Music]
gotta drop him before he reaches the far
left ah
[Music]
uh wait what did I do first
um uh this
ah so we should lure him and then yeah
okay okay
thank you oh
but what do I do about this last little
[\h__\h]
won't that kill me
I know
I know this is it just
makes itself blow up
by touching all my Jewels let's go
let's go
okay okay I I didn't consider that at
all that I could just
let him fall on his path
now that I have that under consideration
ooh destroy everything okay okay
um
okay
[Music]
okay let's not touch this one yet
that's for sure
maybe this one
[Music]
no wait do you have to be really fast
with this one by any chance
[Music]
let me redo
oh wait right I forgot that this shoots
arrows I thought again that The Rock has
to land on it
so that it like shoots catapults The
Rock but that's not what that was okay
foreign
[Music]
okay that one first okay I get it now
actually the bottom one first
[Music]
there we go and there we go
and last one
[Music]
okay okay it wasn't that difficult yeah
no I know
who ordered the Yago burger
no Yago Burger is always welcome
find the treasure
I see it I I found it
[Music]
um
I need the wizard for the dogs
what happens if I open this one first
okay
[Music]
ah
I gotta drop the dog before he goes that
way oh no actually ah
oh
oh it worked out
I thought I had to redo but there we go
double kill
bite totally not accident no no no no no
destroy everything
okay no treasure for me I don't I don't
know what I'm why I'm doing it but okay
um
you fight little Goblin
and and then you find the other Goblin
because I got TNT
for the last
ah but actually can you guys fight each
other now
ah [\h__\h]
nah damn it okay
I gotta redo
retry
um
I want to drop the TNT
on them or actually maybe you don't even
use the TNT in the end because I can
just drop him down here or can I know
well first of all
this seems
good no and then maybe I'll just let him
drop now
as long as I still have the lava here
and for the little Goblin
I guess I'll uh but then
yeah no then I have nothing to learn him
over to the TNT it ah oh
okay except for myself
let's go
ah but it doesn't open me up the new
ones yet I don't have enough
um proof of high IQ
okay okay okay okay okay
oh but then uh
I I have to redo it already
ah let me redo
retry retry how about
um
I have an idea
I thought the goblin would move once he
sees the ogre
never mind he doesn't
okay
[Music]
the older it goes even though there's
not a real path maybe I'll make a path
first maybe then Goblin wants to go or
Goblin is very very focused on me though
understandable how about
hey
[Music]
am I not chasing it
is that not absolute cheese
just relying completely on timing
how do I get a higher IQ
give me 85 I need 85
no you're just Smite ass stop
kfp you'll know how to please me man
okay
um
[Music]
what is it there's too much going on uh
I know ah
[Music]
ah
almost I thought maybe it would just
slide down and I can drop it in the
right moment but it doesn't slide at all
um
well I don't I mean so far there were
many moments where I didn't even use all
the materials given to me so maybe I
don't have to
[Music]
oh
oops
[Music]
all right yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh wait oh wait I forgot one important
thing let's hope this somehow still hits
him
so close
foreign
[Music]
I'll just try it completely differently
I need him to kill the little
little one
does he not go for it he must yeah but
then again
[Music]
I'm
a little if I do that a little bit
earlier when he's still on the way I
could get like a lucky try again maybe a
lucky timing thing
oh hi hi you annoying little [\h__\h]
oh
interesting now we're fine
Maybe
[Music]
it just slows down that way because I
still have the slides yeah I knew that I
knew that
I'll get a couple of new ones are
opening up
shall we give it a try
stains 19.
[Music]
and then where's the problem
oh killing him
oh
[Music]
at least we died I destroyed everything
I just thought everything including
myself I should get extra points for
that
[Music]
um
foreign
I mean at some point I will need that
but I don't think I need it on this but
I guess I do
[Music]
but he can easily take care of those
boys
I ah wait I guess I just take him out
now let this one drop in the lava and
then hope this one walks into the bomb
okay no I'm good I like yellow glasses
thank you
ah that works German always works
but it barely gives me IQ I need to
clear all of those to get closer to 100
stage hundred
okay don't go into the lava I'm sorry
I'm sorry
uh
is this connected no okay
doggos together strong right
you see
wait this is so easy I I feel bad for
feeling so smart because this is too
easy
[Music]
try
IQ plus one I feel how my brain is
getting really freaking strong wow
need to go back to the map for town no
thank you I I I'm in the right place I
think I'm currently in the right place
what the [\h__\h] is this
[Music]
ah no the water won't go to the lava on
this way unless
one drop is enough apparently okay then
uh
[Music]
do I need these materials I wonder
honestly I think he will just ah
[Music]
yeah not although the lava will be there
too early and I can't oh wait
Ah that's too easy the lava shouldn't
the lava shouldn't be doing that I think
it's making it too easy
we take those I am really I'm not
allowed to
it feels wrong it just feels so wrong
[Music]
bunga
here kill this one too and then hey this
one's too easy too oh wait wait oh now
we have to drop it on the lava and then
drop the
[Music]
I was a little bit a little bit
too early on that one
I think mostly it was the right way to
do it
[Music]
I think I'll just do it the same way oh
it even broke those spikes down here
oh wait
[Laughter]
[Applause]
no
[Music]
oh okay I think I I will have to kill
him a different way uh
uh can I
lure him somehow
um
I guess maybe I don't eat the ogre until
the very end
let me see
like if I was able to destroy the spikes
can he like actually walk
over them
but it doesn't all cool down
[Music]
that's my problem because he dies here
what if I push one of the oh okay
I thought I could push it over
to get closer to the little Goblin
just experiment yeah yeah I'm I'm
experimenting
um
let's try this first
[Music]
I don't know
that doesn't help me at all either and I
don't know
oh oh really
um
laughs
ah wait an adult
so do we want to cool it down right away
probably right
I mean
we need them to walk over
wonderful
okay
yeah yeah having it
drop early like that gives me more
control over where it actually lands I
should have should have seen that
earlier oh but uh now uh yeah
thank God okay
no collateral damage let's go I feel
like two stars even really thank you
thank you
I think if I clear this and I have
enough IQ for the next level
what's this
[Music]
now jump over here and you stupid man
hey I don't want it oh wait this these
are not really
no no
no it's okay walking in the very very
fresh uh
cool down lava I don't think it's that
cool yet could it be I think my feet
will be very very much in pain
[Laughter]
I don't really want to really clear all
of them isn't there like another game
that I haven't tried yet no oh that's
actually all
actually guys I will leave it at that
maybe
because I saw all the games and I think
it will just take too much time I I want
to keep the stream really short actually
because I want uh to make some food and
try to sleep at a decent time today
which will of course will not work
um
could I have 114 IQ unless she played
longer than me I don't really I I I'm I
already know that I could reach uh over
9000 IQ if I wanted to
if I wanted to maybe I will off screen
I just wanted to go for them quickly
they're fun though I I love this idea
like it's so original to make a game out
of these stupid games but just make it
better like wow big brain I love it I
love the idea behind that
um on the weekend we'll be playing GTA
what's the name of this game I at the
bottom left it says yeah you want those
games right so here you go now let's see
you clear them if you type in yeah
then it should already come up on uh
Steam
I will be there thank you thank you I
will see you there and uh I think
I'll end it without Super Chat rating
today but I think oh thank all of you
for watching today
and uh thank you also for watching the
whole 30 stream today earlier today for
me it was 9 A.M
um
have a good rest boss thank you ah it
was a lot of fun but it uses so much
brain juice
a big brain game for big brain gamers
only
thank you thank you I did my VOD Reps
for hotel I hope all of you watched it
yet because I know it was at a difficult
time for na viewers I'm sorry about that
but yeah it was really the only possible
time frame
sometimes we have to make sacrifices
for the greater good
um
I'm so excited for you guys to hear it
yeah finally dance
first original single maybe the first of
more to come who knows one can only hope
but
um I think en management is very
motivated yeah
hey
hint of the style
I I can't I can't
maybe I've already placed a hint
somewhere but
um
I I will not hint at the hints now
anyway
[Music]
[Laughter]
if you guys are bored go and play this
game it's fun maybe put it on your steam
uh deck no steam deck is that what was
what it was called
steam deck Ryan and play it when
traveling
when you're really bored hmm
bye
happy that's it thank you guys
[Music]
GTA
GTA on the weekend weekend on the GTA
oh we're gonna finish GTA on the weekend
so
I hope you guys will be there for the
big ending
and maybe DLC in the future but yeah
[Music]
bye bye bye
what's your GTA what's your city
what's your GTA what's your GTA what's
your GTA what do CTA
thank you my fellow K-pop lovers in the
chat
the few ones
tried my best infecting the other ones
you just got here well time to watch the
archive
bye-bye yeah yeah