foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
sorry I went to also water my
plants on the balcony
things you can do during the loading
screen oh so many things
oh [\h__\h] it's so hot oh my God wait let
me bring my friend
ah
it's so hot
[Music]
come on hey
oh fan
[\h__\h] summer you know I am I'm
actually well
I'm happy
about going to
Japan soon
because
it's currently way less hot in Tokyo
than it is here which I didn't think
would be a thing I I looked up the
weather
uh and I was like I thought oh it will
definitely be more hot in Japan because
I know summer in Japan is humid and hot
as [\h__\h] but no uh it might be humid but
it's like way less hot
and see me
yeah the bird is migrating for summer
no [\h__\h] it's it's like so hot here like
the past few days
I don't know we're having like a little
bit of a heat wave
or I mean it's not even a heatwave at
this point because I think this is not
normal
in Austrian Summers
yeah uh recently it's been like for a
Celsius yeah uh 30 to 34.
degrees
uh very hot and no no [\h__\h] clouds
no clouds
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
yeah
and even in the now we have reached the
time where even in the night it's hot
so
[Music]
sleeping at night
with an air conditioner
um I'm looking forward to that I
remember last year when I was streaming
in the summer
I remember saying something like because
I was suffering remember when I said
that if like next year if I suffer again
I'll just book an Airbnb or something
that has a uh an AC and I'll just stay
there for the whole summer well
no I'm not doing that but in July I am
gone
several times
I'm leaving the country
I'll be gone three times
um I mean I'm counting the upcoming trip
so
um three times for short trips so I'll
be I'll be elsewhere a lot of the time
yay and hotels usually have aircon so
yeah on the Jet Plane
um August might get worse yeah I know it
was July yeah
well maybe August maybe August if I'm
not going anywhere in August which I
don't know yet
then I'm I might take a [\h__\h] break
I might take a summer break
and go [\h__\h] off
[Laughter]
I might just go elsewhere spontaneously
[\h__\h] the summer [\h__\h] it
um
go tell someone who has they say nobody
has a c here
in Austria only like shopping malls and
um well you know Cinema and hotels and
supermarkets like they all got AC but
it's not normal here to have AC in
apartments even when they're or houses
even when they're expensive like even
when you pay a [\h__\h] ton of rent
you don't have AC here because like 20
years ago the summer wasn't this hot yet
in Austria either
and yeah so like there's no AC culture
the the when people when companies build
buildings
I I you know I've been like you know
living in like new apartments and uh
they always like offer
you two like you know add on stuff if
you purchase it
or even if you rented possibly
but it doesn't come like with the
apartment by the get-go
but I'm hoping that you know sort of
sort of in the future they will um do
this yeah something something global
warming and and so when I buy an
apartment in the future
if it doesn't have AC then I will uh I
don't care how much it costs I will but
I will pay to have it built in not the
central ones I mean the ones that you
have in Japan
global airfryer
the units that you can see because I
really like Japanese Aces
I like seeing them and not having them
built into the ceiling I like to see
them because then I know what they're up
to
um
yeah
I don't [\h__\h] want the window I can't
I can't have a window unit here reasons
there's like no I I but but I'll try to
get out of this rental uh sooner rather
than later and then and then yeah into
the summer in the summer if I suffer too
much I'm gonna go through an Airbnb or
something but even airbnbs don't really
have a scene I gotta go to a hotel
so
so um maybe August full month no kiwawa
oh because because shitty internet
connection in hotel so only
um only uh Twitter
spaces okay
five Twitter spaces per week from uh
very very uh windy AC hotel room
uh no no I cannot I cannot like I could
never forgive myself for like
disappearing a whole month without
preparing anything or not streaming at
all no no
um
no no
so anyway uh uh uh
[Music]
thank you
I am tangenting
[Music]
I went to swim
before stream swim before swim where's
my Minecraft logo here
why is it not pink it should be pink
let me make it Pink
how do I do this in OBS
image mask
color maybe this
[Music]
um
so being great exercise yeah but it was
less exercise and more
you know trying to cool down
and OBS needs more ways of editing
images
I don't know how to do this stuff
maybe ah maybe this oh
um
[Music]
uh sorry got excited about the pink
maybe a bit more like this oh
look pink Minecraft
wow
oh pink pink pink
apparently I'm the only one playing
Minecraft right now
oh well it's not even
it's not even so like what I'm missing
but it could be online you know and fury
wait is this
this is the red window to capture yeah
sorry I'm really my place to really my
pace so thank you for a man but she put
20. oh my God
really my face is my base
my peace
I want it to be bigger can I make it
bigger bloom
[Music]
is that a good good window size No Maybe
a bit more
that was a Minecraft God
okay we're bigger for myself not for you
guys
what is it ah
there we go
there is no bgm
not yet
[Music]
you know there's really cool new bayou
mean
in my Cuda
right now
we got updated
yeah cherry blossom and also
also well BTM difficult to choose also
there is like some I didn't even know
about this because everybody only talks
about the cherry blossom
about apparently
there's
there's also
like some what what is it like ruin
excavation whatever
thing
[Music]
do you like the PGM
sniffers sniffers
okay camel
yeah but so I was thinking the reason I
didn't put any of that in the thumbnails
because I was thinking
um
don't know if I can do all of that
in one stream or if I even want to
forcefully do all of that in one stream
you know because it's content I could
split it in two streams
um
okay first of all
[Music]
and checking
wow so the oh
question
[Music]
um I
assume that I have to go
really far
to find new biome
or can it be somewhere where we already
loaded in chunks no okay I have to go
far okay okay no no problem
no problem
um
okay we'll take a shulker of course
do I have a relatively empty one this is
relatively empty
there
okay and it's even Pink Perfect
huh you want to find your I'm gonna find
my own or has anyone in the en server
already found one
I'm not gonna go to the resource ever no
no I I stay in the end so ever this is
moon this is my mom my home
over why oh is it like a certain height
I don't think so fauna did Kelly did
cat Kelly
went all the way to find uh
in El server
I'm asking in the Ian server
right
you can travel 40K plus if you're that
crazy
[Music]
you're right you why are you sounding
kind of like well then okay then do it
your way why are you sounding like that
I always do it like this I find these by
all means because that's part of the
adventure and I I go my way come away
now can we continue that
Beyond
[Music]
bye
yay
come on come on
[Music]
that's one of my favorite uh
songs from as a master from back in the
day
but I mean I also haven't just haven't
listened in to the new ones anyway
right now it's just trying to sort my
inventory before we go before you know I
walk over there with a lot of [\h__\h] in my
stuff
come play yes I talked about it in my
last stream
bring ice or fireworks yeah oh yeah yeah
I I I I will bring more
don't worry I am in the middle of
preparing
[Music]
I have five Stacks now okay
maybe a boat
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] are all the best
what
[Music]
yeah I'm in a singing mood let's see I'm
sorry I'm in a good mood because I went
swimming and and I had my Korean lesson
which was did not help my good mood
because I felt more like
very stupid
and
hmm I don't know nothing's entering my
brain anymore and it's going so fast and
I can't keep up anymore
um
[Music]
I I
I I'm feeling very stupid when my some
same name my teacher
[Music]
me because I don't know anything
I'm suffering
[Music]
a constant stream of random noise
uh I'm just trying to entertain
wait if I make a bed with akasia planks
it doesn't look like katsia does it
[Music]
they all look the same right like the
frame looks the same right
small bites I'm trying but she teaches
me so much every freaking week I can't
keep up
[Music]
oh they should let us make beds in cute
colors too I mean not only the bedding
but also the frame
better mode
[Music]
she's doing her job
I mean you know I could
well
I don't know the thing is it's ending
soon I'm almost at the end of I don't
know how many lessons
I originally
paid for but like half a year or so once
per week
we're almost done like she we checked
you know the upcoming lessons we have to
like skip some or delay some because
I'll be gone here and there
but I think we're done first week of
August
[Music]
um no and I'm I'm thinking maybe
extending it but I'm I don't know I
might have to wait a little bit to
extend
what am I doing what is this
that's not the one I wanted
[Music]
because she's going on a vacation or
something I think
for a while so I
oh yeah but I want the same teacher you
know so we can continue where we left
off and you know I like her she's really
nice
um we chit chat a little bit in between
you know her hammering information into
my brain
trying to get out of the Austin heat
yeah yeah
it's too hot
she cute why are you asking that she's
married and she has children
hmm
anyway uh
I guess
all we can do
is how rare is the Sakura biome
how rare is it actually
as rare as the Mesa
[Music]
I didn't answer the question
she's not single obviously
[Music]
um
just rare
than Mushroom Island
okay
oh my God
okay well
um
[Music]
sorry brain slow
brain always used up by Korean lesson
[Music]
what am I what am I doing
if I need more food
what am I doing what was I doing
ah I came for golden armor actually I
didn't tell you guys there is no golden
armor
because we're going to the never I was
drinking go to the never drive my ice
road to the Mesa by homie then uh make
the tunnel a bit longer
and spawn somewhere after the mess of
Miami
[Music]
so that way we already have like a
direct
um path continuing from the Ice Road
and and that would be easy to get there
again in the future
and yeah
[Music]
um I just hope I'll just you know when I
end my tunnel somewhere
I have to hope that wherever I ended
maybe close by there's what I'm looking
for otherwise I I guess I get rid of the
portal and then go a bit further I guess
I don't know
um but anyway let's make some
something
[Music]
I don't know are we making a helmet or
something but that means I need some
obsidian too right here five for a
portal right nice easy I still have eyes
was it the blue the packed eyes
that I need
[Music]
10 for a portal what
I have crying obsidian I have so much
grown-ups and I never use it and then
maybe I have some down here
10 for a portal what if
[Music]
I hear I got more okay well I might just
bring my never
um Ender Chest
um let me take this because this is from
our Mesa Adventures I can
put this away
[Music]
okay yeah it looks like
wait what
I'm confused I thought I was looking at
my Ender Chest
okay
a lot of
[Music]
Instinct this out
this we can keep
[Music]
um
some fireworks
lace right no fire resistance and I'll
never stop oh yeah I still have to never
star well
uh what were we planning final was gonna
do something with it no
[Music]
oh wait flint and still good good
portion of healing more totems
yeah making a beacon where where were we
gonna do that ifanna ever asks in her
stream oh where is where is the beacon
uh the never star you can let her know
it's in my basement it's here she can
take it whenever she needs it
if she needs it why do I have it
when did when did I get it in the end
um
but if she ever asks for it she's like
oh I wonder I wish I wish I could make a
beacon right now oh
I wish I wish I could make a beacon
right now oh
um who has it again
Kiara oh too bad
um
it's in her basement
[Music]
okay maybe we can get it oh
I hope she doesn't mind
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh yeah tell her it's uh it's here
[Music]
I don't mind fauna
um no sorry brain slow very slowly just
put this wherever
[Music]
two shocker boxes
maybe two would be nice actually
okay
[Music]
yeah and once I'm there I can like mine
absolutely everything well do I need a
home maybe
for I saw that there's there's like
flowers that grow on the ground oh can I
take everything shares
fierce
[Music]
shoes
Heroes
cheers cheers for the leaves
oh sheer shears
cheers
everything you have to do yourself
everything gotta do everything yourself
sharers have to make shears
ah
make sure share shares
okay a pair of shears
and a golden
golden shoes
okay okay
then I would say I'm pretty prepared I'm
actually gonna
um
you know I placed an ended chest in the
Mesa biome Ryan
then I placed another one somewhere else
now I'm out of
um inner chest I think
or
it has been a million years since I made
one
[Music]
so
something to write the portal
[Music]
torches
and under eye I don't do I have another
eye
I have an obsidian
in a fan like maybe I saw one
and the Pearl right same thing right
[Music]
laughs powder
what
blaze powder too
for then the chest
what
combine powder and ender pearl huh
lace powder and pearl ah oh to make the
eye
Oh I thought this was the eye okay uh uh
wait blaze rods
I have
[Music]
we need
whoa and that's been a while since I
made one
okay how much powder wait wait and
there's
[Music]
thank you
wow wow
it's teaching me now I already knew how
to make that
sometimes game forgets all the recipes
you made before no
okay a new end the chest
oh very good
preparing preparing preparing
[Music]
reset yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
oh and we have shears put them away
already but we have them okay
I think we're good to go oh actually I
guess I didn't need that much fireworks
because most of the path I'm traversing
Through the Never
through the en servers never answered
servers never regions
I just
this is
a way to set a respawn Point without
dying without blowing up a bed
whoa innocence when is that a thing
I'm a copper Cow Island Mesa Bayou me
and now we're adding a fourth stop um
foreign
just don't touch that too long
Howard's Island
I called it kawas Island
[Music]
did they
long time ago yeah
I don't think anybody's using my
Express but eh let's I can't see [\h__\h]
yeah we should probably turn the
um thing off in the when we're in the
never Ride video Center Shader oh
did I read cow cow is left with what
did I read cow
is what did I
I need to watch the VOD I did not did I
[Music]
did
did I block myself in did someone block
this in
what are you doing here
they won't attack me but did I what
happened here
[Music]
someone was running from them
but you won't attack me Ryan have fun in
the boat I guess
okay we go to the huh
I can't place it
there you go we'll go to the end of it
[Music]
and then
we'll build further and hope we get
lucky so far I've always gotten pretty
lucky pretty fast
[Music]
finding the
finding the cow is land it's really fast
[Music]
Elena reacted because I wasn't sure what
it was at first
jump scare Galore
wow this path is really long actually
[Music]
well
because you guys never answered my
question whether it's blue or packed ice
you never answered me
[Music]
I can answer my own question now because
I can look at what it is
in bed I have the bed
blame us of course I do
blue better factors ah yeah okay right
both was fine but what am I using here
let me check
blue eyes and Cactus
both
guess I'm using both
[Music]
am I shifting tangents yeah yeah I am
guilty of being all over the place
because I actually there's like many
things many things many things
I wanted to talk about can I talk about
you know what I learned in my Korean
lesson today
[Music]
foreign
I learned the yo form
the
[Music]
um
instead of
or so on I learned more yeah friendly
form
yes and I learned
foreign
from two so I can say from Ice Cream
today and
um
from
we started
sometime 5 PM so
oh
no oh no story of
um
[Music]
and
put and then until maybe
maybe your
maybe y'all see your your [\h__\h]
[Music]
your ship is no no yeah yeah your ship
is she uh
[Music]
okay brain feel slow because that's what
I learned today
blue eyes packed and blue eyes blue eyes
blue eyes
the ice what's better right
[Music]
so uh the thing is the putka team was
not so much of a problem the from until
you can also say it for locations by the
way let's go from home to school and
team
right but but yeah
[Music]
um
that was not the problem the problem is
the the yield form
oh
it's just too much I'm already
struggling with
um the
[Music]
Nida form
because not always like not always it's
very obvious how you
conjugate the verb
and thank you form at least at least the
one good thing is that apparently like
for for
the form the polite
speech you know [\h__\h] off where I say
for example
when I ask I ask mashitsun Nika
so the da changes to GGA
it's like a or kka more like that but
in the yo form you don't have a word
that makes it into a question it's
instead you're like okay you say oh
I go to school and if you want to ask
are you going to school you just ask you
you just ask with changing your
intonation which I suppose makes it
easier right
somehow because there's less that you
have to remember right
just intonation just checking is this
where my Mesa biome is right yeah okay
okay
don't understand but agree thank you
thank you isn't it simple yeah but then
there's like
five different ways
that the your form will like
form with a verb
verb according to my teacher she taught
me five different ways depending on
what for example if if in the
verb there's a A or is if there's an ah
then it ends like this if there isn't
then it ends like this if it's a Hada
just the single verb Hada then it ends
like this and then and then also if it's
then it ends like this so there's so
many different
and and I I after she told me like all
five of them were some examples like I
was already like my brain was already
fuming and then she then she teaches me
um
then we read like a like a like a
sentence yeah really long actually
really long sentence and I have to put
in the words
and then she's like okay how will this
verb will be if it's a you form and I'm
like
um
uh
[Music]
uh um brain not responding
error ever
[Music]
I had
absolutely no idea it doesn't need to be
free Tom
one two three what
it doesn't have to be but we're doing it
like that
[Music]
yeah I was not Computing Kiana exit I
stopped responding exactly
[Music]
and I just found so stupid but I guess
it's okay that's something you just been
taught
like a few minutes seconds ago
that you don't immediately know
[Music]
how how to use it right is it is that
okay
[Music]
wrong thing
I hope that's acceptable
except
German
I pronounced it in German okay I got a
problem with that
but anyway I I mentioned I was quite
proud when um the put katji came up and
put put don't put
and I remembered a meme that I saw a
Korean music meme that I saw recently
and I was like something
[Music]
wait I have funny meme please let me
teach you
[Music]
it's it's okay okay see this is why I
don't want to speak Korean on stream
like that
and it's like a it's like a g a but in
Korean the the ga there's a ga and the
GGA and the KA but the even the ga you
kind of pronounce more like strong like
k okay
but you would write it in romanite
status with G anyway
um why you gotta make a weird
[Music]
anyway what's going on I'm I'm looking
for a new biomi but also I'm telling
people about my today's Korean lesson
experience where I felt absolutely
overwhelmed
um
tell me guys when I should stop
[Music]
so my pickaxe is not gonna
uh
deal uh keep up with this for very long
but anyway the meme the meme the meme
the meme the meme the meme where are my
Korean Bros Korean Bros green Bros
I want to tell you about the meme
the other day I found YouTube suggested
me a meme
Korean meme
that there's this one phrase
that is the most supposedly not really
maybe
it's somewhere up there the most used
Korean phrase in Korean songs
and I watched it and I was like hmm oh I
didn't know this phrase I didn't know
what it means but indeed I did hear it a
lot in Korean songs
you know what it is
[Music]
Sue
that's from head to toe it means from
head to toe wow
and it's using a lot of songs and that
one was hot issue yeah
[Music]
we have more other pickaxes I have my
silk touch one
[Music]
I don't even need to make it this tall I
think but you know
felt like it looks pretty
um but yeah and then I showed her the
video I quickly
showed her the video
she didn't laugh but she was like yeah
yeah same same word
I was so proud I'm like look look look I
recognize this phrase that you're
teaching me from this Meme and now I
understand
yeah
so I think Modi is head
in Korean
[Music]
I don't know if I'm saying it correctly
to be honest
okay how about until here when I go out
here shouldn't there be a new biomy
[Music]
oh that should be
calling
[Music]
I guess I'll use the surface for a while
it doesn't matter
[Music]
I will not go to the news ever
I saw
um
I saw a clip
two where I talked about this recently
about refusing to you know do
like use
um or get rid of my my thinks and
whatever give up on feelings and go to
other places that are more efficient
and some of the replies oh my God I had
to shake my head because because some
people don't get it something
some people just don't want to get it I
don't understand why
why would I not prefer to use something
that I built over what others build
numbers one number one
second of all I built it with my mom it
has even more sentimental value due to
that
um
number three
[Music]
I know where things are there I'm used
to it thus I shall use it number four it
just has a lot of history in my streams
and all that if I give up on it now then
it was all like for nothing and yeah
number uh I lost track of the numbers
but it also it's just aesthetically
pleasing to me because you know put we
put a lot of work into the design and
you know creating the whole thing
and it's not even that Phoenix Sun isn't
efficient okay maybe it's not as
efficient as
some other Farms or so
okay but I don't need it to be much more
efficient though I'm very happy and
satisfied with the efficiency that I
have in Phoenix then
it's fast enough for me and yeah yeah I
play how I want
it's just like it's my town and we have
a lot of history there I want to use it
I wanna I wanna continue using it also
mommy she told me
mommy my mom she was really happy about
me
um
you know showing Phoenix Sun again and
improving it and all that
she was watching the stream you know she
was very very
uh please
by me going back and improving it you
know she said oh it looks so good you
did so well
no
[Music]
mama told me
why me too but why not use more
efficient
way why YouTuber
wow because because
I can like like seriously I feel like to
me
I I just don't need it to be any more
efficient than this
I'll use other things like fauna's fancy
fish farm
instead of Amish farm now
yeah because that okay exp when I need
EXP
then I usually like to have it really
fast
but I also didn't if if I had built if I
was the creator of Amish exp Farm
that was my thing that I would probably
possibly still refuse
what
[Music]
I would probably still refuse to use fun
as far
and then in that scenario
and I mean you know maybe I would even
try to improve it and make it more
efficient but uh yeah because he wants
to use things that you built right if
nobody else is gonna use it and I mean
somebody's gonna use it
oh
even Emma uses fun as Farm well yeah but
that's Amish
that's Amish she doesn't she I I isn't
she very critical of her own Farm
but I I really like her form though and
if that was what I created then I would
continue using it but that's you know a
difference between me and Anna Maybe
she hates it she likes how ppv looks I
like also yeah design wise aesthetically
with all the like leaves going down
yeah I would say that
I miss Farm is prettier
watching all of these answers thank you
thank you very much we're pretty close
to finishing Zelda yo
gosh there's so many topics can I make a
little note
there's no hashtag I want to make a note
[Music]
I want to talk about so many things
okay so for example
um talk about indirect and talk about
[Music]
it
I have I have things in my head and now
I forget everything
[Music]
okay what the [\h__\h]
um
movie
[Music]
collapse what collapsed
no what do I have to say about the
collapse that I have something to say
about the collapse
maybe I don't know
uh
ah yeah hair appointments thank you
see I'm forgetting everything
before the stream I had so many toppings
topics in my mind where I was like I
gotta talk about this I gotta talk about
that I gotta talk about this and that
[Music]
ah yeah thank you shoulder
stuff
toppings yeah toppings
um
is there something else
[Music]
yeah I knocked my brain out
you made me
okay maybe not for now
stuff I cook finally I got to tweet it
again because I I
here let's go into that
um tangent right away I finally fixed
the Twitter problem
because you know I have two private
phones right because one is old and the
reason I continue using it because
there's like this one Bank banking app
that I have on it you know when I have
to send something so uh and and and then
I have to use the app to like confirm it
and I'm thinking like if I uh
saw ancient debris
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
um then the same this really yeah the
Authenticator
what
[Music]
what what
it's pet rock yeah
stop stop distracting me
um
um um
um yeah yeah yeah so for authenticating
basically that's the only purpose
that's why I'm still keeping that phone
uh oopsie
I think
oh there's there's more reason but it's
not really a good reason
um
and I'm like oh if I have to put this on
my new phone I probably have to do some
annoying authentication of you know
my new phone to use it there no that
sounds annoying
so I've just been using the old phone
whenever I need to do that but sometimes
it's actually quite handy because when
my old phone and my new phone went to
the battery then I still have my old
phone as a backup leave a blue so you
know and then I've been having this
issue for like I don't know two months
where sometimes when I tweet
um
my app world crash actually not
sometimes but very often my app will
just crash
right
I told you guys about that so many of my
tweets failed because of that it might
be a good thing maybe in some way
because sometimes I was maybe gonna
tweet something that nobody really wants
to hear and nobody cares about and it
kind of stopped me but a lot of the time
I just wanted to show you guys what I
cooked for dinner and I tried to share
it with you guys and then I just can't
because I write up this whole tweet
hoping that it will work this time
and then it crashes
and crashes and that happens so often
yeah you guys missed out on a lot of my
cooking I need to make a post where I
post all of the ones I didn't post
um
but yeah
[Music]
so
then more and more often I would use my
um
my
question
actually I like this maybe
I would use my
second my old phone to tweet because on
the old phone at least it was still
working
[Music]
and then recently even on my old phone
the Twitter app was suddenly bugging
around like when I was for example
opening up the replies to a tweet
not in my reply section but I opened up
a tweet and scroll down to the replies
often it would crack or like actually
pretty much almost always it would start
crashing
the app would crash because of opening
replies Sam
yeah
so
both phones my Twitter app was [\h__\h]
now recently and I'm like okay I have to
do something I have to do something
about this because like when I looked up
the solution it just said oh try
deleting the cache I did that and it
didn't help
sorry in the end I just reinstalled the
app and
that did the trick indeed no wait no the
funny thing was I I reinstalled the app
and then I had some troubles logging in
actually
[Music]
it was kind of weird
it was bugging around a little bit but
then finally I got that fixed too
[Music]
I'm switching by the line keep on
Switching because I want to use both I
guess
download more RAM
but yeah now it's finally working on the
new phone so now I can
finally peacefully tweet out my kitchen
kiwala's Kitchen Posts again
um
yeah ah
[Music]
okay yeah more more things
so oh yeah
um
come on
so now you will now kiwawa will cook
again more because ah
because Wawa knows that you guys
want to see what Wawa Cooks
you know
oh there we go
again
[Music]
foreign
there's nothing to explain first of all
because
ketchup is like it has maybe this like
childish image
doesn't mean it's bad okay
I mean I normally I think I I actually
always used to eat fish fingers when I
was a child with mayonnaise
but anyway this is uh a recipe from
hello
and they currently have like a campaign
going on with this like I think it's
Pixar an animated Pixar movie
called Elemental and like for every week
they have like a themed Elemental themed
dish and I think if you get three of
them
[Music]
I think you get a free movie ticket so I
was like hmm I'll try if they have good
dishes then I'll try making them I guess
um oh I'm almost at the end well I am at
the end
[Music]
so one of them was that like fish
fingers
with
um
[Music]
the potato cucumber sound which also a
lot of people questioned but it was
really good so give it a chance please
it was really good
and and the dressing was a dressing that
I feel like you
usually have live
the potato salad
it's not like typical American potato
salad with a [\h__\h] ton of mayonnaise
super [\h__\h] unhealthy excuse me for
making something healthy
because like some people are like
that sounds so weird uh I I wouldn't eat
that
usually the picky eater
no you guys are like oh that's weird
May was great I I will say yeah Mayo is
great normally like I eat potato fries
and all that with mayo
um
but yeah this one came with ketchup
which yeah I agree it's kind of like
simple and kind of childish yeah but but
it worked really well it tasted really
good
it did taste really good with the fish
fingers I oh my God I'm like I had a
little bit of trouble
cooking it
uh because the oil Splish Splash swish
swish swish
my hands felt so burnt in hindsight it's
my fault I could have done better
because
um the way like I wanted to flip the
fish fingers so I used two forks so that
I have better control over them
and so I had no hand open to hold
something
in front of me
to yeah
keep the oil away later on at the end of
the process I finally started using the
tongs and then it was way better
but until I got to that point I had so
many oil burns on my hands you don't see
them at least at least they're really
like like really low-key Burns um
they're really low-key
I want to make um oh
[Music]
I kind of wanna
I didn't bring any wood did I I want to
make a sign but I guess I can make it
later I'm gonna make a sign that says
right side
um
probably Sakura by Omi and down Mesa by
Omi but okay for now
um
let me get the belt
we'll see where we get out on the other
side I feel like we're far enough
wouldn't you guys agree isn't this
enough far enough
oh yeah right there's hanging signs now
yeah
otherwise if you guys say it's not
enough then I'll
I'll have to repair my pickaxes
[Music]
um
yeah I'm traveling to find you by yummy
explored a lot of the old world in that
direction
did I
like past the Mesa
[Music]
oh yeah to find
um what was it that that tree the Cave
the Lush cave Ryan
but it didn't go that far
than I
I want the train to be like very close
but okay let's just check what we can
find
um
foreign
make a little space for
portal
[Music]
how big
are we gonna make it
um
[Music]
I'll make it here is this
one two three four five six seven eight
nine
no ten
has to be a full circle right I haven't
made a portal in a while
[Music]
four ten for the four portal I can skip
the true I can skip the corners yeah
so here here
[Music]
or does it have to be wider
come on bottom Freon [\h__\h] okay
not quite
[Music]
nice
like this
okay and then
were they really this big
[Music]
wonderful
one two
three one two three
oh
[Music]
yay okay
I'm scared
[Music]
oh
I'm not in the same message am I I think
when I was flying over my over my own
Mesa like soon after I found more
missions I think
what did the courts say the court the
court say
this
how far am I from my own muscle
it can't be the same as uh at least we
spawned elsewhere
so
it's just a coincidence
[Music]
yeah yeah 12K
be the end of my mess up nah it's just a
coincidence
pick it up
yeah taking a screenshot let me fly
around a little bit
[Music]
um
remember
[Music]
straight back straight back straight
back
let me
it's different there's Temple Temple no
no Temple
so now I'm going I think kind of I don't
know which direction am I even going
what's that
okay
[Music]
left myself forward Mesa
well we we will investigate a little bit
to see if there is a Sakura by Omi
is it normally like on the mountain or
where do you find the sakur down
[Music]
I think it's a new this is all new I
think
it's all new
[Music]
I mean that's a big mess up
I didn't go full circle there is and
then there's no way there is no way
[Music]
sheep
foreign
that's my portal I found it again let me
go
um wait
portal currently is facing
[Music]
uh I came out like
this
I think
that means that means if I
wait I I went straight and then I made a
portal face in the right side of my
Tunnel right
so if I want to go
forward in the same direction as the
tunnel I would go this way maybe
keep going south look at the chords
South okay
Let's see
[Laughter]
we can figure out how far straight we
have to go
[Music]
assuming that this is really the right
the right direction right
[Music]
uh to extend the tunnel to be directly
at the right by all mean
[Music]
something like that right
song
I don't know it's so well
[Music]
like that
yeah okay we have to go quite a bit
further because I have yet to find
me
[Music]
at least I took a screenshot of the
coordinates of where I spawned
very smart
[Music]
snow
so sorry I didn't see if there were any
replies
is there like usually a certain
environment where the Sakura biomi will
spawn or is it randomly
[Music]
any Green Mountain areas
okay
should be a waste of me or did you look
it up
Twist of me
and we need to go I need to find one
that goes straight though just so that
it makes it easier for me
for the tunnel making
[Music]
yeah I Spike by Omi it looks so cool
though
[Music]
I could get more blue packed ice here
right
oh yeah I'm too fast I'm scared I'm slow
it's so slow but this must be new chunks
otherwise it won't load so slowly would
it
[Music]
[\h__\h] is this biome is normal
snowy slopes
[Music]
oh my God
we were up so high what the [\h__\h] is like
Mount Everest we're Above the Clouds
I think I've ever seen such high
mountains in uh Minecraft before
like naturally
[Music]
foreign
what Ender cities are only
I mean they're only in another
right
[Music]
City
no way so
for this
[Music]
wait that makes me really curious
foreign
[Music]
I just wanna peek and take a screenshot
so I can maybe if I later on when I
explore an ancient shooter
can you see it like if you peek in oh
but herewards
[Music]
not open not really
here maybe
a pie hook
I don't want to find a bug oh this is so
scary
this is so scary
oh just another opening
oh I hear goats
[Music]
is it like
like how do you
how do you get into that just poke a
hole
I want to see it thanks for the
memberships
minus 51.
okay now whatever I won't look
I won't look it'll be a surprise if I
ever go back here and try to find one
[Music]
okay
oh sh it's night time
South
I spikes
very snowy everywhere here
very cold
very different from real life
[Music]
um
nice feeling
see so many stars
[Music]
why
oh wait there we go there's some more
we're getting rid of the snow
[Music]
it's like split right in the middle
between
no one not snow well we have we have
trains and mountains isn't that kind of
what we're looking for
[Music]
over here
the the green Greener ones
the more luscious green ones
[Music]
it's not really a mountain
circle around this area but I I needed
to be straight
here
uh remember this Lake
I'm circling remember the lake and the
ice
is going
West
West West West West West
[Music]
no no
I feel it
Sakura bayomi in
[Music]
pre
hello
one
[Music]
that's no I saw some pink stuff
I thought maybe it was a very very tiny
amount oh no
[Music]
circling back
nothing here unfortunately
[Music]
oh
that's not what I'm looking for this
time
I looked for that before
and successfully got my own allies
alleys
by my own hands
very proudly
so wait was this the river [\h__\h]
of course we're lost now no no no no
it's right where the snow is mm-hmm
the middle between the snow and the
normal trees here there we go that's the
lake see I'm not lost
now we're going south again yeah this is
exactly that point wow photographic
memory
[Music]
I'm not my goal
let me Circle a little bit here and then
come back to The Big Field that I just
saw
circle circle circle circle circle
circle circle circle
[Music]
nothing yeah
and snow again
[Music]
and while you look for something the
heart it'll be to find well
well I'm far
and I was looking for things I always
found it pretty quickly like the frogs
the Mesa wasn't that big of a problem
either I think
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh Direction
[Music]
wait where am I I don't remember this
Tower
[Music]
damn it
now apparently I'm facing south
first try that was wild yeah but I was
not looking for the trident
and there was the field
but that was not the tower God damn it
now I'm lost now I'm lost
[Music]
[\h__\h] wait if if I from the point where I
originally was
[Music]
let's do some
let's try to be smart okay
I want you guys to help me out with your
smartness
let me open my screenshot
[Music]
um
I'm potato
Minecraft
screenshots
so
we have
we have this
this
so
I looked at the portal but then I went
left from the current point of view
right
um
so here's my question
[Music]
um
if if
um that line that line let's say Okay
um South
North and South one line right like here
and then east and west
[Music]
East and West this line yeah yeah
um my question
[Music]
um
is
uh I can't I can't put it into words
[Music]
I don't even know what my question was
anymore
[Music]
um
yeah whatever forget it
[Music]
once I have
by Omi that I'm looking for
but but oh wait I think I have an idea
One Thousand Seven Seventeen
thousand twelve thousand
if I
continue to go south
then what is going up the the eighteen
seven okay okay okay so if I go the
opposite of South
then I'll go back to the 12 000 right so
if I also okay okay I'm I'm I'm
answering my own question right now oh
my God I'm a genius so if I go back here
then the block I just wanted to get it
back to 187 you know so then I'm on the
same line you know what I mean
oh wait I'm already there okay
okay if we stay around here
then oh you don't see it but just next
time I land
one eight seven one eight seven
just gonna bring it back to 187.
[Music]
you can see the steam coming out of my
head
okay and now
uh the 18 000 which was 12 000 before is
going further up okay okay okay
[Music]
coming out
so we'll try to stay on the line but I'm
back in the line now basically if I go
all the way straight backwards then I
should be back at my portal
hi
um
wow yay positive that yeah do we want to
check out the ship now that we know
exactly where we are and what we're
doing
I want to check out the ship
time
[Music]
why
why did I get no boat what the [\h__\h] is
that there was like a yellow boat
looks like it was made out of hay
oh wow
[Music]
sheesh that's a good chest though
is that already the best chest in here
[Music]
normal why you gotta why you gotta you
know
make it feel like less of an
accomplishment
there's always two chests
found it yay
book book and the bird treasurement oh
yeah right
um
what do the treasures usually have and
also I feel like
I I have I would have to do the treasure
chest now
otherwise I'll never come back here
because it's it's like
somewhere close right
new chunk confirmed why
because there was a treasure map
diamonds hard to see but I don't really
I don't really care about the heart of
the sea
hmm well if I ever need more I gotta get
back to the ship
[Music]
my ex is not what I mean by X is not
right
[Music]
nice to save the chords yes just just
making sure
okay
um
[Music]
that's what you mean yeah yeah I kind of
uh
yeah straight away again
[Music]
somewhere over here
I was like how did I Stray away again
I was going straight
[\h__\h]
I dropped them up map what
no yeah but I haven't
sort of twins
Zelda
jungle
Welcome to the Jungle
[Music]
jungle jungle speaking of I never really
actually explored the jungle properly
when the jungle was in an update I don't
know why
but I mean all there really isn't a
jungle that's interesting as parrots
right
besides that
I don't know if it's really that
interesting because there's not not a
like new type of wood either right
that's 10 years ago
oh pandas pandas and parrots yeah
foreign
they have different things compared to
the desert temples
I didn't know that jungle had temples
too
[Music]
bamboos blocks now they mean
but wait
[Music]
does that mean you can make green
Furniture like doors and stuff
[Music]
oh hi yeah
it's not green though it is rather
whitish I want to try making it that's
cool
did they also add that in 1.20.1 or 1.20
[\h__\h] hell I'm looking for so long
just can't find it
[Music]
we have a portal here at least free
portal
wait maybe I should mind the obsidian
actually
gonna mind it really quickly
what's Skyla doing is she streaming
she's not streaming is she at this time
of day
[Music]
meaning
let me put my never rack all here and
take these things
[Music]
so many boots
maybe no but feather falling and
protection four hmm
soon she answered hello
hello
to get this is
[Music]
right for the never don't have to make
my own ones I'll keep them from my
collection oh my oh my God
come on
[Music]
stream heart Challenger
more crying obsidian I won't use the oh
what I keep on forgetting what it's for
[Music]
what is it for
I know
wait why won't it meant from
from
mining this is it not spam anchor
um
super rare I know I have so many of it
too actually
because when it because it's so rare I
keep on mining it every time I see it
even though I don't use it
maybe we sleep
as well while we're here
[Music]
now let's be
thank you XP
[Music]
what is so special
you're saying only or well then I think
that's just another point to back up my
thoughts train of thought of why
I thought maybe possibly obsidian is not
real
maybe it's only a Minecraft thing
you understand now
so much sense Direction
[Music]
South South
for sure
[Music]
bunnies for me
yeah I mean I know obsidian exists in
real life but that that was the
discussion that through playing
Minecraft
it made me think that because it looks
so unreal and and and you know it's
being used for such unreal things that
possibly
it's not a real thing at all
um
because how could it be
you know
when it does such weird things like
making a portal to the underworld
[Music]
okay I mean
I I feel like I've heard and known this
before
[Music]
another ship
also because you know there's other
materials that exist oh
[Music]
one mushroom only
it's like there must be a Kodak here
there's one single mushroom tree
that means there must be a quarter cue
no there's another one okay
[Music]
what was I saying oh yeah other
materials
that you have in Minecraft some like
never rack you know you don't have that
in real life so you know
the name of obsidian already sounds like
told [\h__\h]
eh open a portal on people's stomach
during a sermon with obsidian what do
you mean
do people do the surgeons you oh
[Music]
whoa do surgeons use obsidian
for a surgery
[Music]
because this Ocean's looking so boring
we should wear at 23k
and fireworks well I think I have
another one in my never chest but
because never chance is somewhere else
in theory
if I find it and then
don't fly back but make portal and mind
my way back
maybe I can make the tunnels meet
[Music]
oh my God should have brought even more
fireworks
[Music]
uh yeah it's pretty it's pretty I buy
pretty I buy
there's only [\h__\h] ocean
[Music]
trying to
not use too many but
[Music]
Kyle can help you in this situation how
you mean by having her fly all the way
here and bring me fireworks
[Music]
and I don't think so
she would do it
oh yeah worst case I guess
[Music]
[\h__\h]
it's called a little bit back to here
because I'm kind of off anyway
[Music]
oh
hi friends nice
[Music]
oh that's sweet they have an Animal Farm
what
what they have an animal
far is there a new kind of Trader I
never saw that before
Sakura Village I know that certain types
of animals spawn very uh commonly
uh in this kind of biome
[Music]
awesome find
no beautiful they have beans they have
pigs they have everything
[Music]
kind of surprised that they're not
building the houses out of the Sakura
um
trees at least but there's no trainers
on it
[Music]
is it because they're only farming
I found this surprisingly fast you think
so you call that fast
well here we have Farmers hi
hi
it's so beautiful
and we can rest here too look at them
[Music]
all right let's get mining baby
how I will get back is a different
question but no I mean we are only 100
blocks off
from our original x a little bit less
even how how much is that in the Never
foreign
the math
[Music]
barely anything right
oh that's nothing so if we make if we
um make another portal here the only
problem is we will have to if we spawn
grab a low in the never we'll have to
make our way up
and build continue building our tunnel
from the other way there
that's usually for me very annoying the
process but yeah
but we're I don't think it's impossible
right it's not impossible
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
um uh
[Music]
that's what this is elsewhere but okay
once I make this rain I can always come
back here
so there's no stress to farm everything
now
the real why is he green the real
mission is
why is it green
was was he green but he has no job what
is he different from the others see the
mayor
[Music]
wait he's also green I guess why is
there green ones and not green ones
bring one sapling
no I went to a farm a lot here
[Music]
I know I can make my own trees I know
and I will but
I might as well you know take some of
this stuff with me and these flowers
but I can make
whoa you know what my mission will be
I'll make a little Sakura Forest close
very like right at the Ian
um like main hub
so whoever needs to
get some of their own can quickly
get it from there and then then
my ice station uh train is actually not
very meaningful
um
but but
well well I mean for me for me if I need
more you know right I'm coping but
if I need more I can come back and then
get more yeah yeah yeah
put it at the end of the Ice Road
uh yeah
yeah my goal is to extend the ice road
so far that I can
get
here easily it's so pretty with the like
bright inside and the dark outside of
the tree
but it makes me wonder
because I've seen Sakura trees before in
real life and I'm guessing that they
would try to make it really accurate
but does that mean that Sakura is I know
they're pretty dark outside but there
are other also this this bright inside
[Music]
I doubt that they're pinkish still
that's just like to add a special extra
I think in Minecraft
[Music]
got the saplings I want the saplings
but how do I get saplings again I have
to like wait for them to like fall down
right
[Music]
after I there we go here's one
after I mined the tree
I was only one
and I have two free Cherry saplings
ah
some sticks
[Music]
yeah I'll get a couple more
chop the tree I'm chopping the tree
I mean you sleep actually
[Music]
uh I'll sleep in the house
what else are we in a village for excuse
me
you can watch me sleep hey monster
[Music]
because of me
because of me they're infiltrating The
Village Golem help
[Music]
do something
nice
nice he killed him
[Music]
I Am The Monster all along
do not spread such filthy rumors no no
off these flowers
but if I if I planned a tree though do
these flowers also spawn naturally
around it or to how how do I get these
do they only spawn naturally in natural
no it won't see okay so these ones I
actually need to bring with me all right
[Music]
increase them
oh yeah I saw that like if you have like
this small one and you throw bone meal
and then they grow bigger yeah yeah but
but they won't grow around it right
[Music]
why
no okay so that's actually the trees I
can make my own but for these flowers
that they're so pretty I need to get
them from here and see that's okay
that's the reason to come here for right
[Music]
at least one good reason
I would say so
no you can both milk
what do you mean
whatever we don't have to simplify
everything okay
I came here for a reason and that is to
fill my shoulder boxes with these
materials
don't ruin it for me
[Music]
beautiful they're so pretty
on the floor
why
normally they don't grow on the floor
but this is just random pink flowers I
think yeah oh it's oh eh it says petals
but these are obviously growing
that's just falling down petals
but honestly
to me it looks like one of those Animal
Crossing
patterns that I was using and other
people were using to make the ground
prettier in there sorry
sorry
in their villages in their Islands
[Music]
are you mad at me for taking your
flowers
be mad they'll they'll grow again I'm
sure
it
[Music]
sorry sorry
they seem kind of mad oh it's because
they're fun
they're puppies going away oh
oh
[Music]
okay they're gone
I I'm free
by the wow how many do I have oh my god
wow
that fills up very fast
[Music]
okay is there still some saplings
yes
[Music]
anymore that I left
in the ground no oh there
[Music]
okay I think I got it
I think I got it
[Music]
okay then for now you know what we will
do we'll make a portal
um
actually let me walk
as far as I can while still staying in
the biome
yeah maybe I'll make it here
that'll be a nice like impression when
you walk through
the portal and you spawn here
won't that be really nice
it's good
let's make portal yeah I have everything
that I need okay okay
[Music]
I make one two
two right one two I need to sneeze
I'm the correct X kind
of yeah at this point it makes barely
any difference is what we have
um concluded
because it will just be a few steps
in the um never
I'll just be a little bit difficult to
meet them up if I don't know the exact x
coordinate of my ice path
um which I don't think I ever took a
screenshot from that
thank you
[Music]
wait where was mine and it just another
chest and no
um neighbor of that
um
know what I mean where did I put them
chests
up here
chocolate box yeah
here
[Music]
excuse me for intruding
your beautiful Village but I'm just here
to appreciate it and share the joy with
other people I have 25 saplings
it's a good start I think because you
know what I I said I don't make a forest
but how about I'm for once I make
something efficient and I make a tree
farm
out of these saplings
[Music]
or these specific trees
where will I be where will I be should
I'm so scared I'm so scared I'm so
scared
what the [\h__\h]
isn't that kind of good if I ever need
one of these fortresses again
oh the lava is just spawning in
wonderful I'm down so low I need to go
all the way up [\h__\h]
[Music]
look it's like all the way over there
I left the Shockers yeah that's okay I'm
just building the the ice path for now
to be honest
I don't know
should block that side of the portal
true
yeah bye
bye
[Music]
anyway
hey that scares the [\h__\h] out of me we'll
make a proper while here so that I don't
fall off
can I
um place down there
[Music]
um
scared
[\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
okay ah
how will I mine all the way back
with my current pickaxes
is another good question
but for now we have to go
up
[\h__\h] I should bring some no we make we
make stairs but I don't have enough
wait I have let me go back once
oh no wait diamonds are no I have to add
one Diamond I think in one of my
shoulders
can you show us before so we can help
you remember yep yep yep yep in a moment
you gotta you guys gotta help me find my
way so I know which way I'm supposed to
mine
I was gonna ask you guys for that anyway
um
one diamond
I could make some some golden pickaxes
then the chest well then the chest is on
the other side of my
Ice Road
that is currently inaccessible for me
respawn anchor to Mark the location
[Music]
because I don't really need it right now
you know what I can do for blocks right
now I can mine some ground blocks with
my
[Music]
with my biggie call me
that's some easy to get building blocks
yeah
[Applause]
I can work with that see how fast we are
and quickly we have enough to make some
stairs up to the ceiling
the never roof
you know normally you always have too
much
of these blocks and you never need them
but right now I need them
okay how many okay that's probably
enough right
to make some stairs up to the ceiling
okay I hope I don't die
um I don't want to bring the shulkers
right now because what if I fall and die
and you know and then I'm kind of [\h__\h]
and I fall into the lava and I lose my
Shockers or something like that you know
what I mean
so I prefer to First build the stairs
then come back
[Music]
and don't think
let's sleep
[Music]
Maybe
I mean I could kill him
he's gonna walk in here anyway sleep let
me sleep yes yes yes
put your lights on the shulker yeah okay
[Music]
I
accept this offer
[Music]
water is my brand
you know what I'll bring
some water with me
I was saying anyway that some water
might be useful
okay
anything else I should leave
maybe the fireworks I don't know
[Music]
okay okay
you can't oh
[Music]
can't place water okay I forgot that one
oh well
but it's not gonna like explode on me
right like that creeper that's creeping
up on me
oh
that's all well that's better than the
Creeper following me over here and then
suddenly exploding in my [\h__\h] face
right now in this very spot
I was wondering if they were gonna
follow me
[Music]
okay uh
what the
what is this why did it speak
okay
um look at these beautiful coordinates
please
um we are where how do I
can you guys do you know I guess I have
to
the facing the the the the direction is
still the same right so I have to go
north anyway
because I've been going south all the
time
yeah I know I've been hearing the guests
too I want to get away from them really
quickly
looks like there's only a single layer
keeping you safe yeah
it's freaking me out
sounds
so if I
oh God
so if it in in in in in the Overworld
um I was currently like X like around
280 or something
um and I want to get to 187 doesn't mean
that it's gonna go down from 34 to
something like I don't know 30 or or
maybe 15 or
you can think about it above
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'm making Stone floors will prevent gas
from breaking them well no we don't have
Stones right now we don't have the
luxury of stones
but we'll be fine it'll be fun once I
make it so the the gas cannot see me
then I am basically non-existent also I
can't see it I keep on hearing it but I
can't see it
[Music]
well then let's make like a ceiling
uh
[Music]
it's completely make it into like a cave
kind of thing
right
[Music]
then
you won't know where you are when you
spawn when you go for here but yeah I
know that there's a fortress here if I
ever need a fortress and I know it's
there I'll make a little window
you know this this is the window
[Music]
and another window
okay and now we want to go up
[Music]
and yeah how how to go up okay okay wow
you can do this I hope though I'm kind
of scared what if I what if lab agreets
me
um
we have to take that risk
I guess
[Music]
[Applause]
how to mix there
[Music]
okay
let's take a while
what is this ocean sound it's actually
kind of relaxing it's like ASMR
[Music]
never heard this sound before in the
Never
[Music]
I don't know if I can keep up the
ceiling though
important diagonally upwards
diagonally I feel like we can adjust our
X position while we are up there
so right now I'll just go
straight up I would say
I'm just kind of like struggling and
like
building this right now
[Music]
I'll do your build stairs
upwards efficiently
[Music]
I like this
ah I should spiral
just Tower straight up
I guess I could make a tower straight up
and then make some ladders I feel like I
can easily make some Ladders because you
only need wood right
maybe I should do that that's way easier
[Music]
okay let's do that foreign
okay
um
is it easier though
because okay I would make like two rows
up up while I keep on jumping on one of
the rows I make a a whole Tower like
that
but then how do I get down
[Music]
that would that would mean I would need
the ladder already when I'm building the
tower no
before I bring my wings yeah
[Music]
okay
um
I don't know how to float
I always struggle with that like when it
comes to floating
the need to float
I would prefer to just make some ladder
really but because I have to make
ladders in the end anyway
well let's not make it with the fan
unless wait if I make a ladder with this
wood would it be pink
because that would be kind of freaking
cute
hey Bale wait if you jump from a very
high height on a hay bale do not take
damage
[Music]
okay no pink ladders
no you will oh okay that is so sad all
right I will um
make some ladders
do I need anything sorry about that guys
do I need anything besides um wood
[Music]
I'm ruining this I'm ruining this
beautiful
[Music]
Village sorry
sticks and planks okay
[Music]
I don't want to use the cherry trees
I don't know why I'm reluctant okay let
me let me use them
maybe
[Music]
unless there's a better option
holy [\h__\h] there's so many though I found
a really big one
[Music]
and thankfully these trees are also not
even that tall it seems usually
so you can just mine them from the
ground without leading to
like build yourself a little a little
codestal thingy
you know what my mom is gonna take care
of my cats again when I'm in Japan and
she yesterday we were on the phone and
she was like
suddenly I don't know where she's like
by the way
um can you please please please please
please please please please please
please please please let me access your
this time please please please can I use
your PC
and you want to know why oh [\h__\h] I just
it's just sad I can reach it easily it
turns out I can't
you wonder why
because like before I just let her use
like my laptop or my iPad always
no she doesn't want to stream but no she
really wants to play the new Diablo
on my PC she said that you know on her
PC she could never make it work and you
know it's also expensive I guess so
um
maybe even
even back
but yeah she's a big Diablo fan and I
guess she found a liking in the new
Diablo so far
[Music]
oh
which is good because I don't think she
played Diablo 3
I think Diablo 3 was generally like not
didn't have the best reception right
[Music]
here's Diablo heavy on Graphics yeah for
real
I mean she complained in higher quality
than I did because she doesn't have to
stream it
so she'll
foreign
[Music]
oh my God poor Pig
come on
so
a poor Pig
I should get out of here but I'm trying
to collect
um the sticks of the saplings
wow
[Music]
rip pinky free Hamza Liam but I didn't
take it I think
full inventory
[Music]
okay I think I'll go back Yahoo
to the Village
do you think that's enough material for
a ladder
for as many ladders as we need
[Music]
I don't know how much I get out of one
single block oh [\h__\h] I hate kids zombies
they suck
[Music]
um
destroy the ecosystem oh no oh no is
that
what
okay can we sleep now I think he's dead
now
another seven stick but makes multiple
from the recipe okay we'll see we'll see
otherwise I'll take some more wood from
the village
but we also need to make uh like a
building block thingy right
which is also
made out of wood
um crafting table
planks
mm-hmm
[Music]
here we go
and now ladder let me check this
what only from sticks oh okay
[Music]
dicks
oh they look so pretty they're so pink
[Music]
wow wow
okay that's a lot of sticks
[Music]
yeah
okay don't waste these beautiful
materials that's uh on it
64.64.
wait what no wait uh no it wasn't
ladders sorry I'm confused pork block
ladder
64.
okay that's not enough
we need
more 23
which sticks
[Music]
okay my inventory is so full I can't do
[\h__\h]
[Music]
um
a couple more
planks
[Music]
there's a show because there's somewhere
else wait
[Music]
leather
I keep on switching back and forth there
we go
wait wait there we go there we go
there we go now we're talking
what's on the ground okay shulker
I have more than enough you think so
okay
I'm gonna leave some stuff
like this
and the warm
okay going back let's build
too many
ah it's okay
[Music]
see me didn't see me
[Applause]
[Music]
didn't bring ah blueberry personally
charged shriek
h
Steph and she didn't
[Music]
damn
what the [\h__\h] she's fighting the warden
what the [\h__\h]
girl what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
my secret hole
why did that I didn't even see a creeper
on on my side where I was
chilly
where I was coming from
hmm
the sand yeah how is the sand intact
actually
yeah
so sand like safe from creeper blow ups
[Music]
I'm gonna do a parameter
on the other side perimeter was the
perimeter
[Music]
uh all the creeper blew up right there
so it didn't affect the sand
[Music]
I was standing on the obsidian okay but
I thought it like affects the
surrounding suit because it did affect
the ceiling didn't it
I went my speaking of my my wall is gone
[Music]
ah
a it's there go away guess
I'm almost gone
wait I wanna
wait wait wait wait wait wait no don't
make me teleport
no don't make me teleport I don't
teleport no no no no no no no
no I can't place the block
oh
[Music]
close portal so ow can I turn it off
dying I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying I'm
dying okay
[Music]
laugh if I get rid of one obsidian block
or what
[Music]
oh oh can I
um no I can't put it on there
you're cool
[Music]
except that one
yeah is the block gone
[Music]
stop laughing you little [\h__\h]
huh
please don't [\h__\h] it up again and we're
gonna make
the
stairs to heaven aka the normal world
and I'm thinking
[Music]
to build it in the smartest way possible
but the gas is like chilling over there
[\h__\h]
okay so we would do it like this
and I was thinking
like I
[Music]
um I'll like make blocks here make
myself higher you know what I mean but
behind me I'll also build the wall
higher okay
where is it where is it where is it
he gone right now
okay
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
he can stay away
please
is she trying to keep the village a
secret
I don't know no no not
why
why does it seem that way
[Music]
I don't think actually it isn't it like
isn't the worth of this like portal this
area that I'm creating even higher now
that we have another Fortress here
because the Fortress that we know the
closest Ian Fortress is like already
like farmed
like you know
Isn't it nice to have another one I
don't know what for but didn't we like
destroy some things that you could get
there normally
[Music]
it's very good yeah yeah I'm doing this
just for safety because that's I need to
go after the ceiling for my ice
track
to
make a meat
[Music]
scary
safety first I I I I'm scared that when
when if I see the gas and I suddenly
will get the jump scare especially if it
shoots me and then I don't know where to
go and I fall down and I die
[Music]
[Applause]
and even if I build myself a ceiling
when it already saw me and
that's what I'm talking about it's gonna
burn
[Laughter]
oh yeah but still yeah but still ah foxy
I panicked I panicked immediately I knew
I would panic
thank God there was a Blog here I can
make that jump
come on
come on wait I have ah I have feather
falling boots
feather falling golden boots in in the
sugar would that help me when I fall
down
that would help me wouldn't it
surviving really well actually thank you
thank you me the days of me dying
[Music]
what why
oh
[Music]
how deep am I what 67
.
I need to go higher I'm fine oh my God
um
that sucks I really liked the way that
you know you go out and you see the
cherry blossoms immediately
why does it have to be like those
oh man
now you come out and you see this
just
okay
um now I have to go out
of God I have so many ladders aren't we
happy about the ladders now
break the portal break this portal
[Music]
oh
but then how do I get
wait but then and then go for my old
portal
are you sure about this
let's let's first see where we're
um gonna end up at um
[Music]
very smart very smart digging straight
up very smart very smart
foreign
[Music]
for sure
and no I don't want to think anymore
but the ladders the ladders don't the
ladders
what if I go down and then I build the
ladder
[Music]
why is it so why are we so low
should I break the portal first that's
what the poems for true
okay I'll break it
[Music]
[\h__\h] now I have to now I have to go up
again
[Music]
thank you
Harvest obsidian oh
well
foreign
wait isn't this like a way of endlessly
producing more obsidian
if my other portal still exists
elsewhere
oh it is
oh my God
[Music]
that's it are the developers aware of
this loophole
[Music]
it's not right yeah then I don't really
need to mine Deceiver
enough obsidian
I should build a whole house out of the
obsidian oh this is terrifying
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] am I am I like in a
mountain what if I'm in a mountain and I
have to take like 5 million blocks up
[Music]
hard to say
foreign
[Music]
okay wait a second guys we don't need
this anymore do we
let's talk about one topic Sun cream so
I went to the pool swim swim today
and I noticed I don't I
feel like I have some cream somewhere
still but I didn't find any okay
so I went to buy some and the store only
had one
because it was a supermarket they don't
have much variety
and I didn't look at the price because
it's just like a Nivea
30 SPF Sun cream I was like I mean how
expensive can it be I I know that yeah
Sun cream sunscreens cream
can get expensive especially if you buy
a really
High SPF one
but like hit I take it I bring it to the
counter
and then the girl that checks me out
she's like
kind of confused like she offers me to
not buy it because I think she was also
confused by the price because I I bought
three things I bought some potato chips
and a bottle of iced tea
and the cream and it came out as like 30
bucks or so
and then she's like wait what what
I think she she every time I see her she
always looks kind of confused because I
think she's not wearing glasses even
though she should
[Music]
um and she was kind of confused why with
these tiny items I get I I have to pay
so much and the moment she mentioned it
you know I didn't really listen to what
the the total came out to but she she
was like this can't be right this can't
be right do you wanna like maybe the
price must be wrong do you want to maybe
like give it back take it I can I can
take it back I'm like eh wait wait
you're right this is kind of a crazy
price
is it like written wrong
what is this snow
no
no why snow I'm supposed to be in the
Cherry Blossom by
[Music]
you know
that's a dollar for SPF exactly
[Music]
if I mind this will it fall on me I'm
scared
[Music]
and we need to coordinates with the OG
again yeah
snow next to the Village maybe uh maybe
maybe we're not that but it's a gravity
block
it better be it better be
[Applause]
okay what was I saying oh yeah so I was
really confused we were both confused
and I thought I found yeah there must be
a mistake like maybe they have the price
wrong in the system ah
[Music]
but which way is uh
what no I saw this with I'm in
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
dad
ah what what the heck
down Dig Down
[Music]
I'm not gonna die wait where's down
where's down where's down where's down
I'm I'm always down where's down where's
down where am I where am I where am I
where is down
I'm safe I'm safe I think I'm safe
[Laughter]
why
ah this is so scary I was outside of the
snow
[Music]
I wish to get one then we'll place this
here it will keep me safe
why Mom
[Music]
please let me go
powder snow what will every step
that I take be like that so I better
make myself a pair
[Music]
leather shoes or a leather shoes good
against all the Snowman
[Music]
yes oh see how smart I am no it's
raining
[Music]
you can
where is the village
[Music]
I get a bit higher I I could see it
maybe wait no this is a tiny piece of
the Cherry
[Music]
anyway that's
maybe that way
do I have to go south or north or
346. let's get closer to like 200 maybe
I don't know and we didn't see it if
that's the same Village is it
[Music]
is
just the right way
[Music]
oh yeah it looks like the the other side
of the village yeah I see my shelter
boxes okay
[Music]
such annoying like sudden incidents
we did
[Music]
should I bring something here in
particular
[Music]
I think I'll make some more
[Applause]
we wanted content yep I am getting that
sounds so simple to go somewhere get
some blocks and go back but no no it's
not
not simple at all
wait did I
um
okay
ah
here take this
[Music]
is our portal still there that's the
important question yes
yes sir
at least one good message yeah anyway so
it turns out the price was real like she
called the colleague
to go with me to the product to check
you know if the product was written uh
differently
yeah I defend the falling boots wait
this will now bring me back to the real
portal right
will it
[Music]
better
yep
um um so then the price on the actual
sign was the same I'm like kind of like
like genuinely shocked it's so expensive
but the the both of them were so nice
and then I think the
um the other one was it was the superior
of the girl and at the checkout
and he just you know was like sorry this
is it but if you want I'll give you like
25 off of the price and I'm like hey yo
what
what that's so nice thank you I'll take
that
I will take that
[Music]
yeah how can it be so crazy expensive
pretty SPF is nothing that doesn't even
help me from
[Music]
um
fending off a sunburn it doesn't even
work for me
I need like 60s
[Music]
yeah and it was Nivea like Nivea it's
not Mommy I feel like you know all the
other creams are not expensive it's just
I guess only the sun why is Sun cream so
I'm so expensive that just
how expensive can it be to create that
huh and it keeps us from not getting
skin cancer so can you please make it
affordable thank you
[Music]
what today actually
I am interested now now that I'm talking
about it what is in there
compared to other creams that keeps the
sunburn away
what magical thing is in there
so what is it
diamonds
gold flakes
obsidian yeah like just bullshitting me
so far now what blocks the UV
iron
[Music]
Google it I don't know who to believe
everybody says something different
check
[Music]
check what makes sunscreen
um
keep uh work there it is what makes
sunscreen work
physical sunscreen contains physical UV
filters that reflect block the sun's
Rays before they penetrate the skin
while chemical sunscreens contain this
is what we're talking about right
contain organic compounds that transform
UV rays into heat
uh okay that sounds ridiculously
um confusing let me Google in German
pass
is in Sun and cream
[Music]
loosely
organizations
what are the UV filters made out of
yep
well I don't know this doesn't really
help me I'm speaking of Oktoberfest
[Music]
sink and titanium oh
so interesting that that works like that
I'm just stalling because I'm scared of
the gas
[Music]
wait
okay okay
how do I how do I go back okay you see
you see here no but I also didn't really
see him before last time and then he
just suddenly appeared and shot me
that little [\h__\h]
at least we the only reason we went back
and and were in that Bamboozled
situation was because I wanted to
feather falling booths right and now we
have them and now falling down shouldn't
be too painful right I would survive a
big fall hopefully
[Music]
I don't know
the higher you go the harder for him to
seal really so
we just gotta quickly reach the ceiling
I thought that was him
[Applause]
it looks like him
now he's close okay there he is and go
down go down go down leave them to see
me see me he didn't see me he didn't see
me he didn't see me go away go away go
away
pre-recorded why would you think it's
pretty recording it
[Music]
oh
well didn't hurt that much
there's something that looked like the
ceiling there by the way
[Music]
but we'll probably have to dig a little
bit more even there because then there's
a
the Soul Sand but that's not the ceiling
really oh God it's still very far
[Music]
yummy oh come on
I'm so bad with ladders
[Music]
I know
wait
[Music]
crouching the ladder to stay still okay
second row of ladders
Maybe
one more ladder
[Music]
foreign
that one topic I'm just shocked by how
expensive it is I ended up buying it and
I uh put it on my body but I hope I'm
not getting a sunburn from it I also put
on after sun so sunscreen and after sun
both
[Music]
I feel like I'm gonna be fine yeah
looking at my arms now I feel like
usually when I get a sunburn by now I
would already see it
[Music]
and I don't
[Applause]
save this style
okay
[Music]
how about coming out of the Soul Sand
suddenly
it better not I don't think there was
like
foreign
[Music]
he's above me oh I see the the other
ceiling the ceiling above the ceiling so
progress
[Music]
sheesh
ceiling section
I'm too scared to look above
I want to wear like an umbrella or
something
oh okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
I think an umbrella would help me I want
umbrellas in Minecraft
something to Shield you from the Gaze of
such enemies
I want to hurt you
ah
[Applause]
get on it Mojo
[Music]
hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
so where was he is moving did you see
him
I don't see him
[Music]
no oh that almost killed me
where'd you go
[Music]
I wish I could put something there that
would like
[Music]
you know bounce me off maybe jelly or
something like that
a bed bed Works no wait
Are you seriously asking for me to put a
bed
in the Never
are you you you you know ah ah just okay
you can do it as long as you don't right
click it
foreign
I don't know
please please have mercy on my soul oh
[Music]
what did he despawn
he was he was going that way
suddenly right behind me no no no no no
God damn it
I'm just not shaking please leave me
alone
what I mean with that I'm just you know
scared
ceiling ceiling's getting closer
[Music]
okay next tangent
um oh yeah shoulder step
I posted it on Twitter
[Music]
see it where is this [\h__\h] I should kill
him
to him
so maybe you saw on Twitter guys but uh
yeah I I I bought this like here they
call it taka band
I mean there's also a lesson
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's fancy word
called elastic band this means it's a
elastic nice reactions
done you should add the floor here for
now what do you mean oh for jumping down
maybe yeah on the side
good idea
no he's aiming very well but he he
shoots at the point where I'm standing
on top so
if I jump down if I wouldn't jump down
he would totally get me
[Music]
here is a level okay
while they're saying oh yeah I bought
one of these
these uh they're they're not made out of
latex but they are kind of like latex
really thin strips of latex-ish uh
something oh I'm running out of material
[Music]
um
and the reason I bought them is because
I remember
that being really really
useful like it actually easy to use
when I had physical therapy in Austria
several times before but then in this
one physical therapy they use these
these latex
tape thingies
to stretch in many many ways you can
like make it easier to stretch like
every part of your body
seemingly
and also I noticed when I was using it
yesterday
[Music]
not just stretching it it literally
really needs some some muscle
so you can build muscle with it too
while stretching now is the gascon
somewhere it's always there we cannot
let our guard down
yeah and it has like it came in five
different variations
um depending on the color
some are even like yep
um stronger
stronger than others [\h__\h]
that we're more like difficult to pull
and stretch than the others and it also
came with a little booklet that has like
instructions on how to
uh use it what kind of stretchings you
can do and which part it will help but
the reason I really posted it on Twitter
was because of the typo did you guys
even notice the typo I wanted to roast
the booklet
[Music]
oh
cause on top of the booklet on the cover
uh
yeah I'm still there
we didn't shoot this time
[Music]
there we go yeah yeah Quick stats
I'm in
with these kind of things that you get
from Amazon so often will there be
um typos yeah but I mean come on on the
cover
foreign
[Music]
come on
I was reading a little bit for you to
find more typos and there were more
typos inside but like
it's like sometimes they write the same
word right and then they write it wrong
what's what's going on there huh
that the person who wrote or like
translated the manual because there's so
many languages just type it all by hand
but like speed typing I try to finish it
in like
five minutes
how else could you make so many typos
of course no quality check but I get
that because I I'm I assume it's a sweet
product so
there's no no typos and though no one to
check the typos
anyway I'm really again kind of out of
materials so but I'll pick up the Soul
Sand now I guess
is this the ceiling now how do you isn't
there like a a set ceiling like always
at the same Block in the Never
foreign
ing is a dying job yes saddling
are six pretty high
128.
or 19. please no lava please don't lava
please no Lava that would [\h__\h] me up
that would [\h__\h] me um
we're safe from the gasp now
okay
nice window here I'm gonna close it up
[Music]
there's no way he'll see me now
at least I can mind this with my
um ah never mind
I can mind this move my shovel I was
saying but now I need my pickaxe that'll
be fun
we'll be fine
[Music]
if I were to mine some um what's it
called again
[Music]
the stuff you get in the never the not
not the first Marine the quartz
I could get exp from that right
[Music]
yeah maybe I should go look for some but
this area I don't know it scares me
scares me
okay
but wait I have one diamond
I could re repair it oh see we reached
the ceiling reach the ceiling
okay okay okay okay let's make like a
little base to stand on right
um
[Music]
and decide which direction we're going
wait which direction are we going
North right in any case North
[Music]
um
a little bit less X as well but hmm
I would need Stone pickaxes where I am
ah
what's the chord I don't really know I
don't really know actually if
you don't think I ever took a
screenshot
[Music]
man
I I I wanted to meet so I I kind of have
to get it right here
when I start the tunnel
[Music]
I'll just go a few steps over here I
mean it it could work if Kaila went to
the beginning of the tunnel and told me
the X right
if she just tells me the X
and maybe also the why although the Y
should not make a big difference
[Music]
it's busy though isn't she and you guys
said she wasn't streaming but surely
she's streaming now right
yeah she's exploring really far
[Music]
and die and dig from the other end
um
[Music]
yeah I can explain that to her but
um
don't don't worry
it's not streaming why would she do
stuff like that when she's not streaming
that's streaming content
[Music]
yeah my respawn is in the village now
um
tell me [\h__\h]
really
[Music]
do you wanna we see
oh clink
[Music]
hi lion oh she almost makes me want to
adopt her as a whole no Tony
ah where could we see
I'm okay I'm in
I am in Japanese BC
server
[Music]
is she a real one she's the real one
I'll explain everything to her
I have confidence in getting her to the
beginning of my eyes path who knows
maybe somebody
maybe she she should know where you know
my house and in a house Etc is right she
probably at some point saw it before
I'm sure someone took her there before
maybe like in a tour
[Music]
I I I I don't I I could really use a
little bit of help I am so sorry to
trouble you but you can't hear her one
second I'm streaming by the way as you
may know
um here wait a minute
what happened what happened
um so I I'm on the en server so first of
all can you make your way to the Ian
server oh okay okay hold on don't don't
worry you can take your time take your
time it's okay I I can just die it's
okay okay well done yeah yeah okay
trying to kill the warden outside of a
stream
oh no no no no I'm I'm not I'm not
trying to kill the word
I'm hunting for the trims the new items
in Minecraft the update one
ones
um
they have like 16 dreams
and I was like already
knife done and I have done on stream
like uh nine of it I think eight eight
eight eight eight of it and then I kind
of do yeah like
yeah you know um there's I I feel like I
just cannot do it like all on stream
because it's gonna be like
unlimited stream of finding yeah I I
actually never heard of the armor trim
before so I didn't know what you were
talking yeah it's a it's a new update
it's really new it's really new okay
well done okay so let me explain you my
situation so okay I'm gonna answer it
and I put like a long time ago I built
in the never in our main like never
portal Place uh we I built an ice path
an ice
rail before to get to the Mesa biome
okay yeah and uh that's a long time ago
but today I wanted to find the Sakura uh
and so for that I I thought okay I'll
use my eyes track and I'll go even
further and then I continue to extend
the ice path and now I'm basically like
really really far away and trying to
build the ice path from the very very
other side where I'm far away and then
make it meet you know I wanted to meet
paps so so so so right now I'm in the
never and I think I'm kind of like like
somewhat close to the ex
um you know XYZ I'm I think I'm close to
the X path where I should be but I'm not
sure where exactly I needed to be exact
so that the two sides meet you know what
I mean
oh actually there is a calculator about
the nether portal in the Overworld oh
yeah but I'm I'm already in the never
and the other side is also than ever I
just need the the path to me so for that
I would ask you to go to the beginning
of my ice road because I'm not in the
ending of it and just tell me the X okay
okay okay sure sure do you know where
our portal is our never portal
uh not really but I can I can try okay
it's okay I can explain though
um do you know where my and Ina and
gouda and all our houses yeah I think I
think I kinda remember but it's okay if
you take the uh you know you spawn
somewhere and then there's a train right
that goes through muna's legs and
Ollie's legs
take that and then you will be in the
main myth area that's where the nether
portal is
okay here uh
uh take your talent take your time
how are you doing today Kyla
fine just playing games the whole thing
yeah nothing to do what time is it Kayla
almost two
almost two yeah
okay time
where are you right now keep me updated
uh hold on I'm still
um
trying to put all of my items
yeah in the and their chest take your
time can you are you good at
multitasking yeah yeah yeah okay so when
I just keep talking you you can still do
the things yeah okay I can't
what do you mean like you you talk with
your viewers too right like yeah
and making sentences when I'm playing
Minecraft and doing things than when I'm
not playing Minecraft and doing things
nah you're lying you're you're lying
you're you're good at it
was from what
what's interrupting myself and losing
track and I'm like where would I well
look
I make no sense really
okay I'm just I will just die I'm trying
to find a way to die um okay yeah the
gas was interrupting me that's the truth
[Music]
where should I die
anyway everywhere is a good place to die
no no I'll just I'll just call the
warden again hold on
here
yeah Lord and I'm here
is like so slow faster
oh I want to meet more than two sometime
mm-hmm so wait there's there's armor
trims where the warden is yeah the
ancient city the armor trims are they
all in the ancient city no no no no
they're they're like 16 right so it's
like 10 different no no no
um eight different places eight probably
I don't know if I don't miscount okay
like what are other places for example
okay uh the ocean Monument the sinking
ship yeah and then the
the desert temple
places
yeah interest but the ocean Monument one
you need to defeat the what is that the
Elder
Guardian the big one the big creature
one yeah and then it will drop newly
spawned uh new new spawned chunks right
yeah yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
Kyla is dead
okay uh R.I.P
I'm taking all of my items first today
and this update was I mean decently big
with the ancient yeah you you should do
like exactly I mean if you if you really
love to explore you can do that like
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's my main thing
in Minecraft I'm so bored when I have to
build something that's for me
that's why
yeah yeah so my next plan is after after
I'm done with my Sakura cherry blossom
thing I want to check out the ancient
the ruins the ancient ruins
Kyla doesn't really build either I guess
so you're more of an Explorer too
I usually build off shrimp though
so that I can focus
when there's a new update somewhere in
maybe half a year or so I don't know how
long it takes but if there's a new
update we go explore together okay okay
we go together
then you can go elsewhere but keep one
thing that we can go together okay okay
okay
sure right away don't worry I'll do it
right away with you
if he also enjoy exploring so much and
you know I always check out these things
alone but it would be nice to go with
someone
hey let's go
okay
I'm heading out to the en portal oh okay
um
and then I need to go to the portal the
nether portal like the general one right
uh yeah it's like in the middle of the
myth houses like across in a house and
so on
so after you after you write the the
little train through all these big Muna
and Ollie and Ahmed figures you go past
the big kfp like the the Rainbow Road
and the kfp
and then and then you should already
kind of see the portal you just go
straight
okay hold on
um the pants to express right that was
the name The Punchy Express
hmm
is this the first time that we're like
one-on-one
kinda right yeah kinda in the Stream
yeah yeah on stream
this one Kayla and kiwawa
[Music]
you're the only one that got my name
like correctly what do you mean yeah the
other is like Kayla
yeah
but I mean it's fine like it's just like
kind of surprising yeah yeah I get that
though because like for me it's not as a
big difference is your name I think but
for me everybody calls me Kiara Kiara
like they say it's so English but I
always just say my own name is Kiara
like Japanese yeah yeah yeah
so that's like why I also pronounce your
name you know more Japanese kailan
you know
Kayla yeah that's right yeah
a lot of people call me Kayla Kalin Kyle
and Kyle Kayla but you yourself you call
yourself Kyla
yeah uh no usually the ID members gonna
just call me Ella instead of that's so
cute but when you say yeah full name
when you say the full name oh yeah yeah
um
I'm in the nether already yeah
so you spawn in this little like fenced
area right
yep yep yep then you walk out the fence
and you turn left immediately okay turn
left turn left steps
first okay go up go up up okay
eventually you will reach the top okay
just go up the stairs right yeah
you are so fast Kyla
okay and then oh yes the eyes you see
that nice okay now look I don't know if
it matters it probably doesn't matter
but look look to the look towards the
eyes and then tell me your coordinates
oh just this one yeah
there's a boat with big lens is that
intentional no not really but ignore
okay okay so you want the coordinates
like um x y z in uh no I mean um where
should I stand like besides the fence or
in front of the ice I think it's fine
okay okay so it's um 31 oh
uh do you need the Y yeah let's get them
all 120 120 and minus 53. minus 53.
okay you are an absolute Angel oh wait
ah okay never mind sorry one more thing
can you is there a chest somewhere there
yeah with a boat inside yes yes a boat
yeah can you take the boat and go all
the way to the end of the it's really
fast don't worry okay just quickly go to
the other side because actually at the
end of the Ice Road
um when you get off I built like a
continuation an extension
um you have to get off the boat once and
go to the right side there's a a second
path that one is probably better if I
get the chords for that one
hold on
[Music]
um
do you need anything like
shelter chest or anything because
I have
um all I need I just need to make the
connection from the ice road but I'm
like really far away
[Music]
but the only way she could give it to me
is if she left the never and then flew
over on her own found me here because
there's no connection yet guys
she doesn't need to no no no no but I
mean
um
I mean a pickaxe would be nice but no no
no no no
[Music]
no no
I mean I mean can you can you continue
working with other pancakes yeah my
problem is my both of my pickaxes are
pretty dead and I need to make a really
long tunnel
that's why hold on I'll figure that out
I can give you my outside coordinates
but then it would take you ages to read
here to reach here I mean I mean you
have made like the
what is that the nether portal right
yeah but if you uh
well yeah yeah yeah there is a portal
where that is relatively close to where
I am I guess yeah
wait hold on this one
wait I have already
arrived and then there's like an
intersection yeah
where should I go after the eyes did you
get the end you got off of the boat once
right yeah and then there's like stairs
don't go down go right I think on the
same height there's a continuation okay
continue okay you saw
yeah I continue speed speed speed speed
speed
do you even have a pickaxe that you can
give me right now
um I I I can I can I can just give you
mine it's okay okay I'll give it back to
you though
I think I think I have fit but hold on
hold on I'll I'll yeah I'll check if you
don't have it then it's better to go
back now than afterwards yeah I mean
yeah right do you have enough fireworks
because it took me a couple of fireworks
the fire oh yeah yeah the portal to
where I am
I
oh okay oh it's okay it's okay uh all
good all good I'll get all the no
worries no worries
uh this one
I should have bring
[Music]
okay this one this one
okay so I got from the
portal you should what did I see when I
got I I think I I have a screenshot of
what I saw just to confirm if when you
get out of the portal I I can confirm
with you the coordinates that you should
have
okay so I go out from the portal
okay okay and then it should be 187
yep 71 and 12 000 something yep okay
okay okay now I go outside of my portal
and I tell you my Overworld coordinates
yeah
it's
um okay do you have to probably write
this down it's quite a lot
I mean you can
just
type it on game problem okay it's good
oh my God genius it's gonna be easier
okay genius it's uh 259.
all right now and you will notice when
you get in the area there is a village
with uh with lots of uh cherry blossom
trees
okay and it's very beautiful
okay okay so but actually you have to go
south mostly
um you're moving to that place no I am
here right now and then I mean I mean as
in you're gonna build whatever you're
gonna do after this there I'm not gonna
live here but I'm just building a
connection so that you know we can mine
I'm probably gonna be the only one using
it but you can always have uh cherry
blossom trees here oh yeah if someone
needs a lot of cherry blossom trees then
you can come here you know you know how
everybody uses like the Japanese server
and the resource server and all that but
I I'm a little bit stubborn and I want
to continue using the en server and find
things on my own not use things that
people already found so I try to find my
own resources you know what I mean okay
okay yeah I mean
that's kind of great yeah thank you did
you go out to find your own cherry
blossom bayomi yet or not yet
uh yeah because I pass it through like
several of it right because I
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you can't even
looking for it
oh no there is like oh wait there is
like a jack picks here
what so if you so if you um trying to
find ancient city right you need to find
like Jack pics
[Music]
yes there's gonna be like probably
ancient city there I just passed through
it check check picks
Jack picks
pics check
check okay
um
is that what I found guys when I was
exploring today because I found some
really really really really really high
mountains yeah the mountains I've ever
seen yeah I think the en server got a
lot of
high high mountains yeah but you gotta
go really far away
but yeah I found something like that
this is kind of interesting that was
that was jacked Peaks really yeah okay
then I know where to go next time yeah
to explore
but just be careful
wow is it dangerous
uh when you I mean not oh there's a
woodland Mansion here what I missed that
yeah
there's also trims in the Woodland
mansion by the way oh
nice
why I found everything when I'm when
when I'm not really did it right now I
know
it took me quite a while to find the
Sakura today oh me hold on hold on do
you want oh let me let me just take a
screenshot of the Woodland Mansion so
that probably later on I can hand you
over the coordinates okay I might have
explored one before but maybe I'll go
again yeah because you need the trims
right like let's say because that I
guess is a new chunk probably most
likely
yeah and then this one is close just
besides of the Woodland Mansion there's
like a frozen picks so maybe there is
like um engine cd2 there
Oneness
wow Jack picks oh no
maybe you're looking at the same ones
that I saw the jacked Peaks yeah
now that you're coming I'll take my I'll
take these boxes with me
shulker boxes that's cool
[Music]
where I am right now
ten thousand more
well be careful when you fly not that
you like Bonk into something
accidentally
okay let's do some some some Chit Chat
while you're on your way have you ever
been to Japan Kyla
yes
but it's like
um just a vacation with like a tour
leader and something like that you went
with a tour
how was it tell me about it
I don't know like joining a tour usually
just kind of tiring
but yeah
wait did I forget to ask about the
second tunnel chords did I
wait
maybe I did
do you really need it because it's kind
of snow it's okay later later yeah you
have to go back anyway yeah yeah yeah we
just have to wait a bit a little bit
longer it's okay
anyway yeah yeah and please continue
to The Hobbit homes in New Zealand
yeah
yeah what what what what the life [\h__\h]
what what the life that told you
didn't they sometimes already before the
pandemic of course what why why why why
why why why why what did you do you do
you love Lord of the Rings as much as I
do oh my God that's the question
actually
what was the answer
guys can I just
teleport somewhere oh my god of the
Rings why did you go there
yeah because of that the same reason the
tour just brought me there and I hi
you actually went just to see New
Zealand and that was the part of the
tour yeah yeah part of the tour oh my
God and then you saw The Hobbit holes
and it didn't make you want to watch the
movie
know that the tour in the bus right they
kind of um
play The Lord of the Rings movies but I
think I think I think I think yeah I
think I think that's because if you
don't watch it properly you better not
watch it at all in them yeah I know I
know I get it I get it no it's okay no
worries I just I just slept okay yeah so
so all good all good
come on
coffee
of course of course but since I got no
reference about it probably I just like
ha ha ha like that but but it's cool
it's really cool it's cute it's cool
yeah and where else wait the the New
Zealand tour wasn't part of some kind of
worldwide tour where Japan was also part
of it was it
why do you always go on tours I've never
been to a tour like that before I just
traveled
it's because I'm like I mean my parents
like
um yeah my parents so I just like yeah
okay yeah okay
so wait was that was the the trip the
idea of your parents originally
going to New Zealand was there any idea
uh because they have this kind of like
you know they they want to like um just
go as many countries as possible before
they probably cannot walk you know like
yeah and then they took you as well
wait that's nice
but it's like oh there's outposts here
I'll just take the screen yeah I'll take
off the screenshot and we'll hand over
it all of it for you thank you thank you
yeah because there is also trims in
Outpost ah okay wow
hey it's like a schnitzel yacht in
German
what's it in English again uh
uh
it's called again
you guys tell me
what is that what is that scavenger hunt
yeah that's fun let's look at the hunt
in if it's your Han do you know what
scavenger hunt is
I'll tell you oh my God I can teach you
something
I know it like in the Indonesian maybe I
don't know probably there's an
Indonesian word
um it's like when normally you do it as
a child I would say you
um get like a uh you need to find
something
so oh God how do you even explain that
how do I explain that how do I explain
that hey there is also a Sakura biome in
the 18 000.
money
yeah you get a list of items to find and
then you have to find them you know so
like in Minecraft now this trims oh
yeah as a child I think maybe maybe you
even did it before
it's like a fun children party event
[Music]
um
what's a [\h__\h] 18 000 and you were
just going straight right now right not
really I think oh no yeah no no why not
it would be faster if you just go
straight
because because it's like a habit yeah
of getting distracted with all of the
things
yeah
I was trying purposefully to just go
straight because I wanted to make the
tunnel easier to connect you know I
don't want to have any Curves in the
tunnel I just want the tunnel to go
straight straight straight
place to go to go make it straight and
you get out of the tunnel and then you
have Sakura
yeah okay I'm 19
000. okay like if you if you had to
build something and you need Sakura now
you know you can come here and use my
Sakura sure
yeah okay I mean I know where it is
right now right so I'm gonna go okay
we have a customer
it's free of course
wow Kyla got the permission to use the
resource from E and this is kinda this
is I don't know if this is kind of good
or kind of bad because
because
actually right I was like trying to oh
myself for like the resources from the
Ian well as long as you don't take 50 uh
electrons
hello
then we're good don't worry how can I
stop like how wow
oh by the way I'm sorry I just
disconnected for the sleeping part and I
lost the accordions I'm in 20 000
already what is the X
wait I read it again the whole thing
these these
okay okay two five two five nine two
five nine okay that way
where are you now
000. oh I'm close I'm close I'm pretty
close now yeah
I'm closed let me stand on top okay
then
oh and with open arms
[Music]
I think I can I can hear you from
from the sky yeah I think yeah
[Applause]
[Laughter]
um
you can hear me from Indonesia
yeah
okay
if next time I I come to Austria in
Austria oh don't go on the tour just go
yeah yeah I'll make sure that I call you
hello hello
tell me all the countries you've been to
before because you've been to so many
apparently
ah
I think
the one religion that I haven't
gone to is I think
only America oh
well where in Europe have you been
oh the the general one like Paris
um okay okay um I've gone to West Europe
um um
um
um yeah that part of area the East one
not really have you been to Germany
in Germany yes but I kind of forgot like
what what a tourist destination I was
there Berlin
I think I think have you been to Austria
Austria oh no I really need to uh I
don't know somebody just made me know
because yeah when when we when we went
to like uh when we go to a tour like
that right we we went to like a lot of
places like oh was it a Europe tour like
a general yeah
the West Europe tour and the South
Europe nice did you go to Spain
yeah did you go to the Netherlands
yeah true true did you go to the to
Hungary
yes yes yes yes yes fine did you go to
Italy
of course of course did you go to
Switzerland
of course we went to every
day except Austria because I think
Australia also but I kind of just like I
just forgot you know like I really need
to check the itinerary yeah
yeah I need to know of course of course
yeah yeah
London of course London yeah check
check um maybe not I think once yeah I
think
I think once yeah whoa did you go
because I don't know can I remember some
more European countries
did you go to
[Music]
um
hey there's the village yeah
wait wait what where should I go um I
mean maybe I'm in front of the portal hi
hello
okay
[Music]
oh my God Kyla you know what
you know I used to play MMORPGs back in
the day all the time and right now the
moment I saw you I got this feeling of
like holy [\h__\h] this is like a high level
player who's like 50 letters above me
that's that's the vibe you're giving off
if you look look at this look at this
you you see the dress
oh yeah that's the yeah I just wanted I
just want to look so high level to me
yeah that's the trim you got the
Austrian flag on your head the Austrian
flag red let's go
thank you so much for coming
it's so it's almost night there is no
creeper here better with problems and
there are some
isn't this place so pretty Kyla I
already took some trees
pretty Ryan I'm gonna sleep over here on
my floating bed I will somehow find
where is my bed I don't know or maybe I
can just fix it it's okay
easier
with NHS this was actually also a
problem I had that I left my under chest
uh what do you want and you have to self
watch
um
you have the silk touch the cakes yeah I
have it but it's like pretty much broken
now
um
because I'm building the tunnel yeah
because if you want to take the under
chest you need to still touch right yeah
yeah yeah I have that but no worries I I
don't need anything from the interest
either I think I just I just need a
fresh pickaxe maybe oh okay
beings
I wonder what she got
the big what the okay Kyle I have in her
and the chest
my workshop looks empty
fireworks show
nothing inside
she's just imagining it
actually actually
I could repair my own pickaxes probably
because I have some diamonds in my under
chest
all that done done done because because
right now right in the in the updates
you really need the diamonds for sure oh
okay yeah you really need that oh
[Music]
maybe maybe
I think
will you use them to duplicate armor
trims so they're more important what the
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] already like I was already
struggling to gain more diamonds now you
need it for another thing
[Music]
and you there's still no way to make
like a diamond farm right
no way there's no way of doing that
then why oh why would they do that no
but I don't know how how much I really
need armor trims
I think I think
just take
my my pickaxe is also not just just take
this just take this just take just take
it and probably just rename it it's okay
I'll I'll make a new one for me twice I
will uh oh two thank you I'll bring it
back to you I'll find your house and
I'll bring it back or maybe you can just
drop it in the temple later on or maybe
no worries like because you're far away
find you we'll find each other you'll
probably be online the next time I play
Minecraft you'll be somewhere okay okay
okay sure sure
um you really don't need the energy
chest you sure about that
yeah
if you really need it I don't know do I
need something guys
oh I think now I don't
I decided to not fly back I decided to
make although
um
do you need food food no
no okay all good yeah guys should I fly
back with her
and go to the start of or should I or
should I just build from where I am now
where I started
I don't think I will fly back though
what I think I'll just die again
but then I don't know the coordinates
yeah I mean I can just die and then just
go back to that
um portal yeah it's a portal or the ice
it's gonna be easier
yeah I'll build from here then okay
because I already started anyway kind of
I'll just leave the Ender Chest here
then okay
I think that'll be useful for the future
anyway
so if you ever need to Blossom stuff
come here
because I will be the only one using it
probably
oh
you look so cute without your armor
what I'm cool not yet
no I know okay where can I die here I
can kill you
oh yeah it's an honor to be killed by me
right uh of course yes
um
sure you do not have anything else
firework all good
um
yeah now I don't need the firework
anymore but they're in the in the chest
anyway
okay uh
okay then
anything else no no have you ever seen
powder snow before in the game
the one that um that one kills you yeah
the one that kills something yeah yeah
some close by oh in case you want to die
I love how this is it is it that one
like in front of it yeah yeah that's it
that's it do you want to die by powder
snow
not really like um it's gonna be painful
right it's also going to be painful to
have you stab you
uh
I don't know what what can I do um
ouch
[Music]
ouch no no I will I will die with this
oh I'll try oh yeah
this get this not gonna be painful right
um
well I have some painful experiences oh
no
that must have hurt
okay hold on
um and then I need to are you sure
you're human
yeah of course you died you left nobody
behind you just left you poof there was
no body
that's my soul hold on um where is the
the closest and richest in the Yen
Surfer there's one at the never portal
I don't know where exactly you are right
now are you in the I'm in front of the
what is this the temple
the spawn area is it the main spawn yeah
the spawner area yeah is there and it's
just there there probably is I just
don't know where
then maybe you take the train to the
nether portal because there there's a I
know there is an NHS there
or maybe I can just hold on I'll just go
to the
portal first to the news
okay okay
I'll go back into the never so what do
you need um the the the coordinates from
like before you left the never right
before
okay the end of the ice train
[Music]
by the way do you not like fantasy
movies
um
[Applause]
honestly I'm not really watch movies
though like it's not about fantasy movie
it's like General movies I just don't
watch movies I'm really sorry
all your free time with gaming
yeah
like that do you never do like Movie
watches for your members no I I I I I
did once I did once I tried but
every single time I watch movies I just
fall asleep so
are they all boring to you maybe you
just saw the wrong movie it's not really
not really but I feel like it's just
like you know sitting down and then like
just looking at the screen it's just
like um
not relaxing right I mean I understand
that when you watch a movie it's easy to
fall asleep once you know it's cozy
do you watch it when you're lying in bed
or not really I mean I mean um I have my
friends like um asking me to go to watch
movies I also fall asleep so um it's
just it's just I think I cannot because
I just cannot watch movies I think
[Music]
what about anime do you not watch anime
then
uh back then I watch anime with um my
siblings but it's not like the anime
that I want to watch too like it's just
like my siblings gonna say like hey this
one is a good anime and then I just who
do like um watch along with my siblings
yeah so it's like that
but right now
[Music]
I just played James
yeah
wow maybe you wouldn't fall asleep
during a movie if you properly get some
sleep before like eight hours and then
watch the movie it's not like that it's
not
[Music]
it's not it's not like that feeling that
you know a human usually falls asleep
when they're tired you know it's a sign
of being tired it's my defense no in my
defense
I've I've never fall asleep when I'm
playing games no matter how much I sleep
or how late
understandable don't that make sense
though because you're like focusing on a
task and for for movies it's easier to
fall asleep because you're not really
doing anything
but it it will be even easier when
you're actually when you're sleeping you
know
but I mean
I mean instead of watching movies
probably it's better for me to just
sleep
but you have to well my point was you
have to watch Lord of the Rings
that's that's what my child also said
about that like don't let Kiara know
that you haven't watched a Lord of the
Rings
so good really it's really really good
and especially that's why I was asking
if you like fantasy because fantasy like
in terms of fantasy the genre it's like
the top of the top
um
a lot of learning this is a great movie
I know but yeah yeah
um
[Music]
for you because you said it's made all
the Rings is not mid um
the so you can't even say what's your
favorite like genre
for movies yeah and shows TV shows and
anime
no I just I just don't watch
oh my God you can't even judge that
because oh my God yeah
[Music]
that's that's so interesting I've never
I don't know met a person like that
before who just I mean I guess I got a
lot of movie tickets because I
yeah you know like
um my my friends gonna be like hey watch
this movies this is like trending movies
okay okay okay okay and then I just left
like but I keep I keep all of the
tickets so that if if people ask me like
hey uh do you watch this and then I'm
gonna say like oh yeah yeah I watched
that yeah
yeah I I I I didn't know what happened
but I still keep all of the tickets
it's like it's like four tickets five
tickets per movie
no it's it counts no in pounds not if
you don't remember anything no no
unbelievable
so where are you right now
I'm in the portal
making the boats Kyla what's your
favorite food
I like bitter food bitters oh
do you like bitter food
well do you like it do you like that you
would bite into a into a lemon and enjoy
it just for fun bite into a lemon
yeah I mean why not but my favorite is
actually bitter bitter melon bitter
melon I don't know is that bitter melon
in Austria I don't know they're melon I
think the melon would only be bitter if
it's already like off
sour do you mean sour oh wait I know
lemon was Sour sorry yeah
but sometimes it's really sour you like
bitter food
dinner
[Music]
way better better is like damn that's
like like cough syrup is bitter and and
what else is better
but yeah but I mean not the cough syrup
yeah wait wait wait isn't um you know uh
what's it called
um
there's this fruit that always people
always put into like fruit bowls and all
that that's pretty bitter
um um
um it's like almost like an orange yeah
grapefruit grapefruit do you like
grapefruit
what grapefruit is not bitter yeah to me
it's bitter
what chat isn't it bitter
it's not sour
I think it's bitter
Griffin
tends to be like sweet and sour you know
all the people in chat saying it's
bitter but then a lot of people are also
confused and say it's sour you guys I
think we're both we're all confused
right now what's better and what's sour
but for me I feel like it's generally
bitter um
that's how no it's not sour we're not
talking about lemons anymore
[Music]
I haven't met any grapefruit there's
bitter what
wait so what food is bitter
bitter melon is bitter and then there's
like a papaya papaya leaves the papaya
flower I don't know if
um yeah that's bitter yeah that's really
bitter bitter amount oh that's gourd oh
yeah yeah
oh I hate gourd I think
wait what's Gordon German again gorgeous
there are a lot of uh bitter food bitter
bitter food bitter drinks and ID so yeah
just it's not just
I am in front of the pores also I cannot
go out right yeah no no leaving just
tell me uh the coordinates please in
front of the portal right yeah
I'll just write it
thank you
then okay
wait which portal you're in the never
right yeah the inside the nether right
not the Overworld yeah like on the ice
road in front of the live portal
mm-hmm yeah yeah yeah and then that's
what I need yeah that makes sense with
the 119 that makes sense
okay
oh you're the best thank you thank you
if you need anything just chat me you
know what I need I need to do another
collab with you sometime let's go the
Minecraft exploring collab it will be
fun
maybe we can uh how many trims do you
have by now
oh I think I think I'm gonna finish it
this week oh hey how many trims is
usually in one location
okay so
um there's like
um
one or two oh oh dear yeah because I was
gonna offer that we go together but if
we have to share one or two then I think
you you you can have you should you
should go alone
yeah yeah I mean but actually um if we
the stronghold gonna be can be like more
than one and then and then actually if I
have like the duplicate it's actually
fine too because the duplicate is like
kind of expensive we need eight diamonds
for each duplicate wow so yeah I mean
hmm I will always
be open for any yeah we'll go on an
adventure maybe not the trims but we'll
go on a different Adventure yeah we can
kill the warden together so of course
yeah
okay thank you
[Music]
I'll give you back the the pickaxes
sometime thank you it's okay no worries
good luck for your work
good night don't don't stay up too late
good good good what good afternoon is it
it's already half past nine pm here
okay okay then good night then again
[Music]
bye bye guys
oh that was nice nice talk I mean during
the whole time when we were talking uh
not I feel like I barely you know I
didn't do anything and we stayed in the
same spot
yeah but
we got the chorus
[Music]
um
so let me look at this 22 22 22.
oh this way it's going down so we'll
um go a little bit uh
this way
20 22 Yeah 22 22.
we'll go until we're at 22 and then we
go towards the dead and then we should
like literally arrive right in front of
our portal
hmm
22 22 22. oh
yeah so honestly the sacrament that I
found is like really
right where I needed to be hmm
pretty much perfect location
there's no ah now you don't hear it okay
I switched I switched the
Boom
the output there you go
okay
[Music]
uh 22 22 is here
and then uh which way though
[Music]
I need to run around a little bit here
in my chamber we need to get the 3 000
down right
that's going up this way okay so right
side
makes sense
this way right
and I had a four
wait we can even adjust I think it was
19 right so this height would be
yeah that's exactly
success
we can finally continue guys exciting
when she was standing in front of the
portal she was standing on the ice still
I think right
so I need one more level lower I think
[Music]
two
she was probably on the ice like
standing on the ice
so one more little about probably
oh I got raided I never got raided by
other whole life members
what the [\h__\h] oh my God wait is that the
first time that might be the first time
thank you Vesper
it might be the first time
one hello besties
oh thank you I am let me explain what
we're doing here
I started the stream preparing to go on
a journey to find a Sakura by Omi and
our en server
and then you know because I don't I mean
people already found it in our Japan and
resource but I don't care I want to find
my own because Adventure let's go and
then I uh flew no I first used
um an ice road to the neighbor that I
built a long time ago to find the Mesa
by Omi and then I went to the end of
that left no then I went a little bit
further I built an extension went out
and went to fly to find the circle of
biome on wings
and that took a while
finally found one then I realized oh I'm
out of fireworks so now I have to build
it from the other side so we were trying
the whole time to find the perfect
placement
uh where to you know build it from the
other side so that it will perfectly
meet the other end of the ice tunnel
that I created a million miles ago
because it's literally so far away
and I also brought a lot of those Sakura
stuff with me and we had like a one hour
okay maybe another maybe half an hour
Rescue Mission from Kyla
she
wait this is free tall
wait I need one more level taller yeah
akaila went and because she she went out
of her way to find where my tunnel is to
give me the coordinates
[Music]
um
what an angel
now we know where to go
[Music]
because she was the only one online they
know I'm I'm in Europe so normally when
I play Minecraft the only people who are
ever online is like
well at the end of my streams you know
sometimes you know maybe if I go really
long although this I don't think this
ever happened before fauna could be
online
and
[Music]
who else one two three four yeah
okay I put that I don't I don't remember
the last time that happened
so usually I'm always playing alone
but the longer I play
the higher the chances that I meet
someone
yeah yeah
[Music]
will be streaming or she won't and
she'll just be grinding her train in
Mings forever whatever
Indonesia she is the one you can rely on
she is
um I can't rhyme on that word
well that was pretty good it was pretty
good up to that point pretty good
Kylie used to stream at your time yeah
yeah her recent Minecraft streams I'm
glad she came back but her recent
Minecraft streams have also
been more aimed at any times right
so that's sad too Cali come back to play
Minecraft with me what is she even up to
also how far are we getting now I need
to I need to go to
a thousand
[Music]
no wait no it's not that's not too bad
right we need to go a thousand four
hundred blocks in that direction I think
he built a home she built you mean in
the in the Japan server because she
already has one a bunker in the Ian
server
hey yo what the [\h__\h] no I hate when this
happens
no
no problem no problem no problem no
problem
no problem
I hate when that happens
[Music]
okay okay okay
I've done this before why is there
another one of those idiots around here
[Music]
as long as I'm crouching I'm right I'm
safe right
[Music]
keep on crouching just keep on crouching
just keep on crouching
escape from Crouching
oh God oh God
[Music]
sometimes sometimes I'm not sure anymore
if I'm crouching or not but okay
turn around
I've done this before I've traversed the
never
I mean the
what's that called again where where
would you kill the Ender Dragon the
Ender
where's online the end yeah the end I've
traversed the end before successfully
this this is not something that can
scare me
eyes okay
closing it off hopefully this will not
happen too often
also I should play some torches I guess
I haven't placed any
[Music]
can't watch it's already closed don't
worry
[Music]
fixed it
servicing another centuries in the end
I don't know about that I mean
in the end you gotta be careful I mean
once you have the elytra
[Music]
then you fly around I mean you guys were
always like yeah be careful with that
when I stand I want to just fly over the
islands to find more electrons
you guys were so concerned about me
flying through but then I didn't like
off-screen once and I was fine I never
died I think
[Music]
more
okay
a bit more
crouching am I crouching I'm crutching
okay
yeah I honestly think it's it's more
scary to do it with like the the the
bridge technique
then doing it with
flying with an already existing elytra
the bridging freaks me out
I mean eventually you're kind of like in
a groove right
[Music]
and you just keep on placing one next to
another and it just all works out but
it's still [\h__\h] scary yeah flying is
kind of especially because yeah the
chances of bumping into a newly spawned
huge ass Mountain
like in the normal world
on normal land outside
chances are kind of low right because
the only thing you have is like these
big ships
and the rest is like pretty much mostly
flat there's no real mountains
four hours we aren't in Super Chat
tensions
pillows
what do you mean you think I normally
would read
super Chance by now
I don't know but
super trans we're pretty caught up but
uh I'll try to read them today as well
I don't know when
almost 10 p.m now we can still go on for
a while I wanna I wanna finish this
tunnel for sure
Nintendo diet okay let's talk about the
Nintendo diet yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
wait I should also get rid of the other
topic my topic memo
[Music]
talked about the shoulder stuff anyway I
didn't quite finish the topic but yeah I
got those I got those um I don't know do
you guys call it Tara bands in English
too is it is that just German because I
think the name is actually kind of uh
cool name
but that's I'm gonna use that and when I
was using it yesterday I tried to
remember how I used it during physical
therapy and it definitely felt like you
know I was using my muscles and all that
so resistance bands okay yeah
[Music]
I just stepped on it and pulled it up
and then I also
I just um wrapped it around my
the legs of my big ass massive dining
table because I didn't know what to wrap
it around what else and I just went into
like a set down
and I was like uh
I don't know what you call that position
like like I'm in the boat you know
um
yeah yeah
good stuff good stuff Ken recommend 10
out of 10 because like it doesn't even
take up any space and it makes all of
that like a lot easier and more
motivating
[Music]
in my opinion it's really helpful it
takes up no space so I'm thinking of
bringing it to Japan as well
and I'm going yeah rowing a boat yeah
rowing a boat I mean I have the rowing
machine
but I I I I don't know about the rowing
machine I
how are they fine
[Music]
are they immune to Lava
oh well
the rowing machine I feel like I I think
there's there's something with my rowing
machine that I don't know I have to make
some setting or so because I think it's
like
and maybe it's because it's such a cheap
one because there's different types of
rowing machines as far as I know
I bought a rowing machine yeah a while
ago didn't I did I not tell you
I feel like I told you I bought a rowing
machine
because I wanted to be able to do it
whenever at home but mine's kind of like
I feel like it has barely any resistance
and that's probably because
it's like one of those cheap ones
because I don't like don't they usually
work with like water or something I
don't know there's like water or
something inside and then the one that I
have Works kind of differently that's
why it was cheaper and so it has less
resistance but I wonder if if there
isn't like something
some kind of like setting or something
that I don't know I have to change in
order to use it to its full potential
I don't know what I'm doing wrong
but at least the resistance bands I can
like take
everywhere and they're small and there's
also variations of enough
strength
that you need full potential
I did not read the manual but wow
not really I don't think I mean I read
the manual on how to put together the
rowing machine which is already quite
something I would say
I'm doing all this on my own you know
on her own dealing with her [\h__\h]
hmm
there's a technique to do it effectively
yeah I feel like that shouldn't be too
difficult to get that down
[Music]
am I
still no
no
[Music]
yeah anyway I wanted to close that topic
and talk about the Nintendo Direct so I
want a Nintendo Direct I watched it by
watching someone else do we watch along
yeah and you know
ah but it was actually
really nice because like
his reaction was really good
he was so happy you know he's usually
always so unhappy about everything
Nintendo is doing he looks very critical
very critical type of person my ocean
yeah yeah
but he was he said that was the best
Nintendo Direct
in million years and it was a 9 out of
10.
very excited as well
so for me
you guys know that I'm
um I I like Mario games but I like other
franchises way more that's for sure
like I'm not as deep into the
Mario franchise as I am into the Zelda
franchise for example
but I mean I tried a couple Mario Games
Sunshine 64.
that one that one which one was the one
side scrolling one
but I was so bad at I prefer the 3D ones
and new Super Mario Bros new Deluxe is
that the one
why did you put it oh because I don't
know I don't know I still like it but I
like it more than other games but I like
it less than my favorites but I mean I
think it was worth putting it on my
interests no no no anyway
oof
[Music]
huh
no we are we are we are getting closer
right it just felt like Ryan was making
no promise
[Music]
I I oh I know I guess I don't owe her if
I if I can't tell her that I owe her
I want to say I owe you
maybe she's listening I owe you Ella
under my car
[Music]
you were online just when I needed you
then you came to my
beautiful rescue
it's right it rhymes
and write My Own lyrics now let's go
anyway Nintendo director
um
um yeah yeah
so
it was like I mean all the really
exciting stuff was about Super Mario
Mario stuff I think
the first one the RPG one it looks so
cute I mean it looks very different
don't tender was commenting on how he
fought the Mario especially when he's
small he looks really weird and I guess
I understand like why I think it's a
look to get used to but
I think it's still very much
I don't know like Mario and it's not
that weird the art style I think
yeah yeah I think
it was like Mario was really small right
so
okay he's so cute he's like squished
he's cute
um it looks really cute I feel like I
would maybe play it how long was the OG
um Super Mario RPG like in
playtime
anyone who knows who's got the Deeds
45 hours
short RPG I like that
because you know I'm always busy with my
long ass ape RPGs
so I wouldn't mind having a little
shorter one if it's a short experience
that I'll I think I'll play it when it
comes out it comes out and November
right what was it was that the other one
15 20 20. well that's that's that's
great actually
I'm actually grateful that it's on the
shorter side
never played the OG but I don't know
I've heard the only good things like
everybody's like saying oh that was so
good
can't believe there's a remake now let's
[\h__\h] go
people seem to be very excited about it
and I've seen feedback that said like oh
it's very true to the original from what
they can tell in the teaser
and looking really beautiful and all
that you know fans seem to be very happy
about it
it's good that's very good
so yeah I'm interested in it too it's
cute very cute and then after that they
teased the peach game
which isn't the Remake it seems to be
stand alone oh my God I know there's
been a peach came Peach game before for
the DS right and I never played it I
don't think it ever really
I never knew about it when I was younger
I don't yes and if I knew about it maybe
I would have played it
[Music]
but
I didn't
know about it at all
[Music]
okay we have to do this again
and I keep on double checking if I'm
really crouched
[Music]
okay what was I saying oh yeah the peach
one yeah I wanna play that one too
but I wonder what kind of game it will
be
very curious
she looks so cute it looks so pretty too
and she was doing some kind of
transformation at the end and first I
thought it
she like gonna wear like a light blue
dress because it looked like out of
transformation because it was glowing in
light blue
she was gonna have like a Cinderella
kind of dress you know what I mean
but then it cuts off there
so okay that light blue it doesn't it
probably doesn't have to do with the
final color at all
although what if she transforms into
Rosalina I don't know
she's light blue is Rosalina
like a completely different person from
peach or is it just like an altar I
don't know
[\h__\h] about Rosalina never played her
game
they're different okay yeah I thought so
she's cute heck and cute
[Music]
yeah
um
I'll play it
but for that there was no date
they gave us a lot of release dates but
no nothing nothing really not even a
title right for the peach game
foreign
they had playable days or somewhere
right yeah I was pretty
excited about that too seeing Daisy I'm
very um very big fan of Daisy
I'm too up height and there's no way
that that dude can see me
yellow tones I think it's excited about
Yellowstone what are you aware why are
we yeah there's a new wall where you
wear
while we were with
while we were wet
and then while we were
uh while we were so stressful to me doll
so [\h__\h] stressful but you know
another thing I saw that Dom tennis was
making fun of but I I see potential in
it
um
[Music]
um was the wasn't everybody
one two switch
oh
because
um the one to switch it I play with
is only for two people right
now this could be a potential off collab
uh stream for you know whatever for
example myth meets up again
because I had so much fun with
uh want to switch with goodbye
imagine playing that with like five
people or so because you can't play it
with more than two in the OG right
I mean you can switch controllers I
guess
yeah I think I think it has it has
potential as a streaming game for off
collabs for bigger off collapse they're
bigger than two people
[Music]
yeah so I personally actually appreciate
that the moment I saw it I sent it to
janma I was like look look
up collab game
[Music]
I mean it would be kind of cooler if
there was
um online Cola because then it doesn't
even have to be an Off column you know I
always appreciate having more uh games
for groups
bigger groups and also smaller groups
this and that everything I just need
a variety you know
Nintendo wanted to cancel it that the
everybody want to switch
well well honestly I don't
I I appreciate it for existing but I
also honestly don't really see a use or
a need or a demand for it
it didn't really need to exist but if it
does exist then I will take it you know
but was it really necessary no
[Music]
at least it's not a full price game this
time as opposed to one two switch
what
everybody switch will be cheaper is that
what you're saying
[Music]
what's going on
I should let me find some blocks here so
I should play some more torches ah I'm
not a torches
doesn't necessarily need torches though
I mean yeah maybe for no mob spawn but
anyway
[Music]
onto switch wasn't packaged with the
switch was on it was the same price as
breath of the Wild
and then this one will be cheaper
with thirty dollars
oh like half the price
what are they saying what are they
saying with that
by doing that
it's basically the same game you can
just play it with more people
that's actually shocking then then they
should like just release it as a DLC or
as a free update of the OG game
huh well whatever whatever I'm fine with
whatever
[Music]
but the stunks
yeah anyways
I really like Luigi's Mansion you know
this one's a really Master slash
not really uh not a remake right
remaster of the DS one but wasn't this
one on the GameCube too
Luigi's Mansion too
because I have a memory of playing it on
the GameCube
what who then what did I play Lucius
Mansion one
which one was on the GameCube
that was one oh then I never played the
second one oh
that's fun
foreign
[Music]
trying to rub cat hair off of my nose
doesn't go away it's just itchy
second one is there I've heard
second one is very good
if not the best for a lot of people but
I guess opinions vary
that rap very very very yeah
very well
a very
well I just sound exactly like v-e-r-y
um
English
whatever
I had it okay well anyway yeah I want to
play Luigi's Mansion when it comes out I
want to play the peach game and I want
to play the Super Mario RPG one two
and the other one that they announced at
the very very end I think that was the
biggest hype for Mario fans but for me
it was the other three
the new new new 2D one with the elephant
I think that was supposed to be the
biggest highlight
but I I don't know
I moved about the other three
especially the peach one because we know
nothing about it
[Music]
um
but the elephant one we'll just we'll
just gotta call it the elephant one for
now
I know it has a name but you know it's
its own fault I think the elephant
stayed in everybody's memories just
so
it burnt it in our heads how can it not
be the elephant one like in 20 years
when people look back at all the Mario
games
they'll be like oh there was this one
was Alina and then there was the
elephant one
thank you
that's how it will be remembered
Nintendo are you aware of that
do you really want it to be the elephant
one
it's too late now anyway
[Music]
oh my God
Paper Mario I know it's very popular but
among like Mario RPG fans but I don't
know
[Music]
um
but apparently the elephant isn't the
only thing that you'll be able to turn
into right there will be more animals
and they just showed out
[Music]
things they show the elephant
since
um
one of my favorite uh you know
especially when I was when I was a child
birthday cakes or just cakes in general
was a certain elephant cake
and I'm not the only one in German
speaking countries this cake is the goat
everybody loves this cake even adults
like it's it's just
it's a legendary cake
you guys don't understand it's a frozen
cake that comes in the frozen section
but everybody here loves this cake it's
yeah one of the best cakes in existence
I need to get it
I need to get it I haven't
eaten so long still good I think
everybody every german-speaking person
unless they have some dietary
restrictions everybody has eaten this
cake at least once in their life I'm
telling you it's a lemonade you
you don't get it if you're not from here
you just you wouldn't get it
but this is the name of a really famous
like
child animation
[Music]
um
we're good that we're not mining their
um child animation elephant
um which
[Music]
interestingly finally finally
finally interestingly amusingly
[Music]
where's cloves that very much resemble
what Mario wears
red and blue
um those kind of trousers that have the
the thingies right
and then let's hold the
and and
cap
right the cap just like Mario
the kind of cap that Mario has
that's just any kind of cat but like
yeah overalls and a cat like that and in
the same colors
oh
God so
Benjamin in his natural elephant form
looks like
Mario when he transforms into the
[\h__\h] elephant so every
german-speaking person
noticed this I think
or can agree to this once they see or
once they are being made aware of it
because we all know
everybody knows Benjamin at least maybe
Zoomers don't what can I do maybe
Zoomers don't know I actually don't know
if Zoomers nowadays if the children from
now grow up with Benjamin but
but they could still around so I feel
like yeah yeah I feel like as a toddler
you would watch Benjamin even now
um
let him actually make some light here
actually oh wait that's not loud
oh yeah that's perfect perfect light
source
[Music]
yeah I think they still know right I
just Googled him and right can you
please can some German people type in
the chat Benjamin
so people can copy paste it and Google
it right now
if you just I mean probably if you
Google Benjamin elephant
it will probably come up too many videos
we're gonna make him trend
ah if you guys ever this is such a weird
thing to put on your bucket's bucket
list but if you guys ever traveled to
Austria or Germany or probably
Switzerland maybe even I feel like
Hungary could even have it
I feel like a lot of countries would
have like
this cake and this character
um please make yourself your way to a
supermarket
and find this cake you will find it in
the cake section is always there
and then uh
let it sit in your hotel room
let it unfreeze maybe put it it
relatively small
small you can eat it alone
that's why it's you know mostly for
children's birthdays parties
yeah and then enjoy it enjoy and you're
welcome this is our
most popular
cake
besides
yeah that's the Austin cake
[Music]
I miss that cake in order to thank you
ah don't come yeah
yeah for the ones who are going to
docomi from outside of Germany
you guys you gotta get together and
share if kfb are getting together
shared a cake for me will you and sent
me a picture
worth it
I'll be yummy
[Music]
I'm gonna get it too maybe for my
birthday so
yeah that's all I have to say about it
I mean I kind of liked that like RPG I
tweeted about I saw but I mean that's
just because it was the closest to what
I would normally play in this whole
Nintendo Direct
so
one two three four
[Music]
Hitman
pic man I'm sorry I know everybody loves
Pikmin but
I don't I don't feel like
getting into it at the moment no
Splatoon neither
oh wait
so funny everybody's like like
forgetting about the Pokemon DLC
I mean it's just a DLC but it looked
pretty cool and fury like the Pokemon
looked cool and
a lot of
new car yeah but
the Mario stuff over her shadowed kind
of the
[Music]
ex actually
surprising to have that announced
in the Nintendo Direct another Pokemon
Direct right because that was the first
trailer I think I mean they showed they
showed the the Pokemon before I remember
that the legendary ones
I announced it before but the trailer
was first right first time
not again
how far am I
hey
[Music]
taking really long
what yeah and the pickaxe I have another
one though I have another one
and I'm gonna try to not make this one
break
[Music]
and now we have um we have another chest
on the other side so worst case I can go
back
um yeah
and repair possibly with the few
diamonds that I have
[Music]
um
means more Wawa yeah but my throat is
starting to hurt from so much tangenting
thing
[Music]
the tunnel while I'm making a tunnel I'm
connecting it to the other side of my
tunnel that leads to the Mesa
uh because this is kind of my my special
tunnel that leads to special areas
so this one is gonna now have a fourth
station to get off at if you want to go
to uh cherry blossom by Omi
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
what was I talking about I I wanted to
mention something Aya birthday the [\h__\h]
what
keyword birthday
so I just want to share
with my lovely kfp some thoughts
currently or like a warning
[Music]
um you know I was like pretty hopeful
for a long time
I mean
let's say not hopeful because I was more
like coping
I didn't want to give up on the font
that maybe I could do
the Brady birthday on time and then even
when they told me no then I was still
hoping that maybe it will be
somewhat close
to the OG date
so I mean I still don't have a date
so it's
I don't know I you know now I lost hope
then it's gonna be anywhere near
it's not gonna be in July that's for
sure
if it will be in August is also
questionable
at this point
um but because I was like coping for so
long
I I I I I I I just thought it would be
okay if my birthday stream that's not
the 3D one because there will be a 3D
one eventually there will be that's for
sure
if the one that actually happens on the
date the right date
I I thought it would be okay if it was
like more simple you know because I
thought there would be something bigger
to follow it up soon after
so I didn't really like you know
prepare much
I mean I can do Collins you know like
like uh it's always fun to do Collins
I can do that but
I was watching goda's birthday
and I saw you know
she she prepared quite a long so then I
was like [\h__\h] and
wait now I feel like really stressed out
uh
yeah so I just want to let you guys know
that
um but I think I have a plan now it's
not as special as what good I'm prepared
but I hope it will be enjoyable for you
guys
so my plan is
to start with a countdown you know on an
hour before midnight for me and then and
then
um don't compare yeah I'm not really
comparing but just wondering if maybe I
[\h__\h] up
[Music]
but you know it should have been a
pretty birthday
and whatever so I'm gonna start with a
countdown and I want to have some
call-ins already during the countdown
ideally Ian uh en Collins
um and then that'll be just a short
stream yeah
then on the actual day I was talking
about doing a marathon but I thought
I won't do American I'll do three
different streams
not a marathon
and I'll start with uh what was it the
first one was gonna be around like
1pm or so my time in early one it's like
8 P.M jst
and that one what I'll be doing is
baking a cake or a tart with hand cam
hand cam stream
and during that I'll take because this
is good for jst I'll take ID and
Japanese Collins
um
so while baking I'll have calling so you
can even maybe ask me to do something
but I don't really want to [\h__\h] up the
tart or the cake
I don't want because I don't want to
just for the sake of having them make
funny requests to [\h__\h] up the cake no I
want it to be delicious
yeah but yeah someone will be doing that
then I take a break to prepare because
afterwards I want to do
um
uh scuffed
uh an archived 3d full body karaoke
scuffs because it will be home pretty
you know like I did before
but I thought well at least
3D
not just a normal karaoke that's the
least I can do
yeah
and then after that that'll be out that
I think I'm doing that at like uh eight
no seven p.m I think it's currently my
rough plan
and then
uh the last stream at like 10 p.m my
time
will be uh
Jack box
with as many and maybe also ID although
it will be late for them there's many en
members as possible I already sent out
an open invite hello anybody who wants
to participate this is the time please
let me know
so like a birthday party with friends
you know
having a big collab on my Channel with
the girls
hanging and playing drag books so we
have big variety we will have a we'll
have Collins we'll have
um karaoke we'll have a cooking stream
we'll have a big fun collab
I hope
this is a little bit high and fun for
you guys I mean I would say that's fun
I'm just like you know trying to make up
for the lack of something yeah
yeah I hope it's okay
yeah sounds like a blast I think so too
no
[Music]
thank you
thank you I wish I could do the 3D thing
because I had everything already planned
out in January February
I wrote my PowerPoint presentation back
then already
now besides that I don't I'm not just so
you know don't look forward to it I'm
not gonna release a song cover because I
already have one upcoming
on Sunday that is 100 going to happen
now
um
and I'm not gonna tease my album yet
because
it will be released
quite a bit later but within August end
of August
um so I think it's too early to tease
something on the 6th of July you know
too early I can't
I don't think it's smart to do that too
early
so in terms of like
super special like projects I don't
really have anything at like that I can
show you already I'm working on a lot of
things but it's not really like ready
yet the new outfit for example
I can tell you now it's happening in
July
but after the birthday
what's happening
um yeah because they're currently
um breaking it
[Music]
you guys know what's on the menu these
days
keeping you guys updated
[Music]
you know you will I think in in like uh
close times soon soon soon
you will have some other things that
will
you know explain why I've been busy and
make up for
a lot of things not that I'd have that
I'd need to make up for anything I agree
with that
but I I mean it will add on to a lot of
the hype so
side projects
[Music]
yeah gonna be a big month yeah July
August September the whole summer really
I think
has exciting things
going on and hopefully
before this or ends wake me up
September Ends before the summer ends
hopefully
we'll have my freaky birthday
I have an idea now by the way
[Music]
now that I'm already telling you so many
details you know I'm telling you so many
details always about everything I do
you know I went to I meant to record
some motion capture for a music video
right and originally I was thinking of
doing two 3D music videos right and I
told you guys that I kind of changed my
mind because too [\h__\h] expensive but I
don't know I still kind of want to do it
and but by the time I don't know when I
was when I had to go to amen
um
[Music]
kind of because I wanted to perfect the
choreo of that one song
took so much time and I couldn't even
get The Courier for the other song
already
um
because I I wasn't happy with the first
one yet
so there we ran out of time we didn't
even make the choreo for the other song
that I originally wanted to record it on
this place too like originally I wanted
to create two
one two
record two during my time there
but then you know the combination of
you know lack of
you know not really lack of budget but
just unwillingness to spend so much on
my own pocket
and the lack of time
for the second choreo
we just I was like okay well I'm just
gonna do the the one and for the other
ones I'm just gonna do simple things
simple mvs to promote it
[Music]
but I found
I I figured out
a way to get free motion capture
uh
for the second song
which makes me think I mean that was
only a small part of the cost
but I would have to fly to uh amen again
that's also time consuming you know
I would have to fly there again to
record and again you know a second
choreo that that just I didn't want to
do that so now I mean it's kind of
right in front of your eyes
but it just the timing what needs to
work out is the timing
what I'm saying is if I ever get the
date of my 3D birthday
studio time
I
uh wanted to perform one of my
album songs anyway
at least one
so
I'm gonna ask them to give me the motion
capture data of my performance of that
and then just use it for the movie
can't say no to that can they
[Music]
it just helps me to save some cost and
some time I don't know please
oh wow life hack
yeah so I'm hoping that's gonna work out
but that
yeah it just don't need
to all happen in a timely manner
two birds one stone
two stones one burn
[\h__\h] I'm not finishing this today I
think
I feel like we're barely moving
didn't we started 2 900 and we gotta go
to
one still need one thousand blocks
we're not almost there I thought it
wouldn't be this far what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
with once there's ice here and we can go
on the boat it's no problem but damn
further away than I thought
I'm not finishing this
as long as the whole Ice Road Again
oh I think so that was the distance we
covered before
DJ's the rest girl you can fish it yeah
it will I will
[Music]
get not thousand ten thousand yeah yeah
ten thousand just ignored one that one
zero yeah that's what I meant though no
we need to go from 25 000 to 15 000.
oh no
following goes quicker than building now
ice blocks the placements
I might even run out of the ice blocks
oh
one more
why are you here now you are more
difficult to mine
anyway am I telling you guys too much
like do you guys want to know less
serious and secretive
[Music]
no
you like the BTS talk
um
laughs no no that's my own project I can
tell you as much as I want to build my
own projects
it's fine it's fine
it's fine I'm not getting in trouble
I could if I wanted to I can I could
even already tell you the names of the
songs and all that but no that's where I
I draw the line there
personally
I just want you guys to know what I'm
working on you know
and
been on my mind and
why I do certain things the way I do
them
why I'm more busy at times
and just general I feel like you guys
deserve to be updated because you only
support me
wherever it be just by being here or by
it like financial support
by buying merchandise or sending super
chats or being a member and all that
we're buying my music and all that I'm
like I feel like you
but
you can see it as a benefit I mean not
everybody is a member here but maybe you
can see it a little bit as a benefit of
being a kfb member or being part of kfp
one of the benefits is you get to know
all the videos
[Music]
flop on my nose
I need to stop face uh not pounding face
what's the word
face
bombing my cat what
face planting planting that's the word
I'm paying you guys
[Music]
what 40 months or more than enough thank
you so much
[Music]
cat huffing
yeah but speaking of ketokato let's go
to the next topic that is moving that
little [\h__\h] I've been feeling so bad
because me and smoothie are currently
not in a good place
my cats movie one of my kids
for people who don't know all the
details I have two cats
they are freaking cute I love them I've
been raising them they love me because
I'm the only person they have
chunky wonky she's the chilled one
sometimes you know I feel like she's
she's
so chill like she's a little bit too
chill but at the same time she's also
really like panicky and nervous when
there's strangers
she hides she runs away but like
recently
or no recently it's gotten better while
Smoothie has gotten worse
chunky monkey has been so lovey-dovey to
me
so sweet and like oh it's just
she melts my heart thanks for the
memberships guys thank you
she mounts my heart yo she's just such a
good girl and this movie is pissing me
off I
don't know what to do
you know she always wants um
the the wet food in the morning
and there were times where you know like
before I was
before I was gone
for the two months
I don't think it was an issue back then
I think it happened it started after
that right
[Music]
because I think my brother had a habit
of waking up relatively early when my
cats when he was uh taking care of my
cats
and that created the some kind of habit
for
my cat is moving
to expect
food really early so for a while she
would wake me up really early and ask
for food
and
[Music]
sometimes she would be like really
really
obnoxious with it
but eventually she would stop and and
more or less go back to her usual ways
of
more or less waiting for me to wake up
and then getting her wet food
about this in August already really
sinway was better but currently
the absolute worst it's ever been
she will wake me up like you know she
usually she had some kind of ribbon just
like me that once we go to bed
she will sleep also at least for a
certain amount of hours
the reason about a reasonable amount of
hours but now she wakes me up two hours
after I've fallen asleep
and she's Reckless she does not
stop she's so loud there's not even a
second between her meows
she will go on and on I swear I've tried
to ignore
but it's impossible she goes up right
into my face she walks around the bed
she it's it's just I I I I've I've
endured
her [\h__\h] so often and then she would
just stop before but now she just
doesn't stop she just doesn't stop she's
driving me crazy I'm sorry but like I I
I I I like I tried to push her off the
bed
gently to show her this movie it's not
the time you have to wait
but that didn't work and I feel so bad
because I've been getting so frustrated
I've been like yelling screaming
like [\h__\h]
I don't even look really
screaming
and and she she has no reaction
she has no reaction
nothing
it's not like Bamboozled by it
she's not scared
she's not confused
she's not worried
it's not concerned no
because she's on the face and then once
I knew this wouldn't work but I want to
try to just like uh close her out of the
rooms you know close the door
and didn't work of course because she
will just stand right in front of it and
meow endlessly really loud and that
doesn't help either
um she's too spoiled I don't know what
the [\h__\h] happened for her to be like
this right now
it's terrible
so then you know I get up and like
surprise she's already sprayed for a
million years it's not the thing she's
not in heat
I get up because I can't I can't I need
sleep you know this is a days where I
need to get up but I have a certain time
where I need to get up
uh
so I have no choice I get up I make her
food because at that point it's like
I see that she's not stopping
and then make her food
and I I swear
two hours later
I wake up again
also after I gave her food she ate a
little bit maybe and then she meowed for
like another three four minutes
I don't understand she does that
sometimes
sometimes but yeah 2
again
if I get woken up once at like six and
then at eight and I'm like what the [\h__\h]
I already gave you food normally once I
gave it
she stops for the rest of the day and we
and then we'll eat Kibbles for the rest
of the day
she learned to control me I'm I'm I'm so
and that's when I absolutely lose it I
don't know what to do I tried to I had a
cup of water next to me on my next to my
bed so I tip my fingers in it and like
splush in their face and she's like and
then immediately recovers
doesn't give a [\h__\h] about the water
doesn't bother her
nothing and I don't want to hurt her
obviously so that's all I can do
but but I
think because you know when I'm sad we
were like amazed that my cats
when I'm sick they stay by my side and
all that
really stays by my side when I'm sick
it's actually chunky wonky huh this
movie is just like she's around
the one who really cares it's chunky
wonky
[Music]
in this movie but anyway what I'm trying
to say is you would think that if they
understand emotions a little bit
um
then wouldn't they if they understand my
sadness wouldn't they also understand my
anger
but hey
she doesn't
she's yeah the same issue with my get a
Time feeding Bowl yeah but that's like
difficult with wet food like the
I looked it up already yeah
I'm I'm gonna try it most likely but
it's difficult like four Kibbles it's
easy because
they're dry
for wet food wet food once it's out it's
like it gets you so fast
but yeah at this point I have to try it
um
because she's she's really robbing me of
my sleep
I'm constantly being interrupted
and it's so frustrating
I I even started crying on the
frustrating frustration a little bit
because I don't care I gave her food by
the way at that day a second time
really really angrily
um but the food I I guess like she
didn't like that one
I gave it to her before and she didn't
like that one in particular I gave her a
different one before that but the second
round I was like okay
I'll give you this one just because it's
fast to prepare
I don't want to be angry
and cats I don't know what's happening
like normally we're we're all just happy
we're happy family and now she's pissing
me off so much
[Music]
oh frustrating but I gave her the second
round of food and because she didn't
like it she didn't leave me alone again
man it's just so frustrating right now
it's moving why the whole time you know
the whole time chunky wonky is just like
sitting next to me being the goodest
girl of them all
[Music]
she is
greatest
bubble bubble
in existence
yes movie
Rebel face maybe I don't know maybe
maybe it's the Heat
that makes her weird
[Music]
but I think as far as I know cats are
not that affected but I don't know 30
degrees or something like that
[Music]
yeah when her face for 30 minutes
I was she doing summer last year not
this bad maybe we had a similar issue
before but she was never this bad I
swear
never
I wonder in the one week
roughly
where I'll be gone
pink
maybe I hope she'll treat my mom
different my mom's listening to this by
the way Mom I'm sorry if you have to
deal with this too I'm sorry
I think maybe she'll treat you
differently though because I think she
always treats Strangers Like not me
differently
bringing experience true true do I have
to change what I'm holding
so that like this stuff like other
things don't mend
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
I thought it's more common on the like
on the bottom of the never not in the
top
[Music]
wow it's probably just one though
it's gonna mend
[Music]
[\h__\h] it's because it's silk touch baby
gonna
Bend properly
[Music]
okay then let's mend this one
is that man in the pickaxe it doesn't
look like much
[Music]
or the other one
foreign
[Music]
wait which one am I I use this and I put
this one here
then it'll meant one of them
[Music]
did it meant something
thank you
[Music]
it's not giving me XP at least
I don't I think it's mainly the one I'm
mining with right
I said
orange now it was red before I guess
I don't know
I can't I can't see
I can't see which one is doing it
[Music]
but something happened surely
the offhand okay okay well it's still
very red though
and now
do I need to mind these with a suck
touch or does it not matter
[Music]
it doesn't matter okay
does it give exp too
no no
oh it's not my first one guys
updated
well just one doll I think
just one that's rare though damn
[Music]
it's not my first
but yeah anyway I just wanted to let you
guys know I'm [\h__\h] frustrated but I'm
I'm my my hands are tied I have to
try the
automated feeding one and I'll just set
it really really early she can have it
at 6 00 am for
she if she really wants oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I hope she'll be happy with it she'll
love it I hope so she better that [\h__\h]
so done
and then you know I'm like so angry
during the night and then I wake up and
it's like you know like a couple that I
don't find I wake up and I look at her
fluffy cute face and I'm like I'm so
sorry I'm just
I love you but all right now I also hate
you I'm like I really do like why are
you so [\h__\h] annoying but I love you
I'm so sorry for screaming at you that's
literally me every morning though
why am I why must you be like that like
sometimes I love you but you know
sometimes you drive me insane I feel
like that's literally things that
couples say like 100
I've heard that before Netflix shows
even
I love you but you you know you drive me
insane sometimes and drive me crazy
[Laughter]
and and I'm so confused because I always
I always
um praise them right I always praise
them in front of people
there's no time out box no I'm not
putting my kids in the timeout box
I always praise them to friends and you
guys and my cats are the best behaved
cutest kitty katutis they can do
anything without me telling it them you
know they don't scratch furniture
they knew they knew where the toilet was
when I didn't even like when I wasn't
even able to show them
uh when they were kitty cats and just
came to my home for the first time
her metabolism
kind of metabolism disease
please
yeah I'll
um
I'm not sure if it will really be
something but I have to bring them to
the vet anyway for getting
[Music]
um
vaccinations again
so when I find some time
[Music]
I'll get that done and then they can
check I don't know how you would check
that though how do you check for a
metabolism that sounds like cannibals
metabolism
disease how do you check that
the blood oh okay okay
I wouldn't mind just also doing a of the
site for different reasons
height allergy test with them too I
wanted to do that for a long time
allergy test
[Music]
I need to know
because I keep on Switching their food
and I still feel like something
they're reacting to something not as bad
as like around like Christmas though you
know when I
um had an issue
[Music]
it calmed down but I feel like there's
so something and I tried so many
different cables
um
but I kind of I don't want to switch for
a million people I don't think it's the
food
at this point it's not good for them to
keep on Switching the food either
[Music]
it's a problem because you're traveling
more to see no no no no no no I haven't
been away
since what February no February she
doesn't know what's coming up
yet she might get upset when I'm gone a
lot in
July
but it will always be really short
periods so
not gonna be too bothered by it
foreign
[Music]
wasn't that where was I recently
where did I go didn't I go somewhere
recently
America
right that was that was one thing but
that was also really short that was
under a week that was like
four or five days
crazy short
[Music]
too short
yeah
I wish I wish I could only tell you good
things about them normally I always only
tell you good things about them
and I feel
a little bit ashamed
I really do
a little bit
oh no man it's weird
I feel like a bad cat mother right now
because I cannot control my cats or one
of my cats other one
cute baby
[Music]
no family is perfect
same with teenagers there's only there's
no way
[Music]
only has good things to be said about
them they're not even a little assets no
no
[Music]
the cats are not little ass hats
good babies
[Music]
looks up to me like he wants to jump
online
lab then he jumps over my head it's so
tilting
cute
foreign
I wouldn't complain
[Music]
who else is streaming right now from Ian
or Japan or ID is anyone streaming
I feel so alone right now you know
I feel like I'm a
Sanctuary for viewers right now
literally nobody oh my God I'm literally
a sanctuary Holodeck says only me
I am a sanctuary
you're welcome
fun and one hour
Minecraft form
[Music]
save us I'm here for you holy qawwa is
here for you Saint kiwala's here for you
then pets what the [\h__\h] what
pets
[Music]
i i i i i i okay
okay
to each your own
right good morning
good morning
[Music]
oh my God
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
the promise I can't really just go the
whole time
even when the block blocks break so
easily because I needed to be a certain
shape if I just don't go like
it will be a mess and also there's holes
often so I need to be careful such as
now
don't shoot me don't shoot me
you might fall into jazz and well we're
not playing Zelda right now but yes
I guess you could call it a chasm
or a chasm
no no no you're not gonna enter here
it never is the underworld continue to
Kenny
I think your pickaxe will hold ass yeah
I know I know I know I'm not even I'm
not gonna I know I realized a while ago
that I'm not finishing this today
I thought I would I was
I didn't think it would be this far
but you know at least I can
certain with the position of the
direction if I didn't have those chords
in the end it was just
digging mindlessly I would wonder if I
would have like passed the tunnel at
some point on the side and that's why
that's why it's taking so long
at least we're we're gonna meet it
directly eventually we we've started it
out perfectly
we prepared it probably
effort is marble thank you we are not
making that we're tall all the way back
to the start right
no
only two where to mess up uh station is
[Music]
which was also already pretty far
sheesh
[Music]
I have a huge dent
on the bottom right of my hand
[Music]
from
the table
Edge
gamer hand
starting to feel kind of rough too
that the hand I mean like like it's
rubbing off skin
cool
gamer and excessive resting in
oh
wait my my face
down there it fell down
[Music]
my bucket
baguette
what is the Super Chat oh
ah Europe vacation won't be able to
visit your hallowed land I will see Loch
Ness what
[Music]
oh have fun and have a safe trip
hmm
[Music]
no no
baguette
[Music]
oh it does sound like a bucket bucket
bucket
but it's 11 pm now maybe I should end it
and then we
well maybe not because my throat hurts
I'll tell you one more changing guys
we had
birthday plans most questions really
important
um
let's say you go to the beach
[Music]
you have to bring maybe if you're not
going alone let's say I mean either way
no but let's say you go not alone
you bring one or two towels because the
person that goes with you maybe doesn't
want to bring their own bag
and you bring something to drink bring
your wallet bring sunglasses you bring
sunscreen maybe a little snack you know
there's a lot of things you have to
bring from my experience I when I went
to the beach
I I felt like I needed a relatively big
bag for that
a relatively big beach bag
so how big do you guys want your beach
bag
[Music]
I guess it's hard to describe to me how
big you need it
decent living
um men don't use beetroot well you will
because it's very useful
towels take up a lot of space you know
[Music]
carry-on size oh yeah see you can use it
like that too
because like currently I got like a
photo of a sample and we were like isn't
that too big
that looks kind of too big
too big I think we're gonna make it a
little bit smaller but I hope we don't
regret it and be like
that one doesn't fit in after all we
should have made it bigger
hmm
[Music]
well
winter for us will be summer for some
others of us and whenever summer arrives
in your place then you can go to the
beach with it but you also don't have to
use it necessarily for the beach you can
use it for I don't know for a hike maybe
I don't know or for traveling on the
plane I don't know
it doesn't always have to be used to the
intended way
thank you I guess I don't know I want to
know how big it should be but really
you guys can't answer that question for
me I need to find the answer myself in
my heart you need to dig
deep down and ask myself
how big
because especially in like seeing it on
the photo it's also kind of different
than seeing it in person
I wish I could see it in person
[Music]
you cannot fight this back battle for
you
yeah I have come to the realization to
well I think I'll be using the beach bag
for sure like I need it
I'll be using it
I'm looking forward to it okay
[Music]
oh my ceiling is too low again
you guys shouldn't be lazy and take your
own stuff what are you talking about
size is not the most important that's
what I believe
but for a beach bag
[Music]
I am porn
okay let me go front
I'm going to want to have a large bag
yeah yeah gym bag
I don't think I don't think would really
look like a gym bag but you can use it
as a gym bag I guess like a maybe a spa
bag it's kind of like a spa bag honestly
but the looks of it
like at least from the spa bags that
I've seen so far like in those big
Resort Hotels they give you this big bag
with to bring your towels and your
slippers and whatever and they're like
pretty big
oh
it's one hotel and I went to the spa bag
also
I think functions
[Music]
we had a hiking back too that's what I
remember
picnic back oh yeah you can use it as a
picnic bag I think so
everybody needs a picnic bag
some or maybe I mean if you wanted to
you could even use it as a shopping bag
because bit sturdy you know as a beach
bag it's gonna be a little bit sturdy
hmm
[Music]
yeah kind of arrangeable I guess so
yeah but yeah picnic that makes sense
I think it makes sense you could use it
like that you know have fun with it
alrighty
should I mind that
[Music]
wrong
thank you
I shouldn't be minding a dust silk touch
right
what's mine with this one
[Music]
confusing confusing more please
it's already
so greedy
[Music]
okay that was that Birch question and
then yeah hair appointment I suffered it
was yesterday it was yesterday right
ah it was so painful I mean it's not the
first time I know this feeling I know I
know how it is
some people reply to me on Twitter like
what hair appointment can be so painful
what you guys don't understand it's not
the haircut
I I
[Music]
go Illusions so you don't really see it
usually but I had some roots and wanted
to
um bleach those you know
yeah and that [\h__\h] hurts
and then on top of the bleaching
oh God there's a pickaxe half of the
bleaching when the scalp was already
like
sensitive
goes another uh
never color and normally that alone
doesn't hurt so much but you know when
it's when it's bad when it's like on top
of the bleached skull poo
huge headache and
really not nice
foreign
[Music]
happy with the result so yeah
worth it y'all
staff was really nice there too
I think I found a hair salon
where I'm quite comfortable at
um
already second time that I went there
[Music]
it's a great year
just wanted some maintenance to know
before I go to Japan because they didn't
want them to see me like that
it was time
maintenance
[Music]
yeah yeah you know recently the massages
are the two massages I went to recently
after my
uh America trip
they were amazing
so I found my ideal
or like
go to massage place too
[Music]
sounds really good stuff really nice
easy to get an appointment
um
good atmosphere
[Music]
listens to my request doesn't make me
feel unwelcome because the last place
definitely made me feel unwelcome
thank you
unappreciated
[Music]
you found some good places lately yeah
finally I'm glad
I'm glad I'm so glad I'm like like
feeling like a gladiator
[Music]
speaking of gladiator oh tomorrow
members the only movie Once along I
wonder what we should watch and maybe
just uh the second thing on the list
from last time that like was second
place yeah we should yeah actually never
mind so already decided because that was
my plan anyway right to watch the other
movies too at least the the cat one the
kitty cat
okay
[Music]
yeah I've been watching
cats too just kidding oh we're watching
uh the boots the boots cat
[Music]
the newer one the newest one
because it got second place last time
[Music]
I'm eating my buttered popcorn
I hope it's good
and maybe some nuts maybe some
pistachios
pistachios these days
oh
hmm wait is that too high yeah
okay because my nose is pissing me off
[Music]
being so itchy
and the pickaxe is dying
I am gonna make my way back now
to start which will also take a little
time I guess
what does that have to do with ladder
cause I'm glad and Gladiator is a movie
so I got to the moving idea
you're good go be free thank you I like
them too but they got really expensive
recently what butter popcorn
how far did we get in the chords oh let
me check
good question
[Music]
walking those couple meters back is not
gonna change a thing at this point
[Music]
yeah the tunnel is hacking long and yet
we've made
uh two thousand two thousands
[Music]
uh I think I started at 29 000 no
I think
so I did like 10 000 blocks
and I need 5 000 more I think
okay so I did more than half
maybe I'll do the rest on my own I don't
know
um
two over to the right no it's not no
it's perfectly placed
it's all calculated perfectly
um
[Music]
thanks for the memberships
thank you oh yeah did work hard on this
today it was fun
[Music]
fun
finding the biomi is so pretty any I
didn't even show you guys all the things
I can make with maybe we'll do a little
build and and we'll you know
look at all the materials that you can
make with the cherry blossoms I mean I'm
sure you guys already saw most of you
elsewhere where you can make
with it but yeah
oh my God
it's so long
[Music]
if I brought my electron blue in here
hope you can find a camel yeah but
that's in the desert right and I'm I
guess that's where also the no wait
because
the the ancient ruins were the ancient
ruins
and yes I will put ice here
oh the last torch
close
we're pushing us now
nah take too long I just want to go back
and be in a safe space when when I ended
up
[Music]
thank you
gotta go to sleep now good night thank
you for watching yeah the ancient
ruins are in the Jack pinks oh okay okay
wait
yeah
no no I don't mean the ancient city I
mean the ancient the the ruins the new
ruins ecology yeah I thought it must be
desert okay sorry miscommunication
[Music]
archeology [\h__\h]
that's what I want to do like
soon next time
[Music]
so those are newly generated
um
[Music]
newly generated uh
okay
noise
going come on
you're so late yeah you are yeah I can
only just wow
I Wanna Be an archaeologist next time
yeah I I have like absolutely no idea I
just saw today when I was looking for
um
update images on Google
that's when I saw that there's like so
much
new stuff besides the Sakura I didn't
even know about it
have no idea
[Music]
it's a well
stuck
I'm stuck in the world
come back
[Music]
no I made it on my own
um yeah okay so so so so
[Music]
Oh I wanna go now
if it's okay I'll go I'll go now
place it now
remember why why do I need to fix the
well
[Music]
why it's working
um
it's all right thank you I'll eat the
rest of my on my face fingers they were
so yummy
they were so yummy they were juicy and
and crispy
oh that was so good I hope they're still
good now
why why what why is it important
I'm right at the Village from water
poisoning oh come on
[Music]
salty
why
no
listen I'm I'm having my ending speech
ah my ending tangent so yeah um
yeah I I hope it's gonna still be good
now second day
I'm gonna
I'm gonna throw it in the oven I guess
to get it warmed up but not making like
blah
so I will keep its crispiness I think
so
how much longer it will end now
safe once the place oh my God
oh my God you guys are so obsessed with
the wow airfryer true but nah
maybe
um I'll think about it
but what setting like I don't know
[Music]
anyway I'll see you guys for members
only stream tomorrow and oh I haven't
actually [\h__\h] I have to get up early for
a meeting
then until the member stream I'm
planning to learn a choreo
I have to learn a choreographing today
and tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
I'm hoping two days is enough because
it's gonna be um pretty simple one I
think I don't have to save right I can
just leave the game
sometimes I'm unsure
good luck practice thank you I really
hope I can get it in my brain fast but I
think I think it's not
too rough too difficult
I was pretty the same like not as simple
as like some others like shiny smiling
story
but still a little bit rough
a little bit simple somewhere in between
so but I probably after the meeting
we'll take a nap
it's too early it's like 8 A.M or
something
for me you know I can't sleep early and
then this movie is gonna freaking
interrupt my sleep again
yeah it's like eight
Thirty
I'll be awake for a little bit and then
and then wake up and then put up the
reservation
for the members and then I'll dance
dance dance dance dance dance dance and
then we'll chill together watch a movie
about Kitty katos
this movie please be good yeah please
I wonder if I maybe
give her wet food for dinner for once
maybe she'll leave me alone longer
during the night but I just don't want
that to become
like something she gets used to that she
always gets it for dinner too
then she'll annoy me in the evening and
the morning and we don't want that doing
yeah she'll expect it all the time
so pester me about it while I'm
streaming probably
[Music]
but I gave her I gave her you know to
make up also
I gave her the um stick
she was very happy
she's by the way she's not mad at me or
anything she's like acting like as
always like you know cuddling with me
purring letting me carry her around and
all that
um
[Music]
if she's not angry at me but I'm angry
at her and she doesn't know it uh
typical typical relationship
[Music]
you angry
the other one doesn't know doesn't
understand
[Laughter]
we're way more bothered than they are
him
toxic right now it's really a toxic
relationship
I tried I really tried to ignore her for
like as long as I could but
this time she just she just just doesn't
let go all this time
foreign
[Music]
I don't know where to ground her
earplugs
I don't like the feeling of them but
yeah
but but I think even through those I can
hear I have some earplugs here I think
but my brother left
anyway my mouth is really tired of them
speaking so much but I think I
I talked basically about everything I
wanted to talk about
yay High Five Guys nice
nice
[Music]
still constantly ignore
um I really I mean that's what I've been
doing before
and she will even eventually give up but
this time she's just not giving in and I
needed to sleep you know I was just
hoping you know
or just stop but she doesn't give me
another version
that's what I've been talking about like
I've been really trying to make her
understand I'm angry and she should stop
but um
oh wow
oh well anyway anyway
tire her out during the day so she can
stay awake to bother you that's that's a
fan though she does sleep
[Music]
being a [\h__\h]
wow she doesn't care about the water or
fried screw
sprayed water at her like four times
in a row
[Music]
just like
stunned for two seconds
and then she's back at it
really shorts done
[Music]
yeah I'll look up the automatic feeders
right up the stream all right guys
thanks for watching Kill Everybody
[Music]
thank you guys for watching it was fun
I'm hungry I'm so hungry I'm gonna meow
it movie now for 10 minutes
telling her how hungry I am and that she
should prepare food for me let's see how
she reacts
[Music]
will she show up
that little [\h__\h] better not show up no I
love her I love her though I love her so
much
uh
[Music]
lpnt here
thank you guys thank you shadow
[Music]
what what do you mean tweet
foreign
[Music]
uh up what time is
it then let me link it to you guys one
second
ah ah no it's uh going to premiere
[Music]
good night
and I'll retweet that
find it
[Music]
damn it
good morning
[Music]
okay bye-bye