[Music]
oh baby I'm looking at what remains I
couldn't tell you the same I guess
that's
Al if you couldn't tell by now I'm
hopelessly waiting making all night to
break through stuck in in an endless
loop how the night of Truth asking
[Music]
why I can't
redo the past and present call me to
truth and every part of my being do the
best feeling tell me what am I to
you
I can renew the part of me I lost it the
view hooked up for the wavering eyes
leavs me
paralized taking to step step but I keep
moving
[Music]
on concern is spilling up your lies once
again I'm over broken I'll save me if I
can let it go let it go now by now I'm
hopelessly wasting way to the cor
inside it keeps
eating away at me every day asking
why
I can't
redo the past and present calls me to
truth and every part of my being up the
best feeling tell me what am I do
you I can't BR you the part of me I lost
in the view hooked up all over waving
eyes leaves me
paralyzed taking two steps back but I
keep moving
on and I try to change me but my mind
can't just erase me any more than I have
already done looking back I'm ready to
admit that it was all me who destroyed
everything everything I
am caught up in mind in
myy that doubt puts out my
[Music]
life I can't be sure of who I am or when
I'm a
li I can't
redo the past and present calls me
to true and every part of my being got
the best feeling don't tell me what I'm
right to
you oh I
am
[Applause]
[Music]
turning