[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
no stop playing with the my hair
I don't see the comments
you forgot the comments
sorry
[Music]
what am I paying you for what am I
paying you for chihuahua
[Music]
let's just not talk about that okay
okay
and this is
kawaiiope
you don't have a bad block no this is my
my private account are you [\h__\h] me
you don't have ad block on your private
account
I can't afford it look at me I'm made
out of socks are you kidding me
I don't believe
you somehow I just don't believe you
[Music]
oh
am I doing it right
huh what's up
hello Jack we are takamuri sock version
today yep yesterday
I have four heads today oh me too no
wait away girlfriend let's go
and today my possibly also be the debut
of Girl Scouts please no please please
no I just I I felt really bad like
putting him in the cage it just didn't
feel right so
she put ghost cat into the cage and then
go sky was like
[Music]
I just felt so bad about it right yeah I
couldn't do that to him you know he's my
sweet baby well currently thank God he's
like looking at other stuff yeah other
things to break ghost cat good ghost cat
biggest of UPS to ghost cat I guess
well so today uh I'm finally not alone
with my sock puppets yeah and the life
inside uh Kawaii bomari is actually her
so yeah I used to love the Muppets so
here we get some realistic acting
oh by the way like how are you holding
up and sat there well you know my brains
are falling out every once in a while
but what can you do when I do it's like
I put my my small finger and the ring
finger like here oh okay small fingers
like easier to hold like that and my
thumb is like I'm also pushing up the
mouth here oh okay fingers ring finger
so really only those two
um pointy fingers and there are the
middle finger the [\h__\h] your fingers in
there
like these ah I see how to suck puppets
and that's pretty good
so these are wacky yeah yeah
oh my god I didn't even show you again
my my proudest creation is this one
[Laughter]
that's pretty good I love the the teeth
you really went to town on those units
[Music]
one row of teeth oh okay okay because of
course she doesn't have bottom teeth
yeah everybody knows that and also I'm
so proud of the hair because you know
she has a spiky hair that goes sideways
I don't know how to do them with the
wool so I gave her feathers and I
painted them very nice
I can't be stopped
I can't be actually falling apart like
she's not easy to use for you
gotta put it back together I have the
evil one oh oh George George is here
George is here too can you make me a
cowboy sock puppet possibly all right
well but probably you would just have to
put a cowboy hats on them yeah careful
he'll try and walk on the keyboard
yeah oh God he's getting ready to jump
please have mercy please have mercy on
us please
please
oh there he is
okay hey little buddy come here come
here please don't do anything erratic or
knock the camera down I'm [\h__\h]
begging you
come on little buddy we can play later
it's just right now I'm playing with
kiwawa we are adults playing with sock
puppets okay fully grown adults playing
with sock puppets in my home that I have
for for adults adults
let me scare him off
yeah let's get the [\h__\h] out of him like
[\h__\h] this and he dipped I'm out of here
yeah you can always count on me to scare
people away I'm gonna Reaper after all
so leave it to me okay so well how are
you doing today I'm okay I had a big
rehearsal today I rehearsed for uh the
Apex live yesterday I rehearsed for the
um for my 3D ojirome the day before
um I did a fourth Fest rehearsal with
someone else and then before that I had
a literal Scythe swinging lessons again
with death Sensei so that he could
reteach me how to swing the Scythe to
defend myself so how the [\h__\h] do you
swing aside when you have no hands
or you are the hand
okay you know what you tell me Kiara
because you're the one that made this
stock puppet okay why didn't you make me
hands why didn't you make me a scythe
what the [\h__\h]
this is just how it is okay
learn adapt overcome I think
hold on it's an acronym for something I
just forget what it is
overcome overcome is the last one
dude what are you doing there but Bubba
what are you doing
improvise adapt overcome
maybe all right maybe it's not an
acronym
[Music]
like a little like
they're going into battle
exactly like that oh my God
if two two wants to come up she'll come
up come on tutu you want to say hello
everyone
[Music]
tutu's curious about everything
rather doo doo because you smell like
ass all the time
all the time
24 7 smells like ass
you will have actual permission to come
up here
uh she'd rather eat the rest of the
puppets sorry cat's gonna do what cat's
gonna do
cat's gonna do what cat's gonna do it's
the red actually
oh There She Goes
I can't believe you're leaving our our
en mate out to be eaten by my cat
who's a little tutu it's nature I guess
so what do you think about Mommy like
this tutu
you like Mommy in this form she's taking
her away
how did you not expect my cat to want to
take the rat away
come on
just let her just let her do it just let
her take Bales to her layer all right
she's lost interest knowing that she
can't actually take Bae to her lair
sorry tutu you got debated by Kiara
real sorry about that I'll give you a
treat later I'm gonna explain this to my
cats anyway I'm sorry
[Music]
oh she's gonna walk on the keyboard
what I want to do
um is also this um karaoke reenacting
because then I was doing that alone
um I had problems because I only have
two hands so now we have four so maybe
we have more options
I think we should warm up by starting
with
wow wow
wow wow World Make some noise Make some
noise
Make some noise Make some noise
Make some noise Make some noise I'm
gonna stop
[Music]
as long as you don't knock over the
camera I don't care where you go
it's gonna be fine
good luck what are you trying to do
I've never used that before the app
Navigator I don't know what that is you
know the laptop better than we do
dude
I will play this now and Chad you will
tell me if it's too long okay
she loves the sour puppets she's really
really into them dude do you love this
song puppets oh you got a carrier she's
still got bait
she went after bay again
you know she's gonna go into that bag
you will not stop her from getting bae
wow
let's go okay are you guys hearing the
music
wow wow
noise
[Music]
yeah leave it to me these are my moves
Supreme worm moves
[Music]
get your world get your world
musically low okay
um
is
ghost cat under the hair
you scared the [\h__\h] out of me
[Music]
here we go here we go
stream
[Music]
here we go freaking down break it down
break it down break it down
[Music]
[Applause]
get your world
oh
boy
[Music]
[Applause]
your little sock is I mean your your
form is so goofy
like this it did you see that she's just
washing
she's just watching like what the [\h__\h]
it's not as like chaotic as I thought it
would be ghost cat lost interest
quickly oh yeah yeah is he not under the
table oh no
no I thought he was under there and
that's what you were looking at oh no oh
is just looking at the camera like she's
planning on pouncing on it
this is still here Bales hasn't been
abducted yet we might want to sacrifice
Bale's uh Bale Bae to the greater cause
and give her to tutu just saying who's
every time every time that we use Bales
she says that she feels like we're like
not not talking to her like she's in
trouble oh no one ever really calls her
back I always call her best and then
everybody is like who's Nails who's
Bales who's bails is she ate your name
to bae
yo yo sorry I don't know what it is but
I just I
um Bells
like a mother figure
doesn't want what the [\h__\h] sounds like
balls
balls balls balls
like the balls on your nose balls
what if I got your nose
what if I got your nose no no no what if
I got your nose what if I got you hold
on yeah what no I'm gonna fight you I'm
gonna break I'm gonna break your puppet
I'm gonna break your puppet unbreakable
Kimmy Schmidt you cannot break me the
[\h__\h] um who is that it's a TV Netflix
show I think
um
You probably I don't think you would
like
is it a girly show it's
it's is it like Gilmore Girls It's not
like yellow girls uh I wouldn't say it
says girl as girly as Gilmore Girls but
it's just like stupidly funny stupid I
like the the plot though because it's
about uh Kimmy Schmidt who was like
stuck on the ground
uh in a bunker
with like three other ladies and then
eventually she comes out of the bunker
after years and years and years and then
the world is like so fast crazy
different yeah and that's like the whole
comedy about it
oh no I mean that kind of sounds like
something I'd like somebody says it's
the same humor as ferty rock you know
that oh yeah I like that show oh see I
don't know that one that well it's kind
of funny what's that about funny rocks
that's the one about the um that's the
one about like the TV station right guys
yeah
and like the newscasters or something oh
it's not Anchorman it's it's like a am I
is that by Tina Fang is that is that
what it is that the one yes okay yeah
all right that's what I thought it's
about 30 rocks
I got a couple Chuckles off of watching
that a parody of NBC
or SNL
yeah you gave me some Chuckles well
we have to watch uh Gilmore guys Guild
more guys thank you yeah I came up with
that because I was like oh yeah the
Gilmore Girls thing and when I was
reading the script I was like uh is this
a typo or should I really no it's not a
typo I guess you were just protecting us
from copyright story yeah Tai hen nah
copyright strikes thank you for
protecting us from that also you're
welcome Kat Harris from my own cats that
I brought with me oh Austria oh tonkers
and smoothie no
oh no I mean you can I mean you can have
them maybe I don't want them that bad
jeez still here it's LOL
okay
[Music]
um but we'll have to
um Make some noise Make some noise
okay so we need
um I'll be I'll be the Bro house broken
gouda because it's difficult to operate
her okay and then you can be Iris and
amen how about that okay sounds good so
you'll be switching to Iris
now I have four heads let me do let me
do a little surgical procedure yes I
love uh I'm his teeth
[Music]
so justice but I don't think I did it
justice it's very SpongeBob core
um true true yeah we're changing the
sock tuber models camera right angle
what's up the camera angle
we mean it's fine it's fine
ah Erica oh God she's like so broken
oh my God your head is not attached to
her mouth anymore it's oh Lord it will
work for one song I'll make it work hold
on I'm gonna have to do irises backwards
for various reasons you put on
backlights yeah otherwise it's just it's
hard to explain
I can see a bit
Mike yeah that's okay that's fine
hey all right I'll do Iris on that um
God
[Music]
well I mean it's it's our new update it
update looks good
she has the same eyes yeah that's that's
goodbye eyes
it's gonna make it to the museum uh yeah
I just worry about you know the staff
whoever will be in charge of putting
them into position I hope it will go
well oh
Emilio what's up
what's up
like spontaneously who's singing and
then react all right I'll try my best
I'll try the Snowman
[Music]
[Applause]
yourself
[Music]
today's this play time
[Applause]
[Music]
emotions
y'all are freaking psychotic
attack
it
Iris it's Iron Man
this is next
complicated
[Music]
give me something
yay
[Music]
it's honest
Amelia
whole Lab number one detective right yes
action
okay
that was enough to scare titu away
okay I think you can take up Iris yay so
virus I think you can put on diamonds
because next time will be free people oh
boy so I will be fun and Mommy okay you
me can you guess what that will be chat
[Music]
again
I love the song but I don't know who
sings When so you might have to like
give me hints if you remember I'll try
my best I know that movie sings a lot of
the longer parts
all right all right here we go long time
no see
your hair is around your nose let me
help you you had a stream with these
just you right yeah twice like one one
members only and one uh public one oh
very nice yeah but you guys if you guys
have seen the sock puppet magic they
have and also of course I use them for
the Advent calendar for Nelly if you
remember I remember that apparently I'm
falling now
hi
[Music]
um
no you're not please do not jump up on
that box
two two I'm [\h__\h] begging you now do
not jump on that box
do not jump on that box
do not jump on that jump on that
[\h__\h] box
please
some cat hair
yeah sorry that's kind of hair
everywhere
I imported it please oh
do you want to play with Iris
to come play with Iris just don't
destroy her because they have to make it
to for uh Expo thingy that's true
they're gonna be in a museum
[Music]
I have a toy for you it's Iris
I'm sacrificing Iris what yes you have
to stop here
we go she'll just go from hyrux to virus
together
[Music]
I think it's smooth um
knees
[Music]
ladies and gentlemen welcome to snow
Miku hello
[Music]
thank you
years and
I hear that beat from town the cute
angel will come down
[Music]
Mommy
baby
[Music]
nice nice
serious fauna bye-bye
[Music]
wait I have an idea
remember
[Music]
um
that we could reenact oh we could do
like nope it's a plastic yes you're
getting the plastic
[Music]
done
I want to do things I have like more
than one dance
[Music]
I want to see uh Callie doing something
alone even Nanny one of your songs which
one do you want to read oh
I wonder
uh a more funny one oh we could also do
miff or treat but the problem is just
we'll be missing one person uh yeah we
can just throw myself in there like just
as like a softer
[Music]
Cali's solo performance and then we're
gonna try to
oh wait look at the iris and caliber
more singing red oh nice idea all right
I'll be Irish that's cool okay
I'll do this
who was this is this a toy that's a toy
exciting
[Music]
us we already did that come on world
you're late
I already did that here you go here's
I'm ready come on I'm ready to go I'm
reeling to go
[Music]
let's go I wish the Moon is
dead and now I can't get rid of all of
these thorns
singing
inside of me
[Music]
red tomorrow that's a day
dread sorrow can't turn away
[Music]
levels
red sorrow can't turn away
can't turn back
[Music]
now once again so I can chase you down
we are five minutes away from
continue
[Music]
or else just fade away
yeah you're killing it you're doing good
pedals
[Music]
[Laughter]
for me sabotage
[Music]
that's called karma boys
incredible
all right I got you
I got you a Little Help From The Shadows
a Little Help from the Shadows I think
it ripped off her head from her mouth
sorry I was retiring sorry I was dead
sorry
did we ever do an archived karaoke
together or only on our captain ah we
had like one portion be archived
and one was not archived so like Lion
for example
[Music]
I wonder if
are you old long ago long ago it was
this before I left Japan yeah this was
during the bye-bye stream I believe good
good old memories
don't worry guys we can't do Jet Plane
because this room is archived don't
worry about it they have like real bad
flashbacks
you ready
yeah
no I just I was trying to scare him away
oh
God
what are you doing buddy okay buddy I
really can't you really gotta get ready
okay
gotta be ready before I'm ready for lion
here we go come on ghost come on ghost
[Music]
s
hey hey hey
hey
[Music]
that's me
another song
[Music]
hey hey
all right take it away
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
don't die
[Music]
um
here we go
[Music]
picking up
[Applause]
[Music]
my brains came out
I'm getting a little aggressive
[Music]
this song is dope I was listening
[Laughter]
I am totally naked naked in my lower
body all right by this one pixel that
they saw no I
never are you naked am I I can't tell
all right let's see what should we do
next ah yeah
um
[Music]
oh wait actually I guess there's an
archive of it right foreign
there it is
[Music]
yes
I'm a big fan of this song
Ricky
income
[Music]
[Applause]
you know
[Music]
nice Harmony
hey what up what's up
[Music]
um
wow some Harmony going up you have a
Harmony
[Music]
wow
thank you for reminding me
[Music]
my brains
[Applause]
[Music]
much difference
yeah thank you you're welcome it's one
of my favorites once again
that's cringe yes yes it feels good yeah
[Music]
she's here
um
[Music]
it's too easy
you're here
you will not
again
[Music]
a a
h
um
[Music]
we can't
hey hey hey
[Music]
you know it kind of looks like my veil
oh nice nice I'll put it back in there
[Music]
awesome
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
la la la la la
la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la la la la la la
la la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la
[Music]
[Laughter]
mine don't really do that
[Music]
they'll calm down don't worry I hope
that's okay though I don't mind oh my
God thank you for 15 membership give
totally yeah let's go let's go maybe
some deadbeats got those yeah let's go
watch the Wawa membership oh by the way
guys is there like something you would
want these two sock puppets to talk
about maybe like sock things ooh sock
things what's what's the kind of
struggles you guys have of songs hey
koala what's the stinkiest shoe you've
ever been inside Steve his shoe yeah you
mean as in like someone else's stinky
shoe yeah
[Music]
no only my I guess I'm usually only in
my own shoes for me had to be girl's
shoes because she's the
she's the certified stanky member well
what that reminds me you know when I was
recording bringing it at Emma's place
yeah
um I needed to borrow socks and I
borrowed good as socks back then were
they stinky they ended up no they were
like not stinky before she gave them to
me but you know I made them very stinky
wedding so much because Anna's place was
like hot as [\h__\h] oh and yeah I was
dancing the whole day and at the end of
the day I was like sorry sorry go down
for doing this to you and then I came
from practice stinky socks but oh she
can throw them in the washer yeah
hopefully she's in lines yeah yeah it's
fine what do you think happens when you
like dance for eight [\h__\h] hours yeah
the deadbeats do that to me too Mori dot
dot I hate that I hate when they do that
stop it's like what what did that do
wrong listen because sometimes I really
don't know what what they mean and
they're like yeah they're like what and
sometimes they do it on purpose just to
make me like freak out like that it's
code for or it's obvious dumbass it's
not
levels of you know
Toleration yeah
what
do your feet get stinky if you don't
wear socks and you put shoes on
I mean I normally don't do that unless
like in summer when I'm wearing like
sandals
what do you think about people who wear
socks on their sandals
they only exist in Japan
oh well outside of Japan
[Music]
cringe
cringe you know I think maybe I only
once or twice I've seen someone who
makes it work
but usually I don't think it works but
you do you you do you this is a sock
podcast now soccer cast yeah so let me
let me see Chad let me see any any
problems
um like speech related problems are okay
too tell me about your feet related
problems anybody have warts on their
toes what what's on their toes oh my God
you want to know like TMI are you gonna
show me a word no I don't I don't have a
voice on my on my foot now but can I
tell you TMI yeah maybe help people who
Awards on their foot what the [\h__\h] yeah
this will really be an idea
we talking about what I think when I was
like
um maybe when I was like 12 or something
like really young I had I think it was
Awards on on the back of my foot okay
I'm sure everybody has it maybe once in
their life yeah I don't know why why why
do they happen though yeah well there's
no reason guys tell me tell me by the
way but so I had it once in my life okay
and
um I I don't know where I got the idea I
think I saw on the internet somebody
wrote that a banana peel if you if you
like rub the banana peel over the words
it will like just you know heal it and
it
I put I rubbed the banana peel over the
warts and then it just fell off kind of
like the next day it was kind of gone
are you sure it wasn't just a placebo no
really because I didn't do anything else
besides that and yeah it worked I was
like shocked
I mean it kind of seems like a dirty
filthy lie but all right if you say if
you say a word then I believe you
hey
it seems like it sounds fake but okay no
it's
not it's this what do you think I'm
missing too yes that's fake
[Music]
on your back she's my
cohorts no Anna's here with us she's a
secret guest it was fake no fake no
[Music]
if it has a lot of vitamin A that might
actually help oh why not just find
vitamin A and just rub it on the wound
actually it was actually a watch to
begin with I mean I think so
I'm not gonna look up words just now on
Google to then discuss Myself by what
they look like why not I think that was
what it was can you prove it no I can't
prove it now just believe my [\h__\h]
words I never lied to you as you know
I'm always honest to you guys all right
find a wart on your body and put it on
the camera
[Music]
currently oh yeah you want to prove it
is it wart in English word oh
in English
[Music]
here there's your Amit you happy now
I don't care I don't think she will let
me in English oh
you smell no no no
no no that's great what's gonna say
about that ah we should let amateur
fight
let's go fight I'll mess on my fight
it's wrestling time
Polo WrestleMania who can destroy each
other first oh boy
let's see if I can turn my hand or hold
on
[Music]
you're on my right my right arm was
really tired from swinging my Scythe
around now my left arm is gonna be
really tired I'm Gonna Get You flexing
on me with the the doctor that was not
heavy
that was not even that was happening
heavy no it wasn't
that was not the hang
hey I don't even know how I can't I
can't like replicate how good it looks I
don't get movement [\h__\h]
[Music]
shut up Watson
I'm not toxic I wonder if there's like a
like a Amazon
oh nice idea I'm not toxic what's the
best amazona clip of the internet has to
offer look up I missed on it hot
foreign
[Music]
gets really embarrassed when Anna tries
to look at her feet IRL three years
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you guys
honestly oh
yeah Kiana is in the background oh
let me see
[Music]
recommended
I know who's talking
they all sound the same to me
who was that that was me
I just hear good at screaming I think
that was pretty good no I'm
not happy that was a pretty good one
though
that was a pretty spicy one snuggles
ooh
I'm gonna go to IRL we're touching grass
and smelling weird things together we're
just talking with things
oh my God
I'm gonna share some my real facts
uh-huh oh
ah
what's this oh is this the rust is
[Music]
hello
uh who is this
[Music]
hello
it works hello
[Music]
um
I'm here to talk to you about your
boat's extended warranty I don't have a
boat nice try
uh can you put me um
list please
um well uh how about after after you
answer the survey I will put you on our
iron iron intensively checked doodle
call list uh how long is the surveyor
and
it'll take no more than five minutes of
your time I greatly appreciate it you
see I'm paid on commission and the
higher the rating uh would you possibly
care to leave a Google review as well oh
we would really appreciate that
all right sorry guys I don't accept spam
calls
is she still going I hope she's still
going
[Music]
foreign
taxi and detective agency uh here to
notify you of a new business opening up
in your neighborhood
how old is that is it free uh first ride
free one way one way what happens at the
end of the one way you have to pay to go
back if you want to ride back
take me to go back uh-huh gas is
expensive okay we'll just uh letting you
know if a new service in the area you
can call me back at this number huh you
won't be getting any five stars
not a scam it's business
stop streaming now goodbye everyone
thank you for watching
foreign
[Music]
[\h__\h] has been reached
thank you please call again later
that's the end I loved it
cute Perfecto detecto so that's where de
facto detecto came from I never heard
that before I think oh I did but it's
for a thing that nobody's heard yet
never mind never mind
[Music]
oh 20
years
I mean I've ran into my right hand oh
that's right
wow okay I was thinking about that too
how about we do you you
um it's a bit difficult to control her
but do you want to control gouda real
quick for we're gonna reenact the one
two five clip oh God
all right one two five I'll give it my
best
aren't we all a little broken inside
it's okay okay aren't we ghost cat
aren't we all a little broken inside oh
[\h__\h] oh it's not plugged in one of the
cats must have unplugged it
yeah it's okay you can just there's a
little hole in the side of the laptop
here okay look it should be on that side
I think the cat's unplugged it
yeah
they like to they like to sabotage me
there's nothing I can do about it I I
think it's something to treasure because
one day when they're old and and slow
they will not like they won't sabotage
no okay
wait did I mess up
no I think I thought
thank you
Okay so
[Laughter]
[Music]
am I crying
Okay so
is I give you the benefit of the doubt
that you still don't understand what I'm
talking about
is that we have in in Australia we have
the no the grades uh one two three four
five which is one two five uh
[Laughter]
how would you even get such a stupid
idea that's so ridiculous
oh my God and then in Germany it's one
two three four five six okay so that's
that
okay and then number one the eins we
also call sagut
wasn't it
well yeah I feel like I was missing some
I feel like I was missing some context
yeah
where's the context
of songs me
yeah yeah I'll just throw myself in the
middle like okay
okay someone else
um yeah wait who who's myth again
who's
[Laughter]
[Music]
what's up puppets
he's just been sitting there peeking at
us the whole time oh that's sweet yeah
he hasn't been doing anything except
messing with the headphones
[Music]
damn it you have to put on at least one
like two two hands all right hold on I
know
I'll do it hold on
ghost cat don't mess with the puppets
though please I'm begging you little
buddy now I'll give you treats later I
promise I'll give you some treats
please
okay
yes it's close enough
profit yeah okay here we go come on
Cowie
[Music]
let's go Kelly go Kelly go Kelly
it is
those red teeth
[Music]
can't escape
can your sugars
[Applause]
make yourselves more straight please
you can't no her brain no it's her veil
I mean my veil
is Art mimics reality it's fine
oh look at that Smith I'm repeating myth
beautiful
[Music]
with that uh I will hint you guys I'm
planning uh an off collab for after the
3D Shenanigans yay yeah um probably on
like the seventh of yay March I want to
do something like a game show on my
channel yeah yeah it's not quite a game
show because there's not like several
games but it's like one game that will
do planning it right now
yay let's go get excited Cowie
yeah Kelly are you alive
because this weekend
this weekend yeah
[Music]
they're gonna be 3D yeah that's right
Kelly wake up wake up you have to
rehearse for yourself
go I'm fine I'm just paralyzed from all
the rehearsal oh just let her sleep I
hope she will revive herself like a
phoenix until then ah please kindly I
need you she'll be okay I mean she'll be
okay
get excited you guys I'm excited I'm
excited you guys like I'm as I like
previously said I'm like pretty much
done with my rehearsals and all that and
just chilling for now same trying to
calm I just have to focus on the Apex
event that's all um
yeah but you don't really have the calm
yeah it's just storm all storm for me oh
it's storm only storm always only storm
chat is excited the two thank you Chad
I'm glad to hear you guys are excited
for going on the floor as usual yeah I
mean she's it's where she it's where she
belongs it's a comfortable yoga mat
yeah you know yesterday yesterday
um you know I came to my room
uh to uh give me some what was it yeah
yeah
and when she came to my room she was
wearing this like super long
lab coat
yeah that sounds about right it's not
that cold no milky one it's not a lab
coat everybody looked like one it was
like super long and I was like doctor
enough that's the most unicorn thing
I've ever heard yeah it's like mad
scientist you know just like in Memphis
I asked for a permission to tell this so
don't worry guys but it's basically it
goes down to ankles literally a white
like a shirt but it's not like it's like
oversized it's just somehow it's that
design yeah I've never seen that before
scientists
unicorn yeah you know where it's very
unicorn
yes he was basically like cosplaying
you'll you'll be I love that you will be
oh my God
yeah that's nice I like that that's good
you gotta make the characters though
it's just these but you put like hats on
them and [\h__\h] you gotta make them look
like the characters oh yeah
it's part of the fun
part of the fun
what's ghost what's ghosty boy doing
everything yeah
oh he loves to play he loves to play
look at the guy he's a little gentleman
most of the time
I miss you uh Tiara misses you too don't
worry
she had a white hair scout was blonde we
need new socks eh I made so many I made
11 because no yeah because I made two
Grill basically oh yeah George where's
George see George Have You Done reflect
I've done several times it was so much
fun pretty good there no no get your
nail out of Watson no
consists of six members yeah let's go
you heard it here first this one's still
you know I even drew blood on the teeth
do you see that oh wow attention to
detail very nice yummy stuff
cute look at them
looks like only oh yeah people keep on
saying it looks like always now part of
myth okay
what you can make them kiss
good
our fantasies
here we go here we go hold on hold on
this is a big thing on Tumblr back in
the day oh
just don't ask about it
but no it would be the other way around
I feel like George would be like the
really like intense one and girl be like
no no wait I don't feel that way and
then and then George would be like yes
give in to the inner shark is that what
reflect two will be about yeah
yeah the true feelings of the two no I
don't think girl would like that very
much sorry
don't be mad it's just it's just fan
fiction
it's just fan fiction please
please don't be mad Lord lore and yo yo
hey yo I was not ready for this
hey yo where my stream gets shut down
for inappropriate behavior no no no wait
Kelly knows no stop I just want to do my
face yeah it really was a Tumblr kid
no well maybe a little bit I mean that
used to be on on Tumblr there was some
interesting stuff there back in the day
back in the day
is does Tumblr still exist probably yeah
yeah it does just not as popular
return to the Sea a shark is all you'll
ever be
but I can't go without you
don't say things like that you're being
cringed
you're being cringe girl
but
fine I'll just go without you oh wait so
the language was calling us cringe the
other day was huh this one this one this
is the one right here okay no you can't
leave without me
why why are you being so mean to me and
then say that you want to be with me
shut up
[Music]
do you love me
cringe I am you
Buddha wait we still have to kiss okay
kiss
kiss kissing is cringe but okay
no stop eating me
[Laughter]
I'm gonna put on Kelly hey
that's all from George folks
oh no she got this connected what Kelly
is disconnected yeah do you have do you
happen to have hot glue
I might have something that can help
disconnected yeah the the the the the
head is disconnected from no that's why
her brains are so much out right now oh
I see well just let it be a veil
I will have to probably like fix it a
little bit for the
um for the Ohio for the museum it'll
still look cool though yeah it's okay
because you know I've played with them
so many times now they're they're bound
to fall apart I'm going to be some wear
and tear
and now I am
um
cringe I we I had to do it I had to do
it
no you're not quite a myth
everyone else got to smooch
okay all takamuni shippers are going
like that's enough fan service for you
cringe Lords
oh sand here I'll give you back Callie
she's so broken do I have to make Cali
2.0 too he's stinky
and that's that's like one more song
about what should we do how about where
is it
we can do
all right I can serve you
got no uh
[Music]
pretty sure yeah I think we did
I know what you mean by disconnected
that's okay it's fine I'll make her work
I have a special way I see I'm connected
by soul to my little model so it's fine
well okay this is our final song
it's the end of the party let's hit the
road before I have to flashback to
Shinigami
they gotta run but thanks for watching
what I put out though it's not a ton
excuse me sorry hand Time to Say Goodbye
again promise it's a matter of time to
find my best friends it's not the end of
yucky cause every close doors to stick
and you have a brand new sorry one wish
that I can't pretend I don't wanna see
come true I know it wouldn't make a
difference if you thought of me as much
as I think about you but maybe it's
deliverance from the pain I know it's
coming on is
that 49 cause we're immortalized forever
when the songs that we write you know
not sorry but I want to see you again
sometime a song in my heart a world of
Glory falling on your mind words and we
leave it all behind attack
up close your eyes for a minute and
envision a place where everybody's
cherishing life in one safe space and
it's embarrassing to say because you're
the one that I chased but see mortality
is what makes a life sweeter than a
tastes right fatalities fallacies sweet
and sour simmer freeze time with me
refreshing like a hot and Breeze
honestly it's messing with the reaper
mentality sleeping on the fact that
history has told me how to be do I
despise human life something really is
not enough just to see you every once in
a while searching in the darkness of my
world for a smile there's you Mata Asus
[Music]
say goodbye
see you again sometime
[Music]
see you again sometimes
I got the middle finger going through it
time to kill this monster yeah
I choked her I suffocated her she's gone
I think you'll be able to fix her though
you can fix her okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah that was yeah I have the mic on
maximum volume out of trauma
well
Ness no cat accident isn't that right
ghost cat now that you said that we've
jinxed it so we might want to end
quickly
[Music]
wow guys you know what it is on this
weekend uh Saturday is quinoa 3D
showcase this is not it surprisingly
this is
in case in case you thought that it was
this is not it
there's some really really
surprised yes coming and I promise you
guys won't want to miss it it's really
freaking awesome oh
come over
here no no eventually I want to see
yeah everything will make sense yay
afterwards
and then the week after you already know
yeah
together which we've been practicing for
too yeah
[Music]
I love you
that was the chat
no just kidding I love you too I'm
joking I'm joking
thank you for letting me do this here
and for playing with me because no one
else would do it I love this kind of
goofy [\h__\h] no I'm down anytime I gotta
make more sock puppets yeah one day I'll
I'll um where's ID maybe next time when
I get um you know bronchitis and all
that [\h__\h] again wait a minute you have
bronchitis when you made these when I
had these I had laryngitis bronchitis
and a sinus infection wait a minute so
you mean to tell me that your bronchitis
germs are on these socks
they're dead by now what the [\h__\h]
oh that was in in December oh my God
that's it get out of my house
get out of my house no I'm joking with
you it's fine
yeah they don't last that long I'm just
playing around with you I'm just playing
around with you anyway now I want to
play around with your Kitty cartoons
okay yeah we can play a little bit I
have a mess
yeah because he's scared shitless
whatever
I've never seen him so cool
right now he's all tuckered out he's all
tuckered out here everybody you're so
big he has the body of a of a kitten at
the ears of an adult cat oh
I'm touching cattle with other hand
he's soft and cute anyway this Kelly has
to go to the hospital yeah
thank you for coming today
very fun thanks a lot for the fun time
guys see you again soon okay yeah
tomorrow I'll play
um Fire Emblem so I can tell you all my
tangents that have been uh you know what
do you how do you say it like loading up
oh uh accumulated accumulate
accumulating tangent yeah so many the ID
stories yeah you got so much also I'm
performing at the Apex live show and
it's being streamed on Twitch and
YouTube and there's no archive being
left so you're going to want to stay
tuned yeah no you can watch it stream
but there's no archive so go watch it
yeah
well it's better than no stream at all I
guess so just make sure you don't miss
it okay guys so we see Cali and Freddy
yeah oh
yeah oh my God yeah the Stadium's really
big too so come check it out I'm excited
I'm nervous I'm nervous but excited the
rehearsal went really well so hopefully
tomorrow goes good too the tangents have
tangents by now yes I do yeah I want to
hear you gotta tell me
you're so easy okay okay swag and with
that I say in German we say
um
[Music]
[Applause]
there's a curl up bye
see you later guys
[Music]
ghost cat has
become a mountain climber and he was on
my shoulder he was on my shoulders
oh comparing to the microphone everyone
or I wonder that probably doesn't pick
it up I don't know it depends it's a
pretty loud yes hear that please tell me
against them
[Music]
yeah
we also have the cat's purring the whole
time yeah
ouch don't love bite me
luckiest cat
[Music]
I want to cuddle all the cats in the
world
[Music]
she's gonna steal them no these are two
chaos you can't have him I want to
cuddle with them come here baby boy yeah
you good boy you're my good boy
wow his legs get like so long when he's
like that yeah he's got a lot of eggs
he's like a giraffe
[\h__\h] giraffe giraffe goes good all
right oh mommy is a parkour isn't she
is that nice and warm for you
oh no you can't eat this is the real no
no no no he was oh my God two two's here
too
baby stop babies come on little ones
time for dinner I gotta make your dinner
don't fight no fighting