[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
good day good morning good evening
everybody
good morning
how are you doing
here sleeping yeah
kittens whoa there I found something
sleepy and I can only think of a kitten
meow come here
bye guys welcome back to to babu's gate
to be Drew's gate to build those gate
yeah
um
yeah I love you for saying that yeah
I thought you might be impressed by that
reference yeah just by you saying it
yeah just by saying Bilbo Baggins
um
precious oh I need to clarify again why
I decided to stream today yes the main
reason because I had just been I just
went off of a tirade telling everybody
we don't need four povs but here's the
thing
um I realized if people go to my channel
and they're looking for a collab and
there's like randomly one missing they
miss a big chunk of the story so I feel
like I have to stream every single time
because people go to my channel and
they're like oh I want to watch all of
Kelly's baller's gate and then they
click all of them and then they miss one
and then then they're confused
you know what I what you could do for
that I have a solution what let's say
you stream part one part two but not
part three yeah then make a playlist for
battle skate and then just put part
three of someone else in there oh true
that's a good ballad but you know there
are people who wouldn't wouldn't check
it out yeah
playlists for your game series sometimes
sometimes it depends I have a lot of
game series oh my God there's a bug on
my screen let me kill it really quick oh
it is
let the cats let the cats take them yeah
ooh more toys for the cats how are you
guys doing
it's 3 P.M at my time zone
oh wow yeah
emotional people are here yeah they love
it they're like interesting they're
super I'm winning I want to listen
can you impersonate Gollum for me
um
what's tater's brushes
wriggling fish
[Laughter]
that's a solid impression
got him
whoa okay excuse me oh
all right I'm getting kind of nutty I
like it very
I never stop was kind of I have to say
before the stream started she was kind
of savage I love it I was not being
Savage Girl boss mode all right go with
the queen as they said go off Queen I
don't know why it sounds so wrong to
hear you say that to me me yeah
foreign
[Applause]
get rich when we eventually get to
Baldur's Gate I have to play somewhere
where there's lots of people because
apparently there's an achievement where
you have to get a hundred coins from one
one time playing yeah okay I just
realized I don't have shoes on yeah I
just saw that too ew those dogs out for
free for free yeah I was just looking at
your feet actually please stop I don't
have shoes no it's cool it's like nice
and far away just so it's like basically
a little tantalizing but like not the
full thing you know okay I'm happy
imagination
okay you have to feel the Earth become
one with the earth oh no God it's
healthy to go uh Barefoot apparently
yeah yeah so you get scabs on your feet
and then yeah I'm Barefoot all the time
step on some glasses oh yeah oh yeah
people is Barefoot gang yeah I am
Barefoot game well I think it's an Asian
thing because I always
I never understood wearing shoes in the
house I don't wear shoes in the house
either yeah yeah I think that's an n a
thing yeah but once you've moved in
Europe we don't wear shoes in our homes
it's definitely a real I was raised to
take my shoes off when I came in the
house so I don't know what people are
talking about when they say that it
scares me I just see it in American TV
shows all the time and it makes me feel
so disgusted
with their shoes
I've been told it's a TV thing is is it
not also reality
it was just it was there I mean it was
just there I couldn't help myself
they seem fine
one thing uh there was an update where
cutscenes you can listen in you can
eavesdrop automatically so we turned
that on so now it should be easier for
everybody to stay on track with what's
going on
[Music]
will try to lead the way today team
leader I don't know where we're going
but good luck maybe an innocent mind is
the best mind to go through this map I
would say so yeah yeah last time we were
were we done exploring the city I don't
think so oh completely or were we for
the most part we were we talked to the
big guy who wanted us to go who wanted
to come with us to kill someone oh yeah
where's the mushroom guy the cute
mushroom guy he's not cute oh the big
the big wheels as in he's down here in
this game
yeah we're down here hi where's our
Deuter
he is not our guy he is our guy he's our
daughter
what do you say team leader
me you want him to come with us yeah of
course I hired him last time but he
didn't stay so
far
[Music]
slimy slimy friends
what
he's icky and why does he want to ask so
many questions again
oh cause we already did it
wait how do I get him to join again
eh cause we keep the one who joined us
yeah
we did
yeah buddy boy
it reveals
oh
um we might need to kill the guy first
and then he might come with oh just see
the to see the dead body murder but he
was already part of us our team last
time
specifically because she doesn't like
him it reveals it oh he cringed
you made him cringe narissa
good
okay no good
who is he following before me because I
was like the only one who was willing to
take him in
but now he's done talking with me oh wow
maybe another time yeah maybe another
time
do you really want a sovereign named
glut following you around
he's not that bad
yeah
well then let's continue this way
we have something on the map we want to
follow
um well if we keep going this way we'll
eventually come across probably the guys
that we're supposed to destroy okay
Battle Royale is here for battle
I love battle
I'm here we don't have any short rest
left right oh I don't think so we need
to go back to Camp which I don't mind
doing but we might want a long rest soon
because I have no spell okay well that's
not great I mean look into it now too
sure all right go to camp
we're going to Camp Lads do you want to
end the day yeah sure we have a mushroom
camp
[Applause]
thank you hey boys what's going on dog
oh
the good doggy I got his ball what a
good doggy
Shadow heart approves of me petting the
good boy
I don't know where I am I'm sitting in a
van of Darkness
um
okay it loaded finally leave oh
the leg
Shadow heart looks like she's missing
like her bottom legs when she sits like
that oh yeah I can see what you mean
Starion put on some clothes Jesus
[Music]
took it from him I'm wearing his clothes
okay I'm fine if he wants to stay like
that yeah give it give it back to him
well I'll give him I'll give him a set
of clothes okay he can have Michael's I
think Cali needs to give it to him wait
oh that's why we can't because he's not
in the party so he can't give him yeah
[Music]
she's been kind of a hot pose like wow
I'm like spinning around my character
right now
not that I want to see but like I'm
gonna go look yeah you should you should
just as always
this
Wellies
hotkeys yeah because I'm not using a
controller oh are you using keyboards
again yep quickly
inspectus tea
cool I wish when you were a tiefling you
could change your tail color yeah
because the skin colored tail looks very
odd
[Music]
that'll be kind of neat
yeah
it's just kind of
just kind of it's just kind of fleshy
you know just kind of oh well let me it
Blends in with your skin you look at
Carla she has it too yeah she's red so
it doesn't look weird it doesn't look
weird it looks it looks cool
yeah you look a little bit like ah
what's it called
the the Minecraft little thing that
everybody wanted to collect
Minecraft animals yeah
yeah
everybody all rested
yeah I think they don't want really want
to talk what do you call the Syrian over
while he's walking oh yeah where did he
put it
yeah
this is so weird he's getting down look
at him get down he's like yes you've
been scratched his listening oh my God
relax likes it very popular I want to
get down too hold on can I can I do a
can I do a gym yeah are there emotes how
do we know
dancing mode
Let Me dance
I I know I know Carlock randomly does
dances sometimes can we do that yeah
teach us Carla teach us how to break
down I feel like oh yeah I'm getting
down
yeah I'm feeling it uh do it again oh no
emotes yet oh he's screaming strongly
okay get away from me let's sleep
go to bed you big silly wait they're
giving me money we're missing
they're picking up what you're putting
down nurisa keep it up
and I mean for all of us
you're going to be sharing some of that
pot right of course we all share an
inventory anyway hold on a sec
sipping on the coffee hoping I can sleep
tonight
good luck
another player is currently choosing
camp supplies Ah that's what that
message was
yeah wow all right
nightmares what's happening
not again
every freaking time
oh
down
I guess yeah it's because he likes you
the best bro I could totally kill you I
could snap you like a twig my man
[Music]
oh that would be funny melee attack
see um I see how long did you have you
it's been since that's why you were so
quick to kill the girl Hunter to keep
your secret
I'm not some monster I can't prove it I
feed on Adam this is really uncomfy
because you're in your tidy way whatever
I can get
yeah too weak he's thirsty okay if I
just had a little blood nice color I
like that Clara fight better
I'm sure Cali has plenty of blood I am
okay
you sure you want this over blood
it tastes really yucky it tastes like
swamp water
I don't care how much you need you're
not drinking my blood now why didn't you
tell me bro okay I'm joking I'm joking
I'm not gonna do them dirty no
yeah he's a good boy I needed you to
trust me
can trust me
yeah I'm gonna give him my blood become
bloodless and we're not even going to
use him on the team
you tried to bite me how can I trust you
I do I believe you thank you we had a
nice time in the woods I'll let it slide
you could trust me just
a little further
though he's really taking what he can
get
it
he's a taker
fine but a drop more than you need and
I'll kill you go too far I'll drive a
stake through your chest all right no
not a drop more than you need all right
of course
not one drop more
car sounds comfortable dude's so shady
Kelly said soon today for him look it's
only because this big British ogre is
hilarious okay trust me
it's really funny please believe me I
don't need to explain myself further
than that patches your pulse quickens
oh my Shrek juice
that's enough
but what if he kills me bro if that was
a one
I wish it would have been a one that
would have been so funny it would have
been super funny please get all done
sucking enough like does that mean he
can like kill you maybe
oh shut up
what if you like keep letting him drink
more and more like does he kill you
melee yeah his cars don't grab a steak
and drive it it is
just in case you want to kill him so
many people
yeah that's weird this is a really weird
pose
[Laughter]
yes he will kill you
he watches he stalks off
it's a freak what a little freaky baby
man ready to hunt
um did you just call him a freaky baby
man I mean yeah survive he gives me
freaky baby man vibes
you guys need anything else here can we
dip no I mean dip all right let's get
back oh do you guys know what they call
Shadow heart on the internet what yes
and I will not repeat it it's so funny
though
is it lewd
uh
why are you stickering no it's not it's
just gross
they call they call her sharks
[Laughter]
no it's not it's
uh do you know what a shark is
well I could I could put a few things
together in my brain yeah
but surely they mean Shadow heart heart
right no that's not cool let's just say
let's just say they mean that all right
lead the way oh wait I have a request
since we just
um did a quick rest there's a fight
that's really strong oh that I need
that's down here can we go to there
first sure yeah okay down
um what is it there's a weapon down here
that I have to collect three pieces of
it to staff oh
um yeah
um can we go to the seller night Outpost
isn't that where we came from yes so
yeah okay yeah we teleport it's still in
the underdark but we're gonna go out a
different direction maybe Amazon okay
okay
uh selenite
cell cellulite
sillies cellulite under dark my
con it
it's in the inside yeah three points
lower lower right oh I see
okay
cellulite
Waypoint Outpost I'm on my way Temple of
cellulite Temple of cellulo here we go
and there's gonna be a big fight
I'm ready to go crazy with my ladies
okay big big girls let's go
oh there's like a lot of uh statues that
are petrified
I wonder if first they were afraid and
then they were petrified
and kept thinking
surprised I'm surprised
I'm surprised too
laugh for me chat
I'll laugh for you call me
you're funny
thank you hey that's
no it doesn't it's a real laugh a fake
laugh would be
was a real laugh
it was a little fake
not one of these things that looks like
from monster Inc oh yeah
oh
that's a lot of teeth oh my God it's a
big Mike Wazowski
who's that dude
[Music]
I'm gonna take this one oh
Thorn uh probably should have done a
little quick save before
well might as well do it now wrong okay
yeah this is why it's good to fight this
when we after like we just rushed
because this is a hard fight
yeah our enemy too yeah oh where's my
Dash
are the unpetrified ones also our
enemies now yep
seems to be the case
let's get out of here
um oh boy
and stuff
spectator
I wonder if it's better to kill the
smaller ones first
um
I mean it depends what you like I like
the
I like to kill whoever I managed to kill
in one hit usually
um my whole team because then that's
less people attacking
oh big electric shock yeah shock em
yeah
that's our enemies
oh yeah I needed something with my pets
again I keep on footing
and then can I hear them you know a lot
of movements so I'll just do a little
you know
I'm not here really bothers me
I'm gonna do a frenzy
yeah
[Music]
well he's distracted
yeah enter
oh first there's a good way to go
he's neutral now oh where's he go hello
come back
oh he killed him oh
what all right he became a good guy
should we not fight him
no we should fight this guy uh you mean
the big dude yeah
it was a waste of frenzy I can't remove
him immobile
oh no dang it it can't be very useful
this way because you're scared oh Mario
a bit scared of nothing that's
unrealistic come on now
[Music]
he's throwing
yikes
yikes 14
oh he's back yeah hit me
bust it down narissa Bust It Down
frenzies
why am I frightening yeah it dodged the
olive arm once earlier like a piece of
surely I can do something
it's not my turn yet you got yeah
I'm still learning the ways of the
keyboard mouse
yeah you girls will have to
fit probably yep we got this no problem
s
thank you
okay
kill them
yes kill them I need them to die okay
leave it to me so really quick save why
is it red oh you can talk to them first
I think they have information
[Music]
all right
now
yeah jump into my cloud of daggers she's
so smart
Mario big hill
I'm told me yay
oh my God
Frenzy
he's really mad
foreign
[Music]
oh nice shot nice
yeah
critically miss you big dumb dumb
[Music]
let's see one of them should have some
things that I need
there's afraid of raw food I'll take
this in this
he's smoking
oh this dude in the cloud of daggers
he's got a ton of stuff I take
everything
yeah
oh wait let me anyone pick up a ice
looking thing let me see eyes my
character got a Polish drink hold on a
sec
character she I have a pendant then
suspected her eyes uh something that
looks like what
ice ice ice oh remember last pendant
which is a lightning blood wasn't the
memory shard
there's something called a blast pendant
which is a lightning blast
um
if somebody wants that
gloves of heroism that's it apparently
the pendant the blast pendant oh at
least Chet says so
you can take it it's not it's a Memory
Shard I am going to you like it if
that's okay yeah get it okay memory
chart
ah
okay
[Music]
that's all I needed I need two more
pieces but we can keep exploring out
when we when we get close okay we'll go
from here then see what we find cool
follow me yeah
follow Liara
[Music]
oh rope oh there's a skeleton this
girlington he's got nothing they're an
empty doll oh this one has nothing I'll
leave it for you though what is this
there's a trap
oh it's a basic poison all right
oh no
walk down
thank you foreign
[Laughter]
good luck bagel
okay
okay yeah
oh knocked down right when we were short
wrestling great oh this little is
it gonna come out or what I wouldn't
mind fighting it we can find them before
easy hand control not down
oh
it sounds great I'm right uh
yeah you can take him to take him you
got this
I don't know about that uh guys I'm just
a Bard I'm just a lowly Barney come up
here
Mia Mamma Mia is supposed to be the ball
yes indeed
it's supposed to be a boo
hi Sarah
that was strong
not very helpful for Far Away
so oh yeah
you need to take place with no reason
yeah
throw a potion on you if you need it
oh nice wait did you hit him
no why would you
go you're good oh no yes
we're The Avengers
everybody knows bards are just the tanks
just don't panic exactly yeah yeah
exactly perfect
now let's see can I uh kill him
I had a fence
a critical miss that doesn't feel good
I keep frenzying right before you guys
kill him
son of a stop being
stronger and there's Garb it's armor
who can wear this I mean I prefer not to
wear armor
armor
okay it's not armor it's clothing
there's a difference apparently I don't
yeah I keep on forgetting I'm wearing
clothing it's not armor
oh you can wear it it's clothes yeah
I'll put them on
somebody unlock this heavy chest
but I'll I'll try I'll give it a hand
hey cool
that's pretty neat
okay let's see him oh but my Nikki I am
wow I'm gonna use inspiration are you
open in the chest
there we go nice oh
a bunch of them wait don't you open it
Spiderwick yep nice mine now cultists
drow studded armor or leather armor
which is 12. rare light armor
um basilisk oil antidote and a creased
paper
that if red says dark mother Weaver of
Destiny offer us a blessing to slay your
foes may they be strangled by the
threads of fate and I'd read in your
image laugh will be praised
okay nice voice thanks thank you
oh wow this armor looks kind of almost
identical to the armor Liara is wearing
oh really I am and look I just put it on
for a minute this place is scary
yes right
yeah yes clearly oh wait wait wait wait
wait shoot the mushrooms first they'll
explode okay yeah yeah
well no problem we can do that pew
[Music]
you want one Chihuahua
oh you guys want to see a secret place
yes oh yeah
okay
we're gonna jump on these shrooms
save game wait actually actually I'm
gonna jump over here for a second
you got it
see you right okay after you guys yeah
oh crap this is over you oh wow doing
here he's got a helmet helmet
where you know what she says
yeah there you go bye bye you're not
gonna take the skill
oh oh uh the festering castle
Chasm sounds fun
oh there's a lot of people around here
who look like they might kill us and my
health is kind of low mm-hmm
oh yeah there are some freaky dudes
we can join us yeah okay yeah
oh yeah oh we got a house
all right House's buddy
nice cool yes brand new Buddies
all right shall we go there then yeah
wait before
mad
are they are we gonna fight them
[Music]
it is okay to go down there that's all
I'll say okay
hold on I'll let Kiana Senpai handle it
and talk I guess creature is lost in
devotion they look like Merlot might as
well yeah
yeah they're just doing a little dance
they don't care they don't like nice
cool guys
the things they're saying aren't very
calm and polite
not
I'm so dirty
and with everything we need a shower
oh blood
wow
is he Satan
kind of looks like it he's bald made of
blood
they are willing it into existence
that's powerful Magic
oh Lord I've murdered oh sacrifice I
hope you can convince him otherwise
[Music]
I'm no one's often get your bearings one
heavy someone uh
oh I have
investigation proficiency
um actually ball is the god of murder
not Bowl
I'm sure
I will say that then
that's so cool
oh God
you're not the god of murder you just
don't want to be
wow
he's a little ugly guy
if it's blood you want I can make
another offer I can here's my teammate
she just gave her blood to a vampire
it's probably chill
yeah
uh I can kill many more in it oh the
immersive
okay I'll oh favorable Beginnings Plus
four I'll try that I have only one life
but I can kill many more in your name I
guess
good luck
oh wow
I can't even give you guidance on this
yeah you gotta really be persuasive
good luck
inspiration yeah
yeah I thought it's worth it uh should I
really you can also just kill him we can
just yeah yeah
no I won't we're gonna slurp you up
coming foreign
my friends
oh yeah
yeah you went right where I wanted to
put my daggers careful
[Music]
nice this bear did anything oh my God
I got electrocuted oh water there's
water on the ground
I want to get out of there bro
it is a little wet
um
Cali is also in the electrocution oh I
feel like I didn't get electrocuted
though
I'm chilling hopefully it'll stay like
that
my fisherman let's party there was one
there
look at one of them is dead oh ha ha
silly fish
it's my cuddle buddy
need something to hug at night sorry was
that supposed to hurt moriope
well I can't wait to kill this little
blood Goblin guy you can do it
yeah
more real pictures for blood
the Mori ope is the one that's thirsting
for murder right now I'm just saying
I guess I should hit this guy Raven will
help you okay please
oh yeah you did that oh it made him
really upset
show
shove him he's so stupid
nice nice one
so much for your God
yeah who's your god now
and everyone else you got here other
than me oh
I actually named this stream Mario pit
is gone
oh wow
and with the bear
Ursa no what's up
huh
come on
my camera okay oh I'm not down he
knocked me I swept me off my feet
are you late welcome let's do a reckless
attack
oh
it's all right I forget
oh huh I forget what happened
on the ground
oh
there's only like wait where where is
the rest there's only three left and
they're all archers so they're gonna be
up to you Liara hard to reach man hard
to reach how are you gonna get him
well first birth goes and then yeah
I don't know I think I can shoot them
yeah check there's rope netting
From Below is yeah definitely not
optimal ah 85 that's not bad
and then where's the other one can't
even see there's one here oh right oh
over here oh
oh oh oh oh oh thank you uh-huh
maybe easier to reach for you actually
good luck oh nice pink good luck you can
read you you can reach him go back yeah
bagel
get them rough Em Up Rock Em Sock Em
done
I missed oh no
okay I'm behind him now
[Laughter]
I slept on people's eyes
[Music]
it's okay I can't blame you I'd lose
yeah
right there yeah
[Music]
let's go
how far
can I shoot from here I doubt it
oh Target too far they're pointing out
your bird can fly further than it can
walk if you pick the fly it can go
pretty far uh yeah uh yeah bird already
no no
um
okay
nice
I got a bunch of fish stuff I want
to see what's on Bow Wow he has camp
supplies hell yeah that's it camp supply
is always good I'll take your two I'm
God
yeah I know
what a joke he had a a cheap ring and an
agate but that's you didn't have
anything wow that's the spoils these
guys had nothing they're bro damn Yum
Money in the in the chest up here wait
this guy this guy The Fish Guy had a
sickle of ball
oh that sounds kind of nice I'm not
gonna lie
I'm here we already opened it
is this a pearl
nice oh don't forget we can level by the
way oh yeah
when did that happen Billy didn't
realize that level up
we are berserking we'll need your
assistance to make decisions
Ranger level five
fast movement extra attack
we get an extra attack nice
hot damn
hot dog oh boy they'll never see him or
y'all
[Music]
um
I love that freaking song so much it's
so catchy if I hear it once it'll be
stuck in my head the entire day
it's a big sea monster bones
camera I'm getting too crazy with the
camera what's all over here
I'll take it nothing much I think it's
ooh fish Barrel Chasm it's a chasm
okay I made my level up Choice I'm ready
I guess we go and enter that big
foreboding Place huh oh
if there's if there's fish collect the
fish because we can use that for food
yeah there was a dude holding fish
Mario if they use dig on the dirt Mound
I think we get a chest
why do I have so much crap in my
inventory again fish oh starfish bottles
oh nothing give me the fish
I found a message in a bottle that reads
Dad sorry I stopped writing we ran out
of paper on the road I got this from The
Druids maybe that's why they're so mad
at us I hope that this can find you
zevilar says you got lost and that our
old house is gone but I read a book that
says all Rivers find their way into the
sticks when you get it can you write me
back in Boulder's Gate or maybe come
visit I'll write again when I can get
more paper Donnie Donnie knows what the
river sticks is
why do I have a second bear and this one
wears armor
armor maybe yeah he evolves like a
Pokemon yeah there's so much gold here
um
that's that's called the Ecstasy of
murder
that sounds good I love that
cool that was fun good for the
collection
little little gold pieces on the ground
what would you find in the heavy chest
uh some money and some potions I
got a post of giant strength you might
be interested in that giant strange she
already has Giants true
no oh yeah in my you know my own game in
my own game I got Gail a spell where he
can actually make you big
well I haven't tried it yet I'm like
whoa some people may really like this
is the first thing that I thought so I
thought I'd share with the class
some people certainly like that see here
you get what I mean
I get what you mean totally yeah my
memories of the internet Reminds Me of
anything
you guys not sometimes think when you
were at a concert and you're sitting in
one of the back seats that don't see
what's going on on the stage wouldn't
you wish especially for YouTubers where
technology basically permits anything
nowadays so just size them up like
hundreds yeah a giant woman on stage
yeah
science on stage so even when you're
really far away you can see them really
well isn't that an idea of a genius
that's so smart actually
it's brilliant people should pay you
money for that idea Kiara thank you I
already brought it up to management
actually it's good oh my God I brought
it up to Japanese management when I was
in Japan and they just laughed at me
what's so funny
goodbye I'm serious about this okay hmm
like holograms on the you know you don't
see those like
cyberpunky cities with like Holograms
and stuff
yeah like go with your show or something
like that yeah there's like big
holographic women that's what I imagine
oh yeah
like some kind of like Blade Runner
yeah Blade Runner yeah which one do we
go yeah there's a big doorway that we I
mean it's up to you but you know there
was a big doorway over there if you want
to go to it
oh doorway out here okay yes yes it
looks good this is cool too it's just
like a little like a fishing Hamlet
Village looks like Oh wrong way sorry
this way okay oh oh what the oh hey
I'm being targeted by who who I don't
know
we'll find out
but it's oh good luck
oh oh my bird stuck
oh no
I'm just I'm just re-summing them
about to get shot
this area is your Buy
cool
just keep your new spell on the party
that was a spell for the whole party
oh maybe we can shoot that thing Tower
not a turret yeah I think it's probably
the arcave tower
yeah Cali yeah I gave you a movement but
oh thanks Molly smash oh yeah
third magical turret dude
oh
can we show it just keeps going
wait enter turn baseball so he doesn't
you know so he doesn't yeah constantly
there you go I'm trying to shoot
can I just rail him
oh he's 30.
there must be some way to hit him oh I
can't
ah
no it's too sturdy
oh nice
there's another one up there
I have about left
wow people are freaking hero
over there
hero biboo this is the real hero
I'm not gonna try and hit something that
I can't kill
so I'll chill right
[Music]
health potion
stay alive Kelly yeah you're our tank we
need you
trying to get my health back
I'll chill in this corner because that
turret I don't think I can beat it okay
I need to wait till my next turn to get
close enough thanks
for the heels
but it doesn't see me yet so it should
be okay
I'll give it a try to be careful friends
scary looking oh boy
go get a Target is hamstrings you can't
run yeah
hell yeah
what was in the chest
we're about to find out isn't that bad
boy
let me lock pick it
oh it's 15. oh somebody ah you did it
you look sick
I just want to see I want to look at it
that's a big hand from the guard you
know no Sky breaker
of it I mean it's cool but I don't feel
like I would use this any of you guys
like hammers oh because you can throw it
yeah if you could use it he's not
stronger than what I have
for throwing I mean that's true but I
have a lot of things I can throw keep in
mind save game nice
cool
who really came and clutched there that
was cool right yeah
okay oh we are at the Arcane Tower oh
[Music]
is this
the
the tentacle guy told us to find
mushrooms here here yum yeah
oh
inside inside
the Arcane Tower
oh yeah oh wait can I enter turn mode
yeah there's another there's another
thing no a turret
[Music]
all right
people were really taking one for the
team there
yeah I'll I'll offer myself as a Target
as well
uh there's one on the other side but I
am now out of a spell so I can't okay
well actually
behind it maybe I can use shocking grass
hold on let me sneak
probably you won't you see me oh okay
maybe you won't see me boy
oh yeah
okay
wow BJ is freaking strong with his
spells yeah what the hell small but
strong I'm always dead but it's fine you
want a potion
[Music]
uh sure yeah I'm gonna throw it on you
hold on you don't need it yeah eat it
you don't need it oh we're good oh thank
you
swag do we do a short rest
no I healed you because I'm so cool like
that
thank you
so is there a mushroom supposed to be in
here
yeah somewhere I don't see a mushroom
it's magic
I feel it's mad
it's mad just nice view
that's a hella nice view
pretty
eh I'm gonna go there
with the pretty face
did that just transform
what happened to the chest oh the stuff
turned into stuff oh
the stuff turned into stuff
from bad stuff into good stuff
I got what did I get I don't know it's
really into different stuff uh
uh oh I got
a bomb
nice
oh a light bulb I got some scroll I got
some shoes
yeah
neat
but no mushrooms
and she's lying what
people's lying
like lying about what
stuff what
biboo you're not streaming your
perspective you can't lie
and see what I got right yeah yeah
that's right I trust Bieber more than
chat
over here this looks suspicious don't
you think gold ingot I got a skull Mage
Armor some shoes and it sounds legit
yeah
there's no mushrooms here guys come here
come here Mommy come to me oh yeah that
was an entrance what is this an elevator
I don't know I haven't seen this before
but it seems like it so we go up or down
yeah
I feel like we're already so high up
like some kind of magical collection
it's a tower now to get it to work to
get it to work
Jinx who owe me a soda
[Music]
I think I do we perhaps need those uh
like pieces
to fix it that I saw somewhere hmm
hmm picked up some like
mechanical pieces
another Contraption of some sort
I don't think so
you need to power it from the ground
floor eh
are we not on the ground floor
yeah you can see we're like really high
up hey come over here yeah do you see
oh
well that's a way to go
all right
down the mushroom okay
out there
little bit painful
ow no pain
is there machines in here too that shoot
us oh no no no no
but
interesting pretty blue Barrel
those mushrooms here so there's some
moldy cheese rotten cheese wheel
nice
retrospective
I can't redo
I just found a book that feels like
retrospective
I found some mushrooms some timis spores
what's the name of the mushroom that
we're looking for I don't know but I
know we need the weird tongue one I
picked up one oh so we have it yeah
got the fetch Quest
last question
swag
to the right place yeah where is it
is uh just uh somewhere over the rainbow
I want to follow our leader
okay well you want to jump down the
balcony or what up to you your your call
boss well we'll die we will not live can
you all jump off
um
feather fall can I use this do it oh the
helmet is armed way
just remember can we jump down now let's
try it
[Music]
oh yeah
do we have more of that wait you guys
you guys have Feather Falls too you can
jump really I if you're online he
doesn't want to okay here we go right
now
[Music]
uh just aim for a spot try to jump down
no not these booster flowers
like your Peter Pan Kiara yeah bungee
jumping
okay
what else is there to find I want a
treasure trip oh what is this
oh so shiny it's like a sakura tree but
lighting don't don't it ruins your magic
it ruins I don't want magic
oh
my magic fan yeah but we have magic so
if you grab it and we're around throw it
away people digging up
um you can send it to Camp okay I got a
scroll of haze I opened up the building
oh all right
oh
nice perception check there's a hole
a hole oh but people who go in there I'm
waiting oh I'm too big
of course
but how I have mainly but the familias
can't go we learned that before right so
really
I wonder how you're supposed to be able
to oh
maybe if you were if someone was a druid
you could do it yeah
yeah rat can't go oh yeah because you're
actually shape-shift
Hmm this is where we can fix the
elevator cool what do I do about this
disorders of nerves and mine oh I found
a Flawless candle and lackulite
cellulite
last one
some of that up it's in my inventory if
you want to see it I don't know what it
does though
my name was inside
I it's a good song
Good song such a good flow man you all
sound tired AF well you know it's just 6
a.m for some people right yeah six seven
sorry what what time is it somewhere
around there it just turned seven for me
seven good morning it's nine a.m now oh
9 A.M your breakfast time no I said
that's luxury yeah I sleep into like 11
every day what do you mean
okay power generator oh combined items
what does it want
I don't know
where did that thing go
what could it want
um
my pretty
a blue flower ah the flat wow
did somebody pick up the blue flower
yeah I picked it up yeah
okay get in there I sent it to Camp
no oh okay yeah quick go to camp and
then grab it if there's not one there's
another one out here okay go grab it
there should be okay magic no it's okay
no enemies around so you know safe and
sound
magic fire that burns within
my magic okay I need my magic
violent and Powerful
about this why did we send the magician
out there to get them no magic flowers
free maybe don't you feel free
yes I don't care
[Music]
I don't care magic Cannot Be Tamed
not even by you
if no magic I'll just Bonk
yeah it's okay and the moment you get
the flower off of you your magic works
again so yeah it's good all good
pretty flower
I'm so shiny right now yeah drop that
bad boy in there
what's reacting to you
Lord
oh
you made it you did it
it's gonna go it's powered by anti-magic
well we were already at the top on the
mid levels so how does I don't know if
we were at the top top level oh oh
deactivated though oh and it activates
the lamps cute
cute so is there a top yeah they're
still yeah we haven't been there where
we're we're there there's two levels
nice scene is there something waiting
for us up there goodies treasure I have
no idea so we're gonna find out together
[Music]
it's treasure
treasure okay we can go up here
what we are woohoo
you're
so slow
she's so slow because the camera is so
slow for me it's so glowing how do you
guys see the upper level I can't see it
um yeah it's weird your camera just
needs to it somehow oh nice idea Chad
quick say yeah
thanks Dad okay I'm here and send whoa
ah everybody presses it on their own oh
oh but then finally one level so
oh can we get much higher
one more oh this is new where's everyone
we're hitting the Ascend buttons I see
oh oh
decent comfy I see that's how it works
I like this sandal
and what's an animal
well how did I find these people
hello I don't know what's go out of my
way
oopsies I thought all of you guys were
this I
come in peace
that's not true let me persuade you
we can be cool
I might be but I'm going to descend
like hope yeah just one level you can
yeah if I can descend here let me press
the button
so what's an animal a and then it's a
kind of book I don't know what it means
though specifically
you can't be cool anymore apparently I
see I see red dots up there are you in a
fight it would appear so
would you like some help
oh yeah sure let's go up oh
yes I found something cool what'd you
find
we need to get the Yankee
oh animated armor is using range attack
yeah I'm kind of getting slam jammed
over here by a bunch of differences yeah
maybe we yeah we'll be right up away
you just powered up and like went kind
of nutty
okay I'm gonna take that oh the battle
has commenced even though we're on the
ground run bee boo
I can always reload I guess
yeah
these guys are really really tanky
they got a lot of shiny armor
animated
like visible to them
find the game
reload the game
um let's not go to that level yeah
yeah I'm sorry I thought you guys were
very tough that's okay yeah it's
understandable
but we do need to say something you need
to prepare for whatever that is though I
tried to be nice yeah they were not
having it so I don't know what the
proper response is for them I don't know
if you can ever be friends
they're just rude yeah they're very mean
and inconsiderate I think they're better
you're saying you can find books in the
tower to give them commands oh really
so maybe in that second level yeah yeah
or that level right before rather yeah
okay this is the floor you guys were on
yes yeah gotcha
okay
let's be on my way
there are books and then
more books
this is pretty cool
yeah
speak with dead on death and
Resurrection
button
he says
one that doesn't work hey
that was I put it on your face oh yeah
she's lying there oh well please I
didn't mean to it you went on to your
face I didn't do anything
it's too dark to see
turn on some lights
a history of the city of Baldur's great
as told with a Bard's flare oh cool
lower
oral history is a fey run yeah a button
is mysterious
bunny oh there's another chest over
there
what's in there what'd you find nothing
somebody probably already took it
somebody
oh yeah there was a ring
um a magic ring a Mages ring so I'm
wearing it now
okay where's the the disc that you found
before it's in my inventory
um didn't we get the dialogue again I
just skipped it okay Kiara what do you
want to do
um we need to read all the wait wait
save save first and let's read all the
books that we picked up I I read a bunch
of things in this room
yeah I I picked up a ton of books so
yeah
there's one up here
hang on
it's another book I don't think this one
helps the one that I have
just Baldur's Gate history lesson
[Music]
okay
you want to take a bath
I'd like to take a bath if we're taking
one together yeah never mind I'm good
I'll take a shower
[Music]
you really you really set me up for it I
did
so what what about the books who has the
books um I read all my books I only
picked up like five I didn't get
anything books on the ground that I read
there I couldn't pick them up but
there's like a gear icon so I read them
it's just to read them yeah
yeah
on the ground oh and there's a paper
here
the silent stretches and I'm all alone
please can I hold your hands just for a
while oh
it's kind of sweet oh oh wow what's this
ciphers it's an engraved this one origin
what is this pick it up you can use it
to decipher things I think
oh
moriope doesn't know how to read
it's my head Cannon
fitting we can use it apparently for
something but oh
I have a hide bound Journal that says
one favor one faithful servant that is
all I summon no more no less than the
malice do Odin ever had or indeed the
mother of lust herself the yachlo was
quite a sight in all its forms I'd read
of its foul order but I found it
intoxicating like rose water so it
smashed a few artifacts hissed at a
master the archmade should have revered
me for such a Conjuring instead he
threatened to curse me to make me a
rider yet my time will come soon I will
return to menzo Barons and and his
sorcerer then the archmage will worship
me I will be served but I don't see how
that helps
speaking in riddles to me yeah it's just
mysterious
they're saying the books wouldn't have
been in the bookcases they'll just be
sitting around and we have to pick them
up and one person has to hold all of
them oh oh yeah okay I'm Gonna Leave it
to you guys because I don't know what to
do
and I'm not smart same
I'm just a Bard man
big smash are they all on this floor
or elsewhere to
because
I also found books on different floors
oh sort by newest good idea
latest one person has to read them that
person needs to be the one to talk to
the construct
you got to go up first what is the book
guys what is the book name
yes tell us tell us or else
give us the answer
can we save it and see if there's stuff
now yeah yeah okay safe
oh not that kind of safe
go up and see what happens
oh boy
sale
know these words oh we know these words
I see
uh
uh I guess
chat yeah
this one is new pretty yeah
oh he's only bows to you oh
um
oh no remember what it said
uh
oh
yeah oh yeah number three I read this
one can we hold hands
taller
yeah
yes please
[Laughter]
the gears are gonna spin you up into a
smoothie
remember
[Music]
I haven't been hugged in 10 years
just like me flirting with TTS yesterday
can we all go up now are we good are
there more things that we can say to him
maybe each of the different commands are
like you get different dialogue with
them
um
[Music]
okay
sick okay okay let's save yeah uh
Mario but save game
okay I guess if you guys are going I'll
go
hey is she showing you who's this guy oh
he put
nice uh Guiding Light it's a ring
uncommon
so we talk to the other ones too they
don't seem like they want to talk oh if
we can yeah this one doesn't want to
talk
um
you could also Ascend further I suppose
but basically wait wait wait we can go
to the basement now yeah
wait is there even anything any further
up wait let's let's talk to people let's
find out ladder
he doesn't seem to want to chat no
um which is a shame because he seems
cool
nothing up here
okay I think basement it is okay oh my
basement thing is gone
[Music]
it's gone it's gone there's only a
descent okay oh
where does that go maybe it only takes
one of us at a time
oh wait wait you guys go first I think I
have to be up here but yeah because
you're perceiving it or so I don't know
okay go first
there is a kick-ass staff on the top
floor somebody says
I I like staffs
yeah it's on the top I don't know where
though I'm already all the way on the
basement
if y'all wanna want to find that uh oh
for the staff of Arcane blessing is that
what they're talking about I think that
might be it
that just Scrolls down here too but I'm
not really much of a mage so
hey but you can still use them when
they're whenever you feel like you can't
do anything else that's a good point I
did pick up some some daggers
which is pretty cool
yeah I'll take that stuff oh it's nice
to have some Scrolls for backup yeah
that's true what'd you find in the chest
View
I got a ring that gains resistance to
lightning damage which is good because I
do lightning damage yeah
maybe you should give the ring to the
people you keep on oh
[Music]
yeah you know I liked her so much with
the electricity
well if you're sure I mean I'll I'll
take it because I usually I usually
don't get electrocuted you do yeah all
right all right I get the discs I see I
see how it is
oh I see what you guys think of me all
right I understand
oh that's a connection over here
shortcut found
[Music]
oh yeah
well what else was there in the basement
you know oh I'm not sure I don't want to
split that I've already found everything
yeah did we go to the top where's
Marissa
um not wherever or yeah I'll be right
there
keep living
on my way
wow beautiful
hello
we found the staff right is that it
was it was it the staff or was it Arcane
blessing right
uh uh I don't know because that's what I
found at the basement apparently yeah
there's still something left at the top
yeah talk to the construct again some
people are saying that's the 1B boom
okay stuff is great for clerics
okay
lyrics clerics lyrics
I think it is
check out the top floor
we were all on the top floor no no
there's one more above it here near the
table
yeah let's go up
sounds good and up
up
and and up
I'm on my way I'm just taking the longer
path
[Music]
table
chair
and send
Ascend oh I said again
there's a stairway
um oh it doesn't
does it lead anywhere else apart from
just up here
what I heard there was a staff up here
up here
um
there's a great stool
great stool
oh is it this this stool that says stool
of giant strength or whatever people are
saying to talk to the main guy again the
robot there's a stool here it says oh
that's a funny stool yeah double giant
strength
okay oh throw it do you can you yeah
it didn't break it's closed Molly has to
smash me yes
oh of Hill giant strength it's a club
who owns this club let's go to the club
what what kind of weapon is it I wonder
is it magical I'll take it it is
it is magical it does two to five damage
splinters of giants might increases
strength to 19.
[Music]
cute I don't know
yeah it's it's cute it's a cute stuff
it's a cute trick a bong stick all right
let's get out of here then I guess yeah
it's good offhand keep it you get a bow
that profits from strength later oh okay
Coolio it's kind of cool
which level do we want to go to today
I'm in the basement okay basement might
be good
insanely good club they say
yeah nice
and no I wanted to go to
yeah I'll figure this out moriope is not
good with directions
oh there's more tongues here tongue of
mad wait did you guys did you guys
abandon Mario pay up there I mean I
don't see the basement
um
no I don't want to be I don't want to be
a burden Memorial
I'm
off I thought that moriope is so cute oh
that's the kind thing to say thank you
people let's get out of here together
okay we'll meet you on the ground floor
yeah are we lost Dad no no we're fine
the reason it's just me and you just me
and you
keep
here we are
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you I am the prettiest of all you
smell Beautiful I know this is
is there a way is there anywhere to go
from here or was it this was this like a
dead end
um
I'm not sure
seems pretty deadly
yeah yeah
don't know if we can make any jumps here
we can just teleport back to we could go
to back to mushroom Place yeah the
maisonic colony maybe again let's do
that
oh
yeah
cool all right team apparently the big
robot also has a special weapon but uh
yeah okay you have to kill him for it
but he gave me a
plan
okay ah wait do we give the the mushroom
to whoever asked for it tentacles oh
yeah yeah yeah the main guy
was it the leader who asked for it all
right
these are fine specimens
it will only take me he's impressed
wonderful omelion turns away to prepare
the potion
[Music]
next time you must drink the entire
draft
enjoy
yummy the acidic liquid tightens your
throat oh being on the way down
he didn't even ask him what it was gonna
do do you know what's gonna do to you
very good
you may find yourself acting
irrationally irrationally and stay
focused acting up
sounds like you're drunk
[Music]
it's finer boundaries
fluid
like a creature suspended in Amber
oh
oh should I saving throw yeah I mean
yeah yeah probably because you might die
all right I think you'll be fine look at
all those bonuses give me my blush
actually no I want it actually
actually why not
hey he lives
Jose dark holes bite at the edges of
your vision
the foyer cannot draw you in
typical spasms seizes it's fighting the
potion even harder than you are fear
Pierce is your mind like knives well the
mushroom is to get rid of the tadpoles
to follow out your skull
say goodbye to your worm Powers
um
protects me I guess because
it fits in your face now look at your
bonuses you're fine wait
wait oh just barely getting
yay
the cold okay mushrooms The Edge not
today Squidward not today
against itself
potato chips
um
lashing out against that I could go for
some food right now it's morning for you
the Paris
pancakes breakfast
I want to make French toast
I think I'll make I'm not French
um
oh so it didn't kill it no no of course
not
because that would be too easy too early
the outcome was not in my calculation is
this the one that you can smooth more to
this being than me
I figured yeah
yeah you can you can smooth your a
tentacle guy yeah you can have a
chemical moment I'll leave that to you
Mori open no I'm good I already have my
my love although
[Laughter]
I may have another solution
albeit a temporary one
it goes as well as you could expect a
ring of Mind shielding it prevents Elder
brains from noticing my presence
but it will
and negative that's metal I would offer
it as a gift but in truth he wants to
make a deal priceless
I
become your consort
intimidation either give me the ring or
I'll run
run uh
I'll tell you about
I'll tell you a story every Last Detail
indeed
what can you tell me you got a pinky
promise first
um oh I see performance
[Music]
give a dramatic retelling of your time
on the mind so there is a ship and we
were on it
and um it was on fire and the Brain
people and
yeah oh my God and yeah tell me the more
you tell me more
and then Step Closer they blew up and we
got heated off the ship a lot of story
mark
here
ouch
wow good
as well he liked that of course he's
entertained
we are streamers afterwards all the time
you know
he's our audience oh I'm poisoned now
though wait oh
yeah oh you gotta throw up that potion
you have an advantage on saving those
against charms if anybody wants it they
can have it no names oh ring of my
shielding I'm gonna I'm gonna go full
brain brain worms this run time ah I
love charm
your mom likes it too yeah that's why
she that's why she chose as her Reaper
name to be Andorra
and or yeah it's from Charmed right
and Dora and Dora yeah and Dora I don't
remember an Andorra where what it was
definitely from Charmed right is this
like another misunderstanding with like
you know golden golden girls
from Bewitched never mind
wow
it seems we had to never
misunderstanding he's always happy okay
thanks Chad
it's the second time this has happened
with you yeah
it's weird
but maybe your mom still likes trumped
maybe ask her sometimes yeah I'll ask
her it seems like a show she'd like
um
um you know I don't remember the names
too well because it's been a really
obnoxiously long time but the one who
died
the one who ah okay you're like well I
don't know he's too late to spoil it
like this yeah show it's so old but
proof yeah yeah yeah yeah I didn't like
Prue at all it's because I liked her
actor
Oh I thought she was very hot yeah yeah
I would agree with that I like the girl
who replaces her later
Paige
I like the opening because it's a Smith
song
um ah yeah how soon is now but I didn't
know that
for a long time
so I was like oh my God what a based
show it seems like they kind of lost
rights to it because when you watch the
show now on like Amazon Prime or
whatever they replaced the music with
something similar that wouldn't surprise
me the Smiths are kind of
their
um drama baby
um more seem is a character
oh that's it he's a singer
he's a character he's he's the singer
he's a he's a character do you know that
expression Chihuahua
I have a weird weapon in my inventory
the bullwhile's arms I didn't know I
picked that up and it's like his pincers
like a cancer
I'll throw them if you don't know what
else to do with Rob Spencer oh yeah I'd
love to think they look interesting sell
sell it crap crap
why did I say cancer
in my in German it's like the same word
cancer and crab
okay oh there's another Trader down
below okay I'll go find them
here I'll leave you Mario pay come with
me
thank you Marissa
okay I'm actually uh done too anyway let
me go clean out this guy let me see what
he's got Marissa uh is your character
just you
you mean the personality or both
can you describe I haven't seen him yes
I've met him which is a lie
you subscribed
blue tunic
domestic
um
show me your wears really quick that's
what I'm in here for I need to sell some
things
yeah like this maybe we can help her too
though
yeah she's looking for someone right it
seems like it yeah
see I'm
I don't want that Cali is
nah nah
Callie's I I don't know about that
self-insert you're I find you way more
Charming outside of this game no this is
literally what I'm like
no
more it'll be so irresistible to have
you seen a Starion like he's like you
know yeah that's a good point actually
this this character is more attractive
oh my God just being real
I don't mind it so much I really don't
this is huge this Amulet of unworthy
grants resistance to slashing damage
grants vulnerability to bludgeoning
damage that's really interesting
oh even the the little why was it all
guys listening
everybody liked my music oh I want to
play too here oh join me
wait what song are you playing
I'm doing I'm doing the power
I think they're bullying me
let me talk to him again they're young
wow do they hate you
oh you're not good
you're not good to play music yum
well yeah I can hear it Vivo I know
you're doing your best but it's
vibrating oh sorry
is angry
I love how he moves oh he's so angry so
mad he's so upset
oh
[Music]
um just not playing girl
I won't improve if I don't practice
exactly see I think I don't know if this
is a skill you can improve on
oh no don't listen to him
no more performance
are you okay
he treats me good now doesn't care
anymore
that we want to find right I'm gonna dye
my armor really quick
not my armor my clothes
combined
oh my God are you actually putting on
clothes well yeah I mean
oh my gosh wow wait that looked good
what did
the clothing you just had on put that on
again oh yeah no I definitely will it's
just I'm I need it to be swamp green
okay I steam okay Shrek calm down are
you friends with right now or why are
you so
me oh no it's because uh Starion took my
blood yeah I'm still okay get up
afterwards then bloodless till next long
rest yeah there we go now I'm nice and
ogary oh
yeah you can dye your clothes
[Music]
fashionista baby give me some money
and I got a necklace of restoration
which means if I have heel spells now if
I put it on
okay nice voices
put that on next time we see a dead dude
oh okay
I want hmm come on gamers
Gamers where do we go next this way
um
[Music]
and then I'll let you lead but we should
go out this way oh yeah oh God this is
where we started out anyway today yeah
okay well we teleported out of here
immediately yeah oh cool
ah let's go this way okay I think
because that way there's a quest over
there I love this point balance
it's a cute Pumbaa that we have on our
team
yeah
wait wait wait maybe blast that
okay
okay I don't think I added it to where
is that but now
um
will it go away
[Applause]
Marissa just does not care I'm fine
I'm just a Bard man
you are working on becoming more of a
tank day by day mm-hmm
that oh we might know
save scum please
oh there's a lot of bombs let's go I'll
help you shoot them
oh my God you guys are crazy
oh
oh oh oh
[Music]
um
he's is he okay oh my god look you did
it yeah
it was so good
that was hilarious
[Applause]
uh well
why are you doing here get it she's
been worried sick I must hmm
need to go yeah
for you oh you're trouble nice thanks
that's trouble but Michael Bay film
right there oh invisibility oh hey he's
fine he's fast go yeah that was a close
one good for him I'm sure that he has
one HP
hey I know the fire is gone what night
[Music]
I'm picking up stuff oh there's some
Scrolls
but they're proving hard to pick up for
some reason oh there's something there
look at this
sorry let me get off here
I just want to see what's in there
only I can open some money and grease
but I've got enough Grease Grease is
pretty good honestly yeah if you have
like fire bolt or whatever there's some
candles here why is there so many crazy
stuff maybe someone was doing something
they look pretty yeah it's the scary the
scary God candle oh wow this candle
but that's all
oh I suppose everything here yeah okay
yeah definitely completed that question
all right let's let's also save because
of wow that luck
was that really lucky
yeah what you mean there is uh I killed
that guy so many times on accident
uh-huh I tried that too oh there's
another one here is great and doing
great job
Giada is just perfect is what it is
I wonder if the if they want to talk to
us again about the quest
um they will but they'll they'll stay
there so if you wanted we could do the
next Quest where we need to kill the
derger and then just go back and report
all those at the same time yes is the
quest item still there or did it go boom
says chat
item
I mean the guy
it looks like I think
there may have been there was something
it may have gone boom boom Oh well
not bring them I'll get it during my
personal run yeah
you are a magic debuffing us
at the camp okay
okay Liara get out of here maybe this
way okay
follow follow
oh no which Quest are we going for I
don't see anything on the map um we
remember in our last playthrough we were
talking to the guy the the big mushroom
Sovereign and he wanted us to kill
someone we need to find a place and we
need to kill the dirtier I uh was that
like a dwarf or so yeah it's just keep
walking around we'll eventually run into
something
oh there's a village who abandoned camp
Oh rapid Village a little fish in Hamlet
a la bloodborne
all up or down well now I went up
probably down it looks like we're just
going back to the my Synod Colony sorry
but there's some something to go down
here and dead body no
oh he's got a cool short sword
yeah get that little guy
is that good for someone of us
it looks powerful dude has something I
can throw
give me that club I can throw it
oh there's more deaf people let's go
dead people dead bodies everywhere dead
bodies everywhere yeah I'm actually oh
wait who has oh I have this I have the
thing with the dead the dead body talk
to them yeah they need one to five
people talk to them
I'm very curious
mm-hmm
all right I got it now let me say hello
everyone
oh surely
you can move faster now increased by
three meters
maybe the one up there
oh I can
talk to this guy
could you not talk to the other one
um
that's too bad what
eh that's too bad they should they
should tell me that before I talk to
them yeah wait I'll try one too cast
spells it better have something to say
they glue green if you can talk to them
of course they're too damaged Ah that's
what happened okay okay
you can talk
that's a bit of a ripoff
it's a rip-off yeah
did you waste a scroll for that I don't
know I think it was a scroll but I'm not
sure I just used well you have a
necklace yeah I have a necklace I can
use the spell yeah but I can only use it
once
oh well
there will be more chances to speak to
the dead that was cool though
those are you guys okay okay there's a
waypoint
oh chicken oh really yeah there's a
waypoint you got a yummy looking witches
stew
kind of looks like somebody forgot about
their cooking which is something I'd
never do
never ever
forgetting about Curry first oh wait I
have to go down here oops Yeah
[Music]
a couple days let's see it's better
after a couple days
that corpse is glowing green I could
have talked to him uh
do it rest
they got cool stuff let me talk to you
whoa
I wanted to talk to you hey look we're
chill right steps are too loud
fist grips and acts oh you're chilling
half orc intimidation I'm hungry for a
fight but you're barely immorsal choose
your next move carefully back down or
bleed
use my half work
not a bonus I like it bardic inspiration
thank you narissa that's the guy we
agreed to kill okay yeah yeah let's just
pretend like we're friends for now
they'll sneak up on him and beat him up
fine
I'll let you live hi idiot but spoiled
my hunt
and you're dead
what are you doing here
sold you hunting
slave ran away okay you need to be rude
I'm a little slow
even fetch back the leather
all the boss is in Moonrise they'll have
friends hide oh the moonrise Towers
maybe I could help if you really kill
someone for a pair of boots on the help
of a slave catcher
uh would you really kill someone for a
pair of boots
besides we're talking about our life
wow maybe I could help
you don't even know what you'd be up
against try me some protection
yeah get past those Rock flowers again
yeah those are our special friends
jumped off a cliff laughing ah let's go
sounds like fun oh wait
she'll make a run for it eventually
then I'll get a
I don't like him help you I don't know
I'm helping a slave catcher your
problems of your own I'm leaving fine
suppose I'll just eat you then
oh okay you can give it all right let's
kill him all righty
I thought the way that I went about it
was real nice but okay
oh
no no cells I wish you could save right
here or make it make a new save
bam
yeah we can make a save
that should be fine I'll just take it
reanimated corpse oh I have no spell
slots yeah I have none either
oh no I'm not been silenced oh no oh
[Music]
yeah these guys suck they ain't anything
to worry about oh thank God we're just
friends
yeah okay
[Music]
why it's very unlucky the game really
wants us to reload
yeah but I don't wanna that's so lame
wow
that is nice a difficult situation
yeah we can kill him
should be fine
let's do a big old ax swing you know we
have a bear not a berry of a Pumbaa
bomba yeah
I'm playing some music yeah
it's fine these guys ain't
yeah damn there's four of us and
there's a lot of them that's fine
oh they Blinded Me oh that sounds good
yes
who infected the red infected them
that's cool
got it
what nice chill battles am I not done
what is what is this intern ah
oh hey nice
oh come on I was I was listening to that
man he didn't like that he wanna hate
her yeah that sucks
at frenzy it seems need a long rest for
that I'm assuming
oh attack together
good damage
come on these guys are a little beefy
but that's okay
just show them
get out of here that feels good yeah boy
the way he gets back up
actually
impressive
wow he really's got a death wish
oh
that they are very replaceable
definitely a long rest and is in order
after this
yeah
sure I want to talk to that dead body
beneath my shoes
yeah let's go yeah three damages I got
three hits it's still pretty good that's
really good actually no that's fine
let's go
can you stop trying to Blind me thank
you he knows you're strong
you can feel it
you can feel how strong you are that's
all
I don't have any spells
true true
what's happening oh I was just checking
something
[Music]
I'm hard
for free I'm leaving it to you girl all
right no problem
we got it together
let's see because it's very healthy this
dude's about to die oh no this one's
healthy and this one's healthy this
guy's about to die
getting the good oh
[Music]
my foolish the whoa there excuse you but
keep doing it
I wonder how they come up with all these
phrases
and playing a lot of DnD
did you guys see the voice actors
playing DND I did what that's so cool
yeah
hmm
[Music]
it's pretty cool actually I like him
getting distracted by Gail's boots when
he failed a role
cute
[Music]
leave them alone excuse me but don't hit
the Puma I guess I put ice down when I
use freezing people do whatever I see
oh God damn it
see that's why I didn't want to walk out
okay well
that was my reason
oh no no
still alive speaking of Pumbaa did I
tell you guys about the Roomba incident
the whole Roma incident Roomba yeah so
my cat ghost cat sometimes you know he
poops outside of his litter box on
accident
yeah I have a Roomba that you use your
Roomba okay it automatically goes at 9
00 a.m every day and I have been
sleeping and did ghosts
like suck up some fresh poop no it did
the opposite it smeared it all over the
living room
this is bad that's the Roomba incident
s
are pretty small you can't make such big
ghost poops right now it's pretty big
smeared all over the carpet in the floor
I'd get a new carpet
bad it's so easy but the carpet is a big
yikes yeah it's pretty rough it's okay
he's just he's just a wee little lad I
forgive him yeah it wasn't his fault
I can't be mad at my cat for any
accidents either no it's the room at
home for not sensing the poo poo
out of the smelling sensor to them
exactly that's a piece of dookie maybe
let's not go home
I should really activate my room but I
had one like it's still in its box since
like like years yeah damn that's good
because I I don't know I I know that
like resetting it is kind of annoying
when like you change something in your
room
and so I felt like I will start using it
when I'm 100 set on the furniture's
position in my apartment
but I should really activate it I didn't
change Furniture in a while if your cats
hate that Roomba they're going to make
plans to destroy it I.E droppings around
and having it run over them
I know that chunky wonky will be very
scared of the Roomba because she's
scared of my my hair dryer and
everything else that makes loud sounds
yeah
[Music]
man
I have to get used to it maybe she'll
write off that's loud
what the hell wow two dudes get rid of
these double demons
destroy them this guy refused to die I
had him on death's doorstep and he
refused to die
[Music]
it's not but like it
it moves around and chunky monkey gets
sick but googly eyes on it that's a
great idea Chad
give him some googly eyes
yeah I like that
yeah for real
so Cali has your apartment uh been taken
over by like fur yes but I have a really
good vacuum it's a Dyson that has like a
green light on it that shines on the
ground and it shows all the dust
particles and all the hair
would I recommend it
um
not sponsored by the way that's a mix of
cool things I really want the hair dryer
from Dyson yeah
the one that we saw Kelly yeah in the
hotel fancy
word
oh good good stuff
I'm gonna man this fight ugh lame yeah
yeah kind of lame kind of silly
why is it so tanky no we're being tanky
yeah yeah
all right let's see who's left be happy
oh yeah the dumb dwarf dude yeah
right here
yeah then there's another one up but if
we go up there then we'll get
electrocuted
I see they got a spell up there
we're gonna take him out anyway
uh
I shall try to go up
oh
it continues
yeah I'm just confused
somehow
I thought we were done and yeah there's
only dudes up here
okay
yeah we outnumber them now
it was a little bit of a fetus dude
right here
oh I can shoot again but that probably
won't hurt yeah I thought so okay
I want to fight this
wow we have sickness
yucky
well I can do that too though die
wait he moves oh
yeah I get the other guys we got a
corner okay
I got two attacks now that I'm level
five oh that's what's going on it's
interesting which is pretty cool
ham toys
oh I can't hit him twice oh well
I'm not tired do I seem tired no
I'm just chilling yeah I won't see
narissa's Bard has this really chill
music that plays every once in a while
it's like yeah in the chat chit chat
mode with you ladies when I hear it
oh boy
[Music]
get him
yeah yeah want one more
[Music]
I'm gonna jump over here
you want some old man
yeah fisticuffs
ready
um
Here Comes Wawa's Arrow yeah yeah
one more but yeah I only have 36
percentage Yeah
maybe he's just really kind of low and
now it's on 16 never mind Hey I just
moved too much stuff
Hunters is that because of Hunter's Mark
that's cracked
yeah I use it all the time what it helps
thank you
are you okay you poisoned bye that's
fine I'm not done do not ignore me you
piece of garbage
yeah
finally holding
he's got oh this is cool exterminator's
ax can may I take this you guys
yeah yeah yeah thank you loot the body
okay thanks I'm gonna equip it now
because it's better than my current
what's that
stew yummy
from from the stew it looked delicious
that's a garbage guy
exterminators
sheds hard to do it
exterminator
water oh there's a leather
I wonder if they've got treasure back
here no it doesn't seem like it
imploring the recipient to be cautious
around the far shore of the Evan Lake as
durgar of room lights to be prowling in
the area
we might want to do a long rest we
definitely do it
if possible okay yeah okay
I would be curious what he says
I'd like to recast this I'm clicking on
the cast spell button and it's not it
seems like it's blacked out but chat
said that I can recast it
oh
believe in it
just believe
make it happen it only works against
bugs plants or oh you have to sleep I
see
oh okay
oh it's a separate button I see never
mind can't Target Undead I see it's
quote unquote Undead so maybe we could
reanimate it but that's about it anyway
let's go have a long rest I suppose then
if there's nothing
cool before we accidentally run into
another fight I suppose yeah
okay oh time to chill fish hey doggy why
are you holding that weird flower oh
wait you're already there okay
camp
wait the dog has the flower
he was glowing for a second but then it
went away I don't know maybe he ate it
or something and then it oh Gail wants
probably yeah
as little as I do
given you're enabling him
yeah give him something nice
let's crack but I like having Misty's
step but I don't want to give him this
one
does it only let you choose from your
own inventory yeah it's fine I'm gonna
go Gail
thank you no he's indebted oh look at it
yeah oh here you go crazy game yay
yay he liked that yeah he was into that
congrats Gail
oh you're so dirty too
oh oh it sounded positive at first I
need to speak to you to all of you
be unconscionable of me to remain silent
[Music]
um go on you're among friends
to know who I was
for know who I really am he's a dark
wizard well I am well you are so good
I bet you guys all are too yeah but you
can't see it on moriope if an early age
could not only control The Weave but
compose it
much like a musician or a poet such was
my skill that it earned me the attention
of the mother of magic herself
the lady of mysteries
the goddess mistra there he goes after
me and she became my teacher
in time she became my muse
they're born down
he beeped the garden yeah he beeped the
goddess nice oh wow oh yes oh yes show
this company
oh no
mind wow okay all right
how powerful a wizard is Mercy bastard
from the surface of the weave
mistra Keeps Us in check if a goddess
can't satisfy him what could he ever
satisfy him right every time
[Music]
romance everybody in the game the origin
characters do not like that
oh
um
oriopia is God
I'm not I think more than God my methods
try to convince her I pouted
I pleaded
she only smiled and told me to be
contented
inconceivable as it seems to me now I
shared a bed with a goddess
yet I wasn't satisfied wow greedy um to
prove myself worthy little man come now
to the Crux of my folly shall I share
the story behind it or would you rather
head straight to its sordid finale
finale yep and suffice it to say I
obtained an obscure and ancient book
that had locked away inside a much
coveted prize
was a fragment of Primal weave locked
out of time
what if I thought
what if
to all this time
turn this lost part of herself to the
goddess
I'm certain that this dude this is a
short version
domain
oh my God
place your hand oh my heart
I'll suck you inside of his body
keep you up
okay well I guess you guys will be
without your your hot barred for the
rest of the playthrough
s something else is quivering too
[Laughter]
Unstoppable as it digs through and
becomes a lot of you
ever hungry
thankfully the moment I absorbed the
fragment wasn't enough to kill me
outright
it was only the beginning
damn wow very perfect
I was like oh
that armor looks good on you this
nethery yeah the light this I love this
thing yeah
as long as I absorb traces of the weave
from potent enough sources remains quiet
I would have at a fully destabilize
however
real nice hair it does
cool story bro you will die
I will erupt
the exact magnitude of the eruption but
given my studies of nethery's magic
let's say even a fragment as small as
the one I carry
at a levelless city the size of
water Heap really I don't know what is
weave
we might chance upon a king's collection
of magical artifacts around the corner
we might cross paths with a miracle
round the bend
then again
we might not
ice
it must feel like a betrayal
say the word
we're not parting ways with Gail he's
okay bye Gail I'm joking I like him too
yeah
that is yeah he's all right great relief
oh a great relief indeed because there
are tons of magic filled items yeah my
new rallied heart wing and just walk up
to the final boss move Gail as a bomb
and then blow him up yeah that's huge
Kiara
you stand with me I like it but then one
of us has to not be on the team my best
yeah
neither shall I
I'll fight
a resistance
I would volunteer as not being on a team
so that I actually survived literally
yes okay good solution cool good morning
how do you oh
yeah I'm fine just feel a little woozy
my neck hurts how you think I feel be
grateful I'm not a true family Nick
always hurt I bite through them and you
might wake up as a vampire moriope has
got a large chest you know my good self
I carry I'm a vampire
but few of their powers
was that how you could stand the Sun and
drawbacks I should know about I have no
idea yeah for 200 years the sun would
have turned me to sinners
until the crash when I woke up bathed
and it's you know he's skipping arm day
I think the rest of his body is pretty
toned but like some biceps in comparison
to be alive you could use a little voice
you know if he had less ABS it would be
like striking
wandering into homeless without an
invitations
we can figure those out in time they
Bend so weird
do do you like how he's cooking
the if I can help just ask we're in this
together
you're such a sweetheart wow you're
being sarcastic
what if I grabbed your nipples
to get you to shut up would you leave my
party Fidelity is clear
I think it would be funny
there's a long day ahead of us
I'm just say it is impossible what's
wrong with you what do you mean I'm just
being honest is the first thing I notice
he's God I'm staring at me those things
are staring at me
close on this poor man okay we'll talk
to biboo about that because uh yeah I
look at you
well we need happy clothes back the real
issue is we have to then somehow take
our one of us off the team we can close
him yeah let's just keep him naked
yeah I'm good
guys that we have come to a conclusion
oh you good I hope someone in Camp still
wishes to speak who wants to speak
[Music]
go on
what does he want you gotta help our boy
all right I'll be nice to him I'll be
nice to him just for meme yeah oh wow I
I could probably read that because I'm a
tiefling oh wow that's true that is a
good point
let me take a look what are you doing oh
I'm saying hey hey what's up sorry I'll
leave you alone good
this is and we're traveling companions
friends wait wait no if you don't mind
yeah piss off maybe I should kill him
for saying that wow
[Music]
what I get for being respectful next
time I'm gonna beat him up he doesn't
like you anymore let's go you said he
was your master
I'm I'm done with this whole you don't
have to tell me anything you don't want
to I'm going to pry into his life
with all the Mind flares too because now
I know I have to strangle him if I want
to tell me anything was this the nipple
twisting thing I'm sorry I said that man
it wasn't very cool
song is a vampire lord that wasn't very
cool
I've got his coven and a monster
obsessed with power maybe maybe yeah I
mean I'm very sorry
no I'm not I don't care I don't give a
I would like 200 years ago see where
this goes you know I'd love to get to
the scene where I can you know knee him
in the
two men well never mind yeah yeah yeah
well I can I'll I'll lead you there
along the way thanks I'll lead you to
the right direction cool
a vampire's spawn is less oh wait one of
us will have to leave the party for that
I'll do it
they speak no bodies react
it's all part of the deal yeah don't
don't worry don't worry about torture
sometimes I'm taking notes
worry about taking notes
yes I have a bad memory
free now enjoy that freedom quite the
sob story what's your point
foreign
I will
but I won't take it for granted the Mind
flares aren't the only monsters out
there
they're not even the only ones hunting
us
all I'm asking is that you keep your
eyes open and watch out for anything
lurking in the shadows like you trying
to drink my blood
yeah put your back keep me safe and I'll
do the same oh no my friend if vampires
come looking for you you're on your own
I want your back I'm moriope well it's
more could I ask why are you always
sarcastic
piece of
kill him
oh my God there's literally so many why
do you insist on exhuming the past wow
but then he immediately answers a
vampire what a beta I'm joking I'm
joking
don't mean so mean betas are close to
them
[Music]
don't worry about it it doesn't matter
I'm not being mean I'm just trying to
get into the moriope character well
Kiara if you want to get into the Omega
version
oh yeah
never mind I'll tell you later
can we stop talking to him I'm like no
Kiara we can't okay
can I just skip the dialogue yeah yeah
because people get mad when I skip
dialogue but like okay I wouldn't be mad
I want to fight yeah I feel you I feel
yeah yeah we gotta we gotta we gotta
sleep and kill things
we'll skip all the dialogue
like do I do I hate not hearing his
voice actor absolutely yes but at the
same time
it's fine you know yeah
he has a very Charming voice yeah he
does
and he looks beautiful what the hell
still alive
no I didn't rescue you people rescued
you
beckon him closer with animal handling
yeah bonus plus five it should be fine
yeah
that's a good role came to the wrong
stream this this owl bear should have
gone to moonme 3D show yeah I know right
right tilts his head he doesn't trust
such a piece of food from your bag
hungry hungry I like like that
little guy oh macaroon welcome to the
food there you go
toss the food to the album the food
keep it in front what if it bites my
hand off wouldn't that be hilarious yeah
no
no frightened by the sharpness
but if I toss the food at him what if it
hits him in the face
we gotta try again sometimes dang it
will he just be gone forever
sure he'll come back no no
surely
all right let's get out of here yeah
okay it's okay we're fine he comes back
he comes back
you better
hey what is this over here
there's a boat yeah can we take
it and go somewhere
I don't know
should have ate the food
we just bought it
oh yeah yes that's bored I say yes on
the Lakes murky Waters oh you guys went
back
oh yeah
outside of the camp
goodbye
oh
did we get on the boat without moving
bye I also don't see it here we go no
I'm there I'm just telling you okay it's
okay we'll we'll get a waypoint and then
you can just teleport to us easy peasy
all right so cool
the boat looks so nice
wow can we find the one piece
you know
where where is the one piece oh no
uh uh
we have permission conversation by
pressing the ear
oh
boy do you want to fight
who are you
um
your parasite stares briefly then goes
still hopefully they don't get in the
fight
uh-oh
how desperate is that to make an ally of
a topsider
wow I will tell you what the sergeant
told Geck until you have the boots you
will not cross eh come back empty-handed
again and he'll feed him
oh the boots what boots
oh all right we have to fight are we
fighting
but Molly
yeah
I'll go find something else to do
we need you we can't win fighting
without you you can probably win
did we did we say did we save after we I
don't know I can't remember the last
time we saved me neither
all right it's gonna be fun he's already
let me see yeah we'll we'll just kill
him fast
and I've got I got another shot see it's
dead okay now we just have the ones on
the other ship
one two three four five
you got all your spells that's true well
I mean if they're gonna survive it's
cool yeah
have you made any new discoveries we'll
see jump over to the boat like I think
so we're all kind of just long distance
Shooters we are small in number and
rarely stay in one place for long it's
fine and I are working to improve
conditions there is an honest
that is hostile place
um
I wouldn't mind like the feeling yeah
yeah
we're not that far in the flight anyways
the campsite
friends fighting for their lives Mori
out here shopping
my grocery list
hmm yes spicy mushroom
no we can't get the owl bear we can't
it's from waking up
that's what happens when it sits okay
we'll get them next time yeah yeah it is
what it is we have to accept it
sometimes exactly I bet we don't have to
right leave the camera
okay I'm gonna follow you guys because I
don't know where both
persuade our way out of having to fight
them hey is everyone here
yeah yeah yeah
that's cool too violence
let's sail into the darkness with me
without my shoes yeah
no ogre Left Behind where's Geck who are
you okay we could lie
yeah and the name of the absolute yeah
[Music]
um
it's so Barefoot
full armor but no shoes all right all
right
no reason to get your horns in a Twist
whoa there well come on
let's get you to shore someone's
floating in the background yeah
it's so busted
you continue forward and silence ah okay
we avoided a fight thank God
surely we'll get to fight again well
there was plenty of people to fight
okay
you can always beat him up yeah where
are we
under their Grim Forge the Grim Forge
abandoned refugee
oh oh scene
no where oh trying I'm alone on the boat
wow I'm scared my toenails are so long
what where do you see your toenails
because she doesn't have shoes
I'm seeing something different from you
well now I'll see feet either well now
I'm in the other part of the cutscene
but it was just for a moment it's
looking overhead right into those nasty
toenails
you gotta clip those bad boys
no I see your nails
oh yeah oh
the guys with a welcoming party
wait what
are we seeing the same thing right now
no
share private what are you looking at
dialogue to public
spit it out there's no voice acting
um I don't hear anything are we spread
it out Sergeant finally choked true Soul
Nails neck oh no
tighter than a ring on a fat finger
you're me he pay up that's the
trouble he got the gold on him oh no the
game is this conversation's boogie oh no
the whole time I've just been seeing
nice shots of the scenery
there is a conversation going on
it's cut scene is bugged apparently
um it's a it's a popular glitch
I wow
oh can you like explain what's happening
um we're gonna fight okay nice I
get my fines oh never mind they said
never mind but we can still we can kill
everyone here for fun okay
basically there's there's a true soul up
there true Soul near I think
um
so we can kill these people if you want
to that could be kind of we could but I
don't know
um I don't think it'll aggro the whole
Camp because they're far away but let's
maybe oh you guys got the Waypoint then
yeah quick save your call Kiara
you want to find these two people down
here we can easily kill them
I think now I we should explore first
okay okay
this is the the Grim Forge
there's a boat
yeah
there's colorful spiders cool boats you
can talk to them
if you lose his body though it will
aggro everyone
oh wow cuties
[Music]
first we score then we kill that sounds
fun
what's happening raised by local
not a clue
and I got animal Harley yeah you're an
animal master of their chatter
and I shall add the bardic inspiration
yes
you see but we have lots of inspiration
yeah you can roll again is that
ridiculous
it doesn't even add the bonuses yeah if
you get a 20 or a one it doesn't add
automatic successful the largest spider
versus the other three yeah
wait oh bullying okay if you leave the
conversation I have animal talking on
maybe they'll say something different
oh
[Music]
Kiara
I want to see what happens
look at this mean girl spider yeah
for real oh my God
my father
okay well it's not quite what they were
saying that is some kind of troll
going on
that jokes
no spider bullying
wow you can't sit with us at the spider
table
was a betrayer
we will miss her
but she oh no we missed some context
here I think so oh oh well hey we didn't
kill this spider dude we did nothing
yeah we didn't he's watching
loot the dead spider
okay what else
besides dead people you can go up the
stairway if you want
oh
yeah
one more people conversation popping off
over there I was around about one
oh they're in love
they're straight to the Shadows
oh yeah
tell the sergeant we won't move a pebble
a pebble Pebble Pebbles
[Music]
booked out it's supposed to be in the
water
oh okay
how might I get one of my own I heard
the true Soul was trapped shouldn't it
your hands
in the man let's see
or maybe because the scene is full of
bugs haha get spiders or bugs
lion more showing
no who are you
oh okay look
your fingers nice and bony Prime for
digging you one near we need to kill
them claw him out yeah he's busy
time for death yeah
yeah time for a bra
I'm too close
we should have switched places yeah
spiders aren't bugs yeah they are
yeah they're bugs they're arachnids
I don't care a bug is a bug if it's in
my house I don't want it there it's a
bug
and understandable have a nice day
someone finished that one off please
switch he is oh oh oh
they're homies
is that an elevator
whoa
I think we got him
you killed this blade
he's not the wrong person oh God
oh
yeah
[Music]
Lord
casualties in War oh yeah
Maurice there's gold there's there's a
bun keep your hands tears
oh yeah there's a dude watching he sees
us oh hey man let's go we didn't kill
this guy he's just
he was chilling
oh
we didn't do that there was an auto save
that scares me just another crate no oh
probably fine
we call that way
it seems like a bit of a dead end over
there
oh okay
should we kill more people oh there's a
path
my perception check
okay
sorry I don't know what I found
um
a secret room maybe yeah there's a check
I got us some Golds uh lots of gold like
115 gold big gold cool
let's just find
nice nice chest
thanks people is a natural war criminal
open up only on accident
I was just trying to hit that one guys
but
it was an AOE that's all right we
forgive you he definitely doesn't and
his family doesn't but we forgive you
there's two guys over here we could kill
them too because they're Witnesses
mm-hmm
I think these guys suck it'll be fun to
kill him
hey yeah no they're beating people up
for no reason
only the guards are allowed to do that
as this one is about to demonstrate yeah
try it perhaps some gold now
forget that attack
yeah yeah violin let's go hey don't hit
it
oh perfect that was cool that was what I
was trying to do
okay
five against one buddy what are you
gonna do
oh he's dead he's super dead
let's see God good stuff
oh
in my inventory you can just take a look
in there just killed under the Yoke of
slavers
yeah people they're like your people
right
wait I'm a gnome right right oh
respect it's all about the respect
I'm gonna see what they're holding
yes yeah what are people's friends uh
yes may you rest in peace what's in your
pockets
[Laughter]
family oh money
that's nice I wanted a ring oh potato
invisibility
can we entered the door I wonder
probably
give it a try
knock knock have you guys ever tried
knocking on the door before are you lock
picking it yup it's open now yes he is I
opened it let's go let's go
[Music]
we'll do that
that build religion check everyone
failed wait no bagel
Bagel you know what this place is
yeah you got the religion killing people
for sure no oh you're right we're Shadow
heart plus Batman Open Door
secret room more secrets secret tunnel
oh never door
I want a lock pick oh it doesn't look
big it's open oh
looks like an ambush
jelly what are those ogre jelly
[Music]
nice a party won't start till we walk in
mm-hmm make it pop tonight
oh we're still going bam bush
what's alive
uh it's up it's upward someone has to
end their turn so we can all move up
yeah
oh nice party all in one spot all hits
oh he's dead
they're all dead I know they're not
still one left
yeah up here
get him
yes
oh wait well yeah okay that's all I
could do
that
[Music]
oh
Frank
I'm getting there we're getting there I
just wanted to shove them
oh
it's nice when you don't have to control
everyone in your party
nice
last shots nice take everything okay
there's some Scrolls here scroll will
fly
it's rare I'm gonna take it just to have
it yeah I'm thinking we need to fly some
special arrows kiwawa might be able to
use them yes
I give them to you they're she'll be in
your inventory thank you
be queef the queef I'm done
I can't wait to sleep
I am honored
I shall make best use of them
my inventory is such a mess right you
can sort it I do lots of Scrolls I don't
know if I'll ever use
yeah we should we should use them more
right and oh there's also still oh no we
took the chest okay is that what the
arrow were where the arrows were it
looks as though we can climb further if
you'd like to climb
oh
candle
oh wow
how far can we get
the question well it seems that since we
can jump that's pretty good
I may need to be eaten
yes please
I gotcha
grow there you go
thank you
it's a little bloody you doing okay
the back looks a little broken you know
hey where are we I'm safely no just
describe this is just a flesh wound well
yeah no back breaking it's fine I'm more
flexible now cool
yeah it's like a surgical operation yeah
oh
friend
looks I don't know but I see things that
we should take like the camp supplies
well let's see if they're worth killing
first I swear to iron hand one more step
she reminds me of Bibles the
SE the barrel is filled with smoke
oh no this is a contaminated somehow
blow the whole place up
be careful
hold on there's something wrong oh does
she knows it clean off I know what you
are one of them I think I saw this video
but if you stay in that conversation I
can sneak over there and you like the
thing you want me oh my God okay come
get me hold on don't make any don't make
any decisions yeah don't make any
decisions yet yeah go go steal some
bee boo steal it can I steal it super
funny
[Music]
so much for the Perfect Crime
holds little sway you'll see come on let
us at least roll for it so you may not
right to see it
oh she's mad yeah okay
that I feel like she she had a reason to
be mad and we could have like cleared it
up yeah is she like a good person is she
a girl she looks like a a deep gnome so
probably she's also probably a slave
here is he temporary hostile can we
disengage no we can't do Unleashed
non-lethal damage non-lethal damage oh
yeah
don't remember how it works you need to
go to your passives and turn it on when
it's your turn it's on I'm not gonna use
any spells I'm just gonna Bonk it yeah
is it on now guys chat I think it is
only melee only melee okay technically a
war crime
what does that mean I can shoot or no
shooting I don't think melee right I
think only one person needs to turn it
on yeah it's on for all of us gotcha oh
um
one person touch it once and then that's
it yeah
uh
so melee does that mean what does that
mean so if you if you shoot it with an
arrow I think she'll still die okay what
what about main hand attack
that's a melee oh yeah to get close get
closer
do a Stampy stamp not in this game in
real DND it's melee only gotcha uh-huh
[Music]
um
she's not dead right yeah nope she's
knocked out
I don't know can we like be friendly
with her when she wakes up for something
I don't know because she will wake up
you can always sleep here and wait until
it hangs up
do you also see like
like a Barbie girl Stone
yeah
do you also see a dark version of her
standing on the stone above her
I think it's a bug it might be a bug I
don't see anything okay
well now we can lose it so now I have
this bomb that does 50 to 120 damage
yeah I have a nuke now can I take what
she's holding it
yeah you can looter cool Rune powder
vial looks really cool
high damage
I wonder when she wakes up I don't I've
never experienced some waking up but
then again usually when I realize I've
done that I just kill them ah
loot attack
no way to wake her up can we throw a
potion at them yeah nice idea
I don't know if that really works well
we could always knocked out temporary
right so she'll wake up eventually yeah
you'll need the nuke
try shelving
sure yeah that was me okay
all right let's leave where she wakes up
yeah we got her new push
the consequences
just kidding yeah oh she's still knocked
out interesting she's just kidding I
thought she wasn't awake now I thought
for sure we'd be able to like negotiate
with her or something no look real sorry
about all that
I love this one
wow
ladies hang out sleepover let's go
yeah
[Music]
loves her ladies
new episode of girls talk
um
so
um what do you think of that asterian
guy like oh my God he's kind of like you
know you know yeah but what about Gail
though like he's also like pretty soon
yeah he's funny okay
and then there's will like oh my God
actually
no I can't choose but I'm guessing
Sarah's already taken it's so unfair
aren't you taking uh like Carla she's
like you know I guess so can you stop
being so beautiful and leave the boys to
the rest of us yeah Memorial pays sorry
for more real pain attractiveness
I am born with it I would give to you if
I could
man I'm so jealous
house night time when you're sleeping I
might just like rip out one of your
hairs and then make a two question
around your time
sticker waist to make fashion belt
yes striking yard trachea is uh throat
where you breathe it connects it's a
problematic
[Music]
okay we were turning
I suppose yeah your windpipe too bad we
couldn't talk to her man and it's okay
but at least she's alive maybe they
patched you and
no I think we're gonna need that we can
use that for later hey
oh
there's a sparkly thing back there
behind the door open sesame yeah that's
I think just the perception venue oh
sesame
ow yeah
can't throw too heavy oh that's too bad
we'll add so much silverware I know we
could sell it for money
[Music]
wine oh I found some camp supplies at
least yeah
good job Liara hey we can get drunk
later
like wine too
my night for the girls you can drag it
attack oh yeah what's left here
a lot we need we we need to go the other
way up the stairs okay lead the way fish
okay don't worry about the rock it's
okay
fish Barrel
fish Barrel okay fish and wine We Dine
tonight
isn't supposed to be here
is that not how you park a boat no it's
bugged
I don't know if that boat was there when
I was there too oh no there's a
different boat that's not supposed to be
in there
[Music]
all right lead the way Liara
okay Merchant yeah moving around I see
we'll take all those goodies
grab some gold and some minerals come
into her Shadow let all that has passed
stone masons
cool
wow no one's aggroed if you want hit
no they do not give a wow oh you
killed our Brethren's sick awesome we
got them too
cool kind of like uh you probably had a
reason
foreign
what should I be looking at Rock
whatever you want well all of it if I
may be so bold
take a look tell me what you see and be
thorough there's so much echo in here
nice
you're right
oh
wow it's really big area
three nine ten
minutes
wait huh because these Halls are so big
yeah so big yeah wow feelings High
ceilings very high ceilings indeed
crystals
hottest of flames smooth the stone and
left sulfuric crystals behind
the fires of the hells have touched
grimfort
Stir It Now
I'm ready to report my observation
it's been thorough I don't know what
that is
I guess I could use it as you need
I wish I had more skills
okay investigate just whatever you can
I'll add people guidance yeah
oh it's just five anyway oh wow
when you don't need it breaks of various
sizes clutter the corridor many split
clean lean too
yet some walls remain fully intact
brought these rocks down they were
smashed through in an instant
who did it something big charged through
here
something very big bigger and more what
do you think
that must be big
I shall try to assist
the statue okay wait
stand out against the weathered masonry
behind it
two Styles two Iris
the statue was carved from newer Stone
and erected by late comers to this
ancient Fortress
standing out
was erected the statue
maybe I am now ready to report my
observation incredible an entire history
written from dirt and debris picturing
an ancient city Bridge
Untold centuries later a new tribe
revives it fresh walls fresh sculptures
until a great hell Beast charges through
toppling the walls and crushing the
people
that explains the infernal play I found
perhaps you might have use of it
yes thank you
's only begun
there is more still to find I must get
you guys let's not kill him okay
yeah he seems chill now we can
trade once again
oh I'll just be quick
okay I'll sniff around a little bit but
not too much yes
[Music]
not a few
I I was gonna sell these potions
I know not the cat supplies
Swift as my feet can carry me
does my feet can carry me
[Laughter]
yeah
we did it she did me story about it
risk being an open
tired
okay rest little one oh infernal
alloying the ridges in this metal glow
faintly drawing your face the longer you
watch it's hellish positions
whisper but this is not like the
infernal iron yeah we need infernal iron
but I don't know what we can do with the
alloy but the Catholic we'll keep it
until
because this is her name
[Music]
a cutscene mm-hmm uh-huh some
unintentional cutscene unintentional
cutscene I just wanted to say hello to
the cows but then they had more stuff
more Mighty elf
cloaks in darkness
ten Masters ago
and ten more
but I remember
there was the work of two and the blood
there was the Thorne's Army
there was the hair Beast
broke them
the Catholic Thorne's name I can't wait
till we meet Catholic Thorne
his voice actors so good
[Music]
yeah impressive memory damn how do they
remind remember so much how old are they
and many mothers Beyond
blessed to see many
[Music]
cursed to see many Die oh
sounds cool
I saw tusks and flesh
smelled fire
and eggs
and smashing smelly omelette
I know not
so I say not
yet
if you not know do not speak
by the Shadows
Shadows
okay so I have no one else to tell this
about so I'm going to tell you guys you
guys know portal right yeah
the voice actor is Cave Johnson
the same guy who voices him so JK
Simmons
[Music]
who's Kate Johnson never mind Erica from
Portal 2
I played I played all the portals even
portal free he's he's the one who goes
on the lemon rant in Portal
ah lemons I remember some lemons yeah
yeah yeah black guy that guy
what's this eye doing here
um it will call reinforcements if we get
in a fight
I was so close to getting into that
chest
no one was there when I tried to open it
then this lady just showed up go away
all right good try just go look about
um
whoa dark just to see her male armor
medium armor
not for me I suppose but there's some
cool armor here oh here's the shadow
heart
there's one on this one too
oh you really same time clad in the same
oh Andrew deadbeat armor
portal free favorite team
gluten free is real
oh
BJ's also intelligence we we're not very
smart
ah
uh okay you see nothing special just
twins
it's endearing though
let's focus on the problems at hand
oh yeah but the armor did I picked up
the green and the others are and you got
a special one
wasn't anything exceedingly useful but
isn't it yeah really wanted to steal
from that traveler's chest oh anyway I'm
back on my way to you guys
oh that's what the animals are for
oh cute Pizza people she looks
like a World of Warcraft character right
now all right
yeah that was the armor I found on the
cramps in my arm trying to whip the
dragon in beasts back to him no don't
hurt them
he's a nasty little guy I'm gonna I want
to beep him up
kill him I mean do it yourself
they want you dead too uh be careful
maybe we saved because uh you can get
tossed off the edge here yeah save game
thank you Maury hoping yeah I wanted to
say though
I think they're just something you gotta
kill them I guess I'll just save
the save islands make sure that long
lethal's off yeah we can leave the guys
but the non-lethal the animals oh okay
yeah
possibly nice idea
oh what was that
you can save them you gotta talk to them
yeah but you have to talk to them before
talking to the guys
oh it didn't give me an option yeah it I
just entered a cutscene when I walked in
lag oh
kill the sphere thing all right I'll get
it hopefully
well let's see
if your Excalibur damn move away no come
back
you piece of garbage
he's back come on surely I can use
yeah
you what no way
[Music]
come back this ball just
making you guys keep coming I'll be or
keep keep going I'll be right back oh
okay
you almost got this eye he's very close
to being dead
we should we should take it to our doggo
and let doggo play with it as a boy this
idea
I don't want a frenzy because I keep
wanting to save my friends yeah I use it
too often all that guy friends eat oh
okay well maybe first
okay
okay well that wasn't on you
everyone's enemies oh no
well we can make him pay for it
I want to take the death seriously with
this beautiful tune is playing I don't
want the poor cows and they're free now
yeah it's a good point chat and they're
free
man
they're into better I have no mercy now
that looks like he can't go really far
right now but later he's mad he's mad
because those are animal Brethren yeah
they look like him just bigger yeah
that's good
[Music]
yeah that's what you get let's go
cows or something you gotta talk to him
well if you guys should happen talk to
people first
who all is what it is
talking talking
sounds like sleep talking yeah I
returned at the perfect time
welcome back the animals have died but
not by our hands oh well yeah
we did our best
so sad he tried to save them could have
done
die
yeah these guys are Chumps I'm not gonna
waste a frenzy on them yeah
[Music]
um
but I'll gladly tank your hits if you
are so bold
yeah
nice one and then another one frenzied
strike
yeah
let's go
that's what you get
that for animal cruelty you little
yeah
why is this one hiding in the corner
because he's a coward baby yeah
everything
wait they're red but can we can still
lose them yeah because no one's around
to watch because this dude has a ton of
stuff
yeah
good stuff I mean yeah I would say so
he's got like fish a fish good good
things and some rings
um about the aminals
animals the animals
the aminals
and animals the aminals aminals
I got everything
no I was desperately trying to figure
out how you were saying it wrong because
I was like it's not right but what's
what's the matter what's wrong with it
it sounds correct to me
all right ladies
where would you like to go next
question uh wherever the restaurant is
going I guess sorry
uh
it doesn't let me lock pick I don't know
it does
show me your insides
lent me an Insight over your inside yeah
yeah I want to see what's in it
oh plus one there's plus nine
uh but I don't necessarily need a uh
someone else you can sell it
okay maybe actually maybe you would like
a nice new cross bow uh wait I will if
you don't need inventory is a mess Let
Me sort by new or whatever
uh okay I'll put it in your inventory
thanks uh
uh it's Anya it's I took your soul coin
instead okay no I'll give it back here
find it it's a green
crossbow oh light crossbow plus one I
see it yeah yeah this is better than
what I have thanks nice yeah no magic
for you Gail this is mine
you're welcome
and anything else here no right oh wait
it actually goes down here it looks like
it
there's just a chest I'm looting it
right now oh okay then we shall stay all
right
on The High Ground yeah I have The High
Ground
[Music]
if this was my solo playthrough I would
read every single book
chess down there it's on there too can
we even get down there wait can I use
feather Fall Again wait everyone come
here and maybe I can feather fall it
looks like there's a place we can
probably climb down to oh
because we can climb back up yeah look
it up from over down there that looks
kind of cool yeah
well wouldn't it be more fun to jump
down okay yeah all right baby
if you say so I believe
okay
[Music]
wow
oh it's a medic
Sam
RPG Staples
was real
I'm surprised
pretty surprising are they strong I
wonder
I'll frenzy if they're strong they've
got 40 Health okay Frenzy
oh maybe it's nice
maybe they're not that spelled
mm-hmm
I'm a reckless attack
maybe yeah it was attacked nice damage
that's all right
don't push them down they have great
items oh okay
yeah
surely they're holding some goodies
right
um yeah I want the goodies
oh it's my turn oh my god I'm an idiot
no problem can't reach the dead that's
okay I'll just shoot shooty splody
oh
I swear to God man I'm gonna lose I'm
about to lose myself
unknown oh it's fine
still getting used to the mouse and
keyboard it would say yeah
jump down here with us join us I'm good
wow
wow we've got feather fall
Oh I thought you meant jump down into
the electricity with it no
I see I would not wish that upon yeah
it's good for me to have high ground up
here for you guys gotta tell me what's
in the chips
I want to know it's just curiosity
a lot of daggers okay
I know now I shall jump down broken
I want to look and see just what's in
there
um there's wondrous gloves they're rare
they're in my inventory I got hand ax
plus one if anybody won that
'd be good for throwing
what's in this oh do they all have good
items oh
is kind of high
you can try don't keep me
keep me
let's give it a try
oh oh okay that's just a week no
okay this opening is also 20.
wait I can do it
I got 21. yeah
this better be something good it's just
oh it's a scroll of evidence
and a scrub magical scroll
um if it's not okay yeah oh so by the
way guys I used one inspiration sorry
about that but it was going to be a
critical failure and I didn't want to
see no problem
um
it's about the kefiric form
mmm strange
what's it mean let our intent be known
an alliance between the Harpers and the
emerald Enclave tonight that we may end
forms Reign of Terror
okay interesting
now you have toilet paper excuse me
oh this is a bug right
the mimic looks alive to me but no he's
super dead for me yeah it's definitely
he's real me
Al to you okay is this where it ends
yeah go up here
ah big climbies well you can climb
obviously
well already in use because you got
those long toenails on your stuff
to really dig in
I really dig into the Rock You Know use
more open can't get there why tiny
hidden chest why can't mauriopa get
there someone's in the way oh wait never
mind
hey
what
all right your turn Mario babe There we
go moriope is just a little slow
you need a hand I'm okay
we're doing next you lead me
is there still something interesting
here yeah there is
rocking right into what I stole from
who's that well we can go down here if
you'd like okay down
okay we go down wherever you want down
down
and then why don't you go see what all
those people are doing okay
what are you doing
oh what the hell what kind of party's
popping off
party
and there's a party oh there's there's
no no oh more more slavery oh they're
slave driving
why don't you talk to them yeah the
words
[Music]
their nose right save my people yeah
okay we can eavesdrop I'm sure my role
will be satisfactory
smoke powder
what if she's smart she won't be coming
back
stole the smoke powder
we gotta give it to them
yeah
go ahead
she's
she's I mean we did knock her out but
she's alive
well that option wouldn't be available
if we killed her they'll die in that
tunnel possibly
my Belgium would die back there blow up
that wall I'm begging you
all right okay hurry imagine being like
in that cave in Forever
we'll save you justice all right do your
best to save
some of the time right you can blow that
you can blow it wait who had we got
two powders right I have a vial it's
something called a
hold on a sec this is called Rune powder
vial the Rune powder inside explodes
when ignited damaging everything in the
vicinity
what does the barrel say
the barrel the barrel they're talking
about the thing we took from philamine
yeah so the the barrel well we have two
we have
a barrel
does less damage look at he was the Lyle
baby okay okay is that right here
augmented voice clutch
are you okay Callie True song Yes you
know she all right she's just going
through it the voice is in her head you
know right
are you nere
what happened here Expedition
passage trapped
gnomes useless don't trust bugs
um that counts a bit of rubble and few
moving figures
all right let's get him out I guess hmm
okay try to focus
really quick is that a bonus yeah
try oh no
I don't think you added the bonus yeah
no
may I please roll one more time yeah
yeah let me add my guide thanks oh thank
you okay didn't know how to add it there
thanks
yay there we go yeah we're good
let's see the results into an image
feverishly debris
well two others lie dead at near speed
their flesh scorched by powerful Magic
is frustration tinged with rage oh he
really wants to be let out and the
Gnomes ain't doing
well how well I guess but what if we
accidentally blow him up
yeah he's probably fine I'm gonna blow
him up
um yeah
because it's less powerful
yeah use your vial okay
do you let's see maybe is there an
option to use an item after we do this
by the way I have somewhere to take you
guys okay oh okay this sense near his
frustration okay I want to help it let
me see if I can just use the item
okay
try it out we'll see someone says drop
aisle on the ground and shoot it with
fire okay let's save let's save first
yeah yeah good idea
you just drag it out of the inventory
and put it on the ground uh-huh get over
smash your way through
just throw it I mean I guess there's
that too
let's see bro
throw it on the ground
I know I have where's thorough oh come
on please I know I'm not an idiot
you can just drag and drop from your
inventory too okay
here we go uh the vial yeah but can we
tell them to walk go away
hopefully they'll get the vibe you want
to go chat with them
just a quick check if it's possible ah
[Music]
drop it on the floor and they'll Run
Okay drag it to the ground gotcha
okay no problem
I'll peel Your Balls Like Potatoes if
you don't move wow that sounds awful
oh
okay I'll shoot it good luck Kylie wanna
step a bit Yeah okay yes
all's well it ends well oh this game
right there hmm
which rocks
they come and they go
who is she
finally
oh nine years old ladies
has been my room is he a bad guy
the true stove
and I just stand there on unshocked that
doesn't seem characters bothered
it's not how I would react finish the
sleeves
for the weak true soul
like you
um
yeah exactly the absolute paid you to
try nears faith
thrin liar is unimpressed
oh it's gonna feel good it is a true
soul
let the absolute save all right all
right all right
oh
you so much just touched me I'll tear
you from live to limb yeah guides my
hand
come at me bro oh I can't wait to kill
him it's gonna be rad
she must have a knife
true Soul has betrayed us what the
I want his clothes
[Music]
oh that's a lot of people yeah good luck
we'll take them
we can take them perfect time to Frenzy
yeah yeah perfect time to Frenzy
uh all right
where's this guy oh see over there
better time
okay damn
I I I'm the closest to the boss so I'll
go for him I guess Pro tip don't end
your move standing close to Lava yeah
that seems smart
[Music]
see how strong they are without their
leaders
good damage
destroy him
okay
maybe I'll throw another one
see how many you can grapple and throw
yeah
okay that was weak no match for us
easy all right stronger
Jones
yeah yeah we'll lose them we'll loot him
after we kill all these other people
this attack
don't go Power Ranger yeah
nothing else huh okay I guess on
and made from history
and in charge
we'll be able to get it again we just
need to take his body
yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna pick up his
body to take it to Camp yeah exactly
his mind mastering my my my board
oh no it became an enemy
oh wow
be careful
[Music]
owie
these guys are chumps
yeah total Chumps on easy mode yeah
sorry baby
wow oh thank you
sweet
IE
Who Dares okay how many can I eat
breakfast as many as you want
as your little people heart desires
mm-hmm
okay
that was awesome wow nice that was very
cool yeah I'm gonna go over here and try
to eat this
fish yeah
all right I just can't I can't force
myself to push it Forward 10 out of 10
lava
maybe he'll come back to his sentence
yeah I don't want to hurt him
[Music]
whoa there with the burns
no your master oh it's okay
protects me now
then it was a shield
isn't that sweet
yeah his butt smells kind of bad funky
oh I can't attack right now okay right
in your face
whoa
that looks so good right oh yeah just
line up right there yeah
I'm deed strike
yeah
man
a lacerating strike actually so you can
bleed
yeah nice
oh
[Music]
it looks like a science I like it
okay and I get one more shot
um
Corsair Greymon
all right that was cool that was a
Lightning Charge right that was very
cool
oh there
recycling
resize
um
all of these guys are bad guys CM yeah
okay
yeah that's what I was thinking I was
hoping you would use that
yeah the best time to use it yeah when
they're all clumped together like chumps
how the am I surviving this I don't
know
um
oh my God
is a phoenix too yeah I don't even care
about attacking with my boar right now I
just want to save Wawa
do your best
lava yeah a bit difficult there's
terrain do you have a like incredible
lava walking loafers Jesus
oh Carlos would be proud of me yeah she
would okay get out of there yeah can I
jump please
hell yeah yeah oh my God
all right who else um
okay let's go there's just two more left
one is in the tent and yeah the other's
up there
oh I could get him actually now fully
there now
okay okay okay you wanna make it
difficult
smells like fried chicken
oh no
oh easy mode yeah imagine we're on easy
mode and it only took me down like 40 HP
or so imagine this on like non-easy mode
you're dead yikes
it's pretty yucky
easy mode love is gentle in tactician
you die right away
Z I believe it
thank God
you're so close
that's fine yeah I don't care I'm I'm
not afraid they're almost dead
ah done
yeah one HP
okay who's the last mother F-word oh
he's up there
shoot him one more I got one more
oh yes
brimming without magic oh worms
so we have a mind player specimen a
thousand gold
a dagger plus one
um sort of Screams
he has food I'm gonna take them oh what
both side
and then we can eat bread okay
thick layer of dust coats the bottom of
the lantern
oh Dusty
um
investigation
let's add bonus
thank you nerissa
not that you needed it
wow
this lamp
Magic Lantern
look even closer at it okay
this is Pixie Dust
all Left Behind after a picture
didn't he like imprison a pixie inside
Tinkerbell was in there oh no okay I
picked up a bunch of rings you guys if
you want to look at them there's also
one called a deed of ownership yeah I
have some weapons I have uh George's
great sword uh a shining Savor of skulls
and um a new bow
so Kiara we can't access your inventory
for some reason will you send me those
boots
yes I I was trying to put it on you
directly but wait
I'll hold it at the bottom of your
inventory thank you finally you will
wear shoes finally no more naked feet
can you pick up near's body and bring it
back to Camp later yeah I can
yeah it's a trophy we're gonna put him
in the camp
might be useful
oh
he's right here thank you okay I need to
bring you guys somewhere
else
really quick let me oh really thanks
really quick I need to send some stuff
back
then to Camp I need to send some things
to camp
because oh yeah you're covered right now
very sorry okay let's see
Goblin scimitars send the camp
okay let's have a whole body I'm holding
yeah only level five
oh cap of Wrath do not send the body to
cap
uh we could but we can also just keep it
too does this count as armor this cap
yeah
it's really cool I don't know if it'll
not work with my build sadly but I like
it
looks interesting it's not armor yeah
okay
actually yeah I'm Gonna Keep It on thank
you
let me send a couple more things really
quick camp
okay now you may lead the way okay come
with me everyone well first someone
talked to the Gnomes Maybe
oh I might still be too many too much
holding they better be thankful
oh okay
um okay I do want to throw the weapon
that's it
all right come with me
um all right one sec just a moment I am
walking very slow because I have many
many items
um y'all got Misty step
I do not have that
probably somewhere
I have a scroll of fly does that work
too yeah that works
Kelly if you need something I have a
screen don't worry okay okay fly over
here
roll a fly
come here so they have space Oh
yeah but it's more fun if you get to do
it yourself the first time don't you
think let's see scroll will fly no
Target
I disagree with that oh wow where could
we possibly be put it on yourself
and then you get like a fly option you
can't get here oh why option yeah like a
skill on the right I see thank you get
them right thank you thank you
wow what oh another way more oh boy oh
nice Coolio the Asian forage
oh cool
so they're special or around here you
can find if you look hard enough and
then you can also find molds and uh like
over here right this this thing nice
mold like
asbestos no you can find molds make
armor
iron here
[Music]
they're mad we're here they don't want
us to be yeah
mm-hmm
you dumb dumbs actually I'm gonna climb
up the rope in a second so get ready
the big jerk damn it
actually I could fly
well damn we keep on missing
calm down eventually
yeah
animated please come down please oh
there's one here too he's coming down
for to meet us and then meet us with his
sword meet entry yeah critical Miss
dummy
King there's more real bet
all my health oh yeah right my health
was pretty cool
well well
[Music]
only five
kill him somebody kill him
no I got him
oh whoopsies
I didn't think it would throw them up
there by the river
that's the song actually hmm
yeah can we do a short rest after this
maybe sure yeah or a long rest because
I'm out of spells now oh yeah yeah okay
and we're getting closer to four hours
so once yeah
this is probably a good place to end it
I think we got the Waypoint so we can
come back here whenever definitely
growing um
sorry
[Music]
well he's still there he's just down
there ah
he he's actually not even dead
yeah
why forty percent wait wow he just broke
his back at school
yeah I killed him nice nice
all worked out down down down by the
Lava River
poking legs for you
honestly the maps of this game are so
insanely beautiful and detailed
sometimes I know right just go away with
my camera and look at everything because
it's yeah it looks amazing
what is that like oh my God sorry am I
are we still fighting
yeah you're still alive
why are you still alive
like a balloon
I'll just I'll just try to hit normally
this time
[Music]
come on
okay before we long rest let's go get
some stuff
oh
yeah kind of come down where the body
fell I always picked up a mold so yeah
everybody asked me to pick up this other
mold here it's for me I believe yeah
yeah
um ready I'll take it for now okay seems
kind of heavy yeah I definitely won't be
able to hold that oh wow you're melting
don't melt uh don't die I wonder what
this could be
mythrow vein we know what missile is
don't we key on them isn't it like a
really nice mineral mid frail mid frail
almost yeah it's mythrall close enough
see you guys
okay
well that's a good point to uh we'll get
out of the lava area and then we can go
long rest and then save and uh start
over
and not start over is call it a day all
right new game time I'm tired
let's restart
oh
nerissa needs sleep
legally yeah I do
understandable I have a stream earlier
than usual tomorrow too so yeah some
sleep will be good F0 f099 Deathmatch I
wanna play that too
it actually is seems to be really like
Smooth in terms of like servers even
though there's like 99 people racing
with you they have their dedicated
servers so it actually like Works cool
I'm excited to test it out oh this is a
jazz
I take another eyebrow a stinky Cloud a
stinky Cloud
yeah I want that
oh
uh we need to use some Scrolls a bit
more or I guess we could just sell them
no no
no
okay
in my solo playthrough I use the Scrolls
a bit more yeah oh if we save them
um I might expect one into Wizards like
yeah
I I might be doing that too later
I might do I want to split with Rogue
and uh wizard wow okay
yeah learning spells just seems useful
you know
good shall we go to the camp then I
guess yay yeah go to camp
oh naked lady lying down on the ground
oh is that mythical oh did he suck her
night Warrior mintra she's like naked
naked
oh
wait wait hold the girl whose armor we
stole
I think he's haunting us
it's a glitch I definitely don't have
nudity on but I'm still nervous
okay she's weaved perfect only on the
lower part
yeah yeah yeah I'm on my screen it's fun
yeah yeah she's she's leave
are you sure cute I just feel like it's
like from the camera all right oh it's
fine Callie I mean go talk to our
favorite NPCs what's on yours when in
doubt Callie just think about it the pp
game that Bells played yeah it was okay
that is true that's okay then it's a
good new standards are being set it's a
very good point
[Laughter]
um
she just glitches around sometimes
she'll haunt the camp you know I want to
put on the ground this freaking dude
yeah right
get him on the ground
oh at least he's not naked yeah
what's his body oh what the my bolo
upset about is trying to loot a guy that
we brought here what the
is a bit special
I mean I'll pick him up and take him
somewhere else damn no no no it's fine
yeah right
wow I love how they make camps for each
like specific area that you're in right
there's so much love to detail the
attention to detail I think that I love
it I can't say I'm not respect to the
but once you've taken a little creator
there's no telling how he's gonna
convince me no brain worms up
he's not enlightened
ah he doesn't want them it's fine
with these parasites yeah he's fine well
I get three worms Lacy where did I put
that guy
this was in my inventory a second ago
I was
he mentioned dark justices and we've
come across all this I didn't I didn't
realize we were watching sorry Kiara
what I'm not watching anything it's a
coincidence I mean I'm watching you yeah
that's what I mean I was skipping text
because I didn't realize you were
watching it oh no no five but I'm here
no problemo hold on
how did we steal them
Volo
yeah let's keep your hands to yourself
what the Volo Jesus
what why is he so mad why is he so mad
you have a little leave if you let him
perform eye surgery yeah
wait I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll I'll
I'll give up my I'll give I'll let him
do the eye surgery on me unless people
wants it you're gonna let yourself down
eye surgery okay
for real good eye surgery
we have specimen uh yeah I picked it up
you guys won't care if I lose this body
here will ya
I don't think we can take his clothes
but we need his
something from him later so just leave
leave him in like the your traveler's
pack my Travelers oh even my chest
put him in my traveler's chest
nice chill rotting body yeah it doesn't
look like he's holding anything right
now
sucks we can't take his clothes we can
take mentors that doesn't make any sense
that that seems a little uh no right so
it's because myntra is uh a companion
you can recruit her if you do certain
meet certain requirements near is not
so that's why I'm in thara is special
and you can take her clothes and
underwear okay I get it well I'm glad to
stuff his body in my chest
the chill dead body in there Mario if it
does not need to explain
all right baby
yep all right let's see
Volo yeah yeah definitely seems like a
trustworthy dude if I just
tear in your eye I could quickly
dear sweet God
quit the shoutings
I suppose I can
bling bling I'll need to research the
particulars however oh
and I'll have this little issue sort of
a good conversation
is that it
for now
it needs time apparently he needs time
just a bit longer
now that you know it to the next long
rest
I should tell you oh
okay okay
surgery kind of scares me I don't really
want to see this understanding yeah I'm
pretty gnarly
yeah
all I'm asking is that you keep your
eyes open oh we have another suit what
more could I ask absolutely the wearer
bear is the absolute
brands
are you still trying to raise them up eh
just find a vampire that will drink your
blood conversation
trust me I'm just I'm just chatting
giving the Naps a little more screen
time I see yeah yeah yeah because you
know I'm not giving my perspective so
it's fine transforming into a grotesque
monster
no no
it's coming Marion crash reporter
error has occurred and the game has quit
unexpected okay let's arm rest
well let's end the day yeah I guess yeah
what about you
Relic no oh yeah there's a freaking
cutscene thank you
no it's annoying it warn you again Erica
that may be caused by problems in your
game installation what the heck what the
yeah we can just verify your
installation next time you launch the
game sure oh
wait
yeah just just wait we'll just wait
eh no I mean is it it's fun
that's fine it's fine uh I don't want
you to miss out on it
eh okay wait um it's just two bad
fighting each other yeah they
really hate each other's guts
kind of hot though
yeah I agree but it's now downloading
content for some reason
really slowly
uh
don't worry about me anyway okay
when uh bee boo continue
okay uh
let's do something precious to my kin an
heirloom girl fights
this artifact is the only thing keeping
us from becoming slaves
that's cute
oh they're gonna fight either way I win
ah she's one of those either way oh did
you know Lazelle is only 23.
a youngling I know a baby
oh but hey wait
you chose this we all saw this coming
spare me the justifications coward
if anyone asks I'll say you were trying
guys if you want to see what's happening
watch Galley stream to be more boy I am
um
uh
sorry frog lady
the new update caused it me listening to
someone else yeah because it happened
the moment I clicked on listening into
the conversation range
um
[Music]
it's the artifact we need not her
let me up and I'll show you
not Lisa
that's a promise
we need her we need her
can I turn my back on you
never
Hey
listen the grip on your pride for one
blasted moment won't you we needn't be
enemies this plenty of those to go
around already yeah you're being so cute
[Laughter]
ladies
whoa
yeah let's not pit two band
against each other girls
in this entire party
and then you guys
yeah enough girl fights to go around
okay well that was the end of that and
it looks like it did heal up koala as
well you know yeah
yeah yeah that's good let's close the
game yeah so we saved we save and leave
good time today good time respect even
though you girls were tired
good old time with you guys ask for the
usual it's always a good time anything
yeah promote a talk about what are your
next dreams happening
um
I have a stream tonight I'm going to be
watching perfect blue with my members
and then uh Monday uh around similar
time to when this stream started this
morning I have a collaboration with
onigiri on Twitch so are you cooking
she's cooking I'm directing her how to
cook a dish of my choosing that sounds
fun yeah so please look forward to it
yeah
I just want to say again uh stream my
album and my new MBA it's good please
also there's a Korean version of do you
up now it's so cool I didn't even know
you could sing in Korean like that
sounds so good thank you I learned
Korean over the past
um yeah first half of the year uh I took
private lessons so now I'm pretty decent
I might say nice you're amazing korean's
so freaking hard good job proud of you
Kiara
yes okay
what's up what's up what else
um let's see for for Mori
um I'm gonna be streaming um I'm gonna
be streaming f099 uh pretty early my
time 9 A.M my time
um and yeah come hang out I heard that
there aren't custom lobbies but that's
okay well I'll try and get in a death
match together anyway
um and then I'll do that for a couple
hours and then
I'm always taking again a really little
small vacation but I think they'll do a
members only stream that night while I
sip some champagne and just chat with
you guys
um
yeah some champagne I think a little
sippy
um and then yeah that'll be that day and
then the following day is endurance
karaoke until the big 2 million three
hundred thousand
I have I'm preparing a lot of songs a
lot of them will be reduced
names
it's good
yeah so that's what's up with Mori how
about you people
uh I have a shave in six hours yeah oh
good night
and then
um we're playing armored Core and
hopefully we can finish New Game Plus so
we can PVP maybe with Molly sometime
yeah once I get finished with it yeah
[Music]
take a nap
yeah by the way uh seems like next week
there will be no baldus gate which is
actually surprisingly the first week
since we started where we're not doing
anything interesting yeah we made good
progress surprising yeah oh we really we
really are we're almost done with act
one kind of not really kind of but yeah
somewhat wow
everyone what's up
everybody
bye-bye everybody take care of
yourselves and we look forward to seeing
you again next time
[Music]
thank you