[Music]
so
kick kick kick
[Music]
welcome back nice to see you again
sorry to keep you waiting because yeah
koopa was asking me mommy mommy when are
we gonna continue porto
sorry i was mommy was busy kobo mommy
was in america
mommy was in big big america to record
some stuff
busy busy busy yeah now we have time
i i think we are currently at chamber
number four
excursion funnels or whatever that's
pronounced as
um i hope we can finish the game today
but cooper said she can play
maximum free hours
so we will see yeah we'll see we'll see
we'll try our best
yes uh also do you remember how to play
the game kobo
maybe let's see
okay
perfect perfect
perfect okay i'm orange and i'm big and
you're blue and you're small let's go
and it's so perfect the color and the
size it's perfect right i forgot it was
this perfect
nice
i have to build this new course just for
you thank you glad to see you've noticed
that you two have become extremely close
oh
i'm not sure i like that yes he's
jealous
is your glados in english or in
indonesian
english oh okay
i don't know can she
that would be
funny because i don't know she's so
sassy
oh oh what does this do oh
air gesture whoa
sick moves look at me cobalt
i did a flip you can try too
[Music]
no oh wait oh
there's a portal thingy up there we're
sending you somewhere ah
i'm not sure where i am oh
nice to make fun where am
wait did you see something to make a
portal over there there's that wall yeah
yeah but where are we going with you
when i'll come with you
i'll come with you oh i wonder if it's
okay to come with you
mommy up here mama
okay okay
nice
i'm following you
or just
oh
but
it's not open okay it's not open oh we
have to fall down
[Music]
there's something
here i can make portal here like oh in
front of me but
really
then i guess i'll have to die first and
then come through your portal
maybe
but choose the right color
no no no can't can't because
there's no bridge here you will you will
die immediately oh there's
uh yeah that's okay there's no platform
here
[Music]
not sure what happened there all right
let's try again no problem
or is it maybe the other way around is
it this way it doesn't matter maybe it
doesn't matter
maybe it doesn't even matter
okay and this time michael first maybe i
have an idea but i would like some blue
here can you put some blue
well i can't oh you can't see it well
come join me come join me
okay
come over here
how do i say uh come over in indonesian
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
so we have this
same thing again this time i go you stay
okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
what
hello camera okay door
okay which color did i use i used yellow
so
ah let me catch you this should work
yes
[Music]
what's glass talking about also chad do
you remember how to
uh
there was like one key where you could
show somebody something on the screen
not making a portal but like signaling
something
i wonder what's happening
f
f is a pain tool f ah it would be
pointless
entering the test who's carrying oh here
oh yeah who's carrying i'm i'm totally
carrying kobo totally so we have a
uh catapult
oh no oh no oh no
no no
i was a testing subject so that kobo
could be safe that transpired just as
you said it would nice ah what does the
this button do
ah it opens up there and there's a
portal thingy
and then we have one here
now we already have an airflow
i know i know i know i'm going there
okay
why
i don't know why can i
yeah it's not quite straight ah
if i can't reach there how about how
about now oh okay
maybe higher how about now
uh but it goes the other way it doesn't
really help you i guess
oh nice yeah
over there i kind of want the other
direction
oh oh wait you're over there ah yeah i'm
over here
i can make portal here oh
well wait i'll send you some more air
wait
there's there's a button here oh
that's touch
how can i touch it
i think it was eve
oh you're right
oh i think i guess you can send it over
here somehow
ah so i can keep the ball on the button
i suppose maybe
[Music]
ah yes oh i got the ball
nice i wanna if i just keep it
on the button is that what the purpose
is i hope so
okay
um in that case i'll try coming over to
you
oh thank you okay thank you
[Music]
um
not the perfect position kobold um it's
a little bit on the side
and that's not i'm maybe a little bit
more to the left
okay go down first mommy oh i can try to
jump over
oh wait oh yeah you're right
where's the
where is it okay i'm here
where are you oh no problem no problem
ah but that ah that gets rid of the
portal yeah okay okay right right
how was it again like
here
oh yeah more over there
yes yes
now we got it it's okay now um
okay nice and yes
oh no wait i should ah yeah right i fell
down because the black oil disappears
oh
yeah you're right so
you can't go here
[Music]
okay why
ah i think i can uh i can't you know new
one look you from here oh
yeah i can hit them you're too short
you're too short to go
it's a smile
but at least we can try no no that won't
work cover
we'll make the portal again
oh yeah
you got the small model
[Music]
there we go
yeah the wrong opinion about you you're
not too short you can do it kobo but but
what went wrong so i
when i go over there
the my portal disappears so the airflow
disappears so there must be all right
why is there a laser here
why is there
that over there
oh well there's even more stuff over
here
where
where are you mommy
like the the end of the room ah
yeah yeah there's another portal thingy
portal placement over here but
first i need to get to your side hmm
um
from where you are currently you can't
uh
you can't reach the
platf
yeah i can't it's so high i'm too short
you can't make a
a portal here right over here
i can't do it it's here
[Music]
barriers
wait it's so easy it's so easy though
i think it's so easy oh is it
wait
i
why no is it is it easy maybe it's not
easy
no that doesn't reach
i'm thinking thinking hard
yeah we
we have to think with portals kobold
we have to think of portals ah
i think
wait wait so i flow over there and then
and then what if i ah
no
i'm thinking maybe i can get myself over
to that side and then flow through oh
like i wanna i'm gonna go over here
[Music]
let's uh just try to make portal there
maybe the the test try
make portals
wait
i'm confused i'll just jump but it'll
just get rid of everything again
don't call me uh i wanna see what's
behind uh here
yeah there's a okay i
uh i can send you there
if are you able to go for the red portal
or can you not reach this one no i think
i can't i can't do anything here
i oh wait wait a minute
uh let me
hang here
and my portal will be gone
and your portals you're there
and maybe i can make portal here
i don't know for what but yeah
that's the laser
is i think i love it for later maybe we
have to
get both of us over there
[Music]
lock the laser with the ball
oh
the ball
yeah
wait
um
okay that means that well
once we're up there right now we need
the ball so we can get up there
if we want to go over there we need a
new ball
um so this one will disappear so first i
think both of us come over there but i i
why don't you make a portal here
to descend to send the ball immediately
you are uh wait you want to stand the
ball only wait
you can try sending the ball only wait
wait um
what's our plan actually i don't
understand we have to send a ball there
right yeah or because it will block the
laser
wait um how about uh we switch we switch
uh rose
can you make a blue portal here
yes and i see it from your point of view
and go
um
[Music]
ah
yes
[Music]
oh
i can make a portal over there from here
so
idea idea
uh idea
um
yeah do that
uh-huh
and now
i send you the air back got it
uh wait yeah we have some connections i
think this is new we have a new
connection here with the airflow
right because we can
wait where's your where's your light
blue one over there i see can you try
flying oh uh no but right no the the
things disappear
ah
yes but do you see it
now we have
the airflow glowing over here
we need to send the ball to the lesser
right
yeah the laser yeah yeah yeah
oh
you try
throwing the ball uh on the catapult
like putting it on the catapult or
flying together with the ball i don't
know
either with the with the
ball or without the ball
now
[Music]
if only the ball will fly then the
portals don't disappear yeah let's try
the ball only
i think the ball will disappear through
that oh yeah that's right that's right
that's true too so
so doesn't it
so this man
[Music]
on purpose let's see where uh ah this
way ah this way it goes for the yellow
one maybe we i have an idea i have an
idea
i have an okay okay okay okay
i think i'm getting closer we have to
send the ball through here
uh so it goes the other way which means
the light
the yellow one it must go
i must go um here
now my red one is in the way
light one light yellow okay
uh
and then i send
huh
can you make the blue one there again uh
the
dark ear blue
dark blue there
[Music]
maybe on the other side
on the other side dark blue
on the other side
now the air is going to the laser
so how about
[Music]
i think we're getting we're getting
closer kobo don't worry
i know i know because now the ball can
flow over there just if we make that
last connection so now it's going for
light blue
light blue white
[Music]
the ball
um
i will send you a new ball
okay
and
aya can you stand on the button
stay on the button okay
um
oh did it fall down yeah um yes i get it
and now
[Music]
um
i have to turn on slow mode
slow mode
wait uh can i can i throw the ball
to the
you know i wonder if it goes that part
you can try
i can send you a new ball if it doesn't
work
yeah okay
[Laughter]
sorry
[Music]
okay
and
how do i say wait a second in indonesian
mater
[Music]
i think i have to make
a portal like
can you
open the the door again stand on the
button
yeah
um
there must be a reason why i can reach
that so there should be a portal there
maybe
but why
ah
no
what did
[Music]
how about
uh can you
put the portal here again the dark blue
one
thank you
yes
wait uh-huh
ugh
[Music]
do you have an idea
i'm still thinking
[Music]
oh
man
sorry zero iq here me too
okay
uh put the
point are you putting in here no
can you if you were down there
can you make a dark blue here
wait
i think
mommy mommy yeah
mommy mommy mommy mommy i get it
let's try to
[Music]
oh you know it will flow wait now it
will flow no no what was that was the
wrong the wrong button we wanted to okay
[Music]
and when it comes back you make the blue
portal there you'll make the blue portal
here right okay
um
no
do i have to do something different oh
let's see what happens
so it first goes
through the yellow
portal oh and then i will go back the
other way to the
aha
ah
i
can put
a different portal there
yeah can i put should i put the yellow
one there
but
you still need to
but you still need to go here to make
the portal here
ah
make the portal behind and you can do
that there
ah
well i will test well i think it i think
it will disappear huh
well you're sending the air with the
blue for the yellow ah
but then then it will just come back to
me no
bye bye um but that's so okay oh that's
okay
okay i'll send another one
new ball
oh
ah
okay
maybe maybe
maybe yeah
maybe you can't
oh it went right over there
okay
whoa interesting
oh
this button must be have
a poor pose
yeah
because we have an
inception
[Applause]
it looks like there's two balls now
well yeah i think we broke the game
nice headquarters hacker yeah we hacked
the games
nice and i wonder
if there's one one step is missing
that's probably so obvious um
it's probably so obvious
this this one must be have a purpose
because we haven't used this button yet
i mean i mean we have to send a ball
over there first to get someone to the
side at least
[Music]
but
um
uh-huh
uh-huh uh-huh
i will
uh should
wait so to wait kobo don't do anything
yes okay
don't do anything now it's
now it's floating there
keep it open
yeah
i make orange portal here
[Music]
finally
that was totally me
[Music]
you know i just woke up maybe maybe i
can say that's the problem
i just woke up before the stream your
behavior on the last few tests
you agree okay it's okay that's 75
collaboration points what
blues and she's uh saying it's your
fault
yeah what happened
why is it shaking
why are you taking it
shaking
oh okay well we can already uh
oh
i think we're playing with momentum
cobalt do you remember momentum
momentum yeah
or maybe not i'm not sure i mean there's
probably what the hell
what the hell what the heck
okay well um
i see
ah can you make
first of all
let's make portal there yeah let's make
portals everywhere
there's another one like here
one here yeah but uh probably that has
to be someone else from us uh
um but yeah you can jump down there oh
and then you can
oh yeah
momentum try jumping down there and then
you will fall into the
you you get a massage if you jump down
there you get a beautiful comfortable
massage
okay i love the message yeah let's go
ah oh
how does it feel nice nice back cracking
yes baby not very nice
okay instead we'll do we'll do something
else
maybe with the air here not no
maybe
here
ah
interesting i have an idea if i if you
uh see if i if i would go up here
and then
uh can can you make a light blue portal
here
uh-huh and then and then
uh
when i'm when i fall down before i land
here you'll make a dark mode
make a dark blue lightweight sleep
okay
okay i'm a genius
before i fall okay because i will get
rid of this portal because i make one
here
so when i'm falling yeah you gotta be
fast
okay okay three
two
[Laughter]
but i need to go here immediately when
i'm at the portal there ah
[Music]
yeah i mean we're getting we're getting
closer it's already uh we have momentum
yeah you need to stand on the button so
we'll try again we'll try again
yeah
i'm redeeming myself chat i'm redeeming
myself
okay
so
uh
everything is in place
uh hmm
was that the red yeah that shouldn't be
there oh oh wait oh maybe yeah over
there
wait should i make it here oh there
make it there
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
you know what you just um
uh
it must be while you're while you're on
the button so we have to change the
portals a little bit i think
for example uh you make your light you
make your light blue one no not there uh
can you close that again
okay
make your light blue one here
and your dark blue one already here
maybe
oh
because now you can change it while
you're standing on the button because
those you can reach this one and this
one you can reach
ah okay so but yeah i'll
actually make a portal
now wait no
now i have to think uh
when i fall down oh yeah i make
you you
make the port the blue portal
[Music]
no no no no no no because because we
still need to make a portal here
where was that so you can float you you
won't fall so you won't fall there
okay
but um
[Music]
yellow portal uh below you hmm
yeah yeah yeah
okay
that was teamwork that was teamwork
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay now i can bring the cube
uh if we change the airflow i think or
can i just fall down let me try
i can just fall down
okay all right now i can send the now i
think this the cube needs momentum too
right we need the blue portal again
where it was originally i think oh no no
oh can i not
[Music]
keep just cube here
so it keeps it open for us
but we can go there together
supposedly right yeah
yeah yeah yo yo yeah
[Music]
oh you can't go higher okay
i hope that's enough
uh can i wait
[Laughter]
i'm stuck like a fly a little
fly that's stuck in this stuck in the
spider web
for some reason um i hacked the guy
here
wait wait let me let me i shouldn't be
here though i don't okay
at
[Applause]
[Music]
okay wait how did we do it uh
uh okay let me make four
our
cube is still there nice
okay what did what happened what
happened what went wrong
um okay let me make the portal first and
then you make the portal below okay
orange portal okay okay one
two
three
okay okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
see we're not that stupid yeah
[Music]
that was pretty good way better than the
first one
way faster
nice
cool
nice yes football it's uh i wanted to
congratulate you on one million
subscribers
thank y'all
good job kubo so proud of you
good job good job i want a headpiece how
do you how do you head pet oh wait i
missed the beginning
[Music]
like this
oh oh yeah
okay
are you are you happy and that one
million subscribers good boy
of course i am yeah
yay
good
keep on continuing making the content
that you're already making and
everything will be wonderful
and one million subscribers surely can
play for portal 2 with no problems
because you're smart right 1 million
subscriber is very smart
yeah i believe in that yeah ah let's see
we have more of this where are we even
going
oh
oh bye-bye
oh you're following me i'm following you
okay there's another catapult here
oh
and this thing what was that again
oh what was that again
what is that
i don't know um
[Music]
ah maybe oh no oh normally i guess
okay oh yeah you're just going there
again i guess we need your potatoes
make porto
uh from there i guess you can make the
blue one here when you're back here
i'll follow you
[Music]
this is nice it's like we're swimming
wait did i ask before kobo can you swim
no i can but i can float at least
i can survive at least does that mean
even though i cannot swim
yeah i cannot swim but i can float just
maybe so you're not waiting for some
help
yeah oh that's important yeah yeah at
least something floating to wait for
help in the middle of the ocean yeah
oh
cooper what does this mean
be careful of your of your head
what
um
[Music]
there must be like a laser coming out of
here later no
what is this
yeah i think the laser comes out of
there later so we can send it through
here
[Music]
okay cool
we will
how about we will
you
oh oh now we lost the airflow
oh i thought you were going to die
i'm sorry
oh yeah oh welcome back airflow that's
nice it's so windy so windy
[Music]
there's laser there oh you found the
laser oh there naruto
yeah
i want to see that too lazy
[Music]
we can make portals like here okay
oh yeah that's blue up there
yeah you you see uh can you see my pov
ah no wait i forgot how
[Music]
yeah yeah okay oh
i think we can make something there i
mean
maybe there's a ball or what i don't
know and we try to
get there
oh yeah we need to go oh
oh i something quite a little bit more
on that side damn it
damn it a bit more
yeah now we can reach that place
ah what happened
i fell down
now that i'm here and get rid of my
portal okay
don't run into the laser what does this
button do
i don't know it opened
something
oh the cube there's a cube coming down
from
[Music]
now we bring the cube right here
to where we are
ah
yes
um would you send it um over here over
to us somehow no no no no okay
ah
i can make portal
there yeah yeah yeah
if i send the airflow for you yes that's
that's the way
i think it could could work let's see
how it falls does it blend let's see
oh no
um
we can readjust maybe
yeah just
come on
companion cube reflection cube
okay
[Music]
what do you like to do in the summer
in summer yeah
what are you doing
i don't know
i
i'm just doing as usual
yeah
what about going
out for a vacation or ice cream
i don't know like a hobby in summer
uh
i mean
i'm not not something special i just oh
yeah
oh yeah
i've i i tried something but that's not
what we want to do
uh you remember the one there the yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah we have to send it
huh there was over here was a place
where we can make a portal
so currently we're not using
your blue portals
oh no i want to go here
wait
uh
i want to go there
uh without changing my current portal
wait no we don't ah
before you leave
uh can you make one uh
one blue portal
over there to set the laser
yeah again okay
and
then you can make the light blue one
over here later
[Music]
but i will
how do
did i get over there again uh without
changing
like currently currently we have this
and then we have mommy i think i can't
oh
mommy
ah
yeah we need to make for the yellow
portal here please oh
okay i
will go back for that oh sure
over there
yeah because i cannot go here
okay that was a little bit too far
here
here it is now
okay
oh wait i could go there too oh we can
just we can just go by yeah
yeah easy
how hot is it in in the summer in
indonesia
what how hot is it in indonesia in the
summer
um
i don't know about
around i don't know maybe
above 35
celsius oh my god 45 and it's very humid
right oh we made it
yeah
okay yeah we made it
oh it's an achievement you don't need
that felt good
we just you know we had to warm up in
the first puzzle that's why it wasn't so
good
we can do better
i think in austria it also gets uh like
maybe 30
but maybe 32 degrees maximum or so in
the summer but we don't it's not so
humid it's more dry
so it's not so bad i think in indonesia
it's more humid you know the air is so
humid how well do you really probably
tell me do you trust or humanoid
what if i told you humankind orange
juice
ah
humid is when the air is wet
when the air feels like oh wait wait
cooper did you ever leave indonesia
leave
did you ever go somewhere outside
indonesia
uh maybe outside my city only okay then
you then you only know the the weather
of indonesia right
yeah
okay so you don't understand what's not
humid what's like how is it when there's
uh not humid weather
yeah i'm sorry you only know how it's uh
when it's humid that's that's
interesting oh my god you will be very
surprised if you ever leave indonesia
you will be surprised about you know how
the weather can feel so much the air can
feel so much different
yeah
okay
what is this
river river
[Music]
looks hot though
it looks hot yeah it looks hot ah
does it do we have to try
for example
like this
oh
[Music]
oh yeah go back for the portal and then
oh no um
[Music]
go go
mission of protecting the cube
yeah i'm protecting them i'll let you
i want you to fall
guess so
um
here yeah
oops uh
okay someone ah wait do we have to
send the button through there
because it has the the perfect shape for
the cube
maybe we have to send it there and then
it will stick
yes
oh there we go so smart today
yeah
oh yeah oh catapult oh
[Music]
there we go
big brains
oh nice
they're so funny it's already we're
finished already
i was nice
[Music]
how do i say
has a big brain oh we we have a big
brain
[Music]
how to say it
in indonesia
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
thank you what was thank you again
[Music]
okay pretty cute
i i uh i saw this stream where you
called into ollie's
um call in
olivia olivia excuse me
yeah
you know yeah i think i always want i
want a girl as my child but but maybe
you know maybe it's not so bad with a
boy can you speak in
your boy voice
i want to see how it is you know
it's not it's it's not me it's terrible
temple temple can you bring chapel over
here
[Music]
what do you want to what to say hey
everyone i want just just a little bit
of a talk uh you know
have a conversation see if i can take
care of a boy
hi
[Laughter]
um i'm so happy to have you as my son
uh um what what's your favorite thing
about mommy
[Music]
don't be shy but don't be shy
what's your favorite thing about mommy
about mommy
[Laughter]
um
you know mommy is so kind and yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
really care about me about abaco i mean
about no i care about jebel i don't care
about kobo the hell with that kusogaki
[Laughter]
i only care about table now let's go
check but we're gonna do this together
oh so so you know now you want to play
with me instead of kobo
[Laughter]
why yeah yeah playing with you now okay
go go go table go
make one more portal here maybe
i think i don't know
oh wait that doesn't work that makes no
sense
sorry mommy sorry
that's the first time i ever heard it
like actually makes sense
it's okay
it's okay you know suicide would go
crazy over you right
now i don't know why many people
are pregnant right now oh okay
yeah anyway we'll keep along keep on
floating triple
i'll take care of you i don't know how
where to go from here oh yes chapel
there you go
and the perfect
yeah what do you think about your sister
kobold
oh
i um i don't know i don't know there's
there's
spike
i i don't know
why did it go down then can we stop it
did it go automatically
i don't think so i don't think so
go again go and get in temple
okay
[Laughter]
ah
make make portal again
same point
i'll do anything you want
yeah don't forget that one okay okay
don't die don't die jibble
i'll i'll i'll watch now properly
oh no okay now i understand it just
comes down automatically when you get
closer to it
[Music]
i didn't do it on purpose okay
ah oh oh i think i have no idea wait
yes temple
you have an idea show me show me
oh okay
okay mommy
genius oh my god
ah
ah now you need to let go of that one uh
maybe put it somewhere else like here
oh no i know it's fine i i thought you
could just fall down that's all right oh
there you go temple
yeah go temple go table tell me what's
over there i can see actually oh there's
a button yeah there's one correct
oh it's
oh nice orange
it's reversed shut up gladys
thank you you can't adopt jibble jab
with mine
okay okay now oh there's so there's a
reverse button
what else is there
there's nothing more nothing more i'm
just going to go here okay
uh
[Music]
can you make a
blue portal here okay
okay i know i'll die though will i die i
will die but maybe for now just for now
no no no you want mommy trust me and
then yeah
it's just just no no no you can go now
not yet because you have to stand on the
reverse reverse reverse yeah uh
no you just need to go here right
ah
i think you have to go here and go where
here so we can yeah but you have to
stand on the reverse button
reverse the button the red button
no yes do it do it simple listen to your
mommy ah okay
i'm sorry i'm sorry
there you go ah no sense
okay
good boy good boy okay
that's that's perfect okay
no yes
let me go for it
yes okay
okay and now how about i do this
yeah
i'm coming to you
because now i go for my portal
mommy's back
hi good job
orange do you feel betrayed by me
am i a good boy
[Music]
okay but i want i want my daughter back
uh give me my comment back google my
cooper what give me my kobo black people
back bye bye table bye bye-bye was nice
to meet you
bye-bye mommy
come on
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think i prefer cobra i like cute
cobble
okay it was nice to meet you though
cause like in in the olivia stream i did
not understand the word because it was
only indonesian but this time i
understood everything i'm happy
yeah
okay
okay it's very funny though
yeah table did a whole level and kubu
could take a break meanwhile so now
you're re recharged and really energetic
again right you took a whole break now
what did you do while kobo was gone what
did kobo do when jebu was here
i'm
took a nap i'm
no i'm drinking milk ah
so i can grow oh yes yeah cool become
vega
yeah
okay yeah
okay let's see what do we have here
[Music]
make ah the thing is when we walk
through here
portal gets disappears but
okay
cobalt jump
uh jump okay
let's see where you go oh my god oh
you landed safely i'm surprised
yeah what's over there let me see
there's another
yeah okay
give it a try
um
testing testing
i'm back again
we need to stop you somewhere
i see i see it
i need to stop you somewhere
there's another thing here
when you fly are you able to make a
portal here and here while you're flying
oh wait uh-huh
oh yeah then you can stop yourself i
think oh
oh let's see ah but your portals
disappear when you go through that so i
stop you maybe
uh
i think
what's up there anyway
i guess we can't go there
uh
right now at least i think we do the
same thing again
for now
[Music]
yeah we do the same thing can you repeat
can you just go back i guess you have to
die
or
wait you don't have to die
can you jump into the the airflow
oh that's fine that's fine
[Music]
to
jump to the other side
and then we do the we do the same thing
again with the portals
like this yeah and trust me trust me
kubo
okay okay
and then yeah see now you can go here
but where do we oh
what uh yeah well we'll bring you
somewhere
you're here here here here
so because
there's buttons yeah
[Music]
i guess you have to stay there i think
so it stays open
now yeah stay on the button and now i
think i have to go somewhere
we'll make one here
and we'll try momentum
we have to try momentum
i don't understand what's this for
yeah no because i have to fall through
here i have to catapult myself and then
fall there
[Music]
something like that
ah okay but where do i want to go
uh
i die maybe no
ah
i'll make one here
let's see what happens when i do
this
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
she's trying to get us against each
other but
no no no no
where are we going anyway
i think i think we already make it now i
don't know okay
okay
[Music]
the portal here and the portal there so
you go up there
ah yes
[Music]
and you can make the blue one uh
i guess nowhere i guess we don't need
the blue one right now let's test
testing testings
what's up there what's up here
uh i can oh i can make a portal here
and one i can make a few portals myself
yeah
oh yeah uh i could make one here
[Music]
i brought you some air uh
ah i can make one here too ah come here
maybe with the catapult
i don't think you need the button
anymore
so
i need to go die
yeah
yeah maybe not but okay
wow looking good that was entertaining
that was entertaining thank you gladys
i'm trying my best here
i'm an entertainer
so
let's see i think i did everything in my
power
uh
i could also still make it here whatever
helps you
here or here
oh oh there's there yeah yeah yeah also
um
if you take the
teleport
[Music]
[Applause]
i forgot what was it again big spray
[Music]
yeah let's go
zoom zoom
okay this place looks a bit bigger
oh no what is this
button
[Music]
let me go there
yeah
[Laughter]
reverse come back
okay come back go boy
uh i'll i just oh okay okay
um yeah
yeah
i i fell but i'm okay oh yeah
oh
[Music]
i'm not trying to go here but oh no
oh no
oh oh that's uh your your portals
disappear then
i'll try something else here oh no oh oh
oh
there's i don't know what is this
it could be useful if you're there we'll
figure it out
okay i think i can send you air
i'll send you air over there now you can
send it through here
i don't know why ah for that there you
go
and now we could even reverse it but
what is it for we will never know what
is this for there's a lot of
dangerous stuff there cobalt be careful
yeah i know
where am i oh
i don't understand
[Music]
no i still don't understand what's this
for
what's this one
[Music]
i will i want to check it out i'll go
but i guess we need someone to put push
the reverse button
me me me me okay
uh-uh
uh-oh
oh that looks very dangerous
that hurts where are you right now oh
okay i'm here now um
the problem is oh
i see
huh what do you see there's um
massage
[Music]
it's kind of complicated because there's
wolf beer up there you can see my pov
mommy yes
yeah computer you're here
now you're here and then you go up here
and go here because there's like
yeah there's a wall here and then maybe
go here and then go here
and then go there
yeah
so you're inside a maze right now
yeah that's what it looks like
um
[Music]
it's a big pig
so we have to think hard and do you want
me to be the floating test object this
time then
um
i i see what the difficult part is is
because when you float through
there
uh you have to try to keep on balancing
of the reverse button so that i don't
get hit by the by the spikes
yeah yeah i know yeah yeah
okay okay okay uh we start uh
i guess
like
i think i need the dark blue one here
first
i think
yeah mm-hmm okay so i go there again
but i don't
see oh oh no it's okay yeah okay we're
right here
yeah
[Applause]
i think maybe it was the other portal
wow maybe it was the other portal uh
okay we go up up up up up up
that was very brutal how about this one
[Music]
no you can
okay uh down yeah yeah
oh god and yeah yeah there's one you
know okay nice nice mommy no damn no one
yeah okay okay okay
it's about timing then okay uh there is
a certain
rhythm okay
i see then you have to control that so
mommy doesn't die
[\h__\h] mommy okay
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah why is it so shaky on my
side hmm
[Music]
okay reverse
i think i forgot to make a portal
somewhere where is it here okay
okay
yes wait wait wait wait wait okay
good timing i think
okay okay
[Music]
oh no oh no oh no okay let's go let's go
where where where oh
where's on the wall
[Music]
huh am i blind i don't see another
wall for me to make the do i have to
jump
um
[Laughter]
it didn't look like the right thing to
me okay
oh
oh okay where am i going now oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh
oh oh is that really where i want to go
oh no i'm scared oh no uh
i'm not sure where we are right now it
kind of lost track of where we are
oh
oh there's a [\h__\h] falls down here
there's someone
[Music]
right there i will i will go there and
uh i will destroy them i can take a oh
wait never mind oh yeah there there's
right there okay okay
uh
what happened i think you can break
this
where's the cube
now the cube's here
oh nicely
ah
you can pick it up somewhere there okay
oh the turret
wait wait um
yeah can you maybe
pick it up from over here from that
point
okay okay um
i'm not sure
or you send it through here
where should i send the box
uh if you make the dark blue wait let it
go back yeah and make the dark blue
portal here i'm not sure how it will
fall we can test it
ah
oh yeah
oh now you can let it go
uh a little bit higher yeah
and then you make the red the dark blue
portal somewhere else so it falls down
or the the light blue port uh whatever
just change the portal so it falls down
yeah just to let go of the airflow
yeah
beautiful cobalt
[Music]
and now i guess
you come to me but the thing is it's not
always it shouldn't always be reversed
right
yeah so either way
i
i think i can help somehow by bringing
you here whoa whoa
wait where is the exit
where is the exit the exit is here oh
but how how can we get there oh there's
a mommy kiwawa
there's a
there's a a square button there so i
think the box is need to be
wow okay i didn't see that one yet
but how okay okay oh maybe i can
i can probably uh
take ah no i have to bring the cube all
the way back
mommy mommy oh
[Music]
i let it fall oh
probably i should do something with that
[Music]
oh there's another one here
oh
okay let me try it okay yeah let me try
because you see there's uh you know here
can i
can i jump
with the box um
yeah
let's see
oh yeah
momento
okay okay mommy mommy i will pick you up
what if i just die
isn't it easier if i just died
there's a portal there right can you
make plural here
ah oh yeah
uh there uh yeah i think maybe oh yes
yes yes
ah
oh yeah okay okay
you know and then burgers reverse
yeah
this stupid turret is in the way
go away yeah go away
we don't need to we don't want you
where am i
so confusing
no no i'm going back again yeah where am
i no no no uh um
oh no
[Music]
yeah and then you can go here
and i'll go up ah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
uh just uh
like fall down
yeah we fall down let's go
let's go
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
because my viewers say
when you die i am go prep because i am
miss chicken and gopro means like
smashed because in indonesia there's uh
like a food
called i am go prague
it's uh
just a spicy chicken but the chicken
must be
smashed like
yeah it's just a prank so when you die
my viewers say that you're like i am
good prayer
[Music]
i see it
well
welcomable
now we change the wells and you you go
die because there's a lot of laser
turrets have fun with them go cobble go
walk stream kobo walk
[Laughter]
i am a break my viewers are
saying
it's not my fault what are you doing
with style
okay i'll let this one slide but oh look
at this mommy's smart we're protected
now
they can't get us now
unless
oh
yes
when
you know huh we want some air here here
mommy here
[Applause]
oh oh oh can we jump into it
oh no oh no so many obstacles here
please don't move that where are we
please um
uh we can go here
whoa whoa oh [\h__\h] uh
i can make a wall there we just have to
do the same thing again
oh you're right
okay
you have it
this this may need some trial and error
[Music]
okay so kobo is in charge of air i'm in
charge of the of the shield okay
okay sorry no problem
scary scary factor kobe have you you
haven't uh played portal alone yet right
yeah i have one you should
well i can already make it oh
you should because it's a lot of fun
now i think you have to make us fall
down down there wait i forgot which
portal ah
uh okay
that was the right one
who can't catch us no no
um
oh yes okay yeah wait wait wait
oh oh oh we landed we landed
but where where are there's
this okay nice mommy mommy
oh i thought we already slept not quite
not quite
deploying huh oh
[Music]
okay i take the shield again
up there we're protected now you take
the air again
let's go
[Music]
it will tickle a little bit are you
ticklish go ball
oh oh okay please where where oh no
no no no no no no
no no
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah sad
it's okay we can do it again
on it
yeah okay i have it all under control
i have a dog control
wow
um
yeah you need to
start the barrier
yeah okay i have it i haven't
thank you forever
let's go thank you forever
that's how i better your barrier where
where wow
[Music]
you have less hp than me
i don't know but i died too on
i know
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh we can jump over here huh
we can jump into this airflow is that
what they want us to do it seems so
high what's
[Music]
what
what was that
i'll get easy i can i can come to you um
probably can i okay but where should we
go
from there yeah good question oopsie
um
where's the exit
uh oh
i make my portal and i make it here
i have to
open our eyes
very wide
oh my god oh hi cool book
[Music]
did you try playing hoodoo cure
i have one because it's just not my type
of game to be shrimp related [\h__\h]
what yeah it's a lot of fun
i know but not i'm in you can play with
mommy
you mean the character yeah there's a
there's uh
me you can play me
and you can play gudera and you can play
everybody
uh-uh
i know i know but it's just not my okay
not my type of game to be streamed
that's understandable
[\h__\h] all right yeah but but i would
like to play it but not on the stream
yeah it's just something
um a little problem oh wait you see what
is over there
oh yeah
that's maybe where we need to go
oh
[Music]
how do i say i love you in indonesian
again i forgot
[Music]
[Laughter]
and we can uh support each other mm-hmm
yeah oh do we have to go down here
i think so
oh no maybe uh no that's where we came
from
that door doesn't open um do we have to
make something here
yes oh yeah ah the airflow can you make
it here
oh you're right over there there's a
little
and keep on swimming swimming keep on
swimming
[Music]
oh my god
oh my god oh
i see oh we just go again to the other
side
now i take the air and you but what no i
should have should have kept it where is
them barrier
i couldn't have taken it from the
previous one because uh it deletes it i
think
if you walk through this it deletes it
so
[Music]
there
must be
a while somewhere
where's the wall
dangerous
[Music]
okay
then you'll be the one i'll be the air
this time we switch from
protecting me squeezing
nice good job they can't see us they're
they can see yeah
we go
oh maybe we have to
do i have to make it here
but this is where where we start really
before yeah see see see this robot right
here
from where from down there
what
what's can i make it there no no no
[Music]
yeah you can kill them
oh that's way they don't come over here
but i don't know if that's
um maybe we i only see this one
um
it will take me in the other way
so
we will try kobo
trust me
[Laughter]
we can
oh
but iron we go oh no there's
oh i think it's different now even if we
fall down we're starting somewhere else
because we have a checkpoint
uh yeah yeah yeah uh let's let's just
let go of that
just listen
i don't want to die we will not die
don't worry don't worry oh my god oh my
god what's happening oh you can't hear
mommy yeah yeah yeah mommy
save
on it's a
insert disc they have a do you have a
disk
this here here and good job
yeah
have you ever touched a cd before
of course really because you're so young
i feel like and nowadays pcs don't even
have cd cases
see the uh
cd slots and everything is bought
digitally
so i thought maybe maybe you haven't
touched it
have you ever touched cassette tapes
though cassette tapes nothing bad
happens
let us see little [\h__\h]
little [\h__\h]
that's good job kobo
if i ever have a child the first words
it will learn will be your little [\h__\h]
because i will say it to the baby
[Music]
standard
number four is done
i have a surprise
for this course that ends with us
and free
human we will free the humans
thanks to you i know where to find them
i removed security and powered up there
oh rescue door
mommy mommy something
[Music]
let's go gels we get gels now
tails gels yeah
well i don't know what else but and
that's another another
fun thing how do we get there though we
have to jump somehow there's a
cutter
there
fall down
how do we get there i guess we can try
to
finish five if it's as long as four then
we i think we can finish mommy mommy
yeah or maybe not because now it took us
one hour 40 minutes
how did you get there
there i made i made a portal today okay
sorry i'm clear mommy brain already very
dead okay
[Music]
then let's start chapter five
we might need the
chat's help so we can finish under three
hours please help
[Music]
what's your favorite flavor of milk or
do you just like the normal plain milk
[Music]
you know it
yeah really i've never heard of
something like that before
oh
i i think i prefer chocolate milk
because strawberry milk often tastes so
artificial
yeah okay what is this looks so old it's
so old here oh yeah right because uh
lore
portal lore
uh
so the snare
first of all i walk to the button and
then we press the button
look behind you
behind me what
what is this it's the channel if i stand
here
jump
that's
what the gel's
four yeah
there's different gels this one makes
you boing boing and then there's another
one that makes it really fast
ah you can ah
wait i i stand on there and then you can
jump because otherwise it's too slow
there we go
now you go up there and you press the
other button
which will bring us yeah more blue let's
[Music]
is it the same button
is it i guess not i don't know i use the
same button
wait
okay
oh yeah so far so maybe you can make
make wool there
oh there's oh oh wait it's simple uh
walk through the orange portal
yeah
[Music]
you really are the best this was just a
tutorial though just a simple
introduction there's more gels there's i
think there was three three different
gels i think
oh yeah one what was a white gel when
the white gel you can make portals
everywhere where the gel
is about the humans
[Music]
humans and hide their tracks but for now
i wanted to punish them we only work
with this one oh
look at this call but we can send the
gel through the portal they treat their
friends
oh you're right oh yes we can but i made
it i did it wrong now it will fall for
woo
now you can bounce yeah
where are we bouncing
too oh you can yeah
yeah
smart smart smart smart
what do we have over there i look on
cobalt pov
yeah oh there's a bus
oh and the button and you know what's
over there
see oh
is it safe for me to go to you
i don't know there's mommy i'm coming
oh
i hope we don't need the jalen i think
we need to jail cell but is there
another generator no
there's more space here
oh
uh huh
[Music]
um we
probably have to send the gel
uh
somewhere to us because there's there
only seems to be one generator but
maybe we can bring the gel
there's ah this one this one is sauce
[Music]
if i can reach that from here
interesting
no wait i already made that yeah but i
can reach it from here
that means
what can i reach from there
[Music]
no you can't
yeah i will make it go away but
um
[Music]
where does it go
uh nowhere
i'm sure it went somewhere
where does it go no no
it doesn't go anywhere
nani
um
yeah
you can see on my pot
yeah i'm watching oh it ah that went
somewhere can you scroll in
that made a whole wall blue no but so we
can bounce off of that
but we can bounce off the wall
if we fall through
uh a hole get some momentum
maybe i don't know
maybe maybe
maybe just maybe
[Music]
i'll come back to you
oh
ah yes wait keep that keep that this way
we can catch the with the wind we can
catch the the blue
oh you're right
okay
now i throw the blue stuff over there
and it will go into the wind
wow
now what do we do with that ah now let
it drop let it drop let it drop
when it's when it's in the air i'll send
it again and you make the portal
somewhere else once it's in the wind
yeah now let it fall
we can drop it
on the platform yeah
so we can bounce there and we do the
same thing i guess somewhere else yeah
okay i'll sand it again
okay
drop it like it's hot
there we go okay
okay maybe we can also make it drop
where it is right now somehow oh
ah
can we make it
ah can you put the portal again where it
was before
i
and then
i wonder if we can make it
somehow
if we can bring it over here
by
letting it fall through the portal but i
can only make mine over here
i don't think we can
believe club
we need we need the color here too so we
go from blue
[Music]
what happens if we
mommy i can i can i can okay let's try
let's try let's try it oh my god
let's try let's try yeah i was thinking
if the if the color can bounce off
itself probably not maybe not
maybe not
[Music]
i just pointed at it okay
okay
it's there
eh wait mom
[Music]
my portal is gone
sorry guys who are asking for super chat
i turned it off because i need to catch
up i have many super chats to read sorry
sorry
indonesia has super chats now nice one
yeah
sorry
do wear a shirt and shoes no time move
quickly for your test track do not not
forget to not touch the glass
wait for more
minutes touch the glass
leave your belongings here
do not touch the glass
what's glass
ah anyway that's just a little bit of a
piece of lure touch grass yeah
ah
we're so close we're so close we already
got the color on one of the
bouncy platforms so we just need to go
here
well definitely need one here
i
can't bring it there
i go i'll go over to see what we can do
um
[Music]
no
hold on
momentum
momentum momentum
what happened if i jump down there ah
where am i going i am you going
wait
nowhere
i think i no i should
die
now you are just wasting my time
hmm
[Music]
if you have
this
oh
[Music]
yes
yes helpful
[Music]
what happened if i jump here can i jump
there
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah too far i can't jump okay and we
try again
with the what you do sanding the gel you
you go
make the portal in the same spot as
before
and we'll try
to send it through again
use our thinking caps again yeah big
brain
[Music]
my standard
and then
it's the the the airflow currently is
going up right
uh
ah
i thought okay oh mommy mommy try try
trying to send the gel uh-huh
okay let's see we let it fall
yes
yeah
i was wondering if that worked already
yeah yeah okay now we can i think jump
oh my god
uh
um oh no yes let it go and i make a
bigger jump because of momentum ah but
not really
oh so close
[Music]
yeah the platform opens too because
you're standing on the button nice nice
[Music]
okay company you want to try
i want to try okay
[Music]
let's go
i think i
think
we can make portal here so
let's see here mommy oh oh
i can make portal here but i don't know
the air will catch me okay
okay
[Music]
nice
yes we use our our brain power together
[Music]
yes deadly test
i don't mind deadly tests
how do they know for sure
my
partner in science not partner in crime
so this nick
yeah
maybe we get a new gel now you're going
to need to use all the tricks you've
learned
there's a
bridge made these tests extremely
different
i would say extremely deadly but we all
know for you and your amazing ability to
be reassembled
okay i can make the portal here yeah
[Music]
oh there's a button i didn't even see
that one
yes beautiful blue copper blue
blue
purple blue yes
we can send it somewhere maybe
can can we make the bridge the gel to
the bridge
maybe yeah
we can test it
but we need to readjust them yeah
yeah okay
can you make the portal maybe here uh
where
here
oh no
[Laughter]
he does not make this science that's
okay
we need a blue one here
blue
wait
yeah and then one like there so we can
walk over
[Music]
i don't remember ever doing that in my
solo run before i don't think that's
ever happened before
putting the color on the port on the
bridge is new to me
fascinating
wow
we learned so much today yeah
that is new yeah
okay
we
have this
oh oh confusing
and where
[Music]
okay
but i think my bridge disappears when i
walk through this invisible wall
you're right
i
go
back
[Music]
ah can you make another blue portal
there
one here and one where the
word
so we can have some uh
blue stuff on here so i can jump to you
okay you know where
the
first but where's the gel oh
okay okay guys yeah i see yeah okay okay
let's go i have to push the button oh
yeah oh
oh
okay
push button
and
now when you look at that um
[Music]
keep on pushing the wrong one where how
to awkward
[Music]
nice
lucky for you too i can't control the
world outside of the testing courses
[Music]
you know gladys talks a lot of
complicated [\h__\h] all the time
complicated [\h__\h]
don't don't repeat my swear words people
will be angry that i'm teaching you
swear words in english you feel bad
earlier yeah [\h__\h]
i guess i guess you already used that
word all the time
no no
congratulations i mean not in english
oh oh my god oh
i already made everything blue over here
[Music]
you can also make stuff blue here
probably
sorry kobo where are you now there you
are
i don't know
ah wrong porto
first of all make everything cobble
colored yes
oh no
everything everything must be cobble
colored
yeah
and we make everything into a bouncy
house
yeah you like bouncy houses
i like bouncy bouncy i like trampoline
oh i said amma has a trampoline in her
room i tried it i haven't been on a
trampoline besides the trampoline yeah
i'm a senpai she did a 3d
uh trampoline stream before
oh
there we go
i have let's see
wow wow where else where else where else
might be here
well that mommy like fun
[Music]
i want to do that too
it's fun wait how did you get up there
yeah momentum from here and then
i from there
jumped up from the
oh with the gel
oh she got the momentum
no
i not quite
something was wrong there
come with the gel first i'll come down
with the gel to the portal
oh
i think i did that
oh why don't you do it wait
let me let me i i
[Music]
oh wait the portal must have been
somewhere else but like uh when you did
that ah ah i think there yeah
that's where it was aha
[Music]
i was just throwing stuff around i
didn't realize
now there's so much blue stuff
everywhere why did i do that
good
[Music]
i can't
can't we can't recreate what we already
did
unfortunately
what
just try a few times you should get
there sometime
[Music]
okay i'll try my best
sometimes you just have to brush it yes
already everything is already set in
place correctly you just have to
yeah
yeah oh yeah
[Music]
i believe in you kabul
ah
how did i do it i don't even remember
how i did it
angle too straight um
my angle is too straight
you're right but how
but that's wow
[Music]
maybe
can i make the portals differently
oh
you can see a higher jumping point i can
see a higher jumping point ah
i can see a higher
i know i can do a lot of
different stuff here but
it already worked before
i can't
to my right there's nothing on my right
ah yes
[Music]
i wanted to catch you
i'm sorry
no
can i do it again i move to the side
[Music]
that's okay how did you do it
i know why that was so difficult
oh oh okay
not anywhere
we have once again a bridge okay
[Music]
a button
ah
bring
the bridge there yeah
uh uh higher i guess can i make it any
no
no but maybe i can go there when i want
yeah you can go and it doesn't disappear
go check it out
what's up there oh
i see
i cannot go in
is there
anything else around you ah there we go
we can
make the color drop there
uh no maybe just one
yeah and the one there okay
now we will
send the color oh
this is a super mario side jumping again
the wall jumping now send it to the
other one
yeah
coming
yeah there we go
okay okay i see i see i see let me let
me try to hang oh wow
[Music]
have you played super mario games before
nope
also not your kind of game
no it's just it's really fun though
i want to but i just have completed oh
wait i see some stuff here oh
yeah
there's
what
there's some more
oh
yeah
can i
do the wrong jump here and here
i can send more gel
here maybe
here yeah um
oh yeah you can make a portal there too
that's good uh
yeah yeah we'll send it for the the
first one that you did
but where where do i need to send it uh
uh uh
here for this one
maybe maybe
okay
let's try
that's right
ah
angled over here
i can
ah
okay
i think we try again the same thing
uh-huh then it lands on the bridge
and then
we
ah oh do i want it
maybe i'll send it again
i think it will bounce off
no it won't okay so
i can make portal here
and maybe um let me see though what this
is
ah i see i see
oh what this is not the intended way of
doing it i think i
i'm stuck
you're stuck i'm stuck
do you want that in your memory banks
[Music]
it's close
close close close
like i can do the wall here i can do the
wall
ah wrong
i can do the wall here
and here
[Music]
if we
send the blue color there and i just get
stuck
can we send it
can we send the blue color through
yeah here
right and we get the blue color on this
bridge yeah i'll press the button
i'll go
uh-huh so now i can bounce off and
theory from that and i want the rest of
the color to go here
for that we
ah can you make one here yeah it should
fall through if i get rid of my
bridge right
yeah yeah i'll put it uh
and some somewhere maybe you can pull it
here
oh okay no it's okay now i think oops oh
[\h__\h] okay
go
oh wait but ah no we have to do this one
first and then the bridge because now
the bridge has no more color on it
ah
okay
so close
one more time uh over here please
okay i got it
[Music]
okay all right
okay i'm not good at wall jumping why is
there an empty spot here oh no okay well
i'll try
ah but wait let's let's bring some more
color and let's throw some more color
i'm scared maybe that will fill it up go
go go go more color
yeah okay that's better
there was a little spot with no color
okay ah and jump
wow
[Music]
only on the bridge we only have to do
the color on the bridge again
should i don't move
i just i went a little sideways yeah but
i think it should work if i try again
oh beautiful perfect
maybe i wonder if it matters which side
i jump to first i'll jump here though
no moving no moving no moving yeah yeah
yeah yeah
mommy it's so much
super mario games oh man
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
going pretty well so far gladys is
impressed too
what are you gonna eat for dinner today
ah
[Music]
what's for dinner no no you don't know i
mean i uh i ate dinner already but i'm
[Music]
what did you eat for dinner during these
days indonesian food it's a lifetime
indonesian food called
samoa
what is that
some water is uh
chicken
i don't know
but it's a
chicken dish but i don't know to explain
uh yeah how do i write it i want to
google it
[Music]
oh it looks like um looks yummy
yeah
[Music]
yum yum yum
okay yeah my father
cookie oh nice give me something i want
some some symbol please
i want to eat some more
send me something
the way you the way you stay somewhere
is cute
[Music]
we have a new gel
orange
orange still it's the speedy one
it makes you fast
oh yeah you're right which means we want
it on this platform so that we can zoom
you know ice cream okay
easy
look oh beautiful
wow
it's already open you can walk through
behind you
bye-bye
bye-bye what's over there
um
yeah
i don't know it's a long long way oh
there's a cube dropping down
yeah there's a cube right
yeah you have to catch the cube
while you what uh
we put it here already mommy only if one
stands on it oh
we put the cube on it
actually i want to catch it
where are you koopa okay okay
so i i'll i'll push the button yeah you
push button
and i i'm gonna catch it i'm gonna do a
gamer move
hell yeah yeah okay give him a move okay
let's go
you test it once so you see when it
falls
yeah
there you go see that i will try to
catch that but we have to time it um
i'll pound
okay
three one one
three
[Laughter]
okay three
two
one
after early oh my
[Music]
you shortcut mommy
i'm here
oh short card
now you made your path longer though
because you went back up
yeah you're right nice mommy
oh
that's it that's it
no not yet of course not
wow
we're gonna be stomped on again
by the spiky machines on
oh no
ah it's okay because we'll just zoom
through with the orange color yeah
um
the color
which will
go through mmm
it's really complicated they're even
numbered why are they numbered yeah
there's true one it's two three two
one two
all right i'll try uh to put some color
here first
or on it oh no
here
well first we'll just put colors
everywhere that's the way to go
oh yes yes yeah yeah
we need to go up there
and there yes yes yes yes yes
now we put some color
here
over there
oh
yeah nice nice colored all orange
what's kobo's favorite color is it blue
of course it's
blue yeah
my favorite color is orange what a
surprise what a coincidence
yeah it's a coincidence maybe we should
also put it in these rooms
i don't know should we
should we
i'll just do it i don't know
ah oops
[Music]
i keep on pushing the wrong button put
some more
put some here
[Music]
and now put some here
combo you can already think how we're
gonna do this
yeah i'm thinking
we need to i think that's good
it's good momentum so
so
we can go there
yeah yeah i think we already uh
should already be no problem i'm just
gonna
color this one okay
and this one
and okay i colored everything everything
that's possible
now
we go back down up
somehow yeah yeah yeah
ah
how can we get the momentum
[Music]
hi
you're too small to reach out should i
should i give you my hand so you can
come here
no
accuracy
yeah i think
these walls maybe we have to
[Music]
uh go
from well one wall to another really
fast
copper what
can you make one blue one here
oh no wait
yeah maybe uh can you make try making a
blue one
over there
yes oh you made it on the other side
yeah
yeah oh i'm here
oh
yeah
okay
huh
how about this oh that gets pretty fast
nice
see what i'm doing um
see how fast i can get
um i need another portal probably here
yeah
but which one which one you uh on it
maybe light blue can you put light blue
here
um no no no no no no no
maybe
wait i'll just make a loop okay
[Music]
um
come here mommy
okay
okay you make the purple here like
before
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah and then uh
like this maybe
we can
go there again uh-huh
um
so
uh-huh there
and then i'll make uh
yeah
no
[Music]
yeah i think what wasn't there a space
for a portal there
yeah yes one has to be there what color
did you not use i think light blue
but we need uh-huh so we need more
liquid ah
do we need more orange stuff
so i try to run now mommy okay
oh
okay almost that needs a little bit more
momentum a little bit
just a tiny bit
[Music]
ah
how do i get back there
i'll make a portal for you okay
[Music]
yeah we bought with a loop so i go
i guess i need a light blue
here
i guess okay
you changed the portal
the
okay that was not it oh no okay
[Music]
know this must be kind of difficult oh
okay okay so i'm making it sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh there was something it was it
happened too fast i already forgot
i think it was the red the red way we
did it the right way we just gotta whoa
okay let's go let's go
[Music]
oh and the timing that was the time and
that's okay
all right wait uh oh wait
um
what if actually
what if i just use my do i need uh a
couple can you make a light blue one
where the yellow one is yeah
ah
i guess
because then chad says we can do it with
one room
beautiful
infinity loop
wait oh what color do i need
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh let's make it here i guess
mango
thank you
okay
timing just a matter of timing
ow bunk okay just go straight straight
out
[Music]
what does this button do i have a button
up there
what's up there a button okay
i'm not sure what it does ah
ah we need to both stand on the button
and then this check mark opens the door
well
uh
i might we might be able to
[Music]
do this while i'm here yeah yeah cause i
can also make portals here
oh you're right okay
uh
i'll try to help you can you go for the
blue one again
and then okay okay you go for my portals
this time
run you can you can shoot there right
yeah oh yeah right okay yeah yeah
oh no oh now we need i'm gonna have to
figure out the timing and go
no okay
[Music]
just trial and error
okay let's go again try it again
[Music]
okay
wow
[Music]
this game makes me feel so smart so
pinterest
yes me too
doesn't motivate me
i wonder how much more chat do you know
how much more
because coco
sleep you know
nah
that's okay
do you dream at night or or do you never
dream of humans
they are sometimes i dream sometimes not
and you know sometimes i got lucid
dreams oh what i never had that before
you
yeah
i'm jealous i want to learn that too
wait what did that one do yeah
ah cute okay this box and then creates a
cube over there over here oh
uh
huh
oh dear okay it's really big again
what if i
send
oh stand here mommy oh yeah
oh look where i am now hmm
oh there's a laser too okay we have a
lot of elements oh there's turrets oh no
oh they're not looking at me
me too
do you see these portals
ah
did you see that one here
maybe can you make the
the orange gel come through that one i
wonder how far it goes probably not far
enough
or let's see
[Music]
okay i understand
oh you didn't go far enough oh
nice
can you send one more
oh
[Music]
well we already have like this highway
highway to hell basically because uh
yeah we died there
there was another platform there that is
uh
interesting
no don't go so fast stop stop stop stop
ah let's
let's send it
uh you can't see that one oh
huh
wait a minute can you can you reach that
one
i can reach the
mom mommy
i can't i have to no
oh where did you get the cube from
uh we can make portal there where the
cube oh i didn't realize okay that's
good we probably have to use put it
somewhere where the laser is uh but
there's no platform there so
not sure
how ah we need a bridge was there a
bridge somewhere
but there's no bridge
no branch
[Music]
it
i will learn it until
saturday on saturday i have a karaoke
stream
and i'll sing i'll sing song
yeah yay
[Music]
i love the song the first time i heard
it i was already in love hmm
but i have to learn how to pronounce
how how to pronounce indonesian
it's my pronunciation okay
i think i mean it's not yeah don't think
about the pronunciation you'll be good
you'll be good okay
[Music]
square a cube
yeah
yeah but it will just uh
yeah it won't stay where we want it to
be
but i do wonder is there like a
a portal while here or is it a normal
wall
no no no
no
[Music]
yeah
okay
let's start uh by sending
uh maybe we can before the cube can we
send some color through here
yeah just see where it goes maybe it
will push the target the turrets
over
oh
so hi here
i want the cube is here now
yeah
oh yeah oh
no oh [\h__\h] oh my god it's so scary it's
so fast
can you make a portal again here and
then we um oh yeah and then send the
color through there
oh i see okay
oh my god so fast oh you know when we
take the cube further i think it will
disappear
yeah if we take it for the wall
yeah keep the cube safe
okay
come on
[Music]
it's hard to see where did that
ah
it was
maybe
oh
maybe that's useless but
i don't know
can you make uh
the yeah blue one there
okay okay i'll go uh but can you send
this one a bit more in the middle
is that possible
okay
it's kind of on the left side maybe it's
better in the middle okay
and now i try
where do we go
okay
wow oh no they're gonna kill me oh no oh
no okay i see that is um
now we can go over to that side though
so that's good um i think we can send
the
cube
somehow
without
maybe
because i wonder if the cue blends um
if the cube lands over there
maybe it will reflect everything and
kill the top the turrets on yes yes yes
yes
maybe maybe like this
uh oh no oh no oh
i see
um or like this
[Music]
that's probably not it um
wow when it's
when
okay my my brain is not usable anymore
yeah same
then it just flies through huh
then it just goes through here and then
on it
hmm
we're getting there i don't know are we
getting there
um
oh
there he goes again we're killing so
many cubes on you it's okay it's only a
cubes
[Music]
it's almost three hours i think this
will be our last last room
let's just finish this chapter yeah okay
okay okay
yeah yeah
but i don't know you won't know don't
you even take out tourists yeah yeah
yeah that's what i want to do
but we can't go far enough
i will i will go to the
platform again
when i jump over there
oh i can stand here
what
[Music]
you die i think yeah okay i'll make i'll
make a
a portal
um
what
oh wait that was the wrong one
are you still there okay
yeah you want makeup
oh no
die again
oh put a cube on air kiana jump
but i think you cannot catch the cube
right oh damn it i think i need a
different color
ah
from portal to portal on the ground to
hit the laser that hits the turrets you
portal the portal to hit the laser that
hits the turrets
portal to portal which portal this one
[Music]
this one
on this one
[Music]
i can't
mommy i can't listen
i can send the cube from oh
no
okay
you want me to catch it there okay okay
[Music]
all right let's do that
i think it's hard i don't know all right
like let's see let's see the where's the
cube
okay right there here there goes the
but when you're when but when you
already kept the cube so
when i got the cube you have to
change after after you sense the cube i
think you have to put one portal
the dark blue portal here
after i get the cube
is that
manageable is that too just too fast
let's try i guess uh it sounds difficult
let's try
or yeah because it's it's about a
lighting light bulb light blue light
blue dark blue light nothing dark blue
because i want to then rip the cube i
want to jump
through this one
and land where the turrets are
maybe
let's try i'm coming
again
oh okay i think the cube came a little
bit too late
it's okay
yeah
you don't need to die though if at first
you don't succeed
i know five more times
maybe it will refresh my brain if i die
oh okay then but don't i need my own
portal somewhere um
it feels wrong if i'm not using my own
problem i confused that
can you all bring the people jumping no
she can't
okay
we'll try
again
oh oh [\h__\h] okay okay
and
three
two
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry okay
[Music]
one
okay
[Music]
i go on one no you send it on one and i
go on zero okay
you when i say one you click the button
okay okay
three two one
if i land there with the cube then it
will be uh perfect
so
uh
on one you send the cube
should i go even later i think
three two one
[Music]
don't worry phoenix can die many times
it won't work
yeah resurrect revive right from the
ashes
okay oh yeah read five on nice revive
yeah
uh i'll just go faster i guess maybe it
is about the same timing three two one
[Music]
isn't that what we're trying to do
hmm
huh
when you got the cube i'll send you
to the exit
ah okay wait can you send the cube right
now
right now where uh just where it is like
the same way the same way as before uh
[\h__\h] that but um i want to see when you
push the button
push it now one and then
push it again
one two three one
two
three
okay
okay try
uh oh man that's difficult
uh
maybe on zero
counting till zero uh
i i count
uh
i count um
i count one two
three
and on three yeah
you push the button and then
and then
i wait
i don't know send it again
okay just try to try let's go trial and
error
one
[Music]
um
on the wall one of the wall before
what i don't understand it sounds so
complicated when you guys write it down
wait i wanna see my chat i wanna see my
chat now one of them
when the mirror is in mid-air put the
first bottle to the other wall below
oh actually
on the one just a little down beside the
laser and the second one
on the bottom
[Music]
no it's fine this is cute when you speak
indonesian
yeah
i'm sorry yeah i'm sure it's easier to
understand for you in indonesian so
don't worry about this
no no it's hard not to
see here
if i if i
if i bring the cube here yeah
yeah
[Music]
and like like this
nah it will disappear in the
wow
yeah it did it will disappear see it
will disappear
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
can you send
the cube uh from
from here
up to
just just uh just through here so it
comes right here and then i can catch it
when it comes right after me maybe let's
see
yeah yeah
oh i mean
i will jump i will catch it mid-air
that's way easier to catch
and then i will still fly through there
and you just have to make a light blue
portal here
[Music]
okay let's see one two three
uh okay i need to change the portal oh
speaking kind of hard but okay
[Music]
um wait um tell me when you're mentally
ready
i think i can help too
can i try maybe i have to make a uh
orange portal here when i'm flying and
then i fall for that that's okay that's
okay i i already got it i got it i just
need to okay okay
okay let's try one
two
oh yeah three
okay i guess it deletes it that's right
yeah yeah okay i got it
and yes
now um
what uh
[Music]
i mean the cube is there now
okay
now
i thought i thought we could easily just
block all the lasers and then destroy
them
uh
two platforms beneath the lasers
huh
there are two portals below the laser
yeah this this this platform must have
some
poor do i have to fall through there
and
okay let's try it that way
instead of falling through here i fall
through the bottom one
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's what i was
gonna say okay let's go let's go one
okay two
three yeah
got it
yeah okay oh
okay one is burnt i just go ah i have to
go again i think we have to create a
loop or
oh i just okay okay
i'm sorry uh oopsie
mommy okay let's go here let's go
okay
[Music]
ah sorry i went too early
one
[Music]
ah i could have done all of them ah
never mind
[Music]
yeah just right now okay
no cube
oh they're all gone oh
they're on
oh no you have to come here
you make you'll make the portal now okay
okay where did you put the other one
though one here one here
no one one
one
here one
here right yeah okay okay okay nice
waiting for you
okay
i'm coming mommy
oh is it gonna work call me
[Music]
oh my god
sorry guys it took so long
but the other ones we did pretty well so
forgive us
[Music]
are you sure you're able to finish the
this chapter i'm probably i'm sure it's
not so much left
probably
let's finish the chapter okay
we have more
orange stuff
okay
uh
exit is there there's a little space for
a cube so there must be a cube somewhere
ayah from here
get the cube
oh
but it won't
catch it
i see it
we have to run
over there to the cube
and catch it in the air
okay
[Music]
yeah uh if you stand on the on the
uh thing that makes the platforms go up
the the button or push the button
is it time limited
yeah it's time to limit that
oh one two three four five six seven
seven seven you know
ah okay
i thought it
goes through of course because there's
holes
i was thinking that was gonna happen
okay i'll set the color in other places
for now because that seems a good thing
to do
we send it here
let's send it here
[Music]
i don't think it stays on the
wow yeah it goes through because there's
holes yeah
what's there
is that where we came from yeah
okay
um
[Music]
yeah oh but then i think i have to put
some more orange color there
yep and on both sides i think we shall
uh yeah yeah that looks good that looks
good good enough i think
i know oh yeah you want to try
running around and running
oh yeah
okay
running where do i send you oh yeah from
yeah
ah okay well you can land on there if i
press the button first
yep and then it stays for a while
let me see is it this button
yep okay
how long one two
three
it's pretty long okay
first you start little things
just keep on looping keep on moving ah
that's why that's why i was able to put
the orange color here too so i can be
faster to reach the button okay
and
go
maybe do i need more color
mommy
not quite
why why why why why why
why it can be reached or
i think so
or
who would they want us to
[Music]
i need more color all right
we'll need more color in here
oh probably
oh but there yeah yeah ah yeah that's
better now cause there was some color
missing here i couldn't go fast enough
oh
okay okay
now creating endless kobo loop once
again
[Music]
and here it comes here he comes here
comes
yes
[Music]
oh thank you
i don't know
you gave it to
[Music]
oh did you see my tweet when i tweeted
at you that um can i tweet it at you
that
means
a marriage in german
e-h-e you always laugh like
right yeah and you type it out like
e-h-e it means marriage in german it
means marriage yeah i entered the
security court so every time you laugh
you say
basically marry me kiwawa
really oh i told you i told you
yeah yeah but you also also love like
when i when i
when i say like mommy kiwawa
i mean yeah that basically just says
mommy
marriage it's not marry me if you want
to say marry me
then it's uh
if you want to say marry me it's
me it's a bit more difficult
how do
[Music]
no no sorry because you are my child i
cannot marry yeah we can no no no no
mary
i wanted to i want to kill the
turret personally
okay but uh how do we get the cube back
what
we're so cute oh no oh no
get wrecked turret yeah sure but cube
dooko was that the color
oh it's the orange color how did you get
the i thought you activated the blue
color
[Music]
you need to find the vault door
and how did you get the blue color to
drop
there there's button there mummy for me
that made the orange color drop
is it see that made orange come down
oh
you see that it makes orange come down
no
orange no
wait wait i i didn't see doing that
all you need to do is
grab those colors
this is orange now
oh
oh it's yeah it's already oh okay maybe
we need no more blue
maybe that's all we need
yeah the the blue is just dropping
oh
yeah okay
when can we go
ah
i want to
to go there
i can only jump like pretty straight i
can't jump forward
i'm starting to think you don't want to
i guess it it all the dropped yeah
automatically uh
ah
oh
[Music]
ah maybe put the like a portal there
yeah yeah so we can spread the orange
okay let's go let's go mommy uh
oh
now it's all over that platform
so it's it's bouncy now
oh
oh almost
[Music]
interesting
this close
and you're going to fail me what's
what's wrong with gladys why is she
so
that's so desperate for attention right
now yeah
i think like there is only one way to go
there right
so we need to oh
yeah wait can you send uh it again uh
wait no
if you send it
ah can it bounce off there
i wonder
ah no no no no i know i know okay
send it again please uh
okay now it comes through there and we
have a lot of orange i don't know if
that's enough though
should i get it no i want to send one
more because there's a
little bit more
higher another spot
which will make
the ah
i'll test it out i'll test it out
and that said
wasn't that too easy
i think yeah you just come do the same
thing okay
all right
[Music]
okay let's go on
and then jump at the end
no you're right
okay
[Music]
yeah come from my portal
okay
what do we have where are we going
another portal here
um where would we be going down there
can we jump there no oh you ah yourself
oh interesting maybe the another blue
one here
yeah
dark blue dark blue
oh no we have to fall
we need to yeah we can fall
ah wait what's there nothing um
are we able to reach the dark blue one
from the top
can
we
nah
it's in a weird spot
unless
we go back here and then we jump from
here ah yeah yeah yeah okay
[\h__\h] it
you lost the momentum
[Music]
and you have to go all the way back to
make the portal again
okay
through
here i think
and then
[Music]
uh
here no yeah no there yeah yeah okay
now one more
one more
there
i need to go there first mommy please
pick me up here
where are you uh
i'm here
yeah
when the portal ah okay i think this
cold oh damn it this color on it
okay okay it's okay now now i'm kind of
confused
okay so we can okay ah i'll
i'll try it's kind of narrow
let's say it's too many potato chips but
okay i made it
no diet necessary
okay nice
[Music]
you go right i go left i check out left
side
uh-huh there is a button inside but i
can't get inside
last but not least
this is the last room
really yeah nice
um
it's so hard
oh there's an orange
color all the way at the top so i think
we have to
this one we have to bring on this whole
middle platform the one in the center
[Music]
how do we get there
it to kiwamo mommy i look at your side
is it the same i wonder
no i think it's not
hmm
not the same oh yeah it's not the same
oh oh
oh you can send some color here oh
interesting
oh
okay
hmm
that's
weird because of the
if you leave the room then the portals
are gone
[Music]
oh
there's a
a higher level up there i wonder what's
there
but this is only for zooming
[Music]
you need to go up there
ew it's such a slimy sound here
ah
yeah well i think
[Music]
but how can i get there
that sign says there's there would be a
cube coming out
or does it want us to
make the cube orange can we make a cube
orange which cube though i guess it's up
there
on the ground look at the ground oh
oh
oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
and then you change the
portal where the yellow one currently is
you put your dark
[Music]
maybe a bit more in the front yeah yeah
okay okay
let's see
uh the problem is when i am in the air
um i like i can't i can't move much more
um
[Music]
maybe
yeah
maybe we're trying
[Music]
ah
huh uh-huh uh
i think uh i think i know something
can you try just telling me the same way
again
and i have to look around because there
is portal surfaces up there that i uh
okay
yeah
i'll just leave one
honestly mine maybe here okay okay
[Music]
oh no oh okay i see
oh here i am
i saw
some portal surfaces okay okay okay okay
i i just put one there and then we can
walk up okay
okay i made it
now we should be able to get up here oh
yeah yes
i can't watch this button
hi cube we can't reach you we need the
color
maybe
let me let me let me okay
oh yeah oh yeah i see it
oh
yes it came to me
[Music]
it's covered in orange gel now
yeah
wait why do we want to cube though
um
can you send some more color
wait where did you ah can you can you
push the button
yeah i can tell him
[Music]
one more please
okay
ah nice i think i don't know what that
is for yet but it might be useful later
okay okay
now i was there something to insert the
cube down there
[Music]
i don't know why i did that but can you
send it through like a portal the
[Music]
oh
there's oh okay
do we have to push these override
buttons mommy
come here try to
see here mommy
hi hi
oh
uh
uh-huh
okay
oh you come too right okay okay teamwork
i think we could do it differently too
but this is cute again
that's really cute
yeah
like yeah
what is it what is down here
isn't it i don't know there's nothing
here
oh
i die
thank you forever
there's just deadly water there
there's nothing else there
nothing nothing there nothing all right
here okay then
i have to come back to you
yeah
can you put a portal there and then
there
maybe somewhere where we can reach it or
maybe here
um i want to come back to you
oh okay sorry i'm not here
[Music]
this was where you went before okay why
does the game tell us to go here there's
literally nothing here is this just
gladys trick to kill us
maybe perhaps we even just jump over we
can just jump
ah
glados you tricked us
huh yeah nothing here
but wait do we want
several cubes and if we want three cubes
and every cube needs to block one of
these lasers
because i think they're activating
something
this thing here
but we can we can have more than one
cube right oh
really
okay let's put let's put one down here
first
ah it falls down okay but that's
interesting because ah
i see
i think it has something to do with
these platforms maybe you can stand here
and see what changes when i put the cube
uh onto the laser
okay
ah yes
so i will just send it down and you have
to run over to the other side
and number two no number two
uh
i i i have to do them all kind of like
at the same time almost yeah i'll show
you
uh yeah yeah
what
ha ha
that's
well that's a glitch
explain that to me game
now i need a new cube where did i get
the cube from again
[Music]
wait uh couple can you help me up again
oh wait no i can't go on my own wait
wait wait wait where is the cube on here
god damn it
small indie company is it really an
indie company
okay um i can get the new cube i i got
it uh just need some color on it i guess
otherwise it won't slip wait do we want
it to slip
i think we wanted to slip right
off
no
i don't know why why why do i die why
why
uh
[Music]
uh wait wait before you come up here can
you
uh activate the color
oh no oh sorry
okay okay um yeah we want the
the cube to be covered in the orange gel
again wonderful otherwise it wanted to
come down okay
now
yeah we go over
and you check the
the platforms and i go uh slide the cube
where was it okay
it's uh uh here where was it
[Music]
yeah but the cube is safe all good
yeah it's okay wait we have to run
together
you just need to make a portal there you
have to make a portal it just slipped
over
blue portal
okay
okay wait a minute okay now thank you
and
okay now you go here again yeah
here
okay yeah
bye bye
i think it may be better if that's my
portal because you may maybe you need
your portals over there okay okay i'm
not sure
i'm just making my portal okay
okay
okay i'm gonna
i will let it slip three two one
run run run run run run run run run run
yes yes yes and push the button or
something there ah too late
i think timing is of the essence there
but you have to push the override button
mommy you don't need to you don't need
to
to you know to to allow the cube to
try to
come yeah just just bring your cube
on my cube bring my cube
manually manually
yeah no don't throw the cube
oh you know
um okay please don't make me
i'll make a portal
oh there you are okay you can come up no
maybe you should do
that okay
okay
uh
cube uh wait wait wait wait wait
we need we need to
to tell the queue first yes
it's
uh
red d now
okay
okay i'm coming okay i'll hold the laser
one by one
yeah one by one buy one by one okay
yeah it's me or you
i'll i'll do it i'll do it
okay
i can do it i can do it
okay i'm holding
okay first and then note
second second
no yeah
second one okay
no cheese
okay
out
three is ah okay okay wait let me i
don't know what it is
that's oh you can reach both
perfect
look to the right wait the what happened
yeah we just did some
i think it's in order to open the big
door maybe
we both
uh at the same time we have to trigger
the the button the override buttons at
the same time
[Music]
okay
but then that means i have to let loose
off the cube
i have to let loose
from yeah from
from here i guess and then i have to
quickly come over to you yeah
yeah okay
wait let me orientate myself i will go
to the right okay okay i'll go to the
right side okay
to the right
this one
that's where i'll go okay you go left
okay
[Music]
okay let's come over here
oh yeah
beautiful
is that it can we just jump over did we
just zoom over
go go go wait we can't no no no
yes okay
let's
go in yourself
you're the test object now
okay oh
okay
some blue eyes
there is some blue at the top we need to
override that too or what was that
button for that we didn't really check
out the other room at all this one yeah
okay now it's time for that
oh
ah
uh-huh
okay okay let
[Music]
ah not you again
how do we get rid of those
all right so this one
this one lets
the color go
aha
i make
ah i can't mm-hmm
ah can you make a portal can you see it
from there i guess you can't make a
portal there now
but it will disappear so oh wait there's
an airflow
air flow there's an airflow over there
you see that right oh
no
ah
i see okay look at that
i put the airflow
through now but no so
if you
uh if you can move the make a portal
here
then you move the airflow to somewhere
else yeah
and that should help with something
something with how
can i go there yeah
like this
i can't i can't go up there
you need
oh [\h__\h] i deleted it ah
let me i want to look at it
hi
oh
no oh
no no no
[Laughter]
get some oh
what
no no no no i wanted some color here i
wanted some color
not not the air let me just drop some
color now
for whatever reason we'll figure that
out soon enough
with the bounce we can do something oh
no we can probably bring the air
somewhere uh the air i don't know i
don't know what i'm saying
can we do this all mommy mommy uh like
this oh
i know oh i almost
can't ah
oh
oh [\h__\h] what
[Music]
yeah i think your idea was very very
good
we will work on that
where will be this um
[Music]
there's no reverse button anywhere huh
reverse would be nice yeah no no
[Music]
ah
i want i want the gel to go to that side
too yeah
and
we sent
he said um
can you make one portal here
and one here
up here
and now we let the
color go
and we send it over to that side
uh and now go to the other side i know
yeah yeah go to the other side and make
uh
a portal [\h__\h] ah
i was thinking
yeah i was thinking right right i was
thinking correctly okay
we do it the other way around because i
think i'll i understand
um
we do it the other way around
when you're back
oh uh you just put the
your portal
you'll put the one here
and then one here
[Music]
yeah and the rest leave it to me you
stay on the button
on this
button
and
repress
the color
oh [\h__\h] that's too early that was too
early
um
press
the button
we wait for it to go through
yeah and then we put one here and one
here aye aye no
don't me
i'm scared okay i need to be closer to
here then it won't kill me okay okay
okay can we get the jill to the turret
yeah that's what we're gonna do and then
they'll bounce around and they can't
control themselves anymore
so okay
we sand it again
go go go go go and this time i just
don't want to get killed
one here
yeah
yeah okay and then i drop it
somewhere here
[Music]
now we can safely go to the other side
hopefully
[Music]
there is more but wait there's more
oh do we need to
oh does one person have to stop wait a
minute
[Music]
does one person have to go back and stay
uh sending the air
just the same way we sent now oh maybe
not maybe not
oh do we need more color
should i go back and send more color
cobble is dead oh that's what she meant
with wait wait
oh there she is
hi chloe
it's my brother i'm sorry oh no problem
hello
brother
not chebo not chible
jebbo is not my brother chill is my
alter yeah yeah
ah ah cool
see this one
um that one maybe helps
oh i see
oh
maybe like this
maybe like this one there one there and
then
light blue i don't know
ah ah but yeah we send okay
we sent the air
through there you go up
that way first yeah
and then
[Music]
but that's not lined up perfectly is it
can can we i can can you make the portal
here
yes yellow portal okay yes
oh you did land in it nice
and then i'll make one here
i'm done i'm done
oh there's a platform there
oh yeah
oh there's a button
[Music]
i will just go jump in here into the
water take a nice bath with lush bath
bombs
[Music]
oh you're hello this door should be
opening yeah glad let's open the [\h__\h] up
open the [\h__\h] up
is that camera hooked into the lock
camera
camera in the lock something try
something okay okay glad i was trying
something
try something try something always just
using her test subject yeah well i think
there's nothing here gladys you little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
mechanism can tell you aren't humans
that's right we are not humans but this
lock requires humans
but
[Music]
we're so
top left
[Music]
you did it
we're so human yeah romans can't dance
like that oh
i saw that in the chat
thank you i would have never guessed it
never ever
oh
[Music]
wow wow what
i see the light kobo
i see i see two where are we
we're free
are we
where are we going now
towards freedom where the humans are
gladys believes us that we're humans we
really did it
what happened god testing was worth it
just look at all those test subjects
yeah oh my god all the testing all the
testing yes let's go class
saved science
what
[Music]
humans life be their own worries
as long as the robots survive
everything's cool
[Music]
there seems to be still like a dlc but
obviously we're not doing that today but
maybe another time if we wanna let's
look at the files ooh oh so many errands
is that the credits
yeah yeah yeah there's some dlc but we
finished on the main game
[Applause]
a little bit
painful sometimes maybe for the chat
sorry that well we took so long
sometimes but they're not good
we grew a few extra brain cells today
brain cells really yeah
small indie team that's a big indie team
big yeah
[Music]
um so these are oh no they're using the
people who worked on the game to test on
them oh no
oh that was you
oh there's me
what is all the turrets oh no cute
nice
actually yeah i like it it's fun i like
the music people people people i am
technically late i like you like 8-bit
music it's kind of like that
i
wow
[Music]
thank you ivan thank you jacob thank you
jvo shake up before k thank you james
thank you jane thank you jared thank you
jason
thank you thank you dave deep faith day
[Music]
you need to play portal 1 and portal 2
alone you need to play it solo because
it's really so much fun and there's so
much lore you need to play it's cool
and you will understand the meaning of
the companion cube
okay i'll i'll play
i'll
don't worry after you play portal 1 you
will want to play portal 2
you will want to but you can start
before one just give it a try
give it a try yeah okay
how how did how did chapel enjoy the the
game today
i i think trevor is happy to meet you oh
yeah
what's wrong with you i know i want to
adopt both both chebo and kobold
yeah
is olivia table's girlfriend
are they dating
uh i mean only if you're just
um you should ask her stay tuned you
should ask her out
like a little brother to olivia that's
what olivia said yeah that's sad i'm
sure chavo has some feelings for olivia
and then they are unrequited and shebo's
heart is broken because olivia only sees
chevelle as her small brother but chavo
has failings for her
[Music]
some others there's more voices
on the voices yeah wheatley willie
[Music]
lately my buddy
my best friend yeah he come he only
shows up in the solo game
and cave johnson too you only heard
gladys but there's more characters in
the game actually oh i see
[Music]
my british body is
british wesley is british can you do a
british accent kobo
uh wingardium leviosa wow
[Music]
okay
yeah no
no no
no
i like you're not no
no no
no
oh there it is we finished watching the
credits beautiful
thank you aputure laboratories it was
beautiful
a nice time credit um
my british accent is perfect i don't
know what you're talking about
courses are available you may
redundantly solve the courses at your
leisure no thank you no more of that
maybe one day you'll see but for now i
think we're done testing our brains but
what is this oh it's a dlc yeah
apparently
thank you
for finishing portal 2 with me today
[Music]
sorry i kept you up so late
it's okay i know you're
busy so you're
probably tired me no i can go if
eternally we can play more
we can play more but i i thought you
wanted to
finish uh after three hours now it's
already four hours cool four hours with
mommy
[Music]
i'm okay uh for
four hours five hours six hours it's
okay okay mommy if you're a viewer for
some reason awake on friday during my
stream i think it's in the middle of the
night for you but i will try to sing
and mantra john so maybe maybe you can
be there well i think it's gonna be very
late for you
but you can watch the clip on friday
friday no saturday saturday night
saturday night saturday right yeah
saturday but it's like i think maybe
three a.m or so for you maybe wow three
a.m yeah but actually yeah then it's
sunday
oh
something like that
um
maybe uh otherwise you can watch the
clip i'll do my best
[Music]
saturday what is saturday it's 16.
oh okay it's okay
i'm
watching you what really okay oh i'll
sing it in the beginning then you don't
have to stay up for too long hey
nah
okay
thank you for today hope you enjoyed it
chat uh
somewhere guys
koala action also means
[Music]
water in the fire water the fire
but when there's water in the fire then
there will be no more fire kobold
that's sad
you're right no
don't extinguish me
no no okay okay
[Laughter]
now because you're the phoenix yes i'm
the water a song of water on fire
beautiful
greek fire burns and water excuse me
well i'm not a great fire i'm an
austrian fire if anything all right
cobalt i wish you a good night everyone
in the chat good night how did i say
good night in indonesian
[Music]
what's going on
yeah
and in german we say i'll be there
[Music]
yes it's true it's good enough but i
always have an ending greeting that's of
widazin i always say it
so it's goodbye
[Music]
i write it down so that i don't forget
okay i hope i hope you don't uh you know
i'm sorry if i do uh
i i don't know if i'm annoying because i
no
i love you you're not annoying
never i mean i mean i like um i don't
speak too much it's okay
it's okay because my my english is not
perfect either so you speak in english
in simple vocabulary i speak simple easy
vocabulary it's perfect
yeah
uh at least i understand you because
sometimes i don't understand my own gen
mates
sometimes i don't understand what
they're saying
[Laughter]
yeah maybe your english will improve if
you if you
collab with me
yeah
yeah yeah
for sure yeah
[Music]
asking me to do
this collab stream from the start
thank you so much i'm really happy
i just i just don't want to
end this and this is so cute
because we already finished the game so
we cannot
look at my hands
yeah i look at your hair wait i can't do
my wait no i can't do my heart to the
mother i want to do my hard cry
i give you
i give you my heart
[Music]
give you i give you
everybody
[Music]
you
another game but
no i don't i don't know
we should play like i don't know mario
party with some friends or something i
love mario party or monopoly
we can play a lot of games yeah
okay okay then thank you mom
have a nice evening
[Music]
bye guys
bye bye guys thank you thank you
[Music]
do
you