[Music]
thank you
this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
did you miss me alone
kind of yeah that felt a little bit like
a jump scare
hello
sorry I've been uh up since 9 30 in the
morning oh my God
uh which is like 10 hours ago
I got up early I got up earlier than my
mom that is the most incredible thing
that she didn't wake me up but I woke up
and my cats woke up my mommy
[Music]
okay
um
okay how about now maybe it's a bit
better
[Music]
does that sound better
I think all right yeah yeah
yeah I'm fine um
I am I if I feel alright
hello
[Music]
so and we're gonna talk a little bit I
don't normally do
like this but I had some things to talk
about and show
so I wanted to
um do a stream where we don't play any
games but we choose to chat they sound
tired yeah I'm tired
I'm gonna sleep early tonight too yeah
yesterday yesterday I woke up like maybe
uh
[Music]
11.
oh yeah around 11 and before 11 and then
today I broke up at 9 30. and so yeah
let's see
[Music]
well yeah it's because I've been like
for when you know those couple days
where I wasn't streaming
I've been doing stuff all day
surprisingly hey
mm-hmm I'm crazy for my usual sandwich
ah
so what about you guys are you Genki me
not Yankee
how are you
um
thank you
[Music]
oh amusement park the Phoenix themed
restaurant really sell chicken wait what
I feel like they're still stealing my
concept what the [\h__\h] give me the name
that'll Sue that [\h__\h] out of them
what the [\h__\h]
huh
lawsuit time
well dare they where which country is
this
a few reasons yesterday we'll get better
please do
what do you think of a ghost puppy
Pokemon that's so late that's looking
like a like a week ago or so
[Music]
yeah I saw the bed at night cover uh I'm
so confused because I feel like I wanted
to participate I don't understand what
happened but it was really fun
that was fun I think we were like I
don't know if they ah you know his voice
was so fitting and
I don't know when they were all singing
together in the chorus
it
I don't know I had so much energy so
much fun energy and they like sang in
different like
Vibes and it just still matched so
together so well and I don't know
I was vibing when I was listening
because of course I know the song an old
vocalized song No One surviving vibing
vibing there's so many song covers
coming out that I honestly wish
I I I I should have probably
um
should probably
like I don't know moved it to one week
later but now I just want to play out I
don't want to move it's just because you
know so many other song covers are
coming out now
[Music]
no no it's ready and I'll put up the
premiere after this stream mm-hmm
uh
yeah
no no I think something else happened
but um
[Music]
well you guys are gonna make sure to
listen to for blood a lot right right
you're not gonna like
forget about it and uh you know right
yeah
yeah really
is there a stream tomorrow no
it will be for black day
okay all focus on for blood
[Music]
do do
there's other songs besides
hey
I mean everybody else's like covers
they're putting out are great too but
but for blood must be particularly
special to all kfp members because
you exactly know why
Okay so
so I want to talk about today
uh
uh the presents
mostly
and
my mommy and
I
also want to start out by just
mentioning
have you guys seen
[Music]
today they suddenly dropped it without
premiere
suddenly it was there
uh the
the
last episode of foreign surprising
[Music]
Coronado
yeah
um
they've been doing this program for like
two years
and every member gets to be on it for
like three episodes
and thankfully I actually made it to the
third episode uh Elena was in it for the
second and Iris it was her first time
but I found it very funny yeah that the
last episode of this until now program
where they until now almost always use
Japanese Members Only
ends with Ian 90 Memphis
yeah
um Iris only got one episode but hey at
least you made it in once
um oh yes of course there's subtitles
for all of the uruashu episodes uh as
far as I know at least for the recent
ones I'm sure they have them all and
they're you know half an hour programs
so I think you should watch them because
they're fun and there's like um
there's like
I know always fun ideas from the members
being put into like some kind of game
and yeah yeah yeah every time the third
member
every time someone is in the program for
the first time in a row uh
the they circle cycle circle cycle out
but before that the land the person gets
to be the host on their last episode
which is what I did for this one but
um before
like starting to record I
I oh yeah I was like I was I like we
were like prepping and going for the
script and stuff and then I'm like hey
by the way just out of curiosity who are
you getting after me like who's gonna
join these lovelies after me when I
cycle out and they said oh actually
[Music]
he's like oh actually
um this I guess oh I didn't say this yet
huh
actually
uh no one I'm like yeah I was told it's
ending with this episode and I'm like
yeah
you can't just end it on this episode
like what how am I supposed to handle
this pressure and this
look I'm irreplaceable oh I guess maybe
that was the wrist
hahaha
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
I see
yeah but um
so I I instantly felt a bit nervous but
also honored but nervous to be the host
of the last one
uh I was nervous about it already you
know I was nervous about it even more
um
the thing is
we recorded a tweet about it I didn't
tweet about what exactly was that no did
I tweet that was all about you I don't
know
but I Twitter this was what it was about
at Twitter that we recorded for way too
long and I don't know how they're gonna
cut all that so I I talked about it too
on stream I said I don't know how
they're gonna cut it into the general
normal length that they usually do so I
asked them kindly and they even kept
that as part of the video that they
would please make it a full hour or so
even then they would have cut like half
an hour because I feel like we recorded
for like one and a half hours
huh
name
foreign
[Laughter]
that would only have been 50 and
honestly yeah
I can see where they would have cut it
but then for this one I was like I
understand you want you don't want this
to be a two-hour episode but
where do you cut this we're talking all
the time and it's quite interesting so
far so
how how how should we do this
um
but they ended up cutting it quite a bit
it's like only like five minutes longer
than the last episode
first in full
huh
nah what are you talking about
yeah especially since it was a finale
uh it would have been cool I think to
finish it with a longer episode
I don't know anything about a longer
version
how you're right and I watched it today
and you know it's been a while since we
recorded it it feels like it's been a
month ago so I'm watching it today I'm
like
[Music]
um
this is fine it doesn't particularly
feel like something's really missing
because it's been too long but I know
they cut stuff that would have been
interesting where's the blooper reel
which is not really a blooper reel
because it wasn't bloopers what happens
to the full cut then nothing
not nothing there's never gonna be seen
but I can tell you one thing
there's Elena's segment with the fan
fictions and we did two fan fictions not
just one and uh
[Music]
I'm trying to not mix up with previous
stories I made up
but previously right there was like a
was that in the previous episode where
where if this sounds familiar to you
then it's familiar then then yes but I
think previously it was like
um like something with a burglar in the
store right and then you know I made up
the story and they fell in love
okay yeah but yeah so the thing is this
time uh Danish theme was like uh
unexpected no that was maybe before
I'm not [\h__\h] enough I'm so confused
the first star
if I'm not mixing up things was
um
you this like you or whoever the main
character runs and is late for school
bumps into someone
and uh then we go from there I think
that that
sounds familiar to you right
that's like kind of like you know
anime episode bread in your mouth
run run run yes they
she actually did not have toast in their
mouth I think there was a mention of
something in their mouth but it was not
toast and I was like that's funny
because normally it's toast
[Music]
guess where my story went after that
if I remember correctly
[Music]
um so protagonist bumps into boy
um something like
bumps so hard that
um
um even a protagonist or the bully ended
up with broken bones
the whole body broken I think
uh the other person kind of
um
no the broken bones person sues them I
think for damages they go to court
does this sound familiar
no no this should be the new story yeah
that was cut
yeah went to court
um you know protagonists very pissed off
that she's being sued for this
[Music]
um loses the case
um and one of the things protagonist has
to do
as a result to losing the case is
having to nurse the boy who oh I forgot
to mention I also forgot to mention when
I first made up the story The Boy did
not only end up with broken bones but
also in a wheelchair so this is my story
yeah so
um the the protagonist has to nurse some
boy for the rest of their life
and by doing that you know even though
they did not really like each other
before especially after that whole
lawsuit
and she fell in love with him and he
kind of falls in love with her and you
know then it's even better because she's
already nursing him so hooray happy
ending yeah that's why I was having a
[\h__\h] laughing fit when I was
my second story
that's why
let's walk because it's
her other story
I was like when I got the prompt for the
second story that was that cut so please
go ahead and listen to it on the on the
video
um
I was like
um and then I got like a flash a Thunder
flash in my brain I'm like okay I know
what to do with the story I'm ready
immediately
and yeah there I was telling this kind
of the same story just a different
looking
[Music]
the same way twice but I feel I think
when I made up the first story with the
whole nursing and falling up in love
falling in love with them I think I
reminded myself and partially got
inspired by reminding myself of it by
this movie that I watched before that I
absolutely did not like
um from gosh what was her name
uh I'm Emily that was it
oh the misery no the the actress from
Daenerys Targaryen
was an Emmy like thank you not Emily
Emilia Clarke you know she had that
movie where it's a really [\h__\h] long
ass movie where she also like kind of is
the care take me before you probably
that she's the caretaker for a guy a
rich guy in a wheelchair and then like
he hates her and like I don't know they
don't get along well
um but then eventually I guess they kind
of like start liking each other quite a
lot
yeah yeah yeah I've been through getting
closer and understanding each other
being like forced to be with each other
more or less so
that movie because it was long and
boring
um but that might may have been an
inspiration to my story
yeah so unfortunately my story was cut
as as was everybody else's story
um
while you know during the first
segment
uh I already like my first segment I
already know knew
with how far we've gotten in uh like
in in a long time that
[\h__\h]
I I was trying to keep in back of my
mind that this is supposed to be a 30
minute program and even though the
script is already like way longer than
that
and I I wanted to keep it everything
like as as you know
go go
as possible so that as much as we record
can actually make it into the video as
much as possible but
at that point like before before Dana's
story thing we were all ready
I feel like lagging behind and oh my God
these like these these girls these three
girls they just
can't
cannot
keep it together
I think also especially like
um you know Iris may be good at nihongo
we all may be good at nihongo but in
this in Uranus story
[Music]
um thing
the thing is
we were especially on YouTube it was so
funny
prescribing our stories we all had like
no no nihongo moments where we did not
know
[Music]
oh my god well we did not know what
the hell we were talking about
maybe you know that maybe you saw I mean
it was like making funny word
combinations and I
in ego in English
[Music]
yeah
and yeah and that I think made it a bit
longer than it could have been nihongo
doesn't
yeah
yeah happy Halloween I guess not quiet
release the Chihuahua [\h__\h]
well guys I don't know what to tell you
I have we all three of us had to record
our audio separately so we all have our
recordings and could put it together to
give you a full experience
[Laughter]
but I feel like
I don't know
Elmo
keeps cooking yeah
and the girls probably feel the same way
like a little bit more tonight to
um
only have this be 34 minutes long
[Music]
for one episode
uh
sorry I'm late no problem hello
yeah but but it was it was a fun episode
it was I think I think we were like
talking extra much just because
we all were like
having so much fun and we were vibing
and you can't stop free foreigners free
gaijins on the official Channel can't
stop us
kill I was thinking yo director probably
regrets getting free foreigners in here
yeah
but I I I was like you know
at the end it was kind of weird because
like you know I I ended it with like
saying
um yeah Applause for the for the staff
who worked on this for two years and so
on I'm sure they want to move on blah
blah blah good job for now and then
after we cut
yeah we all said uh like hey good job
staff you know just like normally we
don't really like talk about what's
going on on their side but yeah this
time
oh it felt like a like the end of an era
um
there have been a lot of good episodes I
think and they put a lot of work into it
every time
um
get a new program well they always come
up with new programs that's the thing so
of course you get a new program that
they make new programs all the time
it's not like you know
it's not like there's not gonna be
anything on the official channels they
always have stuff new stuff
oh yeah yeah
the subtitles were really good all the
time too and the visuals yeah yeah yeah
for for all the games they always come
up with like videos and visuals and
graphics and and logos and all that
really cool like they always put so much
effort into it and I think they put
effort into all of the official programs
um so not only this one
yeah it was fun being in it for free
um episodes It's kind of dragged out
longer than it should have especially in
this one episode because a certain
someone
never never was able to schedule it
come on was very busy every time
every time a schedule at the date was
proposed
is it busy
so it ended up taking much longer than
uh I guess originally planned but
finally
no it was not me I was ready anytime but
one time you know when was that one time
the recording was supposed to happen
while
I was in Korea I think
I think and then
and then
I was like you know I said okay to it
Without Really realizing that it was
gonna be while I was in Korea
and
um
that was that oh I was somewhere else or
so I don't I don't know it was something
it was overlapping with something with
me being somewhere and I was ready to do
it anyway even though I was like [\h__\h]
damn I should have said no
I was told oh sorry
um you know someone else can't make it
so uh we're not doing it I'm like oh
thank God
I'm not the one I'm not the one I'm not
the reason this cat moved again got
moved like so many times
so yeah
um anyway that was a lot of fun and if
you didn't watch it yet it's on the
official uh Channel and I retweeted it I
mean
[Music]
yeah I hope they will
for official programs always fun always
fun
all right and now and now
I want to show you we're gonna talk
about Valkyrie connect
um
[Music]
um presents and previously I got some
presents I told you about like the bean
bag and
brain empty
but like uh the the cat's toilet which
is moving flawlessly and my cats are
using it really nice
[Music]
so so that was presents from Hollow I've
purchased the the club sponsorship
participants that they thought they
wanted to gift to me right so I also
thought of gifts to give to them I have
yet to like see them showing off
anything
um today did you guys see anything
because by by now I think they have
their stuff too oh but um one more thing
was you guys thinking of smaller gifts I
think 25 or so
pick one espresso tickets
those are not for me though but yeah
painting
uh yeah uh I'm so sorry
I hope you got the dress stencils you
wanted
what are you talking about
did I ever say I wanted those from my
mom
I mean I remember at the time I was like
telling you guys what you could ask for
ow oh okay no did not get those
oh I forgot that I mentioned those thank
you for you know asking for them though
um but
I did not expect
too much out of this to be honest but I
was quite surprised by the quality uh of
and usability of the gifts so here we go
I'm gonna show you
um
so one morning I wake up and I get
delivered oh four or five big boxes from
Japan one of them being something to
wear and the rest being from WellCare
connect and I took photos of pretty much
almost everything
that I got so let me show you
uh we're gonna put it here
we're gonna go through this
so present number one
oopsie Minecraft Lego
now this I'm gonna be honest I don't do
Lego but I like Minecraft
oh I guess just because I have it now I
guess I will build it at some point it's
kind of cute because foxes are cute so
good choice cool
who in the in the chat is there anybody
in the chat who remembers asking for me
to get Minecraft Lego
[Music]
no definitely not me
gone I will say
um this is not uh the best gift
Lego is cool but I'm I'm so far from
that age
but uh there was another Lego gift
that is with cats totally unrelated to
Minecraft
I wonder if that was also someone's idea
like
cat cat Lego like
what
yeah yeah yeah whatever whatever I'm not
interested in it like even when I was
smaller my brother was playing with
Legos all the time me
so much
I wonder yeah the other the the cat one
I did not take a photo of but there's
another Lego set
um
okay so this is one of them
let me like
and then put them put some of them
oh by the way photo taken on the orange
beanbag
[Music]
that I got
testing
[Music]
yeah orange bean bag huge bean bag it's
been very useful
so next we have
a cute big bird plushie
from
chick very cute this one's really cute I
mean the lips I don't know what this
burp injected into its lips
[Laughter]
especially the upper one is plump as
[\h__\h] I think this was like a lip plumper
gone wrong kind of accident but you're
looking fabulous you know we all make
mistakes when we grow up we try out
things like that to improve our
ourselves our looks and then you know
let's just help no one comment on it
um but yeah
um
[Music]
it has like a little backpack actually
it's really cute you can even open it
my boobs
it's pretty big actually
yeah I wonder who who followed this one
anybody who remembers it
did anyone ask for specifically
or chicken or just a chicken I wonder
I did not me probably oh really
makes sense
that makes a lot of sense
I don't remember mine at all yeah you
should have remembered
me really
you asked for specifically a chicken
with swollen lips
all right next we have this was cool
this is really cool I was surprised to
see this probably it feels like a
Japanese viewer would
um oh wait maybe maybe not because
actually I think some of the
um
you know other participating members
gifts were also included in this
partially I have proof for it and
somebody wanted me to get like a bathing
set right I think
and this might have been part of it I
got like a [\h__\h] ton of bath bombs I got
free
free separate sense
from different brands of bath bombs
I don't think all of them are like you
know supposed to be from one member but
I think some of them might have been
from you guys like somebody probably
said bath bombs so they added another
set
[Music]
um but yeah this is for the bathtub and
it could have been meant to be lapunas's
gift Maybe
[Music]
um this is like Japanese style you know
you know maybe you've seen it in anime
or so but they have like this normally
uh in
homes in apartment homes there's so many
plastic just plastic but I guess in more
traditional places it's like wooden but
they have these bowls and they they pour
the water over themselves of this I
guess
um like a little bit
uh and then there's some like wooden
balls in there that are apparently
you can they have like different uses
even you can put them in the bathroom
but you can also just put them in your
closet for example apparently they help
getting rich or spreading a different
smell
um you know like I don't know apparently
it's got different uses yeah
uh-huh it's a foot bath oh what it might
be mothballs mothballs I guess that's
that's it was written on the on the like
description that that's also one of its
uses
um but it looks like really cool and he
is proper wood and it looks like not
from Austria so it's a cool thing to
have in my home
[Music]
foreign
Okay so
I wonder
[Music]
um
next we have a switch controller
well I think it was specifically a
switch controller uh when panda look
very cute
anybody who remembers wishing for this
for me to get
or maybe just a switch controller in
general
it's cute I actually only have one like
proper controller for the switch so this
might come in handy at some point
when
um I have someone over for off collab or
someone who knows and we don't wanna use
but can you use two pro controllers at
the same time
question
because I know there's like only like
two us no free free USB slots maybe yeah
you can oh cool
um
nice that will be useful then it's
really cute I don't know how good it is
seems kind of like all brand never heard
of this company but it has a cute look
to it doesn't it
have you guys heard of the company
is it Wireless I don't know
um yes wireless connection vibration
feedback motion function turbo function
what's turbo function
what's that
no
[Music]
uh-huh no one knows
autoclick
Button Mash
oh
hottest what for spamming buttons does
the normal the normal switch Pro
Controller not have that
[Music]
um
please do better in Mario party games
oh people couldn't say ah she's cheating
what if I'm actually like really just
doing better huh
and then people still gonna say I'm
cheating with this controller now
everyone else I
ow
ah God damn it
how can I make use of it
without making it all videos
turbo is almost always slower than
someone doing it normally no way
[Music]
oh well well
um speaking of switch and speaking of
games
next up we have three different gifts in
one
[Music]
which honestly are good choices
I wonder if someone you know went in
there and said undertale some of the
Persona Bob as long as a Nintendo switch
Sports
because basically like okay I'll have a
like really strong longing to play
undertale right now but who knows one
day and then it will be useful because I
have it and all of these games like I I
don't mind playing one day I can
consider playing them one day and I
didn't buy them yet so actually amazing
choices
actually amazing choices yeah
free games saving me some good money
because I don't get tax um refund on
games unfortunately
um
[Music]
yeah Persona like even if I can't stream
it ever
I will definitely play that privately
one day it's PS4 though I guess that's
fine I have PS4 and the other ones are
switch games
um
no I asked my tax person if I can write
them off as business expense because
like it should I feel like probably some
some streamers do that but she was like
no I'm like huh but that's literally the
only reason why I buy these games yo
it's PS4 games oh okay cool
that I don't have to get out the PS4
you're right I forgot that
it's complicated didn't expire but it's
complicated
um let's just say it's not like that
they expired but they didn't even begin
yet
like grow old before I get to stream
Persona games or but uh I don't really
you know it's not like I had a really
really big wish and need of playing them
so I'm okay it was more about for me
it's more about Square Enix man
for me it's all about screenings there's
so many games from Square Enix said I am
waiting since before my debut to play
for you guys
please please
yeah one day
one day
[Music]
pray for me oh my God just like a couple
days ago I saw it on sale on Steam is
this still on sale because I was like oh
[\h__\h] I should buy this I want to buy it
but then I didn't
is it still on sale I wonder
I mean look
[Music]
who we are I guess when I type into to
where we
it doesn't give me what I need the world
[Music]
it's the Neo one right
uh it's not on sale anymore
it's not on sale
anymore but I think I have it on my wish
list no no I don't now I do so please
please Square Enix tell me when it's on
sale again
I played when I was younger I played the
the uh Nintendo DS 20 before
didn't get really far because that was
[\h__\h] at games and I did not understand
what the hell was going on and how to
play this game but I liked it very much
anyway it was cool
um
I like that
so I think nowadays I will I would do a
much better job uh because now I'm a
gamer by profession
yeah
yeah the combat was so difficult right
oh thank God it wasn't only me I didn't
understand man
[Music]
foreign foreign
that's a very different title
wait that's like
it's completely different vibe I feel
like it's a wonderful world it's a
Japanese title which is so
so positive but then the world ends of
you gives me this apocalypse kind of
vibe of title
hmm
ah yeah yeah didn't you have to like yes
like someone live like online I don't
know you text other players right in the
in the DS version
I don't know
cool game though because it looked like
it had like really it still has very
specific
[Music]
um special
Graphics I like the girl
um with the shorts and the okay they
both have short no wait short skirt
what's her name again she was so cute
from the first game
[Music]
yeah but hey the new one I love the
character designs of the new girls
but why
isn't you completely new characters
right all of them
the girls are killed the new girls are
killed damn there's like a golf girl and
like an emo scene Harajuku girl they're
both like so edgy
[Music]
right
the girls what's up with them they're so
edgy they look like girls that are on
their way to the next anime convention
oh my God
[Music]
so like I said yes it is Minecraft Lego
set let's go
um so
um anyway thank you for the games
they're they're actually really good
choices I was
delighted to see them now uh back to
back back to the bath set of course
I got some Lush the I got a bunch of
other bath bombs but they were off brand
not off-brand but I guess not just
Brands I have never seen before but
Japanese brands are some you know nice
looking bath bombs too
um but these are Lush now I have so many
bombs I need to take a bath like every
[\h__\h] day
if I wanted if I took a bath with those
bath bombs one bath bomb per day
um I could probably take a bath bomb
bath
uh two months
in a row with no break
if I were to add the bath bombs I
already had before that that I never use
I just have them because I I like the
idea of bath bombs but I don't like the
idea of taking a bath because I prefer
taking showers
yeah yeah but I have so many bathrooms
and they're all really fancy and they
look so aesthetically pleasing so
yeah I'm gonna take some more baths
so that's your skin the possible
[Music]
so I need to start using them
let's go bath bombs a whole pool
um
[Music]
so I was to get clean baths to relax
yeah but as I said many times before I
get like nervous and anxious in the
bathtub it's like it's not even that
comfortable like I could just if I want
to get warm and cozy I just go to bed
and it gets cozy and warm with my kitty
cats while watching TV on the big screen
and like actually feeling comfortable
because everything's soft in the bathtub
like I don't know the water is just
water I'm like sitting in warm water and
like what am I doing here even when I
watch Netflix or whatever
it just feels like
like a waste of time
gets comfy and water there's like jelly
bath bombs that make the water feel like
kind of like jelly not not like full on
Jelly but like a little bit jelly-ish
so that could help making it feel a
little bit more cozy but also kind of
weird
because I don't I don't think I like
that I don't think I want the water to
feel like jelly that's kind of
disgusting
but anyway so
nice more bath bombs
nice soup I like them I just I just
never use them but I like them next gift
I was very surprised I'm like what is
this took me a moment to realize
[Music]
pretty different
embroidery Stitch sets with instructions
um and all of them are with a black cat
who who suggested this
you want to remember this because it's
so cute and I think I've talked before
about getting into embroidery especially
for a hand cam stream but it seems like
very difficult maybe I can like start
practicing once with one of these try to
make one of them
must have been fun oh my God it does
look like snail yeah
oh maybe I can make one and then give it
to fauna when I see her next because it
really looks like her snail
[Music]
they're fun are they difficult
I think you suggested I mean like who
wrote it into the actual
but did I did I I'm a genius oh my God
I'm past Kiana
genius and surprising and gifting things
to Future Kiana
oh my God
oh my God like I wonder what the others
got because I think it was big brain to
actually tell you guys what would be a
useful thing to give to me
nice
if it was really me did I mention this
I don't remember
[Music]
yeah
I wanna make this I want to learn how to
make this it's really cute but like once
you're done what do you do with it do
you like use it like as like a a girl
kitchen cloth or do you put it on other
like t-shirts or something I don't know
what you do with this you frame it oh
but you can can you already embroidery
Stitch can you count you also embroidery
stitch on like
like a kitchen towel or so
[Music]
oh
I feel like that would be good
gifted as um as a like a little
um to go cloth tissue or towel like in
the summer I think it's really useful to
have like a tiny towel in your bag so
you can wipe your sweat if you're
somewhere where the summer gets really
hot
[Music]
like yeah napkin okay thank you that's
the word I was looking for a napkin
handkerchief yeah yeah yeah yeah
but you could use it like that
the kit is a great starter to learn
all right all right all right
[Laughter]
too fragile I wonder if it is
towel always important says handful hmm
rough treatment can damage your friends
well then that's not damage it that's
not be too rough on it
[Music]
I'm gonna learn to do something new with
this
so this is also a very good gift 10 out
of 10 three different sets even I think
it was not with with uh I think I have
to get my own thread and and cloth
though because it didn't look like it
was included just just frame and the
guide
[Music]
anyway
next we have also something useful
[Music]
can't speak to that I did not know this
exists cooling heating cup warmer but it
makes sense that it does exist
uh in pink
it does Cooling and he
dancing
it's not very effective oh I can imagine
I picked that thank you but yeah I can
imagine it's not being that effective
because
chatting even just by the packaging
it does not look like a product that
makes a lot of money
the packaging design
just it's not very convincing is it
cup of a little more effective oh well I
want to try it it's kind of like a cool
idea
[Music]
cool idea because you know I like to
drink tea while I stream especially in
the winter and when throat hurt for
longer streams
um
As Seen On TV wait doesn't say that
anywhere I don't see it no it doesn't
fast cooling fast heating Smart Touch
maintain warmth latest design
is dying but the package looks like it's
from 20 years ago
[Music]
uh oh wow butts butts
how does it cool
how is it I understand heating with for
electricity probably but how does it
cool the thing
just does it turn itself off is that it
[Music]
oh
and only one was part of the club not
not anything inside
I guess I'll have to test it out
a mini fan inside
well I wonder
[Music]
ideas
well we'll try it out if I'm if I do
like a 12 hour stream where I need my
tea to stay warm then I munch right out
mmm
or I'll gift it to someone else
would you guys be
um very disappointed in me if I were to
give something to someone else
would you
yeah no way
from you
no no okay okay most of you guys say no
which that's what it should be because
yeah it's not really even directly from
you
[Music]
so next up
is a nice fancy high quality looking
towel from a Japanese towel brand in my
body in my body in my body
[Music]
uh it's not a big towel it's a small
like hand towel
or face towel uh which I do like to keep
my face towels separate from my other
towels trying to keep the face towels
away from the calf hairs
um so when I wash my face and then put
on makeup
that in between those steps I don't get
cat hairs on my face you know
so I I like to have no cat hairs
whatsoever on my on my face towels but
once I wash them in the washing machine
once with something else obviously
that's like the end of it so it's nice
to have a new one then I don't have to
wash the old ones and when I want no
when I watch the old ones I just like
reuse them for something else but every
time I need a new face towel I just go
with something new but recently I don't
do my makeup often so this whole
procedure does not happen very often so
I don't use them much often anymore but
it's nice to happen so it was um it
looks like a good quality yeah it looks
like a proper
you know good brand that really
specifies on this so interesting gift
[Music]
um
I need a second washing machine maybe yo
I'm talking so much in this talking
stream now my throat hurts man [\h__\h]
ah
talking with no stop
no non-stop talking
oh my God I'm drinking water but oh [\h__\h]
uh I don't have my fruit candies here
because the cleaning lady put them
somewhere else
I know when they are but they're not in
this room
[Music]
drink more drink more
keep talking and nobody explodes
[Music]
why why cleaning lady
wait
it was nice though and
um I did do a lot of pre-cleaning
but it was very helpful especially that
she wiped the floors thank God because
I vacuum cleaned but I I never wiped the
floors I'm sorry but I
it's just so exhausting
she did it though
it went well yeah I mean the whole time
I was like kind of feeling like oh what
should I do so most of the time first I
was eating breakfast and then I was like
um just watching something on TV the
whole time but yeah wiping the floor is
really exhausting
[Music]
oh thank you thank you Judy Kunis for
saying that for being so honest
we have a cleaning lady no don't
it was a one-time thing it's the first
time I ever hired a cleaning lady
um
she was really nice so we had some you
know nice conversation in between yeah
she liked my cats
as everybody does obviously
everybody loves my kids
I'm gonna do it again oh not planning on
it anytime soon because it was expensive
and I just I don't want to spend so much
money on something that I could do
myself in theory
even if I the money you know
did monetary approve
um
no because she asked me you know she
asked me
she was like yeah you're cleaning all
night over didn't you know like oh [\h__\h]
you know she's like yeah I know I I read
it and I'm like well
yeah I did so much and she was like how
much did you pay and I said I'm not
gonna tell you Mommy because I know
you're gonna judge me for it and she's
like oh oh no tell me come on I won't
judge you and I said no mama I know you
will judge me
so so I uh I insisted on not telling her
and she eventually gave up but you know
yeah
no not 500 that's crazy
[Music]
I don't want to tell her because
she would she would judge me
[Music]
crazy expense it wasn't it seemed like a
normal price more or less
for that for also for you know my
apartment is pretty big
um
even though I live alone it's pretty big
so it takes quite a lot of time and she
[Music]
yeah also spent a lot of time vacuum
cleaning trying to get the hairs out of
my carpets and stuff
yeah well she tried her best
[Music]
um
she only messed up like once or twice
like you know one time I have like a
um like a like a some some
like
stuff that I put on my face like not
really oil but some kind of like
um special
something
um and she spilled like she put it on
the bed on my bed to just put it on the
side for a moment and then she didn't
realize one of the bottles was kind of a
serum yeah it was kind of open and it
was so new there was still like 99 of
the serum was still inside and it got
spilled all over my bed and made a huge
yellow
stain in my mattress
uh
which I will have to explain every time
someone sees my mattress
without uh
[Music]
uh a blank a blanket or whatever I'm
gonna have to say this was never me nor
my cats
this was from a face serum that was
spilled by my cleaning lady
I tried my best because she she
this at least I have to criticize a
little bit she did just kind of like
leave it like that and just let it dry
while it was really really strongly
yellow
um I trusted her because she's the
cleaning lady but then after like an
hour it was still wet and it was still
yellow so I like wrapped
um with a with a sponge and some I don't
know soap a little bit on it to get at
least a little bit better and it got a
little bit better after I did that but
it's still rare the stain is still there
that's unfortunate
uh
nah I'm not gonna ride the battery
um review
um now it's not gonna get a refund I
don't want to be like that it's just a
stain but also I lost a lot of like
pretty much all of the product like it's
empty now it was full before and now
it's empty and those serums are a little
bit on the expensive side
but it's okay
I'm I'm not mad it happens damn
I'm not angry
um
oh
[Music]
it's just annoying that it happened on
the mattress
if it was the floor or whatever we could
have cleaned it up
um
[Music]
yeah it was an accident yeah it's okay
ah actually I think
I've spilled something on an old
mattress before too it also looked like
you know someone may have had an
accident
and then when I moved from an apartment
to another apartment and friends were
helping moving the mattress
I was like feeling really awkward about
it I was like should I explain this
stain or should I just not make a big
deal out of this it's kind of ah and
also oh yeah one time
um
one time
was it chunkers
was this movie remember the story I told
you about me taking my cat to the vet
and getting
getting them like um castrated I guess
and then I I kept them wrapped up in a
blanket on my bed
and they were like you know still like
hypnotized
could not uh sterilize yeah they were
like
I was sleepy
cat Street
yeah and then
um I was like staying with them because
I was worried about them and they looked
like ghosts
um like they looked so dead and I stayed
with them for as long as I could but
then for a moment I needed to leave the
room and then one of them tried to in
their zombie mode leave the room because
she really wanted to go to the toilet
and she did not get very far she made it
off of the bed but she was like laying
in front of the
door to my room in a puddle of her own
pee partially
um she was only like only her leg was
like in it I would say
but yeah she didn't make it because she
was like Lina sleeping mostly
sleepwalking kind of fighting her body
to make it to the toilet
I didn't make it so that was on the
floor but then later on I realized uh
chunkers did not even try to get out of
bed
[Music]
she did pee a little bit on my bed uh on
that day
and that's okay I'm not mad I love my
ketokato's accidents happen and it's not
like she had any control over it
is
it's like a like a baby that can't like
move you know like what what what what
and I can't know what am I supposed to
do place the cat in the in the cat's
toilet for five hours until they wake up
properly
that's like no no I wanted them to feel
warm and comfy
so
diaper yeah I guess
yeah but it happens so that's why
another reason why my old mattress had a
stain
um
[Music]
foreign
I'm not sure if the those are all the
same mattress
um but I think I think the cat one and
the other one
might have been the same one I'm not
sure anymore I don't remember but yeah
you know anyway stains are awkward so
let's hope no more stains
[Music]
from Hello Kitty
you guys know
I was like
this is actually kind of cool kind of
funny so
um this is an instrument you put the
batteries in
and then you um like touch
the like certain like any spot of the
long part in the middle there and then
you open Hello Kitty's mouth because
that is actually like soft plastic
and and then it will make like sounds
like a screaming baby kind of
oh and you can change it to a low-key a
hiking a mid key and to be honest you
can literally make music with it
cursed um it's funny it's so funny
it's the first time I tried it out and
um the day before yesterday I had in the
evening I had a couple friends over
yeah
um we had dinner and at my place
and I was like hmm
I'm a good host so I'm gonna bring out
some fun stuff so I brought out this
thing and started playing with it and I
have to say it's a good conversation
starter and and an interesting object to
show off when you have friends over
there yeah they were like a little bit
fascinated by it
and then and then and then and then you
know actually one of my friends had
birthday
um like starting from midnight and we
were singing happy birthday you know and
then I brought out the ukulele and gave
it to my best friend uh who can play it
much better than me
me
[Music]
we tried again to do a little
collaboration but um I I have yet to
really get good control over this thing
I will Master it one day
it's this is the easiest instrument
almost
[Music]
but yeah it was fun to use and then the
others like messed around with it a
little bit too
[Music]
yeah I like this gift called it
um
[Music]
party object number one
yeah it goes like no
no no no no no no depending on where you
touch it
was salad John you think some
I wonder Hello Kitty automaton was a
study Jam's idea is that so good idea
then
good idea okay next is something that
was a safe bet with me I guess because
we all know I love alpaca
Here Comes
new alpaca friend welcome to my alpaca
collection family
it's very fluffy it's about the size
like a little bit bigger than
um the the like my my full hand I would
say
it's very fluffy you can barely see the
body
and it kind of is like a beige color
that was me you're probably not the only
one who wanted me to get like alpaca
plushie or something it's not really a
plushie I would say it's more like a
doll
um
but you know I can always have another
alpaca
not the only one
so relatively big alpaca okay and now
here comes
the tiniest alpaca I have ever seen in
my whole life
[Laughter]
tiny you can see by how close I am at
the bean bag
it is like it if I would put it on the
table it would be about the size
[Music]
so tiny
tiny it's so cute though
oh it's so tiny
hi it's like voodoo doll yeah kind of oh
my God
it's smaller than smoking while I am
it's such a tiny one I don't want to
lose it I'm scared of losing it
foreign
[Music]
but tiniest tiniest bubble bubble alpaca
ever thank you very much I wonder if
someone wrote into the
uh suggestions give her the tiniest
alpaca you can possibly find and then
they went on Google and they typed in
tiniest alpaca ever and this is what
they got
to the sunny alpaca I wonder
so
next we have
who is this
ah yeah
yay
two link to link to link to link wind
like a wind wiggle wind Winkle Wind
Waker you guys know how much I love Wind
Waker and Zelda games now
[Music]
ah yeah he's cute he's a bit looks a bit
goofy yeah but he's really cute
he's about the size of
I don't know what to compare it to I
think he was a bit bigger than the
alpaca
um but yeah he's very very flexible he's
very cute and it's like official
merchandise from Nintendo apparently
he's so cute ah
foreign
[Music]
that would be cool
okay next more soft things next we have
a memory form
memory form
pillow was in there I'm using it already
it's on my bed and mostly it's not me
using it it's stronger as using it
choker's new favorite spot to sleep on
it's
s new favorite space to sleep on is this
it's really flat
um
uh so normally I had like
um three pillows on my bed one is like
kind of similar to memory foam pillow I
guess it's like you know the side
sleeper kind of pillow that's kind of
flat
um and I use that normally in connection
with like my favorite pillow that I
bring everywhere even when I travel it's
like a really soft one that's like in
like
swoosh around my hand in any way
so I use those in combination normally
and next to me I always have like a big
floppy pillow because
I don't know I don't use that one but
smoothies sometimes like to sleep on it
you know and just you know for
completion sake since I have a big bed I
just keep another pillow there but now I
ditched that one because I don't use it
anyway and put the second this new four
pillow right next to my pillow and now
tonkers is always sleeping on it because
she has the perfect size to be
completely on it yeah
it's hers now
yeah I wonder when she will get sick of
it because normally they have like a
favorite sleeping spot for a while and
then they change it
and then they you know they hang
somewhere else but they always always
somewhere on my bed but just in
different ways in different positions
[Music]
oh
ah but also good gift I'm not using it
personally but very good gift I might
switch it up and give chonkers my old
one and take the new one instead
who knows will she notice Maybe
remember the first gift Lego Minecraft
we have something related to that
I already said we got more more Lego but
I didn't take a picture of that but we
also got more
[Music]
come to visit me you're gonna think I'm
such a nerd it's really big like it's
proper prop size
it's a Minecraft
diamond sword slash pickaxe if you pull
down the thing and turn it around then
it's a sword because it will be like a
diamond sword on the other side
yeah and the the ax becomes the the
handle kind of yeah
it looks really cool and all that but
[Music]
I'm such a nurse
it's kind of cool though like this has a
cool mechanic really cool official
Minecraft merchandise
it's cool
um oh maybe I should have given it she
here mama if you're watching this
do you want it
I could maybe use it in your garden the
pickaxe maybe can help you
[\h__\h] I should have given it to her
[Music]
ah she's like more of a Minecraft nerd
than I am
as you know
ah and I should give her the Lego too
maybe like you know she needs something
to do because she's alone a lot
um because she lives like in the middle
of nowhere
maybe she needs something to do
next time I see her looking for that
stuff
oh God foreign
[Music]
before going to sleep I had it in my
history in my YouTube history
ah
so
we're getting to the end of it
um as I said like some photos are
missing there were like a couple more
bath bombs and um actually I did not
take a picture but it arrived as well of
[Music]
um another scratching pole that's shaped
like a huge carrot
[Music]
which is probably the cat's toys that
someone wanted me to have
[Music]
and uh I got another cat tree a while
ago that arrived separately which I
already built and is already very
popular with my cats
a a cat's tree a small one that's like
kind of like the height of a table
they've been using it
and and uh Ina's glasses that she uh
wanted me to have uh they were um not
Gucci Chanel Chanel glasses
to be honest I'm this is the first time
I touched like high brand
sunglasses before because I always just
use cheap as [\h__\h] glasses and I'm gonna
be really honest here okay I think they
look cool and all that but just by
touching them
I would never know that these are
from Chanel because
yeah it seems like you pay for the brand
it makes no difference they feel really
light they feel kind of cheap like it's
like they probably used what five bucks
or less to produce these I don't know
how much they cost I think sunglasses
and stuff like that are probably one of
the cheapest things you can get in these
kind of stores
um
yeah but
it's like I for some reason I expected
them to be really happy
they were really happy I guess it would
be really uncomfortable to wear it right
so
of course they're not gonna make it
really heavy
other girls will be impressed I know I
don't know if they will
it's hard to notice because like the
Chanel logo is like really tiny on the
side of the frame
um but I guess I'll wear them every now
and then
yeah I I I only have one other pair of
sunglasses and they are like like
pinkish
um tint so I was thinking yo kind of I
guess I kind of need like a second pair
of sunglasses that's more like you know
black and these are kind of like that so
I will use them and I'm not complaining
I'm just saying that this is more of
like I guess a criticism or a roast
towards high and expensive brands like
you could have you could you guys don't
need to buy from those Brands just buy
yourself a normal ass sunglasses because
they feel exactly the same it's really
just about the logo we know you know I
didn't know I don't know
first time I had like something like
that
um
oh another shot now perms don't know
hey I I think the clothes they make are
surely high quality and nice
but sunglasses they obviously cheap out
on those products
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
classes overpriced in General Store
glasses
I don't want those perms
like just being honest you know I'm not
being sponsored so why should I you know
like sugar coat it
yeah yeah
expensive stuff doesn't mean it's good
cheap stuff doesn't mean it's not good
yeah I mean there's some cheap stuff
that's good but most of the time cheap
stuff is has like a reason why it's
cheap
food I feel like I feel like food can
still be very good but cheap products
like you know actual products you know
they either break easily or you know but
for cheap food I don't think this this
is the same case
[Music]
it's a real obviously they would not you
know cheap out and send me fake glasses
obviously it had properly the whatever
license or whatever so they're real
um there's absolutely no reason where
they would cheap out so far they've been
sending really cool stuff really
expensive gifts like my toilets
okay
um
extremely competitive supermarkets
compared to say to us
in our supermarkets are good because
they're competitive
[Music]
I'm actually not talking about like
food I'm more talking I was like
imagining like street food and I don't
know cheap restaurant food from cheap
restaurants I don't know even though
it's cheap can be really good or just
when you cook something yourself for
cheap ingredients
if you combine the right things
you know those videos where they compare
like
um the same dish made with ingredients
from like you know different price
categories
if you're like good at it you can still
make something really delicious from the
cheapest
um
ingredients right right
[Music]
I'll be a five dollar round versus 500
well doesn't need to be a 500 Ramen five
five or ten dollar Ramen already [\h__\h]
amazing
[Music]
visit Indonesia to find Cobble
aha
thank you for the invitation are you
going to pay for my flight
would you please
um give me your credit card number so
since you were asking for it so eagerly
and you really seem to want me to come
what's your credit card number and the
security code
um
can I buy business class please
are you also going to pay for the hotel
please thank you
[Laughter]
uh okay okay okay what was I saying that
you know there was some some stuff that
I didn't take pictures of but uh here
comes the last gift that I have a
picture of
um
this one's interesting turn your heads
everybody
uh screen hanging light
remote control
included I guess I don't know
um but so this you have to turn around
and you put it on top of your monitor it
seems uh judging by the the photo that
it was on the back or so I think you
have one of those
[Music]
what a nightlife for the keyboard no no
it felt like
you put it on top of the monitor
but I'm feeling like wouldn't it be kind
of too bright I mean you can surely like
make it like less bright but it feels
like I I don't I don't think I want like
a long light right above my monitor I
feel like that would hurt my eyes
but who knows I guess I'll try it out it
could be cool
like it could give it a nice look
people say they're even good or useless
[Music]
foreign
uh feeling it might might be like
especially if I'm in front of the PC for
a long time just having the general
light in my room on is probably way
better than turning this thing on but
I'll try it out because it's kind of
cool I like I like the idea of it
it's cool
um
thank you
I see some of you guys like it so you
know I will give it a try I'm I'm I want
to give it a try it looks cool it looks
fancy it looks good quality
as well
so these are one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen
fourteen fifteen sixteen Seventeen and
then two more sets of bath bombs 18 19.
uh
one more Lego set twenty
oh I got another plushie
um that was a Kirby plushie really cute
[Music]
um didn't take a picture of the Kirby
huh really big
it looks cute because it's like running
constantly in a running state with its
arms lifted up like when I was like
unpacking it I was looking at it I'm
like since when does Kirby have ears
because it looks like it has ears the
way the arms they just start on top of
the head
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm like hey did Curry have ears I don't
remember Kirby having ears I guess
that's what it was but then later on I
realized it's in a running stance with
its arms up in the air
it's so cute and really soft and pretty
big
[Music]
so uh yeah those are some some or like
most of the gifts
[Music]
good stuff good stuff a lot of them or
like all pretty much all of them are way
more like useful and
good than I expected
so thank you
um
[Music]
thank you it's like an early Christmas
really I was opening the boxes and I'm
like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] what really yo this
is actually good
thank you
I expected more joke gifts
no please no
no joke games please only serious gifts
no fire extinguish
yeah well
I mean that wouldn't have even been a
joke gift because it could have actually
been really useful in in my apartment to
have
[Music]
but yeah it's crazy how this sponsorship
has been such a blessing
that's how Cali was like
ah it's a cool sponsorship you got there
girl
wink wink
yeah wow
yeah thank you welcome that for choosing
me and yeah yeah
we'll do another sponsored stream
um on my channel uh
uh sometime early 2023 right
we told you before
um
now Ina will be there too in the Stream
and then we'll catch up a little bit I
don't know what we'll do next time but
uh it will be another spot to stream
the rerun yeah Awakening oh actually by
the way the art that I showed last time
it actually got updated I'm not gonna
show the updated version but
um like I I gave some critique that I
feel like it needs more oomph because I
felt like
um when I looked at the Japanese members
artwork compared comparing the old
version to The Awakening it definitely
felt awakened but then I compared my old
one to the new one and I looked at it
and it looked like they were both
awakened you know what I mean so I said
like to actually make like it have the
feeling of an Awakening I requested more
like I don't know special effects and
whatever I I totally understand that you
know changing the pose at that stage
would be like too too late anyway so you
know it has been updated and I think now
it has more oomph and you'll see it uh
when the time is right when when it's
ready you know yeah some pizzazz
some extra um
[Music]
but you know it's really cool that they
like take that critique and they
um work with it and yeah answer to it
it's really really nice of them
to involve Us in the creative process
right
I think so
um
[Music]
it feels like they respect us as part of
the project
[Music]
so that was a gift
um
[Music]
I guess I still have some things to talk
about in theory in my tangent list but
I don't want to use them all up you know
but I'll talk a little bit about mama
okay
so that's the last thing I'll talk about
for today
um and then I'll consider reading super
chats but I'm kind of like a little
tired
I don't know but let me talk about Mama
Julie first so because this was kind of
an emergency and the reason why this
stream was moved to a day later sorry
about that
um
so
uh uh my mom I told you guys on Twitter
she had like a dental emergency like
actually just like two or three days
before that we were on the phone and she
told me that she has like really bad
toothache and yeah she was worrying
about that at the time and then suddenly
suddenly she messaged me and said that
she wants to
um sleep over at my place because she
wants to come over and um you know I
live quite far so
um it's it's difficult to go back on the
same day but she wanted to come over to
go to like a emergency dental clinic
here rather than somewhere around where
she lives because apparently she
couldn't get an appointment uh within
the next couple weeks and that's crazy
and then here she got an appointment at
on the same day at a random Clinic you
know
so the thing is like I was kind of busy
and like uh you know I had to change
plans again and it was a bit difficult
because I was busy when she arrived I
was like working on something
um but yeah she was like she was
watching a little bit and then she went
to the clinic and then she
um she was really nervous and in pain
and not in a good mood before and then
um you know I called her an Uber I sent
her to the clinic
and then she came back I had an Uber
pick her up again she came back and she
came back
really happy really relieved
with no pain was like a different person
walked into my apartment
[Music]
um
she said you know she said that before
from like previous experiences she was
pretty traumatized from dentists and um
she was really scared to go even though
it had like really good reviews
um but she was really scared of like
having her uh
you know having it done without an
injection you know
um because there was a past experience I
hope it's okay to share
um but um she had a tooth pulled without
[Music]
um
you know making it dumb before
uh anesthesia yeah anesthesia I mean
they tried but apparently it didn't work
and so yeah
oh yeah I never had that thankfully but
she had it happen and since then she was
really really really really really
really really really really terrified
which is why she was probably also
trying to drag it out as long as
possible with the current tooth pain
um
but yeah
um she was really worried about it and
then you know she found a clinic that
she really liked so it was good she was
like talking about it endlessly she's
like I'm so relieved
this was so nice and I already know his
face was really close to me and he was
like really he his face so close and
then it makes you feel so relieved like
oh my God and the receptionist they were
so nice too like I want to go back there
again
yeah they were so funny and they like
totally were so kind and I told them my
story and they understood and uh yeah
yeah I am
yeah yeah yeah so she's planning on um
coming back uh because there's still
other things to do and but now now she's
not scared anymore
um
yeah it's um
a good place apparently
told me she told me I don't know if you
have a dentist but you should go here
I'm like I'm good I kind of have a
dentist so
I guess if I need a new one I guess but
yeah okay
glad she's not scared yeah that was a
big step for her but
[Music]
um
before before
um the appointment she
um you know it was really late in the
evening the appointment
um
she had to eat something before and I
still had
left over
um
bolognese in my fridge
and I was probably not gonna eat it
anymore because I had to cook new
recipes as well
um but I'm like like she was gonna buy
something in the store or something
um um soft to eat and I'm like oh
hmm I don't know if this is so good but
if you want you can eat it and I smelled
it she smelled it and we both thought it
actually smelled still good it was in
the fridge the whole time it was just a
little bit of bolognese sauce so I I
made her some noodles because she wanted
to eat it and then basically she ate my
cooking and she said it was really yummy
yay
it was fun and honestly my mom probably
sometimes accidentally accidentally on
purpose because she doesn't give a [\h__\h]
maybe eat some stuff that's way past its
due date
so she really
um is not the type to care that much but
this was this was still okay you know
and she told me it tasted really good I
said it probably tasted even better
fresh out of the
um pot but uh it was so good so
basically I cooked for her I cooked for
her basically such a good daughter
but yes you needed to eat something soft
because her tooth was hurting so much
and I had just perfect thing I made the
noodles extra soft yeah not Al Dente no
no overcooked the noodles to make them
extra soft
[Music]
yeah she was proud she said she's proud
of all the things like that I cooked she
sees them on Twitter and yeah she says
she thinks it's really cool I'm cooking
so much I got over my trauma too and now
I'm cooking normally yesterday you know
after I made her The Bolognese and when
she went to the to the dentist I cooked
uh the the
Swedish meatballs and I posted that was
fun to make
um
now is actually fun
forming the meatballs kind of nasty I
don't like to
you know use my hands for like forming
um and and mixing
uh these kind of mixtures you know
anything anything like that I don't mind
it with my hands but the recipe said use
your hands and it was definitely
necessary to form proper meatballs me
neither same
yeah I guess I could have used my gloves
I still have disposable gloves they've
come very much in handy in handy uh in
the past couple days for other purposes
you watch them afterwards so it's fine
yeah but you know
all the all the minced meat stuck
between my nails
you you
and then the hands feel so oily
meat good yeah
but I was proud of my meatballs
so I'm gonna eat the leftovers of that
now after the stream anyway my mom is
doing better and
um
yeah she like when she came back she
watched me a while longer doing my thing
that I was doing on the side and I was
really tired because I had a really long
day and
um actually
until now
since like
two days ago
since that like you know when my friends
came over for dinner
I've been with someone constantly and I
have to say that socially
um exhausted me
because normally
people over
and especially not for like two and a
half days in a row there was always
someone here and always like someone
talking especially my mom because she
tangents like a million times more than
me which I understand because she's
normally alone so she has to get it all
out when she's here it's also so hard to
get her off the phone
um because she really needs to like let
it all out and talk and talk and from
one tangent to another like I I ask her
one question like I send her a picture
of my plant and I'm like what do I do
about this and she calls me and then she
talks for two hours to me
about all but all the other things and
I'm like I just asked one question
sorry Mommy I totally get it I totally
get it you need to talk but wow so these
two and a half days uh right now I'm
feeling yeah I I was just enjoying the
quietness like for after after mommy
left today
um you know we had breakfast and
uh I did some more work and then she
left and I I just continued working not
on the PC and then something else
for a couple hours just in complete
silence
I just really enjoyed the
[Music]
Serenity and complete silence
so nice
[Music]
introvert moment needed some Zen time
yeah
just tell her to become a YouTuber
honestly she would
thrive
by talking so much about what she wants
to talk about yes
[Music]
um
she told me like because like she
acknowledged
um because I was like already exhausted
and I told her that I'm like sorry Mommy
I'm so exhausted from a long day
um
kind of hinting at me wanting a little
bit of silence and she was like uh yeah
I'm sorry I really need my chickens soon
because you know she's she really wants
to get chickens again in her garden
um and she was kind of saying that if
she has a chicken she can at least talk
to the chickens
[Music]
I don't know if I should be worried
should I be worried I mean I'm talking
to chickens too
uh so I guess I'm not one to judge
hmm but yeah she still needs to build a
a kitchen a chicken coop kit
Chicken Kitchen Chicken chickens
belonging to the kitchen I'm telling you
that's why they're called chickens
I volunteer
oh so sweet guys
I don't talk to my cats like not like we
don't have a conversation if I talk to
them only say meow it's not like I'm
talking German or English gem I just I'm
only like meow or hey at the most okay
like oh I don't actually have we have a
Mercedes with them no baby talk well
only like on stream when they come by
I'm like to let you guys know that
they're here kind of like low-key
indirectly talk to them but don't do
that outside of the stream no I really
don't don't make me into a crazy cat
lady
getting there but I don't do that
don't
I say oh baby yeah well to let you guys
know that they're here
you guys they're so mean
so mean
I'm getting there yeah and I I'm proud
of it I'm happy about it
yeah
we never said it was a negative trait
you'll make it feel like it is
as long as you've been asking for advice
but
no never mind I was gonna say something
but that needs a photo attached to it
and I'm going to Tweet it out so I was
planning to tweet it out because I took
a picture of something related to my
cats I wanted to show you guys
um I'll upload it
um
anyway yeah I was saying cat lady if
anything
I'm sane and proud cat lady
cats did back seat meals satisfire ah
yeah okay well they had a very
intelligent moment there and I had to
make use of it because I needed someone
to tell me what to do
so what
hmm
[Music]
uh mean mean chickens I come back after
you know not streaming for a while and
before that was froggy llamas I've
really been gone and you guys are are so
mean to me
why
[Music]
oh yeah she wasn't me talking to the
cats it was Fergie Wawa that's right
foreign
[Music]
I won't be starting tomorrow but I have
four blood coming out and I will upload
or I'll
I'll I'll
wait I will I will try my best
to make and upload a schedule within
Sunday if possible or past midnight
perhaps
because I don't want to stream on Monday
probably Fatal Frame and
um besides that
nothing really that I want to say yeah
did you say do you do the behind the
scenes it was so funny right I wanted to
[Music]
say about that
um you know how this happened right I I
said I said on stream oh wouldn't it be
funny
if if we uh I talked about these kind of
videos right and then Kyle carrot made
it without me asking for it
and then
sent it to me but sent like a version
without all the additional like voice
lines
so I said how about I make some extra
voice lines and noises you know
uh so that was added and then another
was perfect yeah
[Music]
yeah you're welcome I'm I'm so proud of
it actually when it was premiering I
watched it with all my friends
[Music]
I I showed it to them because they were
over here for dinner
so the premiere that's also why
everything was happening so late I'm
sorry I was like trying to fix some
things of the video while I was like
hanging out with my friends I was
running back and forth every now and
then what did they think they thought it
was funny I mean I probably thought it
was the funniest out of all the people
it was a bit awkward
but I think they understood what was
what was going on
[Music]
yeah a bit of
a bit was I was busy man the past couple
days doing stuff and even though it
wasn't streaming I was busy hmm
[Music]
do they know what muscle cars are they
don't understand the joke no definitely
not
definitely not
and they probably didn't really register
that moment anyway
I probably didn't even acoustically
catch that one
[Music]
um
your friends don't watch your streams no
no they uh at least my
[Music]
some of them a little bit do my best
friend does I think
I think RBF told me that
he does
a little bit sometimes I think
some of them do
and definitely they do catch some some
clips at least um
here and there
um
by the way now
do you want to hear this
hey don't want you guys to worry because
right you all understand RBF is happily
dating my best friend
they are happy for a long time the
problem is that
um
my best friend she's so busy she doesn't
really have time for me you know I
wanted to do stuff with her but she's
like I don't have time to really meet
you until like January I'm like hey yo
what the [\h__\h]
so I'm like I kind of wants to go hiking
man so RBF says well yeah she doesn't
even have time for me anymore either and
I also wanted to go hiking and I'm like
Ayo so we decided to go hiking together
without her because she has no time and
I want to go hiking before it's like
starting to [\h__\h] snow
um
but you know she was really like
genuinely sad about being busy but seems
like she can't really do anything about
it
and she's she's totally fine with it
like no one's worried about anything
here they those two
I can see them marrying
any moment now like I'm absolutely
rooting for them I want to be the
bridesmaid I wanna
[Music]
be together those two like it's also
like they're kind of the type of couple
that
um they're not obnoxious to be with you
know you know there's like some couples
that when you whip them you you feel bad
about not having a partner yourself you
feel kind of lonely and all that but no
they
not at all like they make me feel so
comfortable and they don't make me think
about any stuff like that and they're
they're not like obnoxious like about
showing their love for each other so
much like I mean sometimes you know like
you know slap each other's butts or so
together but something about them just
makes me root for them
it doesn't piss me off you know normally
I look at couples and I'm like
it all
explosion please but I look at them and
I'm like I just want them to be together
forever and make cute little babies
because they're gonna be so cute
they're so cute they're like the most
wholesome cutest kindest couple ever
um
they're so cute
[Music]
they're so cute they're so cute
ah
so yeah I'm I'm gonna go maybe hiking
[Music]
I told you guys I need to you know I
want I want a hobby where I can go
outside you know and I mean hiking will
probably definitely especially because
it's getting cold it will not be like
something I will regularly do this will
be more like a one-time thing
but at least I'll get outside yeah
yeah
touch some grass yeah
very soon probably before it gets cold
um it's a seasonal hobby well I hope
it's not delayed
I have to be rvm's groomsmen or I'll be
like how about I am the officiator oh I
could get a license I can be efficient
nah I would prefer the role of the
bridesmaid I think I've never been at a
wedding before but I want to be a
bridesmaid I think
[Music]
um
yeah I'm sure RBF has someone else who
he would want to be his like dude
yeah he has a minister I mean it's
possible but I don't think they would
really want that it's kind of weird I
don't know and they have they do it all
the time and like Netflix shows and [\h__\h]
like sitcoms where oh the best friend in
the friend group is the officiator like
oh oh so actually it just happens to be
the fact that I have a marriage thing
licensed thing so I can marry you
especially you know when they're like oh
oh we want to marry right now but we
don't have a minister oh no like oh
actually I have a license to marry you
too what a [\h__\h] coincidence what a
coincidence it's like every [\h__\h]
sitcom out there every [\h__\h] American
show
has that happened
[Music]
please stay
oh
[Music]
who has such a license because if not
then it's definitely not realistic
because it seems like in these shows
everybody has it
[Music]
apparently you can get it really easily
though so I guess so now
I've officiated free weddings no [\h__\h]
way
really I guess I should believe you okay
but most people say no I actually do why
do you have it I've got one yes I do oh
my God
huh
but those situations just are too
unrealistic
people want to marry and then suddenly
ta-da
[\h__\h]
oh it costs money
500 bucks
it's quite expensive wow I wouldn't get
that if I was actually like if I if if I
wasn't actually like planning to
do something with that just for fun
seems unrealistic
[Music]
would be really lie to you Daniel
no no no no no baby no no no no no no
lie
no no no no baby no no no no you don't
cry
what you gonna do it all turns out
[Music]
stop stop stop stop lying
hahaha
you can get your money back what
by being paid by the the couple
[Music]
catch the flowers oh I'm
terrible at catching things I would
probably not catch the flowers
unless I am the only one standing there
and
the bride is like
aiming at me directly and even then I
could [\h__\h] it up but it's more like I
would [\h__\h] it up if it was an actual
ball I think because if it's a ball you
know it's round and then even when you
like about to catch it I would be the
type of person who would be so nervous
and and not confident about catching it
that the sheer lack of confidence makes
me like kind of fumble around with it
the moment I my fingers touch it instead
of just grabbing it I just kind of like
juggle it and it goes somewhere else
that's
that's what usually happens I I could
catch it but I
I [\h__\h] it up somehow I always [\h__\h] it up
somehow
but I think
um
a flower bouquet would be easier to
catch
because they're not round
does that make sense
it's less difficult to like
juggle it around eh no it is yeah
what am I saying I don't know what I'm
saying you know what I mean right yeah
[Music]
original wedding song from Kiana oh can
we play with kissy weddings Oh you mean
like a sugar
[Music]
kind of song right here
show me good loving make it all but what
makes a song
a song that you would want to play at
your wedding it's just I guess it has to
be romantic and happy and like you know
very much
um like I love you you make me happy
kind of lyrics
okay okay okay that would be cool
it's potential to be that I think but I
guess it's Japanese and you wouldn't I
mean
would you
open card Challenger knows all about
love and all that
[Music]
I love conqueror
but you know songs lyrics are so often
about love because what else
can you write about seemingly about
nothing else
so I'm sure I'll in the future have more
songs about love and one of them will
surely be fitting to be used at a
wedding if you really want to
[Music]
um and I would be happy to
even I would be good I don't think so no
those are definitely not songs I would
want to hear at a wedding I mean I mean
maybe at the after party or whatever I
don't know the weddings have After
parties they have something like that
right where they eat food and all that
and they dance woohoo but like the the
one wedding song nah do you and people
and I can't imagine that
no way they're good songs but I just
don't imagine them like that
the reception oh yeah yeah
but no
no
yeah yeah yeah this is
no reception maybe yes
anyway
um
I I told myself to read super chats
today at least a little bit but
am I feeling it no
should I be reading them yes
do I want to know
you guys are so kind
I am I have been up for a long time too
remember and um I still need to eat and
shower and sleep early
[Music]
you guys are just so
fine but at least you know we got to
talk a lot a lot about you know I'm
getting you guys updated on what's going
on shower or bath I couldn't shower
I'm too impatient for bath today
um
I can sleep Tanto thank you
[Music]
foreign
have you heard what I've been saying
so far hmm
thank you antonym
oh be a bucket let's see yummy thank you
so much for being part of cave before so
long
yeah yeah yeah recently I've been up
longer more than normally so it's good
that I've been like fixing it a little
bit
[Music]
um
so I inspired a bit no no no no no I'm
good I'm good don't don't don't don't do
that don't make me think about it
[Music]
good luck sleeping only thank you oh God
my eyes really tired now
yesterday I didn't even need it
I didn't even mean oh by the way I
finished watching Malcolm in the Middle
all seven seasons that was so fast
somehow
[Music]
um
sad now I need to think what to re-watch
next
for a brain empty sleepy moments
don't
[Music]
get I know I was trying to go into
pekoras
introduction but I'm I segue into dun
dun dun dun
the middle is a good
I feel like it just by the looks of it
it doesn't does does not look as good as
like all those other shows
[Music]
it's good really
um I I guess I should go and watch those
animes that I said I was gonna watch
um
[Music]
foreign
ah I want
that one looks really good I feel like I
would love it
Apple TV
I'm not gonna get another goddamn
subscription just to watch one stupid
ass show
oh but uh all right I said
I have to watch I have to watch the
handmaid's tale new season because I
said when I'm done with like Game of
Thrones I'm gonna Jam my sale and then
but I'm not ready for it yet and I was
I'm more like looking for a show that's
like you know relaxing
um so
eventually eventually I'll launched
anime sale my mom has been catching up
with the handmaid's tale but I haven't
[Music]
yeah just one show and that's it
descriptions why why
[Music]
Coda and pre-historic Planet if you like
nature dogs and dinosaurs no I don't
foreign
I don't really not particularly
um
so I would really just watch it for
toddler so
are you watching YouTube
well it's not like on on any of those
services
I don't want to like always have my
laptop connected via HDMI to my smart TV
just to watch like animes I wanna that's
why it's so good to have like more
animes on Netflix nowadays
yeah Crunchyroll
oh I don't I don't have a Crunchyroll
thingy
I guess would it I guess it would be
worth to get huh
oh wow anyway uh
[Music]
yes I watched the last episode of the
hospital dragon
uh I feel like I mentioned it before
[Music]
um
I don't want to annoy you guys too much
with my
Siri has reviews
but
yeah well I don't know actually the only
thing that really like stayed in my mind
from that episode that was like really
like you know something
big that happened I guess was you know
spoiler alert
one of the boys you know what happened
I'm not gonna say it but you know one of
the boys that was like the moment the
moment
the moment she you know talks to him to
tell him what to do it's like such a big
um death
flag oopsie yeah but I think it's so
obvious like I was like oh that's a flag
that's such a flag
um
oh please don't go and then you know
he's there and then it seems like he he
leaves safely but of course not yeah
that was gonna happen but then you think
he escaped safely but now of course not
um
[Music]
that hurt I was like I knew it was gonna
happen but I was really really really
holding on to the possibility of it not
happening
hmm and now I'm just really pissed off
that I have to wait two [\h__\h] years to
see something again of that show
I would have hoped really that they make
it within 2020 free what the [\h__\h] like
what are you gonna do with all this hype
that you created
yeah I've heard it's gonna take two
years 2024
they're killing their own hype I mean I
know I understand it takes a lot of time
to create this like if they could do it
earlier they would obviously do it
earlier
uh
[Music]
there's always books
okay last tangent not really a tangent
last thing to say speaking of books
you know
I I watched an interview
of the
sheesh forgot his name
about the dragon guy the guy who writes
the dragon books yeah yeah yeah
and George RR Martin thank you and then
I only saw George okay that's all I
needed
uh and and and he introduced his new
book yeah so I'm like this book does not
look too big so I looked up how long it
takes to read it the rise of the Dragon
an illustrated history of the Targaryen
Dynasty volume one
it looks so fancy you know so I looked
at that and it takes apparently only if
you read at 300 words per minute it
would take 4 hours and 15 minutes which
is sounds crazily short I don't think
that's like 100 accurate but it's also
good if it's shorter because
well done there's something easy to
throw out there to the book club
and you know I'm just kind of biased
because of
you know Game of Thrones and [\h__\h] so I
said
hello my sweet how much is 300 words per
minute
but okay so I said
um to my book club I said hello this is
very selfish but I have a suggestion and
since you girls mostly send
I'll read whatever you suggest or decide
I'm just gonna go with it I'm gonna say
I want to read this because this is kind
of like the in the beginning of the
targaryens but with cool illustrations
uh uh and it's not that long I've been
this would maybe be cool sorry what do
you think and then so far everybody said
yeah
everybody said yeah and you know I I
figured that you know probably the other
girls have watched Game of Thrones
um or like are are interested at least I
have heard of it I have seen some of it
and yeah yeah I think they really
um are maybe not all of them but at
least at least one of them was really
excited about it
[Music]
and the rest was like yeah fine let's do
it okay so we may or may not have
decided on the book but I just kind of
chose it because I randomly saw it's a
new book and I just stopped watching
House of the Dragon so it's a nice
connection but I don't know if it's
actually good if it's a good choice for
a book club
but we can talk a lot about
um the targaryens through this
and
I think it's cool to read a book that
also has like some kind of like TV
adaption you know
doesn't seem to be
[Music]
yeah that's a good thing I think
it's a good introduction to a series I
don't think it's supposed to be an
introduction it's more supposed to be
for people who want to know more and but
even if you're not too deep into it I
would say it's still also kind of serves
as an introduction to the targaryens
[Music]
hmm
yeah like a like a history book for the
targaryens yeah
really only good probably if everyone's
into Game of Thrones I think
I think and they kind of laughed it to
me so you know don't give me so much
freedom
[Music]
um
May spell the rest of House of dragon
for you
[Music]
oh sorry are you sure
I feel like I read that this just is
about everything that happened before
House of the Dragon I feel like that's
what he the George RR Martin said in the
interview
did I get it wrong
[Music]
I'm pretty sure that's what he said
um
[Music]
LGT I'm not talking about lrtt the rise
of the Dragon
anyway I'm [\h__\h] tired I'm really
tired
well maybe did anybody it's already out
I'm wondering if anybody read the book
but if you did or if if you want to
please read it and tell me about it
apparently you had 300 words per minute
it can't be read in 4 hours and 15
minutes so go get it and report back to
me thank you
[Laughter]
then I can judge better if it's good for
the book club
okay I have to put up the four blood
reservation now
[Music]
I don't know how that's like wait that's
way too much isn't it that's unrealistic
how much does a normal person read
except that's ever reading speed
it's fast okay maybe it's average for
bookworms
five words per second
hmm that seems okay maybe a bit faster
than normal yeah
oh well okay and in German medicine okay
I need to go I need to go
um
[Music]
thank you for listening and next week
should be more or less back to normal I
mean I might take two days off rather
than one day
um but I mean that's so kind of normal
so yeah look forward to
no blood
thanks guys for waiting for me giving me
some space
good night thank you very much
thank you sweeties
[Music]
okay
next time I come back to the screen I
will probably be like hey yo what the
[\h__\h] I didn't clean up
everybody oh [\h__\h] this is so this now
let me get rid of this now
[Music]
okay
here we go
back to normal pretty
who is this pretty lady
foreign
[Music]