happy halloween
happy halloween happy
halloweenie molly kelly's still muting
herself
kelly kelly kelly
shy kelly's scared of halloween
hi there i'm here hello everyone yay my
stream is on ultra low latency now and
i'm very excited hurray
is everyone too quiet for you guys or
should i turn them up louder
how's the audio adios
i was muted thank you chad for letting
me know anyway ultra lovely
yeah from now on
so should i explain what we're doing yes
please
please please yep okay so
and now we all have never played this
game before at least
uh like 10 minutes before this unless we
play the 10 minutes before the stream
however and i think i have grass crabs
crabs grass grass basics
so i shall explain
kind of similar to among us and i didn't
play it but coulda said it's kind of
also similar to dead by daylight
right yeah in a way yeah
uh basically we are all children
and then among us wink wink
is a secret neighbor like a really old
dude scary dude
that's always in the screenshots from
this game uh
but he's also uh shown as a child
at least in the beginning and until he
decides to just uh like show himself
uh we are trying to like we are going
into a big
big mansion and uh there's keys hidden
up over that mansion and we kids
try to find it and each kid by the way
has different skills depe
depending on which kid you choose so
the the old dudes eventually will try to
stop us from getting those keys because
once we get all the
keys and open all the locks to a certain
door
then the kids win the game and i have a
feeling
that uh today in today's collab we will
never even once manage to open the door
but
that's the spirit
that's pretty much how the game works oh
oh [\h__\h] oh
i'm on low power mode well
i'll be fine
thank you for reminding me i should plug
in my my key movement
yeah that's yeah i think that's pretty
much the game it's kind of easy
um yeah there will be an imposter among
us
we're not gonna mute ourselves like we
didn't among us because
we realized it's not maybe maybe not
necessary however in the test rounds
ina was the imposter and she was very
quiet so
hey maybe action if you're a child
you act like a child
is everyone ready to go into the first
round you're ready
to keep it at 10 minutes or do you want
slightly longer
oh let's make 15 minutes left maybe okay
cause i i think we need more time
especially my brain i just woke up
okay ready up i'll find so i'll be back
watson are you a detective i'm a
detective but today i'm
using my fps skills for good oh
i guess wow
cool ah kelly you gotta return to the
lobby oh yeah okay here we go
push the big orange button the big red
button
yeah here we go
creepy that's good bedroom nice
nice mustache i want a mustache too
okay cool
all right
yeah kelly i was confused because
there's like some doors are you in the
desk
you can open you're under the stairs
hold on oh no nothing in there huh
how could it be how could he be going
don't throw that pumpkin at me don't you
do it
where are you
all right well you guys blame me hi okay
i am still learning i'm keeping an eye
on you
okay actually maybe not being alone i
use this one
callie wants to drink them
yeah i drink i drink in the garden
goodbye
get away from me get away from me get
away
i need to go find the keys oh give me
this what's in
are you hiding what how do you know that
what are you doing hey watson
yeah i died right in the beginning so
okay that's drop and then throw as you
click
oh how do you i'm trying to throw okay
you press the other button okay
oh what's this hey what why did i take
that oh a key
oh it makes you sticky
did you know that how do i know which
door it goes to
it's right here right here right here
right here isn't it try it right here
oh wait that's the door in the middle oh
that's for upstairs that's right
upstairs oh they're probably
okay get away from me get away from me
okay
go upstairs where are you going i found
it
okay i'm not afraid to use it
hello put it in oh
i dropped it i don't want to play okay
you press this
button got it nice i'm a gangster but
y'all knew that all right here we go
uh wait what's this here did you know
you can comment
let me need the key card again oh
i found where the number two key card
goes to oh okay
now i guess you can't really use it
again huh okay oh
well we're opening doors
hello who's there huh who's that it's me
oh kelly hey you know what's going on i
don't know but i found my way to number
two
i found the way to number two so if you
find number two key let me know
look around
what floor are you guys on we're on the
second floor
oh it hurts
i was on the second floor lads in front
of the uh
in front of the entrance to any of the
other rooms
show it to us your sexy body
there we go
no wait what i didn't even get attacked
retaliate
no retaliation here just uh
this day picks predator doing business
also in the practice rounded it was also
uh watson
who was the only one who stayed alive
until he actually died
but yeah watson i don't know where i'm
going i don't know what i'm doing
where are you where
don't are about where she is you gotta
keep her safe
what son
yeah but i don't know i didn't know you
could get there oh
oh my god wow nice detective watson on
the roof
watson wow
no no no she's in the basement
well i can't find anything
how do i get to the oh god what
um they're carrying us as always
i was just impersonating
oh my god
it's creepy just watching you gouda
it's like is she a kid or she is amelia
breaking the game where is she is she in
the roof somewhere is she like glitched
into the wall
playing the game she's glitched into the
wall she's amelia's breaking the game
are you hiding you're in this room
i need some popcorn ow
you stinky little cheesy bread come here
how did you get up there
she jumped there she's a zoomer
can i throw something
huh
there's wrestling you can't throw chairs
wait where are you come here
let me try and turn my chair at you
all right just gonna go get a cold one
everyone enjoy watching watson slip girl
hold on just a second
huh did you put them in your truck with
the candy
no i know that's a little
i want to paint my character i want to
be the one who gets the clues
oh i'm going to be the detective
to find those keys
okay returned who should i i don't think
i was a very good detective i found one
key
uh but i wasn't really pleased with my
job so let's see
um is there any is there a kid that just
beats the [\h__\h] out of
people there's a town
can i can i hit someone with a baseball
bat
yeah oh he's not emailing yeah
i think so there's a character with a
baseball bat but i don't know if you can
hit anything you know if you can
actually hit the ah man i wanted to i
wanted to hurt that guy
okay well let's try my flying objects
yeah oh okay i got you and that's the
counter strike
what's the inventor do what do i do
we want to get into the basement yes
ah yeah what's our goal exactly um yes
there's
a door on the map and then you open the
big door with like the six blocks and
then you gotta get
it we should stick together
aside from the killer of course yeah
let's chill
ideally it's a good idea let's stick
together this time
gang up on him yeah yeah get him
dog piling so with the scout you only
have 10 bullets
and you can only you can only
temporarily
okay i'm gonna call it no it's amelia
all right and how do you uh how do you
press what buttons do you press to shoot
wait uh q and then oh what's this
all right got it now q and then mouse
yeah got it okay
that's easy enough milk all right guys
we're sticking together right
yeah yeah i don't know i don't know
anybody anymore i trust gouda you get
very unlikely that gouda got got to be
uh
imposter again neighbor i don't know
apex predator glisten man
by the way i have a hint
it should go up to the second floor i
think yeah
i also have a key card you can open the
other door over here
oh i know dropped my flashlight
somewhere
whoa there's a coffin looking place
what's in here give me like why can we
pick up useless items
what is the point to throw them i think
you can throw them
boys okay hold on so each no give me
that
sorry each key card has a different
number
uh-huh
why do
oh no it's cali
no i died
i think only like a certain character
can escape
are you upstairs or downstairs i'm
upstairs
okay then i'm downstairs
wait wait hold on wait
i can build a gun oh no
oh no
people who are good at video games
so what
wait what is the what is the goal now if
you're the last one
you got to get the keys yeah you still
have
all the keys yeah it's kind of hard
you can only hold two things at a time
so it's like yeah well there's the one
character that can hold more than
one items um
oh
oh you have to like speed run this oh
nice nice good yeah yeah yeah
there's keys they're not all up on you
gotta match their numbers
you got this you got this
go to door number one no don't go to
door number one
yeah i mean number one
what is this i don't need this oh wait
yeah i do
very creepy
wait what did i do oh never mind
all right how do you get on the roof
wait
keys for huh door and like not like
actual key keys you can find them
in different places it doesn't matter it
doesn't have to be like a specific spot
oh
wherever you are you can still find a
key for the big door
huh
and there's key cards and there's keys
key cards are
to open more rooms and the keys are to
open that
the big door that we need to open that
we need to open that's the music so
you know i don't mean to alarm you but i
am now i now i'm carrying i am with
firearms
so please keep your distance this is a
two
yeah i need a one
doing
you can't stay in the garage the whole
time girl you can't stay
what's the big he do you put it in the
big door that's in the main lobby
oh god that's all the way over here
though
why did you just give away my location
watson
what do you mean i didn't do anything i
just said where's my
gun
good that's difficult man
in front of the door yeah so we i think
if we all stay together and we have like
one person who does like yeah the hell
is son
yeah it could be a good bait i can be
good a good
gonna get lost distraction all i can do
you wanna you wanna start over since
we're not all here it might be better if
we're all here
yeah hold on wait let me let me go back
to inaudible
i wanna twist my i wanna test my how do
i get to you
uh if you grow enough items at the
killer you can temporarily kill the
killer
oh yeah him down as well not only the
kids
what if i shoot him spam throwing items
on him and the
fling shooting yeah
we'll use the slingshot next time i'm
gonna do it
temporarily uh yep
yeah i'm not sure how i feel about that
okay
oh
we can play another round because this
is a lot for one person and you guys
aren't
getting the play we can start over yeah
okay
ah wait i don't have a flashlight like
that
did you just find the gun that's a
powerful weapon
get out of here wait where are you where
is xina
leave the house
quickly and we can start another round
yes
huh would you like to be killed
i would it would be my an absolute honor
where where are you
are you parkour
oh okay you can revive oh i suppose
like a little sickness though
oh no this is sad hi she's outside
i can crawl
oh i'm up
someone said my my screams sound like uh
cleats or
shoes on a basketball court i don't know
what i feel about that
movie
good at still trying to survive
ghosts
it just bugged me
how do i throw stuff
what you want this shark you're gonna
have to fight for it
that's what i'm telling you about okay
there you go
um let's see i like i bet i can throw
pretty well so i'll be
only this kid what are the match rules
maybe we can set it to like
because you guys said there is revive oh
um
what oh there's auto revive on yeah yeah
it's on it's on
but we never live oh when you when you
try when you like
fall and stuff and you measure you
revive when you get missing i don't
think you're at five yeah
okay okay okay okay
oh wait but one thing one thing we can
do is maybe
uh the number of locks maybe get them
down to five or so
that would be good five five
and yeah that should be good and and the
character that godot was playing is
pretty op
if anybody oh then we can build
guns inventor yes oh you have to build
stuff right
yes but you find it's really easy to
find the stuff to build
oh okay i'll be i'll be an adventure kid
then
maybe we should also turn off key cards
so we can go straight to the keys ah
that's also smart yeah yeah we'll see
how it goes
okay i think that makes it a bit easier
for us to win because other than that
i think we were it was impossible for us
to win yeah
wait question if yeah if there's a
neighbor but they're an inventor does
that mean they're
uh i am they can shoot the kids they're
gone
i mean
it's [\h__\h] up this is this is something
else
i'm a killer but i actually don't like
bullet sticks you all in the chat chill
out
chill out now everyone who knows me
knows i don't like guns all right listen
can you turn it off okay yeah yeah yeah
okay okay thank you okay
whatever man whatever for the next round
for the next round should we turn off
player names so we can't tell who's who
yes that's kind of a good idea i should
have thought about that before
i was like i'll sort of make it easier
to hide then because we won't be able to
see
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wait how come
chad is saying in-game voice chat is it
because it's proximity based is that why
you guys are saying that
oh possibly what
exactly um yeah proximity based
uh voice chat and stuff ah it is
proximity that would be cool
we can try that if you guys want
practicing
i'm going in this room what does that
mean
uh the closer you are to somebody the
louder they'll they are
and then the further away they are i'm
sorry i'm sorry
i'm sorry i don't know how to play this
game i'm sorry yeah
i don't know
i don't know how to play this game how
do i switch objects
what's the button switching number one
two one and two
wait okay hold on two oh okay so this is
the blue does this do
what does it do all right it's all
sticky and on the ground i'm going to
leave that alone
kara come with me it's milk
yeah okay wait where did you go okay i'm
gonna stay with you wait what if you are
the what if you are the imposter
trust me by the way i have a i have a
photograph again
of uh where the key might be too oh
where to switch items oh okay it should
be are you gonna have a lower
lower cupboard not one like this in a
low one like a tv cupboard
oh yeah oh
usually she isn't so quiet yes
yes
yeah no yeah no yeah
she's kind of quiet yeah i'm a kid i'm
just a little
innocent kid oh i see walton hello
eyes on watson see wouldn't i have
attacked you guys already if i was the
yellow um
what does this do oh you can jump
is that another flashlight there was a
lot of flashes yeah
oh in case you lose yours i guess
whoa what's going on what's that laugh
i'm scared i don't like it
what why are you guys so suspicious of
me i didn't do anything
that's exactly amazing exactly
yo there were just snacks in here
oh that's kind of suspicious she's
trying to lure us
hold on hold on kind of snacks are you
talking what's this is it a candy bar
hold on trick or treat
smell my feet how is that
what the hell is that what never hurt a
bag
there's a walking pumpkin in the clown
huh it's cali oh yeah
callie i'm scared
you voice chat next game yeah
what are you talking about i didn't do
anything
you can also be the clown and the clown
can transform
into the clown can transform into other
eyes
that's not good it's not great
has anybody found a key nope
no no
i'm in the garden and i'm about to die
thank you everyone for being with me it
was fun but i'm about to die goodbye
sayonara guys have to make
guns
how many years do i i have two probably
why are you so quiet callie
why did i build this waist
was so close to death because i love
that that's it
that's it oh i see i see how it is i
don't know how to grab people in this
game
you killed me i know i i pressed a bunch
of buttons
okay so we don't need the key cards we
only need the what what is that
what is that what is it
it got it money oh that's not money
i'm scared
who's still alive besides me
i am i am hina is alive
i'm doing my best hold on
hey everyone i'm thinking that we all
matter
we ought to recoup with each other and
make a rendezvous point how about that
i don't know about that no not um
normally i would like to
uh we need to make a plan uh-huh
by the way i already got two cookies so
you know what the carrie oh
can she steal the
some nice music playing
oh oh yeah radio
is creepy
look i don't know who you're gonna fool
with that
hang on it's real dark
i wonder why it's so dark yeah are you
lost callie
no i'm i'm fine i just got
i'm scared mom
guess who's your mom pick me up
was someone already here
oh i don't like it why do i hear
wait
okay i don't need my i don't need my oh
what is this sound look at this sound
oh it's falling out what the hell is
that's a shame here why can't i find any
keys
oh do you even lift bro oh the the crow
the curl marks where the key is
oh where who is the grove the curl
behind you
do you see the crow in the oh yeah i see
that thing yeah yeah
oh wait then i i guess i found the key
it's gonna oh here i found the key
uh-oh no no
oh wait
i don't like that noise
oh boy ah wait who's the light
i think the killers are really bad at
video games that's probably who
that's probably who it is the one that's
the worst
is very bad too because they're always
lost
protect me wait where's the where's the
all right
yep you know what are you riding on
you're writing on something on my screen
i am i don't know
what you gonna do with that killer
you got one too awesome
no no yeah right what does it do
you guys got this it's only one
yeah only one left what yeah there's
only two more two more oh okay two more
money yeah
i forgot i just do the keys and then
only four minutes left
there
suddenly intrigued would be nice if i
had a flashlight
well valiant jessica is it not
oh thank you for the tip i appreciate
that here we go found one
yes okay problem
a nice house it's a huge house there's a
hole in the floor
assistant
the thank you for the key yeah hit it
with the weight
hold on like you gotta eat it yeah i
have it now
i have it
you gotta kill her good luck but can you
kill death
yeah exactly see that's it
the killer instincts finally come out
let's punch
okay turn on your in-game audio
oh okay um chat
always on okay voice chat
on always uh let's test it out
um oh you guys are going to try to
talking game
okay
how do we do this hello
wait oh
hello
it's so bad it's so quiet
just for fun
15 minutes key card off all good
how do we turn off the names wait i'm
going to say something
i do not hear ami
i also don't hear her head bob intensity
let's see how do we turn off the names
oh no no it doesn't automatically it's
the right does it automatically
fix it i think discord uh would like to
let us know that they liked it when
discord quality was on
i'm not surprised i'm not surprised
really no like
actually discord this coin's in the chat
wait what what
discord's in the chat what i discovered
listen we're doing this for the
experience
a discord like the real discord is in
the chat i had a check mark next to his
name so i
assume so
audio they will appreciate the score
more
they say they forgive us
is is almost ready
okay this is in-game audio
yeah this right now this is a game
discord size discard sauce
however if it's the real one thank you
for blessing us with our
oh she's restarting the game i'mma's
restarting the game
no problem
what what is everyone uh going to dress
up for halloween i mean for me and cali
halloween is kind of over budget
because it's the opposite of what i am
right
i'd be afraid if i saw callie in the
hospital
that's what that means with a very good
reason
discord discord came to my chat as well
oh my god
discord come to my chat it's great
i'm saying hello to my deadbeats discord
why is discord out of watching our
stream
who knows discord discord i couldn't
figure out how to do the thing where you
when you show everyone's big faces
could you maybe plug that into discord
options so i don't have to use other
applications
could you please
i have some good ideas i'm a good
inventor or how you call that i can make
some i can send you some good ideas
i'll send you an email discord
let's talk business discord let's do
some business
i'm a businesswoman wink
wink but other than that thank you for
your services discord
yes i really much appreciate it thank
you
for real though why is discard watching
i know
we're having fun we're spending the best
halloween ever with
us i just realized kiara sounds the same
in the game yeah and she does it discord
i'm supposed to sound good on this card
at least now when i bought my new
microphone
don't tell me it sounds shitty on
discord wait maybe she's on
like one of those mic uh megaphone
things
i bought a 400 microphone okay 400 or
500 whatever
don't tell me it sounds like a
walkie-talkie
maybe maybe it's my brain remembering
how your old mic sound
i think that's what it is that's all no
400 well spent nowhere these doors
hey watson's here hey what's this watson
maybe we should just do maybe we should
do this card again i mean yeah
okay yeah i think it's fun while it
lasted yeah
everyone appreciate this chord yeah yeah
oh okay all right they're still talking
we're still talking we're not talking
anymore
we're gonna go ahead and meet everybody
and then we're gonna i'm here always
rely on discord
always rely on this course
yeah oh sorry i'm an idiot hold on here
we're going
boom
party so loud turn the audio down
oh yeah it's turning um cause i had to
turn it up because everyone's voices are
so quiet and now it's like blasting over
yours
hi i wanna be the imposter i don't wanna
be the
impulse all right guys i think if we
spread out
if we spread out it'll be better that's
exactly what the imposter would say
wait who is this what anna cover one
round when you spread out when you look
for
keys right right right can someone show
me the way to the roof
oh my god the room's changed who is this
oh huh a thing that happens in this game
whoa wait what the what is one yeah
what is one okay now no one can show me
the way to the to the root
girl
we're looking for keys right just the
key
who's quiet watson is suspicious cool
can you hear me yes yes
yeah wait there's only one person in
front of me where's the
where's the where's down
oh
oh see anyone only the killer would have
recommended that we split up
attracted to death and i are meant to be
listen either i'm killing folks or i'm
getting killed that's how it always goes
every game
in a dedicated relationship with death i
am
i wish there was a way you could just
pick stuff up
why is anyone surprised okay one key
down
one key down we're not fine let's see
i don't know lucky lots of door openings
don't touch me okay
i hear someone say with death you silly
willies
what is that you're weird
right in the beginning though
wait do you know what it's just like
chiara okay what does kiara look like
she's the one with like the the pigtails
oh
he's opening the door he's coming after
you up the stairs
now he's a child again that looks just
like you
look at him
wait you're all dead oh yeah
again you got to carry the game
well i was up against the top fps player
out of holoyen
yes
make it easier for you guys yeah yeah
less oh we can get to three keys do you
want the three
yeah yeah yeah put the time limit to 10
minutes
okay 10 minutes three keys games yes
speed runs
i want to be this guy he holds a lot of
things all right you said spread out
because you were there
before i knew i was here
i understand
okay it's only three keys now
manny what does the money even do it
gives you money
i don't buy stuff in the lobby yeah oh
what does the hammer do are you cool
i'm cool are you cool i'm cool are you
cool
i'm i'm cool i'm chilling i'm sure
yeah all right i'll go i'll go with you
then this would have been the perfect
time for me to kill you
are you sure are you sure you're not
gonna you're not gonna i don't like the
way you're saying that homie
i think suspicious you guys always think
i was just business
listen man what was that
someone broke a pot
broke a glass did i check that before
is quiet huh
don't waste your don't waste your rocks
don't worry yeah waste your rocks waste
your rocks waste your rocks
why would it be wasting my rugs wait
what
oh god
stop it don't leave me i know
i took out your your fps
i'll throw my things with them oh
foreign
i just know how to play my flashlight's
gone
oh can you make things with this
what this shot's not reloading yeah what
my
ears do no they don't you only have 10.
where's kiara i mean i don't know how to
build things
i'm useless now i got one key girls
coming after me
oh
not available right now please i'll get
them next time i'll get them next time
i think my channel is the official
spectator channel everyone
where could eva be
humans leave a message and she'll get
back to you
where is that i think one of us seems to
be a detective to make it easier
is that english oh yeah
uh
how do you escape
option to just go call god
i know i said that before but really
here you know why can we not just call
the police
nice look nice
nice why can't i find any keys
what inna
who's i don't like it that's me and ena
cali right
cali oh she died
as i said dedicated relationship with
death no one's surprised
it's too bad can i see someone right
yeah i know how that feels
oh what's that i have a dedicated
relationship with that
deaf as well very dedicated
uh-huh i heard that's the word upon the
street
i'm afraid i have two bananas now yeah
what are you gonna do huh
don't mind the floor you slip and die oh
yeah
yeah yeah try it
girls
who are you who are you
that's the girl i don't think she saw
you
wait do i want to run away from her from
there
probably running is the best option wait
what
nothing's nothing don't worry about it
wait the crowd that
doesn't mark the key anymore is it
because i went too far away
possibly uh i think it despawned yeah if
you get the key
oh oh
nice oh no
no i know who's got your key
he's got to keep us cheating
no you gotta throw something at him
wait i thought i thought i already threw
the key
oh wait jared found another
i'm cheating he dropped it in the garage
i meant to throw it
because i didn't want to hold on to it
oh yeah
bait someone be bait yeah be baked
i cannot be basically got to stop
basting from from the ground
callie's going to shut up now back see
gaming from the grave
who's this who's this cute little dyke
come here
oh my god i hate that so much dude
where's the last key kiddos where's the
key
i think you know where it is i know
where it is
oh no wait how many of you are alive
that was so gangster you're such a
gangster
yeah you're really decent at it i'm
sorry
uh one because it's uh
uh in 15 minutes it's half past
like half an hour before kelly's oh yeah
okay one more okay yeah let's make it
one to remember
let's see ah i'm sorry i thought i meant
to leave one person so they could win i
thought there was two people left
my bad nothing me and you oh
okay now i watched my channel who was
the imposter
gura okay okay because at some point she
was talking as if she was
one of us that's big brains
oh waiting on you kali oh sorry i was
looking at characters
all right see
oh cool okay i'll i'll be adventure kid
right
let's go who is it yeah
why is he so creepy i don't look at that
perfectly sculpted stash
perfectly symmetrical
here we go all right this is for the win
maybe not so now we have to find our way
around
it's no
she's smiling when she's talking i can
hear it
where are you following oh are you
normal we should stick together
who are you first candy amelia
jumping okay okay okay here we must
stick together we can
i can uh shoot whoever the wait who's
that
i come in peace i'm giving you my
sponsors
you guys okay you guys find gears tell
me
okay oh gears stay in the same general
maybe it'll be okay i'm gonna go
okay i'll follow you out soon okay
what is this this is you guys seem safe
oh my god where's kiara she's uh somehow
missing out i gotta keep getting
it i wonder hello
just trying to find out why are you
running away it's definitely kiara
it's 500 you
no this is good are you the adventure
kid who's the
me gura oh girl okay cool i i trust
you who's this me i'm i'm really
jumping oh i can jump you press spacebar
to jump i just figured that out
i'm fine i promise you i'm fine
giving you a chance to win this game at
least one time
yeah oh my god it's definitely ugh i
dropped my flashlight
there we go to the front door
let's see oh maybe we can find stuff to
build things huh what
what is that what is that where's the
music coming from
oh i don't like it
where are you guys run i'm i'm not kiara
oh okay you're cool right everyone
yo the jackpot i'm lost who's following
me
oh i can almost ah man i hope i can make
the gun soon
this looks like a secret bookshelf this
is
cute little camper
oh hey people nice
outside oh man i don't have anything to
help you someone was here
well we are really high up i don't know
what i don't understand here i am
how do i get [\h__\h] out i mean oh that's
the f button dude
f button i don't know hey there you guys
are i found you
hi camping the main door if you guys
bring stuff we can kill her
there's a crowbar and any gears up here
i wonder
can i make this jump camera
nope that is the answer to that question
oh
wait i can help you when you give it up
by yourself oh
i have one too i think we have enough to
win but we just need to get to the door
all right i'll be bait i can be a
distraction
uh-oh wait why wait wait
wait wait wait
relax she's uh
nothing what can i take hold on we're
safe here we're safe here guys you guys
see any gears
i had a lot of gears i wonder if you
drop if i drop them
i just have to get back
find any gears you guys hey we're all
alive can you believe this
you've got a shooter i got a gun you
have a gun
i don't know i think how do we get here
wait where'd you guys go first we're
getting back i'm gonna go
back to you guys okay i know what kelly
is
nothing
one more left click left click
put your key on the okay
how come we have two blue keys oh we
need a
and i remember we're gonna die sort of
oh wait
oh wait okay oh wait okay you're still
not back
oh
oh i think she died somewhere around
here what you doing callie
waiting to be bait baked
do we have all the keys kiara's got the
red key
all right let me pick up something here
also has a gun
that's not great news that's just not
great news to be honest
well i'm ready for the fight i'm ready
to brawl
oh chroma crow mark's the key who is
alive
oh we only have a minute and 45.
all right
hey bye hey
here wait wait
why is it making noise like that what
everybody
tried it what he's trying to do i'll
throw this at him
yeah you can grab the key a girl
okay huh
okay she's still she's still outside
don't
tell them you stalker
all right what's the plan here oh
whoa
nice nice nice cool perfect okay
oh do i need to get the blue oh no i
already used the blue one we gotta use a
yellow one
yeah there's no way to find the last key
there's only one key though unless
unless there is you have it go
go go we
hold the hold on your clay
well there's two i think
we need more time
i was pretty close to to dying at some
point so
at two points i think and i'm dead
oh from the first second that that it
was me
i could smell it um you're so obvious
kiara just
the way that you are
can you hear this smile yep you can hear
the smile when you're trying to
deceive us but i i really didn't think
like
i was thinking if i'm gonna be the
imposter i'm definitely gonna
die and this will be the only game that
you're gonna be able to open the door
i did it
yeah i think everyone did one oh yeah oh
nice
that's lucky um cool okay
everyone won everyone won when they were
the killer
oh yeah yeah yeah
at the end definitely definitely
yes yeah yeah that was fun that was
funny
yeah the clown was super fun to play oh
my god that's
awesome
oh yeah basically everyone had a win we
are all winning
yeah yeah winner it's the perfect timing
to end but cali i think you have
something to announce
i do my new song is premiering in 30
minutes
there's a party after that where we're
gonna make drinks i haven't figured out
what we're gonna make yet but i bought a
bunch of stuff
and if you guys go on my twitter you can
see the ingredients i bought if you want
to buy your own similar ingredients so
we can all make drinks together
thank you guys how about you guys do you
have any do you have any other
announcements
i'm making food yay
the only announcement i have is i have a
legendary
collab with marin senpai coming up next
yeah
over so who knows what's going to happen
cali are you jealous if i sleep over at
maddie and senpai's place
do what you want
wait just friends i just want to make it
clear we're just friends okay
as are we
nope not last time i checked that's not
what the ouija board says
what ouija board
uh i have uh i'm gonna post a video in a
little bit uh because cali
is is uh gonna give you guys the last
piece of candy to the halloween
scavenger hunt puzzle
yeah and i'm gonna post the video after
her stream on twitter and you guys can
see the final piece
yeah thanks for
organizing this super cute event
scavenger hunt yeah
thank you and everyone
thanks for watching thanks guys
you