we should play a game I have only
ingredients prepared we have some
chicken the famous One
[Music]
I can't be rocking which is it still an
emote
we have the tomatoes salad and pickles
and we have cheese with onions several
patties and now this is the difficult
part because there's three pieces of
bread I'm ready to play the game ah not
of course on the game it's real
real work it's called uh what's it
called
[Applause]
I'm gonna be looking at the screen to
see what I have to make for the customer
and then I'll make it and we'll see if
it's right
[Music]
bottom
okay I think I have to read freestyle
some of this
I think it was another Patty maybe and
then something green but not all of it I
don't
and then look at that
[Music]
it was almost right it was just oh it's
not fair it's not fair one more one more
one more round two
[Music]
can I already started
I really don't remember I'm so nervous
you can't do this to me I think there
was like at least one chicken in there
give me a break please
[Music]
I don't know
okay
this isn't even supposed to build that
you're making me create things that are
not even possible I'm free please
[Music]
please
bread salad bread meat chicken meat
bread okay if I say it out loud I think
I remember bread salad which one
I'll just go with this one because I
think I would have said cheese if it was
the other one right meat
chicken
meat
oh if I get this right you guys invite
me for better right what ah
I'll go with this okay guys
there's not even cheese in the picture
how am I supposed to remember that
well
I mean
in the end this is your job I'm just
here to observe that's my job okay I
think it's better if I just do mostly
Idol work and dancing and singing right