[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
for do a lot of practice so yeah it's
really helpful for me too and well
that's all I just want you guys to have
fun for today
[Music]
um today
yeah
yeah so uh we'll be watching all of you
guys
will be commenting on every one of your
moves
secretly
yeah and after this what do we have
after this rainy
well we're gonna be having a captain
speech from each of the team
so if we can get the leaders to come up
here please
hey what if I shift shift all right um
[Music]
come on
let's have fun today
[Music]
thank you thank you
later
and
next we have risu
I am ready
[Music]
so yeah let's let's have fun today
[Applause]
yeah I love our team leader who is risu
thank you I love you too I love birthday
[Applause]
thank you
yes I
we saw the leaders and then it's now
time for the full introduction of each
team we can start with three candies
please
[Music]
Amelia from Amelia senpai
hello everybody Emily Watson
let's go let's win
[Applause]
um
moving on uh
bae up to you hey do you want to go
first oh okay what's up it's it's me
it's it's big with red from uh yeah
oh
you're okay
[Music]
go ahead okay hello everyone I'm Anya
let's have fun today
[Applause]
[Music]
Indonesia
all right
next would be a girlfriend
[Music]
who is hitting me
go ahead somebody
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
why yeah
yeah nice nice
nice
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
and next it's time for Team for TV to
introduce themselves
[Music]
thank you
oh sorry
next we have Kyla
oh hello hi everyone my name is
the blacksmith from Polo ID gen3 song
[Music]
oh
all right
[Music]
number one let's party I'm energetic
Yankee
real cool yeah thanks I know
who you are next next next we have Kira
um it's currently 6 a.m
but I am and I am gonna be at badminton
and sucker
oh my God
[Music]
we have Mona
covana it serious fauna from hollow life
English Council thank you for not
putting me on the soccer team
it's fun though
what are you participating in for now I
will be in capture the fort and also the
potato sack race
potato
okay we have soda Senpai those are
as
[Music]
music
yay
next Luna semify
hi
hey hi everybody
my name is
today is
[Music]
yeah yeah
yay
[Music]
I will participating
[Applause]
wow
but you know other than like introducing
the members I kind of want to hear
something more don't you think yeah good
idea yeah all right everybody come up
with their own team cheers
[Music]
um
[Applause]
I'm ready I'm ready
are you ready
let's do it let's do it okay okay
opportunity and so let's do our yeah
yeah yeah yeah let's do it so after me
I'm gonna start okay okay
three two one
oh
foreign
hey
let's go again
[Applause]
[Music]
that was so good yeah
[Laughter]
thank you
let's go let's go okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
two one say candy
hi
guys
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
then wow
so the even today
um we're gonna play a lot of games
starting from capture the port or we
call it bentengan and after that we move
to the puta de secrets and after that we
go tug of war and then after that we
have badminton uh from the a side and
then badminton from a b side and also
after that we have soccer and that's all
cool
that's all I hope you guys having fun
now it's it's time for you guys to uh I
think it's back to the interview should
we interview huh yes right
okay okay
[Music]
okay
games games games
about a minute soccer
[Music]
yes we will be watching closely no
pressure
no pressure at all
we're watching and you have to win for
us but no problem
yes okay
[Music]
where do you watch it from
good question
is there bleachers or there's some seats
over there but this is a nice view
actually okay
we can just walk around I guess okay
yeah
whoa Archer
okay okay
sorry sorry sorry
they're a little too playful
woman is looking at us
which moon is the real moon
he's fine
hello
[Applause]
let's go
it's interviewing time
what are you most afraid of of the other
team nothing
for this game
what is your tactic kailashing we have
we're gonna pick if you win we have we
have secret tactics that we cannot tell
here
audience
yeah you guys will see yeah seems like
you guys have secret secret tactics
yeah I wish you guys the best of luck
okay
thank you yeah okay goodbye
yes okay
um
so yeah I will tell fauna in advance
I've already I've already told fauna
before yes
[Music]
is this like three two one
um division uh-huh so basically one
person go to left and three person go to
the right yeah oh okay okay it's just
like all attacking instead of
understanding
[Music]
ship parts
me
okay let's go ready ready I wanna watch
pretty weird
[Music]
yeah
Z
I want to see
okay
[Music]
go go go go go
go go go go
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
but it's okay
they are Gamers they'll be fun
[Applause]
I don't even know what happened
guys
ah
foreign
[Music]
I know
come on yeah
so they were like opening the doors
their strategy there's strategy like we
thought they wouldn't really use the
middle yeah because because we don't
collected already last night but yeah
okay
so
foreign
but we were like there's a lot of um
success
tactics
Hold On music changed
where do we go now we go back we go back
I think they're interviewing the winner
first yeah oh that's right yeah yeah
okay okay
um
[Applause]
[Music]
oh it's getting crazy
don't hold back don't hold back we'll
hit him all right
get me in the actions
that's good right
rainbow
interview
I think the interview is taking longer
than the game itself
[Applause]
oh whoopsies that's not what I wanted to
do next is oh my God
on the right
[Music]
yeah much bigger
did I didn't know let's get the other
side
oh I went to the wrong place
dummy okay sorry
okay
thank God for that that would have been
tough
let's go let's go
gonna be crazy reason why I accidentally
fell into something you can Goof y
it's okay okay
oh still okay
oh no okay okay okay
let's go let's go let's go
okay okay
don't give up 30 win you guys are great
never give up already whoa
oh what's up
it's bigger oh my God
the door is opening if you like press on
that on this
cool oh
oh
okay
[Music]
we believe in you
we need to restart
okay thank you thank you let's just run
for now I think okay just practice
warm up warming up yeah
yeah
where's everybody
a month
Armstrong in the pot right
the pot
awesome
[Music]
okay okay it's fine it's fine this is
the berries okay
oh
thanks
guys
so sorry we have to restart this it's
okay
yeah but you guys were doing really
great
yeah yeah yeah we were watching and we
were in uh we'll be back to you guys
soon okay okay
thank you
yeah yeah
no problem
it's doing really great I'll try to keep
it up no pressure no pressure no
pressure no pressure I mean at least as
they're like first and second our teams
ready ready ready ready ready ready
buddy watching from above oh yeah I'm
gonna go for I'm gonna go above too
I'm watching spot check it out
let's go
around while watching
yeah we're watching
oh that's nice
foreign
[Music]
because we did really make it clear
beforehand but after this after this
race in the other competitions if there
are connection issues uh I think to also
to make it fair for everybody uh we will
not be restarting uh the competition so
um
just wanted to keep everybody on the
same page
no problem thank you
all right
[Music]
[Applause]
here we go
foreign
tell me
it's nice
oh my God
[Music]
thank you
let's go
let's see you're doing great
online
on the game
[Applause]
oh my God
nice nice
[Music]
oh my God
hey don't worry about it
okay it's okay
for everyone
you
guys were fast plus I mean okay we had
the two fastest people though let's be
real so it is
great it's okay
[Music]
you're amazing
you know what someone in chat said three
candies oh my God
oh my God it was oh my God I shouldn't
have read that
I don't know how to explain it in
Japanese man
that was good okay okay okay okay okay
don't forget to hydrate guys
what what is after it is
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
just thinking about it as like making
making ramen
Ramen yeah
um
yeah the other other person
the pink pink is very strong yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah pink is
stronger
yeah yeah nice let's go oh
no problem
someone ever for anyone who wants to
watch can go up so I think everybody's
already I think we can fly later on yeah
hi
materials okay
[Music]
thank you okay
okay this okay
let's go this is the time where I think
I hope my mouse can get like double
click what because
[Music]
no problem no problem okay wow
foreign
[Music]
let's go let's go okay
oh
here we go
let's go where am I okay
we can fly we can fly
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on
you're gonna get tired
[Music]
um I actually thought we were losing
because when I was practicing we were
fighting I was red team
winner go to this I'll explain later I
thought we were losing
[Music]
that kitty cat die here yes yes
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
Matthew
moving the game area
okay okay
[Music]
oh God
look at this okay okay
let's go
boys
[Music]
thank you we can do it we can win this
what is this next
oh
yeah
first oh so it's Kiara and oh yeah
PR and Kyla a badminton yeah
is Kiara back
she was
is kind of like went somewhere
again
[Music]
hey
[Laughter]
you were so good I was watching you
while I was cooking you should have won
honestly
um
oh yeah you go he also win one the
finger uh competition so I thought that
was great good job
yes yes
finger competition
who's that Strat Yes she'll protect the
back I'll protect the front
[Music]
yeah ready ready
okay I'll try to stay calm because
otherwise otherwise actually in the club
already the ball already fell to the
ground you can't actually I know I know
yeah we have yeah thanks so much
if you feel frustrated just shout like a
real sport yeah
ready yes ready
let's just start right away who who has
the first
one okay okay ready ready guys
okay
let's go
they could shoot anymore now okay there
we go oh
[Applause]
good job good job the defense
that was so weird
no problem
where is it
oh
okay
it's on your side I don't see it
freaking nervous I'm so nervous don't
worry you're doing great
[Music]
nice save
it's out
because it's going towards the wrong
side yeah
you have to hit the like
yeah the opposite side for the first
hits after the first hit you can hit
wherever you want basically
I'll take it
okay thank you
[Music]
okay thank you foreign
um
that might go out
nice backup
[Music]
you guys did amazing
we'll take it again
my job here is almost done yeah
oh my God please win let's go let's go
let's win this
[Music]
already
um
everybody
wasn't ready yeah that's fine
[Music]
okay okay
wait
yeah
looking good okay okay
[Music]
okay I mean in real life
something you would do
this
okay don't mind don't mind
do you pass in badminton in real life do
you pass to your teammate
we only can possibly do like one thing
okay
cycle
okay okay
it was in her own field
I can have TV come back
[Applause]
okay
yeah
I'm enjoying this too much
winning feels good
[Applause]
too high that's no problem
[Music]
[Applause]
we sweep
let's go so Kyle interview too oh should
I know yeah yeah yeah okay
oh no
yeah
yeah of course Point wise we did yes oh
oh my god let's go
right now
thank you thank you so basically after
this soccer will be like the what is it
called
the it would be the deal breaker yeah
yeah soccer designs at all yes nice so
if you want to win win the soccer if
they want to win they have to win the
soccer do you guys thank you guys
we will win we will win
oh man
of course of course we have to know
because winning it just felt so good
right now I want more of that please
but like seriously you guys are like
really good at like uh hitting the we
are practicing thank you yeah
evening yeah we practice a lot together
yeah and honestly like Kyla was a great
backup to have behind me like she was
managing the backside and I was managing
the front but they normally shot a lot
of like shots to the very far back so
you know Kyla was always there to
support me thank you
everything
I want to play more badminton yeah
is very strong
support support and
can you keep the server online so I can
play more badminton for the coming
months
actually everyone be freely to play yeah
yeah yeah
foreign
okay so they said that there's 10 point
difference and soccer is gonna make the
big difference yeah we are leading but
we still need to win the soccer yeah
should I maybe try to stay in a certain
area like close to the goal or so any
any uh
uh uh Kiara and Kyla uh are both great
at uh striking right yeah
let's forward while the uh the others
can I think at least one tries to stay
back and guard uh without being yeah
somebody has to stay around the goal
like at least in the area roughly around
the goal otherwise yeah bye okay yeah
before EOP okay okay second goalkeeper
can you can I translate in Japanese oh
please do
um no no no no no like this is just a
little little information that you can
actually dribble the ball oh you're
actually clicking well oh really yeah
yeah it helps a lot
besides just shooting
um
okay
[Music]
yes
and and break after 10 minutes
pressure
[Music]
run
um
are we automatically running no no I I
think you always have to press
yes my little finger gets tired from it
after a while but uh because I'm
pressing it nothing's changing so it is
as well but but but it's like wow maybe
we should
eat bread
wait what where is it where is it where
is it okay okay okay okay
they sent it out they sent it out pass
it
yeah
to your friends
oh
yeah
don't worry don't worry don't worry we
have 20 minutes we have a lot of okay
okay hold hold okay
don't worry
don't worry don't worry
oh it's okay
um
sometimes it just disappears it is
[Laughter]
can she be that close okay
[Music]
get out of the gold town
go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go
Watson's a really good goalkeeper
we have so much time
all right
okay who is it who is it okay okay
go go go go go go go oh shoot that was
before oh sorry
okay okay okay okay what does that mean
go kick don't worry okay don't worry
right side okay go oh
okay I gotta redo okay okay
[Music]
go go go go go go go go go no no no no
no no no no no no no
go go go go go go go go go oh
[Music]
I'll be just staying close too okay
please
sometimes I'm not sure which direction
it went
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
it was not fast enough
okay oh
thank you
okay okay
and take it to the left too again all
right all right
yeah it's like a real soccer match okay
okay okay we're gonna take it to the
left again go go go go go go take it
take it
okay okay
guys
got it yeah oh no oh nice enough
five minutes until break okay okay we
still have times
okay
nice okay
um I need to stay close I need to stay
closer to here
I'm gonna go into the right side
oh
really where's she gonna okay send it to
come here
I feel like it always goes further than
you might think
[Music]
okay hey wait hold on
good defense
yeah they're turning around is difficult
yeah
you feel like you're running I didn't
feel like I am but I'm not holding
control
I'm sorry
ah
it is
close one
wait are we already in the second half
yeah
another seven minutes confuse me
oh
nice nice
okay
here we go
[Music]
intense they're Betty Betty where's the
bowl
yes let's go
go go
oh oh wow he came back to me all right
I've got to stay back here in case they
increase
yeah yeah go back go back
what the
okay okay
let's go come on come on come on
[Applause]
oh
my God
it's okay
yeah I did I didn't know soccer will be
this oh yeah
this is how real stalker works
[Music]
yeah no definitely do that oh that was
that was upon eyes that was a blue night
yes
oh
thank you
it's okay it's okay no problem
Kelly Kelly
okay
[Music]
kick it
yeah maybe just scratch yeah
you can bring it back in the second half
yeah yeah oh my God we have to be maybe
a bit more aggressive
I wonder if maybe I should not defend it
I should strike instead no I think it's
gonna do this okay you're good okay I
feel like I'm doing a bad job no you've
been doing a good job
I think we need more defense though
because we can because we can just kick
the ball to the front we don't need like
that much of like you know we don't need
much of the attackers oh okay defensive
yeah so if we got the ball just kick it
okay yeah
um
[Music]
then it might be hard it might be hard
to get points if we're Yeah because
sometimes when the when the ball finally
goes over to like the goal side the red
goal side I feel like then often there's
like only coyote Senpai there and
nobody's helping her I should be closer
to the goal honestly Okay so
um
eat the whole
time
yeah they're going to be more defensive
100 because they're winning so we we
really need to be aggressive I think
okay
um
[Music]
I'll get it
all right
okay
they were interviewing pickles yeah I
think I need to be more in the central
area
[Music]
nice nice
um
oh
[Music]
yeah
let's just be Senpai and Kauai
I said she's been streaming like at
least for the amount of four years even
though she's only been around for 1.5
years
thank you
boys
bad weather by the way I really hope I
don't DC oh don't worry it's over soon
just 10 more minutes okay
just gonna tell Kobo to chill out chill
chill out
stop stop making rain
sort of a goalkeeper yeah get her out of
there we have to follow her I need foul
options
option
I want to kick them
I'm gonna I want to make them stumble
yeah
as if we have any strategy okay just
just leave it to Lady Luck I guess maybe
there's a miracle comeback yeah yeah
[Music]
um
yeah
she said we have no strategies
wow but our strategy is stronger defense
stronger aggressive everything stronger
okay
let's go
pick quarters
[Applause]
[Music]
okay nice nice kick it off
I
I don't okay
get ready ladies here we go
all right
bring it back
okay okay
um Watson day
yeah she's really good
um Watson
where is she gonna where is she gonna go
okay
no no
no I'm right over my head I wish I could
jump better
[Music]
we can't close it from there I don't
know if we can shift from ah I don't
think the rules are that realistic
it's better to try
what are they gonna do
oh
yeah
it's so aggressive I think we need
somebody doing what is doing over by the
goal can we just follow her
okay
she had no chance it's the goal three
versus one okay
nope
okay
the thing is like I also still have to
turn around every time they're already
looking in the right direction we have
to turn around it's so difficult to get
around the ball
[Music]
are we
it's tonight
it's not your fault
good try good try
guys no worries
we can surprise them they're gonna let
their guard down
aggressive the aggressive guy so loud
I'm ready I'm ready
you might go sideways yeah but nah
nah she wants to go to gura but she
failed she failed
it's gonna be tactical about it okay
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah come on shoot to me what's
about amituri don't we love each other
fun
day
all right nope
got me f'd up over here
Watson's too good
no
okay
[Music]
all right
okay okay
[Music]
all right
you're welcome
thank you
[Applause]
never stop stop
okay
come back
protect me Cali all right I'm trying
okay
at least I scored
[Music]
she wants to confuse us
okay
all right we're here we're here let's go
let's go
[Music]
if we can tie with them we just need to
tie with them yeah
that would be good
no no no no no no no no no okay come on
it's fine it's fine it's fine
defense defense right yeah defense
okay I'm here
I want to do penalty kicks they're fun
yeah
what we gotta do to get penalty kicks
get ready
okay okay defense defense defense
nice nice
defense defense
okay
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
you gotta steal it
nope Cali go go
ahead
and can we get extension
yeah you cannot extension you know like
10 minutes oh
okay
was was a good momentum
nice nice
does fly
it is it's flies I'm gonna get take it
to the left all right there you go
nope nope nope nope
[Music]
nope nope nope nope nope
whatever happens this was a lot of fun
yeah
[Music]
I
have the best team
[Music]
okay
I like them
ah
I don't know
[Music]
okay
definitely they needed her to be there
one more
we didn't even have penalty yeah
at least it was close it wasn't like
they completely destroyed us right yeah
yeah not not like Pokemon unite or
anything like that
even Pokemon unite we did decently but
there was literally do not get gas lit
into thinking that we didn't do well in
that time okay
even though I was watching it was it was
it was really awesome
um
the whole time
good thank you
[Music]
do you want to get taller taller I mean
if I got tall taller I I might can reach
the ball who knows
[Music]
no no we're all the same height midnight
shop
look at our bodies were all the same
not even wrong
foreign
[Music]
I really enjoy all the games even the
ones I didn't participate in so I would
love to participate in all
but badminton easy I think the map is
open until
yeah I think somebody said 21. 20
something something so yes everybody
wants to try it by yourself
Kyla not asking anybody
I'm still trying to get a friend to play
the top of War because I really love
that one my hand is crying
I'll play against you Kyla anytime yeah
no
yes yes no no no no if it's me only no
no I think I don't have the stamina
don't worry I can maybe do it alone
again Skyla oh yeah
I will just die but you know
yeah
it's good games
just a game and that's done
everyone to BC okay
this
okay
when did I look cool yes
we should have been cheerleading where
are your pom-poms
you mean in front of your heart
how strong are you now though getting
punched like this yeah how does it feel
she likes it though Kelly don't you know
she likes it you sure about that just
like back in the day
it's pink
slap slap
give me five stars
Emma did you play soccer in real life
before or what I have I have oh
never had a prayer
[Music]
announcement time
announcement are you announcing your
wedding with someone
congratulations
[Laughter]
[Music]
it was intense and well after all of
those intense game will be announcing
the winners
yeah so first of all from the bending on
the capture the fourth
the winner
with 40 points yes
and then we also have the sack race with
30 points yet again three can you win so
that brings us to a total of 70 points
[Music]
and then Renee what's the next one the
next one was tug of war
in which it was a blue versus pink team
OMG
four how many points pink 40 points
[Music]
and then badminton again two matches
both won by perfily so 20 plus 20 so
another 40 points for per Theory
after three candy was leading pretty we
managed to catch up by 10 points and
then that's where soccer came in and
became the deal breaker yeah
Watson too strong and we are happy to
announce that the winner of the whole ID
cup is the
figure
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
too
I am number one in Elena's heart
[Laughter]
we are going to be awarding the medals
right
yes the team captain please distribute
the medals to your teammates hi I will
distribute
all right
I sent it please
everybody
I put it on now
yeah
[Music]
death metal yes
let me see hey what if I just put on the
gold medal anyway yeah put it on
access to the gold but maybe I'm gonna
put on where it is
[Music]
it's my medal now my medals
the pink one is the pink one is cuter
anyway
[Music]
[Applause]
just like the opening we will be asking
for a few words by each team captain
starting from three candy teams
[Applause]
no no
yeah
[Music]
wow that was it that was really fun
really really fun and
um
can we do oh can we do the
um the the yellow together again let's
do it again
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay let's go okay
okay okay
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
everyone did
um everyone did their best doing the
games
thank you thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for playing with us as well
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
please
[Music]
first I would like to say thank you for
all for dating to uh to actually make
time for this and also I love birthday
theme because they are all
um hardworking so they practice too
oh my God I just I just love the team so
much I love you too
[Music]
yeah
thank you so much everybody thank you so
much for inviting us
this year was really fun thank you
[Music]
one last time
[Applause]
hello
thank you
[Music]
thanks to you
[Applause]
[Music]
lastly foreign
together
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
uh
[Music]
okay yeah
okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
guys can do it now in your own free time
okay
[Music]
should we just go fly up so we can get
like all the time
oh that would be cool
one of the balloons to ships
okay she'll teach us how to fly in
Minecraft wow please yes
I can't get the
game has been updated to creative mode
here there it is
[Music]
all right my hands are a little strong
ah double jump Oh I thought it was just
one jump okay double jump oh sorry it's
okay it's okay it's okay
all right
[Applause]
um
[Music]
are you taking
I'm flying all right let's go let's get
in the dragon in the dragon dragon's
mouth and uh yeah there we go cool
dragon's eyebrows
yeah a dragon's head cool
um
foreign
oh so please make sure that I'm in the
middle so I can get like a better
picture
okay
[Music]
can go in front
um
we can go a little bit
in front yeah
or is it good enough like this name
oh hi all right
okay
this works
this one's nice this one is nice
I'm down now
all right
okay I got one
we got two
um
okay we look us everybody everybody look
up how um
[Music]
look up
perfect
perfect and my chocolate side please
get my good side
make me look good okay okay I think it's
done
sign in
yeah
[Music]
I want to see what's in this ship this
ship is cool oh yeah there's so I ate
box so before wow so yeah yeah I hated
in Indonesia oh and the other one I
don't remember the other one she look
Soto wow I'm an explorer
I'm gonna send the pictures
[Music]
wow
I wonder when the Japan
sports festival is Japanese one yeah
what a
to be an announcement about that
Japanese is Japan in window Kai I
believe
yeah I got it okay wait wait wait wait I
need I need to close my stream first
okay wait was it invitation invitation
only or stream two we we can stop the
stream now yeah okay okay thanks
everybody let me go back
[Applause]
thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
foreign
like button please
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]