first album
point of view
pineapple
[Music]
love Rush
the great Wanderer
[Music]
retrospective
true
[Music]
trying beings
sleep talking bro
[Music]
hinatori
heart Challenger
[Music]
spikes
let me do something new I don't need no
drinks tonight
[Music]
I can't complain
first album
point of view
pineapple pineapple
[Music]
it every every day
I'm walking back
[Music]
[Applause]
to you baby
[Music]
heart Challenger
Sparks
[Music]
okay
stream carroted Grady what
karate
karate karate what
ah
what the [\h__\h] does that even mean
it's oh it's another word for heart
really
ah okay
no that's not how he wrote it though
cardiac extreme cardiac arrest
you under arrest
no I am under cardiac arrest
what what's up what's a Leo in the
context of a of a police situation
tell me
it's a all law enforcement office ah
[Laughter]
and they said something about Leo and
then she was like
oh my God you're August birthday oh my
God you I can't believe that I'm dealing
with an August birthday
it's about the the videos I was linking
in pre-chat um uh police body for it uh
of them trying to uh get a teenager out
of the car of her dad because she's
[\h__\h] entitled uh and and then
she's like so unintentionally funny
uh
her comment to something about when they
say something about a Leo she's like oh
my God August birthday ain't you
oh man
okay
[Laughter]
so stupid oh that's so good
and as you went to jail
yeah I mean I don't even
I don't and I think it's funny how some
people get kind of like really into like
astrology and like oh my God you you are
a scorpion or whatever or this and that
and that's why I can't date you or
that's why I can't date you blah blah
blah it's funny but not that I would
believe in any of that being meaningful
to anything at all
yeah surprising huh
you guys probably thought oh oh oh oh oh
she's a girl she must be into freaking
star signs
that is such a cancer move no way
counters are like super emotional
[Music]
[Laughter]
any friends that are into that I don't I
wouldn't know that if any of them were
like really really into it like I I
don't hear them ever mentioning it but I
do see like when I watch Like American
kind of
um YouTube videos like I don't know like
you know like like
like videos where real people are being
put into YouTube videos
in America they every so often bring up
like
um
the whole star thing like when they
introduce each other they're like oh my
God so what's your star sign
I feel like
it's it's uh Americans are very into
that American Zoomers maybe
also partially Millennials though
yeah
I think it's like interesting to read
your horoscope but
no need to put like too much
[Music]
um
too much weight into it
it's funny though it's an American thing
I think so too but don't worry don't
worry don't worry Japanese people people
do the same thing with blood types
typical for an idol introduction or even
when you're not an idol is telling them
your blood blood type and then it's like
oh my God what you're a B I knew it what
do you mean you knew that I was B I mean
I'm not I'm not that I don't even
remember my blood type
did you guys know that they put a lot of
weight into your blood type
in in Japan
[Music]
best type of blood is for blood
all like Koreans uses mbti together okay
that one is like really complicated I
don't I never took a test like that I
think but if that's like a really
I could see how that could be I mean
isn't that like a really complicated
personality test doesn't that kind of
make sense at least
a bunch of women who were talking on the
ground Zodiacs having certain tourism
house totally true
[Music]
really hard not to notice that a blood
type thing is really present yeah right
yeah blood type oh what's your blood
type
oh
my God
and bti is also just a general
categorization nothing more serious oh
really
scientific sounding nonsense but it's
still nonsense
ah isn't it doesn't that even cost money
like maybe it's you know
like maybe it's all
let me put my tinfoil hat on maybe it's
all just a money machine from the
government
hey it's free wasn't there something
that costs money when you do the big
test
or so
make something like popular
for for young
cult what do you call it
pop culture whatever
um
make it like a like the Zodiac and and
then and then and then ask money for it
not that cultist I'm not trying to say
that quick shout it out
you could take a more official test
rather than one of them maybe maybe I'm
mixing something up though
because I thought there was something
that costs money if you do the big one
good morning good morning indeed you
bought this game because of me oh tell
that to Baldur's Gate or to Larry and
Studios and Wizards of the Coast tell to
them
oh wait chat should probably go
somewhere else
[Music]
um
then really enjoying the beautiful app
thank you I have um
uh
oh
where does Wizards of the Coast to the
publisher
or is and Larry in studios is the
developer or is the lion Studios also
the publisher
like sometimes the developers also the
publisher but
oh
lion is a deaf
are they only
oh because I was just thinking if if
Wizards of the Coast is the publisher
but they also published The Magic the
Gathering
cool
lion is Indy oh yeah yeah I mean I've
heard that and I can't really believe it
how are they indeed look at what the
[\h__\h] they created that's insane
that's actually insane
so I have a problem you know in our
collab game we finished the goblin
Temple that's all we did in the last
stream basically for three hours now
question
um at least I didn't stream it so we
could do that again obviously we have to
I have to get through it anyway right
but do I still have other things to do
uh besides that because I was thinking
maybe I should do the goblin Camp uh off
stream but I don't even know if I have
enough besides the goblin camp
yeah still a lot of stuff to do
it
I have a few more in the area um
okay we'll see I guess I look around a
little bit and if we run out of things
to do I guess we'll go to the goblin
Temple again at least now uh thanks to
narissa Leading The Way
I know exactly what to do
more or less I mean I already forgot
honestly but like who to start with but
at least you know all right we're here
ah
and uh we're here with Carlos
if you remember
um
we were not allowed in the city at the
moment with all of our team
you're really not have salt
we're only here with Carlos right now
because otherwise we're being put in
jail
uh
um
yeah
um should I
do some
things should I
should I do something should I maybe do
I need these stones or are they just for
selling or can I also like craft
something with them
is that you
what did you say Urban bring your
friends if you found yourself okay just
selling
you shouldn't be alone infernal iron oh
yeah yeah we need to find oh wait
is that isn't that what we should be
doing then finding infernal Iron Works
we took the quest last time I suppose
and we didn't get it yet right
and some of you guys said it's
relatively easy to get actually
I want this
uh it's on your map is it right
[Music]
ah there's something down here yeah okay
we can go there what's this Tea House
what
that's the temple
okay then I think the first thing we
should do is find this infernal iron tea
house is fun yeah
what's the Tea House
can we can we have a tea ceremony there
I once once in my life I participated in
a tea ceremony
um in Japan like when I was like
just on on another one of my million
trips in Japan
and I just wanted to do something
touristy because often I just don't even
do anything touristy I was like I need
to do something something to to say I
did something and then I booked a
one-on-one tea ceremony in like uh one
of the fancy hotels in in Tokyo uh a lot
of the fancy hotels in Tokyo they just
like have a lot of things to do even if
you don't stay at the hotel they just
offer a lot of cool things like you know
like all those all-you-can-eat buffets
that are themed after something oh yes
but they had this really cool
um
is there anything you need to shut this
on the Cell at first if you do just some
bits and bobs
yeah this is really professional oh wait
he has no money anymore who else is
selling [\h__\h] or buying [\h__\h]
uh
the old lady regular my regular what's
my regular
isn't it the Smith I just talked to I
don't know he didn't want to sell bye
huh
um but yeah yeah
Tea Ceremony was really
um relaxing
and it was a really really really really
strong green tea
freshly poured
um cool experience
see he only asked me to do infernal iron
bring your friends if you found some
infernal iron
what do they won't buy it's okay my my
inventory isn't even that full but I got
some [\h__\h] to sell
I need to talk to him with someone else
um but everybody else is not really
welcome here
[Laughter]
uh okay
um where could we
teleport to me I guess
everything's so far
I guess
I guess I'll just go to Emerald grass
1.5 million Subs almost yeah do your
part And subscribe
where's everybody else
um
ah you guys are still at the camp oh
are we ending didn't I realize fine
except for Wawa never dull moment should
we sleep for one more oh we should I
guess
uh wait does Carla have to be in the
camp in order to also get the benefits
of a long rest
the thing is we don't have any more
short rests right so we should probably
sleep
um
she is okay good she was automatically
reported into the camp good good good
good good
down by the river
uh
that's not I don't understand what who
wants that oh that's what they mean
oh who said that okay I make your day
better I was just thinking about you oh
no and that delicious moment we shared
the other one oh no is this like leading
to where I think it's leading already
I'm not ready for this
uh is the audio Fine By the way should I
make it louder
uh Savor the memory it won't happen
again
and you
were
how did you survive until now I've only
ever fed on beasts oh drinking the blood
of thinking creatures is a different
thing entirely
we're delectable
um I can't tell but wonder how the
others taste duck
if you
try yourself at the next of my other I
mean you can do Shadow heart I don't
care but I dare you you don't even try
anything with Carly
um
next I'm hurt
oh I was getting tired of them anyway
whoa we're not killing them
they're not them
yeah they might not be as open to the
idea it doesn't hurt to ponder the
question though
take Gail for example he strikes me as
someone whose blood is Rich refined like
well-aged brand okay but the gift
in the Hills would she tastes like
okay you can try her I don't care
maybe I'll get a bit jealous though
um
yeah I don't I don't think she would
really engage in this conversation much
it looks a bit we have an interesting
conversation
intrigued by the possible
he really answered to what I just say RL
notice
[Music]
could I convince you to kill someone
that's useful
no one's getting killed I swear we're
just two friends talking
so
in the spirit of theoretical questions
if you had to take a bite from one of
them
who would it be
me
uh uh the dog is so cute jumping around
in the back I I
mean is this
would this imply a romantic interest in
someone
maybe Carla Jones although the more I
think on it the hungrier I get I better
go find something I can actually get my
teeth into
me don't don't bite the dog either okay
stay away from our next bye bye
oh my God oh my God make him stop
I want to cuddle with doggle while we're
sleeping
that's sleeping
yeah all right
I want to talk to Carla here we go I
like Gail but I'm keeping all my good
gear I didn't ask about Gail
everything fancy he touches meets a
grisly end
grizzly bear
what is she talking about here goes
nothing let's go I thought we would have
a little bit more of a conversation but
I guess not that's okay the hollow okay
Halloween
get everyone here again Target yeah
she's too far right if we just teleport
two over here
oh we can stay together Carla you're
following us right now now you're
falling okay
okay let's go to
um
here so up down something like that
or is there maybe the lower path too
maybe I can try the lower path because
the map isn't filled out there either
okay how's time where is the tea house
is it like this thing here
so
it's called tea house when I'm like not
showing the thing but here it doesn't
say tea house
a tea house is so far but okay is it is
it a part where I fight all right let's
do the iron iron
infernal internal
Eternal [\h__\h] wrong way
the island let's get the iron when
hmm
foreign
guys I'm still kind of tired
oh
[Music]
the bridge
we shall cross the bridge
is anything interesting here is this the
path to the
uh to the owl bear
what's this
ah it's just another one of those uh
containers
okay
sleep tracking yeah I was sleep twerking
all night sleep twerking
in the night yeah sleep twerking oh
that's right yeah
they're gonna make me sleep truck every
day every night
is this camp supplies
it's not camp supplies right 20 bucks
for a knife is quite a lot
ah a broken loot
um
but I'm not gonna loot the broken loot
I'm not interested in your broken loot
[Music]
can't adhere it Ryan
oh time to loot the dead travels oh nice
useful things actually
yeah
Squall of sleep skull of witch Bolt one
step and some armor
nice wow nice loot
goblins drawings
why is this why is this orange is it
like a
like a quest item
there's quite much time there myself
oh recipe
let's pick up all these morsels I hope
they're not
cute poisonous can you guys
stop talking my check
which boat the witch bald
yeah I will read it just give me a
moment I'm uh perception failed what are
we perceiving what did we try to
perceive
yeah
the Dead Sea fling a lot
where are we all right
wait what the infernal heart already
okay cool cool cool where's the letter
um wait did I know
this one
I think
right is it this
scuffed hand bills stands with an extra
extravagant seal Bollywood climbs
adventurous one no is this it
no that's not it
who got the thing I just picked up on it
am I blind
something
like a letter
I chat died oh there you are might be on
the court
this is empty though
[Music]
I'm blind
first row in my inventory this thing
really yeah
love the gloves what gloves
ah see it's this it's not the one in my
inventory okay
it didn't look like a ladder Brown and
thick charcoal lines upon an animal skin
this chat like portrayed the pics free
stick figures the goblin with Sparks
sometimes in its hands a square humanoid
figure and what seems to be an elf each
of them is wearing a simple this was
really uninteresting oh
Journal updated
some Goblin Quest what which one which
one
this one
they are free the guns must have more
than one liter if the teethlings are to
make their way to balder's gate we will
need to deal with the goblins the floor
thinks someone must be organizing them I
should investigate again that's okay I'm
gonna I was gonna go inside anyway
okay
um
um before I go inside I wanna
yes
egg
Charming Little Egg it's just like you
guys where are my charming little eggs
you charming
I'm gonna I thought there was a trap for
a moment
because it was a net and it was emptying
down down
oh wait is this oh
oh
isn't this isn't this isn't this I think
isn't this the place isn't this the
place
didn't I partially enter this place from
a different side
um
but also isn't this the place where we
were fighting I went up here
looking ahead
this is the place
[Music]
let's go can't use accent surprise
can't climb why am I so surprised on my
step
there we go
a Starion starts
well I don't even where are they where
they're so inside
they're over here
okay
uh has look again I want to hide I could
already hide here
I'll hide
time for you and I'll try I don't know
if I can I
uh no because I got a disadvantage
oh well then is there anything else I
could do
um
because they're all like inside
[Music]
he could also go up but I kind of
I know I don't want everybody to go up
there
dude I just don't
nice
get drunk off that Choppers in Camp I'm
Fair
oh
I like how they're having their own
conversation over there oh hey this is
actually oh wow a nice oh a nice little
house whoa they got the fight they left
the stuff on the stove should I tell the
enemies like hey no time for fighting
you left your stove on wow I killed oh
wait oh this was supposed to be an
actual Village before huh
this is so cute look at this
I'm I'm I'm fascinated
we can get some cool stuff here
a portion of sleep
anyway anyway
ah hi
little yawn all the time God damn it let
me let me get one big yawn and everybody
oh
[Music]
um
I think I slept quite well though by the
way I'm quite uninterrupted I didn't
even get up for Smoothie I don't think
she annoyed me enough tonight
good cat good baby
why do I have to start with a Starion
can he not get up there a different way
[Music]
okay okay okay we'll go up here for now
but then we can't oh wait there's
someone here oh
okay we will go up there maybe
guess we won't be hiding anymore though
can I hide behind myself behind the
kiwawa
was this again vampire but ah yeah we
have vampire bite now
do we have advantage against them now
yes
I think so no
okay
that's 56 that's 65.
oh 75. let's go yep
[Music]
does that work no okay hold on
you're gonna push me down though oh miss
good morning from Canada Oh Canada
Oh Canada
how beautiful are your maple leaves
I won't be in Toronto
on the weekend
um on Sunday Oh Canada
Oh Canada
is this not your national anthem
I thought it was just kidding I don't I
know it's not
um why is everybody on High Ground what
do I do with Carla how do I get up there
over here maybe I will Dash
uh that show
that's to the ikima show
oh
there's a lot of people
does she have anything oh wait chat
I thought I was on Carlock
[\h__\h]
well great
great
yeah anyway tomorrow I'll be in Toronto
at an anime convention I mean I won't be
there in person but I'll be there
virtually
so I hope to see you guys there yes live
with Wayne
mm-hmm
so what I'm gonna do with
oh
what am I doing wait where's Dash I will
I will Dash with her
find the button
I've got it
oh okay yeah we're having a paponashi
panel
let's go
what is this frenzy Aya I don't think we
need to frenzy yet although it could
then we can get another bonus action in
the next time because this is 10 turns
anyway huh
because we're all Shadow heart you know
I guess I'll do it now
tell me if that was a bad idea
ends early if you don't attack an animal
attack damage oh
wait this turn is fine right
don't make it end too early
um so
and
heck City hexy
I don't know I don't know we have a
little Constitution
and then we'll Albert's blast
oh
almost fell into that hole
no okay
I'll go a little bit on the roof so
maybe they
can't push me down that easily
if they attempt
[Music]
and the missing again
are you telling me I can hide when I'm
standing here how is he not seeing me
what
is it looking that direction
I mean
what was that
oh well
I want to try the sneak attack series
it's gonna work oh 91. sheesh
or
or yeah yeah
kill him beautiful
Master sneaker stealth 100.
I activated your Alexa what did I say
I do that a lot yeah
I don't know man it's because I'm
virtual and she's virtual probably so we
have a a pretty good connection Maybe
Alexa stream point of view from
takanashikiara
[Laughter]
Siri play a point of view from takanasi
Kiara
please tell me it worked for someone
hey Siri stream point of view from
takanasi Kiara
hey hey
foreign
the Japanese one too
pressing a specific song
Hey Alexa stream uh enough
let me try again sorry Alexa hey
play pineapple by takanasikiara
hey Siri play pineapple butter hey Siri
okay just covering all my bases you know
okay
Alexa heard you but didn't understand oh
my God
no German hey Alexa should be a little
bit uh pineapple from takanasi Kiara hey
Siri pineapple
thank you
hey Google how do you talk to Google Aya
okay Google play pineapple
okay
okay okay I tried everything I tried
everything
ah they agree but they don't understand
no
no Google
what did they say that they asked what
do you mean who's takanashikiwawa
okay still can't go there not far not
not close enough is it even worth going
in though you know it's like
is it even worth because I can just try
to shoot them what's in here
this is so stupid
[Music]
yeah I know she can shoot but she has a
disadvantage I want to give her an
advantage
and jump
[Music]
oh what that's such an under unrealistic
uh jump wait I I don't have enough
movement anyway
um oh because she would have to go a
little bit further back I went actually
too close
really
I didn't think and well here says too
high
yeah no that doesn't work now
shouldn't have moved first
oh
um
uh I never know what to do with her for
attacking
I guess I'll try some fire
40.
but it's so [\h__\h]
guiding build
um which one was that I had this one
65 I guess that's okay
just stay where you are girl
no wow it works for once
wow
I am surprised
missed again
[Music]
okay
ah can I make it ah with a dash yeah but
then I can't
I could push them though but then what's
the meaning of me getting up there in
the first place
jump
how could I jump
I can't I can only get to the ladder but
I guess
[Music]
jump first and move oh
no no
oh
wait should I um
no now I can't I think
oh sexy
damage
bye right behind you
okay there's still someone here
it's reapply although
he's very weak already
ah I missed unbelievable
yeah wait what just
ah
I hate when that happens once oh yeah
it's been a while
I hate that so much that's so stupid
I quit oh
okay but now I don't really need I could
have missed this step somewhere I guess
hmm
um
yeah well great no
I guess I'll I'll
try like getting not too far really
see that's how you do it
don't really need to do that though but
you colic is sick no
no
hiding
shooting uh
can I not shoot from down here
oh man
bonus action Dash
bonus bonus action
wow wow
wow
he's dashing while sneaking I don't know
if you can really call that dashing but
I guess it's because he's staying in his
sneak
should we try something sexy
spicy
[Music]
a key
snake bashing snake snake
okay cool
Shadow heart
no we're gonna we're gonna
um
[Music]
oh I could jump to here
hi surprise I mean Shadow heart isn't
really the ideal person to do this but
okay
um
what do we do
probably not that
why is it all so low
I know for the range for tax is stupid
because I'm too close but
this is so magnificent
I want to shoot it with fire
inflict inflict wound
inflict food
inflict wound
this thing
oh
yeah that was powerful last time I used
it too wait wait wait
a little bit too powerful
okay
who's left only this one
oh maybe that one is still standing
no this is the last one for now maybe
[Music]
we can just do normal
anything really
I win
I don't win
oh wait where's my breath what oh over
there
this guy doesn't even know we exist yet
I think but okay what path lies before
me this path let's do it correctly
when do I have one for dexterity
no right
I do
you guys told me before that really
doesn't matter but like in my logic
strength
in my brain in my smart little small
brain I would think that if I applied
strength and they would attack less
strong and if I apply decks then maybe
there's a lower chance of them dodging
what do I know really I don't know
you always text con Constitution what do
you think that would do
exteriority is correct it can low IC yay
okay
you didn't die
um
and then you hide down there so that I
can get you with a stereon oh mama maybe
I can though
maybe I can
be quick
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
no they don't
Nani
ah
okay
next question then use a spell that
gives poison debuff this is
the strength only anything else is
useless I usually hex the highest stats
if that's what they need to cast attack
apply Depots hex only affects the
building chest doesn't apply to save so
see or attack damage
ah confusing Reno I don't understand
for the lava their chance of
successfully pushing you though it does
nothing to their attacks
excellent Constitution doesn't do much
because hex does not affect saving froze
accidentally affects skill checks which
is stuff like shoving people
[Music]
where's hex is best was probably oh
wow
well
[Music]
what I get from that is that hex is kind
of useless
most of the time so
I just do it for
completion's sake I guess
can we have her just stay here and then
because then I want to explore the house
afterwards on her side I'll just have
her
no wait
um
[Music]
there's there's no one left
oh you know what I'll do with her turn
can I burn this
oh
and you guys just finished it I don't
want to finish it
your choice of which hacks is almost
useless it adds 1 to 69 damage on each
oh
oh oh okay
oh okay
uh
kalak is done here ah there's one down
here
jump
oh we could get damage if we jump this
far but we could
we could
well no I might do it
I might just do it
I'm gonna see that jump wow whoa
I mean worth it don't you think
kill him yeah
didn't we just have 94 percent
wasn't there just 94 advantage
94 I didn't like imagine that right it
wasn't in my dream right
I don't know
what the [\h__\h]
you've ruined my role I was on the roll
not a dice roll I was like on a roll you
know
[Music]
all right
all right then
um can't slow down
can I get him from here no
Mamma Mia oh mama me
[Music]
um
let me go you know I was thinking of Mr
I could go here
no no no no no no no this has to work
I could shoot Carla
why would I do that now why would I do
that ah
come on what do you mean
it was the crazier things in there
the [\h__\h] fence I've seen them I've
seen enemies shoot for shelves before in
the last collab
like come on like literally I saw that
I'm gonna sue them
for being freaking biased
I don't know
that's so stupid
um
more and more I am
understanding though
how to deal with a sterion
it's
fascinating just like
that's a 94 baby
I wonder what the next move is we will
investigate this village now
it sounds [\h__\h] because shouldn't there
be
the iron in here hmm
loot time yeah where do I even start
like there's so much oh my god let's
start with
um
tanakisha
we
we go in here there's still someone
alive over there I think I need to find
A Way Forward
live here it's so cute
it looks so comfy actually even it even
though it's freaking worn down yeah
this looks like my mom's bed like she
has a
currently has a really old like
an antique looking
can I do with this it's still me even
after everything I think looking bad can
I sleep on the bed oh uncomfortable
ah
Soul coins attract what is that
does it explain to me what soul coins
are I would appreciate that why is there
two books
Soul coins as a concept are one of
merciless Simplicity oh simple simple
like an essay
the sum of personal and magical Essence
the soul is bound into a minted piece of
Inferno iron
um
Soul coins are infernal iron
what and and used as currency by devils
and their cohort
but didn't I have a soul coin
quit my job today uh should I say
congratulations or I'm sorry but you can
watch me so let's go
my two packs of sauce and use it that
must be a jerk
they're very tiny pieces of infernal
iron ah okay and we're looking for a big
piece
let's go
they have frequently traded for the
value you can purchase whatever
traded for their value you can purchase
mercenaries for their value can purchase
mercenaries magical items and even few
well fuel fuel fuel with strange engines
and engine engines
in the house however there is a
fascinating culture surrounding solo
coins as well I just vote to the devil
who admitted she has one coin that she
will never sell
uh-huh
but it was the bargain that got her
promoted out of lemur
isn't that the ringtail lemur thing
what she was a ringtail limber what
what what
that's lemur same thing
now what is this a type of devil in d a
devil
why is devil not pronounced evil but
there's literally evil in the word
can't
pronounce things
she connected me to a half elf warlock
who had promises sold to a coin after
death I was able to look at his contract
which is reproduced below
rap produce
I mean this
this didn't really
helped me much but it did uh create
funny pronunciations a crystal ball
oh
how much worth what
why is it only worth one
thing
it should be worth more
bottle rack
oh wait it wasn't that that's rotten I
don't need that
um oh
coffee is that camp supplies
I I would say so drinking horn wooden
desk because there's nothing in there no
stuffed I've never seen the stuffed
hyena had had hung up somewhere before
of books maybe those are called book a
new I like the books in the game
nothing for me
okay let's look in the kitchen
there's more stuff in here definitely
another mirror
bottle racks bottle racks books
okay
the last Light
lasso
this last night of word play
on the last line
where did it go
Diamond City Lights what's inside and
that is
lazarline
supposed to be last aligned
I never heard of that stone before
I gotta ask pomu what it means
oh
reeks Madison bad a critical fan come on
Pleasure
it's indeed lapis lazuli and Light
okay but then it's laser light
the the stone really is it is
what I just picked up
my surprise split because then they can
inspect the other houses without me
having to move so much
and delivery special aggressive plans to
the seller keep away from
plants to The Cellar it serves as a cell
here somewhere that was a quest
ha ha ha ha
my investigation skills are
the [\h__\h] was that sound again
oh
it's good to read the books
good to read the books guys
do I need this antidote
um
it's [\h__\h] screeches
laughs
rotten
yoink we sucked up
and there's one and this one and this
one
said is that is it their old pet or
something
of the family who lived here
sounds like me right
Noble Rot is it rotten
winter nights
[Music]
oh croissant now croissant is banned
forever
for the travel you got me into but we
can we can um
we can summon
the Imp
instead it's like
basically also just
oh
cool you can fly
oh it's quite sober
yeah it is
okay uh it said something about a cellar
oh wait I forgot the portion of sleep
how do I get into the cellar ah yeah
let's see perhaps here oh it Blends in
until you put your mouse over
yeah let's take my allies after all come
here everybody
will they follow me
yes okay
wow this is pretty it looks like Amy's
office
after she
came back from a trip or so
well
no I don't know nothing so far what am I
looking for
like
something interesting must be down here
oh cute shoes
now who knew
sorry it might not be oh cute
might not be so interesting that I'm
like taking
there's so much to you know to open ah
[\h__\h]
wait wait these devices look at that
let's see if poison resistance
you ain't that you want that [\h__\h] boy's
potion of healing recipe
you like that he looks lovely young kids
I don't know where she's getting that
from where are we oh oh wait this is
like it's not where I thought it was
oh
okay
yeah
let's open this ah Alexey of lightning
resistance
Julio
bronze kick kick
suspicious potion
okay
Belladonna
more cool stuff this is like if you want
to do stuff
like uh create some potions or whatever
in this game
this is the place to be oh you need all
of this
this is like a treasure grub
for
Alchemy
crafting Haven right oh more more
Birkenstocks
stocks
you know
the the chihuahuas Angels right that
consist of my beloved oh
what a barrel music producers
Johnny Hira and Moni
uh yesterday Johnny sent me a picture of
the
um
those what are they called again now I
even forgot those shoes not the Birkin
stocks the other ones the the ones that
I don't like
saying I'm buying these now
yeah Crocs and I'm like oh because
normally in our group chat we're always
like hyping each other up
and then and then he's like oh my God
look at these amazing Crocs that I found
and like
um
I'm so sorry I I'm a I'm a Croc hater
but I'm sure you're gonna make him look
good because you have a fashion sense so
you gotta make it work somehow but
yeah hype stops I didn't know what to
say I didn't want to seem
hateful
but it was okay and then and then soon
after
they also showed off their Birkenstocks
and I'm like oh my God
no it's okay Callie also wears
Birkenstocks these days
so wait what am I supposed to suit
isn't this the seller fine to seller
they say I'm in the cellar
I'm in it or is there does it go even
deeper can we get much deeper
oh
it's just like a secret behind this
picture
no it was that worth money
where'd it go
it's gone
[Music]
um
and ALT is not working right now
I saw everything maybe I didn't take
this picture too
I can't see it
I keep on thinking tanakisha should be
here what the [\h__\h]
oh
not that much money but can I get my own
house or so in this game and then put up
pictures
because she was looking the other way
and she sent her to pick up things with
all
right
reception you mean my personal
perception check me
is I supposed to see something
it's kind of dark
is there like uh
Like a Lover
I'm standing very close to it
ah
whoa
okay oh there's the Mona Lisa
take it you wink
food
bone cap
and we make it a little bit brighter
Blazer
my God
in this kiddo
oh
whoa
whoa oh
Nani
I do
I want to read that oh wait mouldering
casket is there a person
[Laughter]
it's really surprised
but it was actually surprise surprise
oh I was like is that a person because
the word casket normally it has people
in there I was like no way I should have
blown it up before opening it
ah
almost a door
you've heard that one surprise I waited
for I waited centuries to finally
surprise someone they must have waited
so long they must have found this and
then and then go into the casket and
then and then wait because they just
want to play hide and seek with somebody
but nobody ever found them and now
they're so happy
they can't hold back their feelings
another attacking means that oh sting
all right so none of them are close by
[\h__\h] hell oh my God
good night but this is um
can I do it like this no oh yes
oh
let's go let's go
what is this yeah yeah okay okay cool
cool useful imp
okay
aren't they not like gonna come out of
these two
um oh and this one
no more or are they still gonna
surprise me with more
hmm
yes be careful no
Maybe
[Music]
no we shouldn't use the steering for
that he does good let's let's focus off
us there and Shadow heart can shoot one
of them before her fire I will try that
um unfortunately it will be hard to hide
at this very moment
um
a better position a better position
indeed yes
subtle
subtle approach
oh girl sorry
um
let's try shooting one of these I hope
so always
someone in there but would he have come
out on his own
foreign
it's only two we want some more action
he was shy
egg next
the enemies would have opened it oh okay
okay well
well there's a heel on who oh
okay like this
oh nice only plus four come on
I should have short rested beforehand
wasn't my HP already kind of low before
[\h__\h]
okay
um Frenzy
you good
close ranks
kill him
ah so close
what do you think
everything
and let's make Wawa take care of this
one now I guess
um so generally
I think we have come to the conclusion
they all suck just do whatever
maybe strength for not being able to
push me but um
these [\h__\h] can't push me
good try
[Music]
uh yes careless rebuke
there he opens it oh he wants to open
the other one
yeah let's finish this one off
I'm gonna miss us
I should have healed beforehand
oh well
uh
tried ah can't Target I'm dead
so according to holocra
which only uh this is really fitting but
it's like exactly the other way around
the undead can bite me but I can't the
vampire but the vampire can't wait who
knows I want to see what holograph says
about this will Mel try to bite Ollie
back did you see guys
the the thumbnail and the announcement
of all these hologram debut
yeah apparently only is gonna try to
bite Mel oh this one seems to be special
because it's like oh lightened
and there's uh there's flowers there
pretty
yeah did you see
um I was surprised to see Ollie
attempting to bite someone at all has
she done this before
um
I don't have Advantage do I
I have a dance against him apparently
all right
we can still do this
can we
missed that's okay
I think
Rogue advantage
if you have an ally next one
oh
My Life Next to enemies can also trigger
sneak attack
oh
gotta try that uh consciously at some
point
um
if this does as much damage again as it
did before then I want to use it on
someone with higher HP you know
what what survival successful survival
of what
what
oh wait this one had to be close by for
this one oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] eh
I can dig her buried treasure
oh
[Music]
the Bible for noticing the treasure
survival is just native nature skills ah
which I will be I talked a little bit
about this in my mystery I don't want to
spoil it I guess outside of the member
stream but let me just say for everybody
who watched the members from yesterday I
I had a chit chat with mommy mama told
you to plan out everything a bit more
and
um
I'm very inspired I have some good ideas
mommy came up with a good idea too
I'm gonna mix our ideas it's looking
looking good
very interesting
and now I'm gonna buy uh equipment you
know for what
this is for I discussed this in the
member stream for everybody who doesn't
know what I'm talking about it's like
preparations for an anniversary content
which anniversary is like in less than
two weeks now holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
so soon
which area is this we are
uh in the cellar of I don't know what
that place is called
you guys tell them
it's kind of hidden we didn't find this
in our collab live room
at the blighted Village that's it yeah
um
who will come out of this casket I
wonder
[Music]
wait I guess I get to do another attack
I guess because it's a bonus action
should I just attack this casket
what would I throw
boots
ax maybe the ax I don't know
sword a stereo I can't if I was too
heavy to throw guys
and for some money what if I throw a
scroll of Revival
the casket
oh she can even throw the casket
[Music]
revive me
I'll revive the fight oh
let me try it this
will help
oh who are you
good morning
Ohio
maybe I shouldn't have woken them up
like that but
well well well well
uh
okay nice
no he couldn't wake this one up
ah this one's also still alive okay nice
Miss
all four damage over here okay okay
oh
who is he going for
okay so what what is this mirror
why is he going towards it
what is he doing
what are you doing is this a special
mirror
let's go
wait
another little bit more
huh
wasn't it just 84 what changed
how do I get back to 84 percent
Too Close huh
yes we're so back
okay
I wanted to get up there for the
advantage of being at least on the same
level of height
but then I got too close okay
okay
your feet will protect you
um
we're healing a lot but maybe maybe we
don't need for any more healing we'll
just do a short rest afterwards there
shouldn't be anything more after this
openly so
shall we try to stop his heart once more
oh what is Tennessee Tennessee tenacity
tenacity
um
oh man
I can still heal though I guess
still get one damage yeah yeah I saw
not enough movement are you sure about
that
me
are you sure about that
oh wait oh hey
what's this
God damn it
I guess we gotta do a
long distance one [\h__\h]
afro
pretty imp
what
what how how
[Music]
that took my action though
[Laughter]
oh at the end well
no I don't
wanna know what he will do
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
we can still stop him maybe
send
him
oh no
[Music]
where was this bonus action right
I don't know 60 is kind of low
um
oh well
I'll try it's 50 50 anyway
Miss
okay
ah okay I thought maybe there's like a
chance that he can like Escape for the
mirror or something like that
I don't know
thankfully that wasn't the case
hey
what's inside by the way
oh same amount of damage oh look good
good money
um who's left is there so ah they're so
cast we want the EXP right but hmm
[Music]
hmm
Starion carrying
let's open this up
oh no attack it
hey
not enough damage let's finish this get
out of the casket and fight Mania
um the one next to it I know I know I
know I know he's still there I know I
know
um
how much two
well
okay
what about the other caskets though
shortness
okay okay
[Applause]
we can continue our battle in a moment
let's let's pick up everything
this one was special
there's nothing really
weave Moss
oh
oh this is just for Advantage I guess
I had this customer what do we do about
this dirt do we just
can't use actions
yeah there's a digging action though
right
dig again dig again
wasn't there digging action
dip that's dipping I'm digging
press out no ah there it is oh
scroll up invisibility feather fall and
scroll of web oh flammable webbing ah
cool cool cool cool
okay dark Journal
dark Journal the German Journal of alien
tough
I pay no service to the gods but by some
blessings this Village believes me and
my Apprentice to be simple healers my
tattoos are hidden my red robes locked
away and my lab secured I have not heard
the word
since we arrived and only my Apprentice
knows me as ellentoff this place is not
ideal for my research but I can never
return home not the way I escaped I'd be
put to death with words to follow
red wizard is that like something bad in
Baldur's game the work here is simple
and allows me to continue my research at
night but progress is slow reanimation
seems easy but restoring life
the press and loot was he trying to
restore the life of these dead ones
[Music]
evil and greedy
like the wizard lady in the DND movie oh
you need to re-watch it and maybe I do I
love the DND movie yeah I love that one
the work here is similar the tone
contains the magic I need but it fights
me at every step as does my Apprentice
at least my familiar has made it easy to
secure bodies without raising suspicion
not a hotel so where all these caskets
is test test objects
this will take time with will the
zilicus find me before I can bring her
back I cannot say but if they do come
for me they'll have to face the
Guardians of earth oh the Guardians are
your uh those skeletons I suppose oh
that was me reading that was part of the
quest or so
right which one was that
which one was that
this one right
the seller
I wish it would just show me immediately
what I just did I just want so hard to
find this menu is a little bit meh
um
the owner of the salad was more than a
doctor he was our Necromancer and he was
obsessed with a particular book
[Music]
wait find the neckerman
when it says find The Necromancer book
was it not the one I just found this is
another one but it's not here I suppose
what's inside
watching so hard
don't open it yet
[Music]
must investigate
oh pretty
can't even get over there can I
sure to save
so what about this mysterious mirror
mirror mirror on the wall what are you
all about
thank you
I know it wasn't just the normal mirror
oh my God
I got it
yeah what is this
repeat the name from the book you read
oh oh
I could
memnon phrase
where's Dad no let's try examining first
maybe and then say maybe ellentov
we're not saying anything yet right
um
[Music]
magic is old and wavering but you
recognize it
thinking long hiding some Secret
the face is crafted to be pleasing but
the personality is just a reflection of
the wizard that created it
name
well I guess it's ill and tough
[Music]
is it evil now is it mad oh it's back
why is it s t e p
stat put
is that like a secret code that I'm
supposed to write down
um
[Music]
smash it into pieces
uh I'm an alley of your Masters totally
and totally
Tea Room
who [\h__\h] my history
uh that wasn't in the book either
maybe it's a bad I would I would assume
but the context by her just asking me
that question her I said remember her
that it's a yeah a bad
bad person at least to Ill and tough he
would be
[Music]
to clean
not to clean but to
treat burns Maybe
well within the within this game
maybe different
a friend but I definitely I mentioned
this possum before in the game too
you didn't read the book which book
eh
to clean a wound
I don't wanna do it
acceptable acceptable
should I have checked all the caskets
first huh
could say anything in me what would it
be
um
probably
[Music]
Ellen top would see his enemies
suffering
I
think
as
[Music]
that true they did want to revive uh
someone
um
it couldn't couldn't it be both one and
three Ellen top seemed like an evil
person
oh
[Music]
I'll say it well even if we're not going
after what illenhoff would say
uh which we would logically try to do
right now because we're trying to
deceive the mirror and even tanakisha
would say I'd see my enemy suffering or
or that one of course but we're trying
to get on the good side of the mirror
right now
oh how are you gonna Purge me
who's happening though
[Laughter]
hey can I stop it I can't quit
oh that's so funny oh that's so funny oh
is it is it going to the caskets
locations oh my God that's so funny
should I reload because what is there
something more interesting that could
have happened if I got all the answers
correctly
okay do I get another try
ah yeah three loads I don't wanna save
scum too much but
um
I feel like I want to know what happens
if I get the answers right
um
it's fun right
mm-hmm
there's no second try yeah
understandable that
the mirror wouldn't want to let me try
again
oh I could just talked with someone else
with like a Starion or so and it
wouldn't recognize
that we're the same group
really
smash the mirror
oh ah yeah we should have followed up
with smashing the mirror at least after
that happened wait but okay before we go
to the mirror then let's let's clear all
the caskets first then
this is after I already cleared out all
the items right okay let's let's let's
kill all the zombies first
um
I want an elegant elegant way of opening
them
do it again
I wish I could open them all at once
um
oh because for only one but then I don't
get the EXP and the items
all right
[Music]
let's go
I'm missed that's okay
ready or not here I come
[Music]
thank you
mm-hmm
a dull moment
never at the moment no need to hide why
because does the Imp being there also
I don't understand
100 percent
ah
almost almost made mistake
yeah yeah yeah we're not done though
we're not done
next is this casket
oh
no one underneath this one
was a fake
which ones I love ah this one
up
there we go let's take a load off isn't
it
ah hello
wait so so now I want to try the thing
does it really count as
um
I guess so
oh wow wow wow
one hit
easy Scroll of bone chill what's that
prevent attack from healing until your
next turn oh and on that Target receives
this advantage and attack rules oh cool
now I think I got them all
that's where I came from right is that
yeah okay
oh this is so cool
I like how far you can go with the
camera without having to bring your
people there
um
okay now we can talk to the Mirror
damn okay
rotten eggs rotten chicken eggs rotten
carrots
looks empty
I'll check everything I had to check
everything
I mentioned some kind of book though
I didn't find another book I only found
that one book
hmm
yeah uh once again should I well it
didn't believe me that I was Ill on top
anyway
um but let's try this again
just for
you know
maybe it helped that I was understanding
it
wow the magic is old and wavering
recognize it mirror is a fingers
uh
who is Memon phrase anyway
two or three
random teaching name
don't sit I do not know okay is that bad
you're gonna ask if I'm an ally anyway
okay okay okay okay okay
yes of course of course
was wait did she agree with what I said
we got further by saying it
the bounce of ointment
the Queen the wound right
what would it be well so many people
said go for it too
it's a smile yeah
it goes even if I can you imagine that
all of this was behind underneath
that little village
oh
Jasmine
cool
and I look at everything oh my God oh my
God oh my oh my God there's so much
stuff hiding here
what's this Acorn truffle Acorn truffle
what is that
that's why is there a truffle on the
acorn
research oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God
oh my God oh my God look at me more for
me the oil from a basilisk moonhaven log
book The collected
reading time baby
a companion of dark Arcana
I'm strange alchemical sketches and
formerly some are written plainly
um
the book is filled with pages and pages
of observations tracking Travelers and
people in the village you turn to the
final pages
[Music]
okay
bottle rack
heal the chest huh
what where
Behind Me Maybe oh yeah there well wait
research notes might be interesting
raise that failed gone to long body
decomposed reanimation failed came back
as ghoul had to kill again speaker that
failed answer some helpful clone failed
means living tissue or animation plus
clone failed had to kill both ghouls
Resurrection failed why a magical curse
true Resurrection I've reached the limit
of my skills and resources the book
offers to help there I accept
so this is all about this one person he
tried to save right he tried it in all
these different ways
and then he was like out of ideas
the book oh yeah the book
what what
there I accept this is the body oh [\h__\h]
this is scary it only has a dagger with
it why
isn't that prop could it
or something like that oh
oh braces of Defense
[Music]
become the bulwark
you gained a personal number because as
long as you're not wearing all my
homework who should I give this to this
rare item
people behind
on death and Resurrection
so I'm I'm kind of becoming a book nerd
in this game
okay
rare braces for her amazing as long as
she doesn't wear armor
eh I have to make her Nikki like this
eh
perhaps to read The Wheel of Time so far
well if I read The Wheel of Time
apparently I will stop enjoying the show
um honestly although I don't even think
I would
I'm enjoying the show by the way I
watched the first three episodes of the
second season yes last night because it
just came out
so so many people were like oh my God
thanks for reminding me when I tweeted
it so many people were oh this is fun
so many people were like um
I didn't realize thanks for reminding me
oh
the Watcher's guide death's promise when
the spare misses its Target
the Whalers next attack role against
when did I pick this up
should I give this to somebody
it's a it's a spare
we use a spare
buddy Ryan
give it to Shadow heart Shadow heart
Maybe
as a ranged weapon no melee
cool
um
of course we could feed some things to
Gail too anyway the book that I wanted
to read wasn't there another book yeah
this one
while the number of Trinkets and
Bargains a hag personally had personally
likewise means that her powers will be
wait is is hack here in the context in
the meaning of an old person
oh
is this actually like a normal normal
wait is this actually a normal it's a
creature
okay
[Music]
I thought it was a
yeah okay uh is it only in in D and D in
this game that is a word for a monster
I'm so confused
uh
fantasy thing
[Music]
there's some fogler okay okay a fantasy
thing okay so buy the number of Trinkets
and Bargains a hack personally choirs
means that her powers will be unique
compared to that of her sisters
hags as a whole can still be divided
into three subcategories
night hacks named as such for their
ability to haunt immortal's dreams like
is this like a wind dance the only the
boring vital Essence until the victim's
Soul can be trapped into the hack Soul
bag they are known for being petty
selfish braggards
sea Hanks
basically witches oh
known for devouring the victim's whole
seahex can terrorize and kill with a
single look when you say they Devour the
with them hole is this like a snake
thing like where they eat the whole body
in one go like or
or do they cut it up piece by piece with
a knife and then eat the whole body in
both ways it's still whole
I guess not I guess I mean yeah it's not
homeless and the body is still a hole
but you ate the whole body you know I
guess yeah it's a snake thing okay okay
no no no no idea why I needed to know
that one gulp okay they Rico fish and
are incapable of making a proper cup of
tea
for the info green hacks they are
beautiful they are powerful speak not a
word why is this so
biased
what was this person being threatened
when writing this book
you have to write good things about
green hags because I am a green egg
Green Egg was threatening
the offer or the green hag wrote the
book
wait if I get the book that's over there
will I revive this thing and then bam
big fight happens or something like that
would be fun
I wonder I'm sure all will be revealed
in time but I don't like it a waste of
perfectly good trouble it's about the
food
um I don't think
why do you insist on why is she so
bloody
vampires all right I guess we're
listening
welcome to the streams I still am
I was never able to resist their
commands but
they won't ever control me again
when it says leave doesn't mean I'm
leaving the conversation or am I telling
him to leave and he will leave my party
I hope it's the first thing
okay okay
I was always worried about choosing that
oh my it's called vampiric touch
to stiffen their life first Enrique in
half cool cool
magic weapon Dark Vision
[Music]
an ally in a protective coma they become
resistant to all damage except psyche
damage
when would I
in what situation would I do that
I know I don't want the rotting basket
I thought something was inside
any more notes
Mark wart
sorry I have to look at everything
because you can see like even when I
look at the most like smallest things I
can get a journal update and it's like
oh my God what thank God I'm being so
thorough
looking at everything
separatory funnel
oh I I picked it up okay okay I think
we're good on this corner
oh
what the [\h__\h] is this
what is this
what bone is that supposed is that a is
that a on like a uh like a key Fair uh
under jaw
Maybe
alligator job
okay guys how do we open this do we just
open it normally
cool [\h__\h]
so Gail just concerned I'm not talking
to you right now this is quirks go
what did I
it's armit
okay maybe yes Darien should be doing
this I don't know but let's go
okay
all right so disarmed
so we're good right
open
okay uh what now what now
open Lockpick
traps
how about the traps
don't scare me these always the music is
always so scary
not the music the sound effects come on
15 ah
can we do it
yeah okay okay
why is it always that these kind of
rolls I roll surprisingly low
so annoying okay okay unlocked
oh
there's a face on it
all right
yeah let's disarm it
oh hey it's my amp basically oh it's a
guard oh it's a gargle just a more buff
imp like look at it
my aim just looks like a gargoyle that
hasn't eaten for one month
his arm
chat in oh come on
why so low
malnourished gargoyle
okay is there another one oh yeah
oh but I haven't perceived that one yet
maybe I should disarm it before I pick
up the book huh oh wait this this is
also something I have to disarm
it didn't perceive that one
or is that one also disarmed Now by
disarming the other one
good eye what the the plate
it's Mort
they did I missed 15. okay
wow
so is everything disarmed now because
it's not glowing anymore so it should be
huh
oh spider spider
spider silk
that reminds me I feel like in World of
Warcraft I feel like I remember a
certain type of silk was like so so
valuable and so difficult to uh get or
so but oh yeah sorry what the [\h__\h] with
brain is coming back to me oh the
memories
um
you know how in World of Warcraft you
could have these jobs right I usually
was doing the one with the Fabrics or so
uh-huh
back in the good old days a million
years ago
tailoring it oh
stop I'm so scared to take it
I'm ready we take it we take it the
necromancy of daddy
the book is locked tight yeah babe what
a book only an oval recess
yes oh do we put something in there
you try to examine the book but the
longer you stare the more those pieces
someone stare into the eyes no
curious
why don't you take a closer look
I'll observe from back here
please don't open the creepy book
that looks terribly heavy why don't you
let me carry it for you
this is like a Lord of the Rings the
ring thing where people are like give it
to me like Precious
believe the poopy drop the tomb ready to
destroy it
um I wouldn't destroy it I want to open
it why is there no opening option
I'm gonna open it
keep it I know
the book is locked tight with no visible
Keyhole ah okay only and you try to
examine I need to put something in there
how how
how do I put something maybe maybe just
be on my way what this can't be the end
of it
can't be the end of it am I I'm missing
something a quest for later
um okay
nah I thought this would this thing
would come to life and attack me or so
um oh bear
cute it's so fluffy look at that hot
stuffed bear oh wait there's something
inside out yeah
Young
killed and stuffed before its teeth were
fully grown young oh okay a young Cave
Bear nothing inside killed and stuff
I guess it would just be stuffings
anyway
oh
more
more things to open
basic poison simple oh
foreign
[Music]
oh
it was connected like that damn this
place is huge oh I just noticed this
huge thing hanging up there I didn't
even see that until now
wow so guys see we found such a cool
place
instead of rushing
to catch up with the collab I think this
is good that we're doing this
so I'm done here I guess
oh
[Music]
hello
good morning we should kill those
damn this was interesting this was so
interesting
act one has like so much more stuff like
this eh cool
you can talk with them okay talk and
then kill
anything of use probably just rotten
fish
there's no way that these are still
fresh and edible but okay
just sitting in in the daylight forever
oh
oh Haze town at the start of combat then
where it gains momentum for free turns
oh yeah I remember this helmet we did
take it actually previously uh where did
I didn't wait wait there was a hole over
there that I wanted to look inside
I'm not done exploring at all I'll take
the whole stream exploring this Village
oh man
okay
incense
selenite necklace and these look like
Pokey sticks
let me take that all of that
oh
I was like who's snoring oh scrawny Buck
bear should we
should we wake him up
[Music]
good morning
oh
it's so close one shot killing him
and my impended that would be funny
please
ah come on
first impression was good on the end but
ever since the one hit that the Imp did
he's only missing now
where's shadowheart
um
yeah oh wait we can do another one ha ha
ha ha
IM can go invisible oh
[Music]
no what can I do for you sorry you're in
the way
this is rotten chicken eggs he was
eating rotten chicken eggs
this stuff might be good though
no
not just another crate
I want to open it though okay oh
we made a mess it's not your fault guys
not your fault don't worry are they how
do I get over there there okay do I jump
in there
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
nothing good here first first things
first
um okay let's go down I can't no of
course I can what are you talking about
for a second
Everybody follow me
let's avoid that trap where are we now
what's this looks very similar to where
we were before but
this arm it's is it like one of those
RPG game chests that will open its mouth
and attack me
shouldn't be too difficult yeah a minute
yeah
why am I wrong Chloe
in this situation oh I love how acrylic
is just dancing
so now we can open it right
High clips blueprints
precise arcs are nearly Drawn Lines
okay
they call for susivac
I don't know I knew where to find
something if only you didn't fail nature
a [\h__\h] because of you now we can't do
this Quest
what finish the Masterwork weapon
find a sassy tree
hey there's like this like so many like
hidden little side quests what the [\h__\h]
like what my oh my God
I'm fascinated
this game is so
intricate like uh first of all I
freaking love games where you can you
know influence the game by what you do
and what you say
and even if you [\h__\h] up something
doesn't mean that you necessarily have
to redo it no you can you can take the
consequences and still keep on going you
know maybe you'll have some disadvantage
but still like manageable
if you want to
so cool like I mean there there's games
out there more games out there that
where you can you know make decisions in
terms of like dialogue and that's cool I
love that I wish there was more of that
but there's not so many where you can
have things like go really badly
and ended not being like a thing
you know I don't know and well you can't
speak today obviously but oh my God
we will blow this up how do we blow this
up
can I blow this up
you get me right you get me without even
saying anything thank you
I'll just blast oh that sounds good that
sounds good it's a little bit more
interesting time but she didn't really
perceive it did she
[\h__\h] apparently
who perceived it
[Music]
only a stereo yeah but wait now it's
gone
why is it gone now
oh wait it works like this okay
whoa
what is this
can I walk on that oh my God wait I'm
like
this is cool
it's not moving it's making the sound
but it's not moving
oh wow
wow
today wow I can make it really strong
oh can I use this for something can I
sniff something that's so cool so good
oh wait what is this
is that why I came from that no wait
wait wait
who's this
should I go up there but I need to go
there where do I go oh my God so many
options
[Music]
approachable East I need to read this
book
nerd Wawa strikes again
but it's volume six
are there other volumes I don't want to
spoil them myself
fire fire pants on fire
yeah they are oh my God oh my God
this game
this is amazing
can I take this
the rest not so important
okay ah
okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
I we'll just check where
where this leads
probably just yeah another exit but
we didn't
we didn't go for the store right when we
entered
we're just opening another path now are
we
it's the exit right okay can I ah can I
go through again okay
okay
[Music]
we're still on fire wow it's still on
fire I don't know why but that makes me
happy
okay
let's go what is this
wow
is there something here
Whispering devil touch those webs or
I'll end up as a meal yeah a meal too
big Speedo but how do I I want to I want
I want to get over there though do I
burn it do I walk over it can I jump
over there
I can I can jump
[Music]
here that should be good oh but she
jumps from here
[Music]
should I burn it
but then it's okay to walk on an okay
but Shadow heart is like
you know making me worry doing me a
concern
Ed you test it out
oh you have to be saved from it's okay
Everybody follow
and what now
okay
the speed does
whoa
we're walking just get out of there can
we
get out of there
can she get out of there get out of
there yeah they joined battle okay okay
okay let's fight let's turn someone
inside out let's turn someone inside out
um
uh I my my shift isn't working right now
it doesn't show me
it doesn't show me the thing
so I know
I'll just do a ranged little truck
because I um I can't
oh 85.
okay that's fine
only slow moving
the fire where is the spider I saw a
spider crawling around like a shadow of
a spider
these are not the real spiders
oh my God what is this oh
there it is what is this place
wow
looking super cute thank you you too
cutie pie
I want stashing where are you going oh
oh oh oh you're joining the battle
okay
hmm I damn it well
I want to shoot
um
are they on a web right web yeah there's
a web here I can shoot on the web now
should I shoot on the web
I I can't can I
whip
those are just cosmetic oh
well
hmm
well I'll go for him then
because 70 is kind of decent
and let's go you should be able to fly
over all of this right
and why is he why is he why is the
terrain affecting him
[Music]
become invisible
I'm not here
there's a fight
let's go let's go let's go
[Music]
Maybe
I can try to jump
oh no
like eh
[Music]
what this is so weird
you know what I mean
it's so weird
no strength short drums I missed I
missed this step
indeed
um
somewhere here is fine
okay
oh yeah oh yeah not much damage but we
blasted him away
you gotta understand I semi understand
what's going on to the range circle of
jumping
uh most of the time I think I get it but
now it was just like freaky
freaky freaky
under their noses
and webbed
oh maybe wait a minute sorry maybe I
should have done
one of those
range to test oh well it's feral jumps
venomous discharge you missed haha
did you guys see it
new outfits
she looks cute
hmm
it's so bright and so colorful and so
pretty
not
yeah very dreamy very cute even though I
have full HP should I still try to do
this
I will not oh just off an attack okay
it always misses
well why can't I do it again
infested
who's in president
where's it going oh there's another
spider
oh why don't you stay
why you gotta make it complicated and
leave
he's got two oh
no
[Music]
um
rash attack
foreign
I really don't like Shadow art in combat
man
she is lame
oh don't eat a stereo
at the cap
nice that's good damage that's what I
like to see let's go so much for peace
take it
she's broken this [\h__\h] action I'm
crying
I can change her
ooh cleric yeah that sounds good
you didn't open that cabin during the
town did you please tell me you didn't
I mean
didn't you can you not watch my previous
do you mean the one where they were you
know having fun inside did you not watch
my previous
stream
my solo baller skate stream what are
these percentages why am I and because
I'm pregnant
try it anyway
yeah
I guess you never watched a bot or the
clips that were made of it
you missed something where you like in a
casket literally
down
I'm tired
brain hordes right now
um
yeah I can jump right
[Music]
casting okay
hi The River Why do I retired I had good
sleep
oh but I don't know
I don't know I I woke up
I uh just looked for my phone a little
bit in bed
then I had breakfast I started eating
pancakes with raspberries and stuff
again and Nutella love that
love that for me
and
and go get them go get him
um then I just started streaming pretty
pretty much immediately so
I know I guess I was like still
very much mentally in bed
I still am
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is going on
yeah we're kind of dying here these two
only these two though
problem is she can't heal
hmm
wait I Scrolls like separate from you
know the spell slots
do they not count as using up a spell
slot
oh
spicy do I have a healing one I guess
wait we have potions I forgot about the
existence of potions but maybe we got
something interesting here anyway
um
what could I use
sometimes
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Greece
with Grease Grease the spiders up and
then shoot them fire
yeah vampire touch just thinking so too
could at least heal me where did it go
on here this one
on home
is it even gonna
reach work
yeah with you I guess we'll try
what just happened
I was immobilized guys
not cool
is my spell gone now too
[Music]
oh hey even with these low percentages
I'm actually hitting I am amazed
can I fly up here oh no
oh yeah
why not
you're here
oh
I believe in you yes
don't buy me
um
[Music]
all right so here down here we have no
enemy left
[Music]
uh
what this
is confusing
I am at a disadvantage
nothing here that I can really climb
[Music]
um
I'll try anyway let's go
oh okay it'll work
[Music]
um
you can't really do anything can you at
this point when they're up there I mean
could she use
uh can she use
um like a fire
Fireball
oh can we throw The Alchemist fire flask
Maybe
wait throwing that is an action okay
just gotta hope that I can do this from
here
how how
on the spider on the spider web can I
um let me just a spider live
okay
dies from the fall beautiful and this
one's on fire let's go
oh you're coming down anyway okay
ah
[Music]
a
um
[Music]
got to move
man
what I expected
imp is such a stalker
wow
okay
let's push my luck again I stare at the
oh what I didn't see it
all right I haven't moved to Starion for
a while true true
[Music]
oh
wow I'll help you in a moment
[\h__\h]
can I
oh wow and I throw the potion on him
how's his work again
huh drop no
no
who saw that coming huh
me
don't laugh at me Carla
I'm not laughing at you I'm laughing
with you
well wait wait asterian we have to
finish this you know
oh
say now you now look good now we're good
get up
get up already
uh cool good morning
what's happening with him
be careful I might
it's been a long day better stop to rest
soon should we do a full rest
Are you standing in the pool go away
should we just do a short one full rest
right um
oh
cave cam
I am fascinated respect shut up how
where is she anyway
I hear
a Withers what's next does she have to
go to press on [\h__\h] the Wither
I don't speak
excuse me
she'll be here here in lycam hmm for
whenever thou Hast needs
as thou desire
stinky
uh well she's already a cleric what are
we making her into
ah
um
Clerk of light
huh
lights Tempest for damage life or
support Frontline
um
lighter my domain
Nightline
I have Tempest
um
so with life she's just like completely
A Healer array of Life of light
um
is better in combat but life feels
better
but she can still heal as a as a light
domain right so I feel like
we don't need the hill so often
it's nice to have her heal whenever I
need it I'm just disappointed whatever
I want her to do any damage so
um
[Music]
can we take a nap
yeah maybe line I don't know
can't do a full Young
full of rest and IRL yeah
no not even full resistor just a small
smaller
smaller smarter
can I sleep for three hours and come
back that's what I want to do too
okay well whatever I'll Trust you guys
[Music]
um
so we choose that
do I change the cant trips
I have been
only using the guidance I don't remember
using anything else
um
current ones are fine abilities
somebody said something about strength
for so
um
help
strength plus minus this Dex
it is
no more strength less Tech okay okay
[Music]
um
okay okay okay
X can go to ten
next 10.
Maybe 11.
um uh
still got one
yeah okay
odd numbers mean nothing keep it all
even oh yeah yeah I noticed it's kind of
weird
okay
um
that's fine too I think
[Music]
it's time for a little chocolate snake I
think don't you wear green
maybe the sugar will wake me up for me
for me I just need sugar to survive
um
yeah I know I could replace her but I
don't
um
I do use her heels sometimes so
mm-hmm
what'd I do about that
I couldn't go plus so I went minus to
change the odd numbers
um
no need for charisma
no
I don't know if she needs more HP but
okay
yeah has to be an even number right
wisdom is at 17 though
[Music]
um
is that bad
the decks can I give him more texts can
I give even less charisma
is this okay
because like people said damn she needs
at least some decks
to like yeah
[Music]
um
don't eat spring and it's so split like
there were a lot of people saying
strength strikes sometimes time strength
Frank strings
she needs 14 decks why exactly 14.
also this is an uneven number two
can I do this but no that's uneven like
I don't understand why is that a problem
can I mean because yeah
now that one's left over I could add it
to
intelligent or Charisma apparently yeah
because the most you can get
from medium armor bonus
[Music]
I don't understand
what
ah
I don't understand I'll just keep
playing this I don't know is this okay
there's so many opinions
yeah yeah
okay
thanks wither
okay it's time to sliver into bed but
without the Wither
this is
oh
gotta level up ah
cleric level two
[Music]
what do we do prepare spells uh
hmm I I I'm obviously keeping inflict
wounds and guiding bold can we just keep
them the way they are they seem fine
what's this
um
bless
I never use it though
finish leveling and then pick okay
why doesn't it do it just at once
are we getting another one
uh
hmm
whatever
I mean it sounds interesting
um
[Music]
only at high level spiritual weapon
spiritual weapon
well let me read all of this The Helio
allies increase the hit point maximum of
five hit points oh
you're a creature from disease poison
paralyzed blindness
uh Warden Ally oh wardens Wardens
Wheel of Time
uh they gain resistance to all damage
and a plus one bonus to the armor class
in their own instruments
same amount of damage damn
poison protection
call me motions
hold ah the holding
I saw that in an accident a lot it's
it was quite annoying when the enemy was
using it
um
right
maybe I should try that
oh what did it switch out
Prayer of Healing 5 to 19 healing heal
allies you can see
being a creature you can I could could I
not replace
this cure wounds with Prayer of Healing
can't be used in combat oh
oh yeah it says here okay
special weapon ah you guys mentioned
this one some of the floating spectral
weapon oh that's cool
I feel like I seen that I saw that in
action too
I don't know
maybe like that
because this healing was enough for me
although
oh yeah yeah I think it's fine
I think this might be fine
um I don't I don't know if I need the
shield of Faith though
[Music]
um
where was this
what's up to frequency yeah maybe
instead of that we use Bliss
I think this is okay
these boots have seen everything okay
now we can sleep
for real for real
um
this is a good one to throw on your
party at the start of a belt
[Music]
hey
this Advanced feature allows you to
build powerful combinations of classes
at the expense of higher level class
features oh
you can only level up one class at a
time why are you telling me this no
so Random
money
yeah
money my girl
um
[Music]
blue
foreign
my lyric writer and Angel Guardian Angel
that's money
hi
Chihuahua's angel
let's go
was saying that I think
oh
silk gland what
web grenade
wait so is it the inside of a spider
that's creating the silk
wow so educational oh my God
I'm Spider-Man now
if I put this in my body can I be Spider
Girl
oh my God where do I go what is this
holy bucket oh it's a Well bucket it's
so holy look look at this
it's like it's gonna give me a quest
egg clutch it's an itchy egg or what
eat itchy egg in your crotch
when I go this place is too big
and yo it's not blood
I don't know where are you
I don't even know where to go
should I go up
wait is this this is where I came from
okay okay let's Circle
don't get toxin
there's a dead Goblin here I didn't kill
this one
I'll take the gold thank you I need to
find a shopkeeper who has enough money
to buy all the things I'm trying to sell
why why can I not interact with the egg
I want to interact with the egg
are these spider eggs
they are
we should shoot
wait that's actually [\h__\h] scary ah
my face protects me I should burn all
the paths yeah bye this is oh God so I
fight it wait how much what is five
whoa
oh no oh no oh oh I don't I um
[Music]
don't fight it I'm scared
yeah we could drop it but then we can
never go down again
that spider is significantly bigger than
the others look at it holy [\h__\h] oh God
everybody with spider
um phobia I'm so sorry
you can choose this fight
how by shoot but if I shoot the tap
won't it just fall down
oh I shoot the pack when I sit over here
that I can't reach but it can probably
do the jumps and all that no
phobia
I can tell but yeah
[Music]
prone when a spider becomes prone when
an enemy becomes prone what does it
do they take more damage in general
but I don't want to give it a try I mean
I can't just come here and not fight the
spider right
so I do it right away do I let's make
this
let's make a quick indeed
wow that did a lot of damage and we're
not even starting to fight no we are
filming oh my God what why is it filming
so much can you not like come up here oh
it's making little babies it's opening
up its eggs oh you said opening up its
eggs [\h__\h] what do I do how do I fight
this yeah bye I did save beforehand yeah
[Music]
okay
um well right now
only my imp can
do stuff so
um well you can't get that far okay well
whatever
become invisible
what's happening wow
yeah I don't know if I'm gonna survive
this depends on many factors I guess
that's what I'm feeling like right now
hmm
the thing is though it's not even worth
really going after them no because like
so far when we fought the spiders before
they were like booming all over
[Music]
and you know what
no one
[Music]
can I
I want to throw
an alchemist fire again
um
should I is that is frozen
it's an action right
use grease first but what if they move
away from the grease right away will
they still be greased
jump near the legend throw I'll come
look here
I could even walk there
[Music]
killable fire I'm
trust me
why did it look like I could jump there
a moment ago for one half a second
um
ah I could I could
probably jump
I just don't want to jump in and regret
that I can't reach it I could probably
go here
it's it's a bonus action jumping is a
bonus action but throwing is the action
I think
better to Dash
I don't know here it says action when I
just hover over it so
jumping in front Okay let's do that so
if I go like here it should definitely I
should definitely be able to reach right
oh
easy house
I hope this works
should we should we grease that I can't
I'm just gonna throw it
I'll kill you babies let's go
okay
[Music]
um
why is this Ariana cowboy
if you had a huge big rock you could
throw it from up here for a huge damage
well unfortunately Bijou is not with us
today
foreign
[Music]
yeah I mean actually I think I can do it
unless the other spiders got too much in
the way
shall we dance
[Music]
mom I will I will trust me I will
um let's
uh
[Music]
hmm
I can cunning act cunningly actually
dashingly go over there and then
just throw
I'll just I'll just go here
oh it'll be fine but
although when they're standing like that
often they're like in the way right
can I go here
so they they definitely see me from here
so no sneaky sneak but
I could also throw like a bomb or
something
but low damage this one so
um this one is
oh I don't have the advantage yeah okay
is this 50
should I do the gray
who's got the grease stuff
it was a scroll though right somebody
said bottle but this is scroll unless
there was
something else
oil
brown ones
huh
[Music]
oh
wait what
okay
we're throw that
will it will it like make the fire
bigger again too
why do I do it on the floor or on her I
I don't want to make a mistake
ignite the fire
oh that would be lovely
okay
indeed
hey
missed what the grease mist or because
there was a little explosion
did she just dodge everything
Beach
um
[Music]
can I wait no no more right because it's
a
okay
can't help it it is what it is for now
all right let's let's use respect Shadow
heart now
money would look so good in the shadow
heart cosplay
we would look so cute
why should she stand can she see them
from here
oh no
I can burn those two
maybe oh
[Music]
let's go
Shadow money
[Music]
maybe I'll use
something
ready to turn all on that casino
should we bless everybody just
very fine I can't really oh wait I can
kind of can it's only 40 percent though
less okay let's bless hashtag bless
so like this and like this and like this
[Music]
let's see you and you and you and you oh
my God
thank you so much
oh we can also summon the spiritual
weapon but like where where does it go
if I summon do I want to do this because
does it yeah it uses up like a spell
spot right
yes to it yeah
try dance bear Mall halberd
great sword and a great ax
floating I wanna I want the trident
is there any differences anyway they
seem to have the same amount of damage
put it near you
near me
First Chinese
someone near enemy huh
okay
hey are the babies alive again or were
they never dead [\h__\h] I thought they were
dead
oh
oh wow okay so it's like a minion now
can it be
20 20 hp wow
okay hello
ouch
oh
piercing strike
I mean let's try
sad
um
oh there they go
stop pulling my trident
[Music]
okay it's up here now oh wait that's
actually ah well it's sit it should stay
for a while right so I can I can turn it
down
before I shoot it down
[Music]
um
I want to fly to you
can I do that okay
nice
well he might fall down too right or can
he and I guess he'll fly he'll he'll fly
down too can I fly away again
no
okay that's fine
[Music]
oh
it's good here I come I'm gonna
shoot you with some fire
where should I get a hit with Carla in
first possibly a melee hit but then
she'll fall down too I guess okay never
mind never mind never mind never mind
it oh yeah we are chasing it I see that
that must be the cheese that you guys
were talking about
hey
I could heal a Syrian
s
did she just say [\h__\h] yes
I love her
yeah yeah I would say that it was
definitely something the devs considered
[Music]
while he's floating
um when creating this area this was
definitely a very very viable strategy
that you know
it's very it's quite obvious actually
you know
so
look on the frenzy and we'll attack the
spider up here
because she's melee anyway so let's have
the other ones focus on the ranged
attacks
why about it
okay
nice
yeah I mean the webs they're literally
asking for that when they stand on top
of the webs
I'm just fascinated it does so much
damage makes me quite happy
why would you go down what
is she going down down
down down down down down
by the road s
stupid [\h__\h]
did she need to go that close really
yeah
down down down by the Spy Dawn no
60. I can't go up again can I can I
the camera is confusing me
like how much I can still go back up
right okay
oh my God no stay up there oh my God why
is she trying to go down look at her
I know you can reach one up there I know
you can what's going on
eh
angle
what if I go here
[Music]
a little vegetarian shall we cut and run
almost dead anyway
let's not worry
um
can I do this oh
this might actually work
you can't reach that far and still have
84 percentage oh my God
and another one oh maybe can we can we
go vampire bite let's go
a Skyrim
[Music]
okay yeah yeah he's got so many actions
I go from here
what about now so
I can oh a little bit further
oh okay it's one stippity step was
enough
here we go
kill it
one
one a dream will it take like fire
damage though the burning damage the DOT
I I would hope so
no I guess not
what what about this Burning
oh well maybe the Trident can finish it
oh
they all attacked the Trident because
they looked away and zero
I am still there right right oh imp
maybe you were here for a reason what is
that
oh wait they're all dead I was gonna say
maybe you're here for a reason
it's dead
all right
let's fly back up then
no that's not where
oh whatever
[Music]
so confusing
frenzied strain what do you mean
let's make it lactate that spider milk
no just normal hit is okay
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
please
wow I can't believe I did it wait we
better shoot those eggs
now or can we pick him up and take him
no it doesn't look like it's an item so
nice soon
incredible I'm I'm I'm happy that we
were Brave and we took the battle upon
us
feeling fresh don't worry about the eggs
okay
let's loot the big speeder
minimal damage too yeah we weren't even
close to dying
oh
poisonous roll when the wearer cast a
spell that deals poison damage it deals
an additional wonderful
do we have somebody
what the [\h__\h] why is there no items
found
huh
there we go uh give it to Carla I can't
really use that
well it looks nice good for boys and
girls what
does Carla have a poison
attack
not really
is this not poisonous necro huh
maybe later we'll get something with
poison
Ed by a poison weapon that makes sense
it does make sense on Hell really
doesn't also look good on her
no it doesn't
no
and doesn't that count as armor though
[Music]
it doesn't look good on her
looks better on Shadow heart
even better on me
and okay on him now we all switched
clothes
oh
wait
back to normal please
this is how it was okay
and
I don't like it oh my God it looks so
funny
do the small ones have anything
slimy little speedons
oh
fancy ruby ring
damn
is there something else hidden here that
I should be aware of what like what is
that
what is that purple stuff over there
can I perceive it
a dark elephant
well it's round
it's an amethyst look purple like the
other things that are in there
oh my God oh my God oh my God they even
tell me
what a spoiler just keep it a riddle
oh my God what is this can I burn that
wits and blade
's the best defense
[Music]
immune
what that's I call that [\h__\h]
it was worth coming here yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah worth checking out everything
on the ground are we done here like does
it continue oh
[Music]
eggs I think
oh wait there's a waypoint can we go
here girls you know how to go there huh
can't get there
wait wait what's going on oh of course
you can
Keep On Moving
of course you can come on come on
come on oh and there's the accent nice
way Pond Yahoo
so where shall we do the thing where
shall we do the injection
nice nice let's go let's go out the
normal way
I'm around
animal carcass
I wanna see oh this is just this uh
okay then I already saved I'll save
again for you guys
um should I I don't know does it like
spawn something crazy then I might might
want to be somewhere else
also where is the iron I still didn't
find the iron
[Music]
what was the the blighted pillows right
it's just choices oh okay
oh okay
um
okay how how how how
that's so weird
you got it right
how do I combine it
and maybe the maybe the quest says that
um
um unlock
oh oh okay
oh my God I'm curious
[Music]
oh look it's locked tight with no
visible Keyhole
only an oval recess in the cover's mouth
perfect
stop caressing it you try to examine the
book but the longer you step
a place to Amethyst in the [\h__\h] I never
discovered
oh what's gonna happen
unlimited power
you tried to examine the book but the
longer you stare the more those people
um we will open oh
Mysterion
why is stereo
because he asked for it didn't he like
in the previous conversation
should we give it to him
no
bet on me okay
well they disapproved
oh
you've battered
but are capable of anything I am since
darkening Sons versing with the Dead Oh
forever
should lay before your eyes why wow it's
and onto your lips forming words you
don't understand
thing is trying to reply
saving for
bro ask your Patron to guard your mind
and
Patron I haven't met my Patron yet I
think in this
wait Patron
and the the mama told me different I
guess there's no mamatory anyway here
but
okay
1d4 1d4
bless me
huh
what's the difference between these by
the way
four creatures uh-huh I don't care
go
ah I don't know
resistance oh okay
ah
resistance is free uh-huh
okay okay I mean that was easy anyway
difficulty classifieds is not so tough
next page oh this is aggressive it's
going back though
didn't we just go backwards though
we just went backwards didn't we and
then and then the page flipped over
again it's a manga
but there's now only
15 15.
and now I can only bless though I know
or resistance is already there okay
never mind
15.
okay
[Music]
we got lucky
okay
let's go
the world around you is gone
oh [\h__\h]
feel claws moving in the shadows it's
scary they pull at you dragging you
closer this book is very evil
okay but I want to go further of course
urge your hand to turn
is it gonna kill me
oh good thing we saved
it went
I don't know about when well who knows
who knows
[Music]
that's not very cool we can try
once more
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
the clips screen branding your mind with
strange runes you see
written fate undone your future
thrumming with power
the book snaps closed
you've seen too much what profane
knowledge is now seared
you you should never have known
well how is it gonna affect me though
this is bad
we managed to read most of the book
observing some of its necromatic power
but it's Snapchat before we could finish
it there must be a way to reach the end
now
can I
uh
what am I what do you want me to look at
hmm
oh this one is this new
yeah it's new when I talk can I talk to
the book
maybe I just
no target though
oh
ah yeah I had uh this necklace
but how do I continue talking to the
book
can I talk to the spider I guess that
the spider is also an animal not just a
corpse so
animal that animals don't work right do
they
inside
oh no it doesn't
corpse reminds them about wait there's
one here
ouch ouch
uh ah [\h__\h] now I have the long rest
book is act free stuff now oh really
okay okay
now I have the long rest to use no no is
it okay if a Starion talks
to the Dead one anyway
that's not one
pile of bones doesn't work huh
wait uh yeah right it's like this
skeleton would work
right
on it
what
I can't select it
oh
well then none of these really work I
think
well
they need to have a working mouth to
talk
the skeleton does I've seen talking
skeletons before
she can make us oh yeah okay
well but I don't know who I would talk
to
um
save and jump into the into the Hall
something down here
what do you recommend I buy your album
I'm obviously interested in physical CD
ah are you saying you can't get it from
the official shop you can use one of
those proxy Services chat please
recommend uh the ones that you always
recommend
it will make it
much easier
pencil yeah look up tensile make an
account there I guess and with tensile
you can order from any Japanese shop
that does not normally ship to you and I
think it's also like a more reasonable
price right
oh yeah I do there's geek Jack too my
album is also the physical version is
also on geek Jack look in the link in
the description should be there the kick
track link
but geek tag sometimes also quite
expensive
um
attempts or so expensive but reliable
you might want to compare I guess
but yeah
easier would be geek check I think
for you
but sometimes
[Music]
messes up things a little bit from our
experience why are you guys saying to
jump in there
oh
no no no no no
[Music]
foreign
s
I saved I did I did
why you guys never look when I say
you have used featherfall first does it
even work on the whole party
what's happening
huh
oh it's the whole party
well are we dead
no
does that mean I died
[Music]
it crash
laughs
huh
let's try again
of course I didn't do final fall you
guys just said save and then jump nobody
said save and then feather fall and then
jump
and you probably did it on purpose you
wanted me to die once
okay uh feather phone
who has it
has a H that's it you are nearby Alice
gained immunity to Falling damage
wonderful what a wonderful thing to have
[Music]
um
again
like this
that's a very different way of falling
very different scene now
oh
foreign
I didn't even think about jumping down
there guys
we go deeper and deeper and deeper this
was like the Shadows Minecraft territory
[Music]
what's happening
is this
Outlander Abbas jumper colic is inspired
is this I was gonna say is this a place
that's like connected to
bye
is this this looks like this looks like
the place
yeah but we can kill this one easily we
just killed oh there's more
ah
is this is
this doesn't look like it
where's the
where is this
safe Zone
Mama Mia that's a lot to explore
I hear Maybe
could be it
over there there's this big gate over
there it looks like it what is this
though
it's not
um
ah how did you see me
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
I will explode this today this whole
thing wow it's gonna take a while right
oh man he's got the high ground but he's
gonna come down to me right right right
right
[Music]
have a little fun
all right
we're gonna fight We're not gonna run we
missed
wait
can I
um
of course it's hot in here
where's the blessing
where's the blessing this is the
blessing
you
[Music]
okay
um
how about a halberd
[Music]
een there
Museum
I didn't know you could skip 75 percent
of act one like this
I'm not trying to skip anything
I'm actually trying to go as detailed as
possible
[Music]
no
this is my happy place
you're a happy place
what makes you say that
I don't want to walk over there you walk
to me oh man
[Music]
I'll try
hmm moving
you come to me
I'll Shifty to hide your whole party
okay we're gonna go
over here what the amp that has so far
proven himself very very of being the
replacement of quasel
so far three misses are the free attacks
oh
it's okay I'm happy with the skills that
are being shown to me right now
oh
yeah he just skips Carla why
weird
lactate
we did lactating damage
oh
oh nice oh what the what
you killed my protagonist
the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
um
I can't give up not now
oh
hello
[Music]
um
don't you die on me yeah where's my plot
armor
came to the wrong neighborhood I'm so
scared
it's so pretty though
I just the only
only living things around here I wonder
um
[Music]
yes
from the blood okay
you can hear the Right video again up as
long as you oh
oh I don't have to help her up first
okay
frenzy versus Frenzy
the HP went down but I didn't see the
attack happening what's what
is this bug
that must be a bug right
I heard the sound effect and nothing
happened so okay well at least we hit
apparently
um
yeah this fight is going fine I don't
know why we were so scared of the
middle Towers in our collab we could
have totally fought them
easy
and now now we're getting all the damage
back that we were supposed to make when
we were missing oh opportunity attack
oh he's running oh
I'm dead imp almost dead that's okay
it's okay we can just re-re
en
[Applause]
[Music]
we summon him
um
what do you mean come on
okay
yeah do the weapons have short movements
seems like it
actually
why can I not Elder blast
o
because I just woke up
[Music]
can I do something else like throw
something
probably not right no actions allowed at
all I assume
chunk of potion I don't think I can
because it's grayed out too because I
already used my hex bonus actually now
okay
well Shadow heart maybe you feel me then
but first asterian
I'm an advantage for both of them
let's try this one
but
after eight
give me big damage pray to the iron
Jesus and give me big damage please
I guess I gotta go back to church after
all
Christmas
let's go
oh we're car lacking now
for locking and car liking
go for it
that's nothing compared to what asterian
just did it should be ashamed
no what the [\h__\h]
no damage
now even we could finish this we should
we should finish them off except instead
of healing while we're healing the Wawa
[Music]
um
what how
I guess a fireball could do it
46. no
the other one's 80. oh oh let's do that
one
safety okay
okay one down
one more one more
down by the river to beat the end just
changed
I've noticed I did a big kill
oh let's go where is it where ah there
you are why can't you just attack
normally go go go go
whoa whoa
you missed everybody except for me ah
zero
that's okay we're finishing this now
okay
another big one
two
peace
just do a normal one
ah really
[Music]
wow and wait don't do not get exp when
I'm dead
for her
does she get exp
I do okay as Darren is caring
on the diet as a family Amulet of the
Unworthy
were they unworthy that's so sad grants
resistance was sliding them again this
is kind of good
true
oh wait
principal grants
vulnerability
isn't that negative
yeah
huh
it would only be good to wear this if I
knew that I was going up against an
enemy that does slashing damage but no
bludgeoning damage
how would I know that
I guess I'll feed it to Gail
would be funny if this Minotaur had like
the opposite necklace
but no okay
well
how we doing
all right time to see what's new Horrors
waiting for us
can I talk to them
the corpse remains
okay let's go let's go was it this way
yeah I think so
enjoying BTA PC free
there's more
um
maybe I go camp
Mamma Mia
okay it's not just those two now we know
Young
mother mother
oh very crystal in oh fresh one
wow
let's go this way I hope it doesn't
spawn another Minotaur I think we we
fought the one in this area
so let me just loot
it's a sassy tree down here what what
what did I need the sausage refer again
something
something oh
that's cute
I'd pass them
let's go let's go oh
blast mine what the [\h__\h]
this arm that [\h__\h] right now
do it I don't even need uh maybe I did
need it
12 10.
trash
where does this go
oh
huh
what
huh didn't like this Army
it was more well I guess
[Music]
oh what in the nine Hells is that
the coming
um okay
[Music]
still your mind to this unusual one this
might be some Devil's Ploy don't listen
to it
yeah
should I cam
AWA wow we're trying to catch up oh nice
blah blah
cute
mushroom cam
cute girls throw a ball held firmly in
his mouth oh you have balls
hmm
let's start to move one hand and slip
the ball from his dress with you oh
let's see I wanna wrestle the ball but
he only has extras for this one bonuses
oh nice
hey I don't like eating them but these
kind of like mushroom glowing especially
glowing mushroom cave by omis like those
are
um
excellent Divine exquisite
you just put his eyeball I think where
your hand went that's where his eyeball
was not his mouth ball
I've I've hit
cute dog oh my God
cute
I have four DMS ah yeah
okay
I received the ball
okay two steps
anyone else who wants to talk wow oh my
God printing
[Music]
wow
wow okay okay oh Gail
oh oh okay okay okay
yeah okay
I need to consume some powerful magic or
it may become volatile yeah I'll give
you something it's okay I have a lot of
stuff now
uh I guess I'll give him the amulet I
don't need it right
now
[Music]
this one's so cool
what is this weird sound in my ears
[\h__\h]
oh my God this is like weird days
somewhere do you hear this
the bats
sounds so funny
wait I keep on tapping out sorry there
you go
oh
okay for this one yeah
you happy
oh
[Music]
hmm
it is a strange experience
each time I knew I can't
lost soul is splunking through the
darkness that is me only to be
sacrificed on the dread altar of the
heart but
I feel quite right
it never feels right but it relieves
this doesn't relieve yeah oh
um
it doesn't
oh
please tell me I didn't just waste my
magical equipment just in Chief aren't
you
magic isn't having the effect it should
have yeah it's not like the last time
like a rainstorm that quells a forest
fire
it drizzles why are you Romancing so far
no one
fire remains undefeated I don't quite
feel like it yet but nothing good
please I need to think
I'm not in the mode Trace My Steps to a
Glade of calm
I think
thank you for the artifact
it's a great deal of trouble it was too
a great deal of trouble indeed you're
welcome I guess I'm sad I didn't help
you so much but
well
man I could look at this stuff forever
but we shall rest
and go fight more minotaurs
this is
how many do I have
um
only two in the area
I mean a tower I mean a tire
maybe that's the Australian way of
spelling it and actually it's spelled
minol t-o
Australians say we know Terror
okay so uh help
let's
can we get over there can I jump there
why is it so purple
should I be scared
let me also check in the crates though I
think they're just supposed to create a
wall but oh on torches
hey
I'm looking forward to reading that
fully
thank you
oh four of those kids Mercenaries
useful friends
if you can afford them oh that's a cool
logo
what what did you just call them
oh
oh that's a a big looting area again
arsonist's oil that belongs to me
oh my
oh no I hope nobody's gonna get mad for
me stealing all this stuff
um
the naming sense of all these Camp you
know they could have just made one
General item camp supplies but no they
just create a million of food and
drinking items and they make it sound
and look so yummy
ah
hello so much care for detail
should be easy
it's not sailing if it's not red exactly
game game
Logistics yes
there's a salami you can use as a weapon
oh really
salami
I love black Mommy
I hope I didn't miss much
um we are focusing on finding the iron I
still have in front of I thought I would
find it quite quickly in that little
village but then we went deeper and
deeper and deeper and now look where we
are now
is it actually like on the Overworld and
I my mistake was going so deep
we'll find it well we're finding many
exciting things so skip that where's
what I skipped it
I mean I skipped it
it wasn't
it wasn't the Fords no no the bakeware I
was so happy about the the big fire
was that in the house with the hole in
the middle
it was up a lot hey
guys you should have stopped me
that was our original purpose oh
wow
wow starting a fire
where does this leave
oh we gained experience
why are the others not following me
no
oh they look so pretty
um
yeah that that that looks like a rotten
lemon if I've ever seen one yeah
wow
so realistic
Barrel aged collateral
I don't drink alcohol but they just make
it sound so sophisticated
what are we trying to perceive this time
[Music]
yeah yeah I'm probably just gonna
teleport to the Overworld but I want to
continue here too so maybe until I find
the Waypoint in the mushroom World down
here I know where it is but we went the
other direction because this is
curiosity inducing
Scroll of fast life oh
why did it jump why did the chest bounce
this game is a horror game for me jump
scare game
Wilder's jumpscare another one that's
why there's so many
um lock picking tools here huh
it was a trap that's what I didn't
perceive right
it's okay it was just
it's just a small one
I'll just try again
you don't spend the tools if you succeed
oh wow I didn't realize that that's why
we have so many too
if they keep on succeeding
I think that's pretty much
everything
I tried to open
now we can leave
I think
this one I opened too right now oh
I guess not but that's okay I don't need
it I don't need everything
um
can I take this without falling down
souvenir be careful hysterian
okay
this one I didn't loot you're saying
are you sure
[Laughter]
I'm just here to pick some locks and
flex oh okay
I'm not here to loot I'm just here to
show off yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
coming back
in the other direction wait how do I
jump jump
maybe just maybe
maybe Wawa
you can jump
here instead
do it smart
okay that's I'm impatient okay
let's go
oh there's a path down here too but
uh
I don't know where to go okay let's go
down here
it's so pretty
ah
the urge is urging me
dark or heavy chest which chest is that
have a test have a chest
it's inside
oh
nice perception
let's get going do we have to lock pick
oh no
scroll up whole person
cool
how's my weight looking ooh we can just
move some things I guess
um
here's some beautiful jewelry for you
just for you
I'm not making you carry it so I don't
have to carry as much no no I just want
you to have this beautiful loot
everybody gets a share you just get the
useless stuff here then take a ticket
send food to the camp oh
oh
no it's okay that sounds annoying
doing that one by one unless there's a
do it for all options
ah cute I have a cauldron raise a lot
well which one which one
add this one
ah 10 pounds
all right okay
known to cause confusion
best not get too close him masks
what did
oh geez
don't get too close she says are they
gonna automatically puff puff puff
can we go up here
ah this is where we were okay so
oh
what are those what is that that enemy
down there
interesting
maybe we should try to get to that big
door first then
mushroom enemy
wow
what is that
what the [\h__\h] was that what is that
ah
what's happening
[Music]
huh
oh
is it not gonna let me in is that what's
gonna happen to me
can I not enter from this side
I don't know
oh okay so I won't get that Waypoint huh
in that case
maybe this is better for another time
when we get the Waypoint and then from
here on out explore this whole area
you can't try but won't involve
yeah yeah I know that's from the collab
I know I know I already recognize that
quite immediately
I could get in from the side
[Music]
I see
yes I could I could try
um I don't want this journal though
hmm I can't sleep with without the moon
and stars as a child I prayed to them
before I ever knew salian's name is that
blasphemy when I walked to the
battlements the only light I see is the
glow of their eyes out there waiting I
know the high initiate is making a plan
he'll get he'll get out he'll get us out
of this
[Music]
is a prayer
Naruto
okay let me just get in this journal too
who's
moaning
in the mushroom lands
vaying glorious to think my Deeds worthy
of a personal Journal but as I watched
the Drone Mass outside our gate I
realized my arrogance is already of a
far costlier sort I see no harm in
tipping the scales a little further not
for me but for those who followed me
down into the dark
they deserve to be remembered in a shade
Northern Remus Lost In The Deep panels
as we fell back from the drought
initiate folk of the northern race
crashed by an arrow and succumbed
succumbed to poison
it is
who stood against the rider with only
her mice and Hammer and initiates they
are
the entire company for they have seen
and suffered too much to be called
nervous
we've collapsed the tunnel behind and
have made ready to open the gate perhaps
we can carve a path through and if not I
enclosed a list of names let the animals
show that whatever their end the cause
was the same one high initiate Jesus
wished to stamp his name in the history
of his church he saw a 240 path through
the darkness not realizing but there are
some places the light was never meant to
touch he was a fool
yes it totally sent Jesus
I'm so proud you guys normally say my
accent doesn't sound like anything is
supposed to sound like but now you guys
are saying it sounds like oh excalib
Ur uh it sounds like um like Scottish or
Irish and I'm quite happy that I'm at
least sounding like anything at all
it was good Irish
why is there an ex caliber
or is it the master sword
I'm improving it was very good oh my God
night light cute
is it gonna hurt me
there's a helmet next to it too oh
why would you fail now
Carla how about you take it
pull it out
Blade impales the stone before you oh
it's pretty silent vigil
grab the sword of both hands and pull
um yeah I think she just got the
strength for it
15.
oh
oh wow we have an elixir of Hill giants
cool plus two only
should we use it
I feel like
huh oh cool
guidance is enough what else am I gonna
use this
normally I I
save everything for I don't know when
but now I actually said when else am I
gonna use it can you believe it that is
so out of character
with 10 people for the blade do we get
them we get it yank the weapon slips
free from the stone she is Arthur
whoa whoa
oh
we're saved follow I love
that is so cool
it's not as good as what we grow
apparently in terms of damage
um
oh it gives me
falar aloof Melody
it's a Bard sword
the Risa
does she know about this
Larissa
I found a pirate sword in the mushroom
place
we could get it in the colaba
do you know it
could get it in the collab next time for
you
we have a wave
point there
no I don't think she's watching right
now
hmm
Shadow heart can use it for that debuff
buff though if you want oh really
foreign
which what what do you mean
what do you mean
this one
hundred percent well
I don't know what to look at
[Music]
pretty unique weapon and then it's a
long sword with the Finesse property
meaning a DEX belt can use it
I don't know
she's not proficient with it
[Music]
we'll just keep it for fun then at least
for now it's cool to have
I would like to have a book here to
explain to me how that sword came here
why is there not a book
why is there not
why the draw inscription on display it
appears to have been recently carved
it's translated though I have to leave
you I will Dance Forever in Alice Alice
tries light
someone had to leave this blade behind
me because they died
that's why also the the helmet is here
can
I need a book to explain more
why is there not more
is there more lore it's an Elven God
oh
tell me more tell me more like does he
have a car hey
can I just walk by
someone's laughing like crazy
[Music]
that's not funny
it's just not funny huh
[Music]
she has been what was going on she has
been down what do I I can't why uh I
guess I'll go to the side
or so
that's why it's asking me to oh my God
stop shaking despite everything
laughs
there's no time to waste
is that why why I didn't even change it
on my own ah where I'm helping to get oh
maybe later
[Music]
I thought I should just move out of its
way
what the [\h__\h] is that
well now we're fighting it then it can't
bother me anymore a bullet predator of
the dark is it gonna suck me in like the
in in the depths of
tears of the Kingdom
it reminds me of that
fine that's about as much as the spider
had mama mama mama and there's not even
more spiders here so
Sarah let's go
wait
each other heart bless
bless us please
[Music]
foreign
wake
me
[Music]
up bring it maybe
um
he has resistance no way no no you think
so
examine the how
[Music]
um none
yeah
we'll attack other monstrosities before
going after smaller okay so if another
bullet shows up maybe the text never
blood
I just love rolled yeah
um
weapon how about a big hammer
yeah
I won't give in
Never Gonna Give You Up I'm Never Gonna
Let You Down around
[Music]
I saw that coming 65 wasn't so nice
um if only it had four more percentage
then it would have been nice
one that we do with friends
and then
um
can we reach
that's what I thought
[Music]
well dashing and so on will use up and
um on your actions so I'd prefer to
go here and maybe do a ranged attack I
guess
yeah
for a javelin throw a weapon
Javelin doco there we go okay
55 not so much probably gonna miss
um
well
even dad is only 45 but we did hit
now what are you gonna do Dash towards
us
oh oh what is that deadly leap
no
what the [\h__\h]
it's okay uh Shadow heart was not hit by
it if I see it correctly so everybody's
also still blessed
very deadly very very deadly
um
are we in hiking
a little [\h__\h]
yeah getting some HP back
and done some decent damage now
Elaine the Wawa
45 that's not really worth it huh
um
fairy fire
all right
defense
if I throw that at the monster isn't
gonna hit a Starion too
when I get out of the underdog and
obtain some more levels
oh
fine so far we're so fine
it's a challenge I like it
you can name it so it doesn't
if I left click it is it is she just
gonna drink it
like let's throw it like this
oh that's only for that's 100 gonna miss
that's so gonna miss right now
[Music]
acid
um okay
better get to it oh it actually did not
miss I am impressed
ah we have this problemo again
um
I guess I'll just heal myself
I got the big potion
and yeah now
this should do some good damage I hope
yeah 15 okay
follow up with a frenzied strike and I
miss
that's not so cool Carla you are gonna
look so cool
I mean
ah [\h__\h] yeah this one has so bad
movement
Soldier we ain't no soldiers
what's that soldier song
that I'm thinking of
a dead car is dead
no not that one not
no I wasn't thinking of Soulja Boy
leave that the leap is crazy
um
can I hide
why is that working
Too Close oh
wow
um
go for it
huh
yeah better than nothing eight damage
thanks for the membership welcome cute
egg
Charming egg
oh we've been mainly reached there
really
I thought I just don't have to be in the
red area and that's it
how's this doing now still 45.
but if it hits it hits
well
but we got a revive color
um
and
what else could we do 60 oh fairy fire
might be good now
I think I'm wait what 40 wasn't it just
60 a moment ago
huh
oh on the spiritual weapon that's the
spirit oh
okay it will make me lose Plus
when what case I thought what whatever
all the cases where I would lose Plus
oh
so charging anything here or
whoa
so this I could do but this I couldn't
right because concentration this I could
also do
this I could also do okay okay
can I do it
yes I need to try this out but
this I could also do okay you know what
it's just time to try it even if it's
only 45
okay
um
well
to keep going all right Wawa are you
feeling better
you're feeling good
is he hexed yet no
okay now let's Edwards blast him out of
the way go
um
now this is my
she's not doing so well should we focus
on attacking or On Healing
should I just die again
maybe I'll take one of the big potions
okay
I was attacked just kill before it kills
you
I wonder if I could throw something cool
it was just a frenzy strike
okay but it's so loud
healing would be a waste it wouldn't be
enough to take another shot anyway okay
but look at this 55
gonna believe okay okay
[Music]
yes
now
our Hammer also gets a chance
unfortunate for a road
where are you bro you're not escaping
the back
you're not escaping that but
you didn't just escape the battle did
you
no
[Music]
can I find it again and it will be fully
healed to full HP or will it continue on
what it had so far
it won't be fully healed plus 45 it only
ah okay it healed like 40.
that little [\h__\h]
ah I put the wind back in my sails oh
why didn't I drink it I should have just
whatever
um what the hell
I was going this direction was I there's
actually
is that even the right path
sad a lot
there's some stuff here
that is so is that script though that
sucks that he can just like disappear
oh that's a little combination oh get
confused by one blown up by the other oh
[\h__\h] can I blow them up before they blow
me up
[Music]
um come back come back
foreign
nice
and now we gotta get a bit closer though
but yeah we could get a chain reaction
beautiful how about this one
Noise Okay that one's really far hey
wait if I walk into it now is it gonna
affect me no now it's gone
and over here ready for this birthday
ready for this
okay
there's some wait don't go in it yeah
there's some cool stuff there
what the
[\h__\h] are you guys
noxious
dweger Sports servant
um but at least they're like low level
can we not be friends I can't talk to
them
I don't necessarily fight them
when will they notice me
wait what is this way late
I don't know where the hell I am and
where the hell I'm going okay this is a
kind of a dead end huh but it has a
chest so let's go that way
we have to explore everything
come out come out and fight me [\h__\h]
come out you little [\h__\h]
fight me fight me
he's gonna meet me somewhere hmm
lurking in the Earth why is it empty I
came all the way here it can't be empty
huh who loaded this before me
who came here to loot this before me was
it you guys
I'm so disappointed oh wait it goes up
here too
that's where I came for came from
I loaded yeah
it was a Mania
that is
oh my God
well you can't can't blame me it's
really confusing there's some dead ones
here this one's pink
what happened
can we [\h__\h] in a friendly manner
that's the rest of my group oh
oh good question they're too scared to
jump over huh why don't you just jump
automatically I saw you do it before
well in it
why do I need to tell you to do this
why was like Patrick from SpongeBob
after eating a chocolate
Nara
I don't like that
comparison
before
this many paths lies before me and talk
to me but oh wait I thought
actually yeah talking to them seems to
be the number one option
nebulent me young creatures sing many
voices the harmony of an entire
Collective you need my help
sovereign
that's the voice the choir fades
single Melody rises above the others
Rossi and commanding
I am Sovereign
wrapped in fungal tendril no the
sovereign
State your purpose
exploration
[Music]
can I
just over and have a parasite too tell
us the only six safe passage in your
search for treatment our travel is
taking Adventures you can understand and
focus on the servants from my purpose is
private let me pass
these tricks
[Music]
um
wait let me let me get into my character
didn't I have something that like
generally wants me to intimidate people
anyway wasn't that kind of my goal
deceive and intimidate or so and I get a
lot of extras from this role
six for blood
free
[Music]
um
well
[Music]
that is actually really just what I'm
doing right here I'm not really right
now looking for anything to help me move
my parasite I'm just looking around
I'm sorry
I I'm just curious curiosity killed the
Wawa
fungal Roots weave through your mind
seeking your true intent it's the truth
my friend drones a new Melody
cautious but welcoming welcoming descend
to me
the persistent music
Sovereign expects you see we're gonna go
even deeper for real snows that way
yeah
it's like that what
that's not deep that's not lower that's
up high but how deeper into the forest
maybe is it that way
there's shops
is it like a city like a oh Waypoint
found huh I didn't see it
all right then we'll go that way
Airborne Lake Grotto
a Grana let's not touch the Dead one oh
look can we talk to them
let's have him talk
why'd you die
what's wrong with you
the corpse Twitches in response to the
spell so to this we can talk right it's
delicate filaments
[Music]
Circle what Circle I don't even know
about the circle how did you who who I
like its living counterparts the corpse
speaks in your mind
a sprout
that's it that's all you'll say hush die
bam
great Great Wall it was
heart heart
and free the friend writings okay
um
these Great Walls what they what did
they want no
the dwarfs wanted to gnome deaths that
that but you guys are not gnomes
hmm
that was your role in the circle
huh no oh
would be the one with the circle
Sprout's job was to grow
cute
floating no way
here
all together
cute this is power wains you can ask no
more questions
it was very interesting
foreign
you look more like a dwarf
you look like a dwarf
what
why does he look like a mixture did the
Dwarfs
make baby with a quick word
or Sprout and then why can I not talk to
him
okay is it a bug
fungus and
some glaze the grotesque creature's face
and body it's a mushroom voice drifts
into your mouth eyes he just like he's
upon the misshapen servant he's he died
and then the fungi grew on top of him
hmm
with my time to press ahead and look at
all the cute little baby mushrooms oh oh
here it's not allowed to take any of the
mushrooms oh okay I have to resist
they're walking like zombies
what who the [\h__\h] oh why is there a
tiefling
Trader
ah a visitor you're a welcome sight but
let us observe the customs of the locals
yeah the scholars brow tenses his voice
spills into your skull the spores
connecting mind to mind
his face that can really look very
deeply
oh
perhaps not
your mind is far more complex than that
of the fungi
[Music]
ant
the feeling is mutual friend I have only
passing familiarity with the surface
races but I found that there is as much
to learn from an individual as there is
from a community so it is with the
miconits They Live In Harm's Unity but
each has a unique personality
my colleagues and I are working to
improve conditions in the underdark this
need not be such a dire hostile place
okay cool it's curious to find a surface
dweller here what has brought you down
so I know I couldn't stop myself I just
I was I
a while ago but now it feels like feels
like ages ago I was on the surface just
clearing a camp and now I'm down here I
just went deeper and deeper I don't know
how it happened yeah I I literally I got
lost
oh let's not say that that sounds like
it could be offensive to them I don't
know
phenomenon in the underdark I'm afraid I
asked what you were searching for to
begin with
eh
I guess we'll tell him seems like should
be okay you were infected by an illicit
tadpole no it's a miracle you're still
intact you must be worried sick but have
no fear I have a friend no not that
worried to assist
tadpole inside her head but she hasn't
turned
that's impossible
are you looking to have it extracted
isn't
huh
weren't these
didn't I see them on
eh
why is he
aren't uh he's a good are there good
ones
die please hold
I understand your rage against my kin
one of my brethren forced a tadpole into
your eye
or ear they do ears too I could I would
have preferred the ear I stand with the
Society of brilliance
yeah I still don't really know what that
is
[Laughter]
Michael needs wouldn't appreciate us
fighting here I'll listen
yeah if that settles matters for the
time being
would you like a diagnosis well I guess
open your mind to me you're
let us see what probably very
knowledgeable about it
relax
mind search your own
okay
[Music]
as a mellow one's mind peace is yours
the tadpole are there more of him
friendly ones that are on the earth this
size alive
awake oh nice smug this is most unusual
the incubation maybe should be complete
as should your transformation oh but the
lava is infused
it appears to be in some form of stasis
it's just plot armor dude
uh
well obviously the answer is gonna be no
because then the game would be too short
if he could just extract it so what
happens if the stasis the Stacy's go
away I can only theorize
but I suspect your transformation would
be both
agonizing and oh but that's is that meta
gaming should I ask the question anyway
well yes but that wasn't my point
oh yeah so can you extract it
oh the probing was useless in the end no
it appears to be shielded from physical
and magical influence and even without
the shield the extraction would involve
severe cranial trauma cranial trauma
well that's [\h__\h] if if it's both
physically and magically
shielded what am I gonna do I just maybe
I have to convince my mind player to
just leave on his own
the sound doesn't sound ideal it is
the process
yeah I don't like the armor on color
either should you transform
I will happily perform a new examination
[Music]
um
foreign
I have never set foot on one myself
they were our warships during the
greatest eras of the illicit Empire
we ruled the entire astral plane from
their decks the design was lost when the
gift rebelled and ended our Dominion
that gift check
the all the gift checks all of them
I really love this sentence
my apologies
experience was not tomb
thank you
oh
be away
wage stasis oh there are many alchemical
substances that can influence the mind
uh bypass what kind of alchemy are we
talking about a tincture
[Music]
subtle psionic
I would require
fresh ton of mad
but be warned you his brain is in their
natural state both of these mushrooms
can be quite dangerous
timasks cause confusion in those that
approach them
tongue is
self no no it's not what is what does it
do
what does that tongue do
what where do I I know where to get the
thin masks I mean they're all over but I
didn't see any tongues
tongue of Madness
did I see that somewhere
eating those doesn't sound I love it
where did I find it
um well yeah I know is that also a
mushroom because she says mushrooms
the underdark of course although they
are quite rare and their Discovery
perilous but so far I couldn't pick them
up I would have them in her possession
she served mistra as a Clara so we get
it from someone else Lenore
Lenore not lemur right so
um
Southwest when I last saw her although
her Tower does have a tendency to move
Southwest of the underdog or Southwest
of the Overworld
why would a Clark have a bunch of
dangerous mushrooms well why not why do
we have so many mushrooms for camping
materials in the on the dark oh okay
Southwest
um
I'll come back when I find it Swift
even Swift okay and now can I use you as
a shop too
welcome back have you made any news I do
enjoy a good bargain if anything in my
private collection yo he's got a good
amount of money
what else does he have
race sickness fog Cloud charm all the
daggers
oh
Fringe philosophy was this the life
fringo
pretty
the wire can stay in a dark up to 12
meters whenever you burn an enemy you
gain two turns of heat
I
think
Mel's first staff cute
psychic Spark
traditional Dart whenever you cast magic
myself is anybody casting magic Missile
I don't think anybody's question
circle of blasting scorching Ray
wait
hahaha
I just read genital striding
the staff is very good
for for Gail I'm not bringing Gail along
though
um
I think I'm good I'm just gonna sell him
everything
[Music]
uh
should I sell the books now that I read
them I guess so I want to make my own
Library
read this
I think pretty much everything did I uh
no need to keep them oh that's so sad
do I have to read this
I'll keep that one
no push I'm keeping this one so until I
find the other ones I can't move it okay
um
I want to find the other volumes
sell coins
[Music]
um
why don't we have that head
so stinky
separatory funnel
fluoride charred
[Music]
wow oh the pictures the pictures
25 16.
Isle of saloon
oh
[Music]
okay can I switch to
um
this one's special the storage
interesting
what are these books
Jesus Book around according to bumper
I think so far I always like every time
I picked up a book I read it
quite immediately so we're probably good
oh Nyx
keep the shovel I need to shovel oh is
it for those dirt dirty dirty things
okay
thank you for telling me
um
chain mail
okay looking clean
oh he's gonna run out of money
any seconds now
foreign
clothes I'll keep them for a little bit
longer
cauldron
we almost got it
Second Shop here too oh okay
well she's pretty much empty
what about these Soul coins
oh wait now I understand the sentence I
think these coins can power infernal
engines is that necessary to make the
infernal iron perhaps
when we're looking at an infernal engine
though it was powering itself even
without the coin though
save the song okay okay
oh ah
okay then we'll definitely need them so
let's not sell them
oh here
rotten mushrooms maybe you guys can
restore them
um
that's so weak
okay
we left him with a tiny amount
of money
very well I have mushrooms to catalog
okay good so let's continue
Trader appear as encouraged by your
interest in this
of course you'll need to pay for it
no more
only when my father was free to read why
do you want me to
pay for that
wow
where is this
Big Boss
oh these ones I can loot these ones I
can't why
did I come from here I don't think oh
hey this one I can also look what is
this randomness
there's a there's a gnome
whoa
there's um
oh my God I watched this video of an uh
like a big big Ox being transported
um was it an ox I'm not sure being
transported monster in a car that was
like altered uh this is somewhere in
America did you see it yeah yeah the car
that was like altered like half of the
car was like cut off
and he was just taking the ox for a ride
or something but then this is so funny
they don't even mention it a bull yeah
they don't even mention it but you see
in this some some of the scenes of the
back of the car that like
the back side of the car is like just
covered fully in [\h__\h]
from the bowl
nobody even talks about it
and they're just like well this this guy
he was driving his um Bowl around I
guess we're sending him home he
shouldn't be driving around with the
bull here but it looks so cute so so
comfortable and I mean it was probably
not that comfortable but it seems so
calm seems the shrooms are letting in
more people happy you see Bella on his
own on your way in dwarf no balance his
name no
I don't think so have I deception yes
I've met maybe you know what I'll say no
but then
I'll do it I don't know why I would do
that why would lie about that but we
like lying don't we
I totally have oh my God yeah
wow so devilish where ugh never mind
idiots probably wandered someplace else
since you see him again tell him to get
back here to me okay but he's gonna say
Jew as it is
okay who is he to you my useless husband
oh send him for an errand it's no
surprise he's made a mess of it
um
oh she's also a Trader I could look for
him for a price
please I know better than to promise
coin to a stranger the colic improves or
he won't okay longer
what a Bladen wasted a beat come all the
way down here for nothing
okay well
I tried
does anybody have animal I have a scroll
for animal jet
maybe we should use it
um
does it look like ah this one
ah no that's animal friendship convince
the Beast did not attack you
uh maybe I don't have it
huh
animal speaking
animal friendship no ah what
I do have a potion
is it worth it
just for this until your next long rest
hmm
when did I last longer long rest now and
then drink it
ah
not worth it
oh we'll drink it
um
does it just work like that
he treats me good now oh the husbands
kicked me anymore anymore
oh okay yeah it wasn't really worth it
couldn't even have a proper conversation
Sovereign glut
en what does that mean
s
oh
how far you've come
reach into memory
tell me
a home
um somebody said I should talk to him
after I talked to the sovereign
maybe I'll do that
don't do that then
these people you know they're also
colorful I like it
but anyway is this where I ended from
[\h__\h] I went in a circle again
down here
lasso light
I'm too scared to pick it up
what's going on here
where's the Sovereign is it like over
here
tonight no I feel like I feel like this
is dangerous I might want to jump
um
well they just walk over normally can I
do that too
oh okay never mind
the water looked that was him yeah
the dead body one was
oh
wow that's you ah you're feasting
okay I went into the into the right
direction though what's over here
that's where I came from that's where I
really came from
hello
I have finally arrived
this place is a little bit of a maze
very pretty
yeah I can't really tell any of them
let's talk
suffering's thick fingers strong the
corpse at its feet
droning Melody greets you as the
creature turns its gaze to you
stalker
I show you a memory
watch I'm not a flesh stalker I'm a
sleep Docker violent Vision grips I am
talking America dark dwarves chopping my
canid remains
hmm
The Sovereign song slows to the pace of
a dirge
why why people so greedy
[Music]
what
the suffering song halts is it okay now
it's been five hours
I sense your resolve hmm
lends the rot
destroy them
Invaders we can manage that better than
picking this fight surely
shadowheart who asked you to talk excuse
me
um
why did these Dragon are attacked
first world into familiar shades
gnomes in
nuega
[Music]
it is a guest huh
then you mean the Norms where your
guests and the dweger started attacking
them that still doesn't really say why
you Harbor a fugitive gnome
[Music]
Sovereign says nothing but you hear
appreciation in its song
[Music]
um
but what's the once the dwarf's problem
of The Gnome I get context for it later
okay
sure I'll handle them then maybe they're
high on all those Sports they don't know
what they're doing
it will help you exterminate
huh
The Sovereign gives you one more Vision
a wall that finds party to reveal
glowing life oh I saw some Vines
[Music]
circle of service
we will await word
okay sure
um
hey sport grenade okay all right so I
have to uh oh you revived oh you make
him you make the Dead
dwarves into servants like that
oh
good recycling
okay so now we go to the other one
necromancers wow
interesting
the injured gnome
oh
oh what the [\h__\h]
that's uh
that's a dinosaur
hook horror Sports servant so you're
telling me there's a non-spore version
of this
dinosaur
oh wait there you are
fresh what does tongue
there's a there's a German word called
glutes
but what does it mean in English in this
context
memory
memory tell me of home Happy five hours
I'm so tired today but I might end it
soon
oh
from gluttony okay
uh
tell me of home
Envision the banks of Shield Tara green
and third element imagine the bustle of
the city's Marketplace the wine I don't
know any of these places
uh
my home is wherever I travel it reveals
its own home in
retain Market corpse
corpse
I am a sovereign
oh
[Music]
cleanse different Circle oh
I mean join you
you can join me
oh
I'm not traveling with some overgrown
mushroom oh does he would he replace
someone in my team
can you make yourself useful
becomes your ally
[Music]
I'm crazy
ah you mean okay if I kill someone we
can raise them back like we just saw
cool okay
he's like a pet oh he'll be a familiar
okay cool
cool very well
[Music]
mm-hmm
we cleanse the rock together so with him
I can make more and more and more
familiars
oh
just for the meantime I guess though but
oh he's following me
nice
thank you
okay is this the
who's in there a pale corpse
that's not a gnome that's the tiefling
isn't it
I must enter this place
are they hiding this from me
my reward
a drone
killing the dwarves if I kill them
oh okay thanks I guess
hmm
okay
probably actually a good place to start
but I want to wait we have a waypoint
here right let me just get the freaking
iron
now we have this Waypoint I need the
um if I go to blighted Village it should
be
should be good
[Music]
might die if isolated from it just stay
here remain
remain in the other doctor this oh oh
but I can just get him back right I'm
pretty sure
it's on the map
here
times
or is there another one
[Music]
okay so the house
with the whole another time
[Music]
let's go
oh my God normal air
can't believe it
and then
oh there it is that was quick okay
[Music]
so
oh
wait that's where I put whatever I'm
supposed to find I guess wait wait wait
you guys said there's a ladder
could you do this for me please
well some may did you finish it
yesterday I had to go to sleep did you
finish it or did you take a break and
you're gonna do finale part two
you did right did you not struggle with
the like for me the switch between the
boats to the helicopter it was just so
sudden I failed each time and then
redoing it takes so much time because
you have to start from so far back right
did you struggle with that you should
you did it like 10 times
oh my God
I had to do with fixing task manager for
the last qte oh is it the the like was
there this bug with the FPS
oh my God
see I ended up just giving up because
apparently it really wasn't much more to
go anyway and I was so like pissed off
already
I was so mad I spent hours and hours and
hours and hours on this game and then
they're just so [\h__\h] rude to me at
the end I was so done with it I respect
you for
going through with it man you're such a
gamer
like that at the end
and
[Music]
ah
at least give more checkpoints
okay that was a really bad role
oh we can we can mod roast me right
um mod
I'm also mod on resume Channel
welcome to the mods team we have so many
fifth tools I do I do
let's try again
ah there we go so
and
fun blacksmith's note and whoa
see the forge
[Music]
ah this can help diamond patch up my
engine a skyer
exciting
I can throw that maybe we picked up the
whole Barrel
26 wait
uh
what if I drop it
does it explode no okay good maybe
that's not bring it
it's not bringing
um
what I made wosami a handyman oh because
what what because of the Rancho
wait so I don't actually use this
but you can use it maybe for other
purposes maybe in the future we just
take the
the iron
to the
uh wherever here I guess it blocked a
lot yeah that's okay I'll just teleport
to Diamond
don't I have any closer Waypoint
and this
it's actually so weird
is there no Waypoint inside oh wait do
we even really want everybody to go
inside maybe not or should we test it I
guess let's test it let's save
and see if they're friendly yeah yeah
they should be friendly now right
we had a couple of long rests
surely they forgave me open up please
[Music]
you lead the group people like you and
your face
looks good so far I'll wait for it where
are we that's why that's why
that's not mess everything anything up
now please we don't wanna anger anybody
okay huh okay you know what I would love
to eat right now
roasted almonds from the Christmas
Market
I know I have this sudden urge for it
that's so weird not helping it we're
exposed now okay oh
roasted sugared almonds actually you
know what I think I saw them in the
supermarket before
anyway damn and hey yeah I'm back
yo the search was unnecessarily long I
got so lost
but
we found it please let this work it's
Skyrim
the weight of it
and that blaze of Chaos
I can't imagine this where my heart
should be must be quite the experience
does she need more than one because you
guys said there's more than one
quite common
I think
there want an act one one you have to
install it I'm afraid
I don't think there are thick enough
gloves in all the Realms to protect me
that kind of thing oh she doesn't mind
yeah
put it in show it to us what is this
camera angle that feels
still burning hot as Hell's Hole
feel changeable what does that mean
cheers mate cheers me
I haven't got any solutions now but I'm
not giving up
so it means you can control yourself
better maybe now
so we had some kind of Enchanted coolant
huh find me again in Boulder's Gate oh
if I'm worth my salt we are involved
escape the game take care
and hopefully the next time I see you
I'll have something promising to report
hmm pocket any infernal iron you find
along the way
it seems like we'll have to be looking
very close in every freaking corner for
that because to get this now
I looked I already was looking in every
single corner and I didn't find it I
missed the one thing I was looking for
yeah I know I know she wants to talk
okay chill chill
let's talk progress Damon's upgrade
didn't cool me down but it didn't juice
me up huh I don't think I've ever felt
more powerful
um
[Applause]
let's find some more evil for you to
smack or find more infernal iron and get
you that second upgrade too
sooner rather than later would be good
burning serious fuel
you heard me meowing
hi
[Music]
hi English movie has entered the room
and you're doing oh just rolling around
on the on the floor
um
she wants to burn something
sounds volatile I'll keep an eye on you
will you be okay oh [\h__\h] yes I'm ready
to burn all night
I could eat a giant Badger is it almost
time for dinner
maybe maybe tonight we burn together and
go up in ashes oh wait I'm not a phoenix
in this game damn it can't do it
oh
um
yeah a cool story bro
um we shall continue this was a lot a
lot and I was worried that I would be
forced to go to the goblin Temple
already here I am so far from it still
chilling in this area
oh it's been five and a half hours
actually it's 5 27 now
or 9 9 27 in my local time I have to
read some Super Chat stuff
I think I'll might get a snack down
well to my areas you can do before
Goblin can
oh okay
yeah how's the map looking
yeah there it looks like there's we
didn't go to the
to those no
that was actually one of the goals but I
didn't expect the blighted village
to bring me so much content
holy [\h__\h]
we just casually ran over it in the
collab
but the whole mushroom world
we should probably check that out in the
collab too
because there's the whole city there
yeah money
you're playing this game too
Nani
damn what about this area there's like
still so much I don't even know what a
map ends that kind of sucks they should
make like a border so I know how much I
could still find
oh wait it does end there's no way that
I can fill out all of this
I can't continue scrolling here but
there's no way that this is all
yeah it's not it's not that big right
um nah okay oh it doesn't go to the
edges okay okay
yeah because there's like water here
um
well
I'd love to play more but damn
this is actually finally a good point to
stop
I should make use of it
um
yeah
we're exposed
damn
[Music]
I didn't quite
um play my character like evil today but
that was just so much exploration anyway
and I was just immersed
into the world like crazy
um
yeah lots of combat lots of exploration
and lots of combat
lots of books too lots of cool stuff I
enjoyed that very much
let's go
um here okay
are you doing an evil playthrough well
kind of I decided my character is
actually evil
and so and in previous episodes I was
acting kind of bitching towards
everybody
evil but like maybe not necessarily evil
but but she cares about herself only
mostly or her success and wants to take
over the world I guess there's nothing
evil about that I mean you can you can
take over the world without being evil
but
little little [\h__\h] it's a little
[\h__\h] yeah
doesn't care what what she definitely
isn't uh is not is uh compassionate
so
yeah
oopsie
all right
so
let me fix the chat
[Music]
you don't have to seriously though you
don't have to moderate anything no
worries
[Music]
you
go
[Music]
yeah I have to write Super Chat I'm
hungry but let me just get a snack and
then we can maybe I'll bring some
popcorn I have I ate
too much chocolate these days
the rainbow
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I guess this sounds like it could be cat
food to her
so she attacked me
[Music]
I think it's my only Savory snack so
much
sweet savory
it's my saver
save you
um
[Music]
for everybody who missed the member
stream
I am so sorry
[Music]
to announce that tomorrow's streams
will not be Final Fantasy
I'm so sorry
[Music]
there's raisins for it
well let's not talk about it this makes
me sad
I can't redo
what I have done so
[Music]
um so probably Hotline Miami
tomorrow since I can't stream for that
long anyway
because yeah
um
[Music]
this is actually a good thing
but the convention for me
is like in the evening time
I'll be done at like 8 PM or so or not
yeah 8 pm
this is much better than having to wake
up early in the morning for something so
I appreciate it but because of that it's
kind of like keeping me from doing a
long stream
um
[Music]
yeah the time
wait huh
did I end up putting in the right time
let me see him
oh hey I need to upload the monthly
wallpaper
ah no that time
right after I made that schedule
I was notified anyway of the Toronto
Convention time
right after I made it
um so that changed anyway to me
streaming deciding to stream at 8 30 or
so instead
after I'm done with the convention
um four and a half hours later than
scheduled
foreign
16 cancel all together which is tomorrow
[Music]
I know that
not so many of you are actually
interested in it
so
I'm sorry
but I still feel like I should at least
give it a try maybe I'll at least start
it and if I like it then I'll continue
it if I don't if I'm not like Dad
Enchanted by it then we can drop it and
I can play it privately
[Music]
yeah
we're trying at least for like one or
two streams
and then I'll decide what to do with it
um
I was thinking that
even if I don't think it's good to
stream it
and I'll definitely play privately
it would be nice to have a
a big jrpg to play offline
[Music]
but yeah I will play it because I
announced it a million times now
[Music]
and I I I was hyped up for it in the
beginning it's just I killed my own hype
so
[Music]
no Powder skin has nothing
no I mean
I don't know partially maybe a little
bit I don't know
as I said we'll see
if it catches my interest
[Music]
um
I couldn't play it right away
because I was like in Japan right
I couldn't play it at release
[Music]
and then I know
oh yeah because of the London trip I
said I don't want to start a big Series
right now
[Music]
um
yeah this and that
oh yeah my outfit got delayed I was kind
of waiting for the outfit that's too
um
oh yeah yeah now first I deleted because
travels and then I delayed it because
the outfit was delayed but then I could
still already play something some some
bigger games so I decided let's pick up
GTA
and then if I get the outfit then I can
play
um FF on the side
but then yeah
then that's where all the canceling [\h__\h]
happened
[Music]
now picking GTA was not a mistake
no because it was fun I had fun
[Music]
I was waiting for an opportunity to play
another GTA game anyway
[Music]
see see how many people are enjoying it
you know everybody has different
um
genres and so on that they enjoy the
most but GTA was very popular so
[Music]
what you're snacking on
hot mama uh proper corn sweet and salty
that I bought and I stocked up on in
London
[Music]
I
I didn't get the PNG yet
because
um
[Music]
there were some complications and uh
yeah I was told to have the PNG go
through management because like all the
all the communication went for
management
um
and he only uploaded it on Twitter right
so I was like okay this is not a PNG so
I went to management and I was like um
can you guys ask SWA for the PNG and
they were like
yeah
we'll do that and then some things came
in between
and I think they were sorted out but now
still waiting just a couple days ago I
asked so how about that PNG did you guys
get in get it like you know for me
and then one staff was like oh yeah I'll
ask
it's like it goes over
several people somehow I suppose let me
ask again
because I think it was forgotten again
[Music]
where is it
um
[Music]
okay
how about now
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
now I'm asking for another update
I want my PNG sword I want to try
putting it on my back I want to see how
it works
[Music]
okay
thank you
I just ordered the cereal PV thank you I
appreciate it
I hope it will arrive soon everybody
um remember Link in the description in
case you haven't ordered a physical
version of the CD yet I would be very
happy if you wanted to order it or just
get a digital version in iTunes or
wherever because we're charting right
now and would be cool if we can start
even higher in some countries where like
in the top five in the music streaming
services so whatever you have like
Spotify or anything similar to that go
check out my album there and listen to
it there that would be really cool
[Music]
mind
do I have
[Music]
feelings training point of view Stream
Point of View don't check my phone oh
thank you
I bought antifreeze on Amazon thank you
yeah Amazon music also
don't forget about Amazon music we're
doing pretty well on Amazon music too
hmm
[Music]
I bought it on both thank you
Spotify has a lot of views I don't use
Spotify I don't have Spotify so I never
knew
um until you guys posted screenshots
how many
streamsori and Sparks Etc has
I didn't know it was in the Millions
I honestly did not expect that at all
what the [\h__\h] I thought it maybe at most
will be in the
in at like 100
000 or so
I think people were actually listening
to my music on Spotify
that's that's crazy
[Music]
I can be blamed for a lot of those thank
you so much let's get them
the new songs up there too 124
000 monthly no way
people actually listen to my music
regularly what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
like on on the Music Services that's
that's so cool
what the [\h__\h]
that's so cool where do you see that why
are you surprised I don't know I just
never felt that because I never saw that
and I never like really like like saw it
these numbers I don't
I haven't been told like my actual
like numbers of you know my my streaming
numbers on on music platforms
and I don't really
you know normally stumble across them
[Music]
I didn't think people
would really listen to it much on their
free time when I'm not forcing them to
you know
but that's so cool
it's really nice
hmm
I'm I really am happy to hear and see
that
um
so that now there's this big gap between
the five new songs and the five old
songs so let's fill up the gap
[Music]
um
I don't know that
horrible
[Music]
it's time limited for one month I think
to buy it
[Music]
um yeah if people still want it
afterwards and it is doing really well
then we could extend it possibly but you
know just get it in the one month if you
want to get it ideally
[Music]
yeah
you look great you look like a character
in a tails of game
will it be called Tales of kvp tales of
chicken tales of the usual room
hell's no
tales of
well they always come up with these like
weird weird names like Symphonia
I Rise a rise is like basically what it
could be named for me because a phoenix
Rises that could be my Tales of title
phenoxia
[Music]
tales of vervia
yeah there's a big question
there's a Reaper wait there's a there is
a
h
I didn't Tails or Reaper
yeah yeah there's already a tails of
rebirth now it felt so fresh when I just
read it out loud but yeah a pretty old
one PlayStation Portable and Playstation
from 2004 2004.
it's quite good apparently I don't play
it though
I want to
[Music]
see they already used up so many words
that I could use
[Music]
it was like a visual novel um
now the names you guys are coming up
with they're surely jokes right because
they don't really sound like they could
be a Tales of title
[Music]
um
tales of myphopia could be
something maybe
tails of
[Music]
I feel like they like to have something
with like er at the end
[Music]
in terms of Austria
tails of the race yeah
[Music]
anyway
let's just say Tales of arise is my game
since I was the Ambassador anyway
[Music]
proud Ambassador well I still am I'm
still out
[Music]
I'm
yeah I'm Alvin no
Carla is basically elephant
[Music]
um
me and Carla combined are basically
elephant
which is another reason we should camp
together tonight
[Music]
and create Allison
bye Sue
[Music]
yeah
maybe I'll romance room
I'll be very honest with you I know it's
funny and all it's just a funny
aspect I guess also for content
but if I were playing this like
privately I don't know if I
don't really care about this aspect of
the game at all
it doesn't
um feel like
I I don't feel the the the the rush or
the
I don't know anything any interest in
making that happen because I don't know
it doesn't feel real to me anyway
because they're all kissing my ass
I could do it with any of them so it
doesn't even feel real
I guess it just doesn't feel worth it's
just it just feels fake it just feels
forced
it's funny haha but I don't need it it's
too easy too
um
yeah and it's I don't know I don't need
it
[Music]
um
yeah
it's just a little
comedy but
[Music]
don't need it if it gave any extras like
extra Buffs or something
then at least there would be a reason to
do it I guess
[Music]
but there's not right
they will reject you if they hate you
yeah but it's pretty easy to make them
like you
[Music]
generally
yeah I like the all the interactions I
like the conversations
but I just don't really feel the need to
romance them
you know which game is similar and
doesn't have this problem Dragon Age
problem as in it doesn't have Romancing
in the first place is that what you're
saying or a problem as in there's
romance but it's more difficult
[Music]
very big difference between you and
Marissa narissa is just horny
she's just horny
[Music]
but yeah that's a big difference
horny Bonk
[Music]
she lost one horn though imagine it's
full power full horny
oh enough
uh what super chats are we gonna read
we've read the collab Baldur's Gate ride
did we also read the solo louder skate
number one yeah we did because it's
purple for me the link is purple so
let's read Korean stuff the super chats
oh there might be
a lot of Korean that I have to read them
um
[Music]
uh
what's working again [\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
I will read super chats
um
Korean Bros
[Music]
was it right the first time wow
oh my God
oh
okay and turn around thank you soon me
uh
[Music]
mint
mint something
um
[Music]
Italian
thanks for the pinks Super Chat
thanks to your Korean skills have
improved a lot now I think that was
better than me come on don't hang
there is no way I'm not that good yet
that you could say that but
yeah I
I should practice more off stream on my
own too I'm like completely ugh
I can't
can't I need I need someone to push me
to do it
[Music]
cards
combat link I can't even get myself to
look at it
but it's still somewhere in there don't
worry so far it's still somewhere in
there
[Music]
um he he or no
set
pure
[Music]
that it says
hope I read your name correctly I don't
know what it means though what does it
mean is there a meaning to it
oh
yeah
I read it correctly I think hero Dawn
star I see I see
unicorn help you can ask I'm
intermediate but I might be able to help
with any basic things thank you I mean I
do have supposedly some friends and
colleagues who can speak Korean too
though
um although I do feel uh like I don't
want to bother them
[Music]
there was this one time when I was like
I didn't have much time to complete my
homework
and there was something I didn't
understand
so I wrote to a certain Korean speaking
colleague
and unfortunately she saw it too late so
she couldn't help me
not she
she helped with her
[Music]
yeah
but in in theory there I have some
people who know the language and Theory
speaking of yeah bye I I in the past
months I kept on checking the do you
release date
[Music]
to see how much time I have left
um
when was it
[Music]
nine 19th September well it's enough
time to do what I want to do
um
[Music]
okay
although if I do that that will maybe
kind of
move around the other mvs that I was
planning to upload but yeah I was I was
I I will do something for the one year
anniversary of the wheels
and I kept on pushing it away because I
thought oh I still have so much time and
I still do it's enough time but yeah it
just reminded me
thank God it reminded me
[Music]
um
language thank you for the pinky don't
worry about it Kiara you are an
intelligent person also your language
skills are so good keep doing it we also
keep studying English
not English if you just wrote this whole
sentence on your own it's also really
good
[Music]
study hard together
or at least a bit harder than I am
studying now AKA I'm not studying at all
how many signatures did you do not much
time left
I did 200 in my member stream minus
three
so 197
so those those I just did that in one
stream so we're good we're good I can
I can catch up it's gonna be okay
foreign
[Music]
thank God I was having trouble reading
it
[Music]
I told you to give it a try didn't I you
tried it I didn't say it like you you
wanted me to say it I I stumbled over it
[Music]
hey good Strider good try
what there's actually like a little
message there what does it say
oh
just a nice sweet message
saying I'll always cheer for you in
Korean
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
la la
thank you soon
[Music]
it was only half successful
for the pinky Pinky
again
[Music]
but it's already holy [\h__\h] already
September
the year is going by so far didn't I go
to Korea last year in summer
it doesn't feel so long ago it's over or
like around a year ago
[Music]
yeah I was planning on going this year
but I did say I didn't want to go in
summer
um now I don't know if I really have
time to go and
um Autumn but my friend I did tell you
right and to tell you that my friend
also wants to go to Korea or kind of
wants to combine a trip to Japan and
Korea and so I said all right
that actually sounds good maybe I'll
join
[Music]
um so that was if that happens that's
like more in winter time I think
you're super snake Mario
[Music]
the wedding
the wedding is in October that's in
Japan though that's not in Korea
so I've been in Japan in October for two
reasons one is Secret
and one
is um the wedding
[Music]
secret mission basically I'm recording
something for
um
[Music]
somebody's
3D stream
[Music]
say that because that's vague
could be
could be anniversary
could be birthday
or whatever
[Music]
I mean not my own anniversary or
on birthday
because that's not happening
birthday is in
December now
so much for being a cancer
sufficiently vague too
and then for the anniversary I don't
even I haven't even gotten any
information about when that could be
[Music]
hmm
if I even get to do
one in for you
[Music]
oh my God this popcorn is banging
hmm
this bag has some has a lot of
strong flavored ones I like it
[Music]
yeah it's popping off
uh-huh
okay but I've read those
next is Hotline Miami
[Music]
Hotline Miami shouldn't be too much
either
[Music]
there's a rainbow in here
purple
[Music]
let me drink
yeah
dog Hood thank you Father
[Music]
rainbow
Horror Story dance has almost 1 million
views on now it almost has 1.5 I think I
stopped singing my hip swimming in my
hips and shaking my arms so to ask if I
could dedicate a while a kiss to looking
for the top might need a minor surgery
in the future oh for what that's your
boob thank you Wawa back to dancing
between
well wait what you didn't know about the
surgery or about the Super Chat
adding on to my previous red to tell wow
that even when scuff happens we always
appreciate everyone's hard work thank
you oh ah because of the the the concert
was that around that time
was that the same time
I'm sorry you had to find out this way
uh are you doing better now
what happened I think I saw something in
my recommended tweets on Twitter
[Music]
just Twitter sent showing me all kinds
of stuff that you guys are up to
doing okay now okay but you get a kiss
uh get well soon okay so let's just say
you're not well yet mwah and now you are
but that could you get one too
[Music]
double kiss for a beautiful rainbow
thank you so much and yeah I mean I
think uh I mean it was a of course at
the at the moment it was like a bit
upsetting maybe but in hindsight like
not a big deal right just having it
moved to one day later I think the
reason why people were
um and also us were like really like
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
because we didn't know it wouldn't be
postponed to like a week later or
when when but then it was just the next
day so not a big deal hmm
and everybody got refunded yeah you got
refund it let's go and then it was free
of charge so in hindsight in hindsight
good thing for you guys
stressful for
um the cover staff I am sure that they
were extremely like nervous and stressed
out about it and that's what I'm really
worried about
[Music]
um because they were surely trying hard
to make it work the way they wanted it
to work
[Music]
and and then having hundreds and
hundreds and thousands of people being
really angry at them
is probably not so nice and then the
streaming service was probably also
really apologetic and feeling really bad
about it and in the end they refunded
everybody so
everything's cool but you know I I just
feel bad for all the stress they must
have experienced
in such an important moment
no
they were surely a lot of them were
surely up throughout the whole night
because
no I saw that I'm still corresponding
to us
throughout the whole night so
[Music]
um
yeah they've worked so hard
but the interesting thing is I thought
what was it
something is being streamed on spawn
right
something
[Music]
blue Journey
so we can use blue uh spawn
oh okay uh towards live also so really
why was just this one on done I don't
know that's probably internal reasons
that
I don't understand
um
surely there's some reasons well it
doesn't matter in the end
[Music]
they did get it to work
in the end so all is good
um
[Music]
yeah yeah we saved money to
I mean you guys I say we as a new
yeah
for free
um
all of my one day one appearances for
free
[Music]
and a game of Crete Duncan
the game recruit again thank you soon
Patsy thank you soon
I know exactly what you're scouting
foreign
[Music]
Reds Super Chat to follow up because
apparently that's when we got 1 million
million views
for Holy Tony Dance I'm so proud and now
you know what now we have to get
pineapple to 1 million
it will get there I feel like the
algorithm is not so friendly to it at
the moment possibly but that's okay
I mean foreign
to me this video is doing as per usual
[Music]
actually
um
nothing is like doing where's like the
the views are doing as per usual the
other things are like over
um above usual
like
um the
uh average watch time
and
clicking I don't know how to just
translate it it's all German for me
yeah as long as it doesn't get cheaper
night yeah and I think it shouldn't be
the case that's fine it's fine if it
doesn't reach like
certain Milestones right away I just
in general
I mean you know I spent a [\h__\h] ton of
money for this music video
so I would be happy if it would be doing
well if it succeeds
[Music]
um
but it's okay it can take its time a
little bit I don't mind
um but also like just because the the
song and
the Envy in my opinion is really really
good I want more people to see it and
enjoy it
[Music]
why did you not release it before the
album
because I don't know
I am do I look like a PR genius to you
I'm just trying to come up with my own
plans
and this is the best I could come up
with man
why am I
because I wanted it to be
basically I wanted it to promote the the
streaming numbers of the album
if I upload this one before the album is
released then it can't lead to streaming
numbers right away
if I release it basically it was
basically on pretty much on the day of
the album release
for like you know 24 hours later or so
so that way everybody who sees the the
pineapple MB and hasn't paid attention
to the album yet that way they can
um
further on go on to the uh album
foreign
audition started yesterday did they
the problem is I think for Austria they
asked for a new song right now an
existing one for Germany last year I was
able to apply with do you
I think they said an existing song is
okay
[Music]
the album was the focus
yeah of course all the yeah yeah every
song shall be in the focus
[Music]
on its own get some time to shine that's
what the mvs are for and and the mvs are
mostly just to remind people maybe also
people who missed for some reason
pineapple completely later on they'll be
reminded by other mvs that are going up
there they're all just for promotion for
me too
get those numbers higher obviously
those streaming numbers but
um
yeah
and the reason why I'm putting
another 3D MV at the very end
is because
[Music]
well reasons
I don't want to have two insane 3D MBS
right after another I'm putting the last
one uh the the second one at the very
end because I want it to give it another
final push
final push of attention
[Music]
so and I I put a lot of font into it
myself you know
I'm spacing it all out too yeah
[Music]
just keep on reminding people over the
course of like three months
that I have an album now
no you know there's always a reason why
somebody might
miss the first week of promotion maybe
they're on vacation maybe maybe they're
just not much on YouTube during that
week for whatever reason maybe they're
busy at work busy at school
but then later
they can be reminded of it because of my
negligent
question is that the opposite
[Music]
um promotion
insistent yes so I'm spacing it out yeah
for persistent yeah for three months and
give it a last big push at the end with
another big
and be hopefully that's at least the
plan for now
[Music]
um
I mean
it's really just my personal
taste I guess
but also the fact that I know that the
most work
was put into pineapple and sleep talking
because they had the most time they were
done the earliest and they had the most
time though
so in term when you look at it at a
production value
point of view then those two have the
most production value musically
yeah and they also fit
the I am the possibilities
uh in terms of like music videos that I
wanted to do for example for pineapple
you know I have a new pretty outfit with
a swimsuit so the only song that I would
really put that on is for pineapple
because it's a summer box foreign
[Music]
every song sounds like it's got a really
high production
well yeah the thing is a lot of them got
really rushed and they were done like
really last minute so
um
I couldn't plan anything with them and
and I I wouldn't want to have full
quality for bmbs for all of them anyway
because I don't have the money for it
[Music]
um
um yeah
[Music]
also
the typical 2D mvs will be fine
[Music]
that'll be fine
a unique outfit for the album I can't do
that
[Music]
um
in terms of like 3D like I could get
something like
in the quality of those like uh pre-choo
models the smaller ones
um but I don't seem to be allowed to
commission my own 3D outfit for my real
3D model
to put on top of you know what I mean
[Music]
I was like you know because I was really
desperate to get a 3D outfit
um so I was like can I just pay for it
myself can I
you know commission it
but apparently not so I have to wait for
ever I don't know why but I have to wait
forever
uh being able to do a solo live in a
venue big no no not big but like real
life venue you know what I mean yeah
uh like Cali
or another
big milestone like one million two
million three million
so you know how realistic those two
options are anytime soon
not happening anytime soon
but I was lucky this summer you know or
not only this summer I guess the Ian
Idol outfit is already since spring
we got many new objects
four for The Outfits I have a kimono I
have the idol outfit I have the swimsuit
the swimsuit with t-shirts too yeah
[Music]
yeah
yeah so you got another kimono
the Christmas outfits I don't know about
Christmas outfits I don't know if I'll
get any
this year I asked
I asked could we this year get Christmas
outfit but I don't know
happy six hours thank you oh my God are
you a bot
just like
you're so robot or robot or robotic
robot robot like just like a browser so
in character Bebop Bebop
hahaha
you know small 3D models yeah but that's
well
[Music]
not
suitable for serious music videos anyway
practice I have
fought everything through I have my
reasons for doing things the way I am
doing them
you know Dominique K you shouldn't be
sending me concert funds when there's no
concert happening
thank you though
yeah I'm cooking I'm cooking on my own
[Music]
um
seventh evil Duncan oh and that code
again what thank you for the rest of the
chat friends
thanks for the red super chat note to
self hide from tension after she's had a
bad dream love to see you quickly
kicking some Miami behind
yeah I've been having so many bad dreams
last night was okay I think
but yeah the past two weeks I think I
had so many bad and weird dreams
concerning dreams
[Music]
must have been connected to me being
really stressed out
um now it's gonna get bad time sure
[Music]
no I wanna dream normal dreams I want to
dream about cuddling my cats and wake up
next to my cats and then proceed to
cuddle my cat's IRL
must be so stressed I really was
um
no
oh well
oh oh by the way yesterday
I just want to say I really didn't do
anything I was like
um the thing I tweeted
[Music]
some people were like well that sounds
so weird but again other people were
like yeah yeah that sounds like
teenagers yeah think about it the more I
think the more time passed and the more
I thought about it the more I was like
yeah yeah that's a that's a completely
normal thing to do yeah yeah it seems
very reasonable no but I was I couldn't
even paint it for you
if you want
[Music]
quickly
so
[Music]
this was when it was when it was already
dark and you I didn't even see so well
[Music]
this uh
it's not working
[Music]
where's the tip of my
pen
maybe trunkers bitted off
where's the tip of my Wacom pen it's
just missing
honestly sometimes I see chunky monkey
like I'm nibbling on it maybe she broke
it just ripped it out okay let's do it
with the mountain it was a path here
[Music]
I was walking
calm calmly normally
on this side
and I was only holding
a little cup
from McDonald's
I was walking this way sticky Wawa and
then I saw quite far actually really far
away like two girls they were standing
and suddenly they were like
[Music]
are holding each other's hands
and then they started like uh
what's it what's the word like hippity
hoppity dashing
really fast while laughing
um like uh skipping yeah really fast
skipping like big steps
but they were taking up a lot of space
because they were like like their arms
were out like this and they were like
yeah they were not so close to each
other they were just like you know
connecting hands like this and I saw
them
your fast stashing at me
well I was just like slowly walking but
they were like because of the way they
were spreading out their arms and how
they were like bouncing bouncing they
were taking up like so much more space
of the pavement than they normally would
[Music]
and so I was like a little bit slightly
going to the side but it was like I saw
them coming closer so fast without
caring about them being about to like
Bonk into me I was like
wait They Don't Really Wanna
they don't really seem Cooperative to
them
so then the girl that's on this left
side closer to me the moment they really
are like
like one or like five centimeters next
to me in this moment
she stops for a short moment
looks towards me
[Music]
and she screams
okay maybe more like
[Music]
and then to get or they keep on uh
bouncing that way and when when they
screamed at me it was really really loud
and it like acoustically like
I had to say is
um
the the area was like bouncing back the
echo it was echoing that that's the word
and so the people they were actually
like uh
like really close to like behind right
behind me there were a lot of people
seated
um outdoors and they saw and heard it
and they were like they were even like
oh hey
like I was just like turning around like
what the [\h__\h] are you stupid quietly I
was saying that
was shocked what just happened and but
there were some adults sitting there
like ah
and then there was a doggo there who was
like really shocked but also surprised
by the scream so the dog started
um barking
and and you know they were like
immediately back on the way to like
continue jumping so they were jumping
towards the dog
really fast this was happening really
fast
yeah and the dog was like
because he was surprised and then they
were like ah they screamed even more
and then the adults even more were like
hey hey you know
so everybody was just minding their own
business and they like made noise in the
late evening for no reason
um you know I was like baffled at what
just happened
[Music]
I'm not gonna say she like
uh hurts my eardrums but I I definitely
felt it afterwards
for like three minutes that she screamed
into my ear [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
yeah
this doesn't happen all the time though
but it definitely felt like some kind of
tick tock challenge or something it's
not like this is normal okay this
doesn't happen to me normally and I
really didn't like
[Music]
um ask for this to happen I was just
like I don't know I thought maybe maybe
they were drunk or
I don't know what the [\h__\h] their issue
was
they looked like they might have been
like I don't know 15 16 17 no idea it
was pretty dark so I couldn't see him
um I would have tripped them Yo I would
have loved to do that I thought about
that in hindsight
but there's
I know until they screamed at me I was
just thinking oh weirdos
I wouldn't have felt like I needed to
trip them
and when they screamed at me they were
already at the same height
of path that I was on so I couldn't have
tripped them there
[Music]
um
yeah always always in her inside
but I did not what's the word
I did not
say or do anything I was just walking
slowly normally in like in the normal
Pace I wasn't even like looking at them
until they started charging at me I was
like
okay
but I didn't give them a weird look I
just gave them a like a normal uh huh
look yeah I'm provoking I didn't provoke
them
[Music]
no it's maybe for some people confusing
but this is just teenagers being weird
okay it's not that unbelievable it's not
it's not even that much of a crazy story
it just like confused me because I also
don't go outside that much so weird
stuff doesn't happen so much to me
[Music]
teenagers are just being weird but that
doesn't mean then I did anything too
dumb
now
[Music]
and I only think they did this that they
had the balls to scream at me just
because I was like
uh
a girl that maybe didn't look too mature
to them if I was like some adult man or
lady they would have not done that I
think
um
yeah because I was alone yeah
oh God
[Music]
for a moment I wanted to punch them for
being stupid
[Applause]
I want to let out my anger
[Music]
it's okay though it's not like it ruined
my day it was just so weird
the Hat
this never happens like what
the few times I do go outside it's not
like [\h__\h] like this happens all the time
I was just confused
yeah and it's a nuisance because it was
late and and like their Scream literally
like
echoed through the street
and it bothered the people who were
um dining outside too
so yeah weirdos this is why I don't go
outside it doesn't happen all the time
though
they were probably on something I don't
know I really don't know I didn't smell
any alcohol but they were passing by so
fast so who knows
teenagers are just a plague sometimes
they really are
it just reminded me of all those idiotic
teenagers from school school times
[Music]
I have a perfect example by the way I
have a K-pop example of how they were
charging at me
[Music]
here um
I'll give you a time stamp can you
please
watch this
it was even faster than this of course
but
visually this would explain everything
here it says timestamp
I love this dance move though it's so
cute when they do it and they're not
bothering anyone and not charging at
anyone it's the unforgiving one
[Music]
with hand holding they were doing this I
was for I was thinking yeah maybe they
were inspired by La seraphim
and just feeling like they needed to
charge for the streets like that
yeah yeah
it's very specific but it's exactly how
they were charging at me
exactly like that but just even faster
laughs
hmm
I love that dance move
I love it
it's such an addicting dance move even
though it's just skipping
but you must think about how you know
this also this is also so professional
like look at them they're in the middle
of a choreo and then all five of them
have to catch their hands you know they
always have to be in the same space
formation so that you can actually
hold hands like this and immediately
um run off
it's like they're so coordinated you
know
the space between each person is so
important to have this work and then and
and then you know hand holding it has to
be practice so that it goes so smoothly
and you're not stabbing the other with
your nails or whatever I don't know
I appreciate how how smooth they're
doing it
generally this whole choreo is so cool
oh my God can you guys if you still have
the video open go to
um zero minutes and and 38 seconds
oh
watch me now the part where they stand
in a line and she completely in a in a
90 degrees angle Falls backwards and
then slightly tilts her heads towards
you [\h__\h]
they do that twice in the song and then
another one of my favorite moves is
a little bit more before that is that 28
seconds
this is my bias by the way Jai won
this looks really good in in their
actual live performances on stage two
yeah so the flow from her crawling on
the ground and then later the other girl
they're on the line and they she does
the 90 degree angle
um
yeah they're all like super flexible and
oh my God this choreo is so cool
there's like times where I really wish I
was a whole K-Pop group of several
people because that opens so many
possibilities for choreographies like
cool formations like this
but unfortunately I do my music solo so
yeah
sometimes I wish I could do all of these
things
all these cool choreos
I was on to something with do you yeah
I've been getting this feedback uh like
twice or so the other day
um oh my God Kiowa you're like a like a
whole K-pop group in one person a whole
K-pop girl group and one person I'm like
let's go
cute compliments
I wanna I want I want to have like five
people to do all these like cool
formation are they really difficult you
know and you know what I especially hate
is
um
What's called the positioning you know
remembering
positions like the red spacings and all
that especially if there's no numbers on
the ground normally you put it somewhere
they just they just put the camera in a
way that you don't see it but normally
there's numbers on the ground so you
know where to stand
um
but if there's no no numbers on the
ground it's so hard to guess
how much space is between you and
someone else when you're constantly in
movement
if you're standing correctly that's like
so hard to guess anyway this choreo is
God like
[Music]
yeah it it does take [\h__\h] in a practice
mm-hmm
[Music]
but that's just stupid that's like not
me me five times the problem is also
that you know I have to record it with
five people I can't like do interactive
choreos on my own
I would need to
mocap at the same place
five people including me
but you know Amazon only takes
one person pretty much
uh head cover Studio I can't use so
so I can currently not do it
um I feel like maybe in the future maybe
we can
um
make my music videos even more
interesting by
you know
using the full potential of
choreographies that would be cool but I
would have to be able to use a bigger
and high quality Studio like the cover
one and I would need to hire more
dancers or I don't know maybe it could
even be an actual collaborative song but
yeah
yeah yeah this this stuff it's it's not
just
five people standing next to each other
that's not what I would want to do
because that's boring the reason why
it's so cool to have group
choreographies is because they can
interact and and and you know
they can switch positions and all that
if I'm just recording it alone five
times that's gonna be difficult no
no members interested in something like
this I mean surely there might be but
can we do it
choreographies are so satisfying to
ah
mmm so good
um
[Music]
it's still not sparkling I love song
sparkling weight which which 48 seconds
wait let me see which one do you mean I
love song sparkling I love that so much
oh
oh it's the most replayed part
wait which one
[Music]
[\h__\h] I love the chorus wait which which
part though
I'm not sure which part you actually
mean
there's so much going on there's so much
happening
I wish I could play the music right now
it's so fun
can I just send this in case you guys
are interested you don't have to watch
it but in case you're interested
this is a solo Kpop artist
recently she hasn't been so active but
her songs are so girl duh she's such a
queen
oh
[Music]
make me Sparkle
Sparkle Sparkle
ah
I wanna mommy are you still listening I
wanna make a song like this it's so epic
so much fun
I I also like oh my God all his all her
songs though like stay tonight
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I was having a
moment [\h__\h]
yes yes yes yes yes yes oh yeah let's
close the paint now you know okay
don't blame me
where was I oh yeah I asked back in time
what happens
thanks for this hilarious condensed
stream this was awesome big congrats for
horror Tony dance one million I'm really
looking forward to the whole life summer
reschedule I'm sure it's going to be a
great time
[Music]
oh yeah right this was the stream that I
was doing like
um the short one that now I now I
understand in what timeline we are
for being there I'm sorry I couldn't
stream as much in that weekend but I
mean obvious reasons right
so sometimes it do be like that
but yeah
the concert was wonderful so
[Music]
um
next up is blue Journey that I'm not
part of
um
so I don't know if you guys are watching
it
hmm
yeah no
yeah it's Japanese members only no in
the end no idea
can't afford oh how expensive is it
do you want a code
just kidding
um
you know
you know for the summer concert I had
codes again like I always get codes from
management to give to family or friends
um
and I feel like each time I'm giving it
to less and less people I always give
some to
um for example if I perform a certain
song that
somebody has created obviously like
foreign
um
you know for uh Sparks do you I
obviously wanted the team behind those
songs to see it
um but besides that I always give codes
to
me Nina because they seem always quite
interested in watching it and that makes
me happy it doesn't seem like I'm giving
it to them and they won't watch it no
promo always watches it
um
so yeah and then
I I I gave my mom coats before but I'm
not sure if she really wants to see it
so I thought you know if somebody wants
to see it they they can message me right
they can tell me can I get a code again
um
I give a code
to last time I gave codes to like an
offered codes I said
for the Yen concert I think I said to my
closest friend Circle I said
okay if anybody wants codes let me know
and then the only one who answered was
my bestie
and honestly I mean it's like it's fine
because
they're sweet friends but I understand I
guess they don't really care about my
musical veins like music performances
and so on
but I really don't have many people to
give the codes to
um
yeah um
I don't know of course part of me
um which is that they were more
interested into it but I can't blame
them I guess yeah
[Music]
um
I mean maybe they would care more if it
was a solo concert
but if it's just like me performing one
small thing in a big concert then I I
understand how it might not be so
Charming so interesting
[Music]
um
yeah
I just you know because I don't have so
many people to give clothes to I'm like
do you guys want the code
do you guys want to take these codes off
of my hands a giveaway I can't do that
now
codes are for
friends and um
family
I would totally give you guys codes but
I can't
I've given given codes to
this this chick called utano Pandora
that Panda that Panda girl
brotheli doesn't care bro doesn't care
sister also doesn't know I don't think
they care so much to watch a concert no
no
if they ever want to see it I'll gladly
show it to them
I'm gonna tell you watches them mama
told me watches my streams and she's
watched the concert before two I think
not the summer one though I think
um
it's okay though it's okay
what about this movie and chunkers
they're forced to watch it
they watch me practice too they want to
see the end result
summer concert didn't have my money yeah
so what there's they're always watching
online only anyway it's always online
codes
um
but I I generally definitely understand
how it's not interesting for people who
only know me to watch a concert that's
like I don't know three hours or two
hours and I only get like five minutes
show time or so
summer concert this time
this summer I got much show time it's
showtime baby
show time
if they like they they do like anime
yeah
hmm
totally fair it's not everyone's thing
yeah yeah it doesn't change that we're
the friends you know
um but I feel like I feel like there's
this weird
difference like if I was doing
like let's say
like theater
because I have a friend
uh one of my best friends she she does
like you know some kind of theater
and everybody makes an effort to watch
her theater even I even though I didn't
care about
um the thing it was based on the the the
story
um but all of us still made an effort to
watch it you know to support her but I
feel like there's this I don't know how
to explain it there's this difference if
it's something like theater or like
anything you can go to in real life
people will feel more inclined to
support their friends to go there
you know what I mean
but since it's like virtual
uh I don't know it's just it just feels
so
not personal I guess
um
and maybe they don't even really feel
like
they're looking at me you know
maybe they have uh this like
this connection oh busy I might still
have it off okay
maybe it just feels disconnected to them
you know what I mean
um
so
I think I can understand and relate
huh
but anyone
who cares enough to actually watch and
it really means a lot to me both you
guys
and my friends and family yeah
because I do put a lot of work into it
after all you know a lot of sweat
um
[Music]
so it's just as as much effort as those
other things
[Music]
yeah yeah unfamiliar
and I mean if they don't really watch my
streams in the first place they're not
gonna really feel
like any anything
about it
some of my friends like pick up some
clips I think watch clips of me
sometimes
um
no
like like two two of my friends I think
they've mentioned before watching some
clips one of my friends like he was
really interested in the Baldur skate
stuff so he watched a little bit of the
Bowser skate stream the first one
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah
yeah okay my friends are clip Watchers
[Music]
it's okay though I stream so much like I
don't expect anyone to really watch
anything but when they do I'm like
honestly shocked like when they say
something that happened to me on the
stream or so I'm like
[Music]
you watched that
it's so surprising and rare that I get
really baffled by it
[Music]
my mom is like the most up-to-date I
would say on everything although she did
miss the Baldur's Gate solo second
stream so I was like Mommy Mommy I did
already stream it again she's like what
oh my God I missed it
are you sure and like yeah I streamed it
I know
[Music]
well she was like oh God okay I have to
catch up I guess
catch up on that
shocked Pikachu face every time yeah
every time they seem to know something
about what I'm doing I'm like
oh wow I'm honored too
[Music]
are you sure you screamed that yeah yeah
she wanted me to stream more
um solo
I told her though that the second collab
stream already went much better
and and that's you know it was pretty
good so
I advertised it to her too
[Music]
yeah it was good right the second collab
I mean we're still kind of rushing of
course but honestly if we weren't I
think we have to rush to a certain
degree
um in order to make any progress as a
collab group but uh I think it's okay
like at least we looked at things
together
mm-hmm
yeah
yeah yeah no good progress
[Music]
since you're still around yeah yeah it's
it's actually giving me the opportunity
to do all the side stuff uh on my solo
run you know what I might do the goblin
Temple privately down so we don't have
to watch it again
and we'll just focus on everything that
we're not doing in the collab streams
[Music]
sounds good I think then I might
continue it I don't know I'll continue a
bit more
I can't stop
[Music]
was narissa spoiling
don't think I
oh I mean she definitely knew what to do
but story-wise did she spoil anything I
don't remember her spoiling any story
[Music]
anything
apart from Raphael I wait was a referral
to Satan or or the masochist
[Music]
that was such a surprise like huh it was
so Random
what
she didn't really spoil it for me though
it just happened like uh
she didn't even know she was going up
there right
like she didn't know that Satan was
there right why was he there that's so
weird what I don't understand
I'll understand one day maybe when I do
more solo streams
so rent is
it's a trigger it's a random event
what what does he even do like don't
tell me but I'm just like so confused
about his whole existence
[Music]
in any case now you got one
I will learn more later
[Music]
Satan
or the devil is like in games and shows
often portrayed as like some kind of
handsome
good-looking gentleman
not only visually but also weirdly in
the personality what's that about
is he's handsome in the Bible too
hmm
I see
[Music]
oh my God you guys are spamming how am I
supposed to read anything at all
how am I supposed
thing
[Music]
great thanks for all the information
can't read anything
thanks for sharing your knowledge with
me
[Music]
okay let me just stop it Lucifer was an
angel so he was beautiful
Satan's attractiveness and Charisma is
meant to be reflective of the Allure of
sin
and also his characterization when
trying to tempt Jesus ah Jesus
it's supposed to be Temptation contempt
people if you're not hot
and charismatic well good then I am hot
and charismatic
[Music]
but what does that mean wait does that
doesn't that imply that if you're hot
and charismatic you go to heaven and if
you're not you go to hell is that what
they're implying
because if you're not then you can be
tempted by Satan
so weird
that's what I take from that
hot people hot charismatic people go to
the heaven
so I'm going to heaven
the other way around
that's my takeaway
can I have this as a takeaway please
thank you
[Music]
it implies that physical Beauty and
superficial Charisma are not to be
trusted they can conceal and wicked
heart and evil intent oh [\h__\h]
hot and charismatic people all go to
hell
I'm going to hell
no
um
I'm just jerking
I'm dumb I'm saying that
maybe maybe if you're at least one of
those things maybe he's still got a
chance like if you only charismatic
maybe you can still go to heaven
you would think that heaven has
charismatic people up there
because they did good things in life
right
so I feel like that allows for some
charisma
wow
welp
who knows it's a concept that
I don't really care about anyway
but if the I guess the concept that I
was raised on Heaven and Hell
more or less not really not my family
didn't raise me religiously at all but
I mean that was automatically religious
but I wasn't like my it's not like my
family drags me to church or anything
[Music]
yeah
well with Hannah saying you're like
have you studied like in University
about Satan or were you so you're so
knowledgeable sharing so much knowledge
so much wise beautiful poetic knowledge
Charisma Beauty exists independent of
being a good a wicked person it's more
just a don't trust or judge people I
know I know I know I know I'm just
joking
uh
my parents used to drag me to church
against my world but now they let me do
whatever I want well thank god oh thank
God ironically
you know the concept of the Purgatory
was um what
I don't understand
no but I did stay at a Holiday Inn
Express left but where are you saying
that's hell is that what you're saying
you're funny
that sounds like hell
um
foreign
[Music]
look it up holiday
in Express in Express hell
uh
I can't really find anything about it
just oh my God it just mentions
Manhattan midtown West
located in Hell's Kitchen
[Music]
uh
it's just because it was like
associated with Hell's Kitchen
in-house kitchen
[Music]
Hotel California
it's not even that old it was part of
their advertising campaign
that they're a shitty hotel
so far off track
commercial
wait let me look it up on YouTube
holiday
in what do I look for Express commercial
foreign
Express surgeon
Holiday Inn Express commercial
helicopter and express meltdown which
one
[Music]
I want to be educated
surgeon likely has it okay
SpongeBob
I forgot you guys can hear it wait
baby
am Hospital
wait what are they saying I wasn't
listening
how's everything look it was good it's
real good
what's this BP
120 over 80. okay folks close him up
you're not Dr is he Satan
[Laughter]
what does what so they're saying it
makes you smarter
[Laughter]
risks people's lives because you stayed
in the holiday and expressed the [\h__\h] is
wrong with you
quite the punchline
wait you're not the doctor no but I I
said in holiday in expression last night
and he rips out the cable or whatever
that is
oh my God I'm so happy I
learned about this
that's basically all it is oh my God
oh my God
I'll I'll try to remember this and then
and then bring it up when in like a
hollow Ian collab conversation hoping to
impress them with my meme knowledge
[Music]
in what situation could I bring it up
maybe if they roast me about not being
good at some game or so I'll be like no
well yeah but I stayed in the Holiday
Inn Express last night
and I'll be the only one laughing
[Music]
Bae wouldn't get it she's a Zoomer I I
was so surprised
the other day
um
wait
[Music]
like uh
if you
[Music]
what was that
it's like there's like this whole
category this whole genre of Bale's
clips of her not knowing something
of her
is learning something new and being
confused about it
it's so funny she has a series of it
really makes you think
so funny
she's I don't know but I also don't know
a lot of things
I also get educated by you guys a lot
but something's happening balance
Bales doesn't didn't let's type in Bales
didn't know
males did this this sounds surreal
though Bales didn't know that Sonic was
originally a video game
bales
Bales didn't know I guess that she has
to finish antibiotics Bales didn't know
what a PS1 is that is the most surreal
one to me
what what
[Music]
at least you know what a PS1 is oh my
God I saw the clip I wanted to face
Palms so hard
to Zuma to have a PS1 what's a PS is a
PS1
the handheld one
[Music]
handheld one that kind of looked like a
mini switch but it wasn't I mean what do
you mean it's like isn't it logic that
PS3 you know we we know PS3 is 4 PS5
they're all like these big things right
wouldn't you like or maybe she thought
it like started from the small handheld
one and then became bigger and bigger
I could see that yeah I guess yes one oh
no that's the PS is that a PSP yes I
love the PSP
oh
well I also never had a PS1 or a PS2
but I still know about PS4
[Laughter]
Bales didn't know the overnight fast
that's one of the few memes that I
already knew like from before
Bales didn't know Team Fortress 2 maybe
that's good that she didn't know Bales
didn't know about Teen Titans I've heard
it before but I don't really know it
um
wait what there are so many things in
the movie that I was so surprised about
I didn't know that Mario was a plumber
excuse me
know that Mario was a plumber I didn't
know that Mario was a plumber
explain yourself go I'm sorry there
might be some spoilers from here what is
up is that or I don't know
Mario was a plumber how do you how do
you explain this outfit and all the
tubes I never knew his law I thought he
was just some some guy in like you know
who's had the hearts for Princess Peach
I mean okay I still wanna like protect
her and say it's understandable because
he like does he have a game about
Plumbing specifically no right like it's
mostly about like you know rescuing like
a hero an adventurous hero like link
would save a princess so Mario is just
like a modern link basically
so yeah I mean yeah somehow everybody
knows but it's not like they add I mean
he looks he's he's he has the outfit of
a plumber but it's not like they say
I don't know our hero plumber I guess I
don't know he doesn't fix Zelda's toilet
or anything I guess
Mario is not a modern link I'm just
trying to make reason of this okay
[Music]
yeah he uses pipes to move around the
world they could just as well just be a
cute gimmick I guess
[Music]
well I wonder I wonder if she thinks
link is Zelda that's a good question
[Laughter]
no no surely sure
I want to believe
[Music]
she knows that from Mario Kart you think
so
yeah she must
[Music]
uh she's funny Bales is funny
she's funny
[Music]
oh man
shocking
shockingly
okay uh the next stream I should read
super chats for
[Music]
oh my god
um oh okay
my God
I just want to give you like
this this I don't think I've ever seen
this before
uh
[Music]
even even for birthday and anniversaries
I don't think I've ever seen this
phenomenon before
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
this is in order of how they came in
super chats from the Baldur's Gate
stream because I guess it happened after
the refund was announced
[Music]
oh my God yeah
what the hell
the hell
[Music]
but after this it calms down after this
wave
it gets back to normal so
I I made dinner last night I can
probably eat I've left over so I don't
have to completely cook a fully new meal
don't worry guys I'm gonna read this
[\h__\h] otherwise we're never gonna end it
[Music]
power refunds were sent straight to Wawa
thank you guys
[Music]
okay here we go and it's against monkey
thanks for the pinky cover said they
were refunding they won but it looks
like there was a hole in my wallet oops
would really sell a job with the concert
and honotoni dance looked even better
live and I'm happy you got to perform at
peculine I loved both place thank you
yeah I mean the the music video already
spoilered a little bit of the choreo AKA
just the chorus
um but I'm happy you guys got to see the
full choreo it's fun
[Music]
thank you
it's fun
yeah that was fun performing
I hope we can do more together
yarn I renewed my subscribers oops
uh and yeah it was again honestly a huge
surprise I told you already guys
huge surprise to have USA can be brought
up at all
thank you and no thanks for whatever
attack your performance on MC was
definitely the best part of the concert
for both days you are such a biased
little [\h__\h]
uh honestly dance was absolutely
incredible the second bang was also
super amazing I'm so proud of you my OC
you're really the absolute best thank
you I'm really glad we got an emcee with
Polo Tony because the song is so short
right so
nice
nice nice
we got two MCS lucky
fun exciting and then one I even got to
lead it hmm
as the main MC
[Music]
Parts in the concert were nice and long
felt less rushed
um I think generally like I I like how
they
um did the MCS this time because it
wasn't just a a get-together of
some girls saying oh yeah we just
performed this song and this song and
this song how did you like it oh yeah I
really like this part of the choreo haha
like I feel like for many concerts when
I was still watching as a fan and then
even also as
um you know a member
that was a criticism I honestly gave
them I'm like
um like this it's not the fault of the
girls because they're they are most
likely being told to talk about it but I
just don't find it interesting
to just keep on like that like if that's
what if that was only one part okay but
the emcees for the longest time just
literally consisted of a recap of what
just happened
um and I was like watching so many other
Idol concerts from you know Japanese
Idols that have been doing it for many
many many many years and they just come
up with much more interesting things to
talk about and banter about and it's
just so much fun yeah so
um
so I think it's going in the right
direction by having
um it be more about something else maybe
they
tried a bit too hard to like put a mini
game into every single MC
maybe that wasn't necessary but I think
it's more interesting than just talking
about
um
yeah what just happened what we all just
saw
and just repeat
so that's cool I like it
I like it
[Music]
I that was that was your neck it wasn't
my neck
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're the only one who heard it so it
was you
hey
Mama yeah me and Muna you know in the
rehearsal it wasn't it wasn't planned
that Muna would stand next to me but I
thought you know it would be good if I
could
um translate for her and also just
because I wanted to stand next to her so
in the rehearsal I ran over to the other
side and then I pushed her back like
pushed her over to my side and then we
just redid the thing
[Music]
um because it just became part of how we
were doing things yeah
but the reaction during the rehearsal
was better because pecora was quite
surprised at what was going on like what
the hell are you girls now
spontaneously ran over to Muna and
brought her to my place yeah
[Music]
yeah
wanted to make her feel
um not so lost because I was feeling
like if we're both on on the edges on
the outer edges and she doesn't
understand Japanese she might be feeling
a little bit lost but just by standing
next to me maybe that helps
maybe maybe no anyway oh thank you
for the pinky cover wanted to refund me
day one but something went wrong and it
was redirected to Super chance amazing
work cancel your beloved was the best
performance and your second performance
was really damn good good singing and
spicy moves thank you yeah yeah
choreo had quite a few spicy moves yeah
I mean like I don't mind doing them
uh it was interesting to see pekola
doing them though
like hello
I I just she's not the spicy bunny right
it's not really it's not spicy so
[Laughter]
I think it suits Muna quite well though
right
pricingly spicy family friend family
friendly young that's what she is so but
yeah we got got to see a little bit of a
different pick what I said by there
and right got nothing so the rest of the
chat your amazing boss loved all of your
performance thank you
thank you for watching and for
supporting from afar
thank you I appreciate it thank you
you're the best mwah
Jacob 47 attention for the pinky
congrats on your absolutely amazing
performances at Splash party seeing you
in the opening and Horror Story and also
can performing on stage with such a
treat right right man
ah I was really really happy with
getting so many chances to show myself
this time yeah
I mean I don't want to you know even
assume that it's gonna be like that in
the future too I don't want to get my
hopes up
and obviously obviously stuff like that
should be rotating anyway out of
fairness
everybody should get their chance to
shine
yeah so it's okay
[Music]
yeah but I enjoyed the little Spotlight
that I had
this summer on me
it was my turn thank you Jim Tracy
thanks for the pinky the concert was so
awesome and it was sick to see you on
both nights congratulations on getting
to perform a solitary live and on stage
finally
getting to perform with us again Plus
open the event yeah I did I was show
opener you were amazing this weekend
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah it was exciting I hope I hope
that Homeless summer will be a thing
again next year I hope we'll get new
swimsuits but I don't know
maybe maybe they'll do another swimsuit
creation contest they were like did you
guys see all the other options there
were so many and they let us vote
[Music]
this one that we ended up getting was
not my first choice I think it was one
of the ones I did like the most probably
um
[Music]
yeah we got to choose
majority vote so that's cool I hope we
can do that again but like even the Idol
concert Idol outfits were reused right
for many years until we got the new one
or for me the first one
um so I don't know how they'll go about
it in the future
I can't imagine maybe summer outfits
could be like a yearly thing but I doubt
they're gonna come up with a new Idol
outfit next yeah
no
not going to the idle outfits will
probably stay for a while like this
[Music]
at least one more year yeah
at least
[Music]
yeah yeah it was a huge process if I
think back
um for them like more process for them
than for us obviously but uh thinking
back on all the correspondence that we
had like checking back on everything
um yeah
yeah
it's a lot of work and they have to
create all kinds of I mean at least they
are basically all the same but they
still you know individualize them a
little bit here and there so no no
yeah and I really like the idol outfits
that we have
so
if if we were like you know real people
and you could just saw an outfit it
would be easier but they have to be
modeled in 3D so it's
more work and it's more uh expensive so
not so reasonable to create so many if
we were only like five people
and then more reasonable maybe but we're
we're a huge group
I mean I guess you could just copy paste
it
but
well well well well well well well
I'm happy with what we have now
I just wish we could have gotten the
previous Idol outfit before getting the
new one
I wanted to wear that one I wanted to
wear that one too never got a chance to
wear it
there's only fan art of it of me wearing
it or any of the myth girls wearing it
OG one
[Music]
which version of the old oh yeah right
they were like free versions Maybe
[Music]
ah wait let me look it up
um Holo live Idol outfit
okay
I guess maybe in this picture has all
free free of them yeah
[Music]
this one
oh this one
[Music]
so it's basically just the top that is
different I guess
[Music]
I think the one that looks the best is
the one that Lamy has
[Music]
the most flattering I don't like the one
that nanachi and Portugal work but I
think that the one that they are wearing
looks better on girls with less boobs
actually
then on big boobs
then this boobies look weird to me
they look a little bit saggy to me
laughs
the one at bottom has I think is a
decent
one no
actually that one has a tummy window and
the Lamy one doesn't
so you might want to choose it for a
tummy window
[Music]
mmm
it's like the most
[Music]
the bottom one mommy mommy yeah
that's like a personal I uh individual
customization
the the head accessories are all
individual
yeah yeah I would have chosen one of
those
um
[Music]
maybe even bottoms
how to choose it
foreign
[Music]
version
yeah
I think I remember
yeah they could all look good though
[Music]
I found one when I look up whole life
Idol outfits one of the top results is a
Hollow myth fan art of us and
in the idol old Idol outfit oh another
one oh my God so many
see people really wanted to see that now
you'll never get to see it so sad
[Music]
bright mode of bright parade you mean
the the shiny one
and there'll be more chances in the
future to see the the shininess of it it
was supposed to be like a wow surprise
effect anyway
[Music]
throwback surprise for future Ian
concert nah it's not happening if only
would be nice
[Music]
oh remember this though
wait remember this mama lonely design
takamoli Idol outfit
it was a more proper illustration of
that too but uh it was I had I think I
asked her to draw me something for the
karaoke stream the thumbnail and then
she came up with this really intricate
really intricate outfit
you have no memory of this
I really like chaos a lot these give me
like Macross vibes macress Idol vibes
um
issue
I really like those because I love the
Macross
Idol outfit vibe
mm-hmm
[Music]
Cheryl and Blanca Vibes right I mean
maybe me I don't give up so much of a
Ranka Vibe but in that combination
I can see it
sends it anyway anyway anyway back to
Super chats oh enough tangent
where was I
um I think next is Jim Tracy
no no didn't I read that one too
[Music]
thank you
Ultima MK2
also I Read Super Chat let's go
hi
hi hi
that one seems unfamiliar to me said
Gucci what is that
but good stuff
you're into it you're so into it I love
it
you're passionate you're doing let's go
I love to hear it thank you thank you
don't be shy to do it maybe in a
in a real like maybe convention concert
or something like that again in the
future
from majima really
I don't remember that
but thank you for the cheering
I appreciate it very hard hyphen thanks
for the pinky I love the concerts and
was so glad to get to see Horror Story
get full recognization as a group you
could tell how much work you and
everyone put in and as always you just
have a way that is uniquely you when
performing you're just amazing thank you
really
thank you yeah you all know how proud I
am of her Waterway
um
I was very happy when I was first told
that horotoni will be picked up by
um I guess like management to become a
unit and have like stuff produced I was
like oh my God
let's go I don't have to spend money on
Skyrim
[Music]
let's go they believe in horror Tony
um
I felt yeah I felt very
had to say
confirmed that's not the right word
[Music]
Valentine yeah it's pretty similar word
but only validate works
thanks thanks
yeah good stuff good stuff thank you
blue Duncan for the pinky congrats on
all of your amazing performances and
splash party always so proud of you
thank you so much blue you're so sweet
thank you
um
it was a blast it was a
a very very very
awesome weekend even though stressful
but it was fun
you blow me away during both of the
concerts your MC parts were great I
loved all your songs especially the
choreographies and all the effort
everyone put into them Clarity shows be
proud I love the nice camera choreo from
staff sun too
camera choreo
what
are we talking about you wrote that with
a fever
is that
[Music]
camera are you like the camera angles
yeah yeah
I think cover stuff usually does a good
job at
you know camera angles
um
very sad or
yeah they do be quiet uh they they like
to show some fan service that's for sure
I've noticed that yes
[Music]
official stage debut made us also proud
of you and the girls and you were so
cool in USA against bang I became your
friend became your fan all over again
not that I ever stopped thank you thank
you oh man bang was quite a challenge
but thank you I'm happy that you're
still a fan of Wawa my loyal chimping
thank you for all your love and your
support I'm glad you enjoyed the concert
it was
a big event that had like so much build
up of the whole whole summer ah
yeah
now it's over so sad
thank you though
um
went by so quick yeah I thought summer
like whole life summer would still
continue after that but I guess I didn't
really understand
what all of this was for I didn't
realize it was um
[Music]
foreign
until they said it oh it's the end of
whole life summer I'm like what
oh we're not continuing after this oh
yeah but it's still summer I thought it
would go as long as summer usually goes
[Music]
I didn't understand that the concert was
supposed to be the finale of whole life
summer
go ahead me
go ahead
unless you didn't understand it either
[Music]
you allowed to do it now yeah yeah
okay
[Music]
I was in the Stream one day and yeah
Bond
but then it was so soon and would you
really think that whole life summer ends
before summer ends why
[Music]
speaking of
speaking of Summer let me write a
message really quickly
hahaha
where is the right thread for this
um
[Music]
where is it
oh this one I think
hey
[Music]
estimate update
um
December imagine December hi I'm finally
take
[Music]
anyway
uh
[Music]
I can totally see that happen
and
please welcome thank you uh especially
was great totally dance made me actually
get up and dance
and there's a part in USA can emcee on
day two where your head is resting on
muna's shoulder and so adorable and also
thank you
yeah Muna was really I told you before
but Muna was
my rock
during this time so
we were each other's Rock
and roll we were rocking rolling
so yeah
I'm so glad she was there otherwise I
would have felt so
out of place
I'm like interacted with all of them
before sure but it just doesn't it
doesn't feel
um it just feels like a work
relationship and even for that
not very
deep either sadly
um
so with Muna I don't know
we have
gotten quite connected I guess that's
also it's got to do with like me going
to
Indonesia as well I think that made me
Bond automatically with everybody from
ID immediately
they make it really easy
make it really easy
[Music]
I love them
for the recipe love always amazing
performance day one is cute one one day
two sexual true true true I mean dating
was like overall I guess more sexy
because of the opening song by the way I
know where the money went from day at
one refund oh to me
I think is what you're trying to say
thank you
[Music]
yes
and I feel like the opening
um like for me was a cute and then her
story was fun wow
um and yeah
that was again one was like the mature
Wawa I guess the cool sexy woman
spicy spicy yes many Wild Ones
um yes yes
Slavic fellow thanks for the pinky no
refunds stage W was amazing five
beautiful burps
so happy that I got to watch my Aussie
Rock estate on both days before you
dance it was like a bang
no you know you putting up those
um emotes next to each other
once again I feel like it's so unfair
that
well I feel like Subaru can relate to me
here
but Dana she's got a p-file amount and
people use it for her
hourly mode and people use it for her
and and Louis got the hockey mode people
use it for and they're actually those
animals right people from me
use the [\h__\h] chicken when I'm not a
chicken I'm a phoenix
and Savannah well she's a duck so it's
okay that she gets a duck too but you
know it just it doesn't look kind of
feel weird to you I'm the only one who's
being depicted of something I'm not
I'm the only one
hey wait a second
what's up with that
now put yeah put the put the turkey
instead of a pea fowl for Wayne and I'll
feel a bit more
treated fairly
[Music]
there is a red bird emoji at least I
guess it's not red uh everywhere maybe
it's only on smartphones though
is it
but it's not really a phoenix either
[Music]
yeah in my YouTube channel it's blue but
on my phone I usually see it in in red
a red bird
[Music]
yeah desktop I guess it's blue
let's kill it it's the dead Twitter it's
the Twitter bird seeking
um protection from what's happening on
Twitter
it's seeking uh what's the word
Refuge yeah
we must protect it we must help them
yeah he fled to our chat hi to the bird
are you okay
you must have gone through so much [\h__\h]
man just being bullied out of your home
that you have nested in for years and
years and years happily and no one ever
hated you wanted you to go and suddenly
you get kicked out oh my God I feel so
bad you you are welcome here you're
welcome at kfp I should I'm so sorry
it's actually my fault I should have
bought Twitter when I said I was gonna
do it
two years ago or so
I should have done it when I had the
chance which I totally had totally
totally
oh man DC dinosaurs Flappy boy thank you
for the rest of the chat with a date of
Triumph foreign and it's unofficial
leader
but kind of a visual dog we got the
first official 3D and performance of
Holiday Dance and you absolutely kill it
with your voice during bang good call
reverting to PG free for today and not
killing sad Voice by playing Asian two
yeah
yeah that is a voice killer for me holy
[\h__\h]
uh
rough
it's such a fun game but I can't help
myself I literally can't stop screaming
[Music]
help me help me
save me
thank you no Flappy boy
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies such Pride
filled my chicken heart after seeing you
on stage Center of your unit singing
your song doing your dancing from the
thousands Pride for someone who fears no
boundary who shines brighter than
sunlight and who even while facing trial
of the trial continues to smile
your performances this weekend were
amazing endearing and alluring
entrancing and hysterical
[Music]
for this incredible weekend and thank
you for always working so hard thank you
for always supporting thank you mwah
two pinky so you get a little kiss
ah wow so many praising Charming words
thank you oh my God I'm gonna turn red
like a tomato
[Music]
thank you thank you
happy you enjoyed everything so much but
you're praising me a little bit too much
the game of green things with pinky
sings since since we are getting a
refund I can't think of a better way to
spend the extra cash and to Shipping You
Away
uh with hours upon hours of Courier and
lyrics practice and memorize for this
you more than deserve it also Hospital
funds for your ankles
yeah
ouch
I survived it though
survived let's go
thank you thank you thank you thank you
we're supporting Wawa and for using all
the money on me guys you guys are crazy
should have kept the refund money thank
you what the hell why are you guys so
nice why yeah
why
don't get it [\h__\h] you guys are crazy
thank you thank you
counting chicken sandwich
I'm over the the big pink red wave
spankenheim dancing Crusaders
thank you for the rest of the chat until
today's life was amazing I like to dance
so much also today is my birthday can
you say happy birthday to me I love you
thank you
Lulu are you here probably sleeping
right now right
congratulations
[Music]
um ah you are here how do I say happy
birthday in your language again
I must have heard it before what was it
[Music]
how do I say it again
and her pants too even her shoe yes
happy birthday to all of your pants and
your shoes
happy
[Music]
something like that
I want to hear it uh
[Music]
I need to hear it because pronunciation
is so important
oh gosh that was very differently
[Music]
it doesn't sound like an R what the hell
yeah
it's so difficult oh my God
recorder
this extremely the first word is
congratulations
on your birthday I hope you're having a
lovely birthday I mean it's already over
but
growing older growing Boulder together
we
[Music]
oh
what huh oh yeah I think I heard about
the Phoenix emote being a thing
sometimes
um growing not balder Boulder Boulder
thank you
ziply also thank you for the recipe
you're amazing Splash party dance was
such a treat to seem pretty and your
singing was especially beautiful in bang
you really had a perfect voice for it I
couldn't stop smiling this was a good
day
well it was a good day indeed
um a very hype day
oh my God the hype never ended on that
day because they combined it basically
into one day last I guess the n a time
zone it wasn't really Monday
[Music]
anyway thank you sir please for
supporting me and watching both
even though I only had one performance
on second day thank you so much for
supporting me one of you
three hours of sleep
[Music]
you guys don't accept
watching ball time you must watch it
live
but I get it you want to watch it live
to not miss out if it's a fomo it's the
freaking fomo
hmm
20 plus hours oh my God
they also waited so long to announce
when the actual day one
is happening after all
so I feel like a lot of people were just
like on alert
and didn't expect it to be that early on
the
most people thought just like me that it
would be like maybe okay maybe uh one
week later or so
[Music]
yeah I was free I always noticed for you
guys before so
that's not ideal if you want to catch it
live and you live in a different time
zone where you're supposed to be
sleeping oh well
you guys made it anyway thank you
[Music]
soon
Nathan cotton drinks with the pinky
concert was great while I was saying
you're not in one but three songs on
both days I love how good you sound of
suicide in the opening song and love the
dances with the other songs the MC's
were pretty good too here's the next
year thank you
ah oh
oh the blood donation
oh that's sweet
you're singing with suicide made me a
bit nervous but um
yeah also honored thank you Nathan it's
a rare combination so I gotta enjoy it
while we have it
thank you so much because chunky bird
cute oh my God you're cute thank you
soon Studio raps
[Music]
again and again
oh my God okay I'm out of energy there's
still so many to go
I have I think I have to stop it here
at car Lash
56 I have to stop it like my my face is
like feeling like it's gonna fall off
hey
I have convention tomorrow
[Music]
I'm I'm worried and nervous about it oh
my God it's been a while
I think it's been a while since my last
conventional appearance I'm nervous
ah
[Music]
where's the con Toronto in Canada
have fun Toronto you guys too some
people are gonna come and see me right
I'm waiting for you
but you'll probably be more waiting for
me than I am for you but
let's wait together
[Music]
my birthday today happy birthday oh
oh you'll also be there oh my God isn't
it quite the journey
happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your shoes
happy birthday
literally one of the only interesting
things happening at the club ah thank
you but
yeah I mean honestly for me when when I
go to conventions here in Europe like
I'm never interested in a program either
unless they bring some really
um not even then even when they bring
some big anime
opening singers I don't really care that
much it's cool it's impressive
I'm sure many people get hype about it
but
the only performers that I really got
hyped about in the past is like when
they got hello projects groups to Japan
Expo in France that was hype for me that
was [\h__\h] hard for me that was the
best thing ever
um
[Music]
and now for you
use when we go to your conventions
we are the highlights that's so nice
I'm gonna
slap myself now
um
to wake up and
not die
um
I'm tired it's been eight hours
oh my God at the very moment when I
looked at the clock in OBS it just
switched to eight hours from 7 59 to 8.
at that very moment oh my god wow Magic
uh yeah I'm too old man I'm I'm too old
for this ah
uh please stream POV Stream Point of
View Stream Point of View please and
pineapple please do me a favor everybody
after the stream go to Pineapple music
video
watch it fully at least once
please that wasn't so loud and reality
it was one of my most quiet cracks ever
it really was sometimes I do the crazy
loud ones that scare even me I'm like
what the [\h__\h]
this was Tiny it just was picked up by
the
by the mic louder I guess I don't know
if I can raid it's can I read it
let's see can I make it comfortable for
you guys
[Music]
um oh
let me see here
now I can't
[Music]
I don't think oh wait no maybe I can no
no it has to be upcoming videos or
streams of me
yeah sad also I forgot to put a trailer
for this I should be putting trailers ah
it's open
right I didn't have a trailer for about
this kid remind me guys whenever I put
up a room if you are there early when
I'm still in the pre-chat
feel free to remind me kiwawa are you
not gonna set a trailer
you did really
right Corona I can't it doesn't doesn't
have raids on
you noticed three minutes before the
stream started well that's too late
yeah if you guys can remember then
please remind me
okay okay I'm gonna go now and eat food
and go to idle meeting I haven't been to
an idol meeting in um over eight hours
so
in German
thank you for watching today I had a lot
of fun playing Valdez guys
foreign
[Music]
bye bye love you guys see you in Toronto
mate
good day mate
[Music]
don't they say mate too
damn it what do they say
[Music]
oh
there's an a yeah but I can't just say
that that's nothing that's so short
goodbye
[Music]
foreign
sorry for ending the stream sorry I'm
gonna just try to apologize for
everything
sorry guys sorry for tangenting sorry
for turning off the stream now sorry I'm
so sorry sorry for saying sorry I'm so
sorry it's all right sorry sorry
I sorry I
sorry sorry
[Music]
is that how to say it
sorry sorry
maybe I'm about to break sorry sorry
mate uh sorry eh
sorry sorry
hey that sounds surreal
[Music]
all right thanks for the chat
that's about it a boot
it
is that Canadian
sorry about about it
[Music]
oh my God
exaggerated
[Music]
I'm sorry for mocking I guess I just
wanna I just want to relate
I want to sound more familiar
[Music]
I wanna it was cool and cool English
uh accent
sorry
if you try that tomorrow they're gonna
cream yeah
they're growing so green
I'll try not to then maybe
yeah yeah let's try not to
[Music]
laugh
a crack the Kraken
krakening
I'm going to sleep on the floor now with
moving
[Music]
the