[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
why hello foreign
s are um I think
um they will be doing promotion first on
their stream
and since we already did our promotion
yesterday so we're just gonna chit chat
right now I guess
oh my God good let's go
more promotions the merchandises links
are still in the description by the way
if any of you guys are wondering um it's
on our description it is on my
description yep yeah on everyone's
description oh oh I kind of want to
wanna
see
yeah so apparently uh I did an oopsie I
said that oh my God yeah pre-order is
closing an inner sloth and a hollow life
website no it's actually yeah
yeah that's only for the whole life
website
merchandisers you should still be able
to get them
even after even after the day yeah yeah
yeah for the whole life one you can get
it until 11 59 PM GST today today
November 28th today
it's just still going so you guys can
chill
[Applause]
um
perfect
wait what
do you know
oh oh okay
okay I'm born oh my God
oh
listening
[Laughter]
hey it's my
it's money it's money
guys I mean
happy
yeah oh my god
oh yeah yeah
um
yeah oh but here's the question for you
guys
from all of the merchandise that hollow
life and Among Us is having right now
which one do you guys are most
interested in
oh um I like the keychain with all the
IDS and eons like the cool keychain
what was it called again the emergency
meeting oh I like that one too the
emergency kitchen yeah
the key holders
yes I love them what about you I love it
hmm
there's a lot of you in here there's a
lot of you same same emergency
um
she was the one who asked you know
[Music]
I'm very much interested like you guys
said I like all of the key holders
Miyabi senpas especially already put an
order in that one
oh yeah remember you guys you guys you
guys can get any OC from hollow life
Productions
[Music]
even Stars ain't that cool I actually
haven't seen the Stars One the Stars
merchandises
it's a lot more like a charm yeah yeah
I need to check them out
I think if if we're talking about merch
I like the plushy shit
the real picture it's so good
right I wonder if you can get like the
Airship if you buy the whole thing
like an all-in-one air shipped out the
whole thing
that will be spicy
yeah get them all before
before wait uh-huh before what before
tomorrow right oh yeah
no it will be gone by today if you're
talking about like Indonesian time
yeah
[Music]
so until this night until tonight until
tonight get it while you still can't
walk yeah
11 59 pm jsd today
[Music]
I kind of want it but they don't ship to
Indonesia unfortunately you know what
you gotta do you need tip
oh my God
[Music]
contact
guys
oh my God
[Music]
I
soundboard I love that sound effect
Ive tips then tricks
papaya
hi
[Music]
hi oh just in time
to die and make another one thank you
uh okay should we just play the the
basic the most basic one for for the
first one I'm not sure
I'm okay with anything okay
basic it is
I think it has already had a Omega
stream like this right like four hours
ago or so yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
no we're kind of promoting and chatting
at the same time just now
wow
um
why are you guys so fast
so fast
right
inside before me
[Music]
really closed
a new one one second I don't trust
streamer mode
[Music]
make sure to have yourself
okay all right
streamer mode works hello hello
hi hello
hi hi
hello hello
everybody's really tired huh
the tight hello is sending us yeah
it wasn't like a morning voice do we
want to do like uh you know a classic
introduction of everyone
[Music]
hello everyone hello Tanya malfisa from
polovity second generation how's my
voice is it is it good
thank you
and I really love ly love that it's so
fancy
you're welcome
okay available next what's up it's me
the red I'm tired
um
the rat I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
to being the best sauce rat that I can
[Music]
oh no you silly
is in the room yet I don't sit here in
the room no I'm not oh yeah
I think next fun now we are hiding why
are you hiding coconut I'm shy do you
want to hide yeah
oh
Cameron
I just didn't know what to do right
trying to hold a life classmate kids
[Music]
oh you're really kind of naked compared
to everyone else yeah I don't know what
beauty beauty is is you're just
beautiful you don't need yeah that's all
natural yeah the natural beauty you know
you were born naked the natural beauties
I'll join you convinced me
you're turning to Nature
promoting the clothes
[Music]
hello it's me Oro crony from Halloween
I am going to kill everyone
no if I killed you first crony
foreign
[Music]
yeah
well I think that needed it but um but
then nothing happens I'm sorry
oh my God
oh say again crony is is this loud
enough now
um
yeah I hear you yeah okay
thank you oh we should be fine hey me
crazy
how did it let's have a fun promoting
steam everybody
amazing
thank you for bringing the energy that
we need
we need that caffeine help by your
energy I fell out of my eyeballs
[Music]
in your eyeballs who's panties
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
Indonesia generation
[Music]
we did that only
[Applause]
The Voice amazing intro
thank you for waking up so early
I love you next up amazing
hello oh hi I'm Nash
I have a stuffy nose to go men
what you didn't register to me that
you're saying oh hi I thought you were
saying Ohio but then you just cut it
halfway because you can be done
I also heard nashimum instead of Nana
she's just saving letters I am saving
time here come on
oh
yeah
[Music]
but today
all right
all right okay bye
[Music]
oh no I'm the
the way the way it just cuts down like
that was kind of fun you're not gonna
lie
oh wow there's only four tasks
okay
okay oh there's a lot in electrical I
have to do lots of stuff and electrical
oh no I'm Gonna Be Alone
oh no whatever will I do
oh that was early
oh that was wait what
the Octo foreign
okay
there you go
hello
foreign
[Music]
what
I think we only have one left oh mommy
oh
somebody died
hi I missed you hello I missed you guys
hello hello oh hello
um
buddies yeah there's yeah all yeah
where was everyone at
I just arrived on the shield
several times
when Bales you're muted in case you're
trying to speak your muted
and only two oh sorry
um
I was in storage and there was a clear
way to the left you know
electrical
yeah yeah I discovered the body
go in that direction right before I
discovered the body
oh
cranny would you like
what wait oh but like I've been
traveling like everywhere else like I've
been traveling the right side of the
section so I didn't really notice
anything like I was checking samples
three seconds before that I when I found
the body why did you not report the body
if you were there
[Music]
[Applause]
or something
yeah
we've already lost two crew members
[Music]
yeah we were on the right side
um yeah
all right muted
I only have one task Left Right Next
wiring
God setup kind of scares me not gonna
lie
um
um um
oh oh
oh oh oh oh
[Music]
because you just killed her
did you all see it yeah it was like it
was like
I was like it was like in front of my
eyes
we were all there together so cronies
kind of sauce yeah she has an obvious
um reason to do it
he and Anna were together though
well goodbye girl now wait can I undo
mine well you know okay fine I'm just
gonna like yes I am the Imposter but
guess what
who's the other one by the way that was
the other one this was the other one
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
all right bye bye
bye bye Tony really
[Laughter]
I don't know I don't know man that is
kind of sauce wait who was there like I
wonder who is there like beside me like
there was like crony me and then someone
else in the room but like I wasn't
paying attention was it Mumy
um
was that Lumi or Zeta I like I don't
remember
I don't remember like
I was too focused on like crony um
killing Bae in front of me I was like oh
[Applause]
oh my God
there's a problem for the oxygen in case
someone doesn't know
that was really fast
if someone if uh someone is being
choosing as imposer and the Imposter
said that the next imposter is someone
don't believe it
were in the room which means that
they're gonna be innocent the only two
people remaining if I had to choose
between the two
ah made
up the confirmation yeah but thank you
for not voting me out appreciate there's
one person missing in the room local oh
hi oh
thank you Ollie like when I was about to
walk over and Anya was there and I was
like crony you just got me in so much
trouble
[Laughter]
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
again it was like people were there and
then everyone else seemed not convinced
and I'm like she killed man
[Laughter]
that was so funny
yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
and then like okay
were the ones in the room
yeah and like I was like I was hoping I
was hoping that Zeta would say something
so that people wouldn't see I didn't
think
yeah yeah I'm very lucky that ran the
funny thing is that I was like I was
about to go out from that room so if
only you had waited for like a few more
seconds I probably wouldn't have got
that
you know
crony learned her lesson for next round
right yeah
I can't
but
wow I don't know man
I don't know man I think it's about time
I get my imposter roll because
yeah anyways time to do my task oh
wait why did she go up to me like that
just now
what was that
Kiana I think that was Kiana
ooh sauce
oh
no not the not the card task what
ah oh no grunny
space
it's very dangerous
two times in a row right yeah
let's try to turn it on but people kept
turning it off
I just kind of like stopped and watched
and I was like okay honestly I was at
there at the scene too but if you
wouldn't have just admitted immediately
that it was you then I wouldn't have
known because there was so much going on
[Music]
I was in there I was in there because
electrical was out and everyone else was
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
how can we know it was her we don't know
if it was her
there were so many people there
the animation of Corona killing it okay
too much
yeah I saw it I don't know because like
I saw it that's why the way I saw a
movie like I don't know I just arrived
no no it's not Mommy I saw granny in
front of my eyes killing it really not
very unfortunate
[Applause]
oh no oh no besides what Luna said crony
just incriminated herself right away
anyway
thank you for everything Tony I'll
remember you yeah
who knows
I don't know
I feel like if I feel like crony will
vote for like the the other imposter
I feel like I don't know I feel like
she'll be the type to like do dude in a
moment of desperation I don't know is it
fauna
some music
oh okay
oh yeah I need to do my task electrical
oh no
Ollie Muna
ah
oh yeah
Senpai and then
gonna sell it one more person
oh Santa
why don't you go to the electrical if
she wasn't gonna do something if if she
wasn't gonna do a task why don't you go
inside to the electrical that was kind
of stuff it's not gonna lie
okay
all good
like she went to the electrical for like
one second and then she she went out
immediately which I think is kind of
sauce
which I think is kind of sauce
hmm
press to start
man I love oh I love the task in this
map they're like simple enough
take a break
huh
you don't need to wait what okay
guys
oh
foreign
call the meeting just to check
actually I want to do a little
promotional eventually
and among us
tomorrow yeah sure
um why did you go to the electrical for
like one second and then you went out
immediately
oh I was just checking to see who's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there I don't know man
yeah if you don't have any tasks like
inside the electrical then why won't you
go inside you should be doing this I
just want to see who's inside and see if
I could stick to anyone I mean Ollie and
me were like going out of the room why
why didn't you like go with us instead
because like you're definitely sorry
where is this intense
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
yeah
someone then why didn't you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
yeah
I don't know man
to me not gonna lie but
I don't know oh dear fine I'm gonna Skip
One now okay okay somebody stick with me
then okay
[Music]
at least people for that
I have I think I have um um yeah oh two
more tasks God damn it God damn it I
need to finish wait what where's my
where's my other tusk
what
oh sabotaged oh I got the task over here
oh
um oh my baby I need to go back to my b
I don't know man that was like that was
like very very sass not gonna lie
select huh
okay
Disney
on your son didn't like this
I'm so scared
I'm so scared Muna Senpai go with me
I finished my task
no no I'm gonna stick to Muna senpai
because I don't know I don't I don't
think it's Muna senpai
foreign
okay
yeah then we should stick together
oh who's like alone who's like oh I
think fauna we did found a day I don't
think phone now finally died right oh
Zeta is like out there
oh wanna sound like hello
hello hello
I'm gonna stick with them
I don't mean
ah
all right oh
we good we good
oh
what up what up hello
when we were all in the admin room and
then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the main lobby
isn't the three of us who were in The
Bad Monroe yeah it wasn't me phone and
Kiana you know what's what's interesting
is that Zeta came after that
yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't I
always came from the other side walking
I was walking I don't know I didn't see
anyone teleporting though but that uh
Zeta was like yeah I said I came to
admin
because I saw you guys
yeah we were doing stuff
interesting so that's interesting I'm
I'm interesting
so can you describe the how many steps
you took to arrive at your destination
um I'm just gonna say I finished my task
s
[Music]
the wiring okay so so it could be a task
yeah
with those who haven't who haven't
finished the task
s
sure sure okay I'm gonna I'm gonna go
with Muna Senpai then no uh I'll go with
you guys too and I can
are we voting Anya we need Anya to vote
oh yeah I'm sorry you guys holding you
guys tipping
I I have voted
I know I hope you like space accidents
[Laughter]
let's see what happens oh oh
we want game over
here
[Music]
yeah cause that was so sauce I didn't
teleport by the way
I thought you were just ignoring me on
purpose I have no idea how that song
goes I didn't even know that was a song
until later on
all right
jump
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
um
I'm Gonna Leave
all right so
um
anything but it's cute it's like a
winter one the snowy one yeah
okay let's try let's try paulus I guess
I don't like it that much sure might be
fun okay
[Music]
cold there you go
okay
[Music]
excuse that they don't know the map well
so they didn't know where to go oh
I'm not really familiar with this map so
like I'm gonna get lost a lot yeah yeah
[Music]
good luck
God she's doing it on purpose
man I don't know this map I'm gonna I'm
gonna get lost a lot
I'm so ready for that
I'm so used to live like this what's
that the following me
oh
um
um no
oh
okay
she's not coming inside I think
ah
wait what BD not crony again well she's
not the impossible
um
[Music]
yeah
um what's it called oh office office
um I'm sorry but wow on the office
didn't you report
recently you saw it but you didn't
record it
by the way yeah
I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left from the
office I think so
I was in the office and and then I go
after you knew and go after a new
Lightroom Anya yeah I saw your face it
was like it was dark so like I didn't
see it at first thing but like I saw the
report I was right behind you you seemed
a bit sus
I was right behind her oh she was like
acting a bit sus in that hallway right
before she entered the right office so I
don't know like in front of me it's Anya
yeah but I was behind you away
but I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office I wasn't and I didn't speak
cronie
I saw you I didn't go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think yeah I
think mommy is in your Communications or
something I am here communication you
may as well
are kind of teaming up against Muna
are we folding oh
well I don't know I don't know if
there's enough information or anything
I don't know
the time
interesting oh no phony
foreign
she she said nothing
I don't know man like I didn't see the
body at first but like I was like I was
like I tried to go away from Luna Simba
because like it seemed like she was
trying to chase me so I was like oh no
no no no no but then I saw the report
button and was like wait what
you know
um use God
made the task when this
um but yeah I don't know I have no idea
because like even if it was muna's
Empire it's not like I saw her like
killing or something right in front of
my eyes so I can't really say that it's
her you know
[Music]
oh yeah sorry
yeah it might be it might be bait too
you know it's like a possibility that it
might be Bae is that I didn't see it but
like the thing is she was like I think
she was like the whole time she was here
you know at least she didn't go around
where Muna and I were at I think she she
was like staying at the left left-ish
side
so I don't know
unless she unless she like killed early
I guess unless she killed early and I
didn't notice for some reason but that's
kinda that kinda doesn't make sense
because why won't I not notice
because like I was around office the
whole time
I mean there was like lights out and all
but like you know oh
I don't know
I don't know man
I kind of don't know right now
several tasks left
ah
oh no oh oh I didn't need to do the card
here
I see
yeah
foreign
[Music]
I think I need to wait for this one
wait what
oh okay oh hey everyone
hello
download
[Music]
foreign
Let's Stay Together
at least one of them shouldn't be an
imposter because like one of them one of
them was an imposter um I would have
been killed already
oh where do I need to go oh this oh
that's a lot of dead bodies
wow where's everybody
where I wait where am I I'm here uh
security electrical
security
yeah I didn't go there
um
[Music]
yeah we filmed this specimen
on the way to the Bay was suspicious of
Muna and I didn't see her the whole
round no I was with Mommy before but uh
I go with Mommy before yeah
no not at all I was in the boiler room
still doing my task but
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but I mean
what side are you guys on
um I was mostly on the right
so I was in the in the with suana before
fauna only and Zeta we made right
and we just like standing there yeah
in the emergency room yeah yeah
oh yeah the office and then final went
to the specimen room and then we met up
with Anya and then we went to the
laboratory yeah that was mostly on the
right side of the map the whole time
yeah me so I can't be on the left side
of the map
I mean are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah I guess I'll just wait you said
right side right
yeah oh wait never mind never mind I
guess
we don't have any imposters voted out
yet right that's kind of bad yeah yeah
this is kind of bad I mean there's two
people left right I don't know man I'm
gonna go with one left Luna Senpai cause
yeah
baby you know and Bay was releasing her
it and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win yeah
I'm already done with my test so I'll
just follow people around oh I have like
one more I have like one more uh-huh
cause like if they died she couldn't be
the Imposter and because like it was
either Bay or like Muna Senpai or maybe
a small chance of like move me being one
you know
I think she's following me
hmm
ing
upload
should be done with my task after this
hmm
bloomy you scary
wait who is it
was movie she was chasing me at the end
I was thinking wait or can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill again
excuse me
yeah it's a new mode haven't you I was
there to explain why did you miss it you
should have prepared and you wouldn't
have you wouldn't have missed it uh-huh
what happened right gaslighting is the
victim's fault okay
foreign
missing one person
who gave up who is it
uh get in here
um
I think we can at least squeeze in one
more round yeah maybe we can do one more
and then we can play okay let's yeah
okay
[Music]
wait this one is
oh man okay
oh man
it's okay at least
at least I don't know I feel like I'm
kind of on fire today
she she kind of teleported just now
I was that was actually kind of funny
wait what
oh
what
huh
oh oh
okay
I'm sorry guys that was my first time
doing that task
my bad
oh oh there's a lot of people here hello
and
Bae and Kiana senpai
man I wanted impulsory though now I'm
gonna I'm not gonna follow Santa because
I don't know scary
I think she should be doing this task
right
I mean I mean I I don't know I don't
know but
this one can be tricky
um
ah I was in the middle of that
it's not coming guys it's not coronary
what
[Music]
what what
you thought why did you not record it
then no I was on the security cameras
oh yeah
I see your body
I saw her on the security cameras it was
mermaid standing over crony's dead body
and also wait away
earlier to creep her out that was
fucking fun when she died why didn't you
report her right then and there right
that was her natural state
[Laughter]
yeah
um
you will have reported
I didn't see her body
died
so I don't know I have no idea
um no idea because she was running she
was like there and then she went the
opposite direction so I don't know if
she really didn't see it or she it was I
don't know
was there like like another double M I
think it's a double M
imposter I didn't see Pony die so I I
think they honestly but okay
it'll be all okay
wait oh should I vote
um um
it was it was nice knowing you bye
everybody
my dear I don't know man ume is standing
over like crony's body sounds like
something she would do even when she's
not the Imposter so I'm like
so I'm like oh oh I mean
kind of will do that even when she
wasn't the impossible what the hell is
this how do I do this
oh
okay
um
oh I can go this way oh I don't know
where to go oh I'm lost
um let me do the one task here I was in
the middle of this God damn it
okay
oh oh oh that was scary oh
this one
and then one more
this is
oh does that mean they're not an
imposter because like
just now
the visual task was it I have no idea
um oh oh it's open
oh oh I need I need I need to do a task
over here oh no
so can I assume that yellow Senpai is
not the it's not the Imposter because
like I could see her with the with the
glowing thing and it might be she was
doing something at mapping God damn it I
need to go to the specimen rooms
over here okay there's a lot of people
here okay
gotcha
oh are they following me because they're
done with their task thank you guys I'm
sorry I'm sorry uh
I'm sorry go man let me know
what
open the door
open the door okay okay
wait what oh what was this one okay
um anomaly okay
are we done no
no
I'm gonna assume that Kiera Senpai Keras
Empire is not the Imposter
hmm
I don't know I think she said something
about she that um she never gets
impulsive while while on stream
oh my God
and I think it's it's like going strong
the day
well it's only he's alone like that
over there
was no uncharacteristic of Ollie because
like usually she'll like follow people
around I don't know maybe she has like
she has like tasks left or something
because like I I know how Ollie plays in
this game like when she's like done with
their thought with like her tasks she
would like follow everyone follow like
all the people
but like she was standing alone here
just now and then she didn't follow us
which was
um you know
which was kinda
well
there's only oh
um oh
okay
oh are we all here wait are we are we
missing someone
are we missing someone
oh
good job
good job good job everyone who was it
Moonlight moment again
I didn't kill anybody
uh get out everything's like this is so
hard to kill everyone oh yeah everyone
wants to get me
one
I was going to the seat and I was like
bro this can't be real
pee that you can see people's names when
they're watching somebody that's no I
just saw your your character your colors
oh yeah oh yeah I think you should be
able to like see the colors
[Music]
when you guys know
what I was like about to kill you guys
when you guys in fact but but you guys
instead not in like one side would have
like a different size so I just like oh
this is hard even though I did it
everybody should be off on their own and
isolated at all times honestly
[Music]
can we just maybe do one more round and
in case someone gets imposter who
already got impossible before we restart
or just yeah
I'm going to kill all of you
again
okay yeah if someone gets it like oh
yeah maybe we already got it already
yeah okay
yeah
yeah oh yeah oh yeah that was yeah
do you want to play one more time it
doesn't matter who imposter is if I get
it again
let's do that well like if you get
imposter again either Muno or me we
could just do the emergency meeting and
cast okay yeah I found an imposter I'll
be throwing it
oh fuck
well
ah
okay
I'm so normal about this game I swear to
God no I swear guys I'm really normal
about this game if you guys haven't if
you guys haven't realized
I am I'm so normal about this game by
the way
um
what nutty
wait are we on Hampton
what I I saw someone but I don't know
who it was because I wasn't looking at
the screen but there was someone running
watch
I have to find the Rockets right oh yeah
yeah by the Rockets
I I was stalking fauna and then it got
dark and I lost sight of her but then I
saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking wait where's the
body again I think yes
oh where is the rocket oh uh it's nearby
the laboratory
I've just been in weapons yeah all I'm
saying is not the left side of the map
it's fun did whoever was did they cross
paths with you or did you see them
escape to the left
interesting left left from the right to
the left interesting oh I did see crony
run however I don't know I I don't know
it's funny then she might have
um
this round so okay I will fess up
I I did get it again what but like
should you cast me out no
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
else give me give me the Hat of imposter
and we'll just continue like that
oh imaginary kill people I will just act
as if I did it
so like if I'm in pause for a good
should I just out myself
too many people doing like it narrows it
down too much so I'm not sure we can
really do that I mean we could just keep
crony around
I'll just not kill anyone I'll just do
sabotage
oh that was close
oh man oh close
well at least she's honest she's very
honest at least
I'm honest yeah
I don't know man because like what if
it's like crony got it again but like
the one person the one other imposter
like haven't got an imposter today it's
gonna be hard on the other person you
know
I know it's gonna be kind of rough
um
what
oh okay return in a few seconds
all right
download this
um
on it
is
how do I do this
let's return an oh oh a few more seconds
okay
ah
oh no oh
yeah
we have to go she was like in the
hallway on the left side of the map like
which was like a like a tree
[Music]
full-sized makeup thingy
yeah
not that bad but like on she's in like
the middle left okay in a hallway who
was with someone was with me at
stabilizer so they're also safe
um
I I was walking up with you but then I
went to the left and I met crony she was
coming from that area but I guess she
didn't she didn't touch it yeah yeah
[Laughter]
every time I see crony I won't lie
it's okay yeah anything can happen
it must be the other imposter
fish are friends not God I I have no
idea are you girls skipping
cheers
[Music]
honestly I choose fauna at this point
what
we're going to every single round you
just said that and then muted herself
immediately
[Laughter]
yeah there's like one mysterious person
who keeps voting for fun
at communication now
oh God it's so dark
wait what why do I need to wait oh oh oh
oh oh it's complete it completes
immediately okay
um
I mean
we could crony
Ollie
um and then oh lamp
man I'm like mostly alone this round and
then skying down
it's kinda
foreign
okay
only was kind of like chasing me down it
was actually scary was that my
imagination or because like
Bay Ollie
um
have to do this one over here
[Music]
okay
oh away
foreign
[Music]
there you go
oh
where's everyone
foreign
I have I have a theory like Romeo and
Juliet
what romantic
I have I have a very big Theory so I was
assessing uh Zeta
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since Connie came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that didn't came
out after meeting Anya
um Anna isn't the type that would be
um going on herself doing duties just to
get in anyone's trust if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me so it's either KR Senpai
or bae
Theory
I mean um zombie Theory
why was impulsory I could have killed
you right
or maybe your cooldown was not done yet
all right because we are kind of
dwindling to the final people so if you
waste a if you waste the thing we're
gonna by the way the body was that
um beside the weapons beside weapons
like you better choose yeah like between
weapons
is
[Laughter]
Tony out because like if there's like
the imposters left it's good
okay
I'm here to be honest it's very nice and
not killing anyone I appreciate the
gesture
but like really big props to like the
other imposter doing a very nice job
I'm done with my time
I'll be going with Kiana Senpai oh it's
so dark ah
Let's Stay Together
Kiana Senpai Ollie
whoa yeah
[Applause]
I'm sorry
[Music]
in the Back Bay you stopped me where in
the back
there was on a killing spree
I felt it in my spine when you did it
respect to the ones who stayed alive and
finished the tasks yeah yeah
honestly I was dead and had to finish
the tasks I think it was me I'm sorry
but I did it
okay
that's possible since it was hard for
the other imposter
red but I wasn't looking at my screen I
was like were they someone read no
hahaha oh yeah but is it possible to do
one more since like that that one round
it was just pretty much one imposter oh
so to cut it down another one more round
and then hide and oh do you guys want to
do hide and seek I don't think it's fun
we should remake the room down
[Music]
one imposter and the killing time is
like 10 like the lowest 10 seconds and
pretty much they have to try and kill
every everyone before they finish the
talk
you know who the Seeker is yeah yeah so
you have to you have to say that all the
Imposter when you get it
and you've set the the running speed to
the fastest whoever's making the room
and then okay you count to ten if you're
the Imposter and then yeah okay I have
the player speed on Maxwell oh my God
that is so fast
no report okay
it doesn't get any lower do we have to
task
[Music]
so wait so how many should I do
should be good or two two four
yes
possible so it's no recording though no
reporting um which one do you want to do
do you want to do the normal one for now
okay then lower imposter Vision as well
oh we're not gonna mute ourselves by the
way right yeah
okay okay okay screaming
[Music]
I'm gonna do it again
are you faster
uh it's impossible I'm meant to die in
this I have no idea
oh God
[Applause]
let's just say yes
[Laughter]
um
what is everywhere
dying
[Music]
play the elevator music oh my God oh my
God
let's go
oh God
you don't need to wait what do you mean
I haven't killed anyone in a while
come on come on
where's everybody
died about the downloads yes it's a
dangerous place
speedy hello everybody
[Music]
where's everybody
is it only me and me now
what what
yeah we
um
cute
go grab a coffee
and who
um
I don't think so we can haunt her oh
repent for your sins full enough
oh shoot oh my god
oh you can do sabotage
[Music]
I was gonna click the use button
just skip yeah
give us another 10 seconds so close oh
no it's actually harder than I thought
four three
two
okay
oh
cool does anyone have all their clothes
one more one more okay I'm done
it's possible
wow wow amazing I think that would work
so that we would win what what put it
down okay
[Music]
but I'll change should I change
something any improve my advice was
actually okay
if I hadn't messed up I would have won
so it's okay I think okay all right to
play well if you want to win it's
possible
who's it I don't actually don't I don't
actually want to be it so please no
thank you
okay
well we could just do an emergency yeah
yeah
you can kick her out okay
all right goodbye
goodbye
why don't we just you know doing the
marketing
let's do it
do it dude
he's saying do it is incredible
it just fucked me me
all right will it be fun again or help
no we won easy
it's always a point easy oh yeah
it's a Cosmic Cube yeah
oh
if you love me
[Applause]
should we do tasks during the countdown
or no no no no
stop counting okay I'm counting please
wait what
okay when do we do the tasks we're once
somebody died already
killed me already okay
you guys are confusing me oh yeah
it started
oh man I think it's time
I have no idea what should I do but
the Keystone that is broken
careful now well this is peace
in the cafeteria right now you don't
need to go looking for me okay I won't
uh
I can't do the card
no
oh
annoying me this is so sad oh I feel the
view is so small
not in the cafeteria at all
[Music]
um
one more time and boom finally
oh my God
[Music]
if we lose it's my fault
oh it gets hard when
there's only a few people left
[Music]
I already mentally gave up on that one
day
[Music]
um
I'm so sorry
that was fun
anyone besides me never get imposter me
I didn't never I never got one oh Ollie
and Anna and me we are cursed yeah
it's not fair oh that's cute
I'm going to sue someone I don't know
who but I'm going to do probably maybe
Susie
or hello
so this actually means milk in Indonesia
okay
please give me
how do I say please give me
uh it depends that you can at least give
you can always just say
uh something dong
oh my God
I will marry you or something like that
it's like
anyway guys
right now it's gonna end soon oh I'm
gonna show you yeah in like 12 hours I
think so we can grab the merch guys
acrylic stand yeah
really cool t-shirt
s
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for joining so spontaneously
especially to the IG members who already
did their homework yourself
[Music]
foreign
wow that was fun everyone thank you
thank you to those who came to the um I
guess that was kind of that was kind of
ghetto-ish but like yesterday I said I
was I was gonna appear in like something
I did say I was gonna appear in
something
but like I I still didn't know whether
to like open POV or not and I decided to
open POV today thank you so much
everyone thank you for those who came to
the collab that was so much fun it was
so much fun wow
well I feel like I feel like I played so
many Among Us in the past few months
ever since the collab is actually it's
actually kind of wild
thank you everyone and don't forget to
grab the merchandises
um the links in is on my description
don't forget you know good to know good
to know
uh
thank you so much everyone thank you for
coming
and I will see you guys next time on the
next stream by the way I'm gonna I'm
gonna throw you guys to The Opening
screen instead of the ending screen for
the for the you know for the um
promotion promotional images
um yeah slideshow
yeah for more promotion I'm gonna throw
you guys to The Opening screen instead
but we will be ending the stream
now thank you so much for coming yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]