foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
this is
[Music]
foreign
hello everyone sorry for worrying you
and keeping you waiting I am okay and I
am healing and resting
this is not a big problem for me as my
body feels fine it's just my voice is
rough still but besides that I am okay
for everyone who doesn't know what's up
I had or have laryngitis bronchitis and
a sinus infection all at the same time
it was bad but now it's almost healed I
just wanted to stream a bit and have
some fun
it gets boring here you know
I am going to use text to speech when I
have something specific to say but
besides that I will use this soundboard
that kfp made for me ages ago
thank you for this exclamation mark
exclamation mark exclamation mark
exclamation mark exclamation mark I feel
like it's mostly cursing so we gonna
have a fun time lol
foreign
[Music]
I'll never give up
[\h__\h] you little you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
plant-based
plant-based my ass
just a few samples you know
you little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
No you little [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] Morin
thank you requesting [\h__\h]
don't even think of touching me
[Music]
what
please baby
glory to mankind I guess
[Music]
okay you can stay
Kobo thank you for coming
please join the lobby in online playmo
[Music]
can you give me a PNG of you
what is wrong with you
[Music]
we are live BTW
AKA night at your service and your day
hi everyone
welcome to my mom's stream
Kobo
[Music]
Kobo thank you for coming
yeah yeah it's not pre-recorded I'm
alive
thank y'all
did you sleep
yeah I sleep for one
two
three four
three hours
you are so sweet for coming to my rescue
yeah I love you Mommy
I did also here hi there
thank you
thank you I love you too
that means a lot to me thank you
is that soundboard or are you talking
life
yes yes yes yes yes
the only option is yes
okay
nice
I want to play play by the way you may
have to do a lot of the talking
what game do you want to play
I want to play anything
what is this oh foreign
[Music]
what
natural challenge
what the heck why cannot I hear your
soundboard clearly here
[Music]
did you hear
I hear the Google voice clearly
okay
it's time to do well
let's go
yes yes yes yes yes yes
the only option is yes
oh my God we'll get you
[Music]
oh it's me oh oh it's me
I'm first oh no I'm second oh go go go
go go go go go go go
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh my God you cannot do this
it's just no no
unbelievable I just I I just I'm
so smart
that is yeah yeah
oh that looks ridiculous
what ridiculous no no no
not ridiculous at all
[Music]
ah
I am concentrate
thank you
hello I'm under the water
can you please save me
take your meds Chad
stop being a little [\h__\h]
what
bye bye bye
[Music]
you little [\h__\h] what the
um [\h__\h]
I'm not scared
you little [\h__\h]
I'm not [\h__\h] I'm hurting someone I'm not
[\h__\h]
let's play another game
[Music]
smashing time
smash
smash your ass
let's go
nuts and boxes
I got some boxes okay
go go go go go go go go go go go
catch me outside how about that
what the
unnatural talent I am
what kind of tyranny Smith are you a
badminton player oh my God
oh I'm ping
crazy gun
oh my God
[Music]
drink it shut up
okay
[Music]
mommy I'm hungry I need kfb [\h__\h] sake
can I ask your reviewer a chicken
there is literally
no better fan base than the kfp family
[Music]
number 357
I'm hungry my mom music please give me
the Quran
and then stop leave it to me I'm a good
shooter
shut up
[Applause]
shift never ends here
's gonna be my volunteer be my food
one of you please
yo little
mom you're sick
[Music]
what the heck
take it slow Mom
oh my God
and what what what did Daddy say hi
Daddy Carly my mom is sick
voice
[Music]
no
oh no sorry sorry I thought oh no
yeah
[Music]
and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they don't stop
coming and they don't stop coming
[Music]
and they will never leave again
out of eggs for breakfast anyway thanks
guys
[Music]
yeah
oh my God look at you
[Music]
it's more of today
extra smooth just for you
oh
wait a minute to wear it
one two let me do count quick count
one two three
four oh
[Music]
four
no I can only do four
okay
oh yeah
oh my God
[Music]
well mommy is thinking
oh yeah
one yay
the game
[Music]
am I enough
one two
damn you still can't think King while
you're sick damn sick he says
[Music]
what oh my God oh my God please lose
foreign
one two
three four five
two
three
one raise your death you coward
[Music]
one two three
four five
I'm hungry
no no oh wait a minute
[Music]
I see what
what you do there okay I'm not gonna
[Music]
trap
ha ha
tip
let's end this quickly
oh my God I'm so smart
close down Facebook
no bye no
I just
um
no don't cry
cry don't be shy
let's go
I will I'll show you break down
do Germany
if you've been so good darling
[Music]
thank you
oh my God holy
[\h__\h] I'm not Germany I don't understand
a thing
uh
um
Clara no baby
[Music]
it hurts it hurts and
oh
last one is the snap
[Music]
down here
okay I'll get my hands up here
oh it's a win-win okay okay one okay two
hey wait how do I get out of here three
I can call it
in Germany oh that looks ridiculous
what what do you I want to count in
Germany yeah well how you can say it's
ridiculous okay I'm trying one two three
four
five uno dos dressed
cuatro
Cinco go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go one two
three four five six
what is happening in Germany
[Music]
down
let's go and this little
oh my God
that's so harsh that's so toxic what is
this toxic relationship between mommy
and daughter no it's oh my God you are
a big source of light for many people
who really really need it
desperately
remember it always
you're beautiful
thank you
hello Mommy I love you Mommy my mama
who's the winner
[Music]
yes yes the only option is yes
um
I'm sorry for triggering you
no no no don't be sorry equally I'll
flirting this will even
where's my where's my love why don't you
love me back where's my love YouTube
[Music]
thank you I think you have to go Kobo
but I love you
[Music]
[\h__\h] God
okay
I love you marry me out
[Applause]
okay I wanna sleep
[Music]
I think I'm going to sleep maybe if you
if you kick me out yeah
goodbye
good what good game or a good thank you
so much
yeah so much
thank you so much everybody
I love you just
uh wait wait wait I will translate so I
can leave this room like I love you what
game do you want to play
huh
no more games
oh no more game I thought you asked
I thought you asked for more games
okay okay
[Music]
um
Greece
[Music]
don't forget Kelly
who's Callie
Calliope mommy my wife
plague
experience
okay uh it is
[Laughter]
you're a donkey hey let me get in let me
get in my switch
what do you mean hot silence chat that
was German
PNG please
oh yeah
thing
one sec let me see where my PNG is at
there you go you can use this one
I don't have some of you already
oh it's cool if you don't if you don't
have one there you go you sound a little
different today
yeah you sound a little different
okay though there's nothing wrong with
it
let's see Clubhouse games
Maui
okay
I'm jacking into the Matrix
this Cali sounds
that I don't know the origin of but it's
kind of rude do you remember this
you're kind of bad Cali
[Laughter]
all right well then wow remember this
that's a warm welcome for me into the
street
that's a warm welcome I'm excited to uh
play play games with you
I love I love you
ah it's sweet
yeah
you're okay too that was from it takes
two uh
God that was pretty good guy nice job
sorry for triggering you
yeah now you're
it's cool I'm not that triggered you're
good
you're uh choose a Lobby
oh do I create a Lobby all right let me
create
money my wife ah it broke again damn it
oh okay [\h__\h] hold on I found you
okay now joining Wawa
intense chicken noises do you oh
this is wild what should we play
maybe I want to play by the way you may
have to do a lot of the talking
oh I don't mind uh that's even better
for me play a little chess
and play a little no oh gosh chat's
triggered by chess
chess is gonna be crazy
oh this is gonna be awful
you guys ready for my good chess skills
yeah I'm good at chess oh God they're
horrified perfect
good that's the reaction I want by the
way I've never played chess on this this
thing before and I don't know anything
about Chess so get excited
Kiara's in control at least when you
play here you can't make a mistake
oh true
true
all right chat how is uh this
is your boy
it's your boy how's this move
chat
cyst on no
way can I do a diagonal in this game
I'm just mimicking all of your moves
how about that
maybe I should do something only when
you take someone with your Pawn
oh
okay so you see you know something about
Chess
how about that
why is that on your soundboard
it's a little suspicious
okay
I don't know what all the pieces do
oh moving the bishop
oh that one can go far
[Music]
foreign
you should put it there
whoa
whoa these pieces can do crazy stuff
I hear smoothie by the way
um
threat map what the [\h__\h] does any of
this mean
okay
time to move the queen guys what do you
say that's your death you coward
[Laughter]
power
I'm deaf and a coward I'm sorry
okay well let me see
cannot place that piece here okay that's
fine
um
I'm sorry
what was that are you a death's
Apprentice you're correct I mean that's
a correct assessment
all right what if I move this here
Akira's in control what's she gonna do
he's moving a couple pawns you know
just moving us moving smart that is so
smart
oh
but I don't understand
I guess
what if I put this
here what happens then
oh
I can't play I can't take you
can't
I can't take that Wawa
hell yeah
okay
what's your move
this is my move
um
[Music]
yeah no not gonna move that one
um
let's see what you have to say about
that yeah that's the last time you
played chess I've never played it
[Music]
how about you
when's the last time you played Jess
it's you and a half minute
sir oh it's been a hot minute
yeah maybe against AME
the chess is like life
I'm sure that has a lot of deep meaning
but that actually doesn't have the deep
meaning you thought it did cure
there we go my answer is questions yeah
my question is
pretty good
[Music]
shotgun chess
I like the sound of that
I love that you can hear sometimes when
like Kiara feels a certain way even
though she's sick
oh yeah
that's a really fun indie game
a fun indie game oh I see yes yes yes
yes yes
the only option is yes
I want to try it
my interest is peaked
um how is he doing today
you know I'm okay I um
I did a stream early in the morning and
now I'm just chilling here with you
plan something
you're both
your boy I wonder how old that one is
how old is that that sound clip I wonder
drawing stream it was fun it was cool I
drew a Kiara cookie Christmas cookie
yeah I drew a lot of cookies
I'll show you
pretty cute
you are a cookie
man I'm thinking about the
is it
does it taste good
it taste good I haven't made it yet just
designed it but it probably tastes like
orange Jade
yum yums orange Aid Powerade Fanta
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
I want to make Christmas cookies oh
little Christmas cookies sounds fun
tastes like reading yes
[Music]
these are so wild
going for the loss by default what does
that mean does chess only have a certain
amount of moves you can make
no there is a Cali soundboard too in
case you ever get sick
thanks
sounds fun
I'm intrigued
all right
I've moved this bishop back and forth
maybe three times
[Music]
all right now this is where the real
game starts
this is where the real
the real battle I wish the people mowing
the lawn would go away
what
you could cook around
to get out of here
oh I'm sorry
I'm sorry you're in pain
can you take my Pawn
no
no you can't
no you can't Wawa
all right well let me see what I've got
I love it absolutely love this this is
uh my kink
I like it
oh my God
let's see moment man what if I move my
little Bishop over here and now my my
king and queen are super guarded
[Music]
we got to win the the vtuber chess
tournament out here
we got a train
hey
why'd you do that
why'd you do that Kiara
I thought you were gonna take mine to be
honest
oh I forgot in this game you don't jump
over
huh
please
oh I took him why'd you take him hey
okay
boy
I don't know how I feel about all this
over here
[Music]
oh
these guys can move kind of far
hey
hmm no no
no no where should I go
put my little horsey over here
oh I see
[Music]
I don't see all right don't see
but I I understand I can see all of your
moves and what you're gonna do
I'll never give up
I can read your mind like a book
here we go
[Music]
you don't mess with the with the Z with
the zens and frow why can't I place this
here
there we go
boy
hey
what you gonna do hmm
thinking about Wawa
Wawa
all right you need to retrieve
Retreat full course
[Music]
donkey
I took it
oh I took it
hey
[Music]
retreat
so are you gonna try and take the queen
hmm I can't let you do that
he's gonna be in trouble if you do that
well I'll never forgive you
don't you oh yeah oh yeah at me
you take that back
you take that back right now
I'll slap you around with that oh yeah
oh yeah
what you doing
what you doing welcome back I know
hey come back here
what you doing there Wawa
[Music]
hold on a minute I can't I can't [\h__\h]
do anything hold on
kind of move over here you're welcome to
come back
you're welcome
why are you running
hey that's my horsey
that's my horsey
you're gonna take my horsey from me
Kiara
that's my hey
hey
no
um all right I'm coming your way
okay wait how do I get out of here
[Laughter]
this is a pretty good sound board you've
got the you've got pretty much all the
bases covered I would say
I don't want to just leave McQueen
I am your father
was that you using the sound board or
was that you speaking right now
yes yes yes yes yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
what's going on here
boy
okay
on the drift has got a hold of me
now you're mine
oh
no
I'm gonna take everyone Kiara they're
all mine thank you
thank you
I love you too you're confusing me that
means a lot to me stop faking me out
you stop faking me out right now
you're planning something
[Music]
I don't trust I don't trust her
you must Trust
and then become
#philosophical Phoenix
I'm good
I'm okay
all right that was rude
give me your horsey you took my horsey
I'm gonna take your horsey
[Music]
that's what you get
sorry
just kidding I'm not sorry
where are we gonna go
you want to get my little guy
you can't
[Music]
I see
okay
peace and deed
let me see
what do I want to do here
what do I want to do
huh
I'm good you've asked for my wisdom
let me tell you
refilled potato chips
are amazing
they're all right
they're like a solid okay
what are we doing here
what are we doing
I see
I'm not gonna move this bishop
I won't move it oh yeah
I will not do that yeah
all right let's see
what does Jaco say
no
it's your boy
hey
hold on I'm coming for you now
I didn't know the horse could do that
hang on
wait
you [\h__\h]
no you didn't no it's the game hasn't
stopped yet
you want to come over here and try and
do that
come on over
come hang out with me and the boys
come on I know you want to oh yeah I
know you want to
no there's nothing funny
there's nothing funny there Carol Carol
Taylor Yahoo
there's no danger
what danger there's no danger
what do they mean the king is in danger
I don't see any danger here
[Music]
I am no
no no
no
yay I beat the game no you didn't no you
didn't no you didn't no you did not no
you did not
check
I am get away from me
get away from me you stopped that
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
what are we doing here
what's the move Wawa what's the move
how does Wawa get out of this one
oh yeah
no
[Laughter]
leave me alone
leave my king alone
you leave him hmm
he can fend for himself
hmm
I'm gonna bring the queen over here
come on
come on come sit next to my king
no
you will not
stop doing that
[Laughter]
what the Wawa doing
[Music]
stop you distracting me with your
soundboard I know it's a part of your
it's a part of your
strategy
it's not gonna work on me
this is why we can't have nice pictures
in our photo album
[Music]
where are we going
um
get away from me
we're gonna meet somewhere whoa
we're gonna meet somewhere
check
you want so badly to be over here
you can't do [\h__\h] you chicken yeah I can
watch and find out Come a Little Closer
I'm a little closer and find out Wawa
check
boy
chess was a mistake
it's the worst
just the word
come on do a little Tango with me
we're just doing a little Tango
let's see
uh I don't know how to Checkmate this
[\h__\h]
yeah I don't know about this one
it's pretty rough
this is pretty yucky
huh
this is the yucky yucky board for me
come here Daddy
Come a Little Closer Papa
what we doing over here
can't
player must defend the king
what the [\h__\h] does that mean
well
I don't understand chess
I don't get it
Kiara just take me just take me
I don't want to play anymore
I can't take your cane
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
but I can't just throw
I can't just throw
okay you can see
oh my God
[Music]
where are we going
where koala going
oh now you run
[Music]
she run
I'm here
come here
wow
this is torturous
hi
what was that noise
[Music]
it may be slow
I may be slow but I'll get you
where are we going
where are we moving and grooving
hmm
we're having a little think she's
racking the noodle right now
stop running away from me
I'll get you
check
oh
oh okay
[Music]
do you see a way to free us from this
yeah
do you see a way to set us free
no
it's just no no no
I'll take that as uh as a no it's just
no
I can't throw the game
I can't
I wish I could but I can't
help
I need help
[Laughter]
laughs
[Music]
no
I refuse it's never gonna end
all live
but maybe not much longer
oh lordy
I'm coming closer
I'm coming closer oh okay now we've got
the king in the mix okay
never gonna be able to get this [\h__\h]
come here
let me have you
[Music]
Gandalf
just let me have you
gonna try and Lead me into a trap where
your king
gets me is that what you're trying to do
because your king is protected by the
queen
[Music]
um
please end the misery I can't take this
anymore
[Music]
what a beautiful wedding
Grooms made was a [\h__\h]
[Music]
these kinds of things
hey there
I'm standing off against all of you now
I'm not afraid
um I got a strong King over here he's a
real smart he uses his noodle
using his noodle
we're going for a trap
over here
oh too bad your King's in the way
laughs
oh no
check
no no no come back here
come back here
[Laughter]
with the Rook doing
what what the Rook doing Kiara
come on
[Music]
shouldn't you have gotten me by now
Kiara
fail me
[Music]
I'll take it
oh man what a [\h__\h] thank you
we're finally free
guilty forgive me please
all right I'll take it that was uh well
done Kiara well done
freedom
kelly didn't even believe sorry Kelly
you shouldn't be sorry I'm the one that
suggested jokes
cool I hope I hope you feel better soon
Chihuahua
this already took so long unfortunately
ah it's cool don't worry I know that you
want to play with other friends too I'll
I'll still be watching though so
go have fun okay
and take care thank you so much for
coming I really appreciate you taking
your time
oh for sure I mean I'm not I'm not doing
anything but you know sleeping and
getting fat over here off of holiday
vacation so you good have a I hope you
win the rest of your games hope you win
I just realized I forgot to put up your
picture the whole time I am sorry oh
it's cool I thought that you didn't
because you were so invested in the
chess game I mean which technically you
were but we kind of jumped right into
chess it's cool I was there in spirit I
was just in my ghostly form you know it
happens like that
sometimes anyway that was a fun stream
happy holidays Cali don't work too much
during it
okay I'll try not to I like streaming
though so it's cool I like I like it
it's I hope that you I know you like
streaming too so I hope that you get
better soon
um all right take care of yourself
all right oh peace
peace bye see you later
chickens you guys be good be nice to
kiwawa okay
Evita Zane bye
round pound
you have your own soundboard I see
[Music]
hello okay uh
uh oh yeah I'm ready to join your lobby
um
okay but I'm doing it for you
hello everyone hello kfb I was watching
the chess tournament
how does it feel to be on the other end
Kiara
wwhgatu mean you have your own
soundboard
[Music]
[Laughter]
well did it feel like
last time we played huh
you did the same thing to me
oh that looks ridiculous we are not
playing chess today by the way
[Music]
um
what should we play it comes to those
who deserve it
um
no no
all right all right this one's fast
anyways
you can choose
I like Checker or um I like four in a
row or Domino's have we played that
before
Domino's
it's kind of like a card game
how do you play that with two
also everybody gets each person gets
like a I think 10 dominoes or something
and then there's one Domino that's on
the table and then you have to match
your number on one half of the Domino
and so whoever
gets rid of all the dominoes first wins
I think
it's kind of like Uno but with dominoes
[Laughter]
okay no no okay
okay okay
[Music]
I'm gonna get fixed something
foreign
what are you trying to make me say it
69.
no there's no 69 Domino
wait actually there might be six and no
no no
hold on hold on hold on yeah
it's time to do
now
it's time to this is dominoes
[Music]
oh it's like
I think this is like rolling the dice
pretty much so like whichever Domino you
pick I guess if it's a higher number or
maybe it's lower
CPU
oh my God
so yeah it's like oh no
oh bubba wants to say hi
there they go
oh that's so smart
that is so smart
I love it uh but I don't understand
also the CPU she put uh I guess you want
to get rid of a domino that's weird or
something so she just put her first one
now you have to match either one or four
on the screen
yeah yeah
easy easy
it's better when you can play with two
people I don't know why it doesn't let
you
[Music]
know
oh so if you have one that's double you
can oh my God it happened so fast
you have one that's double you can put
it on the one side
dominoes not very exciting I've never
played this game mode on this
yeah I'm gonna wait wait okay you're
close to the end
wait how do you oh how do you have two
the CPU is gonna win do I have to just
get rid of all of them
you just have to hope that
um the CPU doesn't have
the one oh
wait oh so if you don't have one that
matches that means you have to get
another Domino
I'll kill you the flame of the Phoenix
is eternal
me
oh is it my turn my bed okay ah
how many rounds oh I guess oh first to
35 points oh so you won the round but
you're not gonna win the game if you
don't get 35 points
I wonder if
I don't know why you get points I'm not
sure maybe someone to chat those
let me see okay it looks like my brain
cannot comprehend this
it's the numbers counting numbers and
stuff
and oh what the heck
oh that looks ridiculous what the F wait
they just got 35 points
the ends have to be multiples
oh what
why are we here just to stop it
yeah that's rich coming from you
Justice comes to those who deserve it
what are you trying to say huh
what does Jaco say
[Laughter]
okay this one sucks now we know
[Music]
I'm surprised though with how many times
we've played this game and like collabs
we've had with different members and
stuff I don't think I've ever played The
Dominoes one
have confidence
[Music]
oh yeah you want to play uh four in a
row
no
I refuse oh you don't like that one
yeah
see
this game's cool okay
dice instead of coffee I see this is
your pick huh
I suck at this though
oh isn't this just luck
or is there actual skill involved
yes yes yes yes yes
the only option is
you just you're just playing like once
because you're sick that means you have
better luck than me right now
[Music]
foreign
level
[Music]
wait did you win
was that good you are an enemy you shall
be eliminated I bless my dice
wait is this good
Phoenix is
eternal
Kiana
I don't know how to play this
is this like golf Maybe
a lower number one sorry
I curse your dice
you think I'm funny am I a joke to you
what hold on hold on hold on
foreign
why are you putting dice in that little
pocket
that's so smart
that is so smart
I don't know what I am doing either
and is it first to 63
wait so you kept them oh I see so if you
have a high number then you write it
down okay
yay
yes
wait I'm trying to I forgot which button
switch
second
yeah
no no no no okay oh yeah
that's nice
yeah
wait a natural talent I am
okay now what
becoming okay we're wrong
it's time to do well
oh wait is that good can I re-roll again
what was that
I can roll again
[Music]
okay oh I see I get it okay you can only
write down
okay wait what
you should not have re-rolled there
why not
you had to get high straight
oh is that good
the game told you you had something
whatever
it's better to keep it then
what are you doing
um
[Music]
and they don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming and they don't stop
coming and they don't stop coming
a strike blessing
[Music]
okay
okay I'm gonna keep this one and this
one and this one yeah yeah
such a cute little chicken made his way
up over here oh yeah oh yeah
oh
comes to those who deserve it
why should I keep this
well let me roll
hell yeah
and we roll
this one lasagna sounds good
oh is this good look wait I'm frog
um
[Music]
I can't either get wait what is this
choice
and
okay I get it I get it all right well
I'll just put it here for now oh well
[Music]
she has to get out of free get out of
jail like free cards like
wait
again
okay
you're already about to win
that's not fair you know how to play
sort of thing oh okay I learned my
lesson but I only get 15. all right
because
I guess
the Vanessa side
I can still win
I'm gonna win
no
I'm with you
so you're going for a total of two
what's yet
um
all of the same
ah
well just you wait I'm gonna catch up
no it's experience
in
oh what happened it's your finger slip
that sucks
yes yes yes yes yes
the only option is yes
[Music]
okay let's go
we won't
uh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I see I shouldn't go for numbers that I
already have oh
um can I cancel
all right I guess I have to go before
I see I see
what is a full house
yeah
foreign
but you already got one
three of one two of another
oh
no no
the flame of the Phoenix is eternal
no aren't your fingers slippery
oh you might miss click watch out
all right
I actually checked my switch
okay
oh
I'm gonna catch up
wait what happened
midnight roll
I thought I rolled
I think I missed clicked while I was
shaking it Where'd I put it
and I was just taking the switch
that's not fair
I didn't press any button
s
we live in this situation
me
all right all right
these are coming back from this one
no I'm just letting you in because
you're sick
okay
wait so two okay I'll re-roll okay
I get it now I think I get it
one more
okay
[Music]
I see so you're gonna okay
my numbers in the top row but you have
all yours in the bottom bro
[Music]
that was my turn okay I'm done shaking
my switch
in case I accidentally hit something all
right I don't have
six yet or four of a kind
if I go for five I already have five
written down
okay I'm gonna take a chance
[Music]
oh
wait
okay
take a chance
[Music]
yeah
go go go go
please
what does that mean
[Music]
I see oh what the heck
um
okay now it's taking the switch
uh
okay I have to go for okay you know what
I'm just gonna keep rolling until I get
lucky come on come on give him give up
the good
okay one more one more one more
oh
oh my God
dinosaur
[Music]
sorry
I have to go for a five or six or a yeah
I get it I get it
ah
well you should have kept them
what the heck
oh you ran out of rolls
I'm gonna catch up we're gonna catch up
oh okay oh
six come on
[Music]
oh
I'm catching up what
hey
[Music]
oh finally finally
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait
hold on hold on hold on
let's have only our soundboards talk
Google Google me
[Music]
a second
yes it's me [\h__\h] I'm standing I'm
walking
surprised huh
I don't have that many sounds of myself
and eliminated I'll kill you
yo little [\h__\h]
[Music]
hahaha
huh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
okay now's my
that's my chance I couldn't catch up
all right give me a four of a kind
wait a second one
all right come on
okay okay
come on
oh
now we need a yacht
no
what are you gonna we gotta make a yes
make a Gamble
ah you were number one priority
[Music]
okay
how dare you
oh
the clothes
all right come on
[Music]
okay okay let's go
the comeback
huh
[Music]
you are an enemy you shall be eliminated
all right the sun too bad I was only 30
behind at the end I caught up
so close
I am
yeah yeah
you got lucky because you're sick
look
but maybe not much
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you yeah you're welcome
for letting me win no problem I love you
too
that means a lot to me thank you
you are beautiful
don't doubt yourself
a big source of light for many people
who really we don't need it desperately
[Music]
and this motivational quotes
what is this soundboard labeled as huh
Kiara's motivational quotes KFC do you
sit there and play these on repeat huh
just enjoy the hips
have French whatever
it's Italian
foreign
[Music]
oh uh wait I think I have a soundboard
bite for that yeah
what what was that yeah
oh yeah
Anna
[Laughter]
it was French
ah okay
well City
Kiara is typing thank you for coming
today
oh yes thank you for having me this one
it was fun and
[Music]
I don't know if it's still going oh wait
I wish I could speak normally
that's okay it'll come back soon
all right well thank you for having me
Kiara KFC thank you for watching uh I'll
head out now Kiara I hope you get some
good rest Amelia Watson wink
uh the wink yes thank you Amelia Watson
wink
ah thank you okay thank you
I'll be dancing I love you
[Music]
all right uh peace
peace
s wait
guys wait
today the Advent calendar is a special
one therefore it will be released five
minutes early
which is in eight minutes
what do you mean
[Music]
wtfobs
the video wasn't supposed to be out yet
where the [\h__\h] did you find it
okay my Harvard student made the mistake
Harvard fire him
it's okay but WTF
well
that's awkward
who here saw it and who didn't
forbidden knowledge
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] yo
little
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
oh you little [\h__\h]
oh my God okay chill
I love you all I love you all so much
thank you
[Music]
I'll never give up
foreign
[Music]
okay wait how do I get out of here
thank you
thank you I love you too
that means a lot to me thank you
action
s
I'll be dancing I love you
[Music]
um
Honda talk is on by the way
it will happen on Friday
Advent calendar update in three minutes
guess
we might as well wait I guess
okay you can stay
let's watch it together
foreign
man
stop looking stop looking stop looking
[Music]
real quick
there is literally
no better fan base than the kfp fan base
there's no one better than you guys out
there
welcome to my Channel now take up your
clothes
don't even think of touch in me
healthy is what you want it to be if you
want it to be a cult then yes maybe we
are
if you wanted to be a family then yes we
are your family
we are white and we are totally
[Music]
I have regained my energy I have
regained my energy I have redeemed my
energy oh fine I guess you are my little
pocket come here
okay you can say
it's ready it's ready
go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go
oh no no no no no no
[Music]
you don't need that a lot of people all
right uh peace
yeah
peace
there we go my answer is questioned yeah
my question is asking
[Music]
foreign