[Music]
so
good morning
[Music]
always are you invited
one second
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
okay
[Music]
everything's cool
crispy no not yet it cannot be crispy
yet
new mic when a weekend uh the mic should
be coming
on friday i think but the
the the the thing that goes with it
uh the go xlr
i think comes on
at some one in in one of
three days so ebay comes
on friday saturday or sunday i think
so we'll see whenever it comes i'll
stream
maybe to celebrate we can do a karaoke
it seems lagging what do you mean
really really
what my me am i lagging
yeah can you hear mario sleeping
boy i open the game and what do i see
he's sleeping oh it's them okay
today uh i needed some more
support and because i know that
today's stream today's mario
will be only suffering so i'm carrying
my sword
and my shield
off i thought it was a cat
[Music]
does it sound like purring i guess i
guess it kind of does
a little bit yeah you're right it sounds
a bit like purring like a purring cat oh
how cute
so cute well done i just woke up so
don't expect too much of me
i have to put in the new chat again
i have to do every stream so oh my mommy
he says now in his sleep even he's so
troubled
such a troubled young man in his dream
he says things like mamma
[Music]
do you mia the music fine or
is it too quiet
bye good morning sunshine
[Music]
okay what were you doing last time i
think i
i don't want to go here right now
what is this
[Music]
what's this again
hey i didn't see that
what the hell where am i
[Music]
i guess we're getting right into it
because i fell
into that hole okay this was not good
by the way um i was uh
people told me to ah to practice
to practice jumping and stuff and i have
to tell you
i did not practice anything
how do i do that long jump where he gets
like kind of
not the normal long jump but the one
where he goes like really like
whoosh
i should read the sign oh yeah it's game
like that it's gamer time
thanks for your super dads by the way
i'll be reading them all after gaming
uh run crunch jump
run that's difficult wait
run i'm probably gonna get burned run
uh how do i crunch again
[Music]
run crunch yeah okay okay
okay i'm gonna try that here am i gonna
fall down over there though no there's a
wall
here we go run and then that button and
then that button
my first um super jump or whatever
i mean i did it right
i thought that was longer i thought that
jump was longer
[Music]
but i think it said if you can't jump
well go to the right side
[Music]
well but i had to jump on the right side
what the hell
let's see
[Music]
run crowds crunch crowds
okay
[Music]
maybe i should uh consider the timing
too
i think ah was that ah maybe before
the length was actually fine because it
would have gone longer if i wouldn't
have burnt myself
but we are learning we are learning
i did not do my homework of uh hello
could you please
uh hello how do i focus on behind him
again
i did not do my homework no
no i did it nice okay
oh
um
how do i hold on to that pole again do i
have to push something after or
do i just jump onto it this is in the
way
[Music]
oh
this level is confusing just jump at it
[Music]
okay hello
what do i even what's even the goal
[Music]
um
where do i go there's so many paths
the girls just cuddled up
collect stars
this left was really confusing i want to
find a lake first it has an easy start
okie dokie there's a lake there's a lake
where
could it be there's another sign
hello it's
mm-hmm
so this is okay this goes up again i
just came down but okay i guess i'll go
up again
[Music]
hello
camera please camera
our door
let's see where up there's a bat
[Music]
save me kelly
what happens if i jump down there better
not try it
i don't think that's a good idea is
there nothing here for me
should i go should i go there
there's a star what how do i get that
star
um
[Music]
not tell you to open the door
oh will a normal jump do this
but now i just learned my long jump so
let's try it even though the camera is
horrible
run crouch jump
but don't get hit by the stone
[Music]
difficulty
okay we saved what is this camera oh my
god please make it stop
[Music]
what could possibly be in here
[Applause]
that makes up for all the times i died
already oh let's start
[Music]
oh
i guess there's just that in this level
a lot of stars everywhere
and you gotta uh get them huh
makes sense
[Music]
lake and holy music
oh no not so holy let's go
let's go swimming are you here
[Music]
you grew a lot didn't you
how does this work again i think i saw
this
recently i have to get on her head
but wait before
wasn't she like wasn't i supposed to
like what do i have to do again
tell me
okay don't i have to like jump on her
head
[Music]
maybe not now does it have to be when
she's
facing the start i guess
are you gonna move or not hello
[Music]
lead me to the star please
i have to do the jump on on her head
right
i'm controlling it oh
[Music]
wow could you please uh go there
thank you
did you see that pro backflip no no no
hey that's so difficult
can you can you stop
[Music]
don't just do it now yeah
ah i do it now ah okay well you can come
back up now
i thought she first has to face there
then i go up and then i do the jump but
i guess that's
not so possible you can go up again come
on
i'm sorry kura i'm sorry that hurt that
must have hurt i'm so sorry
itakata
oh my god what do i have to get off of
you
[Music]
go to the head now oh oh i could have
gone
well then okay let's uh repeat that
but
okay okay okay careful
[Music]
here we go
that was not so hard
i had much more struggles at the
beginning of the last super mario street
yay more more more more i like
[Music]
hello
oh should i have gone the other way was
there coin on the other side i wonder
how do i do it again no um
[Music]
on the left i thought i was never on the
left side
[Music]
okay i know how to do this i know how to
do this
run crouch jump kiara
run crouch jump piano
[Music]
it worked it worked okay where am i
uh was i here before
[Music]
fell down no
but maybe there's a coin here
[Music]
uh is there a coin here
mostly moss that's nice
i'm looking for coins but red coins
could you possibly spammy one
oh stupid eye is up there again
they're here oh they're
here oh are they all here i see stairs i
love stairs
no not really can i get up there
oh back flip back flip back flip i've
learned some things
yes okay yeah
oh
oh i see a coin ah
i understand
does it go back does it go back it
better go back
damn it damn it damn it
damn it
what are you doing mario
okay nice
softly please
okay no no no maybe not
what do i do now ah i understand no i
don't understand wait no i don't
understand
i just have to jump over it right well
it goes before me
panic i panicked so much i turned into a
baby
i'm gonna die soon
[Music]
to concentrate
oh this is gonna take a while huh is
there only one coin
in here i only saw one red coin
is there more
honeycomb
[Music]
break the floating i can break them
eight there's eight in this one room
oh i only saw one
[Music]
oh the blocks are hiding the coins can i
make this platform stop
oh yeah it doesn't stop whenever it
bumps into
does it stop when it bumps into
something
what are you doing
[Music]
a five here free elsewhere
i hate you
[Music]
the camera makes it so hard i'm not even
trying to make excuses
okay now let's come up
it stops when i get off the pla oh and
now it disappears oh well i mean we
gotta do this
we gotta do this and come on
[Music]
um
nice almost
healthy
[Music]
we can do this
mathematics there
[Music]
maybe a bit to the left and then
straight
and then no maybe no why you go there
stop
[Applause]
how did i destroy that
box when i wasn't even on it
i jumped on it from the side
how is this possible my daughter
panic move i punched it oh i did
i'm just panicking pressing buttons at
this point
let it go now i
don't even have to stop there i
but yeah i don't even have to stop at
that point anymore if i get it like
correctly
i'm struggling so much i'm so sorry i'm
so stupid
[Music]
i don't see [\h__\h] but sometimes you just
gotta follow your heart right
[Music]
yes and i'll jump over it
saved me somehow
[Laughter]
was big that was fake panic attack
that was big fantastic time
we're getting that we have five coins to
go it's all good
it's all good is there anything else i
can destroy over there
i don't i only see
one more box ah there's one more
okay no come on oh no
mario i told you before you have to get
auntie slipping shoes
[Music]
again
yes and now be smart be focused
did you all see the beautiful artwork my
my papa made for me yesterday he
finished and uploaded it
and i retweeted it already three times
because i want all of you to see it
[Music]
sticking out
of
[Music]
i did not punch that
my panic moves just destroy those boxes
oh my god mario you need to calm down
i don't know what you're doing now
i don't know but i'm getting the gist
out of this
i'm sorry guys i'm sorry i'm sorry we'll
do this
now is the time
[Music]
let's go
maybe i should like baby maybe walk on
the platform
maybe that would be safer
i couldn't react so fast
all right here's the jump
[Music]
oh my god any tips guys
try back flip and scares me
how do i backflip again though
not not that one right is that how do i
do a small backflip
[Music]
how do i is there a small backflip
just don't fall
back but that's so big i'll fall down
i'll try otherwise i'll just stay there
okay
[Music]
i would say okay now let's go over there
actually we're already there hello coin
is there anything left it doesn't look
like it or is one
does the eye have one mana
how do i kill it there's no space to run
around it
how do i climb the pole
the eye does not have one okay
[Music]
then four coins was almost
here
oh
in the sun there is no sun here
[Music]
same room other platform okay how do i
get up again uh
where do i go here oh i was not here
before
uh oh what is that here
[Music]
this will be the end of me i can't die
now
[Music]
thank god my instincts
instincts led me to quickly escape
panic yeah i thought that was poison
right
[Music]
okay
i would say it's not going so bad i
think last stream was
much worse hello
what do i do here again
probably have to go to the no
to the stone stone balls
i've come again oh are they still coming
oh they're just i know that they're out
there already you've gotten way better
yay without even practicing because i
did not do my homework
no
[Music]
mamma mia
now
[Music]
okay but this time i might get it faster
right
okay chill dun dun
it still feels so hard for me to do that
[Music]
no problem no problem let's get right
into it
[Music]
oh hello how did i do that
also amelia why were you here i thought
you were streaming
or are you streaming like in a second
oh i even stayed on the platform i even
stayed on the platform hallelujah nice
guys this is how you do it
okay this one i don't know if i can stay
uh or maybe
maybe maybe
pro gamer get the plot from disability
i hate you too platform i would never
miss my girlfriend's vibes
look my girlfriend's wife
[Music]
hmm
are you are you
implying that kelly is
cheating on me
[Music]
hey
i think after the stream we gotta talk a
little bit amelia
[Music]
is
amelia stop replying suspicious
[Music]
did you accidentally say something that
you weren't supposed to say
possibly
[Music]
amelia i
think we have to
have a little talk
yes
just use a coupon for what an
investigation
so she can investigate whether or not
cali is cheating on me with her
sounds good sounds good
but i don't think that cali is the type
who would cheat on me
actually i really don't think so
kelly would never cheat on
i me amelia's gone ryan
oh [\h__\h] she tried to escape what the
hell was that
now how do i move on i can't get that
button oh we have to go back
a little
[Music]
oh
nice
okay we're back
at the point where we were
so where do we go again
i have to reach the pole where was the
wait
the pole in the same room
use the elevator to go to the pole oh
stay in the room
yeah there was a pole there right okay
okay again
[Music]
i don't know
i just don't see it right
camera how about i do it again
huh how do i look up again
here's the platform dude which platform
ah you mean that platform ah
[Music]
i smiled you guys are so smart
it's not as easy as i thought i have to
go here huh
[Music]
um
i got scared and kind of tried to move
back
stop it
mario i think you and me we're never
gonna be friends
i think we're just not meant to be
i think
yeah it's not going to happen
oh my god wait there were there
hello paul
it's the right pole right or the other
oh there's another one right which one
wait wait wait wait wait do i have to
use that one which one there's two why
are the two
why are they two
[Music]
yes
how does it work again if i jump now
she will jump on that platform right or
do i i have to look the other side
gosh this camera look at this camera oh
my god
are you are you suffering i'm not even
moving anything are you okay camera
jump okay i did it i did it i did it
oh my god
is there a coin in this box
[Music]
see what do i do with this eye it moves
tall
oh no oh no
i think we got to repeat this many many
times
i can't act that quickly
[Music]
is
you're smart you all are so smart
punch them forgot that i can
punch things
almost i almost glitched
[Music]
hello
okay i can't do this i don't want to
fall down anymore
there's not so many coins in this room
that can heal me
okay okay okay okay okay punch
okay no point i guess it was just in the
way okay
nice five
[Music]
oh what do i do here what do i do here
i just jump over it right
i'll be right back
[Music]
this is uh how you say trial and error
that's just how it is
actually i had a dream this night
where i spoke to my papa on the phone
two times
i'm back again hello can i just do a
long
super long jump over there
oh no you're not with that stupid camera
i guess
[Music]
me playing and getting over it
i think um that's not a good idea
we're so close we're getting there
[Music]
could you not could you not
this camera oh my god oh my god
my hands are sweating
oh
come on now's the time you just gotta um
not mess up this time let's go
yay this is like a like um
when you go up a roller coaster and it's
still like really slow
[Music]
this is the same feeling
yeah i guess i could probably make that
jump
but let's do it the right way i try at
least i will try i couldn't
could you could you not
huh
i'm almost dead
magic kyle
[Music]
why would you do that now out of all
times
unbelievable but it's gone now right it
died right it died by trying to kill me
well that's what you get when you try to
kill a phoenix
or hurt a phoenix you die yourself
that's why the only fitting partner for
me is cali because she's deaf
it all makes sense right it makes sense
stupid bat
sent by callie no i don't think though
she would never do something like that
here we go again
logic 100 right it just makes sense
perfect sense right
i see no arguments wonderful
everyone seems to be understanding me
perfectly
now how do i jump over those things
though
i did it the first time and now i feel
like i can't do it anymore
i just jump over them normally right
or back maybe i can try but i don't
wanna mess up again how do i do this
just stay calm yeah that's it
oh my god what's happening now what's
happening are you gonna stop there
no i'll probably have to go
[Music]
but will i die when i jump down there
how much hp did i have left maybe i
should just don't
jump here
[Music]
yay
here we go
not so bad two stars
in one hour
not even one hour not so bad not so bad
let's get right into it
[Music]
i got there by accident
probably stupid here
probably not here it's at the lake
how did i get to the lake probably here
though
no don't die here
[Music]
i don't know where i am but um
yay
how refreshing
hi gura how you doing you looking for
some salmon
[Music]
no genki what am i doing here though
i need to find i need to find the thing
[Music]
actually there's something here too
what does this one do
i don't know are you going to tell me
something
do i have to mickey there with kuda do i
have to get there with kuda to that to
the door
but i got there a different way too
[Music]
i right here
hello wait that's not
that's not that's not it it's not the
same thing where i went
through last time but what happens when
i did it
okay oh
music
did you just nobody stopping where
[Music]
no
hey
[Music]
why did you not avoid me guys
see this is the pain that i'm talking
about in the title
i had to stretch
[Music]
i didn't think you were
oh come on i don't even remember
how to get to that level now where was
that
or should we do something else what do
you think should we do the same level
again or should we go for a different
door
and have some change of uh
[Music]
how do i get to the desert
i change your face yeah left most door
[Music]
change of scenery basement
oh
actually scared me why did that scare me
at a fake wall oh yeah that was a fake
wall
boy that scared me
[Music]
um
i left off lava painting
see imagine if i'm scared of that blue
for the second time when i already knew
he was gonna be there
kind of i didn't i forgot can you
imagine me playing horror games it's
never gonna happen
stop playing around
[Music]
yay
oh nostalgic what do i do i think this
box when i go on it like it it
jumps around with me right
yeah something like that wait what do i
do with this
what do i do what's the first mission
what was the first mission oh he has a
star did you see that bird is that my
mission
[Music]
i killed it i wasn't supposed to kill it
survive get in the pyramid
[Music]
i have to get into that only
inside the pyramid wherever you like
well if i just move on move towards the
pyramid will i be able to get in there
amelia i see you're still here
or here again
[Music]
oh you remember what you just said like
a few
minutes ago
[Music]
amelia
you know uh after my stream are you
down for a little discord voice chat i
think we gotta talk
is that okay
[Music]
no no not again
where am i even going am i trying to go
on the other side there
oh
close are we
i'm trying closer go there is that where
i want to go
[Music]
okay it doesn't kill me oh thank god
is like on top of the pyramid
[Music]
oh it heals me nice aim for the sun no
no no no no
where's the where is it
where is it
[Music]
no no no no
no oh
[Music]
i'm so bad at flying though where do i
even fly
with the flying cap i should try to get
the
the bird
is that just an extra life i want the
extra life please because i only got
zero
[Music]
wait i can go inside too right let's go
inside
i'm probably gonna die is this is this a
hard one
[Music]
can i go back outside i don't wanna do
this one
[Music]
hmm
what do i do here
thank you can you tell
[Music]
oh oh i thought it was gonna crush me
i just got a one up maybe the other one
[Music]
what's that shadow
oh
[Music]
yay
i don't want to go down there right the
sand is probably going to kill me right
or is that not
is that not the same that the kind of
sand that kills me
[Music]
i don't know if i want to trust you guys
and with this question because you
probably want me to
die other way
climb across okie dokie how do i climb
[Music]
it doesn't kill you it kills you huh
now who am i gonna believe the person
that tells me
it doesn't kill me or the person that
tells me it will kill me
that thing is kind um in the way
no no no no no no no no
no no i'm not dying
[Music]
oh
i don't even need to be here
oh yeah there's a pole
[Music]
this reminds me of super mario sunshine
the climbing level
[Music]
amusement park
be careful
[Music]
oh
ah this is giving me anxiety
[Music]
i don't want to die i don't want to fail
i just want to reach to go i want to get
a start
[Music]
but wait keep on
no no no excuse me
hello no no
no
[Music]
come on
um
camera hates you but your audience
doesn't so let's do it for the audience
okay please
look that way
[Music]
it moves
i'm a i bit scared say i'm a bit scared
maybe let's do a backflip
if i could see something
[Music]
mama mia
huh
[Music]
you are forcing me to do this again
you won't even let me go outside
[Music]
foreign
pain all i feel is pain
[Music]
oh
now whoever wants to mess with me
i will burn you into ashes
[Music]
oh my god that took me ages
and so much like concentration to get up
there
oh my god
but we're getting better at this game at
least so much i can say it
is not getting better
[Music]
i'm you again i hate you i hate you i
hate you i hate you too i hate you too
don't
no no no
[Music]
don't touch me
hey mitchell i'm so fast right now what
the hell oh we're back again no that was
fast actually
wow so you can go this fast
why did that take so much time before
okay now don't fall down
how about that how about not falling
down
should i do a normal jump or it should
be enough to do a normal job right
when he's here
yeah okay okay and
[Music]
tell me
i fine if i just do it
[Music]
so much pain and so much suffering
but i did it i did it
[Music]
actually getting back up there wasn't
even that hard
i thought it was gonna be a pain in the
ass to get up there again
oh we did the third star there so it was
a difficult one i think i would say
is this box even gonna be useful for
anything i want to try that that
one on the outside
of the pyramid there was one right
[Music]
yeah top of pyramid outside
uh uh uh okay stay here safe point
[Music]
again i think that was the same spot as
before and
now where is your cannon my friend where
is it ah yeah we can fly
uh up to the top of the pyramid right
but i'm really bad at playing
me what what what where am i
what what what
[Laughter]
okay
now we gotta fly
[Music]
oh
i think that that hat had some um
production errors
[Music]
kind of reminds me of a previous
super mario stream we had right
kind of reminds me of something
i'm not very good at flying i'm like
this phoenix is bad at flying
can you believe it
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
stop it oh the star
the star the star hey can you get to the
star without whirlwind
[Music]
did you see that i was gonna fall down
but i saved myself and gained a life
[Music]
i use the hat okay use the stairs
where's oh i don't see stairs
wait can i go inside
oh wait no no no we don't go in there
again no
no no no no okay
now focus remember the times
when you flew as a phoenix for millions
of years how can you forget that
it's like riding a bicycle
[Music]
special
i already did this level up let me get
out let me
[Music]
if i'm going to die am i going to
respond here
[Music]
you respond
but there's another way to get out
pause and exit
[Music]
hallelujah
oh i gotta go from here
[Music]
uh
this time i will fly for real i promise
i promise you i can fly
i'm a phoenix after all and i like hats
so good combination you know
[Music]
let's wait here
ah why do i suck at flying
[Music]
okay
why why why i wonder why
[Music]
but let me get that one
are you really going up there oh my god
okay now let's go
[Music]
can you go turn around
why is he so slow
[Music]
i can fly i believe i can fly
i believe i can touch the sky
come on mario
[Music]
oh
this makes me dark doubt my existence
again cause like chickens
can't fly right and they can they should
be able to fly a bit so it's not like i
must be a chicken if i can't fly
right hello phoenix
i'm sure
[Music]
m
another try at flying
how to fly 101
[Music]
where no
that i mean that's also how you fly i
guess
i guess
here we go my friends i show you how to
fly
just don't get the speed
[Music]
let's get in the right position
come on
[Music]
i think it's because i'm in my human
form i could totally fly if i was
uh if i used my my transformation belt
and turned into a phoenix but i'm not
allowed to use it
hence
there is no help it's because of the
belt it's because of my belt
it's my belt's fault
believe me
yeah if i would transform but i'm not
allowed to transform
but if i transform i look like the bird
that's flying up there
almost almost just much bigger and on
fire
[Music]
so you want me to use the cap and the
well wind at the same time or only the
whirlwind
maybe maybe only with the whirlwind
actually and it could work
come on come on again again
[Music]
does it not come anymore both it's gone
now
i think
i think but do i have to do the free
jumps before i get into the whirlwind
papa no kyoko hits you
[Music]
okay well that works
so will you fly now no no you don't want
to fly
no could you please go to the whirlwind
no no i don't want to die here again
[Music]
no
it's all good we didn't die
okay not yet
i don't know i just don't know how to
fly
i need a tutorial
[Music]
just until i fly right not after oh my
god
i don't need to do that after i
already am in the air right
[Music]
start okay start at the last jump
oh i'm exhausted from dying so often
leave me alone
okay it's not so hard
what is that shy guy doing there it's
not so hard to start
literally right there it cannot be that
hard
so namaste has like a knife
jump jump jump hold it
[Music]
i can't fly without transforming
that's my excuse that's all i can say
go right on the pyramid okay i think
that's the only
choice we have
you guys must be so sick of me
[Music]
so
okay on this side no wait you said right
side
right side from what side
[Music]
how do i i don't see a way to
it can't be that hard it cannot be that
hard
[Music]
run up the pillars
um
[Music]
game over
know what let's do some flying practice
let's let's look into the sun and do
some
flying practice let's learn
how to fly in this level here first
[Music]
because we didn't uh
do it here yet either
[Music]
i don't understand
and quite the speed too
[Music]
what happened why why why why
not
how is that stage so tiny though
[Music]
the speed no come on
yeah this is funny
now we'll learn how to
fly start flying on your own
[Music]
yeah well um here
at least i have more space to play with
but
[Music]
still i don't know there's something
wrong
[Music]
i can't even get higher anymore
[Applause]
[Music]
you want to glide in the spiral down
the falling one style
[Music]
i can't go higher
i can't gain height i can only
lose height so in the in the
desert level i have to
already
[Music]
hat and cannon i still didn't find the
cannon i'm not going to look to the left
side down so i don't get surprised
[Music]
maintain height but that's it
but uh at the point where i jump
to start flying i'm already lower
than the star or now
[Music]
how would i get on the pillars
it can run up
really
[Music]
i'm hungry
oh yeah whatever i think
for the super chat reading i'm gonna
grab my sandwich
and eat it i don't know
try
[Music]
excuse me yes
what
[Music]
that starts
here we go
man that cheered me up at least finally
a new start
okay but we still got something else to
do
you guys are also surprised so does that
mean usually it's not that
easy
helping chicago
that's not a phoenix that's an ugly bird
quite quite rude to call that bird kiara
when the real kiara is majestic
as hell how rude that's not kiana
[Music]
okay so i'll take the hat and then i run
up the pillar
and then but then can i should be able
to
[Music]
win i should be
able to
jump
[Music]
but i don't have so much time though
is he carrying a hat
[Music]
did he steal my weight
give me
how dare you steal my hat honestly that
is so rude
where's my hat without my hat you'll see
you
you'll see my bald spots
[Music]
not
eh
[Music]
but she's trying to she didn't succeed
yet
she did not succeed in stealing my life
apparently i think
where's my hat [\h__\h]
[Music]
denial no i'm not
trying to deny anything am i never gonna
get my hat back until i
i try to actually retrieve it from that
dude
or is it like gonna come back eventually
without even trying
[Music]
to
i take way more damage without my head
oh that's why
i died because i was like wait
previously i was able to take two hits
from those
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
finally finally
are you angry because you don't have a
headline oh my god i did it first right
totally first try
here get let's get back my hat
unbelievable he dropped it but maybe i
have to
uh make him drop it again unbelievable
i finally got that star i can't believe
it
i finally got this done oh wait damage
take care
we don't want to die
i'm so hungry i'm so hungry that my
stomach is hurting
i woke up and went straight into
streaming that's
maybe not the best idea i thought that
was the spot
apparently not does he have that no oh
no he doesn't where's my hat
stop excuse me i don't have my hat right
now you don't need to try to
kill me i don't have it nanda or
[\h__\h]
[Music]
you don't have it i don't have it
[Laughter]
yes here we go danielle
now leave me alone you stupid ugly bird
leave me alone yeah oh let's let's get
some coins
no don't don't think no don't take my
hat
dangerous change danger zone danger zone
what the hell okay okay coins
coins
[Music]
[\h__\h]
i need six more coins oh my god i'm
almost dead
[Music]
oh there's a coins in here
oh there's a coin over there
[Music]
oh
what is that box useful for anyway maybe
on top
corns on top
no way i have to fly to get other coins
[Music]
no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
where's the candle i still didn't find
the cannon
phoenix hates flying yeah i have some
bad
experiences now
cannon has kept next to it what
[Music]
i can teleport to the cannon
wait can i teleport at the oasis
okay
[Music]
quick please
one second please
[Music]
i'm a tired
stop sleeping
i have uh lost my hats
[Music]
ah i have to get even closer
well why i don't want to get here i'll
put the camera
ah so i get the the hat and the cannon
[Music]
wow okay this makes it easy i think but
i
just shouldn't die you know i probably
just shouldn't die
[Music]
maybe maybe we should go straight back
to the cannon
don't die don't nope
[Music]
well i think headless mario
and headless me
[Music]
sent me something really cute on discord
so cute
[Music]
inaudible
so i think it's a good uh good idea to
stop now and read super chat and then
i'll be back for the collaboration
yeah i'll be without head until no that
no i need to wear my hats for the
collaboration
[Music]
i love how i can use my no hat version
for
this game it's perfect
i hope you enjoyed it i think we did
much better than last
stream i mean there were still a lot of
problems when it comes to flying
i think i'll practice flying a little
bit until the next stream
um yeah
so let's move to that uh let's close the
game and move to the chatting
title
[Music]
okay for all the people who are leaving
now and don't want to stay for the super
chat reading
[Music]
so let me let me open the super chat
thingy
so yesterday we we reached the end so i
just have to read the ones from this
stream right
thank you for the super chat should i
disable it already or
[Music]
i'm gonna leave it on for a little bit
more let's see how much we got anyway
[Music]
probably not so much so
probably not gonna take so much time
hmm up bgm gotta get some bgm
so last time we listened to the second
song now let's listen to the first song
[Music]
again
maybe i'll uh read super chats and then
get
no is it is it too loud
now better
yeah i'll just eat after the super chat
oh [\h__\h] now
i'm gonna get my sandwich
i should probably take off my headphones
nice
did i was i in some weird position
do i look cute without my hat i feel
like
you know when you wear like a hat or a
helmet
for too long and then your your head is
like in the shape of the of the helmet
[Music]
uh i got my favorite sandwich yesterday
so i can eat it today
[Music]
time chill time
come on
hmm
ah
[Music]
um
hmm
okay okay
i ate one half
of it
already feel much better now i'm gonna
eat the rest later
ah that was good i like uh
sandwiches with salad and tomato
and the egg inside
that makes it so refreshing
okay here we go
as always number one
you always get the first super chat
[Music]
a week ago i never understood why people
donate so much to streamers but after my
first ever super chat
yesterday and hearing your kind
responses to what i had to say i get it
thank you for being awesome oh
i get how you felt before i get that
but yeah it feels good when when the
streamer that you like
actually actually uh replies to it right
that's why i'm doing these readings
because uh i want to make
your donations your investments
worthwhile so yeah
i'll be reading them in the future as
well thank you shane
the gamer
[Music]
of the first phoenix brigade ensure that
our empress kiara is showered with love
and support as she showers
us flat super smiles and energy we have
phoenixes
we are phoenixes you are felix's i doubt
that
glory to the kfp
[Music]
well said well said accept the phoenix's
part i'm the only phoenix
thank you thank you sakura
thank you thank you soon captain pepper
jack's thank you
[Music]
soon general piccolin thank you
vgamer311
captain pepperjacks
[Music]
thank you
the icon though
it's my birthday in your time zone right
now happy birthday
[Music]
why don't you use my cursed one because
it's cursed
also i think there was something in
there that uh i think copyright wise i
can't use or something i don't know
that was something i think but there's
also i gotta tell you guys um
sometimes i receive fan art or
like collages or something like that
where for example there's something
on there that is copyrighted i cannot
retweet those i can only like those as
much as i'd love to
uh to retweet those i can't
and also for example there was a fan art
that i wish i could show you because
someone drew
all of the characters that hooked papa
designed he this person drew them all
together
so like the steins gate and um
the fgo characters that he did he drew
them all together and
me so like a family and i really wanted
to retreat that because it looks great
but i can't
i can't i asked my manager and they
said no better not i don't know
yeah and then other other than that for
example there was like something like
common writer references like my face
put on
kamen rider or something i also can't
retweet that
yeah i'm sorry i would love to but
whatever i see that i can't retreat i
definitely
uh give it a heart
yeah it's a shame especially that one
where where
the whole papa design family
is on the picture i wish i could retweet
that
[Music]
yeah he made a altera
if you want to see it when it's already
a few days ago
but i think if you check out my art tag
let me see
i think it's a while ago
if you guys want to retweet it you're
totally welcome to do so
let me see maybe i can find it quick
okay
[Music]
so i'll tell you the twitter name
because i found the tweet if you go to
the
profile yeah you can see it right away
so maybe you guys can retweet it
i think it deserves more love
so all
on the bar c-a-n
they have it pinned to their profile it
looks so good
1-5-2 on the bar in on the bar
c-a-n
yeah that's it that's it somebody wrote
it in the chat that's it
good luck on finding it it should be
easy
i think it deserves more appreciation
yeah right it's cool right okay let's go
on
[Music]
thank you found it that's sick right
it's really nice right
yay i'm glad some people found it now
she sells cheese shells
loving your mario's dreams can't stay
long tonight but wanted to show the
sport
thank you so much thank you shane i hope
you hear that afterwards
yeah the pinch tweet yeah yeah yeah
general
[Music]
how can i help you i i don't know how to
free you
ask ask a good out to free you
captain pepper
[Music]
not a good username 360. even in kiara
please be careful today and make sure
the username is safe to say before you
actually say it without trolls and
everything oh yeah i heard something
about that
oh yeah i don't i don't think i've had
that before
did i read anything that i wasn't
supposed to read i skipped some names
already
uh where i was like i shouldn't read
that i think until now i
i didn't uh i didn't
read anything i shouldn't be reading
yeah i think i was already but yeah
i i heard from the other girls they had
they were trolled
oh well kind of hard to uh um
it's kind of hard to react to that
especially if you read it really fast
captain pepper jackson
captain pepper jackson ninja star
captain
[Music]
i feel like what today might be the day
since i was warned now i feel like today
might be the day when i mess up
i just want to let you know that your
streams are always wonderful and
entertaining i hope you succeed with any
future plans with the kfbq
proof i also hope the new mic coming in
right as well i hope so too i can't wait
to use it
i hope it works well because like
usually every time i get something
like technical and then i try to set it
up exactly the way it's supposed to be
it just doesn't work i don't know why i
was always like that
but it should be easy the microphone
connects to the gold xlr that i bought
and the go xlr connects to the pc i
think that's it because i didn't buy a
cloud lifter yet
i think that's it
i hope it will work otherwise i'll ask
cali
captain pepper jackson
ninja star thank you alien
i just wanted to reach out and tell you
how much i appreciate your content a
friend of mine introduced me to a whole
life recently
and i've been following you since your
debut i look forward to all the future
oh i'm happy to hear that actually i saw
i saw the advice yesterday and i just
thought of it again about the microphone
that in in obs i should not
reduce the noise too much because if i
do that in obs
it will but where do i do that anyway i
don't know
i can't even change that during
streaming but someone
said that if it's reduced too much
it will actually mess up the sound
where is i don't think i can change it
now
anyway i also can't find
i can't find uh some a place to
change the noise reduction in obs
was there such a thing
no no oh well
your voice is rather muffled i know i
know i know
i bought a new microphone
with my savings it's all good it's
coming soon this weekend
we'll do a karaoke stream to celebrate
if it
works if it actually works
if you if you lower things too low
eventually the noise made in the
equipment
will overpower the actual signal
[Music]
just want to stop by and tell you how
much i adore your personality
[Music]
you are so strong now but when you start
collabing with japan whole libraries
just imagining the collapse of peculiar
cocoa never underestimate the value of
ping-pong in both english and japanese
yeah i couldn't wait for the
collaborations either ah
i i wanna i wanna try to collab with a
lot of people since
um i can speak fluent japanese so they
won't have problems with communicating
i think most most japanese hunger
libraries except koko
don't really speak english so
being able to speak fluent japanese is
definitely an advantage there so i'm
gonna use that
and guys if you don't know what to write
keep on spamming thank you soon
mercy thank you
james
captain pepper jackson oh and my
[Music]
you look so beautiful in it right keep
up the amazing work yeah
i will
can't speak uh good english yeah yeah
yeah
that is coco and hajamah i would say
sorry sorry you almost forgot
yellow thank you star creator and
thunder
thunder hawk
[Music]
can't wait for the crispy mug it'll be
as crispy as your kfp chicken that's
[Music]
thank
chat again kiara are you are you ever
going to fix the error in your channel
name shouldn't it say mori
kiara or is kelly taking your last name
[Music]
you see cali um know yet
so i better not change the name yet we
will have to
teach her slowly
no i was talking about hollow life japan
that whole live idea of course they can
speak fluent english but i was talking
about japan
especially pikachu mexi mexicano
ruined christine
[Music]
did i say that right probably not
for always being amazing and bringing
smiles wherever you go continue being
yourself
hashtag kfb kfb kfb
kfb thank you
thank you so so so so so much for the
generous donation
thank you thank you thank you for all my
heart
thank you injury to insult thank you
sandwich thank you library the wizard
thank you
viva la chiara general leading the
church today tensho can you tell the
japanese kiara fan club
viewers how much the environs appreciate
their support oh i can
and you don't have to read this mean
part if you don't want to but nihonjin
listen now
or uh
no i'm not going to read that what the
hell uh
[Music]
no
my
[Music]
when should i do a japanese only stream
should i do one what's a good day
what's a good day i actually need to
check the calendar too
but uh
[Music]
nice
have you ever played up dog no i i don't
do you want me to ask what's up dog
i know what you're doing there
maximilian great
[Music]
but you have quickly become my favorite
stream and really looking forward to
your german asmr and next card okay
thank
[Music]
hey
five years old thanks you're super
adorable
what
[Music]
i should probably stop swearing
i should probably stop swearing oh my
god the pressure
but it's so hard to control that because
it's not my first language i don't know
it's so hard for me
keep swearing
[Music]
swear in german it's actually hard for
me to
like when i'm angry suddenly insert a
random german swear word
ah i could try but it actually doesn't
come so naturally when i'm speaking
english
thank you out loud
my first super chat been here is instead
you keep being true to yourself you're a
blessing for
you time zones yay i'm glad i love you
and your fan base
i love you all too thank you
i really love my audience you all are so
sweet
well maybe she already knows that word
maybe she already knows the f word maybe
it's too late anyway
yeah this this time slot is not euro
friendly but my later tab slots are
usually
europe friendly i think randy
all of your livestreams are so positive
and i love your energy i especially
loved your karaoke stream because you
sound like you had so much fun singing
and weaving out
leaving our two idols uh your voice is
so nice and makes me happy
thank you yeah i really had a lot of job
fun i enjoy seeing especially when
there's a nice audience
who keeps on supporting me then i have
even more fun
thank you nico one two two
what unlock a secret star by throwing a
scuttle block
jamboree what what is that
[Music]
yo i forgot how toxic this freaking
camera was
that camera sucks especially in like the
smaller rooms it really sucks
in the clouds confined
i don't know why but it's kind of hard
for me to breathe right now
[Music]
chat actually the previous super chats i
didn't tell you but i always have
problems with
breathing while reading super chats
yeah i don't know why um
foreign
do
[Music]
i'm used to it
i just heard my neighbor's voice they
probably hear me too
in the club
fabian
yeah costs 300 hundred thank you
how do i say that again
each time you die you should switch to
the next language you speak until the
next time you die
yeah i died so often that actually would
um
actually that would work
thank you in the clouds thank you
spartan
2961 arctic foxtrot kitchen all the red
coins are in that room kiara you need to
she's explaining me too late too late
since i always tell myself to read the
superchats at the end
i kind of don't read them during during
the
stream sorry but we got it eventually
so thank you
thank you
thank you for
screaming
[Music]
also will you marry me i'm married to
kelly
but i'm glad you enjoy it i'm glad you
appreciate it thank you so much dan
kishan
roy mustang thank you in the class
elector john 12 pakistan valkyrie
this is agonizing to watch i mean really
painful i love it though
thank you chris
[Music]
thank you
i saw that guy's art it was really good
shame you cannot retweet that
yeah i'm glad you saw it i'm glad
[Music]
i wonder if this name is like a peculiar
fan who
also put in kfc for me in their name
because it's kfc
amir perry
[Music]
she has the same flight skill as the
cuckoo in zelda
excuse me what let me crack my neck
off the screen
did you hear that again you heard it
that was a good one it was a good one it
was necessary
it could be
[Music]
i really having a oxygen problem here
high purple braids 35 tankashan storm
white and thank you
[Music]
thank
if anyone wants to super chat do it now
otherwise i'll cut it off in a second
rob luis thank you
for both mouth and nose i think
it's a mystery thank you the
end and now i will reload
i give you 10 seconds
five six
[Music]
oxygen where are you okay
disable super stickers
[Music]
have a super chat okay
disable super chat
that was it thanks guys last time
all right where did we stop
[Music]
me
it's not much but i wanted to show my
support everything helps thank you so
much
thank
oh you wear the same thing twice
nightmare tell me thank you be there for
the art dance one in a few hours thank
you
please use anything i donate for pulse
and chicken nuggets we're not pulling
today
uh we're not gonna play the game
actually we're gonna make a t-list
a waifu chilis but in the future we
might play the game
in on stream yes i think like for the
current cc especially
my account is not ready yeah
breathe i can't breathe today
[Music]
why
your chaotic energy gaming and super one
personality never fails to make
me smile thank you
thank you thank you thank you for
bringing me so much joy
you're amazing from your wonderful
demeanor to you singing to your speaking
german
keep doing what you are doing from a
loyal kaifp employee
thank you that's so sweet sound question
thank you thank you
thank you thank you sir how do you like
super chats well i mean
don't feel forced to send a super chat
but i appreciate it very much
thank you thank you
bro i'm hyperventilating i don't think
so
isn't that much maurice
thank you thank you hello can you please
say happy birthday
kevin give a house for my friends all
right happy birthday
kevin even house
oh just because you sent a red super
chat normally i don't want to do
like actual name calling but
okay
thank you for all the streams i wanted
you to know that you've inspired me to
try and learn japanese again
keep on being you because you're
inspiring
i'm trying to breathe deeply well anyway
we're gonna we're gonna be done here
soon then
i should be fine for the arc night
stream later thank you
thank you for all the streams i wanted
you to know that you've inspired me to
try and
learn japanese again keep on being you
because you're inspiring
thank you thank you i think i didn't
read that
i'm glad
[Music]
thank you i'm glad you like mine
non-hat hair because it was my head was
stolen
i have to get it back next time
ink shade sorry i'm not gonna read so
many messages anymore because i can't
breathe
on me cake for all dan kitchen roland
warlord thank you thank you
patrick chen thank you rob lewis
[Music]
um
solid h2 h.201
gold
[Music]
um it's not really different part of the
club
frescoes called soap in a tanker
[Music]
okay
why did i read that so weirdly
phoenix 0982
big
[Music]
i know
i lost my pen a while ago as you might
know and i ordered a new one on amazon
and arrived today so
i um i will get into
drawing all the things that i need for
the membership
but i'm also so busy actually uh at the
end of this month
i'll be actually moving so
i'm not sure when i can get the
membership ready but i'll try to find
some time maybe i'll just take a day off
of streaming
to uh prepare the membership stuff
yeah will you be without your head until
you recover mary
hat but maybe maybe
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no i'm not moving
no no
i'm not moving kelly is also moving soon
yeah it's true
but no no no no has nothing to do with
that
no no no point to start dancing
[Music]
my favorite hello life eon member i love
your upbeat attitude and energy and try
to make it to every stream
thank you so much i'm so glad that you
come thank you
thank you
[Music]
please never change and give keep it up
thank you
thank you warrior
dragoon xys
noisy neighborhood ghost tractor here we
go we were just mentioned in the chat
and now here you are
excuse me when do you need the carriage
for the after marriage parade or should
i
discuss this with your boss boss bouncer
priest
oh buddy
funny bunny are you gone i
is are you gonna be our carriage aren't
you on a bike
i don't think we want a bike to be our
wedding carriage
noisy bike no thank you
you can like ride behind us but quietly
quietly okay
[Music]
brought you here i enjoy your wholesome
nature and appreciate how hard you were
thank you thank you be sure to breathe
i'm trying i'm trying here
sarah thank you soon
[Music]
good job on getting the first and the
last super chat
i can drive multiple vehicles one of
them are carriers oh awesome
how useful well i mean your
uh your face is kind of scary
um i don't know if you're gonna maybe
scare off our guests
maybe you can put on a mask or something
then maybe yeah because the way your
face looks like right now it's kind of
scary
[Music]
all right
eat the rest of my sandwich and i'll be
back
in how many hours is it
five and a half hours i think in five
and a half hours i'm streaming
again gold chicken
see you then thank you for watching
this was pat's last night
[Music]
bye bye
bye
[Music]
dog
the hell why you always do that
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
i'm sorry
[Music]
bye
oh man look at papa
streamer
i can't stop yawning
[Applause]
not