[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music]
[Music  ]
[Music] I
did something bad to Canada. I
dropped it from the plane. It's okay
.
[Laughs]
Is it a resort? Don't get excited. I
wonder what kind of resort it is.
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
This might be dangerous
[Music]
[
Applause] [Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [
Applause]
[Music]
What are you doing, Igna-chan?
What are you doing?  That's
what everyone is doing. When you think of
traveling abroad, you have to go through immigration.
[Music] That's
why Indonesia and Indonesia
also came to Hololive Resort
[Applause]
[Music]
So, everyone, please introduce yourselves.
Canyour
[Music] This
is an impossible communication department to train
[Applause] I
want to do the worst thing in summer today. Yeah
[Music]
Yes, it's Takanashi.
[Applause]
[Music]
Summer is back again this year.
[Applause]
Hololive Summer 2023 is finally
starting.
This year,
members from Indonesia and English will also be participating.
[Music]
Today we will tell everyone who is watching the stream in detail what kind of summer it will be,
so please look forward to it.  to
Everyone has a seat over there, so please listen to it directly.
[Music]
Itadakimasu
From now on, Shirakami will be the moderator and
tell you about Holo Live Summer 2023.
This year's Hololive Summer is today, July 1st.  The
biggest Bakebek in history is a long-term event that will run from August 27th to August 27th.
What kind of event is Hololive Sour for everyone? It
seems like there are a lot of events on the Hololive server.
[Music]  You
can see swimsuits and all kinds of HT stuff. He
said that 112 might be there.
No, no, no, no,
Octane. No, we're living together.
[Applause]
Here's the roadmap for 2023. It
's an online event.
[Applause] Well,
first of all.  Today, July 1st, we suddenly made a big announcement. The
main theme song of Hololive Summer 2023 will be released on this stream
[Applause]
Surprisingly, this program was
written by HoneyWorks.
These 8 people + 9 people including Kanata are singing
[Music] I
was planning to participate in today's broadcast, but my throat wasn't feeling well,
so I decided to take the day off
[  [Music]
That's right, Honey Max. It
's a newly written song, but I'd
like you to tell me what kind of song it
is. Sui-chan, what kind of song is it?
[Music] This is what it's
like, what kind of character is it, what kind of feeling is it?
This is everything.  It's like a choreography, right?
Anyone can do this. The
boys dance.
[Music]
I like it. I'm
fine.
[Music] Do you
want to release the music video for that game after this
? A
trial, of course. There
are still more projects starting today.
First of all.  Please take a look here
[Music]
[Applause]
So, the summer short
video Relay Holo-sama shorts will start from today. That's
right. I'd
like you to tell me what it's about without spoiling it.  I
think it's going to be like having a summer festival with you.
Here are the members participating in the relay. It's packed. That's
amazing
. There's also a summer festival in August. That's amazing. Hey,
everyone's videos are summery.  Well, the
characters will be released one day before their birthdays.
Everyone, please check them out.
[Music] I
heard that they weren't wearing yukata in that video.
Yes, this year,
everyone in Indoshi has yukata as well.
[Applause]
Now, let's show it off
.
[Music]
I'm looking forward to it. Are there
many ways to tie it? I want you to tie it. Yes, it looks
like it's ready,
so let's call each one over. First of all,
[Applause] Please
take a seat.
[Applause]
[Music]
It's okay.  It's okay
[Applause]
[Music]
We at JP are going to wear yukata too.
Please give us a shout of transformation.
[Music]
[Applause]
Hey
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you.
So from now on, everyone will be wearing yukata. The
next big event will be July 29th.
Speaking of Holo Live Summer, this is a must-see.
Spread the word about swimsuits.This
broadcast will not only show off the swimsuits.Hololive
's second theme
song for Hololive Summer will also be announced.Volume
2 will also be announced, so be sure to check that out as well.
Also, on August 5th, there
will be a swimsuit live broadcast exclusively for fan club members. There will
also be a Comiket store on August 12th and 13th, and various other things.
[Music] We have
also decided to open a Comic Market store in 2023.
[Applause]
We will be posting information on Twitter in the future, so please follow us and wait for further updates.The
three days of August 25th, Meiji 26th, and 27th
became Hatena, yes.  Question
Cushion
Supply
Yes, it was only for those three days
[Music]
Please tell me
[Applause]
Please take a look at the VTR
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
So, on August 26th and 27th, there will be a
large-scale online broadcast of 53 members of Hololive.
[Applause]
On the 25th, there will be a large-scale
live broadcast
just before the concert. [Music] I suddenly see a new Issei-like thing.  Better
However, as expected,
this live show is all new swimsuit
costumes Yay yay
[Applause]
Everyone's ID
[Music]
Thank you for your role
Yes, this is the title The title is Hololive Summer
2023 3D Live Splash
The party will be held on 2 days The
level is Sunshine Day 2  You
can enjoy the two concepts of the night here.
Online tickets are already available for purchase on Zan,
but I'm sure you'll
also see some fixed comments.
Please check it out from the URL.Furthermore, we
will also be streaming free sneak peeks on YouTube, so please look forward to it.And the
swimsuit design is Hololive.
If you would like to see more of this swimsuit design, please
spread the word about the swimsuit on July 29th,
and the
official program that will be distributed every week during the summer period will also be a sour version.  We are
trying out a lot of summer-like projects in 3D, so please look forward to it!
After the official program, we will be broadcasting an after-talk on the Hololive official channel
exclusive to the Membership DX plan,
so be sure to check it out.
And there are many more
exciting collaboration announcements.  I wonder
if there are any images of the
pop-up shop.It has been decided that the pop-up shop will
be held at 5 stores: Shinjuku round annex Hakata Marui, number round Nagoya Sapporo.  A
different exhibition will be held at each of the five stores that will be holding the event, and there
will also be limited-edition merchandise featuring the nine people who sing the main theme.We
have even more exciting news:
Hololive Wafer 3, which has been announced since April.
This is my first review of 3D Kanako,
but it's actually a Hololive Summer yukata costume
product. It will
be on sale at sweets stores nationwide from August. Not
only will there be 35 domestic talents, but this time we will be
specializing in Hololive Indonesia 1.  2nd term  A
total of 51 people were able to enjoy the yukata, with live and Hololive English talent joining in.
[Music]
Please
[Music] I
want it, and on the back is a
handwritten wish that can only be seen with this product.
After I got my hands on what kind of wishes were written on it,
everyone wrote their wishes properly.It's really
nice and I'm looking forward to it.I wonder
if this one also includes E-chan.I
want to see it again.
put in
It's an idol agency,
isn't it? They're both saying
that they hope all the idols and talents can shine even more. They
're both saying that they're going to have a talent show like this. It's a
terrestrial-
only commercial.
Speaking of summer, Hololive is
set to be aired.
[Applause]
Amazing 28 songs will be broadcast online on MBSTBS network nationwide on July 5th
Cover Co., Ltd.'s commercial will be aired in the Jujutsu Kaisen 0 movie slot
Speaking of summer, Hololive
will be aired.
And on July 7th, the large collaboration
project Hololive City will also be held for the first time with the opening sound alone
Live Twinkle For You's Tanabata, as
well as limited editions and tours
[Applause]
And finally, information on goods
Hololive Summer 2023 goods  Volume
1 is half and half
from 10pm after this broadcast ends.
Let's take a look at each one one by one. First, it's the 3D
acrylic stand Smiley Harmony
version. It
's an acrylic stand with a yukata design.
Hey, this was in the waiting room a while ago
Hey, everyone's cute.
Please don't take it home with you.
[Music]
Running, where are you running?
Cute, right?
Next month. Next, here.
[Music]
Next.  Next up is the robot sticker
set.
And on the right is
this floating ring-shaped thing.
[Applause]
[Music] It's
so cute. I saw this more than before. It makes me
want to sit on it.  We
all want to eat those friend stuffed animals.
[Music]
[Applause]
So, let
's move on.
Now, the design is ice cream. When I
looked at the key chain, I thought to myself, these
nine people are blue in color.  It's true that there
are a lot of names written in English, so
if you try to tell who it is by color, you won't be able to do it.It
's quite difficult, but yes,
thank you very much.
It's Live Summer 2023, and I've
received a message from the management. Is
it okay if I read it for you?
[Music]
Everyone, Hololive Summer has arrived again this year.
This year,
members of Indonesian English will also be participating in Hololive.  It's
going to be the biggest summer in history Yes, today's broadcast Today's distribution I
'd like you to declare the opening of Hololive Summer 2023,
but it wouldn't be fun to focus solely on overseas,
so this summer I'll be focusing on Hololive.  We have
prepared a plan for all members to come together and have fun. Hololive
Hololive Indonesia Hololive
English We hope everyone will cooperate and
do their best.
Here is the plan prepared by the management.
Hololive Summer 2023 Opening Declaration
Pressure Game
[Applause]  ]
[Music]
Let's start, wait.
From here on out.
[Music] From
here on out. Do you have a ball and a cup
? A
ball and a pump have appeared.
Please take them.
8 people playing catch in a row using a ball and a cup
[Music] If
you are the one who is going to throw the ball, let it bounce once and
then throw it so that it goes into the cup
[Music]
So, you are holding a cup.  Please
catch the ball. And this is important.
Apparently there is a time limit.
If 8 people catch the ball in a row by 9:50 pm, the
first music video for our theme song will be released. There
are only 13 minutes left.
What if you don't succeed? That's no good.
So who's going to go first?
OK, let's catch Se's yes, y'all.
[Applause] It's
hard to
catch Se's, y'all
.
[Applause] -
That's what it's like.
Next is the red lady.
[Music]
[Applause]
[
Applause] [Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause] [
Laughter]
[Applause] The
power of baseball is space
[Applause]  Let's
go, let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] [Applause] [
Music
] [Applause] [
Applause]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
It's OK to continue from here Let's do it until we get in
[Music]
Someone's still here  I haven't done it
OkOk
[Music]
[Applause]
I can do it
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Applause] It's
weird, it's a
shame
OkOkOk
[Music]
Next time please  I'm
not throwing it,
but I'm not throwing it, but
everyone seems to be losing weight, so I'm going to throw it. Please
take it.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you for taking it.
[Music] [Music
]
[Laughter] [Applause] [Applause]
[Applause]
[  [Music] I
feel like there was a lot of injustice
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Let's show you
what's going on.
Okay, let me take a look.
[Music]
Everyone, it's a ribbon.
[Music]  ]
That's wonderful.
Since it was a success, I will ask Sora-chan to declare the opening.Okay,
then let's go
KatashimaLet's all have fun Holo
Live Summer 2023
Opening
With friends who believe in each other
[Music]
How can we take on the challenge Our never-
ending youth
[Music]
[Music] All of us,
Hei-chan, the
shining water droplets are
falling down, and I
feel youthful. I
want to show you how much I've grown up.
[Music]  For the
actual performance, I'll give it my all, yes, yes, I have a lot of precious
memories, but I'm still shining with emotion, and I
don't have time.It's a
mixture of
expectations.Summer
begins
[Music] The scenery is
at the end of my imagination
[Music]
The scenery is
precious Don't
run away, go beyond the limit wall
We're still challengers
[Music]
[Music] We're
drowning, as if the
few are
pulling us together
Someone laments that we've let down our expectations It hurts, but we
always fight
Relying only on my pride, I want to fight back My ability that I want to believe in
will be rewarded
Those who want to laugh are laughing There
is no time for the
greatest
summer to begin
[Music]
The response is not enough, more and more I
won't let you regret it
[Music] The
rich
scenery that I have won is
precious  Don't
run away, we're still challengers by overcoming the limit wall  I've
received a message from the management for when the event has been successfully declared open.
Oh, I
forgot, everyone, I'd like to see the MV I mentioned earlier
.
After this, the premiere will be released at 10:30 p.m., and
the channel will remain the same.
[Music] I was
informed that I would like to read the message of the opening declaration on your behalf.
So, everyone, I hope the opening ceremony was completed safely. I
hope that everyone will have a hot summer from now on.  We have
prepared a fun project for you to look forward to.
Something good may happen in the special program just before the August 25th concert. Something
good may happen if you collect as many bingo items as
possible.
What exactly is Bingo
? This
is a game where you fill in the apple squares by completing the tasks.The event runs from today
until July 24th at 11:59pm on August 24th.How
to reach the bingo squares  what is it like
But it
's OK, for example, you
eat watermelon. Watermelon is a video where you eat watermelon.
But it's okay, you eat watermelon in the game, but it's
OK. For example, it's common. It's like
Saran Craft.
So, it's OK to eat watermelon in the game
.  And when I can't stream, I
buy a watermelon, I bought it, I ate it at home, and I
post a photo on Twitter or something like that.Oh
yeah, that's okay, but let's have
fun and play bingo.Of
course, there is also a JP
IDEL version.The content is
the same.  Yes, yes
Now that we're unveiling the yukata
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Let's do our best. It's
free to participate, so I'm sure everyone has their own summer plans,
so
please keep an eye on everyone.
Okay, so it's time to say goodbye to today's broadcast.
First of all,
how was Indonesia and everyone in Indonesia?
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
Everyone is cute, so I'm happy, happy, and I'm
really happy today. Thank you very much.
[Applause]
Thank you.
[Laughter] I
'm sure you've all noticed, but Holo
Live English will be held overseas for the first time.
All viewers, please come and see it.
If you haven't gotten a distribution ticket yet,
please buy it.
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work.
[Applause]
[Music]
Everyone, please buy your tickets.
[Music] I
felt like the story was about to begin, and I was very happy to be able to announce so many things.And I'll be
watching it on Hololive EnglishNEXT,
so be sure to check it out.  I hope you guys are looking forward to it as well.
[Music]
I'll be there too.
I'll be at the English concert, too. I
hope you'll join
us as well. Now that I've had the opportunity to speak with you, I'm looking forward to getting to know you all even better.  I
hope that I was able to deepen my understanding of you,
so I look forward to your continued support.
Thank you very much.
If you'd like, let's go to Aqua's house together. There was
something that I've always been curious about, so I
decided to stream it.  This one-hour broadcast
This person has always been close to me.
This person will definitely exist.
Summer is about to begin. Bye-
bye. I wonder how it was with this kind of person. It was fun, everyone.  I
put on that yukata again.Next time, it
's everyone's swimsuit stream.Even
though we are members,
we can also wear swimsuits, so we want to come.I
saw on Bingo that we're going to stream swimsuits, so
yeah, yeah, that's right, so yeah, at home.  You might
find some swimsuits.
Please look forward to it. Finally, let me
say goodbye to you. Thank you for your hard work, everyone. Let's get excited
this year! Open Yay Yay Year Bye-
bye.
[Music]
By