[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
how long is the pokemon presentation
still going on
[Applause]
how long is that usually
their usual time
what's with your voice
what do you mean what's with my voice
is my voice weird
i sound different
[Music]
it's cringe okay you're getting blocked
time's out there you go
[Music]
huh
is this not how i usually sound
wait how does
you sound normal right do i oh my god i
don't even i
i don't know
i don't even know
i sounded so laid back
okay
oh wow this room is hot
it's getting hot in here you'll take off
all your clothes i am getting so hot i'm
gonna take my clothes off yeah
welcome welcome welcome welcome somebody
stole my chair so i'm sitting on the
floor
bamboozled i never had a chair
on this layout
under the table
[Music]
okay so the i want to watch the pokemon
present from the very beginning so i'm
gonna wait until
it's over which is maybe 10 more minutes
or so
and then yeah
and then we'll watch it i need some pgm
[Music]
it lets you rewind oh it does oh well
i'm gonna wait anyway
um
so today is minecraft with my mommy
my mommy said i should greet you guys
from my mommy
have you received the greeting
you seem too loud
uh my mommy is uh currently
on the server
um
preparing things
because she she has to be prepared you
know
she already has diamond armor
um
and she she told me she put my
she put my
my my traders my phoenix and traders in
the boat
she's already like starting to organize
it my [\h__\h] it's just like back in the
days when i was living with my mom
[Laughter]
just kidding that actually
like she would clean my room sometimes
because i would
um my my room
when i lived with my mom always used to
be quite
chaotic and
messy
not anymore but when i lived with my mom
when i was small
small small chill
she would uh
yeah
uh sometimes give up she would always
tell me to clean my room but
um
sooner or later she would give up and
and just clean the room for me
but she would not really reorganize my
things she would just pick up the [\h__\h]
ton of clothes from my floor
get rid of them i guess
[Music]
and also right now i think she's in the
nether
farming gold
because apparently we need gold for
something
she's also she prepared everything for
the farm that we're making as well
we're making an automatic farm um
for something specific
and i guess we need gold for something
i'm not sure for what but yeah
out of your skin
[Music]
my mom so there was like a minecraft
skin
but i should talk about this later
[Laughter]
i should talk about this during the
stream
okay
so yeah
thank you for the membership welcome
um
youtube
uh susan
fixed the thing that was broken for a
while
uh
which is the superset window
it's just one [\h__\h] mouse click
it took them over a week to fix it wow
speed
congratulations youtube
and
um
in that over one week at some point i
started reading the super chats through
uh stream elements
but the ones from before
uh from like
a week ago
uh
i did not over a week ago yeah i missed
those
but
and i thought i was gonna lose them
because
at a certain point
uh super jets get cleaned up uh
like when it reaches a certain number i
don't know what the number is but
usually if it's like a big event stream
then we have to like save in between
save save them on the file in between
otherwise some get lost
yeah yeah so and i thought they were
gonna be lost but they weren't they're
actually there they are they're getting
eating i think it was pretty kitty kitty
so i put them all in an excel file last
night and now we can read them properly
the ones that i missed starting
with
uh
um
with the waiting room super chats mixed
in with some
um m elephant and um super chats and so
on
and somewhere in between we can also
talk about the new generation because i
actually haven't
uh talked about them yet because
yesterday
what did i stream yesterday
ah yesterday was a tale of a rise stream
that was like one and a half hours so i
didn't really get to
talk about it yet
didn't really you predicted the l
actually that was uh
that was not
like not now that i thought about this
yesterday too
now that i
at the point at the point where i made
the
owl video
i think i already knew about her
but it was not on purpose still
i just wanted to make an owl video
because i recently learned how to make
an owl noise thanks to tales of a rise
[Laughter]
[Music]
it actually has no connection yeah uh
although now that i think about it it
could be it could be seen as a hint
as a teaser from my side because i often
do that don't i but it was not so it was
not so
uh
however i feel like recently i said
something else that was looking at hint
there was something but i think i
shouldn't say that yet but then then
there was another thing
oh yeah casper
oh
there's something there was something
that i said
oh yeah it would be nice
[Laughter]
that was kind of me being like yeah i
mean i know i i know
i think someone on twitter was like um
it's like was like saying something like
you responded to my comment what did you
say i think we we were hinting on
wouldn't it be nice to have uh another
bird and i was like yeah would be nice
to have another bird because i could
speak bird language
with the birds yeah
but i was just reacting to your tweets
uh so yeah yeah
you need to start taking everything you
say as sort of hints no
no as i said the hour video was never
supposed to be a hint
yeah
but uh did you guys know nanasi moment
is a really funny name
because
uh it means no name no name
[Music]
anonymous anonymous
yeah she has no name
oh man hallelujah management
having a funny bone again
it's like they ate something funny
in the morning and they were like this
is it
we call her kiawah
no
[Music]
i read it on twitter and i was like oh
my god i don't know if they did that on
purpose too
cause it's like no name new name is like
who
i don't know i don't know if they really
thought that far
i'm not sure but it would be funny
because it's like a owl noise
[Music]
should i tell you
who my visual crash was when i first saw
the generation
the one who i personally find
visually
most appealing
is uh kuroni
she's hot as [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
like i love i love the dark blue color
and her
artist her artist
her is actually
i mean we all know who her artist is but
you guys don't know the thing
dude you don't know what i'm trying to
hint on okay you guys don't understand
he is a hello project nerd just like me
he's a [\h__\h] freaking otaku hello
if you look on his twitter you will
notice he's a big fan of i think angela
which is one of the hello project units
and it just cracks me up because i've
been i've been
i've been um
like watching his twitter account for a
while because i always thought it was
very funny that such a big big big fate
uh fgo famous artist
is a fan of hello project openly i
thought it was funny like it's an
interesting combination and like he
fangirls on his twitter all the time she
it's a girl okay sorry i didn't know
she fangirls on her twitter all the time
so
i i just always thought that was
uh very interesting so
[Music]
it's unbelievable yeah i'm gonna be
besties with cronies mama just kidding
not gonna happen probably but i'm
definitely gonna like like hint at her
that i'm also a big hello passing fan
and i'm gonna be like yo yo yo
wait actually
we could we could
i think i could
i think i could um establish a good
relationship with crony's mama
and
i'm also like on good terms with cronie
already
we've had some we've had some
conversations uh private conversations
so
i think
i could marry crony
[Laughter]
because her mom would probably would
probably approve
if i if i tell her how much i love hello
project she will be like wow that's a
good that's a good daughter-in-law to
have
no no i'm not trying to marry the mother
i'm trying to
maybe marry the daughter
but i also okay i wanted to do this
whole reaction thing a little bit later
but oh well whatever um
also
hello
also um
hackles bails
haku's bails
oh my god i love her
now
i cannot get go into too much detail why
i love
her but
i wanna i wanna collab with her every
week
when she's out
because
i just need
i need to listen to her
24 7. i love her oh my gosh
yeah
casper
yeah there already have been some
interesting
revelations
because she's a
a rat
supposedly
apparently
she seems to be a rat
uh
also i love her artist too
i love her i've been following mika
pikazo
also for a while before before she
became a mama and i wrote i wrote to her
mama
after the debut was announced i wrote to
her publicly on twitter i was like i
told her something and i was thinking
all this time
months ago
um
i i i'm not sure if the whole live
english auditions is what sparked this
thought in me but i was thinking like oh
i hope for a future generation
uh
of whole life i hope they choose mika
picazo as one of the artists
because
it would just
be so good
it would be a great great style for uh
an artist so i months ago i already kind
of
i felt it coming no i was i was praying
for it and that's why it happened mm-hmm
i have summoned me kapikazoo
ah
yeah yeah yeah
um i felt it in the force
i i don't know i i don't think i felt it
coming i think i made it come
i think i'm i am i kind of summoned it
you know
i summoned mika picasso it's whole alive
that is my
my personal
[Music]
uh
shut up um let's watch the
before we read super chat let's watch
the
pokemon presents
[Music]
uh wait it's standing out right yeah
okay where do i watch it is that
that's french
where's the english one
wait it's still wait no it's still going
no this one is over why is the japanese
one still going
this one is uh over
all right all right
27 minutes you guys did you already
watch it you should watch it with me
wait it's half an hour
i just realized it's happening that
means we're doing a half an hour watch
along oh my god i guess we're doing that
how was it
half an hour long
oh my god once along i thought it would
be like 10 minutes or something
[Music]
okay
uh here's a link
i pinned it okay
i'm not gonna do a timer but
um
we'll just
everyone who comes in
playing around i guess we'll have to
i don't know
chill a little bit
or i guess
nah
yeah no timer
[Laughter]
we'll wait a little bit
maybe i should i should do a timer
and i turn i am going to turn off the
bgm i guess
okay
uh
i'll do a timer forgot sick
no that's not it what's what what time i
don't use uh it's it's not it it wasn't
wait
timer online oh my oh my stopwatch that
was it i always look for timer then i
realized wait that's not it and then i
realized wait i need to stop watch
right so this time i finally got it
right
okay v v clock
it's like a v tuber clock
it's just for me
virtual
youtuber purpose
nice
okay
yo
google no not using google
now
google
uh
[Music]
wait a second
uh
how about
i do this
and i do this
oh hell yeah
shh okay
[Music]
okay the timer time
studio mode yep finally studio mode is
useful
okay and after we watch this roommate
super chats immediately
[Music]
are you ready
hey look it's cronie
you know i i saw all these interesting
interesting um like
how to say
artworks and and and theories coupling
up ahmed with crony but what about me
i'm about time too my whole thing is
about time as well
or who else would you couple me up with
if
if ahmed is with cronie
wait
who would you couple up with who
ah bird amume ah that makes sense yeah
bird
and who would you who would you couple
up with fauna
nature
gouda maybe
then if you couple her up with cali then
who who would you couple up with uh sana
i saw people like i don't know
sana and ina
why
why what is there what is there to
combine
the ancient void and space
ancient ones
oh
okay if you say that fits and it fits if
it fits it sits
and bales hackles
i feel like bales would be with cal you
know
chaos and underworld death and stuff
[Music]
then i i know i would kind of do bales
with cali and then fall now with gouda
because good eyes about water
and all that yeah good eye is a bit
difficult to combine with these girls
i wonder if that's something that the
management was having in mind
that like each council kind of
represents one of us though i wonder if
that's the thing because
they are definitely
thinking a lot about all of this
goodness nature i don't know i don't
know man i don't know and it's like
water is her element so i don't know but
but fauna is more like earth is her
element so if anything
uh atlantis civilization no
burp is mine verb is mine
anyway let's watch it zoom me take them
okay okay go get it free uh two uh
uh uh on go
it's buffering for me why
one more time
okay
um
why do i not what is this what is it
with this video i don't even it's like
maybe is it because it's not like
properly
i know now it's moving
okay three
two
one
go
wait
i think it's a vod thing it doesn't da
no
it's buffering
it like oh dear i think we can't watch
this right now
[Laughter]
miranda lower the quality
eh
okay
how about 720
p
yep much better okay hi thank you for
this
three
two
one
go
all right pokemon presents
[Laughter]
maybe then it finished buffering
yo my internet usually doesn't have this
issue so i think it's because it they
just ended the archive
so okay super chat rating forget this
one forget it
ah
all right
his background reminds me of um
when i went to the pokemon shop in japan
yeah lots of pokemon merch oh my god the
amount of pokemon merch in the pokemon
shop
damn
i went to one in tokyo and one in osaka
before
um
mike sounds different what what is it
with you guys
if maybe it's because like i have a i'm
a like okay what about what what about
now
because i wasn't i was a little bit uh
far away from the microphone
now i'm close
is that is this do is now i sound normal
to you
is this this is this the difference
it sounds a bit different it changes
nothing
i changed nothing
i'ma turn on music
[Music]
if it made no
particular difference and i'll lean back
a little bit again because i think i i
really cannot sit up straight but it's
better to lean back right rather than
crack crouching slouching forward in
order to reach the microphone because i
like automatically do that even though i
don't have to
myself
like when the microphone is away from me
i like
i really tried sorry i really tried to
like get this like slouch forward get
this
round back and then just get close to
the microphone but i shouldn't do that
so i want to force myself to ignore the
microphone because it it fixes my volume
anyway no matter how far away i am
thanks to the equalizer thank you
so i'll just try to stay in the back
can you guys remind me of that every
once in a while
just say yo kiara lean back chill
lean back and enjoy the show
[Music]
i mean maybe this will help if i put the
chair pillow there because i normally
hate it
yeah no
[Music]
i really like that okay that helps no
clue out
i mean i still have my legs on my
on my chair
[Music]
but i can leave this
not like that
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
is
are you saying like l from death note
yeah you could compare it to that so
let's read the freaking zombie test
because i'm like procrastinating and
tangenting too much
oh my god
this is the one
do a flip kiana please what the [\h__\h] do
you want from me
if you ask me this now
do a flip now
you i've added it that's really
difficult to react to
all right you guys
let's go yomi mas
uh we start with oh i should probably
put up uh
but i don't actually have a thumbnail
for this one i just used whatever
youtube gave me
uh
we're reading em owl now okay
it's not that much anyway mr caspian
[Music]
your name is uh like japanese i always
want to say some to you but you always
write in english and always donate in
canadian
maple leaves
so
it's weird
so thanks for pinky
my oshi is very animal
very
except one
which one
which which one are you hinting on
tanaka
which one are you talking about would
you like to go into detail about which
one i am not
[Music]
tanaka
yojo room
silly bird you're a silly bird
rook
thank you for the pink pinkie
hey
my god my mouse recently i have to
replace my mouse it's like constantly
locking in the scroll wheel
and it's really annoying it's doing it
constantly
patrick action daisy
some guy duncan big sweet duncan i
actually have a wireless
razor mouse the pink one
but i haven't been using it because
i don't like the way it moves on my on
my screen
even though i tried adjusting it
and i hate the fact that i have to load
it up yeah i prefer wired ones for some
reason
yeah so i haven't been using the one the
the one from razer at all i've been
using some
super cheap ass no name
brand
no brand uh
thingy yeah
[Music]
wired back bails
can't you use it wired that one no i
don't think it came with a cable no no
it didn't come with a cable
[Music]
that one is wireless
the software
i think i did
yeah it just feels like weird slow i
don't know even though i made it like
maximum i don't know it feels weird
[Music]
is a wrap not a mouse
did she
is that like an official
uh statement
i think we're gonna have some
discussions about that she's gonna
probably try to
um
make people think she's a mouse
which is actually a she looks like a
mouse it says rat on the shirt oh
[Laughter]
literally says
[Music]
oh it says mouse on her youtube
description
well that's misleading
is that for real let me see
oh where's her account
here it is wow
120k
yo bails let's go
i wonder how much it will be before the
before the debut
i add the w
so where is it yeah a member of the
council and the very constant occasions
but she mostly under the approach
this is the first time i read this i'm
not actually reading it much though
and instead when no their mouths like a
mouse like mouse like
they're they're trying to avoid saying
what exactly she is i say i see i see
i say i see i see
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
[Music]
so i just had this interesting
revelation which i i think i had before
already but like rats and mouse is the
same word in japanese
which is difficult because i just wanted
to explain
how
hakkos is implying she might be a mouse
but on her t-shirt it says red so we are
not sure what she is
but i can't explain that when both of
the words are nezumi in japanese
yeah it's a big difference right because
rat is like much bigger and people
prefer mice over rats like generally
because like i don't know there's like
this what is it
this
this general general feeling in the
world
that rats are something you don't like i
mean people still have rats as their
pets
some some people stigma yeah that's the
word i wanted there's this this stigma
the rats are bad and and disgusting and
mice are like tolerable
and cute
don't trust what she said what you wear
yeah she scales me she's just causing
chaos with her t-shirt
my language is the same too in your
language it's the same as well
[Music]
in in german it's mouse
easy and rate
[Music]
it's very similar
miko thought her t-shirt says pad
how
maybe your mayonnaise is an rta gamer
and she just uh heard her t-shirt was a
myth
okay shut up
kiara just shut up and read super chats
it's not even funny daisy
thank you for the high quality content i
love you thank you
and very high quality indeed
that's it with ml now we do the dokomi
waiting room i think i have that
somewhere the thumbnail
um there it is
what is it
oh that's not it
[Music]
where did i save
that one
what did i say of it
[Music]
oh there it is
this one right
yeah oh my god it already feels like so
long ago oh man
it was a great experience
[Music]
so weird it hasn't been that long that
was 20 years it was not
[Music]
it was a short stream yeah because it
was only on for five five seconds i had
to
i had to do that because if i don't go
live and just delete the waiting room
then it doesn't like it makes all the
super chats disappear on my list
[Music]
so i have to stream
for five seconds
eight seconds actually
there they are
taking it very very
very correctly
have you played any pokemon game
[Music]
foreign
what
[Music]
[Laughter]
i guess so
okay let's read these super chats
um
[Music]
kelly
thank you for the pinky
it may be my birthday but i couldn't
resist super chatting as my own little
zebra celebration thanks for being
yokiah oh my god thank you
it was your birthday
i'm so late
sorry
well happy bellina's birthday
[Music]
which one was it
happy melina's birthday
i hope you celebrated well
and hope you're healthy and happy um i
wish you all the best thank you for the
support
crispy chicken madison jacob's monkey
duncan as zoro 604 duncan
[Music]
trevor g duncan
for the two pinkies what is going on
forgive me i have sinned i am the most
foul owl to ever owl what
after kiara tweeted guten abend i placed
my phone down i'm sure if anything else
would happen today and went to make food
for family i missed
i missed ow the m owl one owl i missed
out or what one one one
the m notifications at the premiere you
missed the ml video no
as such i must now hand my title over to
you tenchow
[Laughter]
oh
you're hooting and screech i'll
ah
was so you actually recognized it i was
like i was gonna do like a huddle
uh
noise but i felt like actually you know
what i want to do it properly so i
looked up
owl
noise videos and
tried my best to impersonate those ones
that sounded simple and and recognizable
nice
your hooting and screech owl trail was
so beautifully down done you have proved
yourself to be the true owl of camping
now
i can only feel a great and hang my head
in shame i'm truly the unforgivable
oh
oh no it's all good what the hell
but
you know
i'm a bit worried about you
leaving kfc
because there's a real owl now
and we all know how much you love owls
um
so
i will have to
put you into the usual room until
further notice
because i cannot let you go
[Music]
so there you go
you
[Music]
i told you
it's in the contract
if you if you show yourself
as a loyal kfb employee if you can prove
that to me while you're in the usual
room i will let you out eventually
but for now i have to i have to play
safe you know i have to play sync
have to make sure
that you stay at cave peak
[Music]
stay with the phoenix the almighty the
almighty bob
you can learn things from me i can make
you into a fire owl trust me okay
[Music]
foreign
trevor is not dead okay
he's just in the usual room he's
chilling he's chilling
oh thank you for the red super chat
you also for the pinky that meat and
great room will be full of spaghetti ah
nah
make sure you bring some home with you
seriously though your chickens will be
10 times more nervous than you be strong
for them and have a great time quick
look on fish basket thank you
um
yeah they they were quiet um a bunch of
them were quite nervous
but
uh
you know whenever someone like seemed
like they didn't really know what to
talk about or when they like blacked out
i was always there you can count on me
you can count on your attention to be
there to you know
help you
out
what the [\h__\h]
there it is okay
ah [\h__\h] mouse
[\h__\h] mouse mate
[Music]
wait you taught me before i had to read
your name didn't you
[Music]
hide [\h__\h]
is this person here in the chat
sorry
you should you should write that into
your name additionally
in brackets at the end
thank you membership comes on
i'm reading uh how do you say that in a
phonetic phonetic reading
at the end of your name please thank you
it's been a while
thank you for the super chat oh my god
it was your 18th birthday
18 depending on what country you're in
that means you're legal in my countries
uh that means you're legal
in my country drinking ages 16
smoking as well
wait i'm getting confused i'm not sure
anymore because i
none of that applies to me
wait a second i actually forgot
you're an adult with 18.
wait a second
smoking is maybe with 18.
wait what i'm 16 foot wait a second wait
a second why am i why i always knew what
uh
australia australia
[Music]
drinking age
18.
no essentially anyone over the age of 16
can buy and drink alcohol
except for spirits spirits and stuff is
with 18 yeah yeah yeah
so generally like beer and wine you can
drink of 16 and then spirits of 18.
and then smoking
[Music]
yeah
uh 16 for smoking as well yeah yeah you
guys were so shocked it confused me i
was like wondering if i was really
correct
but yes yes yes 16 16.
i i mean i personally think it should be
uh later but yeah
even if you make it later people who
want to break it
will break it anyway
so yeah yeah i know it's 21 in the us
that's like that's like wow so late i
mean it doesn't apply to me because i
don't give a [\h__\h] i don't drink alcohol
i don't smoke
i never did so
it wouldn't matter to me if it was 16 18
or 21
[Music]
never smoking never drinking gang yo
what's up
i hope i can be a good influence
on the children watching my stream
[Laughter]
besides you know teaching you swear
words i hope i can at least
um be a good influence in another way
[Music]
thank you for the membership
straight edge what what what does that
mean
nice straight edge again what does that
does that mean does that describe
someone who doesn't drink and doesn't
smoke
a person who doesn't drink is straight
edge
you don't do anything bad
ah
straight straight straight ass show but
you know you know how it is with me and
going straight
i'm european
[Music]
tangent edge how about that because uh
wait the tangent is still straight
though
just straight if you look at it from a
different angle
okay i will stop talking
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
the other day you were saying you're a
little afraid that your voice might
sound weird because it's a different
setup oh yeah i was wondering about that
but your voice was actually incredible
that mike you don't need to worry at all
can't wait to hear you sing kanok is
next have fun thank you
um
[Music]
supposedly
supposedly the microphone like they gave
me a microphone first that was just like
a razor
uh
like a black
razor the one that i don't know it's
like really cheap
and i told them that's not gonna work
because actually that was a usb
microphone
and uh
um i brought my goes alarm with me
uh and it you it doesn't support usb so
i was like i can't use that
uh so after that how much does that cost
the usb razer microphone
after that you know what they brought me
next
a 2 000 microphone supposedly
i like i like how they go from like
really low to really really high
like i cannot i cannot prove it because
i don't actually know the name but it
was like a really weird looking
microphone
let me try if i can find it sennheiser
it was a sennheiser microphone
it was like really slim
is that really two thousand dollars or
were they exaggerating
[Music]
to make me
uh feel
like i have to be careful with it
it looks uh
it was really really thin it looked like
a like a little stick
[Music]
but it was i mean it was um good enough
for the its purpose i would say
is that it oh that looks a little bit
like it
shotgun microphone
and not exactly something similar
[Music]
ah that's what oh is that it
anyway it doesn't matter but
so with that microphone it worked and
then i um set up everything um
i set up everything with my go explorer
and all that but we had a lot of
issues
we had a lot of issues um
with the audio and uh
yeah
it's very very very very very very very
complicated
so i cannot get into more detail
um
but it was all in all very complicated
i'm just glad it somehow worked out in
the end but i'm just sorry for the
people who
had to watch it on the stream because i
know the quality was very bad on the
stream i feel like
in the concert hall it was also not
ideal in the beginning but i think just
from the fact that you're sitting in a
concert hall the acoustics are already
like kind of weird so maybe it was not
that noticeable i think if you're at
home sitting there with your headphones
then it is more noticeable than when you
sit surrounded by a lot of people in a
big big big concert hall
um
with lots of noise around you
uh i think i think that makes it a
little bit more
bearable it got better after the first
song i'm happy to hear that
but yeah
i i'm just glad it somehow
worked out we managed
you managed to what then the
noise sounded fine after the beginning
we managed we managed
i like the way of saying that we managed
we managed to deal with your
shitty quality kiana
oh why don't you like horror games isn't
it fun to play horror games no it's not
fun but i'm not saying no
um
you know i
if i had to choose between a shooting
game and a horror game i would choose a
shooting game
now i will i will play a horror game for
halloween
but that was that's probably going to be
about it mostly except if it's something
like
that that is something i can play every
once in a while even though even for
phasmophobia
um
i did i do feel very scared and very
nervous
uh outlast yeah so i saw people
recommending outlast to me well like
good out i'm good at recommending
outlast to me but from what i've heard
outlast
is
is uh quite the scary choice for your
first proper horror game
especially if you're not really into
horror games
so i think we should start with
something
a bit more easy on the nerves
if i were to play more horror games i
don't i definitely don't want it to be a
thing on my channel but it's not like
i'm completely
like against it for both of them above
fps games and
and um horror games
it's not gonna be like a
like a
thing like jrpgs aren't but still
um
like
i don't really wanna play apex or all
those kind of games
um but but
i i i understand that there are shooting
shooter games sps games
that are like one solo player i
understand that and those those are
something i can like
kind of like
um
consider i feel like i can consider
playing those i just need good
recommendations that we actually have
uh also uh permissions for
if it's like if it actually even has a
story
then okay okay i can get behind that
bioshock
would you guys want me want me to play
that bioshock mass effect doom
[Music]
we can give it a try for like one
episode it might not be like a
like a whole series
but can give it a try
bioshock 1 will be perfect bioshock
fireshot
bioshock
bioshock is a shooter unlike any you've
ever played loaded with weapons and
tactics never seen
all access
[Music]
fps with some rpg-like customization
elements and crafting elements players
progress throughout
[Music]
call of duty bioshock infinite mass
effect mass effect has cute girls no way
is the main character you play
but you don't see it because you're an
fps like first person right ah
okay i just googled it you call that
cute it's an alien ah wait there's a
human too the human looks uh
looks like uh looks cute
red hair just cute girl okay
mass effect what is mass effect about
it's from ea
e-a challenge everything
uh
what's it about
what is this about
it's like the story is there a story
the effect of mass
a mass effect is a science fiction media
franchise blah blah blah blah blah the
franchise depicts an alternate universe
where humanity and several alien
civilizations have colonized the milky
way
yummy galaxy using technology seemingly
left behind but advanced precursors will
a lot
[Music]
oh
humanity comes into contact with
numerous other space-faring alien
species some far more advanced than
humans see the thing is um
that already sounds a little bit like
science fiction
and i am not a fan of science fiction
[Laughter]
like universe stuff
[Music]
like space spacey science fiction star
wars stuff
uh star trek
it is science fiction yeah okay i'm not
so much into that
[Music]
yeah sci-fi news
not so much
space magic yeah massive like very yeah
it looks very very sci-fi
yeah more like something like fantasy
would be cool
tomb raider two braider huh
two minutes in fps oh wait a second
right now
oh yeah
the one that used to have like triangle
boobs before
[Music]
oh
yeah yeah that's a that's an fps oh [\h__\h]
i would i would play that it has a cute
girl
not an fbs but it's a tps
eps
a third person oh okay cool cool cool
cool cool
do we have permission for tomb raider
who is the
who is the publisher
[Music]
not impossible i would say
horizon
[Music]
ah
gorilla games don't we have like
permissions for them
oh she she cute
is that an fps
i like the looks of it
a tps fbs tps third-person rpg
oh
but then that's not like um
is it a shooting game she has a bow
she's in fortnite what the hell
well
great person bullshitting
does that count
that doesn't count though you guys want
me to play fps don't you
it doesn't count does it
where's my list for like games i might
want to play
it technically counts because i'm
shooting
will it count it account it counts i
guess it counts
really
all right okay i'll make a new list um
tomb raider
uh horizon
verizon
zero dawn okay
and uh
or is more interesting no i don't wanna
i don't wanna
i'm really scared okay
i'm really scared yeah
resident evil is shooting plus horror
i'll think about it i heard there was
one uh resident evil game that's like
okay to slide into
that was not that scary
i don't know which one it was
four
seven
seven and eight
two
two four
seven eight
but you know what it's like absolutely
unrelated now but i i always thought it
would be a little bit interesting to
play it but it looks very difficult what
was that game again where where piccolo
sampai always had to mute the music
where you put stuff on your back and you
have to carry it around and the whole
world is like really [\h__\h]
step stranding yep they're stranding
i kind of
ever since pick when i played it i felt
interested in it
i i but it looks very difficult it looks
very very difficult
[Music]
pick it up baby yeah
please no
i know
really isn't it's different for everyone
you'll need some practice
a lot of walking yeah
it's hard to fail
watching family
yeah you just deliver stuff yeah but i
don't know it i just it just had
something it just had something about it
anyway let's go back to super chat
story corner dancing patrick's and
packaging
thank you for the red super chat yeah
go go live performance of the little
song that could
what
what does that mean this love area
logo live performance of the little song
that could
help me out here guys what does that
message mean
[Music]
his heart challenge how
reference to a book
oh man
i didn't get it again
little engine that could ah
what thank you for the red super chat
wow
[Music]
thank you i'm confused but i am also
grateful
[Music]
thank you
oh yeah this is where the live
performance started
noise i can't wait to read all the
messages from afterwards india taylor
i'll guess this is already word and then
that ended quickly
[Music]
i don't like reading
german like not that much german
i told you before
it's embarrassing
thank you for the red silver jet i know
you do it on purpose what the frick the
freak fine
why
why are you making me suffer
yeah yeah it's my main language but i
feel embarrassed
when i read it in front of you guys
[Music]
i know i know the whole convention was
in german
oh man it felt um
so different so weird
uh doing the whole convention in german
but
but it was really cool it was really a
lot of fun
it's already been so long ago
i hope i wish it was like a fresher
experience but
um
hmm
look on me
welcome me
i think i think we have to do it again i
think i have to go to dokomi again next
year in order to improve on on the
things that we didn't do so well this
time
uh which is like audio quality and stuff
but besides that i think it was great i
think it was a big big big big success
and i was able to show you guys my new
stage
layout
which i'm really really proud of i
really like it
yeah
and next next year
hopefully there will be no restrictions
so we can really fill up that concert
hall
and then we'll make an even bigger wave
[Music]
yeah
that would be nice
and i want to do another meet in green
because the meet and greet was really
the most special thing about it somehow
about the whole day
i don't know man the meeting great
it gave me
such a special
way to connect with you guys
yeah
it was very special
[Music]
i want to take
almost had me crying
[Music]
thank you i didn't expect that i don't
know why but i didn't expect them to do
that
and we were we were already over time
but my life
also started a little bit too late
and right before um
i started singing
and and with like a few seconds before i
was like the staff was standing next to
me and i was like yo can i
like because we started late does that
mean i have to uh shorten my whole set
and and he was like no no no problem
just
do whatever you want basically so
i i i guess it was okay to extend it a
little bit
yeah
[Music]
but i still felt a little bit scared
when people were asking for an end car
and you know me um i want to please my
chickens so it's not like i can turn you
guys down and i was happy i was i had so
much like adrenaline in me and
what do you call that the thing that's
like happiness
uh not adrenaline but the other thing
[Music]
open dopamine indoor endorphins
endorphins and indoor and endorphins
that's the one i mean i think
yeah i had all that in me so i i i
wanted to do more yeah
[Music]
it's just so special to hear the people
and not only see the the letters that
they're typing in the chat as usual
yeah
but that gave me a chance to redo her
challenger so that was good
jim tracy duncan skye duncan and
oatmeal cookie oh too dark [\h__\h] midnight
danish from black christian dancing
this is your power in toonie and you got
the crowd to be so energetic yeah
i can't wait to see a true power in 3d i
won't miss it for the world and i will
share for your life my wish was born for
this thank you
yeah
can you imagine
the power i had in 2d and now imagine
the power i will have in 3d one day
[Music]
yeah
i might have less power though because
in 3d i'll i would move around a lot and
instead of just sitting down
and who knows i might not
i might be out of out of breath very
soon and just die on stage
what will we do then
wait fast
i love that
[Music]
actually i have some
very interesting things
uh
to show you guys on the one month um
anniversary
i mean one year anniversary i'm planning
a few interesting things
the thing is though that weekend
is gonna be
it's extremely packed because think
about it
we're doing uh
all of us are doing anniversary streams
and we're probably most likely gonna do
a one-year anniversary collaboration
stream
between the 11th and the 12th this will
happen on the 10th
i'll probably have a tails of a rice
sponsorship stream because the game is
coming out and then also
we have uh i think a two day convention
um
or three day three day convention where
i don't know how long the conventions
but i think we
all of us will be there like for two
days or whatever
over that same weekend
but i don't know yet at what time
any of these things are going to happen
so i can't plan yet i don't know when
i'm doing the stream for the anniversary
i don't know when the tales of a rice
stream is happening and i also don't
know when the convention thing is
happening and then you also got a plan
that the rehearsal for the convention
has to be somewhere as well but but
since it's like the same people from
before
um
i already know what kind of rehearsal it
will be so last time it only took like
less than an hour and we've asked so
many questions that i will not ask next
time because i already have them
answered so it might be even shorter
than an hour so the rehearsal shouldn't
be much of an issue but still
yeah
so i know
[Music]
how
that will be an insane weekend
insane
but i'm excited oh my god i can't
believe it's been almost a year
oh my god don't i can't i can't think
about it it's too crazy to think about
it
we've spent a year almost
it's just
crazy to think i spent a whole year
doing this
wow
wow that's that's like a big part
of my
current life
if we combine all the lives all the
lives uh all the reborn reincarnations
whatever uh phoenix lives
then it's just one one
tiny second of it
yeah but if it's my current
current uh
in reincarnation
[Music]
you absolutely look at me seeing you on
the real stage in front of a real crowd
it was a beautiful moment so proud of
you i can't even put it into words thank
you
yeah that was really
emotional
big swing thank you thank you
unknown thanksgiving
thank you for the applause thank you
mitchell triangle duncan
thank you for the pinky
hey
so proud to be here witnessing your
dreams come true even if only on twitch
seeing how many how much fun you've had
on the stage makes me want to pester
every crown in poland to invite you
and maybe do another meet and greet and
wish i could be their specific
especially since it's kind of close to
me but spends too much on your birthday
merch
next time i'll be prepared and come with
a chicken mask hope you enjoyed the
letters thank you
yeah i think i saw your leather i think
i did
yeah yeah yeah yeah i think i did
thank you for the support thank you
[Music]
poland convention what's a big
convention in poland
the gifts no the gifts didn't arrive yet
but i hadn't looked for the letters
anyway before uh when i was in the hotel
mariah thank you for the running super
dad
yay for all the k-pop originals
[Music]
choosing honor of weber for not just the
translations but the time stamps that
make it a chiata pop
you confuse me this look real
but the time stamps that make it
possible for me to stay caught up
ah the time translation is end times
yeah good job red bear thank you for the
support
[Music]
is coming i'm telling you
it's gonna be
the biggest trend ever
sometime in the future
just kidding i don't know i feel like
i don't know i don't know how much more
music i'm going to make um
so i i guess i can't really
uh
say whether or not it will be
trending whatever thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky what a great set
of streams at dokomi i hope you had fun
and i can't wait to see you live in
person myself yay thank you
i hope i hope you got the chance to do
that at some point yeah that would be
great
thank you for the support and for
watching me on twitch
yeah
hoping for a full album pencil i'm
hoping for it too at some point but
that's a lot to organize and a lot to
invest on
a baby metal original song
you mean an original song in the style
of baby metal
if i had the context to the right
producer
[Music]
german lyrics no
maybe a little bit but not a full german
song
rompo thank you for the rent super chat
yeah next time i won't miss this
opportunity for anything in the world on
venice vino confident
that was so amazing i was hyping so much
and i was when i was watching you on
twitch i couldn't stop smiling we need
tension all around the world
thank you
i have been uh going a little bit around
the world so
yeah
america just very recently so
we're on it we're on a mission guys
thank you for the super chat faction
[Music]
choose in honor of the cursed cursor
look curious kirsten
and dominic who made diggy dikikomi and
does dokomi possible and delivered fan
letters to jmt
oh yeah yeah yeah
dominique was the one who originally
suggested
to diggy call me to invite me
and that was very very smart there was a
cursor on a stream on the screen
what
was it always in the same position that
might have been my own cursor i'm not
sure
[Music]
there was a cursor on the stream on the
screen when
stayed it
if it stayed at the same point all the
time then it was not mine because i was
like desperately on one screen on one
freaking laptop screen i was desperately
trying to
switch between all the different windows
i had
it was there for both streams it didn't
move much okay then it was probably
probably not
mine
because i i moved my cursor a lot
maybe it was bales
didn't see any cursor
or
stationary yeah okay then that's not me
interesting interesting
remember when back when you stream those
using only one monitor yeah there was a
time wasn't it but like in the beginning
like a year ago
which i think is a little bit overkill
it's not 100 necessary i would say
because i have to look around so much
uh so i don't actually use the third
monitor uh
unless i do like a garden phone stream
because i use the third monitor as a
tablet because it is a tablet
but other than that i usually have
everything on two screens only
yeah
yeah i think two two is like yeah fine
three is a
for me it feels a little bit like
overkill because i don't want to
i want my comments to be close to the to
the game window that i'm always looking
at and then behind the game window i
want my youtube window to be open
and so on so and that's yeah
yeah
big fan from korea
thank you yeah i want you guys to be
close so i can read it all the time
and not always have to look to one
monitor that's super far
[Music]
away you can easily tell when you're
looking at the chat don't get used to it
i always change the position now you're
here now you're here you were here and
now you're gonna be
here okay
definitely going to try making it to
dokomi next year sadly couldn't be here
for your irl clown debut but seeing how
fun and exciting everything looked i
need to go to one of those in the future
really you want to go to dokomi next
year that's in germany germany far far
away
proud to be a kids be fans seeing your
performances today thank you
i'm so glad you guys were there to
support me
i was really proud of
kfp
during dokomi because uh
yeah
[Music]
because kfp was definitely representing
themselves
they were there
they were making an impression and it
was actually i think a good impression
yeah
definitely going next time thank you
you will not regret it
[Music]
good day hot wings congrats on your
dokomi segments you were amazing thank
you
i always love you singing thanks to
dominic for making it possible to send
more fan letters to you oh yeah
i didn't read for all of those yet
that's where i lost 70 i think it was 17
letters right seven zero
[Music]
that will take a while
that will take a while to get through
but it's definitely smarter than having
every single one of them send letters to
the company
and then having to wait for like half a
year for them to arrive
[Music]
speaking of printers guys
i got a printer scanner a
printer scanner copy a copy machine
and i i tried my best to set it up
but
i'm so pissed off
things never work for me
i set it up and it was supposed to be
[\h__\h] easy
and my pc finds the the printer as an
option it is there but it won't let me
scan
when i go to scanning
on the
on the pc
it says there is no scanner but it finds
the printer i don't get it what the [\h__\h]
i use the manual and i used youtube
videos i used everything
i have the proper drivers yeah
and i also tried to do it on the phone
because apparently you can do it on the
phone as well but it didn't work on the
phone either because you couldn't find
it at all on the phone
so annoying and like i understand that
simplicity
on modern products
make them look more modern but can you
please add more buttons and a proper
menu to the freaking printer because
there's like three buttons on this thing
and something that is supposedly a
screen that tells me absolutely nothing
on it
there's literally nothing i get out of
that no information that i get out of
that screen
that's as big as my thumb
so
great job on simplifying the printer's
design but like it does that i don't
know what to do with it
so i'm really disappointed because i i
want i need to use it for you know
filing my taxes and [\h__\h]
because i want to scan uh receipts
i want to scan receipt i did read the
manual and i watched a uh uh youtube
tutorial on how to use it as well
[Music]
oh man oversimplified tech is a pain it
really is what the hell
don't take away all my buttons
yeah
yeah i bet i bet all of you could make
it work and all of you could fix it
i bet you could
which leads me to another tech talk
um
but
[Music]
oh man
um
[Music]
this is a
very difficult
very difficult for me
um
they're very very difficult
how dumb wasn't that
[Music]
okay so remember yesterday
remember yesterday
[Music]
remember yesterday when i was
supposed to do the tails of our eyes
sponsor stream
and i woke up a few hours before it
and um
no it was not unplugged no
i woke up a few hours before
i tried to turn on my pc
and it didn't do anything it did not do
anything
so i was like what's going on
the first thing i did was check the
cables the connections
if they're properly plugged in
yes everything was fine
then uh what what did i do next i just
pushed push the power button a few more
times hoping that it would work
but no
nothing happened so
i was already panicking
next thing i did was at changing the the
the power outlet sockets
trying different sockets
no that was not the thing either
next thing i did was um
changing the cable the power cable
[Music]
nope
didn't work with a different power cable
either
and i also while doing all this i was
panicking in the chat
and also trying to contact my friends
and i
that i thought that could maybe help me
um
no the monitor no no no no no the pc
just didn't turn on at all like no fans
no noises at all it was not the monitors
here's uswitch you mean the
the zero and the one one no no that was
also on
all of it was on it was all fine i
checked all of it i checked so many
things
yes it was plugged in i already said
that
i'm not that stupid okay
supposedly
yeah the rgb lights were on so i was
like okay there should be power there
should be power because the rgb lights
are on
there is electricity
yeah so i did all these things okay
everything that i could think of at that
moment i also did that power cycle thing
like turning it off and then while it
was off
pushing the button
[Music]
for 30 seconds for example
but it didn't work either
so
um
i actually was able to get a friend over
to my place
to check it out
[Music]
and um
he arrived
pushed
the button
and it turned on
[Music]
uh
so many times and i was so confused i
was so angry and so confused i was
screaming and laughing and panicking and
we both which we both just
[Music]
a lot of times properly short time short
and long and then whatever
so many times it didn't work and then my
friend comes push the button and it
immediately works what the [\h__\h]
so i was like
after we calmed down a little bit
and the pc was turned on
i
i shut it down again
to test if it would probably work as
well again
and i pushed it
in front of
my friend's eyes
and it didn't turn on again
it didn't turn on again
and we looked at each other really okay
so i pushed again
and still didn't do it
um
and then he pushes it
and it turns on
so i put i turned it off again i turned
the pc off again for a second
time
and then
because we were like okay maybe i'm
really not pushing it hard enough
but that's like unbelievable
unbelievable no [\h__\h] way i pressed it
a million times at least one of those
times should have been strong enough to
turn it on
so i turned it off again a second time
for a third time the second time
and then
in front of my friend's eyes again
i pushed it
pretty strongly like like
my friend can uh
like
uh
i pushed pretty strong
and long till like two seconds
[Music]
yeah a test yes
a friend can attach to it
but it didn't turn on again
[Music]
and then i pressed again and then and
then it turned on
[Music]
so
um i felt absolutely stupid and [\h__\h]
and and stupid and uh useless and
stupid
i felt like
my body is
broken
i can
i should never touch computers again
and uh
[Music]
i don't even know
i i felt so stupid
i felt so stupid
i've never turned it up that was a
thought of mine as well
that was a father mine as well
i will just never turn off my pc ever
again
i like i was thinking my friend will
have to do some i like have to open up
the pc and do some complicated things
and all that
uh
but
yeah
my friend left after five minutes of
us laughing at myself
and yeah
my friend even left work early for me
but yeah it was fine it was home office
but still
[Laughter]
oh my god
also i want to um
no one said anything in the chat but i
still want to apologize for my words
choice of words right now
i immediately regret it um
that was
not a good choice avoid
[Music]
have said that
i don't like it
[Music]
very bad choice of words
but yeah um
i do want to say
that i am stupid
oh why why is it see the printer and my
pc and i always have these kind of
issues
i always have these kind of issues
and you know i just feel so helpless in
that situation because i'm here alone in
australia
and and like if if that was a day where
um you know
i wouldn't have a sponsored stream if it
was a stream that i could easily move or
easily cancel
i wouldn't have panicked so much but i
was really really really
i was so like i felt so helpless because
i was trying to troubleshoot also like
on on discord with my staff with my with
my managers
but like
there's not much you can do when it's
only via text
and
i just felt so helpless
[Music]
i hate technology
and i really wanted to do well with
the tips over eyes sponsorship so it
stressed me out so much and they're
panicked
i hate these kind of things
[Music]
thank you thank you for the red subject
thank you come send me now
[Music]
i'm stupid
oh
[Music]
i know i am i am stupid it's so stupid
i always need help from people and i
just
you know
like the friends who were like the
friend who was helping me was actually
like the boyfriend of my best friend
and um
i i often ask him for help and he's very
sweet like they're both very sweet about
it but i feel like i'm just
asking for your help so often
[Music]
okay that's too emotional about
i just
i think it's a mixture of feeling
so useless and helpless and also not
wanting to annoy my friends all the time
because i also
had to ask
to help me build my furniture and [\h__\h]
[Music]
they're super sweet about it but
it's these times when i feel so helpless
living alone and just
i wish my cats could build furniture for
me i wanna i wanna be more useful
[Music]
i feel so stupid
it just
it just made me feel even more stupid
that the moment my friends come my
friend comes in and pushes the [\h__\h]
button it works like what the [\h__\h]
i wasted your time i wasted like two
hours of your day
to press a [\h__\h] button
what the [\h__\h]
i'm crying
[Music]
so stupid okay can we win super chats i
need to finish these super chats
[Music]
foreign
when i was in japan i at least had my
manager genma
[Music]
who was who was also not like
not like
a really really tech savvy person who
could like
who knows everything about computers and
stuff but still it was weird like
whenever whenever gemma was there
things would work she would make them
work she would she would work on it and
then she would make it work
[Music]
she was always there to help and now i
don't have genma
[Music]
don't have anyone
it's okay
okay
yeah i mean like in person you know
you guys like without the chat and all
that if there was no pre-chat i would
have probably gone even crazier but
um
you know it's just way more way more
relieving to have someone come and look
at my pc in person because stuff like
that stuff like that
you can troubleshoot that over
text all you want but
there's
just cases where you need someone to
push the [\h__\h] button right
you guys couldn't push the button it had
to be it had to be someone who could
come here in person
apparently apparently for [\h__\h] sake
what the [\h__\h] man i'm so mad at myself
[Music]
now i got all that
no slime
stuck in my throat
a remote controlled rover
yeah my cats can post about power button
yeah maybe i should ask my cats to press
the power button for me
oh my god
okay i got it out of my system i think i
did
thank you guys
thank you
i know it's a really funny story so you
guys are allowed to laugh because it's
just really really stupid of me
really really stupid
[Music]
i
but at the same time i also feel
sad for for being useless oh well let's
continue reading
[Music]
and
it's just i tried i tried so many things
on my own
it's not like i didn't try pushing the
[\h__\h] buttons
i was doing that a million times
[Music]
oh man
but i guess i'm glad because i was
low-key scared that something bigger was
broken like the the ram or the
motherboard or anything
at least that's not the case right let's
see it positively
i would have gone [\h__\h] mad if this pc
was broken after less than a year using
it
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
oh man
judy thank you for the super chat
ah for the pinky
hey could they help but did i read this
one yeah i did i did looking forward to
i can't imagine the document panel
without your energy and stories and i
love how you made the crowd wave during
the cut organ yeah
i was actually given the opportunity to
do that again recently
at the the the convention
um where i was with ame and megacon
orlando
that was a that was so cool too
like
and i was so scared about about people
not coming
but the room was full it was packed
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay i was so relieved i was so relieved
but no i was just like like
[Music]
why why why why why would they want to
come see me
yeah
now i think i think the concern of
dokomi
was also reasonable because returners
are not such a huge thing at dukkum
germany just yet
and also
the tickets were already sold out when i
was announced so it's not like kfb was
able to store and document for me
because they couldn't even buy a ticket
that's why i was worried
if if there were still some tickets and
a lot more kfc people would have been
able to join but there were no tickets
so it was basically i had to rely on the
fact
on the hopes that the people who already
have saturday tickets that there would
be some people there
who are kfp fans
randomly you know
coincidentally coincidentally
[Music]
and thankfully there were a few people
yeah yeah
so
that's really cool
[Music]
yeah
so if there's a there's a difference
between like
goku me experience and magical
experience because
megacon is far far far away
in america
and it was fun it felt like i was like
overseas but in dokomi
it was like people spoke german with me
and
uh it was very very familiar because
i've been at dokomi before myself
privately so it just felt like home you
know
and being able to
meet people there
it was very respect both was really
special in a different way
okay i need to stop talking oh my god oh
my god
uh continuing the super chat from lftt
you were born to make people happy
singing and entertaining around the
world and i'm and i'm really proud to
support you i hope to be there one day i
hope so too i hope to see you at one of
these conventions one day
looking forward to it thank you for your
support is there any recording of mega
condo of uh the dokomi convention yes
because it was live broadcasted on
twitch for free
so it should be easy to get uh the vod
of that but for megacon
i don't even know like
i saw some people uploading some short
clips on twitter but i don't know if
that look if like recording um video
footage of that was even
allowed i think probably like short
clips are probably tolerable but i don't
i haven't heard of any
like
general rule
if it was if it was that i mean it would
definitely not be allowed to upload the
whole thing
somewhere that you filmed with your
phone
that is definitely not allowed because
that's why they didn't do a stream in
the first place because they wanted to
have it be a very very
exclusive
exclusive to the convention experience
so yeah
but i saw some short clips on twitter
and
[Applause]
[Music]
was fantastic seeing my oshie perform
for a live audience and nail it just
made me feel so proud and started to cry
ah thank you know this has been my dream
a dream of mine to see you performing on
the stage myself i can't wait to make
that a reality someday thank you i hope
whenever you get to see it in person i
hope we can improve the whole experience
even more because i mean
i was not exactly on the stage i was
floating above a stage i want to stand
on the stage
[Music]
this was already like quite an
accomplishment to me but i want to stand
on the stage and not float above it okay
we will make that work as well someday
floating on the stage is more powerful
that's kind of true yeah but yeah i want
the hologram concert thingy that they do
with uh
with hatsune miku and vocaloid um
[Music]
um
that is that is my goal my goal thank
you naveed
really happy to hear your excitement for
it really thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
foreign
um
a full body mask with costume as a
replacement
that sounds freaking hot
um
[Music]
yeah
that's a big goal too spx thank you for
the pinky that was so freaking amazing
potential seeing you perform live bro
cheers to my eyes you are amazing and
deserve the very best next time you
perform live at the con i'll make sure
to be there cheering as part of the
glossy skin too oh thank you i was so
surprised to see people with glow sticks
there uh
i was so happy oh my god that was one of
the things that made me like really
really really happy one of the things
that stood out to me were like some
people having glow sticks and i mean i
don't blame anyone who didn't have glow
sticks because i didn't think about it
either for some reason i didn't think
about a lot of things
yeah but the glow sticks made me so
happy
yeah
maybe one day we gotta have glow stick
merchandise because like for the whole
live concert until now they also have a
glow stick merchandise i should get a
haka nasi kiya specific glowstick oh
yeah um
yeah like a proper one you know the glow
sticks that you have to break in order
to make them
um
work for a few minutes but i want i want
one with batteries a king blade i think
they're called king blades i haven't
haven't used those in a long time so
the term i am not sure about the term of
it but i think they were called king
blades
[Music]
yeah yeah i have a kingwood
oh no we could make a wait you know
those little pendlets which are in like
a really fancy specific shape uh uh
we could make one in the shape shape of
my sword
wow and then we can make it light up
like except oh my god wait a second
[Music]
oh
can you imagine it like looking like
this but smaller and then lining up in
like turquoise at the top like having
different colors
all over
and then lining up in yellow in the
middle and then orange below and then
lining up in in red at the very bottom
and that no
at the very bottom should be like blue
but a light blue you know because dark
colors don't work with pen lights
obviously
wouldn't that be cool it's like a
lightsaber yeah christmas will actually
look like a tiny tiny maybe yeah it will
look like a dagger a dagger
a shiny dagger version of this
[Music]
little
dagger i'd buy it i'd buy two
but
but but please don't stab one another
with it we'll have to make the the the
top of it
very rounded so that people don't try to
stab one another
um
[Music]
okay some japanese people were saying
ken raito
for penn light but can ken k-e-n is a
a sword in japanese
can light a candlelight oh my god
[Music]
it could even be also 10 10 light
because tencho potential light 10 line
but i like the idea of can light because
i mean it is a sword it's supposed to
look like a sword yeah yeah yeah
ina
[Music]
let's do it
let's do it guys
let me put away my sword
[Music]
i came back with food
yum yum
[Music]
i want the sword to stay
oh well
sorry food it's full time now
uh
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you
thank you for the sweet message
looking for the top gun
mickey ryder i actually
i was i was like um
i didn't i
i think i messed up a few times singing
kita making writer cause i was so
nervous i literally forgot how to sing
it
i literally forgot the melody at some
parts and was like improvising it and
trying to stay professional and
and not show off my nervosity
i hope i was hoping you guys wouldn't
notice
um yeah
let's talk
[Music]
didn't notice you were nervous really
really
i was so nervous
wow
rocking
we're hawking
that's
that stage of your first live audience
convention concert i wish i could
have been there for the mohentas hen
authentic occasion it looks like it's so
much fun with you demanding every
chicken clap their effing hands you did
fantastic thank you
yeah i was i was trying a lot to animate
everyone
all the time it was a lot of fun
to get everyone to clap their effing
hands
yeah
thank you for the pinky i'm glad you
enjoyed it thank you for watching my
performance
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat hi
hot wings here some to treat yourself
agenda oh thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
i am glad uh janma made it uh safely
back home to japan
everything went well
i'm so glad they were able to be there
[Music]
the club staff members
my avatar is lagging really
thank you for the membership
[Music]
yo there's been a huge influx of korean
viewers so actually i've been planning
to do a korean durian do a lingo stream
next week
today
yeah i wonder if i should just do it
does anyone did anyone ever try do the
korean duolingo lessons does it teach
you the
the letters
in the beginning or do they expect you
to already know them
should i learn them beforehand before
doing the duolingo
it teaches you hunger
they review it
when i tried learning a little bit of
chinese on duolingo it was kind of like
they didn't really um
it didn't really do a good job on
teaching the symbols that well
they kind of expected you to already
know like a bunch for some reason it's
kind of weird
might be separate
uh
um
[Music]
hmm
next week
and next week
what you see
and i can't even tell you the time or
which day i'm doing it
uh please mark your calendars
on the
oh yeah i want to do it on monday
[Music]
who are you
monday monday
monday uh
what's the time zone
uh
it's gonna be uh
1 pm my time
that should be
like what uh
7 p.m in korea
but do they have jst
same time oh same then it's 8 p.m
8 p.m
next week okay good time for you isn't
it i think it would be a good time so i
am gonna do it at 1 pm my time ksc equal
jst
kiara standard time korean standard time
kim
[Music]
[Applause]
to take like a one hour break before the
minecraft stream
so
so i gotta speed up a little bit oh wait
the dokomi reading room is almost
finished
uh so yeah thank you td for the rest of
the time
and take its monkey dance [\h__\h] that was
it for the waiting room i'm so glad we
were able to read them afterwards sorry
it was very delayed
very sorry about that
and but
but
[Music]
i am done now and we will read the super
chats from an elephant really quickly
and