what
[Music]
come
oh
[Music]
for
okay for
[Music]
is
f
see
[Music]
Oh
yay wait did we start did we yay
W
yeah
yay welcome to
Eden welcome to Eden
Eternal I got oh my good gosh so pretty
wait have you found this well yeah yeah
I've been I've been hiding away though
where are you don't hide I don't know I
wonder I wonder where I am look at all
these KP oh my God thank you for the
gifts you guys have been sending by the
way I collected them all out of my these
are all the
gifts I look so cute I got a pop star
[Music]
outfit I'm trying to find you amongst
the frogs and the random races I think I
got some things double too I think I got
the the Scythe double and the key the
flame key I got double I'll give it away
oh maybe that's pretty cool
yeah I found no
doubles wait how do I know right
there how how does one oh here's ad I
have added you without your
permission without our permission
without the permission wait where's G oh
yeah I'm in the Middle where are you oh
I see you you're the short
you you're the one you're the one with
the gry cat what yeah I guess so so cute
I am sister Shori you must repent for
your sins where did you go I can't find
you anymore I'm I'm here I'm here invite
to party show me your C I am now in your
party there yay I you were absolved from
your sins and I can't seem to activate
any skills here I am absolved of my sins
you're
absolved you're absolved
I'm absolved three times I'm absolved of
my
[Music]
sins are you looking at the kitty cat
yeah all my attention is on the kitty
cat I'm lost again where's the beautiful
kitty cat oh it's it's right
here it is so cute the face it's grumpy
grumpy kitty so maybe you guys have
noticed that we're now not just gigy and
Wawa anymore but no she already called
wind of us playing Eden Eternal and you
like it too I hear yeah I do like it
this is how I met some of like my early
friends
oh only one remained don't drive over us
I'm going to sue
you okay sorry so sh also took took it
to took the the job upon herself to be
our healer right I will heal you from
your sins yay there are no sins I am
pure as it gets oh my God there's a Ms
above us
you how expensive was
that oh my God that's a big
Mount oh my God I want
that that is a large large Mount oh wow
that's pretty cool you know sometimes
people send me like tweets every once in
a while there's like a phoenix sighting
in the sky somehow have you seen one of
those before I don't know what what is
it fireworks or just some cloud
formations or whatever with the sun
setting and then they're like oh my God
I saw you oh my God you were seen in
like Mexico oh my God you were SE seen
here and
there no no no no no that was I don't
think I've seen it I want to see no
really everyone in want to see a phoenix
sighting maybe maybe I'll fly you want
to see a phoenix sighting I'll fly over
to you
yay can you can you like do delivery too
when you go over to us yeah can you drop
off some food while you're
here I would love some food
of the
fire some
chicken that would be
good okay so today we're going to grind
a little bit more but shielding is a
little bit uh below our level so I don't
know you you going to like I can just
try to un off your XP except like the
dungeon depending if it doesn't let me
go through we can do the your main story
Quest so we have I don't know what story
Quest I'm on
they want me to do the ancient Water
waste but I have to do that solo which
was like not a requirement in the but it
says solo but when we're in a party and
we join solo as well we're actually in
there together oh really oh that's
pretty that's pretty helpful very
convenient very misleading but very nice
well I got to go to the ancient
waterways I think that's like in the
swamp which I have forgotten where cuz I
can no longer teleport automatically oh
yeah
they take it away from you I know they
want you to pay $1 for it or something I
know oh my God not good $1 is not too
bad for in $1 for
one uh teleportation or for all
teleportation for all of them I'm not
sure oh well that's I mean
acceptable okay oh wait unlimited for a
week oh okay
and one request uh guys don't right
click follow me you'll always be like in
my screen covering up a
lot try to follow me manually okay give
me some
space
okay not not you girls I mean the the
kfp
oh there's a lot of them I met a kfp of
yours earlier they're like o grinding
off stream I
see and then they said blessed I knew
where you
[Applause]
[Music]
were they're observing our actions
okay
inventory in the swamp what's the swamp
region called uh I don't I don't
remember hold up where's a portal I do
not remember anything from here I don't
remember I think it's around yeah around
the corner outside yeah uh was oh you're
riding a huge bunny yeah I think Rainbow
Forest that sounds like a place that
would have a marsh in it rainbow rainbow
full Forest okay yeah and then I got to
go find the tassos channel tassos
channel okay so that's like at the top
right of the map just just right click
the wait do you have the quest now I
have the quest yeah okay yeah just let
let it lead you atically I got to defeat
Juan and
Angela okay
I you am warping to you once I get for
no I have to go walk to the air balloon
and find my way over I'm sorry to hear
that I know why do I use my
legs right I lost you oh it's just at
the top right um from the Rainbow Forest
or rainbow rainbow fall Forest oh there
so I'll just meet you guys there yeah
the pass
it
exists going in a
circle okay I think I where am I I'm
there uh are you hitting the outside
mobs
first oh I'm at the uh complete right
you're kind of close though if you press
M and then look for my big giant blue
ball then you should be able to find me
your big giant blue ball I see it you're
giant blue ball you got a blue B it's
the biggest ball yeah I only have one
ball though what is happening from here
you must be doing well
in November oh no I'm doing horrible
it's just I'm too strong yes the big
ball keeps growing and growing I know
it's going to keep growing until the end
of
it oh I look your alpaca it's all
Halloween is too yeah thank you love
alas yeah it's so cute I guess we just
wait for the Gia Meister now I'm on my
way I got lost cuz there's a mountain
can't believe there's a mountain let me
look at you let me look shooting yeah
yeah look at you I wish I could look at
you too but there's this guy in the
way what did I tell you guys about Tak
keeping some distance okay wow you're so
you're like a Christmas angel
actually am I I know if you're like the
angel you would put a top the tree just
like Spike you on top of it I love the
bunny the bunny thing is that paint with
it it was gifted to me oh not not that
bunny the bun the bunny is so large oh I
know the the bunny paintbrush right I
actually had this when it was first
released too now my account is gone
though and I also
have hey how long did you play back in
the day um I assume maybe like a year
from like when it started like the
release oh no I don't I don't know about
the release part but I I remember I
remember like certain events and like
World bosses and whatnot cute like they
have Halloween bosses and everyone has
to get together to kill it and it takes
a really really long
time nice so we're all experienced in
this game to an extent to some extent
yeah nice all right uh do you need to
get into the dungeon now uh is G here
I'm here she's okay you're just you're
just so short I can't find you she's
actually taller oh you're above me
you're sorry you're so
short I assume I assume I go here and
then solo and then you guys are good
yeah yeah yeah yeah we
just I I am in the solo experience oh
hey it does work I didn't know that
yeah oh W both of you guys have same
color Wings all right good
luck I We'll Kill Them All For You I
already forgot what my are for
shielding thank you oh crap I keep
accidentally typing in
chat let's let shielding bleach off of
the our exp at least I hope it works I
don't think we're too far level oh she's
pulling all again oh no she is one of
those people I'm pulling all of them T
she not even
maybe maybe you're not even a tank I
know but she is the the mob
killer she got some AOE I
know what a typical MMO move before you
die cuz you went ahead of the
Healer should let oh she's going ahead
of the Healer no no
cuar if you do no I feel like you do do
they give charms I feel like they might
give safety charms don't touch it don't
touch you me oh thank you thank you at
least someone has my
back don't worry I'm killing it so it
can't touch you in the future in in the
future thank you in the future I'm
looking out for your future interest oh
thank you can you also pay for my
college tuition then if you
were but you can't go very far okay I'll
miss you too much you have to St I have
to I have to travel remotely I see yeah
yeah you have to commute from home or I
won't pay for your your college wow what
a what a typical parrot you have to stay
home are you getting good exp oh I have
no idea honestly am I getting good XP
some going keep an eye on my my
percentage I'm still getting I don't
need
that and I wish you could pass instead
of greeting yeah cuz it feels so greedy
you can pass you just do the X oh yeah I
don't need the axe cuz I'm doing certain
things oh I am getting XP good my
inventory oh we're done wow that was
fast good
job nice I got to talk to
S God how do I get to
sib I like a son of a well son of in a
[\h__\h] son in son
in no what is he doing there how do I
get to S actually there you go I have
the left
I will
follow wait where did you go oh I'm I'm
outside I'm about to head to uh s look
for my big ass bunny yeah there's so
many shiny people but the bunny
definitely helps yeah it's oh my God it
has a cute little animation that hops oh
that's so cute a large cute bunny I know
it also takes large poops all right I'm
heading to S did you get that like did
you did you buy that or did somebody
give it to you oh no no I me spend on an
[Laughter]
MMO no it was it was gifted to me
although I did spend like once here
probably I was trying to get a
masquerade
outfit recently or in the past no no no
it was like in the past I don't know if
they have it at the
moment there's this really pretty masc I
lost you oh press M press um I'm heading
back to town really quick oh she went so
far already oh I'm hopping away I don't
know why you're your bunny disappeared
from our view yeah right it's a
camouflage bunny I was following the
bunny the bunny left us and now but it's
with you in
spirit I'm trying to find your blue ball
just just press them it's in
town oh you got there so fast
oh I'm
sorry is probably
fast did you find S I did yeah it's a
frog dude oh after that I don't know
what quest I have like what what quest I
should do I can go to goss mountains are
you guys there in like line are we I
think so I remember being gos Mountain
oh yeah go Mountain was one before Bel B
mhm okay well I I got to go head there
now if you don't mind unless you want to
do your Beluga stuff now I'm not sure
what the reir is no we can go with you
okay I'm going head to the gosland let's
where a there
teleportation gos
Mountain we about to
goss about to gos gosip gos about what
gossip goip gosip everything new me did
you see the new
members oh yeah yeah people said one of
them are is like my
sister it why uh the the green and the
black one I think it's a two-toned hair
probably
oh oh they're so
cute yeah I was I was so caught off
guard cuz I I literally did not see the
announcement oh the the announcement no
I I was the same I didn't know when they
were coming cuz I didn't even know that
there were any coming I didn't know that
it was like coming up at all because
they iame GTA related thing right after
it and I saw the GTA related thing but I
didn't see that like what but there was
also the problem that it's like it's in
Japanese and then you had to skim just
to find the English
part yeah yeah I was I was shocked when
I saw it I was like what what what what
you just scrolling Twitter then you see
it and you're like what's going on
I saw the the teaser yesterday with like
uh the regos members and then said
something about flow and I'm like what
oh yeah I have to admit Flo is a a weird
name to
say flow glow flow glow flow glow it's B
probably because their lyrics will be
flowing and they will be glowing on the
stage bars
bars maybe that's what it is then yeah
yeah regos felt a bit weird too at first
maybe but now it feels like oh and then
it's actually like devis it's devis
isn't it device instead of device I
thought they saw they call it as devast
though oh it's not device I don't know I
don't
know
it it it has to be is theice maybe I I
call it
devast I call it deis my bad that's my
bad you don't have to call things the
way they're intended to call just like
call G G it's a nickname yeah to come on
devis know just going to be like
David when I saw the what was it Tiger
Tiger girl yeah oh the she's wearing
like a docking pants sweater sweat
sweatpants
uhhuh amazing and gives me like want for
yourself no no not for myself but I I
love the the chill Vibe of wearing
sweatpants for your defold form but yeah
I was thinking oh my God that style was
what next to ban saai I don't know I
feel like there's a good Synergy there
and also yeah she looks really tall and
she's blonde and her her art style I
feel like we'll have good Synergy with
KY so I want those two to be next to
each
other and then she got the same kind of
eyes as l so I want her to be next to L
too so much good
Synergy yeah tiger and lion perfect for
those two tiger lion and then big
stat good combinations why are we here
are you do you have a quest the oh these
are my quest yeah I got to kill a bunch
of gorillas for no reason besides that
they are here the Wing gorillas I don't
even remember if I had a quest for
that I also these are wait how many
optional quests do you have these are
just like I think some this one's
required oh holy crap it's so bright why
is the Sun so bright
here the sun came out I know but that
was way too fast for the sun darn
deserts oh good God the
bloom when are they debuts they're
tonight right no on Sunday no I
[Music]
9 oh that makes sense a weekend yeah you
got to give them a few Twitter only days
where they're just chilling on
Twitter I will have to go translate what
they have
said they have I don't know what what
have they been saying what kind of
people are they I need to investigate as
well something in Japanese probably that
I cannot understand yeah I've been star
at them but I can't read their tweets
there's one person who spoken a bit of
English they said like I Google
translated This and like I should reply
too hey I wonder if anybody can speak
English from them that one girl
apparently
not I think Rika is like a a rare one
m I guess so yeah it's it's a rare thing
that's fine they can still learn English
or they can try their best with passion
English what if you just make them learn
Spanish someone's going to do we need
Spanish
speakers yeah bring them on actually is
it it must be really rare to have maybe
a Japanese person also speak Spanish
thinking about it cuz the vowel
pronunciations are really far
[Music]
away gorilla what the heck do I need to
kill
how did you manage to look like
that like
what there's just like big gorilla here
looks
like like not like the
other character that I've
seen
monke I feel so weird hearing the
screams of the
gorillas oh you oh you there now can I
click a I right that works ah you can
click on a point in the map and it will
move you there did you know that yeah oh
my
God it's
amazing it's been a while yeah it
has it's okay
it's I know it's also nice that they
lower the requirements for when you need
to like kill things I think back then
you had to kill 26 of
something oh yeah that I I I think I
remember that Stu
suffering they had to adjust this game
for the times you know that's true our
short attention span
exactly how far did you get into the
game by the way like was there a
particular map you
stopped uh I I just remember I was like
max level and all I was doing was like
raiding and and Guild Wars and stuff
like that PVC
wow yeah I was so addicted to all of
these D more once a new one came out I
just switched to the new one and then I
tried to R there as hard as I
could you abandon this one
huh that one bad well I didn't abandon
this one but you know think it abandoned
us yeah yeah yeah honestly it did it
freaking did did you ever play maple
[Music]
story should guys we should play maple
story I have never played story before
really really big event that's in 2
weeks and it's the best time to start
maple story so you want me to grind that
one now too on top
of it's a really big event what's the
what's the event though um it's like
their hyper burning event where uh for
until Level 250 you level basically
twice per level or like so it's like
plus two on top of the level so you go
in increments of Threes And then you
reach end game well not end game but mid
game faster oh are you TOA B right now
uh I have to turn into Quest but I'll
come back there so let me just turn in
everything I have cuz I cannot Auto
teleport okay
okay hear the little mashing of the
keyboard G are you doing Quest no I'm
just hitting things while where I'm
standing are you guys about to do a
dungeon for your
thing I don't know I don't have any
Quest right now at all oh
really you can um you can pick up your
quest or like some some side quest I
don't want to hold you guys
up I'm only doing W for you no no it's
okay it's okay cuz I'm doing like all
quests I can so I can level up faster oh
okay even the side quest the the ones oh
actually I found the main quest that I
didn't do yet
which Quest is that one a Roa 2 level 23
you H it's it is a it
is it's something with a dungeon oh oh
it's a dungeon Quest we can do that one
too what the heck why did I not do that
one
yet there we go W I am traveling across
the
land Isn't it nice I like traveling
across the land with my
Mountain it is until like everything
starts chasing you and then you die but
I don't think they do that here oh
healer so
squishy I know I'm squish
squish okay I'll wait by the dungeon I
suppose is it that same map yeah it's uh
at the top right of the map
road are you hitting me Oh I thought
that was a player that's an NPC no no
players can't hit you unless you duel
them I'm pretty sure yeah I know what
where did that come from ah here there's
another
person level me up I'm still not leveled
up I will come stand by the dungeon
2 okay
[Music]
welcome on my way speed level how do I
click
there oh are you
ATA oh okay I head to
aoda oh
aoda at least I hope I can I assume I
can did we not go into this dungeon
giggy last time we missed it I'm not
sure I think we missed it maybe that's
an optional
one it does say main quest but I don't
think you even have to do any of the
main quests anyway oh wow there's so
much like Lion King
here all right I am here do as you wish
I will try to
join
uh
this we enter a Solo solo dungeon I
guess so yeah Solo solo all right you
have the quest right uh I do not but I
will run it I am allowed to run it okay
oh I remember this I got the quest in
the
city I don't have the quest it's okay
though I'm just getting XP anyway I
think so so you're Roa
solo yeah Solo solo
okay wait is this is this again H where
I need to talk to someone first wait
wait wait wait I might have to talk to
someone outside first take your time
take your time oh I remember this place
oh yeah vaguely I think there's poison
in here maybe vaguely remember or maybe
I'm lying no there's no poison here this
I lied this was not the dungeon
oh GG's already starting what what a
trooper I cancel my cast I canceled my
cast no no it's okay you're going I can
I can my cast I'm back welcome
back all right go my tank I I'm
going the music in here is so cute what
the heck oh shot why do they want the
claric leave the cleric alone hitting
you I know I didn't even do anything why
are you
them I didn't do anything wrong I don't
know maybe you don't Agro standing too
close no you're standing too close no no
you just don't hit hard enough they
thought you were
pathetic I'm not pathetic no you're fine
G you act we need one more person to
join us and be the tank for us a real
tank I like this song
actually it sounds kind
of like nightmarish or Halloween is it's
cute why don't you like Halloween you I
love
Halloween ah good God leave me alone I
didn't do anything hit
harder okay I wanted to say I saw your
nun outfit oh yeah yeah thank you I'm GL
like it it was blinding my eyes I I
can't help it I'm just a ray of sunshine
it
was Sal your salvation has
come yes you will be absolved of your
sins from Sister
shiori yes uhoh I'm not absolving that
sin
though talk to sh ah oh there's
dinosaurus what kind of quest is this
NPC is behind
me oh crap you're far away well you
don't need healing right now
anyway put this dinosaur here I don't
know is it Go
B in her it's actually a cave Dragon
they're
different my bad it's not a dinosaur
it's drag yeah those are
extinct excitingly chicken
dinosaur
related one day we will get a
dinosaur in
Holo a real one that looks like a
dinosaur yeah and is a dinosaur it talks
like one too
yeah oh I'm in
okay I meant a grill a grill no no we
are getting a
dinosaur a real dinosaur and then and
then she'll let us like ride her so she
can be our Mount too yeah yeah yeah oh
and then she has stubby little
arms I can't wait for her dance practice
she'll be so cute oh my God on the big
stage and then she just she needs all
the space she can get or on us and then
she just eats the whole a because she's
so hungry oh my God I'm so
excited well technically she can eat
your kfp they look pretty
edible they do look tasty yeah tasty my
if I have to pick one to eat probably
them dragon that sounds like a such
name he's got a bow nice a good why did
he not use
it uh I'm a cleric build crap no leave
me alone I'm too too good for
this okay dang what is this thing
underground that doesn't look very holy
for sister shiori touch it touch
it corruption
Arc you cannot corrupt what is already
corrupted I thought you were a sister I
am a sister that doesn't mean I lead a
holy Chapel
what kind of Chapel is this I don't who
knows I think that's it for you guys
yeah is the Pierce guy outside no wait
the Pierce guy is it leaving me
there outside m not work
sometimes I like how this is a fantasy
setting and then there's just like these
meccas and these cars that go the the
desert yeah I mean the the the one like
each Dasha the the car doesn't really
fit in so well I think I know it must
have really good Wheels though to be
able to run or like in these spontaneous
areas
true oh I got to kill more dinosaurs
now not the
dinosaurs oh sorry the dragons actually
these are
Dres I'm just going to kill Drake I'm
sorry for anyone named Drake my
quest I can't get on my
Mount yeah you have to do it from your
inventory it's finicky so
evil it's evil Eternal I don't evil
Eternal I don't want any of these I'll
take
this achieve and accomplish chenana hero
nice but I guess cuz I did the dungeon
here no
nice
okay shiine are you doing a quest yeah I
got to kill this dude named
mathus what quest is that it's just uh
one of my main ones it's not a dungeon
though the fifth clue of the Lost
Civilization and then I probably have to
run the dungeon that we just did it's
why
I perfect I'm just assuming right now
that I will eventually have to do it
again no
problem I'll get another little small
Quest I think I still have a
couple all right I'm going to go be a
mage so I can feel
things are you switching to Mage now
yeah only so I kind of frustrating to
level like separately classes yeah it is
like I'm trying to kill things fast yeah
H got to love all these classes that's
why you always got to like go around
with a partner who brings you through
and fights everything for
you it could be us it could be us we'll
be that for
you I'm killing I'm killing Devils do
you need this oh I I need a rock claw
DRS now oh I need those too again okay
there you go you shall kill unquenched
first ooh so thirsty
huh my thirst can never be
quenched never one thirsty never ever
that's what nothing we can nothing we do
will quench The Thirst you have nothing
you can do dang what if I try really
hard to quench that thirst
M you got to try harder that's pathetic
talk it's not what if it's I will
I will yes okay I like the will that
dirt don't worry give it a try
then okay puts my leg up on the wall Noy
what flips her
[Music]
hair we're going to see some more weird
Fan Art
G I saw that the breast ass I saw I
saw it's beautiful it's so beautiful
it's beautiful you mean yeah
beautiful and then there's just half
invisible nonin in the background have
you see the it's like I consent and then
there's like is there someone who forgot
to ask I think I didn't see that that's
such a meme Lord let me find it I'll
send it to you
Quest done what are these alaka tokens
and why is this the first one I'm
getting what does alaka tokens do
collect 10 and trade them for an alpaka
mystery capsule wow you may have a
chance to win fabulous costumes oh
therea
heyo
casaa no way you could get that so
easily actually they were pretty lenient
with things uh at some point
[Music]
cuz they gave you free outfits I'm
pretty sure they just couldn't be
died uh H
yeah I wouldn't mind using my
[Music]
money Stopping You adult no honestly
just the payment option is stopping me
yeah it makes it so
difficult I remember when I was younger
um I think I also didn't have like
anything proper to pay so I went to the
store and bought the pay safe
cards aw with my little money I bought
like 5o five buck pay safe cards
and just got whatever I could get
there thank you thank
you uh
gorilla okay I have to do this one as a
single
player is it a dungeon I think so Shale
Cavern going to level up I'm going to
level up I'm going toel oh sh
c yeah you can you guys can
come it's called one of the shield
Cavern M on my
way I wonder if we can get a quest for
that too I already yeah probably I just
spammed all the quest
here wait let me finish this Quest I can
just run over
there run geky run with your Spot Run
spatu me and my
spu beautiful
Alpa uh where's
shielding I'm at sh Cavern aha
oops let me just uh redo my hot keys I
just changed into like a Bard here over
here oh but I don't have any b b CL
class skills I don't know
that's it I got nothing else how am I
supposed to kill things I have
arrived welcome a
chein c
Cavern a maybe I can't be a Bard yet I
got a grind someone kill things for me
I'm a Bard I sing okay okay okay I'm
killing thank you heill faster faster GG
as fast as I can you call that fast
that's pathetic I'm trying I'm trying
I'm
trying I want to unlock bar classes so I
can sing and be annoying B so cute
actually Barts are useful for like
hiding but they changed things I think
they changed it why so you could spam
this uh burn skill and it was instant so
what people would do is they would spam
it kite and everyone in the party would
help heal things I remember that yeah it
was so useful and then people would get
you to pay them so they could do it for
you oh really and then they took it out
yeah well they did a casting
speed that's evil will you
accept huh except what you got proposed
to look at the top oh no what I do is I
leave them hanging so no one else can
propose what you just leave it open well
yeah yeah because if I ask that someone
else my propos
right oh is that how it work that is
true but thank you for the proposal I
appreciate you thank you currently being
proposed to please wait I appreciate you
you're
[Music]
amazing okay I'm in the dungeon I'm
going okay I come
there let me let me switch to my cleric
as well I can't wait for Shaman I can
kind of be lazy as a
shaman chill Cavern
okay I'm here yay attack
attack this
one but it's cloth armor I didn't expect
this in the desert I guess I should
actually she rejected me let's
go actually we a fourth player to join
us you know do you know why we need a
fourth player to join us cuz when me and
marry then Shi will be like alone and
third Wheeling she needs the fourth
wheel no it's okay I can I can third
married why
why maybe they allow triangle marries
here in this game I I don't know about
that love is beautiful we need to get
married all of us oops see likes to
watch okay what if I just do like the I
make an alternate account I never use it
and I just propose to
myself online at the same time though
well no you can just make two accounts
yeah but you like on two different
locations I guess I don't think you can
send a proposal to someone who's offline
and then the other Oh you mean like uh
the same character an account I see yeah
yeah they're going to be like this isn't
how are you proposing to this offline
person are you sure you're proposing to
a real
person what if I just propos to a
bot you remember those Bots where you're
like uh you can buy for levels or
something I mean I don't I never saw
like where you can buy them but I saw
them running around and like Fly for Fun
in the beginner area running around do
you know f for fun I've heard of it
that's the one we can fly I think yeah
for fun the skateboard on the snowboard
skateboards those were so fun my
firste trickster oh yeah I never I never
I wanted to play it I never got like too
far though cuz I was a
neither yeah me too and I didn't
understand anything yeah say oh crap no
please I'm just a Healer I'm just a
Healer wor don't worry don't worry I'll
take care of him
shoot look at me look at me guys
oh good God why does he so into
me cat o I can use that yes take it take
it g did you just ran past the boss I
feel like you did that last time she did
she did you did the same thing before
only Kara went for it didn't even see
the boss you have an illness that's
called boss blindness I think she she's
too short to see things
Lon
yeah I did not call gig G but maybe I
should call her gigg gigg ooh what is
this we got to talk to Nica it has G
healing oh nice
Shing I will I will take whatever
wait a I need to I need to enter the
dungeon in multiplayer mode not solom Mo
what the heck we can do that too we can
do it too okay it's pretty fast fast
after all yeah let me just get out of
here but right now you you did it uh
like solo yeah yeah I had to do solo
okay we all do it h cuz yeah maybe you
can immediately accept the daily Quest
from the soul Guardian cuz the soul
Guardian gives you a daily quest to do
it in multiplayer mode oh is it the
assign notice
or oh yeah I guess it
is sh Cavern I the soul
[Music]
okay all right I accepted it multiplay
let's
go my
crap is that multiplayer like a little
harder or just like a little higher
up oh yeah it might be are they hurting
more yeah technically they should that's
why UHS
makes
sense yeah expect four people for this
yeah they're hurting
me well I hope you like
it I do and then I have a beautiful
angel who heals me right after yeah I'm
healing your
s now I missed the time of being a
Healer being being a Healer is so like
yeah it's not a grateful work I think
people are ungrateful usually usually I
really people were grateful and I could
I'm sure they were when they needed one
no one ever wanted to be the healer I
always wanted to be the healer that's
good I never wanted to take the the
sword into my hand and cut people's
throats and see their blood dripping I
didn't want to do that you know I wanted
something you want be like a
paladin yeah no not my kind of
thing if
anything ma then
magic yeah I like magic this time I'm
cut
throat this time I'm coming for blood we
[Music]
K I want to be damage
dealer I want to be yeah I like DPS too
I like being a hunter I think mhm mhm
what the in this game or in like any
kind of game uh usually I like being a
gunner in games
ohra k me I am I
Am GT you're taking too
[Music]
mucht uh thank
you help why are they hurting so much
now because it's multiplayer it's a
little different not a walk in the park
anymore
yeah it's only tank what you can get the
the those sounds like keep on sounding
like World of Warcraft um mlof to
me do you hear
it sometimes well that also sounded like
a
mer think you're too squishy G no no no
it's fine I have a beautiful healer you
can't be so cocky anymore now I know
I'll take
everyone
okay she's still she's still running so
fast as if to break her legs you see the
the boss now I see the boss now why' you
put him there he's
hiding maybe you will regret seeing it
soon
I know we're doing
good ow that is that magic circle on the
ground from you girls or from them no
it's from them whenever you see like
those dark circles just assume it's from
them it's been a while oh they Dro
better items and more items lots of
stuff wow nothing that I
need Goodbye Oh
wait
okay mhm mhm Gigi just runs
in it's not
bad I'm oh my good God all right I got
to focus on Kara a oh they're after me
now they're after me wor wor you might
want to go back for me oh good God oh
[\h__\h] they've respawned they've respawned
Kara I'm heading towards Kiara I'm
heading towards Kiara where's Kiara
where's Kiara here okay okay oh Jesus
Christ I need to kill myself don't die
don't get even more I'm no what it's
okay I can revive in the dungeon no I
forgot yeah I'm I'm somewhere else at
the walk back just run Kiara I'll heal
you after I heal myself just went back
to the entrance okay I'm
dying run run run where
is
y I'm on my way have you have you
learned your lesson ah lesson not
learned oh no K it's okay I'll I'll
revive you if you just want to chill on
the ground right there yeah but I don't
know if you can get here with old
enemies oh Jesus Christ I Jesus Christ I
cannot they're jumping after me they're
coming after me why they com
Happ and I also keep accidentally
texting in chat they ran to the last
person left in the dungeon who still
alive what'll it'll be me once I get
there I I can use my Revival item oh
Jesus Christ a Revival item why not it
doesn't revive you with the dungeon oh
it's better for like outside so don't XP
oh okay I'm in the cavern I I'm here I'm
here I'm here too I'm going back here
hold on hold on let's heal everyone
first I need
[Applause]
MP dad brats that's I should we should
just let her die no no no please
they get back here this instance young
woman there's a giant Guardian right
here M oh actually I think if you take
too long um moms also respawn yeah oh I
was like why are they behind
us well no that's uh that's because
we're doing a multiplayer session I
think recruiting
tank for future dungeons lft
owie
girl
G how could I heal you when you're not
like ow
owie she all right everyone stay still I
need to buff you constantly on
giggy always heal
her you get back here I can't heal you
if you keep running yeah same I can't
attack if you
keep you guys already have like a a heal
buff
anyway oh yeah those beautiful Puffs oh
yeah heart truth that's but you have to
stay close to
me no worries I I'm I'm not like I I
believe in Kiara it is G that I do not
believe
[Music]
in oh she's so squishy I think you're
too
squishy no I'm not I'm
not we need to put you on the Le ow ow
yeah or we just need to break your legs
how much HP do you have oh actually I
only have like a 100 more than you but
maybe maybe my defense is Oh no you're
your is probably
better it's just CU you're AGG gring
them and they constantly only hit me
maybe you should just take them one at a
time one at a time what are we slow
dungeon clearers see this is what I mean
by being a cleric is ungrateful
work we have we have a claring we can
take
more yeah I I would use that logic
normal yeah yeah
yeah he doesn't even get to attack kill
him kill him let's go let's go nice nice
[\h__\h] masing
[Music]
there we go nice good
job M crit magic uh I I just more
magic more
magic they're all like magic stuff oh
you can destroy this why would you
destroy this
thing maybe this one I don't know
what is destroying this D what is that I
don't know but you can hit it are you
destroying our exit
no what is that unchanged oh it's a
quest
item oh you can summon something ah one
of those just okay I
don't got to talk to
pierce Yay good job
I have so much crap in my
inventory yeah this dungeon really
shoved
garbage a level a different class right
now
because my my fif class is like maximum
exp but the other one's lagging behind
the main class is lagging behind yeah go
for whatever you wish for well how do
you what's the window again how to okay
okay um
[Music]
yeah I got a level bars too to 35 so I'm
a oh you have to become a bar now okay
yeah Earth shock
tornado I guess we can both heal
gigy
yay I don't
know you don't have to heal her you
could just let her suffer
[Music]
please
revive okay okay what's
next what's next is I got to sell all my
[\h__\h] I got to clear my
inventory
yeah maybe now I'll need to use my Mana
pots oh it's a one that's my
strongest I need to use the guitars
right my strong yeah you have
to
[Music]
uh Marshall handmade sacred 8009
865 wow it's golden
to so much crap in my
inventory
[Music]
same this is beautiful
this is
beautiful ah oh I have the Legacy loot
oh yeah uh she to find the Legacy things
did you figure out how to get those
things the the what I don't know what
that
is I don't remember how I got that Eva I
think giggy explained it to me um it's
the code the code you can put a code in
your cash shop and then they give you a
bunch of items I forgot what was Eden
500K
yeah I did see it I didn't actually
input the code though uh you should put
the code and it gives you a bunch of
level 30 stuff oh wow but we're not even
level 30 or at least I'm not oh you can
wear it it's just like item level 30 oh
okay I I shall look into it when I
can it's good stuff if you if you get it
too late then it might not be good
enough anymore oh how do you how do you
put the code in
go to the cash shop or click wherever
the cash shop is I don't even know where
it is oh yeah it is I and then reward
code and it should be in the cash up
inventory once you put it
in it just opened up uh the site can't
be reached oh there it is I had to
[Laughter]
reload what's the code again Eden
500k okay
yep it worked thank
you wear a necklace yet there we
go oh that one son of
Eternity because it's not Halloween
anymore Eden Moon you can also redeem
apparently
Global Eden moon going try
that I don't know what it does but it
gave something
acquired
finished what's
happening it oh I got a title Eternal
Guardian successfully
[Music]
read it gives a portable bang and a
noble pass for one
day wow
what what the Eden 500k oh Eden Moon
Eden Moon there's also a code yeah there
no codes
oh this is so cute thank you for the
gifts
everyone thank you Eden Moon Eden Moon
Yeah like you know
Moon you know how to spell Moon I
hope yeah wait sorry where do you put it
in uh so press I and then there's the
the code at the bottom it should do a
popup window and then you can go there
the
moon wow so many codes are there more
that we don't know about um they're
probably like temporary
though why are the merchant so far come
to
me oh Port
nice oh you're a youself dies
useless do that maybe this guy give me
your [\h__\h] M might use
this okay please one
day and I got
Merchant more
more more more more charms more amulet
so many I need to put them in my bank
[Music]
are you girl keeping the treasure map
pieces I have them them yeah I don't
know for what though I just have them
you can combine the treasure maps is all
I know I don't want them you hate
treasure yeah what it's a really good
treasure yeah I found it
wow requirements
dir perfume the scent lingers long after
it's wear leaves close your eyes and
you'll still smell the sweet fragrant
perfume waxing through the air what does
it do effect last 6 hours is this does
this make me irresistable will people
run after me more than they already do I
think you're already irresistible that's
why they're chasing you yeah imagine you
smell but if you smell stinky and people
still like really really like that
smell well some people might see ay
anyway just because it's too
intense I have to get Shaman to level 30
for
warlock oh Shaman is
fun can't wait to put totem
down okay I'm going to try to kill some
mobs here with B level
one let's see I got a sapling on my back
look it's a
sapling it's not bad at all oh thank you
for the however I must be
a must be a holy woman I feel like I'm
stronger than I my
Thief what I've learned to Ste V bomb
what class are you uh Bard oh oh well
Bard's not an attacker they're buffers
yeah but my attack is stronger like I'm
I'm clearing these mobs faster than with
my feet somehow [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] did I
dis
summon
strong already level eight level nine he
goes fast oh this is a
special special
dinosaur or he was a special
dinosaur but he's no longer
M he'll be in the history
books oh my god oh thank you for the XP
this is so helpful not just myself okay
I'm getting my levels too don't get and
I'm getting potions from you you are
such a gracious host I I'm just trying
to you know provide for our family yeah
it's a family once
again we're always a family so
beautiful family I think I can go to
Beluga Bay now yeah I have one main
quest there
oh e guitar sounds there's
also is this let me just finish the
quest here so I don't have to come back
I hate
deserts yeah they're not great looks
just like a desert ravenous Puma I wish
it was dessert appeared I want dessert
really bad I'm thinking about ordering
some coffee oh wait as a dessert isn't
that more like a drink I want a sweet
coffee and then it's like a dessert you
know uh why did you get isn't tiam Su
like a coffee cake yeah that's a coffee
dessert yeah I might just do that nice
tiis Su I want a tiis
su and you should get a
[Music]
tiu all right I want to level up my bar
too level me up everyone is leveling
up just
grinding what does this one do oh I
think this is
the that's a buff I
see don't don't attack my
healer attack attack I have a a non
Shield
heal oh don't don't attack them y be
nice Stone toot Puma Stone
Puma oh I need to get a a guitar to
attack oh I like those I've I've never
seen them before I only hear the legends
of the dino nuggies oh you need to get
some make you one yeah they're such fun
shapes to dip ah when you say you'll
make me one you just mean you're going
to
from I'll make you one from the freezer
okay I mean selfmade would probably not
turn out so well yeah they are
genetically engineered to taste so
good let me put my thank you where's my
Mount here I'm going
to
perhaps uh look for a quest instead of
mindlessly killing
monsters yeah
okay however I would also still
appreciate you mindlessly killing
monster I think that there is a benefit
into mindlessly yeah there's a benefit
for all of us yes that is just my
opinion well I it really helps the
family yeah if you you enjoy the family
then you won't get the EXP I will go to
Beluga B I will head there soon then for
I now have
Quest oh okay I'm out of question in
that area
Beluga Bay time I love Beluga
Bay Beluga where's the beluga
whale can you make your best whale
[Music]
[Laughter]
sound so
[Music]
peaceful it's also kind of like a howl
actually yeah but also whale sound also
kind of more like
cing cing money money money money into
the game credit card
swipe I don't like those whales those
aren't my whales um where's my healer
where's my healer I don't know where you
are my on my way on my way where where
the heck did you go why are you so
far I move the jellies I see I need to
talk to something some soul Guardian in
here always make sure to activate the
crystals the teleportation crystals oh
good PL good PL don't
forget uhoh my poor healers being
attacked what's the last game you spent
money on Fire Emblem
Heroes you mean money as in not just
buying the game but buying something in
the game yeah money
money might have been might have not
done that since Ark KN nights I don't
know oh you buy an ark Knights new
character I never play all the pretty
all the pretty
skins I talk to really good skins gotcha
P aren't they making like another game
yes for AR really I awaiting it eagerly
yeah they're doing like a 3D Ark knights
with mostly like it's very different
it's not a tower defense system anymore
but I'm so excited looks so good the
previews look so good I I need to
BL I want to play let's let's grind day
one together oh I am so in if we get
Herms oh hopefully they had like a demo
and I was like okay you know what we
don't have CS of the game but I'm just
going to try sign up for the demo anyway
um and I signed up this Tak because the
demo was like for influencers you know
oh yeah and and so you had to put in
like your socials and so on and only not
everybody got approv they approved me
and I was like jenma does this mean I
have terms for the game this is like
unusual like this is not how we normally
do it then I was unsure so I never ended
up
playing cuz yeah I didn't really it
wasn't official terms but but I mean
they kind of approved me so yeah they
went through that list of themselves no
I missed my chance I guess cuz I was I
wasn't too confident about it there's
there there're there yeah I've been
waiting for the Ian
release I don't know how much longer it
takes I've been really wanting another
gacha to get
into yeah I'm looking forward to all
these
games I need another star I don't think
I want to play Star rail there's too
much reading
I liked it though but there's so many
characters you have to get a lot my issu
is like I I keep up but then I stop
playing and then there's more characters
and I'm like who the heck is this
now yeah and then I feel like since it's
a strategy game they keep power creeping
the other
characters
a so people are like it's good to have
this character because it makes your
team better and now you're behind cuz
you stop
[Music]
Play N I just do like my basic
characters I haven't spent money on that
one you have it you're so good I
guess I played it when it was released
and then I was like how can I turn down
the double $100 pack and then I bought
it
who you always spend money on your
games I love spending money
you
are you're the most ideal player that's
we're hoping
for I a really good consumer I fall for
marketing tactics really easily and I'm
aware of it yeah do you fall for like
fish scams too or like click on this for
a
coupon no I don't I I fall for like
targeted advertising when you're like
scrolling your Twitter and then there's
like an ad and then you see it you're
like hey maybe maybe I do want
this pinky no those are usually like no
bad
quality weird weird but does it make you
happy that's the question doesn't make
me Happ doesn't make you happy GG do you
like spending money on these things I
don't know sometimes it makes me happy
and then sometimes it doesn't make me
happy oh well I think happy I see
depends on your chance F of Goa
yeah my quest is called scrub a dub duub
oh me too I have that oh someone help me
I agroed the big
crab H sorry I'm
busy both of the bars are like
nah
nah I do need to kill some Eagles soon
but that that can wait I do iron shell
Eagles yeah I'll help kill that now I'm
accepting everything first so I don't
have to like come back to
kill are you getting my kills right now
um I I guess
so I think so automatic
questing no finger lifted two more
Quest I have to kill a tide Rock Turtle
but I can't find one
all right I help kill Eagles actually
I'll kill the the shells stuff do you
have the Quest for
biotechnology H I can accept it oh yeah
accept all the quest so we can just do
it I I must go to accept it though but
first I must kill the the
Eagles it sucks that um you always have
to change your equipment when you change
certain classes
oh well at least you can always have the
the cloes on you just got to have the
set like
inert oh there's a set stuff oh just for
the clo clo clothing not for the weapons
that
sucks a little bit of a quality of
life
yes okay uh Iron Claw equ you shall be
that's probably why I never made like
alternate alternate accounts for these
things like this is my main I don't
really want to grind anymore yeah I
usually also never made any more
characters than my main except in World
of Warcraft because in World of Warcraft
after a certain level I was like cuz I
was still a tiny baby when I played
World of Warcraft I was like uh somehow
I can't get past level
42 and then I kept on making new
characters
and another one and another cuz I really
loved the character creation in world of
too I know it wasn't even that special
but for me that was like another way of
playing
Sims oh World of Warcraft no just yeah
the World of Warcraft character creation
me playing Sims oh I like the Sims I
hope the next one is a game uh well SS 5
is not happening anymore oh really yeah
they announced that they're they
canceling Sims 5 and just forever
continuing to add expansion packs to
Sims 4
a they're they're doing something else
they're making something else but it's
not Sims five yeah it sounds like like
they're making a
multiplayer they're making a movie yeah
making a movie too the community is a
little bit disappointed I also wanted
the Sims 5 well there's a there's an
Asian equivalent I don't remember called
I know what you mean I I'm interested in
playing that too but that's to me that's
just a different game I I want Sim 5
that's
true I want to be able to be a witch in
there oh yeah Eno Eno
yeah I need to play that I think
actually I think I did uh uh uh input
ter request oh
good I'm looking it
up it looks so good they just moved the
release to
when
when oh the graphics are
soting yeah it's like Korean is isn't it
like in terms of the models oh my
go enjoy I just want to make my anime
boys in
there 28th March oh
[Music]
I just I don't know I was reminded um
that
GTA is coming soon I thought it was like
5 years away or so oh already yeah the
new GTA is like spring 2025 or what was
it I never got into the GTA stuff that's
crazy I've almost I feel like it's been
in development so long that wait what
GTA 6 is it GTA 6 yeah it's faster than
the Y simulator but I feel like just
just a couple of months ago I was like
oh like looking at the announcement and
I'm like oh that's going to take like 5
years
but it probably took them a while I
think they just kept it hushed up okay
it's
fall2 but that's still like like only
like a little bit less is it is it fall
or is it uh wi now what would you say
okay then it's a year to
go they seem to be on track so I'm
excited GTA it's going to be good it's
going to be my first trip to Florida ooh
it's going to suck have you girls been
to Florida before Oh only once I just
hear a lot of Florida
news what I I have been once the Florida
news Florida
man how how is this just just don't go
when it's going to be like a
hurricane that's true it's very humid uh
yeah that's about
it nice beaches they have alligators if
you're into like is it more humid than
Japan I don't I want to say Japan just
kind of actually I don't know just
assume it sucks
no offense to anyone in
Florida oh I remember oh sh I'mma die
goblins I did not die oh some me thank
you I have the punish the Glutton Quest
[Music]
now shielding you're 25 you're like so
close to us now oh I guess so let's go
you're catching up I'm catching
up man I ordered like a a home grocery
service and and they didn't even have
most of the crap I wanted so I'm so
disappointed does that mean you still
have to go and get it kind of they only
gave me basic stuff like I asked for
grits like the things that were't Frozen
or or vegetables they they manag to get
me but everything else is healthy not so
much so lame I know
useless I know what's the point of
paying more to get it delivered if
you're not going to give me what I want
yeah they didn't even substitute for it
I want a freaking
broccoli you can't even substitute
broccoli where's my freaking broccoli
make your own broccoli you could like
grow it myself yeah grow it in winter is
that
possible rip out a tree and eat
it why you funat
complicated yeah probably
the Yum Yum trees as you like to say
when you feed it to a cute dog the Yum
Yum Tree yeah yum yum treat yum yum
trees oh Tre i i watch some some Samu
dog videos and when they feeds their
dogos their s dog uh broccoli then it's
called the yum yum
I
think very
sophisticated cuz dog likes Yum Yum Tree
I like yum yums I like Yum Yum Tree me
too where the hell are the Trappers
there you are reminds me of this this
has well the word Yum Yum Tree reminds
me of this Tick Tock cat who sucks on
its paws and then the owner calls it
paaw time
and Records the cat just sucking on its
paw and it gets like really anxious and
mad if um the owner doesn't like pick up
its legs and bring its paws to its mouth
so they need like an hour every day for
the cat to suck on its
paws cute that's so cute it sucks on his
paw so much the paws get all swollen
a that's a bit much yeah should
something else to suck
on what will it it want to suck on this
PA when my when my when my cats were
still babies when I first got them I
guess I got them like a little bit too
early cuz they still wanted to suck on
something and so they always suck on my
fingers it actually hurts a little
bit but was cute I had to let them do
it my cat they just sucked on each other
I had to get them to stop this kind of
g no it's not cute I don't know what
they were sucking on so I had to make
them stop don't make you so L it's
wholesome it's cute they're they're boy
cats I didn't want them to get infected
if their mouth Spin and like weird [\h__\h]
what do you mean what do you mean what
am I mean what do you
mean you're making so curs
Che
thing I don't know I don't know about
that were they sucking each other's Paws
no they weren sucking each other's Paws
I I was scared of what they were sucking
was the issue cuz they were looking for
teeth but they're boy cats they don't
have they don't have the girl
tee oh so they're just ding on each
other I think so they were looking for
milky but you could you did not get the
proper milky from
that
you yes yes
do they no longer do that yeah they
stopped they stopped they grew out of
that phase thankfully I have stopped
it my preventative
measures what if we had cats but the
cats were
[Laughter]
freaky I think if the cats and Shi are
freaky that's too much somebody needs to
be stopped She Stopped they're no longer
freaky yeah yeah they're wholesome cats
now good
good I took them to church and
everything they're absolved from their
sins cats and
church can you
imagine I used to make my profile
picture that it was like a a cat with a
nun
outfit
a wait you didn't you you're a cat owner
right yeah do you put your cat in
clothes
uh no they don't like it I did not teach
them young enough yeah no they don't
they don't want to be in closed
yeah they want to be free shouldn't be
in cloes with dogs I understand but cats
look leave them alone leave them alone
guys they should be in
clothes no no I will Force One into a
clothes no no
no no I tried to get some a Cirby hat
but they always fight
it cuz they don't want to be in close
that's true they need to cover
up this is a world where you have to
cover up or you will be seen as a
they're covered up they have they have
fur on them
naked no I will show you what's naked
isn't there that one naked cat like the
Egyptian
one oh yeah okay that one's
naked I think I think that cat it would
be cute if you would put a sweater on
that cat a self- knitted tiny sweater
that' be kind of cute but besides that
no so you can only dress up one kind of
cat yes the furry
kind the furry kind if the cat if the
cat wants to be dressed it okay like
dress it'll go to Amazon and buy clothes
from there for itself dress up he'll
have exactly no but like if you do it
since it was a kitten then it will
probably accept it and then whatever but
if it doesn't seem like it's enjoying it
then don't do it poor cats Man Poor
cats cats have a mind of their own and
they want to be naked Okay their mind is
telling them feel like some cats you
know are so naughty that they deserve to
be punished and wear clothes pigy I'm
starting to hate you
you're such a bird person I thought you
were going to call her a
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] head
emoji I said that because of you you're
not a cat person obviously you seem to
be a bird person yeah it's a bird
obviously it goes bark bark bark
yeah bird mhm I want a cat but I'm
afraid that I'm afraid I'm afraid to
don't get a cat I want a cat no no
please stay away from the cats I will
take the cats I'll will take all cats on
your radar get a cat and then you can
come over and take it and this is just
my bait to get you to come over to take
my
cat uh that's a weird strategy
honestly what would it work
[Music]
only under certain circumstances I think
oh that I don't I hope you don't enforce
them okay but what if it's just to come
over to see my cat to see your cat I've
heard that kind of uh pickup line before
fromon what oh who wants to come over
and see my cat yeah a well-known pickup
phrase um oh get here and there's no
cat no I don't know I don't know maybe
maybe there is a cat yeah in my case
there would be a cat for sure yes yes
who
knows well if you pay for the flight
ticket I would come over what happened
to your ability to just fly anywhere as
a phoenix car yeah I thought you're
going to drive by I can't I can no no
why not because hookie Papa put a belt
on me and it says in like handwritten on
a piece of paper to not unleash the true
powers of me she's offering to see
should show you her cat and you don't
even have the ability to go there
yourself nowadays we all have phones if
you really want to show me your cat you
can take a picture of the so-called cat
what if what if she doesn't have a phone
anymore it just died yeah I don't have
it's broken phone there there's it's a
broken phone no no that's impossible you
have a phone don't gas light
me bird person she could be like a flip
phone user yeah yeah it doesn't have
flip photo taking capability yeah yeah
the camera can also take pictures don't
gas like
me man I was I was uh thinking we were
going to do quests together today but uh
I I I need to stop done at this point
I'm just I'm doing a bunch of quest okay
you're hitting mon now though
yeah yeah we can 25 now do the dungeon
that's here if you get there what's the
dungeon called I think it's the level 27
main quest called Morty Kora M oh then
you better level me up to 27 have oh
okay yeah when you get there I guess
we'll re reunite yeah yeah I'm just
hitting monsters and leveling up my side
classes
put the morti Kora Quest what what level
would that be
27 oh okay so I'm I'm probably doing the
quests before that right
now go why is there so many quests
there's still like a lot of main quests
I didn't
do it's it's I wish in the in the when
you press l in the quest log thingy
where you see all of your quests that
you can have I wish it would
say I guess it does
[Laughter]
when you click on it I guess it does say
man that title I just collect all the
quest I will have to keep
grinding you're so thorough with it I
like with the the quest stuff oh that's
so I don't have to go back cuz you're
going to be like oh kill birds kill
birds
again well you know you don't have to do
uh them even if they tell you to go back
you don't have well it's more like the
the XP stuff I need it yeah I guess it's
more efficient than just killing mobs
yeah what am I doing here
again what a pig came out out of the N
bamboozle what am I doing
[Music]
here I think I have too many quests now
that they don't show up in like my easy
Quest
tracker too many quests yeah oh Ninja
Tur oh my God I watched your 3 model
yeah yeah and I saw your
your your my wings my my wings your
wings your
wings now it's so funny the the boob
coll
Collision when I saw crony having it
with her like official model I was like
man I wish my boobs would do that and
now my boobs do it it's
fun
nice you can't relate gigy can you I
can't but I can watch
you what if you get like a fake Pier so
you can pretend at least oh yeah I'll
get a fake Pier so I can pretend yeah I
don't know I find joy in watching kiaha
move her arm
and her
chest thank you I was really locked
in to that stream oh my god get you
you're kind of a firsty firsty girl it's
it's fun to watch is it not fun with no
one else having fun watch she just
studying she's trying to relate that's
why yeah that's what I'm here for to
it's for wholesome purposes of course
yes yes yeah now maybe maybe you can do
the same thing with other body parts I
don't know oh what body parts do shei
have that can
like yeah and her pigtails maybe but
it's not the same huh
yeah I guess someone's just going to let
me have to let me use theirs he don't
you have like a mascot that might have a
a little bit of fluff to it or something
can can we
growop a pair of chest something I don't
know either balls or or chesticles oh I
can I'll
ask okay it'll respond you asking the
gods above okay and then they'll let me
know it can happen or
not is it is it the girl or is it a boy
I I hope it's a boy it'll be funnier
that way poo is a boy yeah there you go
yeah I had a feeling and then it can
bounce its popo
[Laughter]
oh you know popo in in German is just
ass oh there you oh my God it's going to
be growing it from its backside yeah
what is
this B
serious I get that oh I think someone
probably killed
something the area boss I
guess oh my God everyone kill kill fast
these tribal Wizards destroy
them
Force Must Destroy must kill
did you prefer the black or the white
outfit
gigy I think I really like the white one
I like the white one too actually right
it's it's like pearles
pearles it wasn't in the music video but
now it is I like it really pretty it is
really
pretty I like the way I don't know the
way it contrasts with your body
it's just a really good
look I I agree honestly thank you wow
you girls would look good in it
too oh my God we can be backup dancers I
want to be the one that holds your
ass of course you want to be the one but
you know that backup
dancer she's she's not getting paid
she's paying me oh it's actually not
true okay I suppose I can
too if I must I I'll do it well you know
you're not just there for holding the
ass you have to learn to hold chodo
properly okay of holding the
ass that's part of choreography I'm
going to train through so hard just for
that b yeah I'm not easy the hold the
ass isn't that heavy oh there's more to
it there's more to
hold yeah it's probably a technique or
something I think that's what it
is you're not taking it seriously girls
I'll train I'll train for a year no it
is serious we're just thinking the
logistics of it yeah yeah what what are
you training on which ass are you
holding when you
train um more than one ass one a fake
one I see I going to need you to send me
a mold of your
asso have something realistic to use all
right I I'll try to figure out how to
take them yeah come be your Christmas
present well there are you know by mouse
pads I never made one but I was thinking
of uh like if anything maybe like an ass
mouse
pad I think good yeah that would
help well I'm not going to do it though
glue it to my wall a and then you just
stand at your wall five hours per day
hold yeah practicing how to hold it to
the Coro of course oh yeah
yeah no you should practice it with
something that can move around like
something more Dynamic like a like a
person oh wait wait what if you go to
park I don't know Higher
One someone to stand there so I
gra I'm sure you could find someone
maybe on like Craigs or something I was
going to say I don't think
so that's
dangerous yeah probably but it's worth
it for the training it's it's the
training flexible and hold your own ass
okay I will start doing
yoga why won't you hold Shan's ass she
needs to come over do you think she'll
fly here
no you have to pay me I'm not a phoenix
though I also have to run my my Chapel
my church sister Shori is not a sister
for a reason oh I have the the quest now
for the dungeon I'll stop doing things
I'll clean out my inventory what's the
quest called um it's called moror 2 main
but it seems like you have to do all of
the other main quests first for it I see
I am still not level 27 I am the young
one don't worry I'm still grinding
you're 26 let's go
yeah you must continue to kill things so
I can level up I'll kill things for you
thank
[Music]
you oh my God there's so many
quests beautiful I have the daughter and
the Pirate Man Quest
oh feel like I did that one too I need
to kill aul
enforcer kill him kill
him maybe not my B is already 24 I can
switch back to
Fe oh yeah right cuz
27 I can get up to next level
I'm on the next level what
is what you doing oh I have people oh I
leveled
up what what is
this
slam Max Max Max Max oh crap this is a
big Elite
group the class skill see are they when
I
switch answered my own
question beef
simulator
before beef simulator wait another one
no I mean I think a new one came out
this year and I I played it I think it
was I only played the first one how's
the second one it's good it's better
yeah I had a better experience I think
that's good I will look into it yeah go
feing yeah I like being the
Fe I like opening locks with my lock
pick did you like that Sky game yeah but
so in the game in in Fe Simulator 2 you
actually do end up in a jail and then
you have to break out of it and that was
always like the most riveting part of
that game just keep going back to jail
then to experience that favorite memory
of yours well it's huge and you can find
so many things there it's really good
oh check it out so I can see what the
criminals are doing I wish there was a
multiplayer version of
it oh I can do a class now that's that's
not one of the basic classes I can be a
knight
oo you do have like a an outfit that's
kind of like a kn a
paladin but probably That's Heavy Armor
what what what what weapon does
KN who the heck is
SLA Night level six how did I I just
switched
Quest I will grinding
you're grinding you're leveling me oh my
God level eight you I'm grinding I'm
grinding thank you thank you for the
grind no
problem I have so many quests I can now
turn
in let's go muchos
Experian atos am I doing okay see
see
Amigos who is ltia I don't see ltia
[Music]
here I'm I'm working I'm working on it I
just alaca coin Stones
Rising Marshall
out of my
inventory does a knight use a shield oh
I'm not dying right
now oh they didn't spawn oh I
see I am I am somewhat of a night myself
level 11 oh they te someone you die oh
you killed I see I thought it was like
an
NPC you always got to kill always think
of killing
first I got to wait for this questions
later exactly Lia hurry up and show
up oh contains witch do looks
boom boom
[Music]
boom
um things what do have Elegant increases
your evasion and your pee healing party
healing no you're double hit you're
healing
yeah each time you pee it heals your
soul
uhhuh P attack p
attack I think like single uh single
attack compared to AOE a player maybe
player not party a
personal
person okay there's a lot of Buffs
what's where where are the attacks
provoke in increases oh provoke good
yeah probably yeah I can I can get the
wait this is a tank class isn't it yeah
I think so can tank you can heal
yourself a
little oh yeah this is very much a tank
class yep
yep maybe if gii wanted to be a
tank do you want to be a tank
now nah no okay I don't want to be a
tank either but tank Tanki K got to be a
tank
[Music]
I'll I'll try to tank a little
bit little today at least only today but
my future is double wielding blade
dancer you know yeah yeah yeah yeah I
want to be
cool you are
cool you're the cooliest increases
malice caused by
attacks malice CA so just more aggro
stuff I guess
[Music]
oh oh hey I got the the moror thing now
although I I do need a little bit more
XP before like
27 okay can you not enter it early I I
don't know honestly I think you can as
long as you have the quest did we just
sink we're sing yeah
s all right I'm heading there and I'll
try to enter early
then such a beautiful moment what
perfect
[Music]
seink orange brain wave we should sink
up more often gy okay it has to start
with sinking another thing up first what
is
it oh our
period first we have to think that and
then we'll be completely in syn oh I
always skip my period though that's
going to be a problem you can skip it I
thought you only skip it when you're
like really stressed just so Buton to
skip it are you really stressed right
now yeah are you okay I mean I'm always
stressed but uh no no skip it in
different ways don't you know the ways a
do you know the way yes yeah I do not
know understand I just uh what is this I
just uh I just don't take a break you
know with no breaks yeah no break just
keep on taking I I don't know I talked
about this before in girls talk I'm
embarrassed talking about it like it's
okay it's okay well sh's viewers are
certainly used to this kind of talk I I
don't know about I guess they
are the grand I guess so huh novali this
is this girl's TI yeah it's like you
guys probably compare sizes We compare
periods I
guess no honestly I I never do that
but I don't know that's common it when I
meet a girl who doesn't know the way
then I like to share the way because
it's surprising how many girls are not
aware of the way I think I might know of
the way because someone has mentioned
this way yeah you just take you just
take it without taking a break you know
the I I I I I swear I I I I generally I
I the real
reason it's from my acne okay oh I cuz I
heard about that method I've never taken
that thing before
though well I take it from my acne for
many years now and and and so my doctor
said I I don't have to take the break if
I don't want to like every week in
around maybe it's good cuz normally you
take it for a few weeks and you take a
week break and then you take it again
and then you take a week break and then
the week break you get you
know but um I I don't want to you know I
don't want to I don't want to always be
bleeding so I say okay no I these are
the
hacks the cheat code girl hacks yeah and
for the girls out there you can also
take if you really don't want to get it
because you have a trip coming up you
can't take it too to try and Dodge it oh
what take what oh you know the your ways
oh yeah yeah yeah to try and get it to
skip so you don't get it while you go on
vacation
exactly yeah yeah nothing ruins the day
more than getting it yeah and also like
when I have like a lot of dance lessons
and stuff it's really
uncomfortable so I'd rather
just yeah always skip it you know yeah
anyway anyway anyway anyway I can go to
the dungeon which which one are we doing
single player yipp the one at the
end okay the moror I assume yes all
right I am inside my blue ball should oh
you're inside already yeah I'm inside oh
on my way
oh solo right yeah SOLO yeah I I did
solo oh oh sh
in hello oh wait are we both heal
healers right now oh no GG is a a bar
bar all
right where's a
b all right who am I I guess I'm
focusing on Kiara unless I take
everything watch this
[Music]
Tanki uh is there like a key on the
keyboard to Auto Select the next close a
tab is the best that you'll have I think
oh GG stop aggroing
everything myself now I can
down who you taking my br
why am I got got to pick up the
pace oh I didn't know this was a race
now why is it a race you got to pick up
the P I can't heal you from far away GG
don't worry don't worry I'm a bar I can
he myself you can't heal yourself enough
if you keep taking
everyone don't worry my God do not
worry okay be be
happy I'm happy look I have the whole
thing the whole I'm just going to let
her uh heal herself then I'm just going
to focus on
Kara not my problem yeah let her
suffer I can't move
anymore not I can't move with double you
ASD anymore oh why must to press
something weird oh maybe you're all t or
something
yeah oh that's a big circle I'm not
exiting this die
why do they all didn't they have more
voice lands for the enemies they all
make the same sounds they all I I don't
remember them having voices honestly
that is a new thing I like hearing the
guitar sound that's nice yeah here's a
song the song of GG's
people
yes I suppose too
weak you're not
weak I'm not doing my job properly no no
you're doing my my abilities now yeah
you're doing great so that's the person
pulling everything yeah I never I never
wanted to be and now you're kind of
suffering for it so now to heal
[Music]
you I've achieved nightm nightm night
Knighthood
yeah level 29
go like how he opens up more paths for
me uhoh they're helping
us aggro on
[Music]
me I don't know what all of these things
do we did it good job good job oh that's
better but I don't want it I don't
really want it we did it we did it and
now a dungeon off of our
books it only took 2
hours imagine what if what if next Ian
REO takes part in Eden Eternal that
would be fun although I think it's kind
of hard to
control
no is it is it rain until you Renee yeah
yeaha she started with members only and
I I I thought you know that would be
cool we would have a four people team
but the only problem is that we would
have like so many different time zones
then like the time that we're playing
now for her is middle of the night so I
don't know if that's going to work
out true that true that even though it
would be nice I mean if she wants to
join she's always
welcome of course I really can't move
I'm locked in you're locked in not in a
good way
negative pressing
buttons try Rel logging okay I'll try
switching channel I'm coming
back and there's so many stats I can't
keep track of what's good and what's not
right now you got to off of her I did I
did I did tell her like oh wait oh my
God you're playing e Eternal too oh my
god let's go please join
us yeah I don't know what to do with my
class skills should I just max them all
or is there an actual yeah I've been
maxing them all I think dep what you
want I still I still can't move only
move click so
[Music]
strange I guess we're done in Bela Bay
are
we maybe there
there's a a multiplayer version of the
dungeon if you want to do that is that
the
daily uh we for that oh no it's a main
yeah it's a
main okay let's do that architect
angle
[Music]
Fon so many
Quest oh now I have Crusade against one
of the Pirates
ah same same okay we're on the same
thing then yeah are we doing Crusade
against the Pirates or multiplayer talk
to Rafi to report your maybe after that
we do the dungeon again
weird just kill the pirate daily and the
Crusade against the Pirates too who is
hitting
me CB you must now become my
food it's
a never
mind oh oh I remember this place I used
to hang out here and just like hide in
here in the Fortress I would try to find
places where they would not bother me
and I'll be like he they do not care I
am here I am hidden
I'm
not so many self Buffs but barely any
like attacks oh yeah that's how B
works oh unless you're talking about
your the night oh I think I'll switch
back got
unlock I got like a lot unlock but it's
just Buffs Buffs Buffs Buffs
travel
to even that doesn't work anymore I
right could it's
left oh my God ever LaVine is in this
Camp wow
autograph
yeah AF she's a pirate
now that makes sense makes sense yeah
with the punk rock VI
yeah
F it's already like November and
Christmas is soon and the year is over
soon it's crazy I I like the end of the
year stuff I hate the beginning of the
year though it's boring
boring yeah like there's something
interesting in January you get maybe
like what Valentine's and February
I don't know I like the chill Ms yeah in
the beginning of the year feels like
okay we have a whole year ahead of us so
much time do but then there's taxes I
have to prepare my taxes
immediately all the time doesn't matter
when but yeah end of the year stresses
me out cuz it's like where the hell did
the time
go I thought I had more
time but don't like it don't like
it
[Music]
Max oh I don't want that anyway
okay huh the vile shark killer
o vile shark
Mage where's the
killer oh my mes are being taken care of
it
seems where are they
here I'm back I'm beeping
again
welcome the wrong weapon though but
whatever I'm appil oh my
God hey maybe she'll make a new song
called skater girl
want to be your girlfriend no way no way
you need a new one oh defeat defeat oh
somebody's doing everything for me kill
kill back to talk to
abine I need to kill a doctor and a
fighter
okay if I I I see them I'm killing giggy
has accepted your
question yeah think we're sharing
okay did you get those uh I assume I am
getting
something I need I need some FEPS to be
killed okay on my way I'm killing good
at killing I'm also
here punch pump
kapow oh already finished collect por
blueprint from gilberd
gilberd G gilber
good feel like my game is so bugged out
I can't do things properly anymore
what's the the bugy
part uh WD doesn't work anymore and uh
clicking on the quest to move towards
the thing doesn't work anymore sounds
pretty
bugged now
move in the middle this no longer bug
now uh no W wsd still work my keyboard
language no should be fine I change to
German no it still doesn't work I need
to kill more doctors you save lives I
take it away
BR happened to you I just mooved from
the
map uh
what what do you mean move
in from what do you
mean mov in the
map you mean click on the map doesn't do
anything on me
that didn't do anything for me
either it's okay all right do I can
accept that's what you get for studying
medicine gigy Moody that sabotage the
evil schemes of v shark saving Beluga
Harbor from these scurvy
villains hero what are you up to all on
your
own walking all the way back
I got to kill more thieves man how much
blood does uh
spill better know it seems I have
reached a a a place where the quest
items rewards are getting better than
the Legacy things so now I have to B and
actually exchange my armor soon I think
that I redeemed the Legacy and then did
not use it
yeah I told you it would be too late if
you wait too long that's true oh you got
to go back to
aine oh there's so much walking oh
there's another dungeon so much flying
oh oh it's probably the pirate one that
one's kind of long I think ooh I
remember that
oh who is
Gilbert Gilbert what you got oh shoot
you're someone I got to
kill remember killing him died too fast
I
guess do I have spamming number
two oh yeah it's G the step Bon then
I'll keep it for a while
longer Good Times set yeah man I hate
the manual Quest it's like I have to
combine something I have to leave this
map just to do it you can't just
teleport me
there uh you have one of those now yeah
I got to do like um combine this with a
formula to make a stone and then you
summon something and you kill them and
then you got to report to someone that's
a video
game okay I'm at the dungeon I shall
await you I will begin killing mobs
you're here you know you can teleport
everyone as the the
Mage oh yeah oh yeah let me just turn
this in really quick would you like me
to teleport you over here they make they
make um the portals don't
they do they make oh yeah yeah they do
well they just teleport everyone in
[Music]
general I
remember you remember you remember I
remember the
20 what do you remember
the
TW crazy I was crazy
once I don't remember do you don't
remember you remember I don't remember
you need a remember remember it hurts
you don't remember I'm not dueling
you oh you have
mercy yes I don't want to kill your kfp
so I get rejected their dual requests
cuz I I can't kill them um this
is I would like to be teleported to the
dungeon when possibly
yes once once I
okay let me walk over
there I will bring you right to the
entrance thank you it's so finicky when
I try to get there and like the button
doesn't go like why can't I just auto
travel here
no okay okay I'm summoning you I'm
summoning you all right make sure to
link your soul oh god oh you L you L
with the wrong
one okay I did not want this I haven't
asked for
this okay okay let me let me walk back
okay I'll I'll
faed you forgot your soul don't ever try
to be a mage ever
again I I'll I wait wait I I I can atone
for
this why is I'm not walking back I had
that last second
[Laughter]
warning it just happened so
quickly did it
did why did you do it a little funny cuz
mes are supposed to be smart with their
intelligence I just got so excited that
I was going to use it g uses one brain
cell for whatever class she chooses to
use it's her only killing and nothing
else well a nice little trip into a
different climate but I'm all back what
a nice trip why this Happ how do I get
down there
uh you have to get for the whole Camp
kind of but uh if you just click on the
quest talk to UL or so then it will oh
make you move there anyway I have I have
so many quests here I have to go to my
L stop stop okay okay stop don't worry
guys just just stay at beluca Bay Town
I'll warp you I'll warp you there I'll
walk I'll I'll I'm in the dungeon don't
warp me it's it's the vile shark main
dungeon right maybe you can't even yeah
yeah that's the dungeon maybe you can't
warp me anyway cuz I'm in here it's
leading me to somewhere else I don't
know where I'm going why is it leading
you I just watched you pass me I know
epic music it's oh it's taking me to
Garrison Captain straw maybe I got to
talk to him
first Captain St what do you want me to
do how you at
[Music]
I need I need to stop taking quests okay
just take me there so I can kill
things okay okay okay don't worry I'm
going to link my soul and then I will
spawn you okay and then I will probably
have to do this at some point again
[Music]
okay okay it's okay you leaked your soul
you won't mess it up yeah are you ready
are you ready okay okay it's okay good J
job you did it you did it we did it we
did it are you in front of the dungeon
yeah get in here now okay is this solo
yeah s
player but solo means something else in
our books
oh time to let Chi tank everything
together wait is even tanking as a mage
you crazy crazy land you can do
everything you set your mind to what is
this Mages are
sque yeah they
are uh uh whatever don't
want okay p p pum
I remember so
well yeah this one the more the free
rooms are still over there there's like
um different holes in the
wall it's a Pirate
Cave I remember
that M coming
back I remember running this dungeon a
lot I think this is the first five
player dungeon actually really yeah
you're going to have five PE
here what was your favorite dungeon I
don't know I'm I like the the malice one
and then the for the world I like the
the world of the witchery stuff I don't
remember those
names it's not the actual name but
there's malice Palace and then there's
the Witch level I I know that um I think
like when you in aen uh and then you go
up to that search building thingy
there's a like a raid or so dungeon that
you can teleport yourself too and I did
that so many times I think because the
equipment that you could get there was
really good uhhuh uh and we wiped so
many times there too oh but that was
that was a good one it was like a palace
looking place with like big
white uh walls and water and I need to
get there we to get there so we can
remind oh I think I know maybe what
you're talking about
yeah what kind
of happening yeah yeah yeah yeah it was
like like somewhere in the high
level yeah it was it we'll be getting
there mhm we'll get there I mean we're
only level 28 now but we'll get there
yeah we're going to get there soon we
level so quick
yeah I know compared to the old stuff
what did we start off with today wasn't
it 25 well I was at 15 for me but we
leveled some classes up all of us yeah
that's something to be proud
of so one day when we're more high level
and and we need to do like Dungeons that
are like that aren't doable with of just
us freedom we'll get some to help us
some high level people
yeah they're going to drag us through
the
dungeons make it easy for
us I still can't believe we're going in
without like a tank technically it's
okay it's Soo it's solo that's you
that's you if you do this in multiplayer
I think it might be
screwed yeah might be rough
very
screwed many
ring I need to clean my inventory at
some
point oh wait leave dungeon why would we
leave dungeon done I haven't done the
things that I need to do I don't even
know what I'm doing in here where's axe
Moss where is Kar okay I guess we got to
look for them no yeah they're in the
rooms on the bottom of the map I'm
killing everything
oh I think it's if you like screw it up
maybe I don't know or if you can't do
the rest of the
dungeon I got another question no
there's way more mobs here still oh God
do I have a Healer here way too many St
I'm here uh hold
up uh wait am am I following GG where
are
you oh you separated you separated are
you not in the dungeon anymore I am St
I'm in the dungeon oh good God why did
you guys separate I don't know man I GG
go go to where kiar is if you can find
her you guys separated a
little K just went back to us if you
can uh I'm fine uh I'm fine things have
calmed
down little
bit all right we should not get a split
up MPC over
I was almost at uh who do I choose to
save situation
here
away okay you're you're there um we're
like around here where uh you're near
this
section did you go past this person no
there you are
can't there you
go I can't wait for group healing I
think I have to be level 30 for it oh
hell
yeah
gring
it okay here should be one of the actual
did you girls already defeat back no I
we haven't been here maybe she has to
spawn if you do a certain
thing yeah where are they they should be
here right
here kill
more let's just let's just kill some
more yeah we just have to kill the whole
dungeon you need to kill all the humanid
monsters to uh spawn them
okay in a big circle what haven't we
killed we've been here each other I must
kill all the humans in this dungeon oh
no about here to the left should have
created
character all
right I'm going to work isn't there
something at the pier that we didn't
kill cuz just like a skull icon there I
will go
oh we can't go there
anyway have to oh here you go there's
this one guy uh really cuz of that one
guy no okay it's not just one guy
there's a few more okay well let's not
split up almost got one
guy I want to be tanked
now T tanking I'm
tanking okay
oh GG there's things down here I feel
like a
babysitter there's things down here oh
there's there is there a boss there oh
yeah don't don't hit anything yet I'm
healing GG over here okay I'm you can
just wait
there that's a boss you shall
die rally The Troop oh he's dying so
fast oh no that's good
now
fell now we can kill the other guy guess
you should knad on that
what did you greed on it you should
read I think you got it did you get it I
got it the book for cleric that's for
Illusionist
ohis are for cleric staffs are for the
Wizards and Illusionist is a
book has the other boss spawned
now
no something
again where are they I'm going to sort
out my stuff so don't die while I'm busy
it's okay okay I still hear it's
probably just like a few mobs
somewhere totally
doable here
oh I don't yeah are you looking
too are you looking the mob I'm looking
I don't want to do this right
here where is
it a main quest daily Quest there's so
much freaking quests I should not have
taken so
much there's 200 fre Goa draws what
where how do I TR this
one really 2003 go
[Music]
draw there any
on
no that was an
event what do you mean in the in the few
days that we weren't playing there was a
200 free gacha draws event
oh wow is that why you guys get got so
oh I found the group I found the group
of enemies
yay all right I guess we head there
don't start the boss without me though
no you don't even have to go here
they're almost dead okay we still have
to find a
boss oh right I I know oh yeah he
spawned he's finally spawned okay on my
way at least he should be yeah he's
here I know now why does look go why
does the dungeon stay in my memory so
much because in order to finish it you
really have to clear the whole
dungeon very
thorough it's also a kind of a big
dungeon
yeah yay we did it nice
Yoo uh you can teleport us out Chi now
that we're done I mean they is right
there too I think we to talk to the guy
in here okay mhm running towards
him oh yeah underc B
shark I don't have a question for you
they killed Charles oh is that the guy
we
killed is it I don't know who's
Charles oh it is it's the guy we killed
up here so we're we're done then well
you guys are done we have to kill
Charles again cuz we didn't get the
credit for it oh what so you have to do
the D it
again to reset it and kill Charles oh
all right teleport us out of here then
so dumb that's so dumb they should like
oh I can't use it inside a dungeon you
must you can't what's the point of
that all right time to head back out do
we reenter yeah how do we re this
dungeon uh there's an option when you
click on yourself at the top left I
think oh reset okay hold to Dam
Shield you know your way around this
game uh only only somewhat oh but hold
up who's this guy I need to talk to
someone really quick you guys can
enter reset it because of uh still had
players in it I'm I already went in but
I'm coming back out okay I need to talk
to a
LaVine has been
reset hello AEL why do why do you what
you have to talk to AEL now oh that's
cuz I I didn't do things in order now
now I can do it again oh let's go okay
we only have to kill
Charles we could just do that and then
teleport out with no you got to kill
anything else for
me okay we'll do it for you okay now I
just talk to oal or
whatever yeah he's inside the dungeon
all right oh you haven't done the
dungeon oh shoot I was about to go in
oopsies all right tank away oh already
okay so we should kill Charles last then
if you have to do the thing oh you have
to kill everyone to summon him
anyway no we killed
him um he was just there oh and then we
had to kill him for the
quest I don't even remember him what
does he look like I thought he look like
a
bear oh he's here
is ah kill the jellyfish to summon
Charles oh
let's not kill the jellyfish then I'll
kill them
last oh I'm
lagging I like how I can just chill a
little honestly when I'm like playing I
just stare at your health same same I
just always have
cat and just yeah it's so chill follow t
heal tank that's all you got to
do B tank B oh that looks like a fancy
sword that does look like a good one
good that I got
it is it
good kill oh it's good better than the
Legacy
sword oh to low levels
it's so weird when the music just stops
and silence now music yeah where's my
looping
bgm need a little bit
better oh another fancy sword nice there
oh but this
one think it's S as good as the other
one that I got but now I got both dual
wielding one day
level
30 I'll I'll turn back into Bard for a
little bit
okay
okay but I won't pretend that I'm a
Healer uh don't you have to be out of
combat to change I
okay I I got the the tiny time window of
not being in
combat yeah
[Music]
g cute
kid once again you must
die your screams feel his blood lust 35
well got to catch up ooh not IAL
chart I need on this actually in what
what is that anyway it's supposed to be
for
okay have we done the two guys before I
got do AAS oh
okay whoever that
is if that's the person that we were
trying to summon last time so hopefully
he summoned
I I thought we avoided he show on the
map but he doesn't show on the map so
he's not summoned
mhm okay I'll run around and see all
right these people my WD works again hey
nice I wonder what the issue was though
don't know
either maybe it was a trial I have to go
through the trial of losing your
wda yeah
maybe it was the class change that
somehow changed
something learn skill Burning
metal oh
yeah hopefully Charles isn't here he's
not in here right he's not thank God
kill the small on anyway
first uhoh something thans after
me I will save you hand off of our
nun yeah I'm having none of confess
something well he can confess the [\h__\h]
off oh crap I am
stunned wow our heal is so strong he SP
sassy I see him
oh yes indeed you do oops he is he is
here with us
oh I see I
see all the way around we go why do I
keep getting stuck on
this Wawa needs to be the one awkward
silence with the bgm keeping is
back oh it's starting again I need to
create a town oh we can create a guild
town now cuz we're level three okay well
yeah you really shouldn't have given me
leader because I'm not online as often
as you guys
and I can't be bothered with that
[\h__\h] but I shall be vice
leader gy do you want to be leader
n HED
but don't worry girl guys I will I will
transfer at the end of the
stream maybe always when I stream you
can transfer it back to me and when I'm
offline I'll transfer it back to you oh
but that requires some being like active
every single time too they are they are
okay they're
committed is it child's
time I got to talk to ol still first
okay yeah don't
die easy easy I'm a bar
too there are a few addicted chickens
I've noticed I'm happy for you I'm happy
I give this gift to you yeah the gift of
mmpg
addiction okay she don't need this back
noise
y your first ever RPG oh my God
what I'm taking your
mmpg uhoh uh let flirting kill it kill
this pig that's after
me oh I'm killing thank you thank you oh
crap I think I should do more damage I
don't know my weapon
virginity uh your mmrpg virginity you're
taking that from them yeah she already
did already did my God
unfortunately I can't take your SE
unfortun what was your first uh MMO RPG
for GG maple story I see for yours is
like um mine one probably World of
Warcraft if we don't count like what was
it Toontown or something like Toontown
doesn't count Toontown should count
though it was Tech count I don't know
what the hell was going on count
everyone first I don't even know if I
was playing the game
[Music]
accurately I don't think I was either I
was too young to understand what was
going on all I know pie yeah and fishing
and trolley I don't think that was I
don't remember the Charlie one I think I
ran out of pie so I summoned everyone on
my friends list that I didn't know to
kill one thing from
me yeah World of Warcraft is probably
the the first proper one which is a
great one to start off
with and I played it with my whole
family a my mommy my brother they played
with you that's nice hard for the whole
family yeah instead of playing uh vage
like
monopo you played MMOs yeah it's fun
because like whenever I would visit with
my brother we whenever we would visit my
father back in the day cuz we was like
separated as families you know there we
would play actual board games then I
come back to my home and there we play
mm
P the
contrast who's Dominic he's not in here
is he when I click on it uh I think
might be outside of the D
yeah
leaving am I walking to
okay okay I'm also
out oh my Mount again I will go out then
yeah sh it's over it's over sh
I will have to do this again
though I will gr away
my
yeah no it's okay it's okay no it's okay
it's okay I had to reach level 29
anyway we can kill Charles no it's okay
I'll kill him I'll kill him just try
okay maybe you can solo Charles yeah
I'll be able to do it it's okay it'll be
a try too much [\h__\h] in my
stuff why can't I sell [\h__\h] why not
yeah that
dungeon quite long dungeon it's not
really well
organized
yeah delivering this
leer ooh an axe US is an Al probably
tank
Oh I thought you said I I'll probably
tank no no no the axes are useful tanks
I think
so can probably just throw it
away I'm
sailing sailing sailing all my crap oh
and I have so much th too and I don't
know what to do with them I think I'm
pathing to the level 29
quest uh explore Wetlands yeah same
let are we going to different area I
think so I'm excited which one is it
what have we been there
already I want to see a new
one what's the next area anyway Wetland
I remember this
area oh I think that's the place I like
with the dungeon got to go kill things
here yeah
oh this one oh my
God core memories are being unlocked
again
a I remember just like like I I never
really had a a group early in this game
like running through all the areas
together from I soloed like everything
kind of chill it's a different
experience mhm I think back then you had
to party up until like they added the
solo
yeah and then for the dung because I
didn't I didn't have anybody generally I
just type in party chat looking for
group for this
dungeon like no one really wanted you
unless you were a Healer or a tank DPS
was so common yeah it's true there was
an oversaturation of certain classes for
sure
yeah tanks are really popular
I mean it makes sense no one wants to be
tank yeah why I think it's because it's
like it's the attention on
you like you is real skills maybe it
wasn't as cool as D and know for the
Healer like everyone has to rely on you
but if you you can't heal enough or if
you're like too op is like well I'm
sorry are you guys don't attack my
enemies first
okay rid of all these items unless your
name is be yeah
yeah back
off I already did
that happy there are happy
alaka uh
NPC why did they happy
a mystery capsule sh oh and it has like
dying head dying Oh I thought I said
someone was dying no no oh my God my
inventory is so full yeah did you get
expanded
inventory yeah quite a
bit oh wow
M I need more food
chest give me your
[Music]
food collect full water
bottles I have so many quests I I'm
going to leave like the old ones like
this one I need that yeah scy items
can't be sold got
a what a
waste I hate the ones oh they're walking
there
I'll keep this
one oh people are saying you can archive
them oh yeah yeah where does it go in an
archive it's like um like an achievement
system or a would
know where is the archive sh is it your
trash can press B and then there's a
yellow icon that's called archive at
like below with all the other other
icons
ah
oh yeah I have some memory of this
interesting okay I need to sounds
useless what is this cash up
items what this the main
last is this just like a
set
last but but oh no it is like something
like cash up items but need more alpaca
coins I only have 10 I can get the
copper mystery capsule I'll get
one I'm opening alpaka gotcha o maybe
you can do like a whole stream for that
I just got dye for color
for a Packa Gotta Die you'll be proud as
a peacock in this dashing shade of
[Music]
lapis wa this is for
you but the the um clothing D for cash
up items and for non-cash up items is
different right this is for non-cash up
items as far as I know I have no
idea oh I think yeah one of them's aacha
one of them you can choose the color I
think
mhm what am I killing
here Lava Rock Devil
die what's with the c me up here we just
talk to streamer pay it no mind oh
they're at this there like they know
us yes we yes yes we are at a region
watch our
streams all
live on
YouTube yes uh M Small Indie streamer
please
forgive please like And subscribe hit
that notification button did you the
Bell button did you see one of the new
members her Ori mark she has free oi
marks if I understand
correctly you subscribe or retweet it's
so Sil but it's so many it's funny but
there's like so many like there's too
many taken now we have to take like two
oi marks instead of one
nowadays must be rough I guess we got
kind of Lucky although mine mine bugs
out depending on the device mine splits
into an eyeball and a like a Yap
icon it's beautiful not wrong I guess
so I don't I don't want
this I should AR
this there you I guess I can archive it
for you you archive it for us
yeah okay I'm going to can I look at
your other archives too what else is in
there no you you get your own personal
archive I have a separate archive for
everyone oh so I I can't take a little
peek at another person allow well only
if they allow you I have to get their
consent of
course what is this a free country I'll
ask I suppose can I look at kiaha can I
look at your
archive uh you can watch my streams on
YouTube okay but we don't call call him
archives we call him waa on demand W on
demand mhm she's so in
demand man Killin thinks that a cleric
is so
slow right just die please just die
already I just
die it's a rough
life okay yeah really those cars are
so the Car mounts n no not they're cool
but they don't match they don't they
don't fit to this world makes no sense
to me is your immersion being ruined
yeah
100% deliver Adventure progress report
okay I'm on
it I need to play this for members only
as well at some point because this is
such a game fun I'm I'm so glad they
allow members to play it yeah really
nice only after we're done watching all
bonari series seasons soon soon we can
do something else kfy soon after so many
months you will be release from your
suffering I feel that I'm like I can't
do anything until we watch all of teen
wol
it for real what what is that how many
seasons does that have um I only watch
Four
Seasons um and they're 12 episodes each
so it's not too bad how long is one
episode like 40 minutes okay that's
quite
[Laughter]
the how many seasons are we watching
with mon series like nine I don't
know
dedicated very dedicated and then
there's movies
and now there's a new that's where we're
going towards man I would struggle with
my attention span for these
things for the they have to watch it for
watching anything that's like a really
long thing yeah well we are we're taking
uh breaks you know between each season
and so on like one week break but yeah
one of the time it has like so much
dialogue you do actually really need to
concentrate right to follow
the so attention span is necessary
cannot have zomer attention SP it will
be rough rough rough
rough they Yap so much yeah have you
seen have you guys seen M like any seen
clips of it like I'm aware it is a Yap
anime I've seen like the first
season Joi did you just [\h__\h] that
that was my monster that was my mob you
killed it now I have to wait for the
spa you deserve
jail absolutely use your now now
children years not in the presence of
sister
she you deserve to confess your sins to
the
sister never had a year sentence maybe
one year we had one one year before but
yeah you get F hell no I had taken it
you are you have no choice ah there he
is okay the spawn was relatively fast
I'll give you um one year
instead one year sentence I guess she
will not show up to to see your your
cat never was planning on it no please
you were planning on coming to see my
cat that it's a guaranteed no what I
thought you were you really were
thinking about coming to see my cat wa
you're your yours sure but um before I
come to see it you must show me proof
that you have a
cat what if she just shows up dressed up
as a cat
camera [\h__\h] she just got like a fuit
me you're not honest to me we cannot go
anywhere with this with this cat
relationship you guys have some really
complicated
relationships Jan what what quest are
you
doing um I am Expedition team fun story
for okay what does it require you to do
killing things like these
flowers
killing I think the game wants me to do
the dungeon oh already wow n maybe maybe
soon I'm close to the
dungeon
dang now I got to defeat a transformed
flower okay
flower I like the music here it's pretty
calming
yeah
no at level 30 you get the school
uniform oh now we a school you you're
going to school
yeah if you look at your quest above it
where it says like you can pick up these
quests and then level 30 gives you a
quest to get that school
uniform you see
it above my quest you mean an
L um it's the bubble with the
exclamation point above your quest uh
tracker ah that one self- Improvement a
c you okay you sound like you're choking
[Music]
I'm I'm fine I'm
fine I just love cash up items too much
it's my
passion and I wish there was like a
swort setting for inventory maybe there
is I know where like sort by
newest
yeah suffering oh is here hello
suffering is
eternal oh okay yeah uh I
guess I'm going to near your
bags where am I
going about Auto
trash are we getting the the school
outfit now oh my God
I like my is so fast I like my performer
outfit but you know got to got to change
clothes every once in a
while through them let's see is it
purple then it will match with my
alpaka
cute cute cute very cute but
okay I'm going to go to aen to I have
some weird territory War quests
okay is that about the man I remember
when everyone was so elitist if they
were in the the biggest Guild or
something oh yeah oh yeah trust me I
always
was elitist about
it yeah and I was cool cool bu wow I was
oh my God sometimes so when when there's
like let's say like three uh like top
guilds and you're in one of them and
then there's this abute huge drama when
you decide to go to the different you
switch to different famous Guild and
your whole old Guild is like what the
[\h__\h] she's [\h__\h] abandoning us and
cheating on us but I'm just going there
why because they're winning in the guild
war like when when when when your guild
isn't doing so well in the guild war
anymore you got to do you got you got to
go to the one you got to do what you got
to do to go is the one that's winning
man
loyalty
loyal got to win got to
win and for me I would just say like I'm
going to go Guild hop in my other
account see you guys or like in my main
account I got to defeat our acelino or
something oh it's not part of the the
dungeon actually yeah I and chilling
until you guys get dungeon
okay I feel kind of bad I'm not paying
attention to the story something about
being Children Of Eden and eternal ah no
no need we already talked about this
like there there's no need to pay
attention to the story in these kind of
games I don't think anybody expect hey I
actually read the story from Aura
Kingdom and forgot
it I was not I tried to pay
attention oh there a video essay oh I
see
Wetlands okay I'm going to go get the
dungeon Quest too for the wetlands
what's the dungeon the dungeon and then
we can maybe call it a day cuz you have
another stream
G okay it doesn't we don't have if we
want to keep playing My Stream can be
pushed back no no no I need to eat
actually I need to eat we'll do the
wetlands dungeon and then we've done a
good amount okay yeah yeah
yeah what's happening in here why are
you fighting in
here Rocky waa must live here Rocky waa
where are you girl you know did you did
you guys ever buy your own merch
you mean in general no in h like I I was
forced to now buy a couple of my own
glasses because I only get one sample
right we only get one sample if we want
one but I wanted a couple more glasses
cuz I really like the glasses the first
time I asked them hey can you guys like
send it to me like maybe deduct it from
my payroll they were like no cuz I
thought maybe that way I can um like go
around paying certain fees but no I have
to buy it like a normal customer so
boo it's also it's faster to buy it
yourself though because they take over a
year to give you your stuff at least for
me no no no it's not going to be faster
cuz I'm ordering for gej
and wa wait are you guys doing the
Branda rude Quest or something
else I'm in I'm at a Branda root Quest
Branda root yeah yeah were you a
different
dungeon uh I just not in
it yeah it's it's called level 30 The
Mystery of the magic water source and oh
is that wait that's not the dungeon
maybe I got a different main quest
there's probably two dungeons here
then I probably I think the other
regions also had more than one dungeon
right oh my God how did you get the
other one uh I I just followed one of
the main stories oh they're right
outside what's going on in the world
chat why are you so many where do you
come from I love this why you well I'm
in the dungeon if it's brand the
root the will of the one called
Wawa Tak started streaming it last week
and we just joined the game and state
YouTube streamer that's me that's me
that's her
SK from Ohio what what are you talking
about don't don't give me a bad
reputation with your skib
guy all right well I'm I'm inside the
Branda root dungeon if that's what
you're
doing I'm trying I archived all my stuff
but I'm trying to find it oh that's the
pain that's the pain now yeah now now I
can't where is it in the
archive well I I just archive things I
don't do it organized can you organize
my archive please
nope please I'm a Healer not an
organizer I I'm I'm not quite readyy it
seems for the um the brand the r need to
do it's okay take your time yeah need to
do one or two more things maybe
L your time
staff almost
[Music]
there bless you thank
you we'll take a look don't lose oh well
I lost my staff it's fine oh no what
happened did you try to fortify it no I
archived it and I can't find oh wait you
can archive
weapons all the Legacy ones I think get
archived they go somewhere and I can't
find the Legacy weapons you'll find
better
weapons yeah
hopefully oh my god Ra ubu XD M what are
you guys typing in the
chat they embarrassing seeing you the
Eden Eternal Community the viewers
reflect the
streamer no no I I I don't do that kind
of Ooo
stuff that's not me that's
me really ra ra o
XD EXC me sometimes I say that as a joke
I say that as a joke I believe leave
you I think I say that more than
uu uu is not
for it can't hurt you
yeah okay do I have the dungeon Quest
now maybe now I have it like your other
costumes what is
this oh there
certificates
oh I forgot
[Music]
about I'm I have the dungeon
Quest yeah
[Music]
y ready whenever I'm inside oh
okay Soo okay me too all right let's do
this
giggy will way once again I'm ready
you're a b now too we're two bars are
you guys all
healers I lost my staff so I I see it's
okay unconventional at least we can all
heal let's go my heal
slots I'm using a sword and a shield
even though I'm in F class right now
whatever it works yeah whatever
works I'm
buffing and you're getting up
pretty I'm buffing I'm buffing everyone
get buffed get buffed debuff the enemy
so hard that it explodes come on wait
what attacks do you even have don't you
have like the slowest attack
technically I have fire and
Whirlwind I see yeah and rocks rocks the
power of
rock uh-oh I think you're taking on too
much everyone's following you uhoh
uhoh
uhoh I love it when you say that it is
so
calming this kill all
disturbing it's okay I think you're
attacking me now don't worry don't worry
don't worry we got them we got them we
got them we have the AOE just kind of
slow I think you also attracted the boss
yeah I made eyes with him and I aged him
oh I
see this is fine we did it it's so easy
yeah
fine really not a good combination of
classes but this is once they give me a
staff I can
switch may I have one lying
around I like how these look like
Christmas trees to
me Christmas trees random Soul trees
yeah but they're shaped like a Christmas
tree can I get a Christmas tree this
year yes I want I'm scared how cats
react to them
maybe I'll put a real one into my garden
ooh but I won't like plant it just put
it there outside it will like stay fresh
longer when it's outside anyway right oh
what's this like cooler are we already
done yeah yeah fast dungeon
what it's a it's a small dungeon it's
not the main one
[Music]
nice
okay well
then well we shall slow prepare for the
end the end of it all
yeah uninstalling Eden
Eternal what the
[\h__\h] uninstalling eaten
Eternal
[Music]
P what we care about the game what
he I
no no I'm kidding I'm kidding no but
yeah uh guys don't spam the world chat
too much okay not not that was funny but
let's uh let's
behave oh you know you can turn off your
world
chat well at least like not this message
thing but the other world
chat I have been not reading the chat at
all yeah for was that yeah I didn't read
it even mostly but um let's not let's
not disturb them too
much all right well thank you for the E
experience thank you for the
gaming yeah it's
fun yeah I love mindess grinding so much
now
I'm so glad I found more likeminded
people like
you and then I can teach you about maple
story soon right you can teach about it
maybe someday but I'm grinding Eden now
I can't afford to grind another game
okay may maybe next month but did you I
saw something interesting yesterday that
Ragnarok online is getting like they're
they're working on a new like on on two
projects yeah like a new Ragnar R online
free and also separately another like
game like
that so I'm I just hope it goes well
Ragnarok 2 is a different experience
from the first one yeah that completely
not Ragnarok yeah I was fine with
it but yeah I saw that uh like in some
Japanese news yesterday it was like oh
my God oh my God oh
[Music]
oh not popular huh rockwork online too
why
why was that because it was 3D right
that's why I liked
it but they were 2D
Fanatics like um I I will say like for
example like if we differentiate between
these kind of like what we're playing
right now 3D and then trickster online
which is 2D but like kind of top down
angle and then maple story is 2D but
it's like how do you describe
that
gy um pixel side scroller yeah Metroid
Vania technically in terms of the map so
Sid scrolling not not really my thing
for like
RPGs I tried let tail that was like
maple story like I don't have a problem
with with uh uh I don't have a problem
with pixel and I don't have a problem
with 2D but like Sid scrolling
[Music]
2D yeah but it looks cute looks very
very cute and I know it's like a good
game cuz people love it so much for a
long time must be good game yeah it has
giggy's brain and heart and wallet and
body bank account intelligence
[Music]
good for you paycheck has that
too yeah my heart is somewhere else but
that's okay so yeah let's let's play
again sometime soon
girlly yeah but also we can always play
members only but let's keep each other
updated on what level we are okay
okay is there a limit on when we should
stop leveling no no like lebling a lot
go for it go for it we'll we'll catch up
with you yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay shall I give
lead yeah who is going to advance this
Guild for us so we don't have to who
hopefully does not disband the kill one
Ser the leader highest
level
dang no but this person was all like
they didn't start with us they were
already high level before
like they cing they have experience but
you better give me promotion right
away there you go don't destroy the guil
I trust
you I the ultimate rage
quit this one guilt explodes
guil what me yes you you're most
experienced player among these
people so help them out yeah I got I
became captain and vice leader yippee
nice and now go make a town that will
surprise me next time I go
online yeah Guild town I remember that
yeah thank you so much girls for no
problem it was a blast once
again a great time playing got some
stuff I think I already have these but
maybe a different color got some cash up
items again
ooh this one's cute must take anyway I
will I will send people to whatever
people there are in the streams MH
y can't wait to do bigger
dungeons yeah y more challenging ones
yeah ones that actually require a t yeah
and with with like good loot Epic Loot
that will fight over
okay I think I'll go read some super
chatos cuz I'm far
behind have a good
one to rest
goodbye
byee all right thank you for playing
eeden Eternal with me I'll continue to
play this game and there's some dungeons
that I can run again at some point so if
I see you guys online then uh I'll
probably just like ask so yeah we'll
probably probably play this for members
a membership stuff I have left for dead
tonight in a few hours so I will see you
again then until then
sh I absolve you from your sins
temporarily