[Music]
do
huh
hello it's it's me
can you guys recognize me
it's me it's me small kiara
it's small kiana very small and small
and wealthy hey
it's me who is that
from uh hollow myth or
udemy yo
what up guys
hello how's it going everyone
did you all just come from the collab
and end my in my quick video premieres
did you see the little videos i wanted
to show off my spin
and i wanted to show off my bounds
you spin my head right round right round
like a record baby
go around go around i don't know
i was spinning and i was bouncing that's
very important
that needed to be seen and it needed to
be seen
in higher sps and bitrate
because during the collab once
once i turned into this small version of
myself somehow
somehow we had some bad reception
let's just say it like that it is how it
is
so we had to do some last minute
emergency thingy you know
got some good screenshots well now
you're gonna get better screenshots
from this well well now now i'm looking
at high definition right you see you see
all my details right
wait i don't where did my feathers go
just realize i have no feathers in in
this version so if i die
then then i'm dead
because without feathers well [\h__\h]
well then we're [\h__\h]
no feathers so am i i might die
i was thinking a little bit for a moment
if i want to do like a re-debut
as this kiana because you know re-debut
is my thing now
but i don't know that would have taken
again so much preparation i wasn't quite
prepared for that um
so now it's too late now we're doing
this i wasn't even i wasn't even
planning to stream
on my own today originally i wasn't even
gonna stream today
uh but i decided after the collab i
wanna you know show off
and talk to you guys and i also need to
read super chats anyway
a little bit i'm too afraid to snipe
this when i'm sitting out this time
well that's okay that's okay by the way
i'm super hungry oh [\h__\h] what are we
gonna do
about this hunger oof i ate i
i i woke up and i ate a pear
i ate a pear and that's it
uh so before we read superchats i might
need to
make something or or order something
that
consists of foof
but now we're going to play sliver for
like what an hour
or something like that 40 minutes who
knows we will see
and we'll enjoy we'll enjoy this
beautiful
version of myself
isn't it cute when i close my eyes i
said
bling bling bling bling
again i can also get rid of the chicken
you can do it you're literally holding
it in your hands eat it that's
you're right wow you're so right but
those are not those are not edible i
told you guys before these other these
are made out of plastic
that's why i'm not eating them um
i don't have a sword i don't have the
sword i don't i have these uh
these maracas yeah
i got and the glasses let me see
uh and oh you want to see my expressions
hey let me let me move myself uh
okay how does it work oh like this
here okay i stand on the chat now oh
don't look at my parents oh my god okay
i'll stand here
can you still see them where should i
stand okay here you shouldn't be able to
see them
right okay
so for example uh this is my normal face
this is my happy face
[Music]
wow wow wow wow
i can only put my hand back if i do this
i think oh no okay
all good all good and uh
this is my oh wait oh you didn't see oh
it didn't see me moving
okay there we go
i did not transition let me go again
okay this is my normal face huh
that was actually i was uh
i was i was standing here and asking you
guys if you see my panties
do you see them you shouldn't see them
i'm moving back okay
i'm playing around with studio mode for
the first time in my life
ah oh wait i noticed something let me
let me do that
real quick
okay good
so normal face and happy face
party party
and i i can i can kind of dab too
like yeah yeah
yeah oh hey
and then and then let me oh no no no
yes
calm down calm down stop someone stop
me stop okay
[Music]
stop don't don't dwell okay okay okay
see this is my face when i'm about to
throw up
from all the spinning
stand spinning to the gate spinning into
the gate
this is my ugly face
why are you calling me chicken this is i
think what i said in my debut stream as
well in my first ever debbie stream
why are you calling me chicken why would
you do that
ah anki
rude i hate you
i hate you and then my surprise face
i look like a fish
it said the slight difference with the
eyes normal face
surprise face
these look like a fish and bitto
[Music]
looking good huh cute okay
now one second let me let me uh
quick transition should i put on my
glasses
okay i want to keep the keep on the
chicken
there we go go better not [\h__\h] around
with me
okay so i'm gonna wear these these
shades because they protect my poker
face
my mama poker face by my poker face
my mama poker face my my poker face
got no chance against me anyway we're
going we're going over
over here we're gonna we're gonna do a
little playtime
you ready play some sliver good luck
getting into my server
only cool people getting i want to see
you try
let's play a little bit and then read
super chats this is only a gorilla
stream so it won't be too long also i'm
hungry
and when i'm hungry then i'm mad let's
go
okay well
you're here to be damn right everyone
i haven't played sliver in a while oh my
god there's casper but with a k
wait this is uh like this is our old
german-speaking people we're invading
the germans
we're invading the germans who always i
shouldn't say that
i wanted to do a joke but probably would
have been a bad joke like
for some people i don't know but but you
know how
when there's like ah
but you know how these like when people
when like when like the germans
are like in the youtube comment section
they always write wait what's i don't
know it by heart what do they always
write um this
this comment section has now but they
read it in german this comment section
has now been invaded by
some what was it what what did they
always say oh that's what i wanted to
say
what's what's this person's name
the commentary oh my god
no you almost killed yourself
don't [\h__\h] around with me t.y don't [\h__\h]
around with me
no no i'm faster than you [\h__\h] you
i mean republic is republic but would
burn this
well well whatever you know what i mean
now that's what i was trying to say not
the thing that you might think that i
was trying to say although
yeah where did i stop myself because
that could have been ooh very bad is
that
are you guys already already sacrificing
yourself smee
when are my people coming when is my kfp
gun coming it's okay i'm gonna grow
strong before you guys come
before you guys find me
let me stop oh
we already got one you quickie
you meant to just stop [\h__\h] that man up
[\h__\h] him up
that's you can't do that you can't do
that
just when i met someone someone who
someone from my gang can't do that
kind of rude
okay i'm gonna stay mad for the whole
stream by the way wow i almost killed
that dude nice one
ew that was even though it just started
he pretty much ran into me how did he
even
how did he even get away from that cause
i love how small
bird is at the top of the leaderboard
even though that person most likely has
nothing to do with
us but yay birds
stay strong i don't mind having that
person
was that what was that name something
with holo myth hello live hello
something yeah
yo you got some pretty colors going on
hey welcome okay every beat is also here
nice jay drago welcome welcome everyone
matt's fine ah i got so uh
like i said i got distracted by your
fights i almost ran into that person
would you like me ah [\h__\h] sorry your
fires distracted me again
uh oops
oops okay
wow close close one coolest one
i'm hungry so hungry
hungry i am so hungry this is
this is german speaking server why are
you here with the
uh american vlog huh german speaking
server
we we're spraying dots here yeah
do what you want if you think that's
what you want to do
oh david dave is it david attenborough
no way that was not david attenborough
was it
did he sacrifice his snake to my snake
did david attenborough's snake
died die from my own hands
oh my god [\h__\h] hell
nah damn
it was that david's spirit fighting back
for what i took away from him
follow the light follow the light follow
the sparkling light
oh my god whoa
hold on four paper oh yeah
i love you you're a good person you are
oh my god there's
so much sparkle i want to take it you're
in the way ah
well yeah we got the advertisements
going on
advertising whole talk for i'm not sure
actually it's it's for me
it's uh sunday night
like from the night saturday to sunday
so
depending on where you at it might be
saturday for you it might be sunday for
you
for me it's correctly speaking it's
sunday
but it's actually saturday night for me
it's after midnight for me one hour
after midnight so it is sunday
technically speaking yeah for esd and
pst it's saturday
better come everyone um i'm thinking
i don't oh my god i'm not sure but what
do you guys think
of me doing holo talk this week in this
uh
with this model because like
i think it would be really funny but i
don't want to draw too much attention to
myself
i know that would be so funny and you
guys are excited about it but that would
i don't i don't want to be the attention
um i don't know dragging and waiting
attention from aki you know what i mean
yeah maybe in the beginning oh
no it's kind of weird to change the
outfit in midway through
i think what's your what's that name
think of a better name dude yeah
he wants to kill me just for a small
skit
let aki have to spot like that that's
what i'm thinking that's what i'm
thinking i also think like it would be
so funny to have one holo talk episode
where i'm
like this because it would just be
[\h__\h] ridiculous
um
[Music]
it's difficult ask aki
i don't know i guess i'm fine um she
probably
even if she would mind she would
probably still because she's so kind
i'll [\h__\h] get get wrecked
you went ah no no ah no
no [\h__\h] i killed him
did you see that did you see that pro
gamer move that i did i
went dumb you don't [\h__\h] with me
that was that i was not someone from kfp
so i'm okay with that
hello piano queen we love oh i love you
too thank you
i'm getting really slow now that was so
good that might have been
the best move that i've ever done in
sliver
oh thank you how kind of you
oh and big snake
what's oh you don't see it there should
i move so you guys can find me easier
okay i'm right now i'm in the bottom
right
let's hear us hey yeah you wanna you
wanna
what what do you want from me huh
you can't get close to me when i die
again i'll i'll show you my map i'll
i'll move
to oh my god i'll move i move away
i'll try stop it you [\h__\h]
when i'm letting out my aggression too
much i i promised myself i would swear
less
aki should use her mookie rosette and i
should use the web yeah
that would be uh funny but
that would be legendary no uh
f go away go away
okay i'm going i'm going up i'm going up
go away i will i will kill you okay
i will kill you out what a freaking
troll
[Applause]
[\h__\h] i'm mad
mad is it did you write down the name
did you write down the name everyone
i'm gonna find him and destroy him
okay let me move um it's difficult
though i guess i didn't then we have uh
[Music]
i wonder if you can see it if i'm but
then you barely see me
and if i go to the left then there's
such an empty
empty area on the right side but i guess
do prefer it this way for today
if i just go here
just stay should you go to the left side
then you'll see that on the map
bottom left yeah
should i take you know what i'm going to
take off my glasses real quick
i can't i can't see so well
one second last
off i'm going into serious mode now
somehow with the wealthyness of this
model
makes me makes me uh turn it into a
gremlin
okay fight let's go
oh there's a big big boy there
do you see wait you still ah you still
don't see the map very well because i
cut it off there one second i'll kill
myself real quick
okay okay no problem actually
cause now that we have the screen like
that
i'm gonna do
done okay
whatever which is gonna it's gonna look
a little bit scuffed today but that's
okay
chose your teeth i don't have tip right
now okay
yeah i don't have teeth right now
oh my god no i wanted those no
there's someone from kfb number 10 on
the leaderboards
have been like you know the right suit
nice jfp amiibo
why didn't you feed oh why oh god he's
huge whoa he's feeding someone are you
feeding me thank you i love you
i'm sorry the big snake killed me
but i appreciated you very much
i appreciated that very much thank you
you're not from jsp otherwise you
wouldn't have
sacrificed yourself to me
thank you did you try to help me
no he's he's on a he's on he's a serial
killer
did you see that how he killed the other
one too
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
okay
nice to meet everyone here okay i'm in
the bottom left now
not exactly so so close to the middle
okay
arc cafe you want to kill yourself for
me
that sounds so wrong oh
are you trying to i are you trying to
kill me or
trying to kill yourself there we go
thank you go away oh yes
i don't know if that's what you really
wanted to do
but you did it you did it right good job
so guys i want to know like um
that announcement that came out before
the stream
that uh the the hololife english account
tweeted with the silhouettes did you
guys like already
because i didn't really see people
freaking out like oh my god they're
gonna be
in wealthies of uh yeah these big
hunkers
oh my god these people i i didn't see
people freaking out
really about it i don't think many
people no no no no
no no no glue you tom
that's from the stream just now so i i
just want to know if you guys uh
is he protecting me i just want to know
i can't speak right now motion
yeah he's protecting me
so i just want to know if you guys not
knew what was gonna
happen did you did you think father was
a joke
you didn't think we would actually do
something like that huh yeah i think
no one really thought that we would
really do something like that
um wait i want to read the comments
but i also need to grow bigger thank you
glue either tom
are you my new mama don't let into many
people you know that you might be
dangerous
not so much space here motion
thank you that's my food my food thank
you
mama and baby again
but the the what no mama no
[\h__\h] you that's what i always say
i'm not sure unless you're helping me
okay
you okay you want to be my mama now
who's your mama oh
you chad no oh my god it's mass murder
oh no
oh no become as god become as god i've
seen this somewhere before in one of my
playthroughs
oh no oh no oh no space [\h__\h]
[Music]
so anyway did you guys
uh decide coming or not okay so
i can't really read much in the chat so
just tell me um yes or no did you see it
coming or did you not see it coming yes
or no
be honest don't try to be cool like
i knew that we could
yes yes no no no no yes yes no [\h__\h]
way
no way
yes no no like after the announcement
you saw it coming or
i mean i also thought it was it was
pretty giving away everything pretty
much
the announcement the silhouettes um the
body shape
was so obvious but did you what did you
think that we would actually be animated
though
callie scheduled tweet oh
oh that actually oh
what kelly's aha
kelly's tweet
[Music]
oh oh
oh i saw something like that like i i
saw her like being like ah
yummy but i didn't i didn't think it
actually came out oh
well then of course you guys saw it
coming
okay well and yeah because someone said
i saw that too
someone um like on on their own
rigged the the wealthy avatars on their
own
like privately and uploaded it to
twitter like
when was that a month ago or so or like
they started at least like a month ago
and i saw it and that's
that was at the moment when we already
knew that we were doing this and i was
like oh
cool is this person reading our mind a
robot
but we were already working on it um
before that
i actually i'm not sure like who came up
with the id
huh it was someone from us
someone was like was it me i don't know
i don't even remember but someone was
like hey wouldn't it be funny if for
april 1st
we would be you know
or someone maybe me said something like
i would
it would be so cool if we could i mean
totally not possible could never do this
but haha it would be so funny for april
1st
we could have this please wealthy and
advertised
as ourselves someone said that
i know keeping like me but at the same
time i feel like it wasn't me i'm not
sure
maybe it was man you know what i want to
look it up on discord
and then and then it just happened it
was just
john from accounting could you not i
guess it was just too much of a genius
idea couldn't
could not not do it not no [\h__\h]
plastic bag
taster now they're all eating me up
with an amazing collab love the whole
pop we it's such a blessing to have jack
box games available now for us
we're gonna be playing that a lot i
think
eh phrasing what did i say what did i
say
what
although with the drawing one i never
knew
what to draw and with the
the other one i often didn't know what
the words meant or for example i didn't
know who that dude was
some some actor no idea i even googled
it
i looked him up while while the time was
running
and i was like okay okay but still like
what i don't i
i guess he's kind of like meme yeah
michael bay
i guess he's kind of memorable if you
like
know who he is is he would you say he's
meme morphy because i
i would say i would guess that what are
you doing schnitzel
i i would i would guess that that that
is why everyone go there you
freaking addicted
uh what do you call those things that go
to the light
now schnitzel you wanted to kill me i
[\h__\h]
cute
yeah the mops are trying to get to the
line
anyway we're gonna have so many fun
collabs of jackpots
it's just it only has just begun and i
want to talk about
who do you think out of her life
had like the funniest or most impressive
um prank or
whatever going on for april fools
because i have to say some of them were
pretty damn good
at
i met with her pregnancy now i think
like
um you would count as holo yen as a team
uh because we we did that we did the
wealthy thing you know
and then compare it to i mean we don't
like comparing but
i thought like personally i was freaking
shocked
that piccolo senpai
did like a whole new outfit like i mean
i mean we kind of did a new outfit as
well
kind of but but she did like the real
thing i was like oh my god for real
what and it looks so cute
i mean it's very specific jail clothes
she probably won't be able to use that
all the time people are following me
you're not even from kfp aren't are ya
schnitzel no
okay oh my god
oh my god
um what happened there what just
happened oh my god
what happened players gave me with help
help help
whoa get wrecked
that was nice in japanese we like to
call that zama middle
[Music]
name
[\h__\h] hell
serves it right yeah we've tried
when you try your best but you don't
succeed
question hello the taco bell and kfp
supporter nice
be my akira you should pick emily89
protect
me please johnson
everyone it's a freaking party
it's a freaking party can can you
can you guys all just you know bump into
me accidentally oh my god she did it she
did it what a [\h__\h] mad lad
so much food so much food so much food
but they all took so much food away from
hearing
my food no stupid stupid
black silver snake
oh yeah i don't know where to go
okay the screaming just killed my throat
thank you for the membership so as a
back to topic
are you okay bye back to the topic
um i was saying that i really really
love fake lesson facing outfit i was
watching this stream
and because she didn't show the new
outfit for
quite some time when i saw the thumbnail
i saw like the hair was different i was
like okay
is she really giving us a new outfit or
did she just
like draw a silhouette and now wants us
to think that she's gonna
thank you that she's gonna give us a new
outfit so first i was like
not sure and then she started to stream
and most of the time she
she like she didn't even advertise it as
a new outfit and she didn't she didn't
really say anything she stayed in your
normal outfit most of the time so i was
like okay
oh he is from kfp i was like okay well
i guess no near outfit i mean that would
have been crazy anyway
that was oh that was my fault
apologize to me now apologize to me now
apologize to me now
so yeah continuing everyone's saying
sorry ah i'm sorry
i know i saw you in the chat i believe
you
you didn't and it looked like there was
just too much going on too much speed
i don't think you actually wanted to do
that so it's okay
okay so and where were we yeah oh yeah
yeah and then oh
and then you know oh my god like it was
funny anyway like it was it was
legit funny like but i i was i was like
giving up on the thought that she was
gonna give us an outfit because i was
always like who gets a new outfit for
april
first like what what mad lad gives us a
new outfit
for april 1st that's not even a holiday
christmas okay new years okay
birthday okay i get all of that
but he pulled first
so i gave up on it and then and then she
did it and i was like oh my god it's so
[\h__\h] cute first of all it's so cute
like and also her room oh my god the
room
with the skeleton with the [\h__\h]
bunny skeleton and i was like okay i see
i did not realize
that bunny's ears have
bones inside i have a please smile
okay because you killed me and i don't
really want i don't really want to smile
but okay okay
yeah so oh my god i did wait but no
bunnies don't actually have rabbits
actually have bones in their ears do
they
they don't right
[Laughter]
so that was funny uh and i like her i
like her new joker
which is like if you look at it closely
it also has like the bunny
ear shape the the lock that's on around
her neck
now what are you doing
freaking stupid [\h__\h] sorry
oh my god i need to chill i need to
chill i need to chill this person
probably isn't even from kfp
so he's not never gonna hear it so
that's okay i guess but
i need to chill i need to chill i need
to chill chill chill
chill kiara stop stop swearing
ah yes by that i saw a good comment her
ears in her new outfit were bent
so if she shows us that
bunnies have bones in there oh thank you
bones in their ears that would mean that
her ears are broken and she would she
would probably be in pain right now
if she oh my god is she okay
is she okay that must be very painful
anyway so then and
what what did other people do
what did other people do we did we did
the wealthy
and then whole live id turned into a
drink
and into guys
hollow stars the movie poster was high a
bit
stream high challenger i love you i love
you i love you
i love you i love you i love you i love
you
really please hello alice nana kill
yourself now thank you
that was your redemption oh my god
so much light i'm gonna die bro
that's mine that's all of that is my
teammate you know what uh
yummy what up oh it's it's so happy i'm
gonna die
um oh my god i didn't die how did i not
die now
oh my god okay that's mine oh my god
[Music]
what has happened
what other pranks did we have hmm
tell me i i was very uh busy because i
was streaming i got up and up
i want to get to them ah
yeah yeah i didn't watch that one
she starts she started when our collab
started
ah is she done is she still streaming
honey
is she is is my senpai still streaming
she's done oh my god i got to check the
archive because wait did she also
it looked like she was also showing us a
new life to see thingy
friendly neighborhood aren't you my
lesbian though where did the lesbian go
it sounds so weird you're just a
friendly neighborhood what about the
lesbians
what happened to the lesbians need to
investigate
what they used to be friendly
neighborhood lesbians i'm sorry that's
just how it is
ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay
that gives me time it gives me time to
go on youtube
i just went on twitter and wolfie says
dan kiana is live so g-rake looks so
much better when it's 12
when it's not 12 ps at 360p
yep um yeah so now you can see the full
glory
isn't that nice the full glory of this
wealthy
life today uh
okay
april fool
no she really also did a live tv oh my
god
a new outfit basically
lowly lolly but to be honest she
she originally already is
quite quite the lowly
she's originally flat and um you know
you say i mean anyway
that's cute i gotta watch more of that
later
old live today what
wait there's an old one what
that's not new
she didn't last youtube ah i didn't see
that what she didn't last you two but it
got
updated old model new costume
better recycle yeah sweet okay did you
just redeem yourself because you killed
me last time
nice one thank you
yeah i like how everyone honestly i
gotta say
up until now i i never really
put much effort into preparing something
for april fool's and i mean i didn't
really have that much of an
audience either so it didn't make much
sense to uyabi
to show that much off
think of something nice teammate are you
trying to kill me or are you trying to
help me
are you are you going to kill yeah it's
oh [\h__\h] i killed myself now i don't know
i couldn't move properly
and what was i saying oh yeah so
honestly
being like in her life having all these
people
um do funny stuff on april fools and and
us halloween being a part of it and
having our own big thing
with the wealthy uh alive to tease
i have to say this is the best april
fool's
i've ever had i was never like
so um how to say
so invested
and prepared for april fools i never
took it that seriously
and really did anything
[Laughter]
that was the most fun april fools ever
hey emily
you're really fat and thick and juicy
looking
[Music]
are you gonna circle me
that was uh why do you call those people
on on the autobahn who
drives you drive the other direction
nice guys
came out of nowhere
i felt that one thank you
i'm still sharing a bit of my my own
chickens
okay get out of the danger zone it's
very dangerous here
i tried to feed you i got close to the
leaderboard but you're so far away i
kept learning everyone oh i'm so curious
it's the thought that counts
i gotta write your name into my death
note it's the second time
alice nana it's the second time
you want to say something huh
i want to say something to me or isn't
it
always always playing so nice always
playing so nice to me sending me sweet
messages and super chats
and now this is this is this is how you
were to me trying to help you
that's german oh come on
let's let's bump each other come on come
on
come on come on come on
there's phoenix food
[Music]
[\h__\h] we
if anything we serve vegan chicken i
have i have
i have come to the realization that i
just haven't told you this before so
it's no reason to panic everyone
whenever i say kfp serves chicken or
anything
like that what i actually meant is that
it's vegan it just tastes exactly like
chicken that's how good it is
and it looks exactly like chicken that's
how good this vegan chicken is
i forgot to tell you should have told
you guys earlier that would have
probably cleared up a lot of
misunderstandings
the usual verb is not a lie what the
hell
oh
so no more need to panic yeah
no need to panic anymore everyone oh my
god
what's going on i said hey
what's going on no [\h__\h] off
excuse me oh my eye of it oh this is
your beat
the lights the lights i'm a muffin i
love the lights
oh i'm eating you alone
oh they're out well thinking that
they're getting somewhere trying to get
close to me
hello friendly neighborhood again i ask
you again friendly where
is where is the lesbians
the neighborhood no
oh my god it's already already one hour
no not exactly let's play like 10 more
minutes and then we reach a good chance
this is fun
i really want kelly's love
has circled me i was inside kelly's love
and she ate me up there's nothing else i
ever wanted in life
that's all i ever wanted i'm happy
if you're happy and you know it then you
really want to show it
if you're happy and you know and clap
your hands
who saw that coming playing slaver.il
without hands
who saw that one coming huh
i totally didn't
lasagna
give me some of that lasagna
oh so many german flags germany german
flag of germany
[Music]
would be nice right now no austrians
playing
oh i'm sure there's some australian
australians
australia australia
[Music]
i can't wink like this dude
are you trying to help me or not what is
this i don't know
i don't know if i can trust you so i i
just i
[Music]
stupid i was i was getting to
chosen i was getting to
how do you call that choose in japanese
why do you call that in english
um greedy i guess so getting too greedy
[\h__\h] fake
can you you know what i'm gonna drive to
curse in german from now on
it's gonna make everything better right
okay okay i don't know how to
how to speak in english but then curse
in german that's like some
high level language
switching next level language switching
okay wait what about oh my god idea
okay so we talked about hulk talk
and how i would find it funny and you
all agreed with me we would find it
funny
if i would um use this
every single paycheck is that what
you're asking
uh if we would use this avatar but
i don't want her to you know i don't
want the attention
it's about her but what if
we do a whole talk
where i'm the guest at some point
and what is one is kiara
like this and one is kiara in her
original
that sounds like a plan
to me
then i can show it off well now who
would be the host though
why did the food eat me i'm supposed to
eat the food
that would work who would be the host i
would say
wealthy while fiata would be the host
while fianna should be the host because
we're interviewing the real kiara
right you want to learn more about the
real kiana i mean i guess when i was
home i almost killed that dude
that's what i was gonna know about
something about well fiora but
it's basically the same person
maybe maybe well fiona is more more
gremlin version of kiara
it's it's that influence i get from ame
because in my head wealthy equal
ame i think it's that it's like that
for a lot of people so when i see myself
in this style
i kind of feel like i'm turning into
army
oh if only whoa did you see that i
didn't even i didn't even try to do this
i'm sorry
actually i actually wanted to
get away from you oh oh my god did you
see that
ah
and duck you
okay we should go to a state okay okay
okay since this is the last round
everyone
go top left oh my god there's a big
snake here
is that number two okay everyone meet me
at the top left
give me your sacrifices let's make kiara
number one
there's some other idiots here damn it
okay let's let's make let's meet uh
middle left
i'm waiting for you
beerus be my sacrifice middle
left let me consume you and we're gonna
get kiara to number one
eat me kiara okay this is gonna be
difficult you're so huge uh
okay uh you are
the best
[Applause]
i'm eating the power okay pudding you're
up next
do it
oh my god yummy yummy yummy yummy i got
loving my dummy oh my god so much light
don't tell the others that there's a
party going on here okay
if people gonna find out they're gonna
eat you but you want to be eating
backyard right okay you gotta
keep some safe distance too like i'm
gonna
okay guys everyone stop just everyone be
in a circle
everyone just be a small circle okay
because if you're like this i'm gonna
die i'm gonna die
no no feet no someone killed the feet
someone killed his feet he's trying to
kill me he's trying to kill me
he's trying to kill me he's trying to
kill me
i don't if you're trying to protect me
i'm gonna protect me right now no he's
trying to kill me
[Applause]
[Music]
we got so many people around here why
are you helping me
help me
[Music]
i said it was the last round and you
ruined it
stinky feet
we were doing so well we had a good
meeting everyone was there
that was not rich quite i said it was
the last round
do you want to see me in full body or do
you want to see me in close
up and see the details
which one
full body
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
i thought of a good oh okay okay i spin
i spin i spin
and then you're gonna guess with which
hand holding up i'm going to be uh
stopping get it
so i spin spin spin spin spin okay
put your guesses left or right
[Music]
wow
now
[Music]
everyone seems to stay left so i guess
it's gonna be right again
[Applause]
okay okay okay which one not which one
now which one
[Music]
i didn't even see that coming didn't
even
plan that one
all right okay
you know what it's time for it's time
for super chats
great
by the way you see my you see my chat
screen right now right
right
yeah okay okay okay still getting used
to transitions
god can i wash my face real quick cat
hair i feel it one second i'll be
[Music]
remembered
let me let me go to an idol meeting too
real quick one second
[Music]
i brought my cat with me
wait not purring
come on
oh angel okay the only thing that's
really missing right now
is food but
it's okay how much do i have oh i think
i have a lot to read though yeah bit
you know what i got i got
i got the not so yummy uh
uh cereal bars
right here ready to be eaten anytime
[Music]
i'm prepared so well
okay they're not very yummy but okay
whatever
nutritious i guess so
i'm not really a fan of like healthy
cereal bars if they have chocolate
then it's much better but i i bought
somewhat healthy ones on purpose
so did i snack on healthier things
ah mom
yeah it tastes healthy
a little bit don't like it
um
my hands oh now we're trying to put them
down
not trip okay okay ohio
oh god i did it wow
okay
now i'm i look like i'm t-posing huh
hmm
wow i'm numb you didn't want to help
okay so we will be reading super chat
from the minecraft stream first
um
can i put up the thumbnail
what's your favorite food
vegan chicken nuggets
what
yeah vegetarian vegan whatever
i don't eat real chicken
do i look like someone who eats real
chicken
i would never i would never do such a
thing to my people
which doesn't mean that i'm a chicken
that's not what i'm implying
[Music]
things in my hands are made out of
plastic but if you're going to keep on
saying that you know what
you know what um
if you're gonna keep on saying that i've
got no choice
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
yeah [\h__\h]
yeah bit
you didn't see that
but now i have no more chicken
let me know start reading uh wait should
i put up
isn't it actually helpful i started
doing that a while ago
not sure about i was trying to do it
because then if people go for the
archive
and they want to pick up their super
chat order to go
and it would be easier for them like if
they go through the archive
to if they see the thumbnail then
they're like ah this is this is where it
should be
so does it actually do that are you guys
actually like
being helped with that yeah
it only provides benefits thumbnail
helps a lot okay okay
then i'll continue doing it uh which one
was it minecraft this one
there we go let's put it
let's put it here there we go
we're reading the super chats now
[Music]
and watch the full vod wow even if you
don't super chat
wow there's people who watch the full
super chat rating even even if they
don't super chan
that's that's wow that's impressive
yeah so many oh my god
thank you
okay looking for your top gun
what is
no not you not you me but you're gonna
make me cry with that
this is my official resignation as i
recently got a new job at jfp
turns out they have both health and
dental benefits and the new torture
dungeon even has wi-fi
plus albedo gives us all the cases we
wanted a much
more affordable price farewell
and it makes me very sad
but you were gone the whole time anyway
it's not like you were here recently
anyway
whatever whatever
albedo kiana's number one pick
thank you soon welcome to the jfp family
minigame
i hope you enjoyed the amazing perks jfp
offers
including paying off all college debt
it's not too late to join him
[Music]
you win extinction everyone changed i
see what you guys did there
a lot of you changed your name to jsp
instead of kfp
i see what you did there and i
must say
under normal circumstances i would be
crying but today is april fools so
i will trust in europe
in the hope of you coming back to me
but the people who stayed with kfb
even through april fools are the real
mvps
roxianna
sorry i'm still eating the cereal box
what the [\h__\h]
still the kfb philosopher not the jfp
philosopher i'm very happy to see that
loyal loyal philosopher
first i want to say thank you it's clear
that you work hard for us and that you
care
you have a gift that makes a real impact
on people's lives your beautiful soul
and we appreciate you
i love you thank you that's so sweet
i just noticed i don't have eyebrows
imagine my normal
model
just with shaved eyebrows
oh my god that's so cursed
that's so cursed
no eyebrows
expect to see it on twitter's alive and
i know it will come
like you remember when we created bald
cali
that was also not good
not good why did we do that
hmm now my nose is gone too
no nose no eyebrows no feathers
no belt i cannot transform anymore i
will stay like this forever
now we're gonna go back
you never had a nose i had a nose okay
hmm
people who are coming in now might be so
confused if they missed out on
everything else
i'm gonna pour in some water into my
garden
[Music]
i'm extremely confused right now please
explain yeah
did you i told you guys in the past
streams to watch the street did the
collab on kelly's channel
and i told you i told you many times
even if it's early for you in the early
in the morning it will be worth it
and i was right wasn't that i was right
you wasted time
well this is our our part this out for
people who don't understand
this i mean this is a kind of a late
explanation but
the way i am right now this thing here
that's
our whole life ian's way of saying
april fools
in german we just say april after a joke
very cute thank you smart
i think i'm going to use this a lot
white small chiara all right small kiara
no okay not yet not yet it's not time
for something like that we need to
appreciate small chia
more first don't you want a kiss from
small counter
[Music]
we didn't we didn't give out any kisses
here at a small kiara
anyway let's go mimi kfc thank you for
the red super chat there we go there's
your first one
i've established the kfp discord branch
for east asia fans just for you this is
the way i express my life to you hope
you can accept it
yes of course thank you i think that's
really cool
thank you so much i appreciate that it's
great that you guys can connect like
that over there
thank you hope you're having fun
thank you so much thanks for always
being here
thank you for the pinky oh another pinky
wait that mix so you know what you need
you can kiss it for dad jonathan
[Music]
second i got carried away with my bits
there huh sorry about that i was having
too much fun
i'll work on it what would everyone like
to see from my deep chats positive clips
flirty shower
flirty shower fox or just stop is an
option let me know
you're asking everyone why not asking me
i would say just keep doing what you're
doing i like it
thank you for your support
jfp albedo's bear
[Music]
for the pinky and again looking for the
top dog soon now let me read the pinky
we appreciate you yes but to cut to the
chase
i love you and we love you no one would
spend six months with you
every why why are people this is the
beginning of the minecraft super chats
why are people so
emotional already we spent uh
no one would spend six months or more
with you every day for several hours
without
genuinely caring for your well-being i
want to write more but the super chat or
tweet only goes so far i love you kiana
pre-shot was emotional but what happened
there
we forgot april fools existed
but it wasn't april fools yet anyway at
that time
for me at least
m
they don't want to wait until you're
gone to miss you that is smart
that is very smart um
that's cute i like that font
and so thank you thank you looking for
the time
for that sweet message
number one fantastic
i um really like your
eyes they are really beautiful also
i also think you have an above average
level of skill in minecraft i i hope
i hope you have an amazing night
i love you too alvida
thank you
[Music]
how sweet
that's your true feelings i know it
good morning i hope you have a great day
and a great student celebration to watch
live but we wanted to send some love and
support before i go thank you
[Music]
i'm so excited to play raza i got a fish
near first though
driving hard with your taste what other
amazing game recommendations do you have
oh well i would recommend obviously take
the tails off
uh um game series
[Music]
and other than that
games obviously
[Music]
something that you might not expect i
really enjoy the audience fear
[Music]
what else
but only if you're into that kind of
game
like i guess i guess like if you're
playing it outside of stream it would be
much more fun because you can take your
time
you can go through those uh uh those
those roots
without having to worry how long it
takes to clear them on stream
i recommend those and
i mean i played sakura now that was also
great but
i don't know if that's your type of game
it's hard to think of anything else
right now
like like they're so obvious choices
like zelda and super mario games that's
just too
too obvious i guess
a pokemon game yeah of course i mean
that's that's another one of those
obvious choices
anyway continuing uh taylor hill douglas
craft works
[Music]
proof that i can show my support and
love of super jets
oh why did you need to why did you need
to prove it ah because
because the super chats didn't work is
that is that one
it didn't work uh for some time
in the minecraft stream well thank you
sorry i'm moving the microphone thank
you for your support thank you soon
very happy to have you here thank you
moon dog hope you enjoyed the stream
thank you for for the proof but i didn't
need it
didn't need it i i know that all of you
are supporting me anyway but it's nice
to read it
as well in front of my eyes
especially
japanese but with no text thank you
thank you though
bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce
bounce bounce
bounce bounce bounce bounce
[Music]
this is my exercise i'm exercising we
should do ring fits with this
oh my god and then then you can finally
see my body move
and then go like this and i'm like i'm
exercising i'm exercising and i go like
this
looks like i'm running maybe a little
bit with some fantasy
sounds good to me base brown duncan
right next to sunglasses and bass brown
duncan breakdown cushion
raspberry one thank you for the pinky
hi mama me and my friends are building a
minecraft world and i was wondering if i
could build a cafe restaurant in the
world of course a bunch of people have
been doing that actually
i would use designs from the ones if
built and all control of the restaurant
will be given to you
i can't be there you gotta you gotta
well
uh they're on your own but you're
welcome to build one i've seen
some people build like like rebuilds the
kfps that i've built i've also seen
people build like better versions
improved versions
i've seen people build like completely
original kfbs as
well
so whatever you want uh you're also
welcome to show it to me
some people had some really nice nice
creations before
okay okay
oh by the way wait now i forgot it again
ah i wanted to
i wanted to talk about it and the sliver
dot io stream
but then i got probably killed or
something but
did you see uh
[Music]
did you also get bamboo guys by that one
from oviedo acting as me
and then the other one acting as cali i
woke up okay
and i i opened my twitter
and i see i see this message
and i'm like queen but but i see the
retweet from cali
and and her like actually replying to it
and being like
what what did she write
that was ridiculous um
okay i found it okay so
it's
when i first saw the first thing i saw
was kelly replying
to me supposedly me
writing to cali who said i love kiara me
writing to her oh my god i love you too
callie and i mean no wait i didn't write
that and then her
writing to dad i apologize because
however you were deceived
that was the first thing i saw was like
it
did ina log into my account or something
what but then the funny thing is
kelly replied to that telling me i was
deceived but
she was the one who was deceived i mean
i loki was deceived too but
but i uh before i could actually react
to it and have an
embarrassing moment like she did
oh my god she she fought
that dad's chiara but i mean with
how many i wonder how many likes and
retweets that had
uh before because when it has like a lot
of retweets and likes it
it seems legit because it must be like
yeah
only the real kiara gets that many likes
on a little tweet right
oh my god that was that was very
uh funny her being like i apologize
quesadilla however you were deceived and
she thinks like she's cool or something
because she's telling me i got to see
but in reality she got deceived
oh man
i just saw kelly student didn't know
what was going on you just saw it now
she realized it later yeah
you got us that's such a such a simple
prank
but you got us with that both of us but
i mean i saw it in the morning and i was
immediately like that's not me
but i was still confused i was like how
how did that person whoever wrote that
did i get hacked like from
for one second because i was literally i
just woke up
i was like did i get hacked huh yeah bit
seems like someone who's nice though if
they're if they hack me and what they
write
is i love you too callie that's pretty
nice of them
so i guess it's not dangerous let's go
back to sleep whatever
no i didn't i didn't go back to sleep
though
deceive section
that was funny oh my god okay
anyway the zero six sanctitions
thank you for the red the time
but what do i see
your message says ina i love you can you
marry me
joke okay since you had a joke there
okay
but i think that was the moment when
inna was on my call yesterday oh that
was fun like hearing him was even though
it was not a collab it's fun that she
jumped in like that that was nice over
there
i mean i would i would if i i i get
i get the i get the idea of you wanting
like or anyone wanting ina to marry them
i get the idea
what can't you someone use my name to
confess it you know it wasn't me please
believe i'm not dd
no it's okay it's a joke anyway joke
it says joke here don't worry don't
worry i get you
thank you thank you
melon search thank you for red super
chat wow this is the best collab since
your last club
yeah but my last collab
was was that not the uh
uh what was my last collab i mean that
wasn't even a collab but
i was gonna cool up before that
[Music]
was it and then
how can i top those collabs though
man every collab is a banger isn't it
collabs are fun
well thank you search i'm glad you
enjoyed it
thank you hope you enjoyed it even after
inna was gone though
thank you very much for coming by thank
you
intentionally left blank but it's not
completely bunk
you don't have to spam that i'm glad
that you came from the future and
telling me
that i will marry kelly but you don't
have to spam it
thanks thank you thank you
[Music]
emoji cap
the character cap use it use it all out
please i beg of you
don't
another blank one which isn't really
blank i see i see i see
mr cass big thunderstorm freddie jackson
20 thank you for red super chat
yeah there's a lot of there were a lot
of new super chatters
is that is that i'm actually surprised
because i think
once inna was in my call
instantly the taco duchess
showed up in masses why did you where
did you guys
instantly come from
from the discord or what how did how did
instantly
all the taco batches show up
that was quite impressive because it
wasn't even announced or anything
from the voids it wasn't even announced
and you made your way to my super
to my uh stream and my super chats
hmm so i'm just gonna assume that these
new people
that i haven't seen before are from ina
just assuming i might be wrong but thank
you anyway
thank you
freddie jackson so you're new but you're
welcome to stay thank you very much for
your support
hope you liked it hope you enjoyed it
len yoshida
happy birthday james mcfee duncan
black friction doctor seven center
[Music]
thank you how funny would it be if this
one sent instead of all the blues i
tried
that wouldn't happen though lol can you
imagine youtube is supposed to attack
well it did actually interesting
are you really trying to send a bunch of
blue ones and i didn't send what was
wrong yesterday what was what was the
problem with youtube
where are we in the chat
[Music]
google payments was down oh
interesting do i not have slow mode on
why are so many people spamming
best 3d model i've ever seen thank you
huh
mode is not on interesting
let me turn it on
how many seconds do you want everyone
uh usually i'm very nice to you and i'll
give you five but you know what i'm
gonna give you
i'm gonna give you eight today
eight seconds what you're gonna do
with that oh [\h__\h] you're a member well
then you're not affected
thank you so cruel oh my god
how mean surprised there's
a still so many people watching this
super chat reading stream
um
[Music]
oh low 57
due to the low population in the region
kiara will be attempting to bring the
numbers back up as per kfe regulation
subject population growth section
ca2 kiana will forcefully breed the
villagers
that that was that was not forcefully
they had a choice
they could have just said no
i didn't force anyone
i put them in the room and i gave them
bread
i gave them a warm home safe home
didn't do anything didn't do anything
bad
yeah actually yeah thank you for the
congratulations like if you think about
it this is our first
new outfit
[Laughter]
it's that's like making freaking history
the first
new outfit that whole ibm gets is
freaking
wealthy left i mean no problem with that
they're freaking cute
but would you have thought that that
would be our first
new outfit holy
prank yes i mean
this is gonna be fun to use every now
and then i'm gonna be like okay today
i am wealthy kiara
today i am this
what will i mean tomorrow
chippy yeah it's like a chippy that's
pretty cute
and while we made the the the art of
course i don't know who rigged it
i asked but i didn't get a reply i'm not
sure who really did
once i know i will let you know
because uh credit where credit is due
right i like to give people credit where
the
where it's supposed to be
[Music]
uh two it's not like only today oh wait
then it's big
rigger i think they posted it on twitter
oh what
did they pull ah two idiots
i did oh he post it on twitter huh
ah so you guys know it before i knew it
cool
i just knew that we were working on it i
didn't know who was working on it
[Music]
did you cut your hair no i didn't what
did you cut your hair something's
different
and i wonder what it is
nice neck crack
it must be yeah i think what you're
thinking is that i don't have my
feathers that's the only thing that
changed and maybe my belt
and maybe the eyebrows but other than
that i'm completely the same as always
that
same size same boobies
same maybe same eye eye color eye color
you can't see it
look closer my eyes are purple
seem a little shorter that's maybe some
kind of
problem with uh the angle and the
perspective
but i'm still the same size hmm
low fps and the low bit rate that's what
it does to me
sometimes
it's so cute though so
cute i love
i love that face i love the angry face
yeah what do you want huh it's kind of
this face reminds me a lot of gouda
that because that's how her anger face
looks like
actually it really does it looks exactly
like that
good on you
it's good as face good as angry face
it really is oh my god i like this
place too but i've never said that why
would i use it
fish
i just love it okay continuing
bristol has big sunken
thank you thank you thank you thanks
doll thank you for red zubat
[Music]
but i think super just finally works for
me now anyway it's nice to come back to
another two
minecraft stream review as always i'm
here with a super chat and i hope you'll
enjoy the playing the game and chatting
with us
thank you thank you thank you for um
waiting
and going for the trouble of youtube
messing things up thank you
thank you even though it didn't work at
first you didn't give up thank you for
your support i appreciate
that very much to everyone else as well
who was trying and trying to get that
super chat come through
thank you it means a lot to me
yeah never give up never surrender yeah
where's your shades
ah okay okay i'll show you my shades
you want me to put one put on my shades
again okay this time this time i'm gonna
do it right
there we go oh wow
hey what up how are you doing
cutie what you doing in this city
are you new in this town huh
could i take you out for a little drink
some dinner
and some dessert
i'm winking right now you just can't see
it
wink wink wink
continuing
[Music]
thank you you're spoiling me thank you
good job thank you was that close to the
end of the
the end of the stream i wonder when i
already got it done did you see the
update that i posted on twitter though
where you saw that pretty much every
every bed was filled up with a villager
i also started a carrot field
and it's much much easier than those uh
the wheat with the bread the carrots are
yeah
much easier so we got we got a huge
wheat farm and a huge uh
carrot farm as well the villagers are
basically stuck
stacked on top of each other no they all
have their own bed okay
and then you play carol's whispers yelp
well thank you jesus again kissing for
you thank you for your support
thank you so much
on campus
oatmeal cookies and i also gave a bunch
of them a joke a joke
a job a job i gave a lot of them a job
so there's uh
we got some fishermen and we got some
butchers
and mesa masons and so on
uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah
they're probably all [\h__\h] but oh well we
got some stuff going on
mason is that not what it is
comedian village i gave them a joke now
they're comedians
just joined the stream and this looks
cute thank you welcome if you're
confused then that's okay everyone's
confused
uh oatmeal cookies and rice of freedom
and so begins slippery slope towards
human experimentation in minecraft as
expected of a proud employee of usaken
i'm proud of you pickle no
i'm doing good things jesus
duncan
this was not towards the end this was
when i got the second villager into the
village
thank you for the pinkie grass an
ancient grandma to chat but just
a young baby to an immortal phoenix and
endless literal personification of death
p.s the reason super chats went down
earlier was because google payment was
done aha
well thank you interesting yeah any
grandma to me is just baby
true
[Music]
foreign
of this thing here was made by the same
person who made subaru
uh live today so we're all connected
again that means now that i have also
indeed if i'm like this and i'm also
half sister to them
if i go back to my normal form then
we're not top sisters anymore
and some
[Music]
any more recommendations for netflix
i i personally still got the
recommendation that i didn't follow
through with uh the the one with the
chess
and i didn't watch it yet because like i
i
i used to like like deep shows as well
now i'm done with community i'm done
with community
i'm watching parks and rec now that's
not even not even on netflix but
i used to like yeah deep shows as well
but for a while now whenever i take the
time to watch netflix or something like
that
i feel like i need something funny and
and and
not happy something something light
and so that's why i've been re-watching
the office
and parks and rec and community and all
that kind of stuff
that's not the only kind of genre that i
like but
i just i need something light
that i don't have to think too hard and
focus too hard on
your friends of course all of those i've
watched them all
by now well if you haven't i don't know
have you watched um
umbrella kind of yeah that was really
good that's on that's there too if you
haven't watched umbrella academy watch
it that's not really comedy it's like
fantasy drama
pretty good though
arrested development yeah that was so
funny too the good place i watched that
one so that was good too yeah
modern family i watched a lot of it
but i i don't i don't like it that much
it's a bit tacky to me
no i still didn't watch brooklyn 99
[Music]
i think i have to get to that malcolm in
the middle is something that
um i watched i watched along when i was
a lot when i was younger because it was
always like in german of course it was
always in
on tv they always showed it on tv so i
watched like a [\h__\h] ton of episodes when
i was younger
but like mixed like it was never in the
right order
so recently a while a long while ago
recently a long while ago i started
re-watching it in
english in the right order of episodes
and it was pretty interesting then
then eventually i stopped uh
the the rewatch marathon thank you for
reminding me i need to continue i
i stopped because i think i think
because i changed location and then my
ip
didn't let me watch it anymore even
though i bought it on amazon
i think that's what what happened
awesome i'm still waiting for young
sheldon to get new episodes
shouldn't they be coming soon i'm
waiting and waiting and waiting and
waiting
and also this is not on netflix but i'm
also still waiting and if you haven't
seen it and if you have hulu you need to
watch
the handmaid's tale
handmaid's tale is so
good i said it before but it's also so
so devastating
that's that's the most devastating show
that i've
ever seen like after i told you guys
before but after each show
after each episode i need to go
into cat therapy and forget about
life i it's so heavy so dark
it's it kills me every time
kills me every time oh oh oh fun
fun one uh what's it called again uh um
um mrs maisel
um what's it called again
seriously why young why not it's so
funny i like it it's cute
yeah my whistle marvelous mrs mazel i
hope that a new season comes soon they
obviously
obviously have issues filming the new
season
because of obvious reasons i hope
they will bring it out soon and i hope
it will be good like
for both mrs maisel and handmaid's tale
i've been waiting for the new season and
it's been delayed so much because of the
the sea thing
and both of the shows work a lot with
with big
big groups of people so
i just wonder how they're gonna do that
and i hope it's not gonna be like
like losing too much of its charm
because they have to adapt to the
current situation
um i really hope so
because i don't i don't want these
masterpieces to be ruined
ah anyway continuing
[Music]
punishment
okay have a new idea
for the usual room because we like to p
we like to punish people in the usual
room
how about we punish them with some bird
puns
endless birds and dad puns they just
have to listen to them
continuously and eventually
they repeat it themselves because we ran
out of
new ones nice addition to the usual room
yay
thank you for giving me that idea
opportunity thank you
please i'll do my job properly please no
you can't run away approved
i wait
there we go
[Music]
you made it real hard for me to read
that i was about to spell it out from
the other side
he turned his name around
spawn flyer down question arnold
robinson
[Music]
kfb that free word should have new
meaning for all of us today we can't be
consumed by our pretty differences
anymore we will be united in our common
interest
oh i continues you will once again be
fighting for our freedom
not from tyranny oppression or
persecution but from inaffection
we're fighting for our right to live to
exist oh no it continues even more
and should we win the day today kfp
declared in one voice
we will not go quietly into the night we
will not
vanish without a fight we're going to
live on we're going to survive
that slide two rats take a chance
thank you i'm not sure what led you
to this speech
but it's very inspiring aspiring
independence day what was it was it
independence day
somewhere in some country
[Music]
well how did you
get where where was in
from a movie
ah
from a movie i don't know that movie
oh thank you
thank you thank you very much for the
support for all those pinkies come
together to two red super jets
so that's why you deserve some kisses
thank you
fanny duncan kristoff san cashion small
what did the man say when he found three
ducks in his mailbox
bill's bill's bills
what i don't get that one
hopefully the others do so that you
don't get
that so that you don't feel so down duck
bill
because ducks have bills
ducks beaks are called bills oh
oh i didn't know that ah then it's funny
joseph diaz duncan
[Music]
just showed up but the stream gave me an
idea carefully brand soap blend called
the bird bath
i i'm not sure if i want to
build something like that but thank you
sounds like a good
great idea
what's a soap bad chia is where people
wash themselves with soap
and then they drop the soap and i don't
know what happens afterwards
oh my god base brown donkey shirt
aperture engineering duncan baseball
baseball language and baseball thank you
i'm also never gonna
give you help thank you ah
look looking for the top-down kitchen uh
sixty-seven thousand fastest screenshot
in the west junction
i think
[Music]
thank you where's your dad swinging for
the pinky
breaking the eyes of girls comes
naturally for you huh one might say
takanashikiya
is uh czech magnet but
that's a good super chat that's that's
really good
thank you i like that one
lovely bag
[Music]
committing war slash human rights crimes
with chiara
what the hell i'm not doing anything
like that
[Applause]
i'm glad you're supporting me but don't
spread slander like that
people people will get it wrong
thank you black [\h__\h] [\h__\h] version
friction thank you for your support
we will be we will be successful with
this as we have seen where we're already
successful we're gonna grow bigger and
bigger
but now we will not do anything anything
bad
that's all good stuff
weird champagne
[Music]
i love you kiara you're my favorite
youtuber today is april fool's day
so what are you trying to tell me tai
chi that that's joke
i think it might be true though because
you're always here
i'm gonna give you the benefit of the
doubt okay
[Music]
you're just you're just trying to
confuse me because you're shy
that must be it thank you tai chi
you're you're you're pretty cool too
you're pretty cool yourself
mostly kids after this thank you mr
rajeev
thank you for the pinky i just got off
of work was busy in the meeting since
you were quacking those birch
yolks but i have to say
they were like poultry in motion
what thanks for the laughs i love you
are you goofy comedian well thank you mr
z i'm glad you're appreciating some good
comedy because nowadays comedy out there
it's not the same as it used to be right
but here i go with my bird puns
totally everything original not being
taken from google
at all just kidding disclaimer i did not
write any of those jokes myself
not at all
the only one i made up myself and then
uh that i am
proud of which is my best creation i've
ever
ever created is
two ghosts walking to a bar
why because they're looking for
booze
[Music]
i'm so proud of myself with that one
that i made that one up myself but i
wonder i wonder if that already existed
because i i swear i made it up myself
but i wonder i feel like something like
that most of it someone must have
thought about about
off that one before right
[Music]
20 40 68.
thank you for red super challenge
writing some nice
nice words there huh i see ya let's read
let's read what yaga had to say
just wanted to tell you how much i love
you
you're at your best when you're having
fun with whatever you're doing watching
you overcome your struggles makes me
really proud for no good reason
but keeping keep doing your best thank
you
even when i'm teasing you i still care
about you having fun i hope you
understand that and can
have fun with it too don't be afraid to
push back when needed
remember you're the boss around here and
you can act like it
no one is perfect and i don't claim to
be any different remember that no one
expects you to be either
we're often our own worst critics and
you being on camera in front of so many
people doesn't help a situation
my thoughts on this and more are too
lengthy for anything but a letter so
i'll try to send one soon
if it passes genma screening please
then i hope it will get there by a
birthday but who really knows right
yeah i mean if you send it soon enough
it should it should make it the question
is when will it make it to me
and then april fool's day isn't for many
hours for me
so this wasn't a prank or anything
thanks for providing us with so much
entertainment over these past few
months who knows what the future holds
but i hope for many more
thank you thank you so much i also hope
for many many more
yeah well thank you for all the support
there's there's tough times but
uh sometimes it's it's a bit hard but
i'm able to overcome it because of you
guys so thank you
thank you yagalu as well
thank you thank you for all the sweet
words looking forward to your next
letter
and to many many many more moms together
with you and all the others
i'm gonna do my best and hope to not
disappoint you thank you very much
[Music]
thank you big big dunk
why can't i me can i leave the basement
yet no because
i'm still here now it's my time to shine
right now stay where you are it's my
time to shine
you're right i'm just a tundra and
you're cuter than smoothie and chunky
it's finally your april fool's in
australia right please donate juice to
yoga he already got them
one more for him
you said i'm allowed to do so yesterday
well okay no i mean you're allowed to be
in the chat that's okay that's okay
but not here on the screen right now no
it's my time to shine
anyway uh so this literally is saying
that you're not
sunday and i'm not cuter than smoothie
and
i don't understand
i don't know which one it is
[Music]
already
and no texture of it so i don't know
what to say but thank you for your
support thank you
thank you very much for the generous
donation
it takes two uh i've answered this
before um
i want to yes we are probably
going to play it sometime soon when
we're both not so busy
we already have uh permission so that's
not the problem
it's just a problem of time now we will
see
[Music]
yeah stop being cute thank you all so
far
your super adorable lovely thank you for
everything you do for us even your
smallest fingers precious
i wish the time we spent together with
neverending to serve the world and even
more
from the bottom of my sim part i love
you
so sweet thank you
that's so sweet thank you thank you
now many many confessions what's going
on and why is everyone
what happened in the minecraft stream i
didn't i didn't really do
talk much about anything emotional or
dramatic
where did all of that come from
you just you just wanted to say i love
you that's
cute i love you guys too
let me take out my glasses
let me think of my glasses to convey you
my true feelings
one second uh
there we go
oh my god i took off my glasses and i
disappeared completely oh my god
[Music]
i love you too
i love you i love you all very much
thank you for being so nice to me
thank you okay
it's nice that my full body fits on the
screen so nicely honestly couldn't do
that normally
now
thank you thank you i think that's maybe
a red super chat
maybe not sure yeah i love you
everything you do has
a unique charisma on you as a person are
wonderful please continue to be yourself
and brad in our day
sorry for my bad english kiana bestopolo
ah who is apollo you're a freaking polo
well thank you for your super chat and
your support
thank you very kind of you
thank you i will i will try my best to
stay myself
thank you hope you're enjoying the
streams
thanks for being part of the cave beacon
[Music]
eh kryptonite pro bowl lands dankeshen
daisy
thanks for the pinky sorry about jv's
offer was
too attractive for us we'd love to stay
dazed i didn't expect you to betray me
like that
we'd love to stay but we just can't get
by anymore only using the local
larp chapters catapult to try to launch
chickens into orbit
what
no more super jets till after four or
four go man i'm sorry so you're gonna
stay like this in jfp
and keep me with this feeling of
betrayal
wow okay
i didn't think it was someone like that
daisy
what exactly is jfb uh that's some old
lore
ah let me explain so kfb is kia
frank phoenix and then and then there
was a
a person uh a viewer in in
in my stream who created jfb
as a joke and because the j
stands for janitor because that person's
title you know how everyone has like
titles who still have they're like okay
if we something something kfc taste
tester for example okay every fire truck
and thought and then there was a
there was a care for janitor and for
some reason that janitor suddenly was
like uh
so he decided to make his own company
and and rebel against me
and try to destroy me so he's been
spreading like
jfp propaganda since forever
it's quite a while ago recap of the
first season
anyway continuing sloth of shadows down
kitchen
what is going on keanu thank you
so much for spreading love around the
world including minecraft
since you were peeking at the villagers
doing woohoo you strike me as a phoenix
who would have hd recordings of the
action
what the [\h__\h] is this money enough for a
copy
warrior is unite what
i don't are you
what
what what
i mean do you i hope you mean you want
you want recordings up
of what's happened in minecraft but it
was literally on stream so just record
that yourself
um
[Music]
turn my turn my youtube archive to the
highest setting that's hd enough we
can't get more hd like that
thank you thank you though
i know you must be embarrassed right now
also no i don't know what that word
means to me it sounds like voyage
but don't tell me what it means i don't
even want to know
i've heard of it before but to me it
means voyage
thank you for the pinky thanks for the
stream attention thank you oh we're out
we're at the end
thank you for all thank you soon thank
you
brian hitch now so thank you that's it
with the minecraft superchat thank god
i need to i want to this is just a
gorilla stream i don't want it to be
like ages long oh my god
we're gonna zoom for the next one
okay next super chats are uh a mix of
this stream and the premieres okay
it's really mixed at the beginning so
don't mind that
i'm just gonna zoom through them so
let's go
[Music]
what is that a poem and i live as i live
out each peaceful day deep in my soul
oh i know i can stay so i wish i had so
i wish i could hide away
full time to want to love keep cruel
faith at bay don't ever take back your
kind hand lest
precious love slip away like a time
stand only we will know
all that was lost scars that we can't
erase show us life's true cost
open the door and walk away never give
in to the call of yesterday memories
that made those days sublime
this ruined house and tom's stolen time
fire them oh come on
reach for my hand and sew away into the
dawn oh i wish i could stay here in
cherished house and peaceful days i feel
that ends up dawn knowing time between
that that's
fire and blunt
we finally have a game that everyone can
play at the same yes same time
also looking forward to your stream
today and don't forget to get enough
rest thank you i got enough rest
actually i
was awake very long but today i'm going
to try to
uh not be awake that long thank you
for supporting us number
oh
[Music]
congratulations i just want to ask you
an important question do you remember
kelly
who's cali
[Music]
thank you i got something back and
who smells crispy that has squishy flies
and makes a good wake up
love your new outfit you spin me right
round very right around like a record
baby right round round
love and enjoy the cool have you a great
thank you you've got that
that description from uh who who wrote
that again that description that
specific description i don't remember
well thank you though i hope you had fun
let's bring more jackpots soon
ah wow is it really me who's training
that's fun thank you guys let's tweet
more tweet
tweet tweet tweet your birds aren't ya
tweet more
[Music]
thank you isn't it great that this is
our first new outfit i think it's ironic
and funny but i love it
uh let's see what the future brings
though um thank you thank you so much
for your kind donation and tai chi
always being there thank you so much
jeremy stewart duncan amarillo offering
auf wiedersehen tickets monkey thank you
thank you the pinky
oh my god what hi can i receive some bad
news from my doctor he says i'm not
actually a monkey
i'm devastated by this news and i must
know now go on a soul certain journey
even though i'll be traveling my heart
will always be with you hey
happier april first doesn't mean that
you're going on a break and not coming
back right
right right right oh thank you i'm
i'm sad that you're not a monkey i feel
quite bamboozled as well
i hope you can't return to monkey soon
thank you
intestinal clouds
uh
[Music]
in your hand are very cute thank you
you know exactly what you did there the
platform
[Music]
okay i'm getting dizzy too uh please
let's bounce
thank you thank you if you guest also
have a new outfit then you might be able
to make it work without throwing so much
attention
well i mean aki separa has a lot of new
outfits but i've seen that before and i
just feel like it would
just be too weird to have me in this i
like if i had like a normal new outfit i
think that's okay to use but this one is
just like
look at me and laugh at me and talk
about me that's what it says
if i'm with someone else in the
collaboration that that person has gen
like somewhat normal outfit and then
there's me
if it was like i don't know whatever
like me wearing uh some
other new outfit that i think would be
okay
get what i mean i think you guys
understand what i mean
i'll use it in other situations of
course thank you
i'm feeling sick but probably just
because i haven't eaten anything
help let me t pose
okay but i'm gonna get through this
quickly and then
go eat some food
lexington the lion thank you james
brewing
the new model seems perfect for an
investigation portion of whole talk
you can't ask me the real questions not
sure what you would imagine under that
but you're welcome to tell me more about
it on twitter
and static snakes
the super chat that's not the red one i
think the later one was the red one
thank you
very of the success
[Music]
thank you happy april fool's thank you
the new office cute i want to push you
like this ah
that would be nice
thank you thank you thank you i mean
even if we don't sell anything maybe you
can make it yourself
i know there's many people out there who
make like pushes on their own
plushies and it doesn't doesn't look bad
i think it's easy
easy to learn so we tony thank you soon
gd duncan thank you for the pinky love
from female fanbase thank you love back
to you
thank you very much hey kristoff thank
you
thank you thank you
lunchbox function the dominion city i'm
thank
that check my twitter joke was got like
yeah i think i was actually thinking of
writing something else
but i was like uh i might get cancelled
for that one
so i went with the one of the twitter
one that one was okay i think
it was implying that all my dudes are on
twitter
anyway so just check my freaking twitter
i had an even funnier one but probably
not everyone would have found that one
funny
pieces without picks without my hat i
guess they do exist on twitter yeah
oh my nose
and so residences thanks for the pinky
kiana and her gang
struggling to find her is peak lesbian
moment boss please make it easier for us
for trying our best to feed through
thank you i didn't make it easy enough
don't you think
typhon thank you soon
what are you calling
small kid
okay scrolling i refresh so let me
scroll
oh god oh no
still so many
okay let me let me let me real quick go
to the kitchen and turn on the oven so i
can put in the lasagna all right when
i'm done one second
ah wash my nose
okay okay okay okay
okay i'm not i'm just not not going to
touch my
face anymore
so where did i stop
where did i stop
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
yep okay base brown duck action type 91
thank you soon gg duncan ready steel
duncan
i'm gonna skip the the break super chats
where you guys are just flushing
hope that's okay
dammit i touched my face again
what's going on
i've been your fans since day one with
my psychic
psycho psychiat psychiatrist
said watching you was making me crazy
so sadly today i have to give you up i
hate
i hate to let you down and i'd never
want to run around and desert yeah i
don't hope it doesn't make you cry for
that soon
so i'm iraq and assuming that that is a
joke because i would be so sad
that that's just joe grant i'm not gonna
okay i see a heart in chat so i think
it's a joke
it better be a joke
thank you
don't listen get get a different
psychiatrist
i'll be your psychiatrist never going to
make you cry well then you better stay
brian hits the vacation friendly
neighborhood lesbian dance and there we
go there that's where the lesbian is
we were looking for a lesbian
that sounds so fun i'm [\h__\h] up but
what can i do it's just her name
thank you worm of viti danger
what
[Music]
to be my girlfriend you are kind
diligent and daring wait a minute this
is not gemma's channel
damn it oh hi danger this is my
resignation letter
i sense that i will have danger after 22
months
well guys where is that
you guys don't understand april fools
you're supposed to clear it up at the
end and be like
in german or whatever has april fools in
english you're supposed to clear it up
at the end
say hi how funny joke ha ha
you forgot about that a lot of you
forgot about it
christoph sunkish and radiant crimson
duncan jesus morales
sit back
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
lucky i have to sing your adorable new
outfit i achieved enlightenment i
realized
that all i need for happiness is armpits
because of this i'm going on a journey
to the far east to train myself and seek
out the perfect armpits to worship
farewell vaquiana
[Music]
you're leaving me for armpits but what
about my armpits are they not good
enough for you
i'm holding my arms up like this for you
and you just
leave me like that canvas nights why am
i holding up my arms for the whole time
huh tell me you see those armpits
are they not good enough for you huh
look i'm dabbing at the same time
oh you also forgot to put something
at the end to let me know it's a joke
sad dab
italy do you know anything regarding
italy of course i've been to italy
uh a couple times probably like maybe uh
ten times
nine times eight times not sure
something like that
not basically i want to go there again
[Music]
italian in school but very specific uh
job specific italian
and i already forgot most of it like we
didn't get far anyway
this new kia is better i like this model
more
just kidding it is scary and i want to
run around and we're really running
away in here okay what's scary about
this
baseball i'm like a shooting alexander
thank you for all right super chat
let's let's hear your your excuse for
making me run into you
never gonna give you i'm never gonna let
you down never gonna run around in
dessert you're never going to make a
crown that we're going to sing about and
we're going to tell i don't hurt you but
i guess
the last sentence here does not imply
here ha ha
damn i mean all right just kidding
you're my sunshine
did you just say zama milo to me
did you just say zama miro to me
ellis nana you are going to the usual
asana that's enough use your room
see you in two weeks two week sentence
usual room bye bye
that's enough killed me two times in
sliver
and now you think you're funny or what
you think you're funny
no what the [\h__\h] i'm afraid since xander
has been offered full scholarship for
his future education and promise of not
being eaten
sand is now a jfp baby how do you guys
even
eat you don't even have proof that they
will give you anything
else
you guys don't even have proof like what
did he get did he hand you the cash
straight away but it might be fake cash
whatever
navy boy now get your brand hits
[Music]
oh anyone do you want a white kiss
oh geez
can't help it huh
touched my face again
might not get very wide though
looking for the job mwah
i don't know it really it really doesn't
have that much of an effect
because look it's just i'm wide
to begin with
it doesn't doesn't do much
it's the only thing that's much
different is the voice
that um i hope you're happy with that
thank you
thank you very much thank you soon for
appreciating me in all forms
and sizes that i come with
black friction magazine shift shift
function jump up zero
zero zero eight dancing thank you for
the pinky
oh no stop it with all the resignations
i hereby give you my resignation is
carefree designated robin will instead
work for jfp as their rubber their work
conditions are much better for robbers
instead of beating me up and putting me
in the usual room they just hide under
the counter
thank you for the pinky you better come
back i mean in your title it still says
kfp so i guess you already changed it
back that's that's good okay
thank you nutella
jfp dynasty chef sorry kiana i'm leaving
to join people who appreciate who i
really am people who don't call me a
fake new channel
starting today i'm a part of the jv
family thanks for the good time
uh-huh okay imposter venom snake danger
thank you for before being so kind
iron hard donkey soon i'm proud to work
my fourth day as a cafe employee but is
it okay if i flood the whole restaurant
with ducks
but you're not actually resigning you're
actually still saying you can't feel oh
my god i'm gonna cry
what procedure should be taken if i said
incidents would occur
if sad incidents would occur asking for
a friend it's like yes
okay no food no problem you can do
whatever you want okay
and just stay with give me
sir dogs gonna wild function
yes do it bringing him over 11 dungeon
stopping him because i was told that the
plan was successful does this mean i can
change his disgraceful name
and profile picture now
also can we acknowledge the effort it
took to convert
my proper picture to jfp course
yeah i've noticed some color changes but
i wasn't sure like what
what was going on there but thank you
welcome back
alvido duncan
whatever whatever
[Music]
haven't heard from you in a while thank
you for the red super chat
wow i missed the stream because i didn't
know
it would be so early but i just came to
turn in my resume
huh
resignation to friendship ended with
kiara
now okay why are you
he's my best friend i guess it's yes i
guess
it's still me but i know something feels
wrong
well thank you
it was nice seeing you again and now
you're resigning again bye bye
[Music]
i want to hear small can i read my name
there
[Music]
and i have to get back to work so keep
having fun with april fools this part is
no joke i have tons of fun watching your
streams
so keep it up jump you're doing great
and i'm looking forward to more
next time you see an ant you can just
smash it
don't worry the last and i've i've seen
i smashed it yeah
i did it thank you thank you
thank you i i hope i i honestly think in
the new apartment there will be no ants
and no flies nothing this will be a
fresh one
foreign
anyway looking forward for foo for
flower to the new
new apartment yeah
you'll get ants if you eat at your desk
okay you know what
i i am guilty of doing that
but in the new apartment i will
i will uh i will
eat in the kitchen
yes i will try let's see let's see if
i'm actually gonna do that
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
m
i'll give you a kiss
thank you thank you thank you for your
support
and your generous donation do i stay
well
hope you like this new me what do you
think huh you should have
if you didn't know what to write in your
super chat you could have just written
about what you think about this new look
was it so hard to think of anything
black friction that lcl smelled like a
unknown i've been missing some of the
streams lately because of the time zone
yeah
sorry to my cea now i set it on purpose
now
to my cea fans
i'm so glad i catched it today collab
and this stream it was so much fun thank
you thank you all so far
sorry for accidentally killing you it's
okay thank you
thank you for coming by and
participating in the in the sliver that
slippery io stream so it's fun to play
with you guys we're actually
uh tomorrow i'm taking the day off
ranked
and then uh and then mario kart
playing with you guys as well and then
paul talk so the next stream will also
be
with viewer participation i hope the
internet connection will be fine i have
a
i have a internet cable for the switch
now as well
i bought one from nintendo it's funny
how
[\h__\h] expensive that is and i looked
up like a similar cable
which was much cheaper but in like it's
basically the same cable but they said
that it doesn't work with nintendo
with switches
i see what you did there nintendo
you will only let us use
in the alarm cable internet on your
device if we buy an extra adapter
but only one from nintendo
i see i see yeah the ethernet adapter
i mean it's okay i bought it it's okay
i just wonder why that is not liking
like
included from the beginning
uh or like why it doesn't it would be
cool if the switch just had a
like a slot for an ethernet cable to
begin with
just let's put it right in there from
the beginning
i was actually so surprised to realize
it doesn't have one
oh well uh
at least there's an adapter for anything
melody mania just some guy with a
mustache
thank you for another red super chat
that i already reacted to but once again
thank you
don't worry don't worry it's all good
thank you so much
impossible snake thank you not a joke
thank you
i love you
i'm snake too you're snake i'm snake
we both snake the musical boy 93 dungeon
links into the lion dagger
thank you
very much
i'm going to have a fight to death now
over who gets to be your papa
no no no no don't worry don't worry i
mean still like even though welfare drew
this
the design is still you know from
og papa
my dearest
my papa forever
a fart like a shirt bracelet free duncan
uh my hair it uh you actually can see it
uh in my normal usual model if i like
move a bit and scroll out enough you see
it behind my
uh you see it actually uh roughly
it's it's like i would say to to the end
of my
uh what do you call that part uh
shoulder
shoulder shoulder should
shoulder blades yeah
maybe a bit yeah but no somewhere around
there
hmm
thank you for always being so wonderful
i hope to continue to support you and i
would love a smooch for momma
thank you for being so kind to me
please continue i would be happy if you
would continue to support me
as long as i am here thank you so much
thank you for the pinky sorry sorry
couldn't send one the other day but just
want to say thanks for always
brightening up a long day
you're welcome you guys also brighten up
my days thank you
i'm glad i can make your days a little
bit
brighter as well with my streams i'm
just just doing
my job and at the same time
kind of my hobby and
i'm just having fun playing games so i'm
glad that i can be here for you guys
thank you
thank you for watching me without an
audience i would not be here
trevor g duncan
i love you kiara and her life i had an
idea for a collab jack games bundle 4
has a game called monster seeking
monsters you can play with eight people
so holla myth
and jen two id can play together hope to
see you
luna miko and marine be babies be elite
babies
what what
monsters taking monsters of eight people
what kind of game is that and the only
thing i know is that
uh jackpot's party game six has a game
that's like among us
but i guess we could just play the
normal among us anyway i wonder what
kind of game that is uh
it's like you're trying to hook up
together what it's a dating game with
vagina
what
what ah
what's the sticky monster now i get the
title
okay okay
oh okay is it like like a speed dating
thingy
don't like that one personally oh what's
wrong with it
how hot is that like you tried to
convince each other while also deceiving
each other
why would i why would i want to deceive
them and and
and convince them at the same time
we gotta try it out honestly today i was
so confused because that was the first
time
we didn't we didn't even practice any
game we just went right in on the stream
i was so confused i didn't know what was
going on especially
the the drawing game at first i didn't
understand at all
like first it shows you
a theme that you're supposed to draw
like
champ of something something and then
right after
it shows you what someone else drew and
you like draw an
opponent and i didn't understand like
what
and now i understand that that person
also that's what they drew
for their type title that they got
and you don't you won't know what title
they got
anyway that was so confusing to me i
didn't understand it until
like the last round
but then yeah it was fun it was fine i
just barely could think of anything
the pokemon one yeah yeah i got
i was just supposed to uh draw on the
opponent for that pistachio but i didn't
know like
but that was a different one that
confused me even more
but anyway everything was confusing but
it was fun
thank you thank you i will think about
it i think we will have a lot of
jackpots game
collaborations from now on anyway so
yeah lots of fun to come thank you
thank you thank you for your
i'm so sorry please forgive us boss the
super chat thing is real tough i
probably shouldn't even be sending this
why because you're in the usual room now
you look different hello
what do you mean you're not supposed to
be selling this because you sent
ah because you yeah because you said you
need all the rest of your money for
for cali on the fourth of april
oh man yeah you didn't need to send you
didn't need to send the pinky
i mean i guess the chances are are
higher than i would read it
because pinkies and red ones are
guaranteed that i will read them
um oh my god well i mean
it's gonna be fine don't worry daisy
don't force yourself to you know send
heaps and heaps of money really it's not
like
i mean we appreciate the support very
much but please remember it is not
necessary
number one we will not
i'm not not saying that that's what
you're expecting but
maybe this is more of a general thing we
will not love you more or less
depending on how much money you send us
via super chat it doesn't
matter okay we appreciate the super chat
and we will read
as at least i will read your name more
often
and read your texts more often because
that's just i need to i need to thank
everyone properly
but it doesn't mean that you know
i love you more i know you i know you
know it daisy
just kind of got me to that into that
direction generally
um but also
don't feel an obligation to send
millions and millions of monies
to us just because
i don't know it's some special occasion
or even in normal streams just because
you want to say
thank you and so on
i don't want you guys to feel pressured
that's not good
not at all please
is orange your favorite color orange and
i like pastel colors
and i like uh purple and
white depending on like what we're
talking about like if it's if it's
about furniture it might be a bit
different if it's about flowers it might
be a bit different
but if we're speaking really generally i
guess orange purple and
uh and pastel colors
and white
and thank you for the super chats guys
thank you thank you really
i read it i read it
i'm not ignoring you i love city i
love titty i suck it sounds like [\h__\h]
i love titty
oh we had that before though
but you do love them i mean yeah i
appreciate them
very much
[Laughter]
ah my great junior danke sun
evie
are really amazing you're an amazing
person i love watching although i can't
always understand everything but i make
my effort it's worth
the effort for you thank you thank you
so much greetings to brazil
beta alex thank you for the red super
chat
my workplace pulled an april fool's joke
on me by giving a ton of work
how did you tell them how funny they are
i missed everything i just wanted to say
i love you tanjo and i want to thank oh
my god you missed the whole collab and
the review oh my god
that's sad want to thank you for
everything you do
please keeping you this thoughts and
april 1 joke and not my true feelings
i love you too thank you thank you so
much
i hope that work was not too tough
welcome back
work is priority i guess well welcome
back you always you always uh
always have a place to come back to in
my streams thank you
thank you for the membership welcome
congratulations on fully hatching yay
just want to say thank you i love you
and i'm so proud of supporting you
thanks for always putting a smiling face
on us and building this wonderful
community i love kfc and i'm glad i can
be part of it i'll continue to support
you
thank you i'm happy and very glad to
hear that
thank you so much i'm glad that you guys
can find some happiness and enjoyment
from my streams
that's the most important thing the
thing that i'm striving for
in my streams is to make you guys
happy entertain you guys possibly
make you laugh every now and then
so i guess mission accomplished in that
case thank you very much
thank you first time in the livestream
welcome thank you
see you jeremy steven just want to say
i'm also a fan of the tales love series
nice
a favorite one i mean i've spoken about
it a few times uh
i got a couple favorite ones no specific
one
and but tales of cecilia one and two
and berseria might be my favorites
and this barrier slide
and another refresh
i wanna i'm so sorry to say this but i
wanna
end the stream and eat food
tomorrow i'm gonna go for all the
questions from hellotalk if you haven't
sent the question yet you better do it
now
can't guarantee that i will see it
because there's always hundreds and
hundreds of questions
and but tomorrow i will go for all of
them
uh i will take some time
and prepare for the talk and know that
even though it's uh a bit too early
because the stream before that would be
mario kart but i i'm just
tomorrow i have a day off so i want to
get a tomorrow done you
that's better anyway having it done
earlier rather than later i don't want
to get it done like
my lasagna it's not in the oven yet
don't worry i could put it in now though
probably okay
[Music]
when i opened when i opened my
sorry i'm i happened
when i opened my refrigerator freezer
i saw it had some yummy ice cream in
there so i'm looking forward to eating
that ice cream later yum yum yum yum yum
[Music]
say new person thank you
i haven't been able to catch a live
stream in a while but i'm excited i'll
be able i'll be able to catch more going
forward oh
i'm happy to hear that like there's a
lot of people who tell me they'll be
catching less and less because of
working or whatever time zones i'm
happy to hear you're catching more
here's a red superchat to make up for my
absences
potential welcome back i guess thank you
thank you very much
to a fun summer then i guess i hope i
can entertain you well
welcome welcome welcome please enjoy my
streams and thank you for supporting me
thank you soon rando
impossible
is a joke it is a joke also i just
called to say i love you gentle
thank you i'm glad it's a joke i already
forgot about
uh it anyway uh did it say i hate you
goodbye forever
i erased that from my brain no
[Music]
i don't want to hear anything like that
or resignation
no never heard of it it's erased from my
brain
brain no i will remember it forever and
that will i will
i will use it against you i love you
just kidding
i'm getting a bit crazy right now
hungry hungry very hungry
thank you skye nero thank you
sir one on one
[Music]
second
i'll be pursuing my dream of starting my
own fashion franchise please patronize
mojo for right to phoenix mfp
you know what you know what
as long as you're not with jfp that's
okay with me
i'm not even mad
good luck you will not
be more successful than kfb because
that's impossible because we are having
a
monopoly in this industry
and we are winning son
but i will i will i will support your
endeavors
good luck as long as you still come to
my streams every now and then okay
please thank you
james with me thank you thank you for
watching
no substitutes only the best only the
freshest
wait what are we talking about james
i don't get the joke
but james are you here please explain to
me i want to understand what you're
talking about in your red super chat
because otherwise i can't
react to it properly can't be forever
that's it
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for the membership welcome
cute model thank you aren't your hands
tired
no no
carefree plug into the freshly served
yes with a vegan vegan chicken vegan
it's an older advertisement for pizza
only the best ingredient oh
yay ads thank you
thank you
[Music]
hello
brazil i remember the time when i was in
brazil it was really nice
um i want to go again
sometime come to brazil come to brazil
oh god i hear them coming i can't do you
hear them coming too
do we hear them coming they're coming
they're coming come to brazil come to
brazil
oh there they are oh here they are
oh now
i love it thank you thank you for your
support
senior emcee seth thank you very much
careful thank you for red super chat too
all these chickens leaving kfb to us who
choose to stay get a promotion of a
raise and like a new talent more money
would be nice to
you're welcome to give yourself a new
title and you're done
and yes you can give yourself a raise
which only means that you'll be paying
me more so that's okay i mean that's the
logic that's how it works here
you're welcome to give yourself a raise
anytime
because the money that is called
wait i forgot the word for in english
the money that is called
income
is paid to me directly i don't pay you
you know that right you're asking about
the raise knowing that
salary salary
not celery now no veggies
so if you're happy with that go ahead
give yourself as much of a raise as you
want
thank you thank you
i think it's one of the coolest thing
ian has done before going to smoking
thank you i think it's pretty cool too
yeah
um i think it shows uh
humor of the en management that we are
allowed and
we're supported to do that and i
appreciate it it's pretty cool
i'm glad we did something special for
april fools
i want to say thank you to the
management who
picked up that joke idea
you know what okay i wanna
april fool
[Music]
it was me
it was me 17th
december
i posted on in our discord
[Music]
uh that that uh
those wealthy live today's that were uh
animated by
r e and pc
and i wrote uh ah
i wish we could use these lol
live to the rigged wealthies
please let's do it ah
oh my god it was because of me oh my god
oh my god it wasn't me
[Music]
such a long time ago my birth brain is
working so hard but i can barely
remember i think it was me though yeah
it was me
yay
fun yeah
genius
okay continuing where was i'm bronx 819
thank you thank you thank you for the
red super chat again wow
heavily delayed just kidding love you
attention oh thank you i knew you
weren't just kidding but
oh i'm glad you clarified thank you very
much
love you too oh neck crack and dab
dab crab thank you thank you hope you
enjoyed today's
stream bronx
also i'm glad i finally have sunglasses
i noticed that because of your your
uh profile picture being my my kiana
with glasses
icon i'm i'm so happy i can put on like
shades now and be like cool as hell
yeah they add so much like smugness
love it exactly that one
that's it that's the one desert stay
cool duncan
say the greatest thing
there will be no april joke because the
ass output is for me a normal day why
did i read that in
german because i think you're german but
anyway
jackpots was fun hope that we will see
more of that or other games like
what is that butterfly and here are all
of them
if you know that song
[Music]
i know i know that one thank you
see i knew you were uh there's a little
bit of german in there and you're
standing in europe so i'm i'm i'm
a king you are german person
or australian who knows might be
australian might even be switzerish
thank you wow kiana is kind of flat
today excuse me rude do you want a band
do you want to be banned
what's with that avatar oh my god
there's so many people waking up now or
whatever
and coming in now and don't know what's
going on
funny watch the collaboration that we
did on cali's channel
that's where we did the review of our
new outfits
live to be updated
hello i'm switzerish really cool
i've been to switzerland one time i
didn't see much wanna go again
switzerland is so pretty
so uh this is for mario kart oh thank
you 4am for you oh man
your move fixed my sleep schedule a week
ago
that's a good thing i guess i hope you
can watch the archive mp7
i saw that one jordan thank you for the
pinky jordan
thank you no text there so don't know
did you forget to write something
thank you for your support thank you
alex duncan thank you also for pinky you
said i become a millionaire for
investing in carefree after you become a
millionaire
hurry up and become one so i can become
a millionaire
well it's probably going to take a while
until i'm a millionaire
i'll do my best to become a millionaire
starting man thank you i hope
down the line we can get some unique
outfits yes yes definitely
an actual outer review would be
interesting ah sounds cool but not sure
if we can never do that thank you though
i'll see what i can do
rezzy doesn't should not yet not sky
down the shin story corner thank you
so
[Music]
please say this is the last refresh
and then not yet not functioning
shout out to kelly we've known each
other for eternity your heart's been
aching but you're
too tsundere inside we both know what's
been going on i am the book and you're
tsukumi and if you ask me how i'm
feeling don't tell me you're too dead to
see
is this like some quotes from a takamori
fanfiction
or what
oh is that a recruit
no i said takamori rickro
the [\h__\h] is beautiful
we've known each other for eternity
your heart's been aching but your toots
and it doesn't really fit well you gotta
make it over there
inside we both know what's been going on
i am the bookie and your dads will call
me
and if you ask me how i'm feeling
don't tell me you don't get to see
okay ever to do
dancing thank you happy late birthday
[Music]
and we have to be vegan what
you guys don't have to be vegan
i'm i'm not going to eat you
i'm not
back battling back battling i'm never
gonna eat you
never gonna eat you up
never gonna fry you down oh my god
never gonna
[Music]
fill you up with food and then
hurt you okay okay let's make an
original song someday
like that something like that thank you
spanking time no worries there's nothing
to wear please calm down become
come with a k okay people are we good
generator elvis thank you
my daily celery ew i actually don't like
celery
every second for salmon what happens you
want to finish it off with a nice
rainbow
you know what you know what i'm gonna
go i cut out the super jets
so that no one can do something else now
it's nice to have a rainbow at the end
of the stream how
how hopeful and poetic is that huh
and also i just want to end it now
and brown history slime neil duncan and
we747
thank you for a beautiful rainbow
did you wait for the end to do that one
thank you that's very very kind of you
thank you so much for your support
of course i'm using that new appetite
hope you had fun on b757 and everyone
else
and this will conclude today's gorilla
stream which turned out to be longer
than expected
three and a half hours just to play some
sliver and
uh read some super chattels i'll see you
the day after tomorrow uh
to play some mario kart
and i'll see you on twitter if you
haven't follow me on twitter do that
and
and let me help you let me make it easy
for you
[Music]
you know what how about you watch and
heart challenge on youtube here here's
my playlist use it
made it for you guys
play it
please please heck
okay thank you i'm very hungry now gonna
check up on my lasagna beach
lasagna beach
i put it in there because mc was
overseen by a lot of people because i
uploaded that when i was shadow band
and i think that sheep in
um
impersonating cheaper
wait what's monomon in
i forgot the word for it
impressive thinking that cheap
impression was too good to be overlooked
hmm so
okay what happens if i do this
nothing okay cool okay everyone thank
you for watching
and hope you had a fun april fools
thanks to you
thanks to us honestly i have to really
say that this was the best april fools
of my life i've never
done something so funny and awesome so
i'm glad we did that
and let's let's do something funny again
next year i gotta i gotta think of
another geniuses
idea see you
soon follow me on twitter and watch
hashtag vocation
thank you for the support love you as
always um bye
bye and in germany
[Music]
fun
you