guess how many people are left in the
house
oh no okay i have three go in
we go out
three go in
oh
well i'll wait wait
well i mean
i mean uh uh well i don't know which
country are we talking about what
country are we i'm using the number four
whatever which country no it's different
it's nine nine one or whatever ah in my
country it's one four four i think
i have that i have never called
wait i think i think it's one four four
it's like um because okay let me explain
it's actually really cool like i'm so
surprised you guys don't have the same
thing because okay listen listen listen
so um
and uh uh no wait no no no no wait wait
one for four
one for four is the um the thing um the
the one that goes down and and heal you
uh
that's the fire thingy not the fiery
uh ambulance this is because you know
the four looks like a plus and the
the plus is like the crust you know of
the ambulance that's really smart that's
really easy to remember and then there
is a one for free that's the police
because the free free looks like the the
things that the handcuffs you know
that's really really really smart and
then there's uh one two two because it's
like it's it looks like the the thing
where the water comes out from the from
the thing
which deletes the water
understand
this is literally
if i would be put in such a situation
where i finally for the first time in my
life would have to call such a number i
would be like
[Music]
[Laughter]
i'm feeling sick now using water
but don't you think that makes like a
lot of sense that one to two it looks
like uh like the fire
the thing the long thing that looks like
a snake
and then the 133 looks like handcuffs
and 144 looks like the you know
uh
a band-aid or the the thing yeah fire
hose yeah yeah don't you think that's
like really easy to remember
other countries should do it like that
[Laughter]
well what the hell
that's how that's how uh we were told in
in school
yep
you weren't the definition of chaos
that was easily understandable
fire hose
fire hose that that holes there is a
pants in
that's funny
because lie all your pants on fire
now you have
to oh my god my brain is um
i just stop can't stop stop
stop no one can follow your thought of
train you're trying to fight