[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
honestly
hello hello
I'm gonna make me some cheese I bought
some honey
[Music]
oh oh honey
no I don't have a teacup
[Music]
but I have several plastic cups stacked
on top of each other hoping that it's
not gonna be
too hot what do you think guys
oh no let's see how can this work
well also don't have a spoon I have some
plastic cutlery
oh oh this isn't hot
this isn't hot for for our plastic
cup stacked on top of each other works
yeah it works works
[Music]
is this
um
okay that's still too hot
[Music]
um
uh
uh happy to watch live again hello
hello you look really cute thank you
are you angry cause I'm tired I wanna
sleep
I I haven't slept in or like slept as
much as I want to for for a while now I
guess but that's okay I mean
I slept enough in theory and like other
people would say is it that's enough but
I just feel really exhausted because
yesterday I
oh yesterday was
um
yesterday was
tough
um
I
danced for eight hours
and
then
I recorded some more like audio things
speaking of
have you seen
uh a Twitter an 11 just just when I
started the Stream
uh
Valentine's stuff got announced
so in two hours there's a
Valentine's Day with whole Lab English
[Music]
um uh story
thing coming out
um
I wonder if I can
I've never done this before but I wonder
if I can like
um
because I'm gonna end my stream at that
time probably if I can
like lead you guys there how does that
work I still don't know
how does that work wait is that like
um
highlight
how how do you do that
redirect
[Music]
oh
look up radar inside stream ah I don't
see anything
customize ah here it's like a
and then I guess can I put uh the URL no
Valentine
uh
Valentine's Day live
[Music]
ah
I don't have the permission
whole life English has to all of English
has to permit me
I have to like not in the white list me
[Music]
hey who's in charge of the whole live
English Channel
I I I wanna I wanna funnel my viewers oh
one second there's still here
at
[Music]
can you whitelist my channel
and channel so I can read that right
viewers to the
Valentine's Day LOL
mm-hmm
foreign
perms
[Music]
everybody it's nice to nice to finally
know how this works oh my God
but you know my my throat oh
[Music]
person in charge was watching my stream
anyway
and was already on it wonderful
you know I have to say last time I was
here
in Japan recently
uh the air was so dry
and I was like
you know constantly drying out my throat
but at the moment this is not the case
it doesn't really feel dry but my throat
just needs a little time to warm up I
think
I'm actually surprised that it's not
that the air is not so dry I don't know
if it's still the room I'm in or if it
really just got better and like I was
just gone for two weeks still and then
suddenly now it's just decent
[Music]
um
not the throat mask yeah I got those but
I wouldn't say they really worked
[Music]
um
leather and air can change at random
like that
aha
they prepared the villagers for me are
you feeling sick again no I'm not
feeling sick but oh my body is so sore
it's insane
[Music]
the the premiere for those videos is in
two hours right yeah yeah okay
when is
when is Cali streaming
[Music]
ah yeah time white listed
uh okay okay okay
Valentine's
[Music]
but uh wait does that
uh
eventos
if I if I set it down are you already
being redirected now
or will it wait until the end
I I don't want to
probably
okay then let's
I guess let's not do it now but let's
keep it in mind you guys gotta remind me
okay so yeah there's that and uh let me
just check so I don't say anything wrong
but I'm pretty sure it's okay but oh
oh yeah here we go let me show you the
picture
[Music]
oh Susan why why my internet always
buffering
yeah well look at that
uh
Valentine's merchandise yeah thing we
have been preparing for you guys
and it includes acrylic stands of those
illustrations that are very cute as in
like
um Valentine's Idol like outfits yeah
yeah and a button badge
I haven't even what do the button badges
look like I haven't seen them
no no no no no how do they look like
oh there's a image just for my stuff oh
ta-da
that didn't work oh it saved it as a web
page
[Music]
I I
Windows why why aren't triggering me
like this
why are you trying
to tricky
you little [\h__\h]
a little [\h__\h]
everything you gotta do everything on
your own everything has to be
complicated yeah webp what's up
ah yeah the button is cute
yeah and then there's a voice
and a leather I wrote a letter
uh
what did I write I mean I'm not gonna
tell you but
um
I think I think it was a good letter
yeah I hand wrote a letter
um
[Music]
no it's a couple days weeks ago no days
maybe when did I write that I don't even
remember anymore I don't know if it was
this day or last day oh anyway all the
background from the acrylic stand is
cute
um
let me post link
um foreign
[Music]
we kind of went for
um
a more let's just say mature look for me
this time rather than cute I think
there's probably let me see it there's
probably plenty of other cute girls
uh yeah
yeah even cronies pose and face is more
on the cute side yeah
um
the others all just look kind of cute
I don't I don't get the sexy vibe from
anyone Kelly is kind of like cool
let me let me see
Kelly's kind of cool
you know it's a cute and say so Buddha
is obviously just cute
Ahmed is
can't look closer
I mean I wouldn't say it's like sexy
either
[Music]
yeah they are looking looking cute
everybody looking cute oh mommy is cute
[Music]
well you can get a full set too I'll put
the letter let me see is the leather
included like I suppose so
wait so you get it as a paper wonderful
in an envelope oh is that that's like
it's this back design it is like an
envelope I guess maybe
[Music]
it's
a voice different of course
what did I record
[Music]
ah I remember when I recorded
um
everybody's voice is like a situational
individual thing yeah you know what let
me let me put this
foreign
[Music]
can't really read it but oh well
you want to buy all of them they're
really cute aren't they
yeah I'm glad we made something for
Valentine's Day so that's the
merchandise is happening and as I said
the video I'm gonna like I'm gonna lead
you I'm gonna bring you to the video so
don't worry
um I'll move you over there guys at the
end of the stream
um so I'm gonna be streaming for maximum
two hours because I have dance lessons
afterwards and
um
yeah uh I'm exhausted and uh yeah yeah
[Music]
will you survive um I think today
will be uh less tiring than yesterday
because I already know uh dance lesson
for today will be on the easy side
yeah I don't think it will be too
difficult
[Music]
um
I already saw what I'm learning
beforehand and it's I mean I don't want
to sound smug
that sounds mug but
um
yeah okay
I guess let's play uh holy cure sorry
for the late
at least this time people are not
um trying to rip out my feathers because
I'm not playing the game yet and instead
I'm tangenting like last time everyone's
like when is this [\h__\h] playing the game
like
unbelievable
the ball disgusting
[Music]
oh
nothing
[Music]
the reason I'm singing this is because
those lyrics mean how what's going on
what what is the what what why how
for sure
[Music]
foreign
how to make it fit this is I'm so bad at
this
doesn't have to fit perfectly right
okay
let's I bought I used up my money to buy
some stuff and yesterday you know I was
last time I played I played it on um
Studio PC right I didn't play it here
and so I had to like install it again
and like move my save data over and then
first I was like I put it in the wrong
folder I didn't put it in the app data
folder I put it in the game folder
thanks to my membership and then I was
like why is it not working
but just to test it out you know I I
went inside the game and I played uh I
started playing a little bit with Ahmed
just to like create a save file I was
hoping to create a safer because I
didn't see any save file in the game
folder but I guess I was looking in the
wrong place and then
um I just started playing and I just
wanted to play it for five seconds or so
and hoping that that would create a save
file but then it didn't but anyway I
played the whole 20 minutes because I
just couldn't stop myself and
um without that was like a clean game
like no nothing bought from the shop
couldn't even use my special
and I just casually cleared easily with
ease
the normal stage 20 minutes without me
just for a warm-up
I was like ah I guess I'll do the whole
thing I guess I'll try oh
no voice
[Music]
yeah and I would I would
I I would say that it's more difficult
because I didn't have any extra stats
and uh from the shop and so on you know
what I mean don't you agree
just default game it is right yeah but
it didn't feel difficult I I did feel
like you know
uh I was getting Level UPS slowly slower
than you know I should be but
[Music]
I did get up to level 50. uh
interestingly anyway that is now
overwritten because I managed to
eventually figure it out thank you for
telling me reminding me uh how it works
okay is it Kai okay no no you are real
strong with just one weapon yeah well
they're all strong so anyway do you guys
hear you guys don't hear it yet right
um
let's see
uh
slow down
there it is but oh it's so loud
okay
how about now
the only candy I mean I'm still booting
I'm very slowly booting today I'm sorry
I'm so sorry but I didn't want to cancel
the stream either because you know
um
there's a there's a secret I have a
secret guys right now
I am
I'm trying to you know
I'm trying to
go along my schedule properly
because I will not be streaming on the
weekend
[Music]
uh
yeah
pregnant
oh
[Music]
and and there's a reason you're planning
a beep
um
there's a reason why I'm not gonna be
streaming on the weekend and you will
find out soon
who should I play with
um
who was a
kisenpai was a Healer right and
previously we we were able to clear with
was it Shion oh yeah it says that I have
the one win with her
ah wait I have one win with with akidoso
Senpai as well
oh
look
same with kiwama first
uh I guess so okay
[Music]
um
ah we should do we should try time mode
too
do you think time mode is
which character is the easiest for time
mode
wanna
uh let me see if I can oh no uh
redeem
I know I have another single tear
[Laughter]
s
oh no yeah they have the the fancy
outfits now all right let's play
um
I guess time mode I don't remember how
to play with kiwawa oh boy
I don't know
okay wow Fire trail all right Phoenix
sword
so you're supposed to do it how do you
do it faster than eh
because I saw people like posting the
scores but like how
do you do it fast
oh
focus on damage
[Music]
well
let me just figure this one out first
okay we don't have to like
beat anyone's high scores in the first
try
ah the stolen piggy bank but
um I don't think now is the time for
that I'm not
just fight lumau
kill it faster using hell and make spawn
faster to another hotel
that's the Strat huh I I'm I'm too tired
for that [\h__\h]
I would say that I'm increasing my
damage by increasing
um my range because that means I can do
more damage uh over a bigger area you
know
[Music]
right yeah so that's fine
music is amazing the music is incredible
oh
okay
maybe fan beam
oh
close that there's a there's a cutting
board um collab with
um something that turns into um
the
queue collab right
We Roll
okay I'll go for mine oh what the [\h__\h]
up
[Music]
oh triple baby
School
Ian curse Ah that's what it was right uh
The Cutting Board and the encourse right
maybe we can get that yeah oh okay now
that was kind of my my
[Music]
um
reflex
what does my
special do again should I use it oh I
didn't even change the
keybinds
um
special let's do
space
[Music]
oh increase them actually CEOs tears
were perfect that I got those
uh gives you free revive if you happen
to die during a special and of course
damage
oh yeah okay
I don't know if I want to use that now
yeah yeah
as well use your old unless you think
you're gonna die
well I mean
yeah music's so low really
okay I I made it a bit louder
um
okay one reception
yeah I'm gonna increase my damage
oh
[Music]
I think my damage is pretty good now and
wow that fire is
huge looks so cool
should I throw in the dancer because
I don't know I haven't really been
taking much damage until now but
foreign
that last sip of my tea had like all the
honey in it
I normally I don't even like honey but I
always put like a lot of it in my tea
you know that but I don't really like it
if you can taste it too much
no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
increased damage by 30 or go on with
Phoenix shield and Dancer
[Music]
um
okay
oh my God
what is that
that died fast
oh what does the what's the collab item
for uh the tears it's a microphone it
looked like a person
whatever it is it's dead now
oh
microphone with legs
two increase Max ice cream
I'll go for this
I'm going full damage
[Music]
oh you know I want to tell you something
but I I feel like maybe Ina wants to
tell the story
so maybe I should let her is she
streaming today I'm guessing not
feather mmm
but do you think I'll get so close to
death
she's dreaming right now
did she tell you the story already did
she just start I wonder
are still streaming
do not tell you the story
started at least an hour before me
ask her
maybe we should tell it at the exact
same time
oh we should tell it together
Tina
I dm'd her let's see if she'll notice
I just said Ina though
okay this one cup It's gotta do the
trick
I think the off collab tomorrow yeah
there's an off collapse tomorrow indeed
are you seeing this
storytelling yeah
um
I don't want to disturb it what is she
doing right now in Pokemon
[Music]
no wait actually no
no
that's it
Elite Four
I walk in the park
[Music]
but she's kind of offline
someone's going a little bit overboard
with those explosions oh hello
yo I'm killing those bosses like they're
and cutting through them like butter
[Music]
I need to get the cutting boards
so I can do that Kona ball my encourse
is almost Max
foreign
[Music]
I mean I could also just go to her room
no
blah
doesn't work she doesn't see my call
no but if I just go to her room then you
guys won't hear the story
um
so lucky shackles
um that's like a buff
um
I guess I'll just go for the tears again
for real though what what's the collab
item for that one tell me tell me please
please please please please please
please
open up her stream no
no a ball this looks to me like a like a
ball of strength for a cat
apply
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah okay okay
oh no
oh my God it's uh iris's thing
hey
I toot as I please
Bloom and Gloom gloom and Bloom yeah
Bloom and Gloom
boom and gum
uh
uh Spider cooking
wait cooking and curse oh that's
combined
like cooking collabs with the tears
all right
[Music]
what is it gonna turn into
oh yeah
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no there's so much food
dropping holy moly
I don't want to waste all that food I
don't I don't want to overeat
only one way to find out
final cooking
it's going really well so far isn't it
[Music]
I'm not scared of you guys
uh what what how does this work
oh yeah swap confirm
uh no uh strengthen
I guess finish okay sorry no more
Doodles we have to have priorities guys
and your priorities are just ridiculous
guys think about them
I like the do-toed machine too but you
know
oh I was watching the super Senpai
stream yesterday
[Music]
okay I mean I guess I'll take it
okay yeah and oh my God
especially the part with pecula Senpai
and kamato Senpai was so funny even
though I didn't really know what was
going on and that really tells you
something
that it's so entertaining I mean I
understand Japanese but I guess I just
didn't understand the context
police
was so funny um
cleared every stage of me thank you
okay now we're ready for the collabas no
not quite one more one more
[Music]
pickup brains would be nice to though to
be honest
because there's so much experience
you know what are you guys watching it
some en members and Kobo was also there
but I'm like
I'm like [\h__\h] it's like
ridiculous though it's ridiculous
day the the things that they try to
charge them with are actually ridiculous
because think about it for a second and
you will realize that the person in the
wrong was not the person you're trying
to arrest but the people behind it or
whatever include a party or so involve
starting
oh
yeah gouda was really logical and
reasonable
honestly don't try to
charge it well I I guess I'm just
charging you with anything now because I
don't have anything else to chat you
with and I just need some reason to have
you on the Stream
which is a really serious
uh honest
um criticism but it was funny
nonetheless I mean
but what the hell like trying to charge
Kobo what should I do
trying to change Kobo for entering at
six years old apparently I didn't know
she was six years old entering the The
Host Club
at six years old trying to say that
that's an illegal thing I mean yeah but
that's you wouldn't charge I know I'm so
serious about it but it makes absolutely
no sense
Ina is telling the story oh is she
telling the story
ah
they could tell it together
she saw my message okay
oh God I'm feeling so hot in the sweater
oh my God
and she will share some other time
she says okay
it's a good story though
she wants to focus on beating Pokemon
okay
what so confusing make up your mind
enough
actually it's a super sampai
was um I met someone by the other day
and she asked me like do I have any
crimes on them and anything I can report
and yes I had something and I feel like
actually that was
um which one
why is this one
View
oh that doesn't work okay
I thought only they only show the ones
that work together
what is this what is it
Broken Dreams oh the dream is dead and
there's no whole bubble Shield also
slows targets oh
oh I'm sorry
sorry
wow wait so doesn't does it not do any
damage is it just a shield now
laughs
[Music]
um
oh Ian curse and spider cooking what
a shield and what hard to see but the
teardrops hits on the whole oh the rain
oh oh I didn't see any rain
okay okay
tear rain I get in all right
oh yeah now I see it I'm just like
there's so much going on on the screen
like woohoo foreign
beam or something else what was that
[Music]
don't forget about your old I don't need
it
uh
fan fan yeah yes don't steal
no I don't know yeah
there's a list
oh I didn't know about the list
um upgrade but I need the cutting board
please bring back The Cutting Board I
turned it down once and I need it now
[Music]
I need it I wanna see
anyway back to topic yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
so when sample was asking me and the one
thing I said like I said both of them
it's kind of hard to come up with any
crimes uh honestly but I do think that
Atlantis crime
was very very
um reasonable can I do this one later
because
uh that one is true
but good as somehow
got herself out of that because she said
you know well the involved parties
aren't here ah there it is so I can't
talk about it now
wait not a little I guess in theory
that's a good logic but
she she was
saying she was guilty of that crime
yeah man
unbelievable oh well and then
what what what am I saying oh yeah for
Ina I said the only thing I can think of
is
the fact that she is letting people
uh wait and freeze should almost death
which is torture outside of her room
because she won't let them in because
she didn't clean her room it didn't only
happen once it happened at least twice
so that was what I told her but she
didn't use the crime
she didn't make use of it I feel like
she could have arrested Nina otherwise
but okay
that's when I talked to one of Sam fine
as I said many people have suffered
because of those actions oh let's let's
pick up the anvils I guess
get out of the way I need to get to the
Anvil
okay
beautiful beautiful
how much longer does
how many did I do until now
um
foreign
oh hello
I guess they're going down pretty fast
before I killed five thousand
oh I didn't even look at that number
before wow
[Music]
[Applause]
yay yay if you need legal help before
this you know but they're called
yeah look at
clip and I don't think she knew what it
was about
but I I know
if you're telling a knife
[Music]
my damage output is crazy
gotta go
oh sticker what delay between attacks um
ah I get I should get rid of that
makes way more sense now
ah only if you left
I don't think I'm breaking a record uh I
think Mooney is holding the most recent
record but
and I wasn't even trying
whoa
oh what's there it doesn't pick up
everything
wait what am I looking for
I don't even know
because they're both level seven
um
maybe crit maybe suck it
yeah because yeah
find yourself
okay everything on the screen
9 49
9 49.
I didn't even get to do my last call
Apple
wait hey mate
[Music]
what
I'm already done yeah
yeah what was mommy said mommy did seven
minutes eleven
oh my God
oh my god well this was my first try
okay
[Laughter]
but easy easy
Suffering From Success
it's pretty orangey it really
oh can I change into a t-shirt real
quick it's getting hot again
oh
my calls
pumps they call it coughs
coughs the things
back of your lower legs
yeah
they've been oh man I took a bath
yesterday I tried to figure out how am I
how my Japanese bathtub works because
normally I'm always a shower type but
yesterday oh I decided I need to fill
the bathtub and soak my whole body in
oh in the hot hot water
and I did it and I put some bath salt in
there too
yeah
um
but I guess it didn't help I guess it's
not like a Miracle Solution
unfortunately
um I was watching Gilmore Girls while in
the bathtub though I meant
my my bathtub
um Gilmore Girls watching uh set up was
um
quite funny
oh because I
I I I I I moved uh I moved the side
table into the bathroom which you know
Japanese bathrooms are like these whole
shower rooms where there's no normal
floor like the whole room you can soak
the whole room
you know yeah
um so I I I I put the side table in
there and then I put my tripod for my
phone there and I put the phone on the
tripod
and just watched like that because there
was no other surface to put it on and I
didn't bring my my iPad or so this time
because I left it with my brother he
said can you can you just leave it
I wanna watch with it
um
so I had to remember just watching on my
phone the whole time
the whole room is a shower exactly yeah
yeah that's what they're like in Finland
what
really
oh little bro wants the iPad well he's
my big bro
no it's okay
um
yeah well I guess the bath was nice but
my calves my whole body my shoulders my
arms my calves especially though [\h__\h]
he died
uh I just beat follow this record yay
foreign
got the ultimate Phantom Styles oh yeah
how does that work
anyway how many coins did I get uh wait
this is not what I meant four thousand
only
from that
Nani
oh well I wanna play
um you know when I never played the hard
mode stage
should we try that one is that difficult
I wonder
who who should I go with
um
[Music]
a bit difficult it's called hard for a
reason
all right one not too bad
fauna makes it easy
oh healing Zone and this one final gains
a 10 second invincibility buff
um foreign
last time yeah but I don't want to
always use the same people right
Kiara can clear heart rather easy with
just your turtle
all right I'm gonna try fauna why not
um stage mode but
uh wait I also never cleared this one
eh isn't that the heart wait which one
is the heart mode yeah this one
yeah okay and then we'll try the other
one
the office one
ah Kawaii
didn't even think about that one
are these leaves are confusing me
can one whisper each stack kill stupid
okay
hey I don't like her way of attacking at
all
ah
it's so hard to control
the randomly oh
yeah
[Music]
don't try to aim
is are they gonna drop food because it's
not looking good
uh
oh no
no
I don't I don't like it at all
[Music]
yeah yeah
it's easier at high level
oh
[Music]
goodbye
give me that food
no no no no no no no
we barely used
I'll try I'll try
senpai
hoping I get more
of a reasonable chance
oh
[Music]
so that was also unkillable
no no
um anyway uh yeah belly dance
[Music]
foreign
oh these are kind of confusing
got it
do her thingies just do what they want
do they just attack at random
[Music]
hey auto aim
yeah bye yeah bye
[Music]
foreign
I feel like the other things would be
very helpful but
[Music]
belly dancing very important we gotta
get that going
[Music]
it's sticker
I can't wait to stick around [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h]
oh my God what the no I'm going down I'm
going down
oh
I did the hip attack
to save myself
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe I'm not ready for Hard Mode let me
let me do the office
let me do the office with aqua
our spinning broom nickel dealing for
100 damage okay
[Music]
with this one I was always struggling
when I used to play it broom
just like me for real for real
I was cleaning
the other day with a broom just like her
you'll get it you'll understand
eventually
um
[Music]
everybody saw me dance
foreign
dear Lord
I guess if you're happy with that
I hope you clean when you get visitors
though
um additional projected to all
multi-shot weapons maybe not yet
[Music]
oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no is this
one also 20 minutes probably right
quitting broom awakens
does it like freeze them now
no bombs no no no
they're all 20 minutes oh well okay
uh I wish my voice wasn't so funks man
[Music]
make way
oh what's this one weapon heads have 10
chance to stun enemies temporarily okay
thank you marno
now I should take a fruit candy I'm
running out of my the ones that I
brought from home they recall that oh no
that was the last one actually I did run
out officially
[Music]
it's okay
now
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] they're bad the cornersuki
wall
find some Vicks you know or anything
really
um
okay you know what I want to go for the
EM curse with the Mana ITA again with
the cutting board
I want to do the new one
I don't want to use hollow
try again because of spider cooking yeah
is that a different one than what we did
last time
wait yeah yeah yeah yeah it is different
eh on it okay spider cooking spider
cooking and create some spider cooking
foreign
[Music]
but these two don't they combine as well
why am I making up things
no well then that's
pen then beam
um
they're both decent to level yeah yeah
I'll try to find the spider cooking
first though
if there are no targets within 75 pixels
gain 40 attack otherwise getting for 40
speed
yeah that's very interesting
anyway I think we're ready now to use
the projectile one yeah because now we
got a lot of projectiles
oh God I think
I'm already doing a million times better
than every last time I played this map
because I think
I would always like run from people and
get stuck in Corners before
but now I'm just staying and chilling in
the middle
stay in the middle thank you a little
don't wonder
[Music]
noticeable Improvement yay
yeah I think so the Mouse
um function helps me a lot now I think
it's making a huge difference for me
[Music]
oh
Dodge nice Dodge
[Music]
what artists do you usually listen to
and music
it's so weird like I used to listen to
music all the time back in the day
back in the day whatever day that is
like when I would go to school when I
would go to work and when I was at home
just chilling when I was at home drawing
when I was at home doing whatever
playing games
uh yeah but
I think I told you guys before somehow I
stopped listening to music oh wait I
have had my
I should do this
just like keep it for myself all the
time
my favorite artist thank you I was
actually never like that I listen to
other music nowadays mostly just
gameless
[Music]
um
I listen to a lot of Whole Life music
lovers thank you
ah
what's that hello
anyway
I let radios play randomly oh I guess
yeah if I had a car and I was driving I
would probably be listening to the music
to music all the time there
uh
but yeah nowadays I don't listen to
something at all and it's so weird
because I don't understand I feel like
that was a like a
like a thing anybody does all the time
like a normal such a normal thing to do
uh
somehow I stopped um but if I listen to
music really rarely
um
I mean it's times like when I try to
learn a new song for karaoke or so so
it's not even like I don't even feel
like this naturally
I don't want to handle see what it did
to me it's making this even more
difficult [\h__\h] that
I hate that I hate that
now that already gave me one like
automatically and I didn't even want it
ah [\h__\h] there was a oh no we're not
using The Cutting Board are we what are
we using uh Spider cooking I didn't
where's the spider cooking
foreign
I could have dropped it yeah
um well
we're dealing with this now weapon will
fire backwards there's no one
might have ah I didn't what just
happened
I wanted to put it back
goodbye
where did it go did I sell it did I is
it on my weapon now I'm not sure
okay well
and an achievement
[Laughter]
oh well I'm in
retry
oh get well soon pale
um well the what is also ID reference I
learned this recently well the special
media is still challenging increased
crit by 15 oh
[Music]
that kind of encourages you to
um
use your special more I guess nice
but that's a above right so no collabo
there's no buff collapse right they
could eventually like maybe no
um I guess I guess I don't know they
don't really need it
yeah the Indonesian classroom
um
no broom all right
uh that was such a cute stream
yeah I'm already planning my next uh
collab with rainy
by the way
[Music]
sooner sooner rather than later
mm-hmm
no no no like actual like streaming
collab not singing collab
[Music]
where's the broom
what the [\h__\h]
apparently Ina was down too now what the
[\h__\h]
it was all gone the whole it wasn't only
a stream down though my whole internet
was done gone
[Music]
at least I feel connected to Ina because
we were both down
yay
oh
well we're back okay I was waiting for
you guys
welcome back guys
isn't that tasty yeah
um
It's The End curse no but this is the
Japan curse because we're in Japan and
the internet is [\h__\h]
laughs
actually I was I was typing what
happened to staff
um Ian Chris Japan Edition
still Ian doesn't matter where you are
yeah but
it's not like I haven't
um
maybe my and curse influences the Japan
internet huh oh well
um
[Music]
I
which one should I want one healing
thing
lifesteal life
I don't know which one though
one okay
foreign
I guess I will just blame my previous
loss on Halu because what the [\h__\h]
it's just rude
[Music]
I'm gonna recharge earphones
see see this is why
this is why they suck you have to charge
them besides losing them
I would say that this is the biggest
problem you have to charge those [\h__\h]
okay and then you're missing time
you're missing out on precious kiwawa
time streaming time all right so like
what the [\h__\h] this is the biggest
argument anyway
hey hey hey hey hey
that was like recently I tried using
them
um awakened because
uh I was in a situation where I didn't
have my oh
let me do it next time what I didn't
have
uh uh like the USBC
earphone earphones headphones
for my phone but I I really was bored
like I think I was in a long trip
with
um I don't know what
yeah so I wanted to waste time
honey thank you um
I guess we could eventually collab those
two because they they uh match right
has been a while
nice nice nice choices
yeah a good good triple what was I
saying oh yeah yeah and then I I tried
to use them and then I I think I was
waiting at the airport for my flight
back or so ah
God damn it um
yeah and and I tried coupling them or
whatever you call it
and it worked only for one side so I
guess the other one didn't charge
properly
but why not why did it not properly
makes no sense you both put them you put
both of them in
a little [\h__\h] come here come here
[Music]
ah
yeah why did I run in there
really the first sticker that I get is
that
no I don't even
I don't even want to
sell it but I could like use it to
upgrade later
yeah well whatever
[Music]
anyway do you guys have that problem too
that they don't charge properly or would
that just me
so that was for me the death sentence
for my ear butts basically no I do just
you I don't use them I never use them
I put them in the case
what the [\h__\h]
but
so for me that was a reason to like
never use them ever again
once lost their charge okay that means
I'm never using them again
was the case charged well I mean I don't
know stop asking questions
[Music]
Chad died on screen the whole time
permanently
uh
it's been frozen for a while
um hello you little [\h__\h] can you please
[Music]
um
hello you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah there you go I fixed it
I think I have potential to become an
I.T person
[Music]
all it people watching my stream right
now this little [\h__\h] underestimating my
job
well well oh
you know
the other day I was in the studio
uh doing something and gouda was also in
the studio doing something but she was
like on the other side of the studio
basically
um kind of far so I didn't hear her
really she didn't hear us
and um
which one should I use
We Roll
all right okay
you was looking for that one
what was I saying oh yeah
we were both in the studio okay and I
was I was in the room with a janma we
were talking what are we talking about
oh yeah yeah
like
uh
it was like kind of late to
um a meeting uh before that
because she didn't get any notifications
because her status on Discord was
um Do Not Disturb but I feel like all of
every whole life member is constantly on
do not disturb nobody's ever just
normally online they're even like hiding
their status or they're just
um Do Not Disturb most people are just
do not disturb right
and gouda has had her status on do not
disturb or offline for her whole time in
in her whole life well me too though so
nobody is really just online ever
yeah so
um she almost she was kind of like a
little bit late I guess she almost
missed the whole thing
so ah let's buy the cooking let's get it
now so I don't like forget
and nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice
sorry my brain slow when playing game uh
you know that by now
exposed nah it's okay it all went fine
in the end because I was just a short
little thing information thing
um and then
when I was sitting in that room with
Jenna I was like on my phone uh for a
moment and like checking and I saw I see
on Discord
status on Discord
looked somehow weird to me
do you know why something was something
was really off
it was Green
she was online
and I'm like yeah
did she get like hacked or something
what's going on
it's not normal
something's wrong
the first time in two and a half years I
see that status out there and I'm like
what what this is this must be an
imposter it's not normal like this can't
be her like what is going on and I
thought from as I said I showed it to
Jen and we were both like
brain broken
and our thought was that probably
it's because you know she's uh on on the
studio PC doing some work and probably
locked in on the Discord there and it
made her
um
it made her uh
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
it may draw online which is like
automatically by being on a different
computer although I don't think that
actually works like when I logged in it
just kept the status that I usually have
nice dances thank you
oh well so we were like oh I guess
that's that probably that but I wrote to
her like oh my God good up and I sent
her a screenshot of her status and like
did you get hacked or something
and then she writes back to me
and she tells me oh no actually
she did it because she almost missed
that meeting and she's paranoid now
she's scared that she will miss it again
or miss anything again so
she she's all she was online for that
moment but I don't think she she already
switched back to her normal usual ways I
think
I guess it was just that one time
man
that's a good reason yeah that was quick
yeah
battery died your school
you guys are unbelievable you have to go
because your batteries die
that should not be the thing that stops
you from watching me
unbelievable
[Music]
I guess I could I could increase exp one
more time
foreign
hey can I just give credit to my gaming
laptop for being able to handle the
damage numbers
just fine
I didn't wait I mean it's lagging a
little bit now but
all right fine the studio PC was not
able to handle those
hmm
your laptop is better than your PC was
now I'm talking about the little Studio
one though
should I should I get this the pill now
I kind of want to use it but I need to
like get those collapse going though
never mind I I have to get those collabs
look at me look at me it's like I'm
playing Touhou
ah
surprised we didn't hear the airport
yeah my my laptop has been
doing fine yeah it's pretty quiet the
whole time I've been using it since I'm
here I wonder why that is
I guess it's just not over here I think
it might be like an overheating thing in
previous times
the pattern yeah
is the broom cooler no it's like pretty
normal temperature
uh what am I doing uh yeah whatever
goodbye okay
[Music]
get me out of here
oh that was so mean no no no no no no
no no no no no this can't be the enemy
oh I'm healing back thank God thank God
thank God thank God thank God thank God
a klutz in a clutch
Klutz looks like it would be a German
word right
but we don't not to my knowledge we
don't use it at least but it looks so
German
oh
okay
um
glasses um damage of critical hits
caused by this Weapon by uh 10 percent
should I like switch with something
what Yiddish
stat
crate is low
strengthen
the bat
okay
foreign
[Music]
anyway
ah ah wait the story isn't over yet
Ah that's the I forgot the the
what do you call and again the end of a
joke
the story wasn't quite over I forgot the
end of the joke
one way there's more the pants line yeah
the punchline
place
we have so much money
[Music]
um
I'm not done with the funny
um switch Maybe
or upgrade
town and family
social knockback okay
fine with me so okay so I wrote to her
like ah did you get hacked or anything
and she's like no I was just like scared
of missing anything else now so I I
switched to online
and then
I said like in a in a decent volume
I said oh if it isn't the consequences
of her own actions
and like immediately after that she
writes me in Discord in caps lock
uh
and I'm like did you just hear what I
said oh [\h__\h]
but then later on I I asked her did you
did you hear what I I said before is
that what you wrote that when eventually
when you know she came over
oh my God I don't think I ever saw her
before holy [\h__\h]
sad
[Music]
subscribe anyway she said um no no what
what do you mean and I uh I was like you
didn't hear I said
um
the consequences of your own actions
and she was like no I didn't hear it and
I'm like oh why did I just where did I
just
say it but in the end I still don't
really know what what she meant
yeah
oh no I still don't really understand
what she meant with that then with the
Caps look I'm gonna say
I think someone was like
y'all made it eh no I don't know I still
don't know
yeah I'm so confused
yeah well the punchline boys then I said
oh if it is the consequences of her own
actions
you get it get it anyway oh I guess that
was a halftime boss
I love half time
I had absolutely no idea this is
happening this time it's not flooding my
socials or so at all
I just like saw one random ass comment
somewhere
yeah uh saying something
about the Super Bowl
oh no I think it was yeah yeah uh the
only thing that I saw
was uh you know my my YouTube or my
favorite YouTuber
don't tendo said like complaining about
the halftime show from Rihanna
saying it was [\h__\h]
um and I was like wait wait wait Super
Bowl is that what you
said wait the Super Bowl is happening
how the heck
oh dear
how the heck have I not like
uh
gotten any blank
I don't know
why why did I not hear anything about
the Super Bowl this time is there PR
team like on vacation or what
I don't understand
a decent show well I ended up watching
it
um I tried to find a video then
and you know I love Rihanna right I love
her
I'm gonna Swap and then strengthen
I love her okay so the first video I
opened that I found because it was kind
of hard to find the video for it I guess
it was just still very fresh
was
um one where uh a hand sign lady was
signing the song while dancing
kind of like really vibing to the whole
thing and on the left side like there
were two screens one with her doing sign
language and the other one was like
Rihanna performing but there was like a
sound delay
yeah but she was like so insulin I'm
like damn girl
kind of like vibing more than Rihanna
herself
I think you can find it if you look it
up but she was cute too she's really
cute
she was like so into it she was so
passionate
Oh My Voice by the way has recovered it
seems
thanks to the recona
you should see them at Eminem concerts
oh my God wouldn't that look like
they're doing like some some
Naruto Jutsu
like
with their hands
oh [\h__\h]
um
I don't know
maybe cut [\h__\h]
um
[\h__\h] I don't want a new item right now
but okay
[Music]
um
then it should be something that I can
collab eventually so bye
that was effective that was that was
good that was good I needed to clear
some room for me
um
foreign
running along with Nick is a good threat
right all right that was like my my big
brain moment just now
yeah it's not a golden one yeah but like
uh where's the golden one
laughs
[\h__\h] okay it's getting crowded now
[Music]
okay okay I cleaned up just like the
mate I am currently
[Music]
stop
bring me the golden Nando
what was I talking about
oh yeah the Rihanna thing so I watched
that a little bit first but I was like
no this is delayed I can't really judge
um Rihanna's performance but this girl
is really
vibing
so uh I looked up like a low quality all
I could find was a low quality uh
recording of Rihanna on her halftime
show
what is this
Eldritch Horror
ah
someone someone's unknown Horrors may
live still up to five percent from
Target defeated and what cool
oh
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
goodbye
this looks like a special it could be a
special attack from someone from Eno
herself hey you for real this is just a
normal cool habitat it's huge
uh thanks for the rain hello
funny thing we're gonna be raining
someone in 20 minutes too
holy [\h__\h]
to your soul
I feel like it's working so well
damn
oh there's a sticker there
oh yeah bye yeah bye I feel stressed um
help me help me
attacks have a 10 chance to hit whole
coins out of targets per hit uh
uh
anyway what was I saying oh yeah and
then I found the Rihanna one and and
honestly I mean
I do have to say like
I mean
she's pregnant okay in that moment
but
[Music]
it was
yeah I mean she's done better
performances but I guess I'll just
yeah I'll just give her the the pass for
you know being pregnant I guess I'm
being on on a really high platform
Yes actually pregnant wasn't she like
pregnant also like like I feel like
she's pregnant for years now
hasn't she been pregnant forever now
uh fan beam was it or idle song for the
asakoko
yes
yeah
yeah she's so for the sick show like I
love her songs
fan beam okay I love her song so much I
love her perfect
I love her she's she's the queen
and her outfit was really flattering
like either she wasn't that far in her
pregnancy or or it was really flattering
she didn't look that pregnant to me
I wasn't sure if that was like the after
belly or I don't know
foreign
but I feel like she's been pregnant for
ages now
I feel like I saw her being pregnant a
year ago too maybe it's her second child
or so
is that does anybody know
s right in my
in my the vision or whatever
okay I think I can do this we're five
minutes left and it's going pretty well
I would like to move a little bit more
to the middle though
let's run with the cat
yeah
boys
okay I'm scared I'm so scared I'm so
scared I'm so scared I'm so scared
okay the lag okay okay here we go
there's some lag now
uh
yeah
I'm scared to go back I'm scared I'm so
scared
I'm so scared
[\h__\h] my father had enough damage output
but these suckers are
strong
but here I am
I'm back hmm
should I maybe buff myself a little bit
um
five more minutes yeah this way very
hard to clear I had felt up
hmm
yeah
she lives
damaging yeah I'll I'll do it I I I'm
scared now I'm terrified
foreign
[Music]
I don't need weapons anymore
okay upgrade for that and yeah above yay
nice
Max okay we're ready for another collab
this is my first collab let's go
you know I know a lot of like Holo cure
hardcore
um uh fans were like unhappy with my
previous plays but am I doing that badly
not that bad right
foreign
I mean at least not now right I'm doing
fine right now no thank you thank you
thank you for the pinky
yeah some people are very particular
about I was surprised like how it's a
fan game but yeah wow dragon fire some
holy [\h__\h] okay I haven't had this one in
a while
[Laughter]
oh my God
wait it's already is that um maximum
upgrade
[Music]
Max Max Max oh I have to sell it oh no
okay
no right now I don't know it's just me I
feel like I'm doing quite all right
cats cat where are we going no wrong
direction guys what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] I thought I aimed you to
the right side
anyway let's burn those batteries isn't
it kind of like a huge fire hazard
to burn them the batteries like this
what happens when you burn batteries
and nickel go to the whole goal Montague
don't don't worry about it are you sure
about that
but yeah I got free collabs so in theory
this is fine but they're they're kind of
um I don't want to Corn myself on that
side of the
am I
it's hard to see my mouse I don't know
where my mouth is
[Music]
um
okay what the [\h__\h]
oh God
I wanna end this ah
yes
[Music]
okay
cool cool there's food up there okay
okay I'm like the [\h__\h] plants
[Music]
my fingers hurt
um
we might as well get another weapon yeah
oh there's a lot of food oh
oh my God what the [\h__\h] is that
it's kind of kind of bomb or so
it's like Counting
please go away
go away oh yeah 15.
I guess
oh
okay okay it's good that I ran back to
it I thought oh God where can I outrun
it but no the it's like the whole field
crisis averted I was close I think that
was really close
[Laughter]
[Music]
bomb has been diffused by burning it
oh God
uh
yeah yeah yeah okay sometimes you gotta
be aggressive
oh look at all that exp uh
I think I'm gonna go for the bandage
yeah just go extra safe now
oh I gotta sell those
selling
could be good on its own I know but I'm
gonna sell them I don't want to think
too much
get all that exp yay
oh my God okay okay okay let's oh God oh
my God uh a cat would be good now
here we go here we go here we go can I
run with it
[Music]
[Applause]
we're so close we're so close we're so
close we're so close
oh God now they're coming from the left
side
um
no really dangerous what I'm doing right
now I'm I'm I just decided to run
through them but um I don't know if I'll
survive this
[\h__\h] do I continue running to the right
side or to the to the left
oh I'm fine I didn't take any damage
the office workers don't want to hurt me
I guess
these are supposed to be office workers
right holy [\h__\h]
I'm gonna die I Don't Wanna Die
which way do I go
[Music]
for real
keep panicking that's my recommendation
Spin to Win
[Music]
okay this area is pretty safe
okay okay throwing them burn them oh
yeah bye bye
-bye
I Don't Wanna Die
that was so I'm so sorry
why won't you run it
there's no way I can tank this
there's no way
maybe up here
but there's some I think there's some
stuff here where I can't walk through
I'm alive
it's not over yet it's not over yet it's
not over yet
excited my special is coming
oh she's now I'm cornering myself again
I can't go
oh
cat you kept me [\h__\h] waiting but it's
not helping much how much longer
ah where's exactly me 20 minutes
uh
last time can will they disappear though
or do they just stay
because sometimes they just disappear
right
I did it
they just oh
oh
so close to dying
oh my God Elsa I'm so hungry I can't
believe it I'm gonna cry
I'm gonna cry oh it's sunny you're small
oh this feels like a total game
doesn't everything feel like a total
game oh my oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh [\h__\h]
burn it down my first time
was yeah
oh my God I'm so happy
[Applause]
just in time
oh
I can't believe I I I I I I I I I I
how did I survive that moment
oh my God
[Music]
anyway oh
amazing I I also thought it was over but
you know a phoenix never gives up a
phoenix never stops believing
yeah and we have a character and I
didn't even know that well either but it
was fun I couldn't play it's fun to use
um
I love the cat
has a good run yeah it was like a zombie
horde yeah thank you
certified hola cure Pro yeah
lots of money too time for me oh yeah
so do I do it now like let's see what
happens
I don't know if you guys like all get
forced to move
I wonder
Valentine's Day
with Polo
faster faster faster
ah there's like a countdown anyway
probably right
I wonder
okay I I did it so what's happening
what's happening I'll be the Zayn by the
way and in Germany we say avidazen but
what's happening
what what what what do you see guys you
get like an offer to move oh I have to
end it okay bye bye
[Music]
experimenting okay