[Music]
so
korean people
oren mania
it's been a while
since the last time i studied
korean publicly
and yay
[Music]
oh the whole chat is filled with korean
again
uh hello
hello
we're using
uh
duolingo today but before that
i
want to
show you
how far i am with my
uh korean alphabet
um
because
[Music]
yeah i've been using uh
things called
write it korean
just some random
uh korean
lang
writing
application
uh that i randomly picked from the app
store and it works pretty well
i'm not completely done with my license
but i'm like uh 70 percent through
so okay
let me um
let me show you
uh i may i may forget some of the ones
that i already know but let's see okay
so we have for example
um
this confused me a little bit in the
beginning but this is
this is ah
as
wait vowel or consonant i don't know the
difference anymore
but it's it's like only in combination
with others
with other
thingies it's it's ah but if you want it
alone
then it has to look like this but that's
way too big
i think it should be smaller but you
know what i mean right this is ah
this is ah
alone and this is our in combination
with other things i think
yeah yeah yeah and then and then we have
e
but
e alone
is just that
right yeah yeah
[Music]
right wait i think i don't remember
seeing
any
in any other way oh
i got it right okay okay uh and then so
for these for the next ones i have um
a bridge to remember it by again so we
have uh
this is
[Music]
oh
because it's over the table
and this is that i know it's the same
uh
this is
ooh because it's under the table
right
now oh
and that is helpful
because
um
here there's something similar
this is
yo
because yo why did you flip the table
over
and this is
you because
why are you
crying you know because this looks like
a crying face
[Laughter]
uh-huh uh-huh
okay but
but
these are again only in combination with
others
uh so i don't know if that was a vowel
consonant i again don't know the
difference you guys told me before but i
already forgot
so
if i just
want ooh
this looks like a puzzle now
then
i think this is ooh
and if i just want o
then this is probably all right
right
no
[Music]
right yeah
yeah
no
[Music]
yeah
wait
[Music]
ah
okay but this one is okay this one is
okay
this one is okay
all right right okay um
anyway and then i know for example
this is a uh
this is
a
no this
[Music]
no yes this was it uh
this was ale this was ale
and this
is
this is
yale
[Music]
this
is
and this is n
uh-huh oops my tablet is sinking
um
uh-huh i noticed something
uh
because you know see here adding one
stroke makes it uh
mix it
you know
into the similar letter um
and then
here this one
i uh remember because it looks like a
beer
and you know like a glass of beer right
so that is b
that's b and if i want p
then
we turn that around
and we have p
ah
oh i'm so smart
oh so smart
okay okay and now
uh what was i missing what am i missing
ah i also know
this is m
i know
this is
[Music]
oh
what else what else
i don't know everything yet but
uh
yeah uh i know this
this was uh this was
[Music]
and then this is
no wait we had that before no no no
no no no no
[Music]
wait that was uh
if if this is m
and and that one was n and that was g
then that one was
don't tell me that i knew it and this is
too
that is duh and that is true
so for example
i know i know i know i was thinking
so again you add another another stroke
here just like that and you make it
sound
more
uh
yes oh i know uh
this is how you write it but i probably
will just write it like this but you're
supposed to write it
like in this order like one two three
i think
um
that is
but for example if you want to write la
then you add
this and then there is
understand
i'm not here to teach you
i'm not here to teach you i'm just
trying to show you where i am with my
progress right now
um
so let's for example write my name
because i think we can do that
my name i think would be this because
that is cool
but in combination with that because
that is key
and then uh
okay
and then we can't use this one we have
to use this one
but it's more oval i guess
[Music]
kiara
like this
[Music]
[Applause]
smart
i know how to write my name i know how
to write my name
yeah
i can sign
i can sign my name in korean now
can i write taka takanasi
i can try
so that's probably
um
[Music]
yeah
wait really like that
or is it
is that ca
yeah okay
[Music]
that looks like a japanese kanji for
hito
i don't i don't
i don't know sure i know but i don't but
maybe that works can i just can i write
this
she
is that okay no
huh
[Music]
oh wait i wrote the wrong ones like this
one
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh yeah yeah wait did i have that
somewhere yeah here i accidentally wrote
ale but i wanted to write
ah
[Music]
is there no
is there no s-h-e
oh i remember one more uh
this is
j
and this is
so we can say
ja for example or we can say cha for
example
so maybe we can say kiara
uh
[Music]
hmm
does that work
sorry did you guys teach me what
is she really this
with s e is there no
s-h-i
oh what
chan is oh its own thing oh i did not
learn that yet okay
okay no c but c c okay okay
okay
so this is roughly
what i know right now
um i know
how you make these combinations now
because
um you start with these simple ones and
then you start combining them like this
for example as you saw this is made out
of two this is made out of two and this
is made out of two but you can make them
uh
out of even four different things for
example i think maybe four is the most
maybe
four combinations like you have one sign
here there's one here one here one here
one here or you have one sign here and
it's made out of two uh one on top one
on the bottom or you can also have them
made side to side it depends on um you
know
i mean for me i see some things just fit
better that way and that's how i explain
it to myself just because
you know
because if we say we want to combine the
the j and the ia
then it's obviously
only gonna fit like this oops okay that
looks so weird
it's only gonna fit like this
it's not gonna fit like
that that just looks weird right yeah
it's it's this is this yeah
i'm smart
[Laughter]
[Music]
it just makes sense
um
yeah
but um
[Music]
so last time with duolingo duolingo was
suddenly throwing like these things at
me without explaining the the single
ones to me
the how to that like they didn't even
like explain the logic behind any of
this to me
yeah
they just suddenly jumps to full words
without explaining
how they are made you know they need to
explain how the babies are made before
telling me how the adults get together
so
um i got pretty far they're still a
little bit missing and i i still need
some time
in my lessons when i look at the
combinations
um
i i need a little bit of thinking time
for some of them
[Music]
but overall overall
yeah overall it's been going pretty well
and i haven't even invested that much
time yet so
i logged into my duolingo account again
and i don't understand uh i think maybe
because i haven't been in there for a
while
maybe that's why uh
i can keep this on the side maybe if i
want to note something down
um
uh i feel like they like got rid of my
progress i don't understand duolingo
anymore it's been too long
uh
but we're gonna jump into the duolingo
portion now
we shall
okay are you ready where do we even
start because i think
did we do
did we do all the ones that have a crown
to it
[Music]
they updated the korean course recently
really wait they have the letters
[Music]
are you kidding me
huh are you kidding me
are you kidding me duolingo
are you kidding me
now
now oh yeah i forgot ale i i know al2
i know
these
i know these
i know
um
i know these two i know all of these i
think
yeah yeah these ones with w no the
double vowels the double files i didn't
learn yet
i know all of the these ones and all of
the plain consonants
and aspirated consonants oh i know k i
know t
that one looks different than what i
learned
[Music]
mine looks like the japanese uh
katakana for soup
same thing
is it the font
it but it looks so different to me
hey can we compare
because
i learned
it's
[Music]
like nihongo
this is chip
[Music]
is this not
they're the same
different font it looks very different
so
this is both how is this the same
[Music]
okay
okay i'll kill okay
i will i will try to keep that in mind
and these ones i didn't look at yet but
it makes sense it's just
repeating the same pattern
well
um
i got over why did they not have
this last time
they didn't teach me properly last time
okay well should we start over from the
beginning and look at it again
wait so can you guys tell me the answer
uh of what my question was before i
didn't see your answer did it does does
duolingo work like this that everyone
with the crown i learned already
did i do those last time
is that how i did it
[Music]
or should i i know i want to go for them
just quickly
a crown is what i know oh okay but but
let's go through it maybe quickly
select the matching pairs okay
wait a second
[Music]
select the correct characters for aah
select the matching pairs
[Music]
wow
i just say ale because in my brain when
i read it i read it in german
okay
one day streak shut up no go away
whatever
shut up shut up yeah i saw the course
update came came kind of too late okay
quick uh
[Music]
over the table
it's like the matching pairs oh no it's
so much
over the table
[Music]
it's easy because the r looks so special
to me oh it really stands out to me
this
it looks like a snake
and then uh under the table
[Music]
and select the matching pairs
wait yeah i think it's this one yeah
over the table
no
don't sit on the table
and
okay
no
don't sit on the on the table see
someone's sitting on the table
no
don't do that
okay okay
and this one would be
kale
k-e
this one is
and this one is
[Music]
we're doing a speed run we're doing a
speed run okay okay okay
oh
well i mean the complicated one is
obviously so
ah here we go again duolingo
ah this one okay i know ng is the circle
and cut and then that should be this one
because it's a combination of all the
ones i know uh where
what
where i did not learn i think
let me try from the other oh i didn't
learn all of these
but let me think logically well this
should be this one
and then
which one could it be
i know that the one
with the doubles
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know
i didn't learn these yet i didn't learn
oh no um
that should be this one
[Music]
uh the one with the circle
and the one with the two
the complicated one
[Music]
i don't know
i don't
[Music]
oh no that's m that's um it looks
too similar to me yeah yeah go mangoman
now they all look complicated now i
can't go by how complicated it is okay
well s is the one that looks like uh the
person they all have that and and it
was um
it was it must be this one
it was uh this one
okay you can't throw these complicated
ones at me yet
no
um
[Music]
are we doing is the first one
or is the first letter sale
[Music]
sale okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
okay can we actually learn words now i
don't want to look at the letters
anymore i don't want to look at alphabet
anymore let's learn letters
okay
what do you mean tap what you hear
there's only one choice
[Laughter]
[Music]
baby
baby bubble
oh
who used to sail
write this on korean oh
are you for real
you want me to ride
[Music]
oh oh
how is that korean
[Music]
we
[Applause]
[Music]
oh it's not that right we're all
confused
we
[Music]
cucumber
what what kind of weird way how how
should i have known you never taught me
cucumber before
i don't understand korean duolingo
oh
[Music]
this cucumber uh
why what is what why why is this so
why is this lesson so
this well okay we learned we as cucumber
uh i forgot which one they used it was a
double one
it was probably this one but what's this
yeah
maybe this i i'm guessing yeah oy
huh
okay we just
[Music]
ah you already have the lesson on level
one still doing things that you know
these words
they never taught me anywhere else
[Music]
this
this cucumber
oui
okay this cucumber
will
oh yeah
[Music]
oh wait were there more parts to the
other lessons i did that i did a speed
run from
this baby's cucumber okay
e e
[Music]
no
baby first right maybe i don't know i
don't know what the order is uh oh
[Music]
cucumber why does the baby have a
cucumber is it eating its veggies good
baby
good
baby genius i am a secret agent like i
was in the 80s
you shouldn't
are you sure you should tell me about
that well i guess if you're not
an agent anymore i know i am a genius
though thank you
or
this
baby
milk
right
this baby's milk oh
this
baby's milk
oh my god
guessing brings you very far in life
write this in korean
baby's milk aki
[Music]
this milk isn't this milk
oh
[Music]
ew disgusting
baby
baby milk
maybe they want to say baby's milk
okay
oh
milk
wheel
all right all right he's not he didn't
look very impressed to that bear i feel
insulted i'm doing my best here
sorry they're on fire scorching hot way
to go
oui
[Music]
that is
this
cucumber cucumber that was cucumber this
cucumber this cucumber
[Music]
okay i i don't like cucumbers you know
cucumbers was just some salt sprinkled
on top of them
are actually a good snack
we made it easy to use duolingo with
your students bring the fun to oh hell
no i mean this is kind of a classroom
now but
i don't really recommend it
um wait so are you saying that there
were more words in here for me to learn
i guess so
let me check then
[Music]
oh that's the one where i said
he only has the sideways thingy as far
as i know oh i didn't it had more i just
forgot about it
okay
matching pairs
e
l
um
oh
okay
there's no words here though
maybe lay there
[Music]
exactly i feel like a baby right now
thank you i finished two lessons with no
mistakes you're ready to level up
okay
what does that do
oh
oh i don't know if i'm ready for
a higher level
ah
wait
what's the max level uh what comes next
is still the same
ah
is it still the same that looks like the
same content
ah
oh
[Music]
same content
all right
well let's go to belongings again i want
to learn more about cucumbers and babies
and how you combine them into a great
milkshake
uh
ah
[Music]
great
korean
wow
oh you give me two choices and
you actually have both
no only one of them written here
wow
[Music]
koreans so good
sorry i'm just making fun of duolingo
oh oh oh thank you for the super chats
by the way
i don't know if i'll get to them today
but uh we'll get closer to them today
um this though
me no
above oh
above
yeah this is not the
this is really not a good way to learn
korean i i
i gave this bird another chance today
but i already know this is not how i
should be learning the language they're
just randomly throwing these words at me
i feel like
but my goal to be honest is i'm not
trying to really learn from dylan i was
just hoping to pick up maybe some words
i mean i know cucumber now it sounds
like
we
um
but my plan just so you know
was learning the writing first and then
getting private one-on-one uh online
lessons from
korean people teachers
uh there's some like services for that
where you can like have a
one hour or two hour lesson through the
internet like in a video conversation or
so
um and have them teach you for a
conversation so because that's how i
learned japanese through conversation
which
but yeah the only reason i'm doing this
with duolingo is because it's the only
thing we can use right now for streaming
oh up and down i love exit song up and
down oh we
we
oh
above
and uh uh we
[Music]
uh i i don't know i never really heard
it correctly
we added we
we
need
[Music]
say yo yo
yo
yo yo
okay
wow
[Music]
yo
this sucks yo
[Music]
same word without the last sign to it
mm-hmm
[Music]
i
was it not eggy iggy
i heard in
korean tv shows it sounded more like
eggy
why does this sound like
[Music]
ah yes
cucumber milk
wow
cucumber milk and that is really
surprising indeed i would say wow too
what fox's milk oh wait yo
fox's milk oh i thought it was cucumber
milk box milk oh my god the child's
yo-yo
[Music]
maybe that's yo-yo i'm guessing yeah it
even looks like a yo-yo
[Music]
the child yo-yo
what wait wait wait wait
wait
we
[Music]
now that's the second one
on the cucumber
the first one was right it should have
been i should have been this one
really
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh thank god the chat is confused too
i thought i thought i'm doing everything
wrong
okay
there's another type where it's only the
alphabet
yeah i saw that but i came here to learn
some words
and i'm learning things like yo-yo
which is
very korean indeed on the yo-yo
yo-yo
[Music]
you
yo
[Music]
nothing sounds like words to me it just
sounds like baby sounds
love
[Music]
oh you
oh yeah oh yeah the yo-yo oh yeah
yeah you yo no no
are you saying the child yo-yo
oh yeah
oh yeah the the yo-yo
is it are they saying
yeah yo-yo
oh yeah
that's just yo-yo
it's not my yo-yo it's the child's yo-yo
it's okay i can't play with a yo-yo
anyway you do you you probably can have
more fun with it
yeah oh yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
what
yeah
um
okay
i am so confused
i i feel like i knew more korean before
using duolingo today
you
yeah
[Music]
holy
i am
a genius
in the guessing game
you guys are so confused
you're down let's be confused together
[Laughter]
fox
milk huh why where's the wow i hear it's
about
fox
fox's milk
oh
oui
wait
we
[Music]
be b
b
b b
we
be
[Music]
we
you
that's so stupid
even the chat says that the
pronunciation even the korean people
seem to say that the pronunciation is
just weird in here
oh my god
on the yo-yo
yo-yo
[Music]
no which one was above again
wait we can look at it
i don't see it
[Music]
yo
yo-yo comes first ah
[Music]
oh stop it with the wing leaves
me
we
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm not happy
not happy about this
[Music]
where can i learn proper korean
here we do basics
no that doesn't look good to me how
would i
how would i know this how would i know
this i mean i can look at it but like
this doesn't make sense to me
huh let's do greetings
you gotta
[Music]
yes there is one choice and i will
choose that you gotta
ignore
[Music]
nice to meet you i am jonan maybe
yes i am
[Music]
don't come at me with that that's
so useless but cute blue cat that you
had song
song
okay
[Music]
i can
i can tell you that i know
what the
choi
should look like
probably
i think
chile
is probably this one yes
because i see the the choi
yeah yeah yeah
what what else
song
[Music]
what is that
what's that last part
[Music]
uh
you mean we learned that before maybe or
it's just a name it's probably just a
name
i thought i'm learning why are you
teaching me names i will never
understand this
tell me words not names
what channel
i am who
i needed
[Music]
to
m
[Music]
didn't we say it differently last time
yeah but why does it go first here
doesn't doesn't she say choi first
tell me something
don't isn't she saying joy first tell
you something to me that
oh no wait maybe not
i don't know
[Music]
his last name is kim
right
look at all that look at all these
advertisements
[Music]
my last name
i didn't look at the signs that well
before and if i was just listening
mostly
[Music]
ah
i don't see it
[Music]
onion
last name
is park
salmon
see now it's two summoners ah
why
now it's two sides
last
[Music]
i didn't see two sons last time
maybe i'm blind minji's last name is kim
minty
minji
uh
song
[Music]
that was so hard i was sweating i was
feeling the pressure tearing me apart
and crushing me from above
[Music]
okay can i do more greetings
there's more right
thank you
[Music]
where do i see a car i see
hmm
thank you
[Music]
my name is dulingo
your name is dulingo
i feel so sorry for you who names their
child duolingo
that is not only a stupid name
because it's not a name
but
duolingo is also like nothing i would
ever name my child even if it were more
like a name because duolingo
is not the best service to learn
languages
who named their child bilingual
who's child abuse yeah do you imagine
calling your child duolingo hello
um
[Music]
i heard it before yeah nice to meet you
that's it
wait man
yeah nice to meet you meet you vanessa
pandas
[Music]
soup
me
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
nice to meet you
foreign
[Music]
something
ah
m
[Music]
no there's more than one person who's
named duolingo say
[Music]
my name
um
ah
[Music]
um
yo
[Music]
okay
oh oh guys are you ready for this this
is the difficult part
it's showdown korean time thank you nice
to meet you
[Music]
um
i guess i'm jumping to level two all
right i guess so
thank you
is there more greetings
i want more greetings no not mean no no
no no
they have something
new is it just the same
g
oh dear
i'm the type e minji
the thing is it sounds
like something else sometimes
but this is a name
it's a bit different
[Music]
my name
okay wait
i had a i had a uh
a problem communicating with my english
brain for a moment because i i totally
know that this is up grammar
someone give me that
um but the thought was correct the
thought was inside of my brain deep deep
in there it was correct but it wasn't
transmitted correctly it happens
sometimes
uh can i put some water in my
in my
cup
what's water again did i learn i know
milk but i don't know about water i know
milk is oil what is water
what's water
water again
[Music]
i heard that before
oh
[Music]
oh yeah i can see that i can see that
all right what are we listening
last name kim
ah
m
pittsburgh
my pants name
is pittsburgh
no no no no no just kidding
my
name
is
no
my last name is choi
easy peasy minty's last name is kim
mmm
mingy green
song
[Music]
oops
is that his name
is this oh what i'm writing my one oh
when i'm supposed to write in english oh
my name
ah my
last name
[Music]
thank you come me down
i am
[Music]
people
all right
cool cool greetings and springs is
pretty
good
so far
[Music]
and i don't know if we're gonna get any
more out of this though out of greetings
oh yeah right there were tips
[Music]
oh there
lots of information
no no no thank you
uh should we do a different one
i don't even want to get started with
borrowings but let me look at the tips
first
loanwords before i made into korean
grammar and vocabulary let's get to some
more effort somewhere you should already
know
aha that's why they that's why they push
some samsung and hyundai on to us
don't be surprised that some companies
and given names don't fit the
romanization we're using korean assets
situations korean is basically sometimes
your sentence final r is dropped
subsumed into the vowel like a british
pronunciation sometimes single syllables
becomes split since korean doesn't
really do consonant clusters so three
syllables united becomes five syllable
aha
they were trying to make a point somehow
what's what's end
can we do this one
this seems this could be easy why is it
loading so long
what are you learning
are you okay okay
samsung is back welcome back samsung i
i have a new phone
[Music]
is
oh
let's go
why are you laughing why are you
laughing
[Music]
why
why are you laughing no not sponsored
what
[Music]
what's happening
what
it has an issue
oh
not good for gaming but to cameras yeah
i don't i don't play games on my um on
my phone anyway
uh
i
just need the camera
gos what's the what's the g os
oh
can i change my phone still
is it the core
[Music]
yeah who who buys phones not for the
camera huh
no i didn't get a trash phone what the
no way
game optimizing system is it that bad
when i bought it
i thought i thought it had a really good
um
you know
no good core
good insights
gos basic app which downgrades your
phone battery runs out like apple
oh well i did notice that you know the
battery died faster than i expected it
to be
dying
oh come on come on you know i have to
blame the lingo for this because
obviously duolingo
manipulated my brain into buying samsung
there's no other explanation pants
i don't know pants
[Music]
hyundai
what is that
slightly
sneaky i don't know what it is but i
know
i know
oh trash
why am i learning trash okay
cindy
is trash
so my samsung
is
according to the chat
nevermind
[Laughter]
[Music]
a
ah i didn't recognize it but
ah now it's that's
the yo-yo is back welcome back yo-yo
okay samsung and hyundai
and
hyundai
[Music]
ready
uh are you speaking
korean to me
[Music]
is he speaking korean israeli
it sounds like
like a korean person trying to speak
english but who is not very good at
english
i is ready
wait what
[Music]
is
ah it sounded like you were speaking
english
ah sure
[Music]
speaking german now i see you wanna you
wanna
cuddle
[Music]
granola
but i was able to read it
so
that's already a big extra point for me
for doing my homework and learning
uh how to read korean samsung
[Music]
i don't know what you're saying but
ah
i totally get you
wait wait
[Music]
[Laughter]
trash and a key
trash and a key and they're just
teaching me how to say you know the
things like
add something something and something
something
these pants and those pants oh dear ee
ago
cool
party
[Music]
[Applause]
okay that makes sense that was that was
fun
yeah
can we do some basics but that when i
took a look at it before it scared me
what do we have here
now that we've learned how to say hello
and introduce ourselves dive deeper into
verbs yes please let's get started verb
conjugation
declarative mood
oh dear
goes it's bad it's it's good
[Music]
i don't know if i want to do this
it looks complicated
i have a car i do not have a car
[Music]
let me try to read this
chat
[Music]
i don't know
i didn't finish learning the alphabet
that's okay
i have it to a certain point where i can
try to read things
[Music]
and
no no i'm not
i wish they would write the romanized
version below
okay
i will
go back here go
status
i can read korean i am i prove it to you
i'll prove it to you okay
matching pairs
[Music]
pull
um
[Music]
jump to the next
no
[Music]
in
um
[Music]
alphabet free we're too good for this we
need to move on oh dear oh lord oh no oh
no
i can do this i can read all of this i
just have not had to deal with uh four
four letter combinations that much yet
um but it is
sorry oh oh
oh yeah you can't beat that because that
would be kang
no i didn't i don't know these i don't
know these
[Music]
apparently this is that
the gap is
this
is
[Music]
maybe that's because
it's like a double thing i don't know
i'll have to look into my other
application
that's the sound that crony makes maybe
a beer
[Music]
all right
all right we're making a lot of progress
oh my god
i i know that word why do i know is it
like awesome
[Music]
where let's go taku
oh no it's just a city what am i
thinking of
heigl city
what am i thinking of
[Music]
i'm thinking of tibak oh i'm thinking of
tibbak
[Music]
why is it now only one
god
[Music]
why
why is it written like this
[Music]
why is the person like this
i feel like i can write it differently
[Music]
because there's an r there and a k
wouldn't it be b a r k
[Music]
it's a silent r
but even a silent r you write out in
letters
you just don't say it
workbook bark bark barbark
but okay
dulingo
we play by your rules
i give you another chance and i must
play by your rules all right i will
adjust myself to you
shake my head duel and go
and take
bark
[Music]
let me look in my notes but wasn't that
s
wasn't that esther
why is that now teal
i am so confused let me show you
now if it were me
i would write
[Music]
i would write this like
what was t again
i'm blanking
yeah yeah
can i not write it like this
why does it say
write it like
this when i thought this was s
[Music]
yeah and then we also had
why is this also cut
[Music]
why is there so many
same pronunciation different meaning
[Music]
but now
when the s is at the bottom it sounds
like a t
um
you know what this is okay i will accept
this for now and i will just have to
um
ask my teacher when i get lessons when i
get private lessons that's something for
another time
[Music]
later later a little later
but that's what was confusing me you
know
okay
[Music]
think this
pickle
yeah
cut oh dear oh it's this again oh wait
you didn't see it
it's this again
cut
[Music]
at the bottom i'm so i'm so confused
gas pronunciation is fast oh
and because you say it so fast because
gas gas gas you accidentally say got got
got okay you were beat friends the song
is now got cut
[Music]
[Applause]
i'll now get harder learning content on
yo oh please no
on the yo
no no
please now
okay
i wanna i want some person a human
person to teach me korean
i
i i
i i can't deal with a computer like this
i need a human to teach me
what else should we do we were on uh two
here too here to here belongings one but
belongings suck let's
let's look at boro wings i guess
sensei please i don't know if cronie
wants to teach me i'm not sure
[Music]
i will ask nabi
now please
[Music]
please
korean than duolingo
even though it's just a translator isn't
there something wrong there okay chicago
right chicago in korean okay they're
just testing me
um
chicago
she
she chicago chicago chicago chicago
pizza boco they pronounce it so cute
pittsburgh
pizzabago
pizza vagon old pizza
that sounds so cute
chicago
[Music]
boston
it looks like a wine glass
well this is it isn't it boss
yeah that's boston
yeah i think so
[Music]
philadelphia
see now i'm not so mad at this anymore
because i can actually practice my
reading
[Music]
p p p p p
p
[Music]
the r is silent here
oh
that that little r
is silent
i think p p
p
this is another r
ah
not silent oh
peter feel
it's just two l's i guess then um
boston pilate piano
[Music]
boston austin
peachburg princeton philadelphia
pittsburgh peterborough princeton
platform
philadelphia
what
princeton philadelphia better start with
pittsburgh last summer pittsburgh
pittsburgh pit pit peach bug princeton
[Music]
princeton
okay okay just choose all the
complicated ones pizza burgers
[Music]
there's not a single korean word here
but okay it's called loanwords okay the
lesson is called loanwords and i'm just
practicing
my reading here we must forgive them
[Music]
chicago
newspaper easy because it sounds like
the japanese word for newspaper
nihongo
pittsburgh
pitts
pits pitch
pitch poor portal or something like that
pizza
pizza vegan
chicago
chicago chicago
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what is that pink super chat
[Music]
um pittsburgh princeton philadelphia oh
my god how many times are we going to
repeat them
peach
[Music]
the entrance the end transit
entrance
[Music]
is there any word i'm missing
i don't know hell
so
oh that's so
pretty
it just
[Music]
i didn't look at it so closely
opposite
[Music]
i just need to change the order i
thought i forgot the word okay
look at this
look at this chart carefully stones
rising endlessly oh it's inspiring it's
fascinating kiana recently is just a big
ball
manifestation of inspiration because i
make you guys work out i make you guys
cook and now i make you guys study
languages oh my god can i be any more of
an idol huh
[Music]
oh
maximum idle i have so much power in my
hands if i can make you guys study and
cook and work out what else can i make
you guys do
what else i i need to use my power
wisely
ah lucio
oh it's almost two hours the time passes
by so fast oh god i wanna i wanna look
into these
let me look into basics
oh yeah this is the yabby okay we'll
just go into it we'll just dive into it
low expectations
okay
we'll force it we're brute voice it
um
okay
i am pun
really pun
really
no way no
[Music]
m
how do you write that
[Music]
um
cool
[Music]
um
she
[Music]
oh
the man sleeps now wait which one which
part is sleeping
[Music]
the man
which part is sleeping ah
[Music]
nam
um
[Music]
my focus has broken i have no more focus
guys
it enters one ear and it leaves on the
other side
yeah i only used a lot of my brain cells
yesterday and it hasn't fully recovered
yet it's not even been 24 hours
my portal brain that's one ear is one
portal my left ear is my orange portal
and my right ear is my blue portal and
this enters the orange ear and then
leaves out of the blue ear
this is what i mean when i say i have a
portal burn
i made that up now i didn't really think
of that when i tweeted out portal brain
[Music]
it's a personal
it it was a long one does does garam
study
stop doubting him why is everyone
everyone doubting him i
am i work
[Music]
can you say that again
i i always forget but this is a eggy
eggy
[Music]
and the woman called
wow it's an actual proper sentence at
this point
they call what on the phone
is
[Music]
thank you
your name is something like
uh
let me read your name
i don't know
ah i'm not so confident yet when i read
something
without any hint but thank you and
continue
oh thank you i know you listened to
orange thank you
come sanita
so sweet i ah everybody
thank you
everybody needs to listen to my new song
color with energy
it's so
sweet it's on energy channel have you
guys listened to it
have you have you have you
that man works
[Music]
on
um
[Music]
m i forgot i forgot something in between
ah whatever
the man and the woman call
yeah
i
[Music]
my portal brain is not working anymore
foreign
[Music]
okay
i had an exhausting week
so this is it this all my my portal
brain can take right now
well i think i at least got some
practice with my reading
[Music]
no more no more no thank you no thank
you
um thank you thank you
but it was nice having all the korean
viewers over again uh looking watching
over me
studying korean thank you everybody i
will do my best to continue
at least i can read it partially now so
after getting some more uh practice i
can
do my best and read korean super chats
without opening papago
[Music]
but
i think my best chance of learning daily
conversation
is not with duolingo but with an actual
human person teaching me something a
teacher
yeah so
let's get a teacher one for the stream
and one for private lessons yeah
i will do that i just need some time
because i'm very busy until the end of
the month which is soon
uh and may is also a bit but i will try
i will try to get it started in in may
thank you for all the super chats and
the memberships i will i will read some
super chats now but i don't know if
we'll get to the ones from today where
did we leave up last time you guys know
but this stream was basically also just
to push me to actually
get started with learning the writing
system so
everything is good mission accomplished
have you come to korea sometime i want
to go this year
it's actually in my mind pretty
pretty
decided 100
but i want to go with someone and i
don't know with who i even want to go
with someone or i want to meet with
someone there but i don't know
i don't know
who
so
yeah i don't want to be all alone i feel
like i would get lost yeah i guess i
need to read easter super chats
i actually i i
i wrote i asked
if anyone wants to go to korea with me
in our discord but no one answered
so yeah maybe i can meet up with navi i
don't know
maybe not we can show me around
it's okay they're busy maybe and
maybe not not everybody saw the message
yeah yeah it's okay
go with rnt yeah rmt is very interested
in going but it would be even better to
go with someone who has a little bit of
korean knowledge
or has been to korea before
yeah yeah
navi will navigate me yes
oh
so sweet yes navi please navigate to me
[Music]
navigation
navi
w emma
that is so smart she's my navigator oh
my god
how i didn't it was like literally right
there why did i never think of it
navigation
no more google maps use navi mama
so thank everybody for watching and i
will i will continue to stream today i
will just read super chats and tomorrow
we have
probably if everything goes well we'll
play for the first time
and
the legend of zelda the wind waker
i'm looking forward to it but very very
exhausting wink
[Music]
can't wait for the stream to thank you
i'm excited too
yay wouldn't wake up
weekends when we go weekends but i
already have to say um actually
i think the
um
wind waker weekends
will start
no not immediately
um it will it will be a thing but not
immediately i don't even man now i'm
like loki thinking maybe i should take
tomorrow off and start wind waker on
sunday
i'll think about it because i need some
preparation time and some chill time i
feel like this week was just too much i
was doing so much behind the scenes
and um you guys thank you
we'll start with a wind waker sunday and
then we'll we'll work ourselves up to
the wind waker weekends maybe
you guys are so sweet i love you i love
you
[Music]
okay i'll tell you about my final
decision later on um now let's go to my
office
and
let's go
what
happened what's happening what's
happening why is there music here
why was there music but you know what we
can we can have some music
[Music]
oh my god
you hear this wait do you hear it right
now
you even hear it
[Music]
yeah it's nostalgic because i don't use
it anymore that often was my original
bgm that i used a lot in the beginning
this one and
this one and uh this one
[Music]
oh my god
let's start with this one
okay
let me go
ah let me go to
youtube studio
yeah the classics
very nostalgic that's casino
once once we got that audio stock
subscription it's like
ah
so much choice you know
it's nice having your own original
that you completely own the rights to
but
audio stuff just has so much
like a huge library that i can
immediately make use of
it's just
[Music]
how can i resist
i can't
[Music]
i am hungry too old odossio i ate french
toast did you see my tweet
i wanted to make pancakes again but i
realized my
bananas are not in the best shape for it
i had one really old banana and i had
three really green small bananas
so i was like
i don't know so i made french toast
instead i haven't made french those in a
while and today
it turned out so good might have been my
best french toast ever
mmm
[Music]
french toast
i still use the older banana i don't
know i used i used one of the older
bananas in the banana milkshake
yesterday and it already tasted kind of
like not so fresh anymore i mean it was
so fine i still drank it but that was
yesterday so today
yeah my i think it's the the placement
where i put them they're like really in
the shadow they don't get any daylight
either
so
maybe that's part of why they go dark so
fast
i could make banana bread but i only
have one of them so
probably not enough and i never made
banana bread before
we gotta try sometime
[Music]
every time oh how about a banana cupcake
if i can't make a banana bread can i
make a banana cupcake i know it will
probably land in the sureki
in the trash
you know what i might remember that word
words that i remember from today
[Music]
a cucumber was like wee wee wee
we
i don't know what exactly uh
what else do i remember
[Laughter]
um
not much not not many new words what did
i learn what did i learn
cool is like that
um
fox milk
oh you are new already fox i already
forgot
baby
i already kind of knew before
no this stream was not pointless i had
to practice my reading
fox was like yo
yo yo yo oh yeah yo yo
yo-yo is not really a korean word though
i'm not sure what i learned
oh yeah carl i forgot
that was at the end so
and i already knew i'm not going to
remember any of that
but but i know i learned
[Music]
nice to meet you mama
this one i want to remember
[Music]
okay
okay okay and i learned a different
variation of anio haseo
that i'm not gonna use
[Music]
okay
we are gonna read super chats
um
from
uh the
easter stream i think
isn't that a cute thumbnail
that is a cute thumbnail i must say
catch up time
okay feel free to stay everybody i will
do my best to catch up now patsy duncan
stratosphere
conduction human extinction rokenzie
duncan
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
what's that new profile picture that i
see
oh it's cute that's from dakuma isn't it
i recognize that style
cute
did you commission that
it's it's me kiwawa
staying till the end thank you
my beloved
help me cuter that's cute you're cute
too
i commissioned oh that's so cute thank
you
welcome eggs please proceed to the next
room where attention will apply your
makeup for the upcoming shift oh
remember that the camp medical plan does
not cover getting spontaneously crushed
by kiana but you will be a glorious
reminder of the consequences for
betrayal
that's funny but nobody got crashed
thankfully i put an extra layer of
safety on them before you know just for
extra precaution
just got here
welcome
never miss kiwawa's tensions for the
world thank you
[Music]
after the trash can excuse me
excuse me
excuse me that was not my fault
that was not my fault
that trash can wasn't even a real trash
can
it was just like
some
some two sticks
two sticks with some
thing on the top
you guys if you guys would sit on that
it would break immediately for me at
least it broke after
a little while okay it didn't break
immediately if you guys would sit on it
it would break immediately
[Music]
no no
no
you guys could lift me with a finger
are you calling us fat
i'm calling you
bigger than me
[Applause]
i mean i'm the one feeding you guys so
i know you fluffalicious butts
[Music]
yes okay no shame in that yeah i'm i'm
trying to get you freaking plump
for that kfp bucket
okay duncan thank you for the sweet
message here's a kiss mwah
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
invite her back to korea
what do you mean
we mean
what
do you mean
what do you
[Music]
what do you mean
is this a joke
[Music]
i want to go to korea
explain kiara
it's jork
yeah probably convention right i was
thinking so too you guys are thinking of
a branch
i am the branch i am the whole tree
felix el thank you for the rest of the
channel happy easter it's the time of
the year for us to paint the new
employees yeah i hope we find them all
and leave no one stuck in the usual room
thank you for your super chat
yeah
painting those new employees was a very
cute ritual we should do it every year
it will be our tradition
painting the new members
yeah already looking forward to next
year's easter then
[Music]
nice to see you again anthony
a big kiss for you
thank you for the red superchat and your
generous support
i hope you're doing well
mod arcade dankeshen randy rj dankeshen
onyo there's a korean name
wait didn't
i just got it
come on kiwa you can read this um
it's so small though
let me make it bigger
oh no it scrolled all the way back up
when i made it bigger
oh
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait oh
wait wait wait wait wait wait there we
are there we are there we have found it
found it found on the sponge foundation
there you go okay okay okay
okay let me look at mine
that
is probably
[Music]
um
that one was
see now when i'm under pressure i forget
everything
away
that sounds familiar
[Music]
onion
yes you did i read it wrong
yes you
yes the one with the shark
the one with the shark face
[Music]
well now chad goes so fast
thank you
oh
it's a super chat that's ah it's mixed
it's uh there is like some super chats
that are mixed into the hand cam stream
this one this is not from this one yeah
it's mixed
it's it's one from today
ah maybe that's why you were confused as
well
that you hear your own name when we're
reading these ones
and it was your first time watching my
stream when i say your name like a
million times
wow okay you know what
uh
now
you
can never leave me
now you
are
part of kfp
you have to love
hey
thank you very much for your compliance
i wonder i wonder if you expected to
become my number one korean fan today
yay
welcome patsy duncan but this one is
also from the duolingo stream for some
reason uh papa duncan's back and i'm
dunking for the red super chat
nice to meet you bonkers oh yeah oh
bunkers oh
[Music]
i have to tell you something guys
um
how did i say this um
so after the bonkers incident
um
i
you know sometimes i do eagle search in
japanese on
on twitter
and
after the bonkers incident somebody
somebody clipped um the bonkers incident
in japanese
oh it's not so bad guys
it's not that bad no no no no bonking to
me
um but um
uh
i've i've noticed yes yeah
i've noticed a lot of the japanese
people
really think i have a raccoon now
like a real
i mean of course it's a real raccoon but
so many
japanese people
actually really think i have a raccoon
now because i
there were a lot of japanese comments on
twitter not replies to me but just like
people who saw the clip and they're like
oh hey wow kiara has a real raccoon oh i
didn't know you can have that as a pet
oh well yeah
and that was before coyote
put me in her news again
um this time with the bonkers news
probably
strengthening the belief on the japanese
side even more
that i
have a raccoon which i totally have i
mean it
[Laughter]
[Music]
getting mixed signals well i'm i'm in a
difficult position right now okay i
i i have a raccoon what do you mean
[Music]
it's a raccoon with the paws of a cat
but it's a raccoon hundred 100
okay
i mean look at the colors it's obviously
raccoon at least i think it's a raccoon
um
maybe
no it's a raccoon
maybe this is okay maybe we should let
them think i have a raccoon which i do
[Music]
see i don't mind um bonkers showing up
whenever
you know in in these moments where
where you know
my raccoon goes bonkers
and goes that's a cheeky thing
it just fits
the raccoon very well
um no raccoon raccoon
it is a raccoon
it's not a cat
so anyway
thank you spanking time
it was just a funny observation
um
it's very cute that people think i
really have a raccoon
because
i do have a raccoon um
but it's very cute that they believe it
because why would i lie i don't lie
um
it's an enhanced truth
it is
an enhanced
truth
raccoon
as we learned yesterday
enhanced truth
[Laughter]
is
name
[Music]
foreign
service unavailable due to temporary
error papa go on
papa go
when i tried to make papa go read
something out loud oh no wait
the way i had it wrong
no dying not cornering but close enough
okay okay
talk cold would have been different i
think
the reason why i read it is cool
accidentally is because it looks very
similar to the japanese katakana for
coal
it's just um flipped
yeah yeah it confuses me some of these
things look so similar and it doesn't
work in my brain
um people have asked me many times
before
if like i ever have a problem with like
my languages mixing up in my brain or
when i speak or whatever
and no they didn't do that at all
because they're all very different and i
all have them pretty much mastered
at a level where i don't need to think
about what i'm saying
but now that korean
is part of it ah
[Music]
became a member
and now that korean is part of it
yeah korean and the signs at least
mix up a little bit
but it also helps a little bit you know
with the japanese knowledge
and welcome
welcome
you see i i got him
the moment i talked to him
he was like oh i need to become a
member now
[Applause]
richard likes
pies duncan
i can see your credit card information
reflecting off the egg quick paint them
before it's too late i'll even have a
credit card
oh thank you for the membership
annyeong
thank you
have you ever had a situation
where you are talking to someone in a
certain language and then the second
lady you forgot to switch back to
english
[Music]
no no i'm not sure
that's a that's a very detailed
situation
[Music]
how are you building credit
i'm not feeling credit that's the
problem probably
[Music]
uh thank you thank you come sign me now
oh my god
let me try to read that
um
what kind of name is that
[Music]
what does that mean
yeah it sounds like i'm chanting
but it was a good uh reading practice
grow up to retreat
[Music]
did you choose a baby name so i can read
it easily
maybe not but if you did then that's
pretty cute
grow grow tree tree
cute
ah
doctor zilla for christmas
and motion
the previous super chat asks canada
which is your favorite rpg publisher
maker
square namco nippon ichi and which is
your favorite rpg franchise tales of
final fantasy et cetera are you really
asking me this question
bandai namco of course
and tales of
do you understand who you're asking this
question i'm the official
english ambassador for tales of arise
okay
forever
all the way back i love you babcock
i was just curious okay understandable
no but um i think in general bandai
namco
um puts out a lot of great rpg games
that i've enjoyed so far
um
square enix 2 if only i could
stream them um
yeah i i mean
they all have great games nippon ichi as
well
they all have great entries so
but
for me it's obviously
you know tails off so
bandai napko is winning
easily
[Music]
thanks for the membership renewal
and kingo duncan
greek easter is next week oh
i didn't know you have a different
easter egg
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat you got
me with that fit show announcement plus
i'm glad kiana has time to meet with
members for new collabs and projects
making new friends and keeping in touch
with others we can commence the kicking
of the spring festivities welcome to
vodka some new eggs
thank you for welcoming my raccoon
thank you
my raccoon feels very very happy about
being so lovid and famous
uh yeah
sorry for
scaring some of you with the fit show
announcement but
i as i said i thought it was
pretty harmless yo
and um
yeah uh
looking forward to meeting other whole
life members again this year
and the whole live english members and
elena
i'm gonna make some special memories
hopefully
i think i need to go to an idol meeting
thank you dr tech
can i go to an idol meeting
a brb
[Music]
my
hello bunkers
little bunkers
[Music]
she won't talk
bonkers maybe i just need to get chokers
[Music]
so soft what a soft baby what
i need one of these for bunkers
in jolly style
it would look so so cute
and you think jolly dress is cute
[Music]
yes raccoon and cat
this is like uh australia
the good old australia
[Music]
yeah funkus could be like hanging
outside the window doing bonkers stuff
climbing outside and doing parkour
and being like you can't catch me huh
i'll disturb your stream i'll be on cam
even if you don't want me to
bonkers
my raccoon
okay wow i have something in your eye
are you good
so tanoki got bonkers
neko got chunkers to
smoothie maybe one day i'll i'll get a
fourth uh pet a second raccoon
called
[Music]
ch
movie
[Laughter]
smoothie smoochie and chocolates and
bonkers
such
i want that to raccoon now
that is adorable
[Music]
perfectly balanced yeah
okay i need to read the pachatos
boondock duncan violet evil garden
duncation
dancy thank you for the red super chat
mwah
dear kiara you always work hard and do
your best to make a stream worth
watching from speaking both english and
japanese to include as many views as
possible to organizing great content and
always giving you all and everything
thank you for all you do stay amazing
[Music]
thank you that's so sweet
i i do try my best thank you for seeing
that and acknowledging it and praising
me for it so kind
thank you and then
you're so sweet let me let me get a
fruit candy by the way for sure
[Music]
thank you very much for your support
hope you will continue enjoying and
supporting my content from now until
then thank you one more
[Music]
hope you had
a fun easter even though you probably
don't celebrate it but together with me
we celebrate every day
thank you tai chi mwah
hey catch monkey dankeshan garden park
thank you for the pink super chat come
sanita
greetings boss i got a smaller one for
presenting postal work in conference
poster thank you for being my night
experiment lab supervisor that you may
not have noticed
uh
oh it's very long let me put that in
papako some of these look difficult
[Music]
yeah
happy easter not anymore it's kind of
late but thank you i was able to read it
correctly part of it and then i gave up
thank you
and uh congratulations on
the award
yeah is it a physical award like a
little golden statue or something like
that
or a silver one or so that's cool
that's really cool congratulations
dr zilla 337 thank you an optimus prime
thank you
typhon
g d thank you
and rent production
made a small fan video for kfc workers
and attention would you consider let me
know which hashtag is fit for fan videos
oh did you not post it yet
i know
ah
i see one are you talking about an old
video you you don't know where to post
it red brick are you here
korean food lecture for tacoma together
and kfp employees
is it this one
[Music]
and what's this is cute
43 minutes
korean food and snack suggestion for
miss takanashi kiara
[Music]
right freak are you here
oh it's so long
oh
it's a whole presentation about korean
food
i saw you
hi oh it's making me hungry
mashed up
ah
oh what the
oh
i hate you
[Music]
okay you know what this could be helpful
when i go to korea
or maybe even before oh
oh
[Music]
wait
oh dear
you're writing it so english-speaking
person can read it huh that
pronunciation where's the toilet where's
the one
[Music]
is where is the toilet and where is the
water dispenser
[Music]
woody
it's even giving me
korean lessons this presentation there's
like words um
[Music]
pop
this is teaching me more than duolingo
already
chopsy
oh
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah
the english pronunciation
underneath confuses me
earl
arrow maya
huh
[Music]
why are you kicking your pillow why
this is well made
i'm just just skipping through it now
but yeah it's uh how much is this
[Music]
you're my teacher
i'm my teacher now
oh
oh now i really want to go to korea even
more
thank you
um you can um stuff like this you can
post under the fan art hashtag that's
okay or the hashtag kfp hashtag fee we
use for
like clips and
for
um
people just posting anything kfp related
and uh commenting about my streams
live commenting on twitter
so yeah yeah
[Music]
okay if you is like you can't really go
wrong with kfp
um
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat guys
what do i do i love takana she's too
cute first stream i'm able to catch in a
while it really makes me appreciate how
enjoyable this is hey you got a good
stream for the first time in a while and
you you watch the egg painting stream
that's a good one
by the way you're always talking about
how much you like massages actually
convince me to book one oh
no no what kind of massage i wonder
there's so many different ones
i really like getting massages but it's
not like they
they
completely get rid of my pain it's just
nice for the moment i should get one
again sometime soon when i got time
hope you hope it was a good one if you
already had it if it already happened
hope it was good
thank you
thank
you guys are working together to remind
me um
about the art
[Laughter]
there's a raccoon
oh it's so cute
[Music]
chart what are you talking about
um
doug hood thank you for the pinky
and mama tell your coffee machine fans
oh
she refused but
uh
i'll use it for something else
for her
a ticket to visit me i guess
thank you all for the pinky duck hood
thank you soon
censored herman thank you so much
yesterday was my birthday oh i'm still a
baby chicken so i'm not sure who's
supposed to get the present so here's
one for you
my first red super for my oshie and i
mean it and for the wonderful phoenix
that lights up my day
thank you
happy birthday it's it's now quite uh
quite a few days have passed but
um
i'll sing you happy birthday anyway
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear sonora
happy late birthday to you
congratulations
thank you for your support
thank you
hope you had a great birthday oh my
there was a pink one there too sorry i
wasn't able to be here since the
beginning but i swear i'll be here with
kfb supporting you for whatever is left
of eternity
well said
don't worry about it
it's not something you really can't
control if you didn't find me earlier
but now you're staying and that's what
counts that what's that's what matters
thank you
soon
jim tracy duncan
counting cyrus dancing open the mic
thanks for the pinky
tantra i have completed the technical
report on today's inspection of the mech
and placed it on your desk
there were no major findings of zero
accidents however the technicians found
an egg in the cockpit we aren't sure who
it belongs to what are you trying to say
what are you trying to say that i
accidentally left an egg there
noah
no
that was my breakfast maybe if anything
thank you
[Music]
hmm i think you're confused
you need to stop drinking while you're
at work
hey
dick rue duncan
hearts of trashes
who's up silly fellow
um
[Music]
is that
a portal brain
portal brain
see
[Music]
like this
it says but i don't know the context
anymore
damn it
i full gore
it's been too long sorry that i took so
long to read your super chat
i have other priorities right now
honestly i'm too busy holy
that was when you said about meet and
greet
[Music]
oh
the month is always almost over next
week it's over
i still need to finish tales of the rice
i said i will do it within this month
i'm so busy next week
maybe i'll complain tomorrow if i take
tomorrow
[Music]
but i finished recording
uh my vocals including harmonies for my
new song
i did that yesterday
i think
or the day before yesterday
i couldn't have been up the portal
because i was so dead after portal and i
still had had to make food and then of
course the food kept me awake
even though i was tired
um
but it was worth it portal was worth it
yeah
okay
uh obvious thank you thank you
great victory one five one zero
i need to sneeze
almost
it's like a in between
[Music]
thank you
thank you alex duncan looking for the
top duncan
alex duncan
[Music]
thank you
oh wait there's nabi
does nami mean butterfly and that's why
she has ah that butterfly design
or the other way around no i guess nabi
came first and then the butterfly design
[Music]
navi is butterfly in korean
thank you
now i noticed yeah
yeah
she has everything themed around
butterflies
i learned that in the past already
really
oh
well
bird brain
portal brain
the game mccree
dominic
and ken duncan
thank
we're done with the easter egg super
chat guys
[Music]
okay
okay the members only i think i did read
during the members only so i can skip
skippery do those
scrolling okay now let's read monopoly
um by the way i can't promise that i
will read everything today
but let's see let's see how close we got
[Music]
that was a great game of monopoly
right
that was a good one
like
there was
there was trading
there was pain there was happiness
there was everything
but we still like had a great time there
was there was a lot of like
table turning
unexpected happenings
[Music]
and i honestly when i put this group
together i wasn't sure
if it would work so well
because
i just put you know i put ollie there
because i wanted to collab something
with ollie then i put reina there
because i love reina
and i don't know i
you know when i think of idea i think of
reina
and then i put ami there because i
wanted an en member but one who wasn't
there last time
and i love ami so
you know i'm a brain goes to ahmed
it was just you know i didn't really
think it through i just randomly put
some girls together and it actually
worked out really well
[Music]
oh and after this collab
guess who messaged me
immediately
[Music]
senpai
he was like i love not playing let's
play monopoly
[Laughter]
i'm like i know you love monopoly let's
let's indeed play monopoly
aki senpai wants to play monopoly with
um
ian girls i don't know about
communication but
maybe it will be like one of the en
members who can speak japanese i'm not
sure
i'll do my best that will be the next
monopoly collab maybe
she she doesn't need to know how to
communicate in english because she knows
how to communicate in monopoly she's
very very very very very
pro
at monopoly she's a monopro
[Music]
well
there are quite a few people to choose
from
so
eventually i don't want to do it
immediately because we just had a
monopoly collab
and i'm busy anyway
so it's not going to happen immediately
and it will need some time but monopoly
will come back international moguls will
come back again
look forward to it
mr kazmig's duncan travertine jacket
monkey thank you mr sanchez
evans
why why
oh because of free kisses
yo
that's too much that's too generous the
someone
someone needs to hold back
mr doug
from super chatting yo
hey boss can i dedicate free kiana
kisses he doesn't even want them from it
for himself
juan to christina manzanita you mean
bonker uh christina wants a ceiling fan
and one of course the papa hook it
all that birthdays this week ah oh you
only
also you're gonna win this time
i didn't quite win but i was very close
to it and if you don't win all those gym
kids will purr and look cute and fluffy
until you feel like a winner oh man
i wanted to lose to see that
purring cute fluffy chickens
let me look at the chat maybe i can see
it maybe i can see it
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's pretty good that's pretty good
it's not bad
that's pretty cute
oh it's pretty cute you know i know i'll
give you that
that's pretty cute it wasn't pretty cute
pretty cute
okay okay i'll give a lot of kisses to
you guys
and went to christina
[Music]
mr ceiling fan
and
happy birthday to all of you
what an exciting birthday week
wow and thank you for being so generous
dog
thank you
[Music]
so sweet you're like an angel
giving away these kisses
maybe he or maybe you're uh what's his
name um amore um amor amor huh
the guy from valentine's day
[Music]
the gamer thank you
um
[Music]
hey
glory to watson industries make
frankie's rules the markets
motto is supporting
amelia watson
i see how it is
that's the
moto sun that i know
nice to see you back again
always has been
[Music]
but but in the end
do you feel stupid now because
ame was third place and i was second how
does it feel
i mean
even even if she wouldn't have um
you know deceived i think
she deceit in a moment where she was it
was already going downwards for her
because i was going upwards too much i
got in i was i was
inclining and she was declining
[Music]
she did so well in the beginning though
yeah
but
you never know
you never know what happens in monopoly
although i thought i thought that was
monopoly
especially because of last time that
it's very clear in the beginning
and i think usually it is
like if you if you like get good
properties in the beginning
um
then you probably
gonna have a good time at the end
but look at me
i went from the very bottom
to the almost top
yeah yeah yeah i had so much bad
luck in the beginning holy that
it's not even
it's not even funny
the amount of times i
landed on fields
my first turn couldn't buy property
while everybody else was buying property
again
and then i was in jail and then i landed
on other people's property and like i
had a slow start once again and i
thought it was over but you know what
you know what
i was still enjoying it
that was rough so respect for me to um
going back up there
negative to positive
yeah
it's the schrodinger's luck
pink bacon 99 duncashin brandon dankesh
and sean are thank you for the pinkie
some fail money sir attention oh thank
you
jail man
that was so up
i was so unlucky maybe
it was because i was the host maybe the
host is unlucky in monopoly
[Music]
also i barely got like double
um
dices
double dice
two in the beginning i barely got them
while amen for example got a lot of them
[Music]
ebby and taco burrito
are done are astonishing optimus prime
star tale duncan rowan hood thank you
for the pink super chat i have to go to
sleep because i have work in six hours
hope you luck holds kiara i'm definitely
going to check the archive to see who
won later oh i suppose you sensed this
when i was already doing a little bit
better
you're saying my luck holds
so you must have already seen
some positive luck there
um
thank you thank you thank you
uh i won don't no need to watch the
archive i win i win
[Music]
kfb always winning
miguel marcie has dancing fisher's
fruits fish fish official thanksgiving
dominic
thank you man
dominican
what was that again what was that again
for the pinky pink sticker
cute
thank you oh this is uh it's like a
treasure chest with filled with cash um
nice treasure chest thank you
yeah i won the beauty contest oh yeah
that's why almond was second that that's
the thing i won
how did you find out
i was being so vague about it
how did you know
pink bacon duncan
random collusion thank you for the pinky
start the fire today
that was
it was not my intention to start a fire
today
did i accidentally start a fire in
monopoly
hmm i started a i started a history
that's for sure
never has kfp ever seen kiwawa so
successful in a board game
kfb keeps on being surprised by their
manager every day these days
such devastation
actually true
naked chicken thank you
thank you for the red super chat gg oh
that's at the end of it now
it was a gg
i agree
i agree with that thank you very much
thai team
good tasting duckies
oh my god there's a polo on my daddy
magura
there you go sound
sound for you
kanauru use it
make an inception
created
create the inception i'm waiting for it
welcome
content acquired
that's what you were waiting for weren't
you
and chris duncan jim transition
s17 b32 thank
[Music]
good game daniel don't worry i have
never liked to sell for you but no
no need for selling legs in that
monopoly game
we were part of the winners okay
no need to sell your leg keep it keep it
or sell it to someone else but keep it
thank you though
thank you for supporting and believing
in your boss
the game recruit duncan changes
duncan and fried screw duncan
there we go
we're done with monopoly super chat
okay
we're gonna do
we're gonna do portal and then we'll
probably end it
this thumbnail is too cute isn't it
oh my god so cute
oh my god so cute oh my
god i did a funny thing with the
background too
i i took a picture of a screenshot of
inside portal and then i moved it so
that it fits uh like in the logo
that the logo fits perfectly on the
portal smart graphic design is my
passion
i'm pretty proud of this thumbnail it's
simple
but it is beautiful and clean
yeah well it's just poor but
i didn't want to put it in front because
then it would cover up too much and i
thought you know this is already
recognizable enough you don't need to
see the whole logo
[Music]
i don't know just because it was there
it looks good i'm happy with this
thumbnail
[Music]
so cute
so cute that face so cute
that tongue people were like
a tongue what
what i never
knew what do you think this is
what you think that is
i just don't
put it out there because
i'm shy
but i do have a tongue
surprise
can you give us more cute panties like
this
i was especially proud of the the ones
that i uploaded uh
when i was making this thumbnail
so you guys got some good pngs on
twitter uh if you guys didn't know
um
okay
let's go
portal is fun let's read the super jets
for the pinky
piano you're a very poke champ
okay
is that twitch lingo
i think that is twitch lingo
thank you
you are also
very
poggers
[Music]
yes
miss pistachis
[Music]
let's see what you're doing don't worry
oh all right now see what you're doing
all of you
title is fetch absolutely lit no cap
it's got the drip bra you're the goat
for your dope levels with this hip lingo
you know totes
ah
beautiful
dope based super lit super lights dope
bass no bass dope super lit that was the
order i think
uh
cocoon thanks for the pinky i loved
portal back then i had lots of fun for
me this was a whole new gaming
experience that i haven't seen before i
hope you get the same feeling i wish you
tons of fun and a nice day might wash
you please enjoy it also orenz hype
oh
i mean
i mean it very much reminded me of super
liminal but you know super limitless was
released after portal i just played it
before portal
but for me i mean
it reminded me a lot of super luminol it
was not like that much of a woo never
seen something like this ever before
obviously the portals are new
but yeah um
i think i had
more issues with
did i
did i have more issues with puzzles
in super liminal
superliminal both portal and super
liminal probably just because i was
trying to finish it in one stream
felt kind of stretched for me at the end
um
i was trying to rush both of them at the
end
maybe that was maybe i just uh felt like
that because i wanted to end the stream
maybe if i would have given it more time
it wouldn't have felt so
long at the end there i don't know what
do you think
i think you did a bit better in
superliminal but that just might be in
my opinion
[Music]
i have super limitless stressed me out
because it was getting really long
um
yeah
and there's also these kind of big brain
games
i mean
you can totally finish it in one session
of course but
maybe it's because i'm a streamer i
don't know but
it feels very exhausting
after some time
no that's how i felt
um
but still nonetheless it was great fun
and uh it was a great game
that could thank you for the rest of the
chat
you're singing with nana was fantastic
boss oh thank you for listening great
harmony between your voices
oh you're changing the lyrics
all that
who
[Music]
wait
what is the melody now no that confuses
[Music]
oh
foreign
i love that song
ah
i love it
and i think
it's just it just sounds so good without
voices
ah
listen to it everybody please
please
thank you doug hood
orange kiss orange
[Music]
and to be done thank you
oh
[Music]
persona songs well you know with gaming
songs like i can't really relate to them
unless i play the game
of whatever song and i didn't play
persona
i don't know
i can't even stream it so it's not like
i can connect with it on stream and then
sing it because i liked it on stream or
so
um my somebody's asking for me to sing
persona songs in karaoke
yeah i don't know
i would love to play persona if we could
no
check this monkey dance and miss fist
dance
get buff missed fist
buff fist
the game agreed thank you
cruz
cruz duncan jim tracy duncan baby corey
wow
[Music]
thank you donkey shin
good luck and have fun with you in your
new job
tai chi thank you for the pinky
[Music]
um
yay
i know all of these i just you know need
need a few seconds to be sure that uh
what i think it means
is really true
i still need some confidence reading the
hunger
[Music]
delta
i see
so many korean people in the chat are
probably still waiting for me to read
their super chats from today
let me just say it's probably not gonna
happen
you'll probably have to wait until
sunday
uh already saying this uh as if i've
decided that i'm not streaming tomorrow
um
yeah
for tomorrow probably sleep
and uh sunday
probably read super chats from today
i like you here thank you
i'm so popular they want to get their
orders they're like they're like uber
uber eats drivers
and they're like hey hey
i need to pick up the order
come on i'm waiting
i ordered something
this is always how i feel when i'm
reading super chats i feel like i'm a
restaurant and i'm cooking up the
the food
for the drivers to pick up
and there you go and there you go and
there you go and everybody's standing in
a line and waiting
yeah
[Music]
but we are all i guess we are
but we are a restaurant
line up
chimkeys i hope you know the right order
yeah
that
wow
i'm having one of those moments you know
like
um
you know that that dress that looks uh
like a different color to some people
[Music]
but
i have it with something completely
different
look at
it to visualize it look at this
does this look like a phone to you or
like a t-shirt
it looks like a t-shirt to me even
though it's a phone
but it does look a little bit like a
t-shirt
doesn't it
now that
it's fascinating
wow
[Laughter]
ring ring ring
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding
was so cute the song orange brought back
my bitter sweet memories from my younger
chimpkin names oh
oh no
it was introduced to me by an rl girl
that i was with back then oh
an old girlfriend
anyways have fun with porno good enough
thank you
oh the t-shirts
yeah um
portal was a lot of fun thank you
and uh
well bittersweet memories
it's probably been a while right so
let's just look back at the
at the
sweet memories not the bitter ones hmm
[Music]
put the orange portal to our hearts
so i can go through your heart
it
but
but i am already in your heart no
random collusion
there's no need for a portal i'm already
in there
i know i know i know that was
beautifully
said
i'm such a
romance person wow
fascinating
poetry slam
[Music]
yeah
i'm still not thinking for those
sorry
i try my best okay
[Music]
jackson let me thank you for the pinky
oh wait
you know
i read the word portal 2
and because of the two
and the portal
even though it said nothing here
you know what it made me think of
and now i'm thinking of portals
it made me think of diablo 2
because there's also
you have to make so many portals in
diablo 2.
the apple 2 is basically
portal
1.5
the missing 1.5 portal
all those portals and they even look so
similar
your mind works funny
i don't know i saw portal 2 and i bought
the apple too
yeah i really is thinking with portals
now but seriously portland is my
favorite series so thank you for playing
this absolute gem do you plan on playing
portal 2 as well yes so originally i was
just gonna play it as a collab with kobo
but
uh you guys kind of convinced me to play
um
would it be 0.5 i'm not sure which one
was released first i guess the apple
maybe the apple i was saying um
you guys convinced me to play
uh the solo
uh portal 2
first next week
but i have to finish it with the next
week so
we're doing both
and
like two parts
next week
two days portal
and then the week after
we'll be collab with kobo
[Music]
don't be afraid to ask for help pull two
is harder
yeah i will definitely have to do two
streams because i read that the average
time is eight hours
someone says 15 to 20 hours what the
google said
google said eight dollars what are you
talking about
six to ten hours yeah that's why we're
splitting it into
two hours
get your british accent there's people
in british accents speaking there
whoa let's go
15 to 20 with side stuff oh wow
i just want to do the main stuff
[Music]
i want to take a nap um
oh
now i'm so excited for my day off
tomorrow thank you kevin
i'm so excited oh i promise i'll play
tennis of a rise tomorrow and i'll
prepare a skyward sword uh
wind wake up
and i'll also do some other things that
i should be taking care of probably and
and just chill hopefully chill a little
bit
while playing tails over rice
i need
i need a day i need a day it has been a
busy week on monday when i took the day
off i also did so much stuff
[Music]
now
and just
to warn you guys next week
um
i have a ton of doctors
appointments
and other appointments as well
so actually i'm not planning on putting
out a schedule next week
i will just make
reservations stream restorations
and then yeah but you already know there
will be portal twice
at least you know that and there should
be a collab with nancy
uh
let me remind myself
to fix a date
and by writing her message now
um
[Music]
ah
actually it might be difficult to
schedule it next week because of all the
doctor's appointments but i'll try
[Music]
okay
i'll just hear out when energy has time
worst case we'll have to move it to the
following week because my doctor's
appointments are like
taking up a lot of time next week
[Music]
i had a spain food box i wanted to do
that next week right i think do i have
it in my calendar
let me check it while i'm at it
next week
um
and i need to make a member stream next
week too but we said we're gonna watch a
movie
uh spain food
i don't know
i'm busy
[Music]
it might it will have to
it might be a weird
weird day and weird time
to watch the movie
[Music]
but for movie watch alongside
i know they're really the lamest streams
to watch in an archive
um
so i kind of prefer to put it at a good
time slot but it seems kind of difficult
next week maybe i should not do a
movie watch along with something else
i'll put a question mark in my calendar
and then
i'll think about it
and thank you guys you guys are so sweet
but i want to do it one every two weeks
so i need to keep that up
thank you guys
small color okay
oh yeah maybe
that sounds fun
i'll see what i can do
um it might not be a long memory stream
maybe just an hour or so but we'll see
we'll see i'll have to
uh
play a puzzle with my calendar and
tetris
[Music]
okay and why was i here uh casey wink
boy duncan the gamer duncan another
wearing duncan
nine five wonderful dankeshen
russell buckets thank you for the rest
of the chat
the cake is a spy
well one thing i learned the cake was
not that much of a lie so you know
i definitely
was
not
disappointed
i was surprised though
thank you russell bucket hope you
enjoyed the stream thank you for the
support
that's a tf2 reference
fortress huh
aha
soldier says that oh what the
that's so random
the game mccree duncan zigga witch
thanks for the pinky i saw you tweet
about this i don't know how to pronounce
that by the way this this this is gay
yeah
this it's not that's not how you
pronounce it right
six and it reminded me to remind me that
my first super chat to you was asking if
you're gonna play it ah i never finished
the game but had fun with hollomans in
my party hope you give it a try
[Music]
are they already available
i thought they come in what was it june
july
this gaia
[Music]
did we have a whole lot of dlc before
already
the dlc is already on the switch
oh
upper chip japanese version only
ah
yeah i'm really interested in playing it
i always had an eye on it
as i said on twitter
it looks really cute to me and
interesting
i love the
the visuals
um
it's very different
still
from the other games that i play the
system looks
weird weirdly
interesting and new to me
but i do want to give it a try
especially now the dlc yeah
it looks kind of um strategic
um
but yeah thank you
navida me to dance
and the chances of me playing it have
definitely
become much bigger now
right so freedom
jackson fb
squiggly mustache oh
there was this whole thing in the super
chats of the taco that jeans
thank you guys for the pinkies
tackle dancing agent squiggly reporting
in i got eyes on the target takodachi
investigator thanks for the pinky good
work agent squiggly proceed with
operation intense head pads
squiggly mustache thanks for the pinky
[Music]
kiana's head it's so warm so hot hot
fire i need water
taco that's investigating thanks for the
pinky squiggly get out of there oh my
god me smell delicious
that's what you get for petting my head
i don't like it
take your god damn hand
slimy hand off of my head
that taco duchy head a hand
ew ew
those tentacles ew
ew
even more eel
than just a hand
i don't like getting headphones
[Music]
thank you all of you though you both get
a kiss because those were two pinkies
each squiggly mustache
[Music]
christina wants a carefree number but
she's too shy to ask
whenever we meet rl you guys meet irl
you live
close to each other
the
that that's so unfair
i want to meet my chimpkins irl
i say that but then again i don't really
i meet you for a screen okay
i'll meet you for a screen
in meet and greets that's that's that's
that's good or or in the audience yeah
yeah yeah
you guys in the audience i'll be on
stage okay okay that sounds good that
sounds good and that's good
now there's there's you know
certain you know
reasons i don't know if i can keep up my
beautiful looks if we would meet irl
like look look look at that beautiful
hair and i don't know i would be too
nervous i would let's just drop my
spaghetti and ah it would be all over
yummy
okay christina number
[Music]
seven
i'm thinking of
making uh
making a number that means
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
well you know what
why seven to nine why are you saying
seven to nine does that look like
raccoon to you
[Music]
how about seven zero one i don't know
why but for some reason i feel like that
gets somewhat close
eh
wait what did i say seven zero nine or
do i mean zero zero seven zero one
q q
[Music]
that's what i mean i don't mean one i
mean none
because the
number nine at least is q
and then you could say that the key the
q
the key of the q is the key of the
tunnel key
foreign no i'm like no
zero no it's new
you know
and then ta
the reason i
i say
seven is because
the letters
t looks like the number seven
yeah so
i tried i tried
[Music]
okay companion cube challenge and doctor
held astonishing companion
why does she punch you
for not having a number herself
the
you guys are weird with cute titty
da
[Music]
da nita
couple names
[Laughter]
ship
i'm shipping you off to
japan let's go
uh
sex nephew says i take back my last
pinky please don't be my companion cube
so you won't die
oh
[Music]
but but but companion cube was there at
the very end so companion cube dying was
a lie too
yeah let's be each other's companion
cube
thank you jackson with the pinky crown
tech also thank you for another pinky
for cubechan they blocked deadly spheres
helped push down buttons and kept you
company for everything i'm sure they
understood your decision potential
ah for cube john that's the pinky four
cubed another hold up
i don't think they understood my
decision
i don't think
i think companion cube still has
some
um
sad feelings about me dumping it into
that
hole of lava
cube john is sweet so
they still
act nice towards me
but deep in the heart
they are still a little bit heartbroken
that i did that
sad
yeah
[Music]
emotionally resilient
okay
i don't want to think about i was
forced i was forced to do it
i didn't want to do it
companion cute
companion
someone sent me a picture on twitter
of their self-made
uh
wooden companion cube box thingy and it
looks so cute
looks so cute i'm sure there's like so
much merchandise with like portal stuff
like especially the cubes
that's so nice
but that one was self made yeah
that's special and it looked really well
done high quality
stratosphere thanks for the pinky can
it's my birthday today hope i hope you
can maybe send me a happy birthday today
of course
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear stratosphere
it's a day late but
yahoo
[Applause]
[Music]
that was yesterday
close enough
not so far off
portal on your birthday how fun
how fun
hope your cake was not a lie
your birthday cake can dance
[Music]
i said it correctly all the previous
times but this time you got me
scribbling on the wall zankasen our
gourd and xavier duncan thank you for
your first superchat
thank you thank you the title was big
brain
obscured
i forgot again
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah it was a
egg and circle it with pancake batter we
call them both eyes
ah
[Music]
but for me pancakes
are something that i need to eat with
sweet stuff i know like i see it so
often in american breakfast so people
have like
a pancake a fried egg and bacon all on
one plate
but for me
[Music]
i need to eat it with nutella or
something similar or ice cream or fruit
and all that
yeah yeah
oh thank you
good night
yeah you guys eat your savory pancake
i'll have my sweet pancake
mmm
[Music]
don't like mixing them yeah i feel like
um even if i eat something savory
i don't want to mix like sweet and
savory for breakfast at least not all in
one place maybe
maybe have like a little moment in
between
first
first i
eat some fruit and all that usually when
i go to a hotel i do it like this but on
my own i only eat like one type of
breakfast in one day but if i'm in a
hotel i usually go get some fruit then i
make myself a sandwich
and
or croissant or something like that
somewhere even before that or after that
i eat some of the
um
shitty hotel scrambled eggs usually
though usually i don't want to eat them
i try to
eat something else or
ask if they can make fresh omelet or
fresh fresh scrambled eggs or something
like that
sometimes they have like mini
mini pancakes too
in the breakfast buffets
yeah the thing is like i i know how
hotel scrambled eggs are made
because
um i know what they use
i made it myself
before
i poured
the mix of the
hotel scrambled eggs into this huge
huge
thingy and put it in the oven
and yeah it's not eggs
it's not eggs
and
it doesn't after eating it like a few
times i'm like ew
ew this is so fake
the egg the scrambled egg is a lie
you can easily notice though if it's
like a perfect color all over then those
are fake
those are just fig eggs if it's like
somewhat
mixed like so like though the colors are
a little bit mixed then that could be
real scrambled eggs
probably freshly made
but
that probably only exists
in
really really really really really
really really expensive hotels
or if you order uh
it you know
separately because even when there's
scrambled eggs in the buffet
life hack
even in relatively cheap hotels if they
have a kitchen that's working at the
moment during the breakfast
you can often ask them to make fresh
scrambled eggs for you with real eggs
and they will probably make it or an
outlet or whatever
life hack
do it
who is that who tells another
what have i been eating
well i mean
okay maybe maybe there's some some part
of egg in there but
it's just
[Music]
get the fresh ones
or order to your room because i think
when you order to the room even though
it's expensive the chances are higher
that they bring you real scrambled eggs
maybe
not eating hotel food ever again no no
no hotel food is okay
but with yeah with
with breakfast buffets and hotels it's
always like
an experiment
some of them are shitty even though the
hotel is expensive
some of them are good even though the
hotel is cheap
i was i stayed in a relatively cheap
hotel
like like four years ago or so and
it was in germany
and it had
it had
a freaking waffle iron and it only had
one that made two waffles uh at a time
and it took a little like a couple
minutes and there was like always like
people waiting in line to make waffles
but just the fact that we could make
fresh waffles there
oh
that already made me so happy
the rest of the buffet was pretty good
too so
the price
and the
the amount of stars of the hotel does
not always mean that they have better
breakfast than the others
yes waffle makers yum yum yum
i rarely see waffle iron
on the buffet
of
breakfast buffets in hotels
i rarely see it
and that was a nice surprise
recently i got a waffle maker
i had one before too but like i ended up
never using it
because they didn't even come out that
nicely
not that ideal
they were just so
floppy and then and then like you know
it was all over the waffle iron
such a pain in the ass to
clean it um
yeah but now i have um
yeah now i have a toast thingy a
sandwich maker that also can in theory
could make waffles if i wanted to and
donuts as well apparently
but i want to try making donuts in my
airfryer i need to test out my airfryer
sometime next month
maybe in a stream
yes
i need to make donuts in my airfryer
oh
let's go
main account got bunked
no
oh no what did you do what did you do
what did you do
what happened
after a stream every stream air for a
stream yes yes yes
yes
throw the kfb members into the airfryer
we need to test it out and see if we
could use it at kfp
yeah
experiment
airfryer experiment
i volunteer there for a tribute
wait that sounds like hunger games
what does their signal sound like again
i don't know what it sounds like again
they had some
some sound that they made
the frying games
hungry kiwa games
the hunger games of takanashi kiwawa i
am hungry literally
hunger games in this situation actually
mean what the title implies
not much about being hungry and food in
the actual hunger games but i i will i
will stay true to the title
in my case
okay
with me
you get
what
it says that you get
robert wareham
tom tornadoes duncan typhoon is
this is already at the end of portal i'm
so proud of you and so happy to watch
you play one of my favorite games ever
thank you yeah awesome
actually really glad that so many of you
guys really enjoyed the portal stream um
i didn't realize that it was
so beloved by all of you i knew it was
popular in the famous game and all that
but i didn't realize
it was that
much
beloved by all of you
[Music]
people love portal yeah everybody loves
portal
so glad you guys enjoyed it thank you
andragons
and dr zilla thank you
[Music]
uh
oh
[Laughter]
what your name was always in in
romanized alphabet and now you write it
in uh in korean so that i
don't know how to read it anymore
thank you for the red super chat oh now
it's back to novel your name is back to
novel why did you change it to korean
before and now it's back to normal
normal is easier for me to read
today all the secrets of the usual room
are finally revealed although we
couldn't find someone who have entered
the room kiwawa destroyed all the things
that was armed with a powerful ai what
isn't this the usual room oh what's the
cake
portal
that was not the usual room no no no no
have you forgotten
have you guys forgotten
okay this is not really it either
it's actually this
oh my god
wish you
did you forget you shouldn't forget if
you forgot maybe it's time for me to put
you in here again
all of you
everybody who forgot about the usual
room
maybe it's time to remember
it's terrifying
oh oh there we go i sent someone by
accident nope that was on purpose
totally
yup
there they go bye bye
enjoy the usual room enjoy
the room of truth
making an example
who got sent i don't know it's like a
roulette it's the usual room roulette
thank you miniature pen
i also love
[Music]
congrats it was fun to see your
struggles turn into successes thank you
what struggles though
what struggles
i think i did okay
there were some
some moments where i got stuck but
you're gonna you're lying to me if
you're telling me that you never have
those kind of moments
where something that is
somewhat obvious
you just don't notice it right away i
mean come on we all have those kind of
moments
it's just i i have them
in
very public situations
where everybody laughs at me when i
don't know something
[Music]
principal flame thank you nick situation
right now thank you for the pinky
congrats on beating the game so it was
so fun thank you it was indeed fun thank
you for watching it until the end thank
you
for
[Music]
um
this game was heartbreaking when it was
no mess with a heart challenger uh
gamer oven
using her estimated 100 iq
to conquer another classic puzzle game
right that wave of glory kiara you
freaking genius
hello
hanukkah
you are
so charming
uh
huh said 180.
no no 180.
he said 180 i said 180 did you not
listen
no i read
180. you didn't hear it for some reason
i am 100 sure that i read it as 180.
[Music]
huh why are we getting stuck there
that's not the point that's not the
point
you guys are not listening anymore you
guys are zoning out because i've been
reading so many super chats
wake up camping
wake the up
it's time for a break
huh thank you tanaka
um you're a good
good good boy
good joking
know exactly what buttons to push
another warren thank you soon crypto max
tungsten's red function companion cube
chad thank you soon
you have allergies
and stormy sky
yes i will play the single player
i will play it first after all dominique
dan question navida media thanks for the
pinky
congratulations killer you flank style
bird brain of yours real good today your
playful was hilarious you're gonna love
portal 2. if you could make a portal
anywhere in the world like in the game
what would you place both ends
where would you place both ends oh
well i mean
i will probably be japan so that i can
go there faster and don't have to take
like a 12-hour flight every time
that would be very nice oh that would be
too easy but the answer was also easy
what did you think i would say
for now i'll take japan
maybe one day i'll place it on
my secret island somewhere
um
[Music]
huh
i refuse to acknowledge that
okay
i'm really hungry now
can i have some of you
to eat to go
have free chicken sandwich
i'm hungry
yes
no run no no no no no
i'm not fried yet okay i won't eat you
there are already a lot of fried people
chiara's fried people
you look delicious
[Music]
oh yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum yum
i'm hungry
i'll go make myself a snack
but i am the snack
but i also have to make a snack for my
snack
a snack for the snack
you guys are also looking like a snack
a snack for a snack
[Music]
snack
i'm so hungry holy the more i think
about it the more hungry i get
what do i do
i must eat
chicken flesh potential mmm
maybe i'll make cup noodles
emerging i have like one
one
cup noodles for emergency
and this feels like a emergency consume
[Music]
i made it to a live stream
wait did you just arrive because i'm
ending now oh no
it's
and next week we might have a lot of
late streams no sea streams i am sorry i
apologize in advance i don't think i can
do sea
streams next week
um
yeah
busy busy busy busy busy
amazing busy but i'll do my best to
still you know stream even though i'm
busy
i'll do my best
oh
i can watch the vlogs thank you
my angel chicken
love
[Music]
okay
i'm sleepy dancing i'm gonna die don't
die we're done we're finished finish
finish finish finish finish finish
finish
everybody thank you for watching google
[Music]
thank you for watching
thank thanks
[Music]
thank you i'll continue to study korean
i promise okay
i promise
[Music]
yes i want to say that i speak four
languages fluently
or at least three and a half
[Music]
okay
and in german we say
alf
and the rest of the super chats i will
read on sunday
i think okay
okay
[Music]
ah the smell
the smell of fresh fresh chicken
yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum
[Music]
do
thank you for coming everybody
bye bye
[Music]
do
you