[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
oh my god i'm so nervous you guys hear
me
yeah bit
kick it again
hello
welcome to my kitchen
[Music]
yay
oh my god i'm so nervous um because my
setup is so different uh
is the audio okay i'm using a really
shitty microphone because i didn't want
to set up my
big ass microphone here um
are you here gloves
you hear the gloves that's actually true
you can't hear that i guess i'm so
nervous and i'm i think i have a
i can't breathe well already so this is
a great start
i'm so nervous to [\h__\h] up and also
because i don't know if i can really
make it properly
the background is cute right okay so i
want to say like originally i was going
to i think i told you guys i was going
to
um
[Music]
it's running in the background man i was
going to a
commissioner
the kitchen background eventually but
i've been so busy so i didn't even get
to commission it in the first place
um so i was just gonna throw together
something really like lame and simple
but
eden exiled once again
did it again even next i was the person
who made for example my legs on the
table and also made the chicken falling
down into my hands when when i give it
like kisses and stuff
in excel made so much stuff and like
yesterday
this person started
making this background and today it's
already finished like what the [\h__\h]
what
and i didn't even like i didn't ask for
it but
thank you so so much it's like it's so
cool like i i thought i thought i would
have like a really lame background today
but look at this
look at this
yeah if i move the one second if i go
over there then my face won't be moving
well let me show you what's behind the
chat
there we go see it's like a fridge it
has a
i'm not sure what's in there
but there's something in here uh okay
let's just
notice something
okay there we go
okay i hope i hope
hey i'm moving again i hope everything
will go well today
yeah you guys are i thought the chat
fits best over there now
um i can move these
tools but
yeah wow
the spatula
yeah those are my tools
the only things i'll be using today just
kidding but uh the table is so nice
and wait let me hide myself
look it's so cool there's like burgers
being made in the background and fries
being made
me okay
[Music]
it's beautiful it's like it looks like a
freaking restaurant it's more than just
a kitchen that's kind of like
i don't know why up until now i've never
like done
this before like commissioned like a
like a kfp restaurant background before
it took me long enough man yeah oh thank
you so much eating exile it's beautiful
amazing so today we'll be cooking here
and i'm so
[\h__\h] nervous that i'll [\h__\h] up there
i think you know what so
um
uh
i think when like okay when i chop some
stuff and when we actually built the
lasagna i think that's when i'll turn on
the um
camera but when i'm actually cooking
i don't think i will um
because i would have to change the
camera angle and i'm just like
too nervous for that we have to do it
step by step i think in the future my
cooking streams will be better and all
but today i think while i'm actually
like when i have something in the pot on
the
uh
stove
i think that at that time i will have to
focus on cooking
and turn off the camera
and yeah reflections obviously like i
would have to put the camera really
really close
inside the pot almost and that kind of
scares me so
because i have a very reflective uh
cooking thingy obviously like they all
are pretty reflective i think but anyway
i got something super super
special
to show you wait a second um
uh i mean everything right now is so
[\h__\h] special oh my god
okay
um
so
sorry
um
um so
uh we're making lasagna right recently
i'm so into lasagna i don't know
why but i'm so into lasagna so i was
gonna because lasagna
equaled
cat and
my audio outfit has cat ears i was gonna
wear that outfit
but
since we're in the kfp restaurant here
my uniform is more fitting reason number
one and there is not another reason why
i am wearing this outfit today
instead of my
uh casual outfit um where i would have
cat ears which would be super fitting
you know what when we eat the lasagna
that's when i will
um
maybe turn into a cat but
er now okay this is the nervous moment
this is the part where i get really
nervous or i am already really nervous
but okay um
okay that's all good that's all fun
well here we have a pickle now
[Music]
uh oh my god my shadow oh my god okay
so i mean the gloves are obviously back
uh peculiar says hi this is so this
makes me so nervous oh yeah there's a
bucket in the background
um
wow my oh that's because it's wet that's
why it reflects a tiny bit that's okay
that's probably gonna be fine yeah yeah
so there's a there's a bucket uh but
that's still not really the thing i
wanted to show but that someone gave me
that at the meet and greet
um in uh
in germany at dokomi
my fans were able to give me physical
gifts and someone gave me this self-made
bucket
um
it seems like
it could be a certain company's bucket
originally um something is iffy about it
[Music]
i don't know what it is so anyway
that's actually that's really cute but
that's also not the thing that i want to
show so okay are you guys ready
i am ready
are you ready i'm so nervous
[Music]
hey
hey how how are you guys
[Music]
yo
how's it going guys
hey
yeah
i'm wearing my uniform
i'm wearing my uniform how's it going
hey
hey fancy seeing you here hey
oh my god i'm so nervous i don't know if
i can really cook a [\h__\h] lasagna
um
oh my god oh my god
hi
safeguard
my stuff
yeah well okay so um
shall we start oh my god the chicken the
chicken makes me so nervous can the
chicken stop running oh my god no it's
okay you keep on running we have a busy
day at kfp busy busy day okay so i think
we have to start with uh onions
okay oh my god well let's get [\h__\h]
started i've never i've eaten millions
of lasagnas until now but i have yet to
cook one on my own and uh i'm very
nervous
well that is uh
okay let's let me go with a big one this
one is a bit bigger
okay
okay oh god
peeling a onion with gloves
i can do it
i can do it wait how do i cut an onion
again
uh okay i'm so nervous
i
haven't cut an onion in a long time why
does it look so weird
ew
is this is this onion okay
i just bought it today but it looks kind
of weird like in some parts
you can probably not see that
what i mean but i'm always too picky
with these things my mom would be like
just get it on just use it
oh wait i i'll it's not soft but wait
i'll i'll just use the other one
this one is uh
it's okay i guess
is it yeah i mean it's probably fine i'm
just always too too careful with these
things
let me check
here okay
careful very careful
okay uh
as we like to say in german
onions have
layers
okay come on you can do this
[Music]
yeah i would like to get rid of these
some of these layers first before doing
this but it's really difficult with
gloves so [\h__\h] it
wow it's really glossy inside is that
okay
it was that really it looks weird inside
i think
eh
i'm not sure man
you don't see it but it's like kind of
it has weird colors inside
let's see if we can get a focus on this
come on
it's probably fun
[Music]
does it does an onion smell weird if
it's not good anymore my mom is probably
already texting me like just [\h__\h] use
the [\h__\h] onion because she said
she'll be watching the stream
uh cut it okay
yeah uh you guys make me so nervous this
is not the first time
i'm cutting an onion okay i know how to
cut an onion i'm just really nervous
uh
i'm not sure about this onion i have
more onions though but these are these
are the newest ones okay i want to just
wait can i use this one
okay yeah it looks okay i mean it looks
it has like
weird brownish colors at this at this
part
but
this part looks okay
okay um
go away go away
don't worry i was using the not sharp
side of this yeah okay so okay now um
can i i wanna this is
that's so nice of gloves
um
um wait okay you know what i'll take my
gloves off for a moment
[Music]
i want to remove the freaking top layer
with my hands
[Music]
so
nervous oh my god
[Music]
wait i don't actually have a wait wait a
second
um
just give me a moment okay
just just give me a moment
[Music]
do you hear the the sound is this asmr
with a really shitty microphone
heart monitor i should put on a hard
monitor right now it would probably be
really really high
uh wait
i can't
i'm shaking
we gotta get uses okay if this goes well
and we can do more cooking streams and
it will be fun it will be lots of fun
yeah
okay
uh
why am i doing it like this
i should just get rid of this part yeah
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
is already used to it so she's fine
oh my god
so
um
someone sent me this great idea on
twitter that uh it would be uh such a
marvelous idea to put um
a
pineapple into a lasagna and i have to
say that's actually a great idea um
now
i'm not doing it today it's okay but i
think it's a great idea because
pineapple on pizza already tastes great
and and and
it's not like lasagna is much different
like like i mean lasagna it's like with
tomatoes
and stuff like i feel like it would be
great
but today we're making a really basic
beach lasagna beach lasagna yep
i actually never heard that song before
i just know that that one part beach was
that yeah that's all i know i never
listened to the song before
okay i have peeled
this
onion
now let me put back on my gloves
my cats are zooming right now
through the
further living room
go go cats go go
oh hello cats you're joining me welcome
welcome to
kfb
okay
okay wait a second this is uh
difficult
um
[Music]
peeled onions
peeled
aqua senpai
hello i'm here hello
hello
huh
burp
oh oh some some burgers coming up right
now
[Music]
burberry's burgers
they're zooming so they're meowing
really excuse me did you hear that
she was like wow
[Music]
oops sorry sorry this mica picks it up
more because it's a shitty mic my my
what did i say this microphone picks it
up more because it's shitty isn't that
uh uh
uh ironic
okay let's cut this onion i've been
wasting so much time but let me cut up
this part
it's so
this is weird though it's like really
[\h__\h] brown you don't see it but it's
like really brown maybe if i put it here
do you see that
wow
you see that it's so brown
is that i've never
you sure
my mom is probably hating on me mom i
don't have time right now
it smells okay
but what are you doing yet
no
i cut that part anyway
okay here is fine this side is fine this
side is not what
[Music]
it's oxidized a little bit it's fine
okay
what are you guys trying to call gordon
ramsay
why
is it because i'm an
idiot sandwich
you don't even see the i want you to see
my arms
you
[Music]
yeah
yeah okay it looks okay it's probably
fine
calm down
mother
please
i didn't see your message if you sent me
a message please calm down i'm gonna use
the onion it's okay it's okay
oh my god i'm so nervous wait a second
um wait a second wait a second wait a
second wait a second wait a second while
we're at i need to get a
[Music]
pot
which one
[Music]
this one okay
let's put this back here decoration
and uh
okay
um everything can't do this
[Music]
i'm so nervous okay okay i can do this
cut the [\h__\h] onion this is the
easiest part probably
i mean i've made um pasta before so the
the whole meat sauce part
is easy
the exact same meat sauce i have made
actually never mind this one this meat
sauce is without uh
[Music]
without tomatin mark which i don't know
what that is in english
uh by the way i don't know how to do
this this thing i i can only cut like
this
yeah oh and one good thing is my eyes
are not tearing up right now
i'm fine
[Music]
if i were to cut myself uh the good
thing is the gloves protect me
a little bit okay is that really enough
well it has to be so we'll throw that
into the pot
and start
by
cooking that
and then later on when the when the
onions okay let's talk about a freaking
plan okay
i have a plan
um
and it is uh the following okay let me
tell you so we are going to
and uh
we are going to
yes yes
um cook
grill whatever
er and
the onions until they are a little bit
nice
and then
we add the meat
and we make it like
we we have to
separate it and make it like beautiful
and i would add some
uh i have some some spices but uh
basically i'm just adding um
garlic but like i'm i don't want to cut
garlic because that always is very
annoying so we're just gonna
add a garlic that's already like
sprinkly yeah i'm gonna add a lot of
that don't worry a lot of garlic
yes
and oh my god i can't breathe
and
uh
so yeah wait uh i don't i don't remember
well but but but but but and then we
will
use uh
to tomato we will put that in there i
have two
uh because apparently it means oh my
gosh it needs a lot apparently we add
some
some uh uh
italian whatever
well i am
[Music]
i bought a lot of meat
a lot of meat
[Music]
two packages of that
two
because the recipe said so i hope it's
really not too much but like we're
making a lot of it
so we're gonna put that
all of that
into this pot
and after the onions are a little bit
cooked right okay
sorry your order is gonna take a million
years
and also once we have the lasagna ready
which will be in a million years we need
another million years or actually one
hour to have it uh cooking in the oven
yeah
so in that one hour i don't know maybe
we'll read super chats maybe we'll just
have a conversation i don't know so this
is fun uh let's throw piccolo away so
that i have space to freaking cook
[Music]
this makes me nervous oh my god okay
okay there's some cables on my cooking
plate thingy right now
very worrisome
um
it will be daijoubu in the end i will
use uh this one
right here
okay so i in order to not go absolutely
crazy right now i will turn off this
webcam
so that i can relax a little bit
um and cut open the freaking meat so
that i'm ready when it needs me
yeah
okay hello meat hello
that's beshte
and let me open
actually you know what you can watch
that
let me open
you
[Music]
don't worry this one opens like that
difficult wait i have a trick
i do it with the knife
i open it a little bit
yeah
and then
i open it yeah
what what do you mean why are you guys
panicking
okay
number one it's open
[Music]
yourself wonderful
i'm a professional can opener
[Music]
okay
gordon what's your problem gordon ramsay
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] up is my kitchen kfp
doesn't need ya i don't need your stupid
advice you're an idiot sandwich all
right
all right let's turn this [\h__\h] off
[Music]
microphone uh you go here
um
because
you worry me being here is it okay if
you are here michael let me put you here
right here okay
careful careful now this thing what do
we do with that thing can you stay there
is that okay if you stay there
i will i will have you
stay there okay
yo
okay
this will all be fine
uh
let me review my recipe
if i just want to make sure i'm not
forgetting something uh
so
so i have this video that i'm following
okay olive oil olive oil i have to put
in olive oil and onions yes yes
and garlic
and uh
we don't need the chili i don't like the
chili don't no chili in here
um ground meat thousand grams i actually
have a little bit bit less than that i
have like
700 gram or 600 something
um but that's okay and then we add
pepper and then we add salt and
then we add the tomato
stuff chopped tomatoes i have very very
very small diced tiny tomatoes because i
don't want the big tomatoes in there
what the hell then we have italian
seasoning easy easy gordon ramsay what
the [\h__\h] do you want do you want me to
cook you with
me to cook you with some balsamic
learn how to write english are you
supposed to be from the land of the
english
and
and a lightly fried exterior i don't
know what the hell are you talking about
speak english to me we speak english in
this restaurant for god's sake okay so i
have reviewed successfully reviewed my
recipe i will now proceed to turn on
the
[Music]
the thingy a hat plateau i don't know
what it is in english even though we
speak english in this restaurant i know
i said it alrighty alrighty let me get
out my garlic
hey at my salt and my pepper
[Music]
hey
okay okay i'm so nervous and uh hi
chunkers hi baby
yeah
mommy is cooking
um
sorry should i is
i'm peeking right sorry i put a gain on
the microphone because it was way too
quiet now i turned it down a tiny bit
oh my god oh wait i forgot the olive oil
i put away all the thingies that are
reflective this is my this is it greek
greek natural olive oil only the best
by bio
peel what's bio in english like we call
all all things that come from better
uh where where animals and stuff are
treated better we call that beeo
products organic oh yeah that's ah
that's what we call it in english so
i've started
buying organic products only because of
course we want only
only good stuff yes okay it do be fast
though it do be fast on maximum heat
and uh
oh my god i can't breathe
i'm normally not
this
weird okay
i'm just really nervous oh you have to
drill down really
did you hear that
i mean now we have sizzling as well do
you hear the sizzling and the drilling
when you stop drilling already okay all
right
[Music]
yeah it's real go baby
at 8pm that's the right time to drill
baby yeah okay
oh my god not so fast please
wait no no no pepper yet but we can put
in garlic yeah okay garlic
lots of garlic
hi cat
what is it i'm cooking
i'm cooking oh my god drilling meowing
sizzling screaming
everything
okay i need more garlic i need more
garlic here it's a garlic emergency
[Applause]
i can't turn this thing around when i
wear gloves why am i even still wearing
gloves i don't even have the camera on
no it's okay it's okay all right all
right all right okay looking good
looking good looking good um meat
wait i think there's there needs to be
more olive oil wait wait
okay
wait a second wait a second wait a
second wait a second wait a second wait
a second
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
yeah drill woo
get the paper get the paper yeah paper
more meat
so much meat
well get the paper get the paper yeah
not the paper okay there's always paper
on this sweet okay
okay
destroy the meat
oh my god okay i'll take off my gloves
for a moment
i see your comments by the way i see
that they're right over there when i
look over there you know that i'm
looking at the comments
okay
let's draw it
mix it mix it this is horrible oh
there's meat
everywhere go go
oh i think something's burning yeah
that's probably just the meat that fell
on the
on the plate oh my god
okay i should maybe turn down now that
this is like it's all right
it's all right yummy
wow
i can't get all this meat cooked man so
much
how do i cook so much meat
oh man
oh man turn it around flip it yeah
yeah okay give it some time give it some
time give it some time
meow oh my god
meow yes yes
yeah meow yeah yeah yeah
who are you meowing at
so it's time to relax a little bit
wait i need to drink water
yes true baby
good neighbor
good timing
[Music]
oh yeah
okay gordon ramsay
what do you want why is the chad always
talking about you let me see did you
send something
if this is how you run a kitchen i don't
know how you can turn a friend i'm not
telling a franchise what's that that me
one of them including fancy
you need a dictionary i want a
froggy or a dictionary over there
wherever you live on a freaking mountain
or something i'll throw it over there
and i hope it lands on the top of your
head and then you get uh
oh my god i
i lost a lot of
meat wait a second
oh my god
rescue the meat
okay
meat has been rescued
right scoot the onion two yeah yeah
okay okay the meat is calming down i
think
oh my god
i kind of burnt myself but it's okay i'm
a phoenix it didn't hurt
okay oh see it's calmed down i hear the
meat juice
sizzling
tiny small
baby meat juice
baby sizzles
yeah
it's so hot here why is it so hot
slowly but surely the meat is
starting to have a nice brownish color
what do you want gordon ramsay what is
it this time you're really needy man are
you in love with me
i want you to cook better you to have a
[\h__\h] baby
i will burn you i will i will cook you
gordon ramsay
okay calm down everyone my cats are
scared of me i don't want them to think
that i'm some kind of scary person only
you guys you guys may think that but my
cats need to know that i am the sweetest
person on earth
okay
oh wow the meat juice oh my god yes yes
we don't want to lose it right we want
to keep some of it
it's good
what
what is it with the super chats man
thank you guys
calm down i'm not cooking for you you
guys are realizing that right i am the
one eating the lasagna
i am the one eating that not you guys
you're not getting a bite of it
okay
you know what i'll give i think i can do
it i think i can show you
a little bit
of what's happening right now
um you sure
don't worry it will be daijoubu
don't worry
[Music]
oh yeah
oh we're doing it okay that's all i'll
show you for now
please wait
oh my god oh my god i need to turn it
around it's cooking very much
well well i still see a few parts that
are a little bit
not finished
a little bit um
pink
wow
my brother no this is not chicken meat
don't worry guys this is not chicken
lasagna who makes lasagna with chicken
meat don't worry don't worry i would
never do that
i wouldn't eat what
i wouldn't eat this lasagna even if you
paid me shut up i don't want to eat yeah
i want i don't want you to eat it anyway
you don't deserve this lasagna
[Music]
okay so now it's looking good okay okay
turn it down a little bit because i'm
stressed out
okay throw in
the tomato sauce let's go
away beautiful
okay
number one and number two
oh yeah
[Music]
that's a lot of sauce oh my god
i don't know if i can fit all that sauce
into my lasagna but if we can't you know
what this makes a good pasta sauce
brief
taco mashikiana
okay okay now we get to season it but i
will show you once again
the looks of it
[Music]
be careful guys
don't get hit oh yeah
why is it so noisy
it's so noisy wait a second what is this
there's something something and now it's
called
oh my god
[Music]
i panicked did you see something
that was that was that was the microwave
did you see something though
meow nah okay okay i will be very
careful the the noise scared me you know
okay now i can season it
[Music]
okay
pepper
pepper pepper pepper pepper
this thing barely gives me any pepper
oh be quiet
[Music]
we haven't salted it yet throw in a good
amount of salt there
don't be too scared
of using the salt
amelia watson
really let's see
she would like this lasagna hell yeah
okay
salt is it i think it needs a bit more
pepper
you want a lot more pepper
marshall
uh italian
herbs
italian herbs are next maybe a bit more
garlic dough never can have enough
garlic
garlic garlic
[Music]
okay
okay looking good
now italian herbs
[Music]
um opening this for the first time one
second
[Music]
okay there it
is oh that's a lot whoops
uh
well grab it give me
okay
huh she's like she's
she's uh
rubbing herself against my legs right
now so sweet she's saying hello
saying hello
all right you're shocking
[Music]
sorry mommy is really stressed oh she's
on the ground running
belly wraps i'll give you belly rubs
yeah
[Music]
oh
okay she got the belly wraps
[Music]
no
no junkies baby
lasagna is not for you it's for me the
big cat
no not for a small cat lasagna you're
not good for small cats big cats
standing on two feet you know what
you'll get lasagna if you can manage to
stand on two feet how about dead
okay
[Music]
oh my god
calm down
calm down come down calm down
it's very saucy i hope it will be nice
[Music]
baby
yeah baby
very saucy
[Music]
okay
looks good should be fine i hope so but
basically
one big part
of the lasagna is now basically done
right because we have the sauce
i'm really scared of making the beja
mail sauce
i that will be the first time i'm making
it and i mean in theory it's supposed to
not be so difficult in theory
and i talked about it with my mom as
well
so
it will be basically
um
[Music]
butter
and then
[Music]
flour flour flour flour flour hi baby
and then you don't want the flower floor
to um become brown
it will become a little bit brown
because of the
uh butter but
you don't want it to get too brown and
you want to like
swirl its world's worst world
and um
baby
what is it
no baby
okay i have her on my shoulder now
you want to
stir it yeah yeah yeah non-stop and then
you throw in a lot of uh milk
basically right oh and then nutmeg not
not meg afterwards
okay drop my cat
it's okay she's not not very patient she
doesn't didn't want to be on there
longer anyways
oh my god
oh my god this smoothie is zooming
another good time to zoom smoothie
okay then throw that away
nice
um let me throw some other things away
[Music]
this stuff the onion stuff
okay
[Music]
gotta clean up the kitchen
all right
[Music]
okay
okay i'm back hello
can i drink some water i'm so stressed
out i'm so stressed out
the water is so warm
[Music]
i drink tap water because we have the
best tap water ever in australia i can
i can attest to that
how long do i want this to cook
how long
how long do i want this to cook i mean
it's gonna be in the oven too so it
doesn't really matter that much
i think
[Music]
okay
reduce it to be less what reduce what
the heat
or reduce the juice in it
[Music]
the sauce reduces okay you know what i
can do that i can do that i can i will
do that
i will do that
[Music]
all right yeah that's a good idea
unfortunately a little bit of meat comes
with it
that's okay
[Music]
the sauce is fine it will dry in the
oven
okay okay okay okay
just taking a bit more okay
all right all right
i got it yes
i reduced it a tiny bit
looks a bit better now
not a little
okay so um
is is that is that it do we just put it
to the side now
do we just put it to the side
it's it's really a tiny difference it's
not that it
just boil oh yeah okay
okay okay okay okay
then i'll turn it up a little bit
will it really reduce itself though
[Music]
boil it up okay okay chunk
i'm the cook here okay i'm the cook in
this kitchen
what is it gordon
there is no point anywhere the whole
meal is
you suck gordon you suck
[Music]
i'll be eating this i don't care if you
don't want to eat it i'll eat it
it's my lasagna
was never intended to be shared in the
first place
um
yeah let's see what my mom is saying
let's see if she's saying something
mommy oh mommy oh yeah i have message
oh
okay
my mom wrote to me cook it longer and
originally in the beginning she also
told me to put a wet towel under my
cutting board which i know it would have
been useful but i didn't do it yep
i have a really really that cutting
board that you saw is really tiny and
very cheap and thin
i need to get a proper one but this is
the only one i have right now
yeah
that's why it's so flimsy
there's barely any space on it too
okay well i don't know we could try to
cook the bechamel sauce on the side
while we're waiting for the the other
stuff to boil
but i'm so nervous about it i'm so
nervous about it let me get the blue
blue flower
and this stuff
okay
calm down
[Music]
okay
who's so nervous i'm so nervous okay
we'll use uh this
this part
okay okay
hope it's big enough yummy calm down it
makes me so nervous when it's cooking so
much
[Music]
i'm nervous you'll burn your eyebrows
um don't worry don't worry don't worry
i'll be fine my eyebrows will be fine
i'm a phoenix no no no body part of me
can be just simply burnt up okay yes i
know i'm lying in chunkers but you don't
have to tell the audience that
don't tell
them it's a secret
[Music]
they talk more to me here for some
reason
than they do when i'm in my office
i don't know why she's very talkative
why are you sitting on the ground right
next to the bed that i put there for you
chunkers
explain yourself
why is the the the floor more
comfortable to you than the bed that i
bought for you hmm
[Music]
no answer huh all right i get it
okay turn this down a little bit
turn it down
sorry i have to is that too loud
there's a lot of um
uh rao
smoke
is it okay okay the the the thingy don't
absolute
i have to
the steam yeah steam
okay
let me watch the video again
that i'm using as reference on how to
make the visja message it's really short
um
okay so
he puts in
uh
quite a lot of uh
butter
four tablespoons flour flour
then saute it then it turns into
something that looks like
thrown up vomit
and that's where you add three cups of
cold milk well i'll just be using the
whole package probably
and then you stir it and it should cook
then you add a pinch of nutmeg
a pinch of salt
don't reduce it too much it will be
thicker when it cools down a bit so
that's you know the thing is
my mom told me
to
put the milk in there step by step but
the video tells me to put it in there
all at once so i'm getting mixed signals
here
my mom was like no [\h__\h] way you can't
just put it in all all right away you
can't do that are you guys also saying
step by step
listen to mommy
okay okay okay let's let's do it step by
step
and my mom said that
it should reach the consistence of like
vanilla sauce at the end
yeah
okay
what i want to read this comment
for of melbourne where we put the solid
before
wet and add milk gradual gradually until
you have the texture
you want to help you you can also mix
your classic flow with some corn flour i
don't have that no no
okay
i need to breathe
oh my god
it doesn't really look like it's losing
reducing uh
a
liquid
it still looks the same to me
it's not reducing
it takes time
okay can i guess how i don't i don't
usually want to cook two things at the
same time but i guess we have to
okay
yeah meow
then is it really not too loud right now
the steam thingy
is it okay
it turned into a
it's relatively low
volume okay okay so
butter i forgot the butter
okay
i hope it's enough butter
wait do i have another one
baby okay i have more brother this this
butter is better
okay
how much butter it says four tablespoons
butter and four tablespoons flip
floor flour
okay
four
spoons
one
no there are mine gloves not cali's
gloves i have one black gloves before
cali wore them
this is not actually not my first
cooking stream i did one where i made
chocolate
how much butter doesn't the resin what
what what what
doesn't the recipe say who do you think
you are
paula dean who the [\h__\h] is paula think
is that your your wife that you
disappointed and
leave alone at home
every night when you get milk
i lost count of how many spoons of
butter i put in there she's another
famous tv show ah okay
sick burn
gordon ramsay
he's crying right now
i'm sorry i love you
i don't know
who you are really but i love you
okay this is probably enough butter
baby
um
okay
i'm so new nervous
okay the floor is ready this has to
happen fast
so let me show you
um
butter
okay a lot of butter
i don't know
that's it looks like a lot of butter
it's not that much i think
this is stuff
wait did you say
this did i say tablespoons or
wait tablespoon is that is a tablespoon
the big spoon with a small spoon
the big one okay so i use the big spoon
i did use a big spoon
flour
flour flour
let's just say male that's the german
way to say it
okay
okay i'm gonna do it
you can't do it mommy
okay
run it for my head
butter melts
when it's completely melted
i will throw in
four tablespoons
of
milk
now should it i wonder if it should be a
tablespoon that's like
like a mountain
or one that's like a flat
cutting board
you know what i mean
i
flat okay okay
let
male throw it in there four times
and then we swirl swirls right here i
have my i have my thingy i have this one
ready too everything that i need
and i swirl and i swirl
and then i throw in the milk let's open
up the milk before i'm gonna have issues
that i can't open it but but i'll should
be fine okay it's open it's open
okay okay okay let's go i'm turning it
on let's go
sauce
wow do you hear them in the house
they're very far in the distance now
okay okay it starts to melt it's
happening it's happening
wow
i think that was smoothie right
oh my god they're running to me i don't
have anything for you
hi baby
[Applause]
okay melting
melting
melting how long mommy how long how long
should i be how long will i be swirling
it
how long should i be swirling it mommy
i'm looking at what's up
how long approximately like after after
adding after adding the milk
is there any like wait i think she said
like the the the flower thing happens in
like
five to ten seconds and then you add in
the milk so it's really fast
wait how much should the heat be
how much heat
how much how much heat medium heat high
heat
how much heat
gordon grams
oh you're gonna take your day but i knew
it it kind of had like a similar feeling
some of the vibe to it medium okay mommy
said medium on whatsapp so i'm gonna
trust mommy wow that's a lot of a lot of
butter wow
okay
yummy
how much is it in the video
no it's about the same it looks about
the same
wait you know what i should uh
probably
oops
um okay let me put the four tablespoons
into this thing
ahead of time
okay
[Music]
it's snowing it's snowing merry
christmas okay
okay
uh
okay okay
okay
um
this is kind of positive
i'm sorry
where's my where's my swirly thing
where's my sword there it is
okay okay okay we'll go
um
butter
no flour yet it's coming though it's
coming
up
okay
it's um
it's okay it's cooking the butter is
cooking do i add it now okay mama said
add it now
i added it i added it oh okay okay it
looks good it looks good it looks good i
think it looks good
okay it looks like vomit we did it it
looks like vomit
yeah let's go
okay adding adding milk i think wait
a minute
okay adding milk
was that too fast did i add it too fast
oh my god there's so much going on
looking good okay
okay time for more milk more milk more
milk
okay okay
wow this is amazing this is amazing it's
a chemical reaction man
[Music]
oh my god my my my arm makes this
exhaust my arm is exhausted i can't
swirl anymore
it's not turning into vanilla pudding
anymore
hello
is it happening did i have too much milk
[Music]
okay yeah it's happening it's happening
it's happening it took a little while
but it's happening
don't skip arm day i skip it every day
okay a bit more milk
okay
i'm not sure where to stop i'm not sure
where i should stop adding milk
but we need more i think we need more
oh my god
ah okay mama says let it cook one time
the even less even my best friend is
messaging me
i have gordon ramsay i have to chat i
have my best friend and i have my mom
messaging me about how to cook this
[\h__\h] sauce
if i still mess it up then i'm useless
you can throw me in the trash obvious
honestly
okay it's taking a sweet time
okay i'm not so stressed out anymore
because it's taking its time
okay ah it's happening i feel it i feel
it
oh yeah okay
okay
i feel it
[Music]
give it some time stop touching it stop
touching it
okay okay yes that's it touch it oh yeah
oh yeah nice consistency
nice texture
no clumps by the way
daisy
i thought you had to go somewhere inside
gordon ramsay we now have david
okay now it's creamy it's getting creamy
again
yeah i should add some more milk i think
soon
i barely used i didn't even use half of
the one liter
milk thingy
didn't even use help
i'm gonna turn this off right now it
stresses me out man
okay beautiful beautiful okay adding
more
adding more
okay that's half that's 500 milliliters
do you think that's enough
because
it's already like it looks like a lot
but
[Music]
i don't think this is four cups of milk
though
[Music]
i would totally show you what it looks
like right now but i need to keep on
stirring
stirring stirring whirl swirling square
swirling
you can always add more it will thicken
as it cools you don't you think wait i
should add a little nutmeg and stuff as
well
[Music]
a second
um
not smack
[Music]
okay
yeah that's good stuff not bad yeah
[Music]
okay
so did should i add salt as well i
forgot probably right
okay
i actually have time
right now
to season it it's amazing
i'm impressed
[Music]
yes you smell the nutmeg yeah
yeah nutmeg is supposed to be in the
benjamin sauce are you guys uh you guys
never made it before huh
[Music]
you're talking to a professional cook
here okay i'm your tencho i know what
i'm doing
[Music]
garfield garfield
move over monday wednesdays are
definitely for the birds
yeah lasagna is a dish you can eat every
day all week
garfield what i wonder what garfield
would say if i would add uh pineapples
to my lasagna
[Music]
oh the meat
is definitely reducing
right now
um however
my beijamel sauce
is still very watery right now
[Music]
sounds delicious right am i right it
sounds delicious doesn't it
okay i think we can turn off the meat
sauce now i'm turning it off
do i need
do i need any
any hat platinum anymore after this i
don't think i do because it goes into
the oven afterwards
okay
okay let's see my alcohol will happen
angst
[Music]
what kind of cheese i prepared a
mozzarella cheese and cheddar cheese
i'll be mixing those too
i hope that's okay for you guys if not
that's okay because i'll be eating it
no parmesan yeah for some reason i don't
know the recipe said i can make it with
mozzarella and cheddar too so
i'm sorry i know it's a little bit uh
scandalous but
i do freaking love mozzarella and
cheddar those are my
my two favorite cheeses i think i think
i would say that yeah my two favorite
cheese is mozzarella and cheddar
cheddar is very sharp what does that
mean that sounds so professional oh my
god
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's just
started it just started getting creamy
[Music]
i didn't swirl for a while now i
panicked
you guys got me all uh um
distracted by talking about cheese
oh yeah it's getting creamy
i wonder if this really tastes like
vegetable sauce
i didn't add did i add pepper already i
i feel like i didn't
didn't add any pepper you know where is
the pepper
ah here it is i think i did does pepper
go into the vegetables
it should be fine right
taste it
now
a little okay
[Music]
okay
a little bit oh that's a lot
no it's okay
it's okay
okay let it cook a little bit
we're almost done with the vegetable
sauce
now we can layer the lasagna
that would be fun
[Music]
okay okay
i love bishop now
can't have enough of it
[Music]
can we see you later in lasagna hell
yeah i'll be showing you that process
process
okay i think should i add a bit more
milk
i will add i will add a bit more don't
be scared of adding more milk guys don't
be scared don't hold yourself back
don't let your dreams be dreams
[Music]
okay
pour in all the milk should i
[Music]
should i
okay i think i think now i'll stop
adding milk if i didn't use the i didn't
i didn't use the whole one later but
that's okay
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
i am back
[Music]
let's let it cook a little bit
four cups 900 ah
well then that's about right
that's about right
[Music]
thank you thank you for the support
thank you very much and read all the
super chats properly uh
probably not after the stream i'm i'm
like so stressed out i don't know if i
can read the super chats but
also because my setup is different right
now
but we will see when i i will read them
eventually that's for sure you know me i
always take the time to read them very
carefully
[Music]
okay i need i need to drink water i'm
gonna die soon
[Music]
okay
how's the visual sounds
[Music]
almost there
almost there please don't read w out i
don't know man i'm i'm kind of ready for
it i'm kind of ready for a re-debut
it's been a while did you already taste
two sauces no
i rarely do that
gordon won't because are you sure about
that what about if i make another
cooking stream he has to come back
[Music]
where where else will i get my guidance
huh
[Music]
maybe from garfield
i wonder if garfield knows anything
about things besides lasagna though
[Music]
you should taste the sauce for seasoning
i'm scared of tasting this though i feel
like it will be disappointing
okay i'll give it a try
um
after it reached some kind of a texture
[Music]
i'm proud of this dough it has no clumps
i didn't mess it up
okay let me try
this will taste weird it smells like
milk is it supposed to smell like milk
hey
[Music]
no yes
yes okay
but why does the bismuth sauce on top of
lasagna never smell like milk
[Music]
oh
wow
um
oh
i can imagine if this is mixed in with
the lasagna it will taste like the
proper thing yeah yeah
okay it has a good texture
um
it has a good texture
i think it needs to be a tiny bit
thicker but it will it will be a bit
thicker after after um
after uh
being a cooling down ring
right
well let's see what mommy says
we're
okay okay okay okay okay then let's just
end it here
okay
i have turned off the heat
yeah yeah okay it's still like
bubbling a little bit
okay
looking good
oh my god we did it i did it
wait let me show you
[Music]
um
uh for sure
[Music]
well i mean it will not really look like
anything but
wow
special sauce
okay
stretch
[Music]
okay
okay i'm gonna um clean the area so that
i have space for my lasagna uh thingy
where we put in the sheets and stuff so
one moment please
i'm gonna put my gloves on again so this
can go away
[Music]
this can go away
this can go
here this can go away
okay
this goes
here
this
this goes here
[Music]
okay this goes here
no need for this
maybe need for that no need for this and
that
[Music]
when this goes
this one
[Music]
what did you just drop cats
did you hear the sound of them dropping
something
okay okay this is
this we don't need this anymore i think
[Music]
this
this can go here you heard it no nothing
broke
i think i think they try to jump into a
box that i have on top of my
top of like a dresser or something and
um when they try to jump into the box
they flipped the box and it landed on my
keys and yeah that's that way that it
made that specific sound it's all good
they just want to be in a box which is
understandable
okay so
[Music]
let's put the camera
over here again
[Music]
okay
that's probably fine now where are my
gloves
where did i put my gloves
well out here
okay the glove check
yes yes i'm gonna put them on right now
[Music]
these super chats of fire i'm excited to
read them
i love it when you guys play along like
that it's funny
you're sure
okay
gloves
mm-hmm is serious about this
you're sure
should i preheat the oven
yeah
should i
should i preheat it
[Music]
maybe i should
oh there we go
okay okay
okay
gloves check
camera let me see while i'm far away
what you see when you're there
yep that's a
difficult angle
nope
[Music]
don't worry don't worry always far away
don't worry
[Music]
this is not ideal
okay stay there
[Music]
how did i do it before
how about how about i do it like this
[Music]
sorry it's taking a little bit of time
because i forgot how i did it before
[Music]
oh
like this this should work this would
work
yeah okay looks
looks good
okay
turn it over there
and cha cha
[Music]
okay
looks
good
okay
so
uh
i know that we start
with uh
bechamel sauce first and
so we have we have cheese
cheese
this is the cheese and these are the
lasagna thingies
okay
okay let me open this up um
i think we will have to use all of them
maybe
we will see
okay
now hold
up see my my beautiful sleeves
so proud
my gloves are looking uh
really messy right now though okay okay
okay
ah maybe my microphone a bit closer
again oopsie oopsie oopsie
i'm gonna put the microphone
over
here
okay
[Music]
some tomato sauce on the on the
microphone no problem right
okay
well
shall we start
hi baby
yeah
okay i hope this is enough bijamil sauce
so basically we put
bechamel sauce
[Music]
i don't know how thick the layer should
be but
um
should it be completely covered huh
you probably need more
wow it's beautiful it's like vanilla
pudding
[Music]
sorry i barely move when i'm looking
over here
[Music]
pasta first no no no no no no no no no
recipe says and mommy said as well
bechamel sauce first
you can't confuse me like that here i
know what i'm doing
because otherwise the pasta sheets will
stick
to the ground
[Music]
okay but i think that's enough
probably hopefully okay
ah
yeah so now i'll put
the first sheet
like that
[Music]
i think if i do it like this i can fit
three sheets
but it's like it has a little bit of air
underneath but it should be fine right
huh
no no you don't have to boil these
there are two when you make lasagna
there are two different type of sheets
the ones that you have to pre-boil and
the ones that you don't have to boil
yes
yes yes
vertical should be fine
yeah it says
it says so on here
[Music]
gosh you make me nervous guys
you make me nervous
[Music]
that
uh it overlaps a little bit is that okay
is it okay if it overlaps a tiny bit
[Music]
it's fine okay well then
then
well afterwards we just layer it
normally with the meat sauce and a
little bit of bijamel in between and
wait what about the cheese the cheese in
between as well alrighty
cheese so after each pasta layer
we do meat
and beijing and cheese
and then pasta
and then
cheese on cheese only on the top or in
between as well
cheese on the white sauce okay
all right so
let's see this beautiful
meat sauce
[Music]
should it just be should it be a very
thick layer or
[Music]
more
hell yeah
thick is better just enough to cover it
okay okay
we're doing it i'm so excited i'm so
proud
is it okay if it spills over the edges
[Music]
more sauce
this is not the perfect tool to do this
but
yeah
lasagna is pretty sloppy yeah i agree
usually looks very sloppy
[Music]
okay
i'm so careful with this
i probably don't need to be this
a little careful here
okay
this is a bit too much let me put that
over here
this is
wow first layer not done that's not done
[Music]
we add vegemite sauce
this doesn't have to have to be so
pretty right
how much
how much is this enough
[Music]
is this enough
is that enough
[Music]
cheese only on top let me ask my mommy
because i'm getting mixed signals here
let me ask mommy mommy she's only in my
main case
okay she says a little bit of cheese in
between so
i will use some
mozzarella cheese
[Music]
yeah
what's your favorite cheese everyone
[Music]
mama one day i'll make this lasagna for
you
the same way you used to cook for me
i'll cook for you
cheddar mozzarella smoked cheese blue
cheese
i don't i don't like those kind of
cheeses but
i'm glad you guys can enjoy them
emma tyler
gowda
swiss cheese
we had a conversation about that
previously
whether or not that is a valid
statement
it's okay though you've got you like all
kinds of swiss cheeses all of them right
[Music]
i guess it's just the way you guys say
it over there
it's okay
we say things differently
in different countries isn't too much
i'll leave it there
we'll add more in between and on top so
uh
sheet layer
[Music]
una
a
[Music]
echo is here
yeah i know a few italian words actually
because i used to take um
some italian classes
i can say
fork fork is for cat full
[Music]
left and right is sinistra and ah
and uh
no
cats are waiting for lasagna
no no this time
[Music]
you want lasagna
no you cannot have the lasagna
that's trunk is by the way
so
i cute channel it
i can't handle it i'm going to show you
a show you'll show your show
meow
okay i think i think that looks okay
she's she's she's flirting with me
she's trying to get on my good side
she's like rubbing her head against my
my leg again and now she's on the ground
asking for belly rubs again i know i
know what you like to do
i know we can do this movie uh chunky
sorry
no
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
now we can maybe add a bit more because
i have so much cheese
[Music]
yeah
it's okay i'm gonna give you a treat
later a treat no lasagna
you wouldn't eat it anyway be honest
she keeps on rubbing her head against my
leg it's so cute it feels good
it feels fluffy no
hello
it's her way of saying hello to me
so cute
[Music]
okay
how does it look guys we need a bit more
maybe uh here
[Music]
binitsu
is this not not enough cheese
[Music]
you know what next layer i'm gonna do
cheddar
i'm getting really hungry and like
exhausted
okay okay okay okay okay we did another
layer
[Music]
pasta
right i'm ready for the next layer right
oh my god how many layers do you usually
have
how this is the the third
third layer i think
how many
layers is a lasagna usually have six
four five all right let's see i mean i
guess we can layer it until we uh run
out of
uh ingredients or we reach the top i
guess
okay
let's do this
[Music]
you guys are hearing bgm by the way
right
i prepared some bgm
i make three to five usually oh
yes okay okay
good good
[Music]
what are you guys eating for dinner
tonight
[Music]
will it be lasagna
i had soup
chicken rice
pizza
[Music]
egg juice egg
mac and cheese you know that reminds me
of uh
yesterday
was it yesterday i think it was
was it yesterday maybe yeah it was
yesterday
yesterday i was um
out
in the town with my friend
um
being
too nice to the ones i should hit it
more slap it slap it real good
and while i was while i was ubering
around
i saw this place
i saw this place that had that it calls
itself
something like
philly
philly uh cheese philly what was it
philly meat cheese what was that
philly
apparently you guys in philadelphia have
some really cool sandwiches
cheesesteaks yeah cheesesteaks yeah
and i was like don't what is that so i
googled it while i was in the uber
it looks so good what is that
what is that
it looks so good i want to check it out
because they seem to be really off like
it looks authentic judging from the
photograph
it looks authentic
a bit more over here
they had some interesting stuff over
there
[Music]
okay i think looking at my amount of
meat we can do definitely one more layer
but that should maybe be about it
[Music]
so
bishop
[Music]
um don't want to use so much in between
because i want to use more bijamil sauce
on top i want like a [\h__\h] ton of bishop
mail on top
that's my goal
[Music]
okay is that enough
okay whatever that should be fun okay
let me use the cheddar this time so that
the cheddar doesn't start crying because
i haven't been using it how do i open
this
[Music]
with a knife
oh my gosh
this
i don't know if it is because i'm
standing and talking so much but i'm
really
i really can't breathe well but you guys
know i have some asthma issues
but for the whole time that i think it's
a nervosity and my asthma and talking so
much and standing and all that
but i really can't breathe well oh my
god
okay
[Music]
oh yeah
yeah
lots of it
[Music]
okay that's probably fine
last layer let's go
looks like um
wait a second i have to cover it too
and i have
it's an uneven
it's an uneven number what the [\h__\h]
how much who follow this
[Music]
uneven number
so
[Music]
i have five more sheets
use it next yeah i guess i can also just
use it for like um
pasta
the rest of the meat sauce and say this
is the last layer
just like this will be the cover of it
and and these two i don't know man
i'll just use it next time i make
another lasagna and the rest of the meat
sauce i will use for normal pasta sounds
good
no need to cover
it
no i have to
i have to
okay well then
i could have made another layer but i'm
not doing it so
this is
the top part
and
well the top part just gets topped with
the rice of the bechamel sauce right and
some more cheese
don't cover
that will bake
cheese and sauce covered with cheese and
sauce yeah yeah wait let me check on my
mommy
[Music]
my mom wrote to me 10 minutes ago you
were doing great gordon ramsay is full
of [\h__\h]
oh discord is in the chat too hello
discord you want some lasagna i don't
mind sharing with you
my mom is so
i also
all sauces eh
you mean all of the beja mel sons not
the meat sounds
my mom wrote all sauces what does that
mean
who is that mean mommy
baste
oh man i hope my i hope gordon ramsay
never hears that but i wasn't really
nice to him either was i
oh my mom says the meat sauce as well
let me look at the video mommy
let's
see layers layers meat sauce
ah yeah actually
[Music]
yeah it looks like he also put more meat
sauce on the very top and then just
topped it off with cheese and all that
i guess so
okay
i guess we can do that
all right
all right sorry for doubting you mommy
that's good because i still got left
over
okay
[Music]
nice
i just never i don't remember noticing
that on the top layer there was also
meat sauce i don't quite remember it
like that
but okay i guess we can do that
but i really haven't actually it's a
perfect amount i think
because
[Music]
my pot is almost empty
i'm almost done with the meat sauce
[Music]
yeah it might actually not be
a tiny bit too too little
[Music]
because i reduced it well
i wanted the meat not the juice
i had to reduce it
because if it if it's like too watery
then the lasagna will be so watery and
we don't want that
okay that's all i got
that's all i got
should be fine
give me a little bit of that
[Music]
yeah
we're fine we're fine
okay
all right looks good
uh
more juice is good sometimes you put the
juice in a cocktail what the [\h__\h]
okay
the rest of the bishop sauce oh it has
the perfect consistency texture
consistency i think is me just um
mixing german with english right now
because texture in german is conscious
tense
[Music]
which sounds like consistency but i
think it has a different meaning
cheese yeah
before the bijamil sauce did that [\h__\h]
up
[Music]
i mean with the layers we did like
cheese on top of the vegetable sauce but
it will be fine
it's a little bit difficult to spread it
oh it's a bit weird down here
[Music]
oh it has like a skin
that part is it we have it
we'll use it anyway we'll use it anyway
[Music]
could have used a bit more beijing sauce
eh
yeah
it will be delicious i believe in it
[Music]
thick sauce it's fine looks good
certainly will be okay i trust you guys
um
wait a second
[Music]
uh
really grasping onto the tiny amount of
bijamel sauce that i still have
uh
i can spread it a bit nicer like that
okay
just don't want to ruin it
so i don't want to touch it too much but
my kitchen is quite big but
now i'm lacking space because i have a
freaking
huge ass laptop
on my
counter
taking up like
half of my space
here
[Music]
i want lots of monsters i want all of
the mozzarella on top
[Music]
this is the vine divine exquisite
that seagull would love this lasagna i'm
sure
the cheese is forming an alliance with
itself
i have to separate the alliance
just dump it no it has to be pretty yup
it
has to be pretty
[Music]
much
when i cook
it has to be pretty
you forgot the sauce no i didn't
it will melt well yeah but still
okay yeah i'm done maybe a tiny bit more
cheddar because we didn't use much of
the cheddar
put more on on the side okay
[Music]
okay i will i know
okay
i will fill up the sides
with cheese
the edges
usually
cheddar edges
i'm so happy it really does look good
[Music]
pineapple oh man i would love to add
some pineapples
next time next time i make lasagna i'll
add pineapples
[Music]
okay
it now only has to go into the oven for
one hour
what will we do in that time
okay now it's half past 9 p.m
[Music]
to make sure
it will be perfect once
[Music]
again you can't reach
okay
[Music]
because the video had two
i'm putting in toothpicks
[Music]
why the video did that because i'm
putting um
putting foil on top of it and so that
the foil doesn't
stick to the
stick to the um
uh
cheese
it's like a birthday cake
[Music]
okay
oh i wonder i mean this foil has
reflections but
reflections that you really can't make
anything out of
so it will be fine
[Music]
but we don't really oh we don't really
need the camera right now anyway so
i think
why do you need foil i don't know the
video has
[Music]
foiled okay
it's a present it's a birthday present
[Music]
baby are you finished now
well it took me a long time to get up to
one 180
okay
okay putting it into the oven
[Music]
wait a second
retreat
pull the thing
okay
[Music]
back in there
the glove protected me
i touched i touched the thing
with one hand
but
the black glove
protected me a little bit
okay
in half an hour i will turn to um above
heat
all by hitting
so at 10 pm my dad i will turn it to
obver remember that guys okay oh my god
can i get a chair right now because i
need to sit down one second
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
oh okay i'm chilling in front of the
oven now
and all we have to do now is
wait
we want i mean i could honestly probably
just end the stream there and upload a
picture of the finished result
afterwards on twitter and on youtube
community i could do that i don't know
what do you guys think
because then i could at least calm down
[Music]
and actually
enjoy the lasagna afterwards should i do
that because it's going to be one
freaking hour man
[Laughter]
[Music]
nothing i think the the exciting part is
over
but we can talk a little bit and then
try it out we can talk for like 15
minutes uh like an ending talk
and uh
yeah i i kind of want to read super
chats but
i don't know i really can't breathe
today
so i feel like i will um
[Music]
kill myself if i read super chats
but
uh tomorrow is my day off
and i might just do a quick super chat
reading for um one or two hours tomorrow
um
to catch up
yeah
and uh the thing after tomorrow is the
mario kart tournament yay
okay i take off those gloves now huh
okay
um thank you gloves for protecting me
mario kart tournament yeah
it's funny how like you know
um i
told management that i'm doing this
mario kart tournament with ian and id
and i request trunkers is looking into
the open so cute i requested for
permission uh like weeks ago
and um
[Music]
apparently a few hours later
only a few hours after i asked for
permission for
a certain time in a certain
day
a few hours later
torah senpai
also request without knowing that i'm
holding an uh uh an event on a mario
kart event on that day at that time a
few hours later behind the scenes toys
had by requested for permission for a
tournament as well apparently
at the same time like i'm starting at uh
10 pm jst
tomorrow uh the day after tomorrow
and for some reason
they also requested for 10 pm jst
on the same day
and which is obviously wait so
management told them
and and that's why they are now having
it two hours before us
i mean honestly for me for me it was
like i asked uh the indonesian girls i
asked our en girls uh what time would be
good for them and and what day and the
only day that worked out in a span of 10
to 15 days was that date the 27th and uh
time-wise it was also only pretty much
that time
so
i i didn't really have much choice but
it seems like the torah sent by and uh
the girls that are participating in her
tournament also didn't have any other
available date and time
except a few hours earlier because now
they moved it to 8 p.m their time but i
feel like that's such a funny
coincidence
how is that oh and
we even requested it on the same day
i requested it like a few weeks ago and
we even requested on the same day what
is that
we request on the same day to have a
mario kart tournament on the same day at
the same time without without knowing
that either party wants to do it
coincidence i think that no it is a
coincidence it's so crazy though it's
crazy i have to drink water i'm dying oh
my god
great minds think alike
it's it's so weird
but you know what so before that's
actually funny because now it's like uh
[Music]
like it's kind of disconnected but in a
way i would say it's connected we have a
jp tournament as like the warm-up and an
enid the tournament isn't that nice
so if you're bored before our tournament
you can watch tola's empire's tournament
that starts two hours before our
tournament
and i will probably be watching it too
to look for like
advice on how to
how to do the whole
like introduction thingy and explanation
thingy
i will learn from those senpai because
she's done this a few times
[Music]
yeah
amelia
watson
requested to
be a shoutcaster however she requested
it
uh a little bit too late
which is yesterday
she was like on her stream and saying
she wants to be a shoutcaster and she
was doing a poll
uh with her viewers with the audience
she was like
guys
[Music]
i don't wanna i don't wanna drive
apparently she really doesn't want to be
in the like she doesn't want to drive
maybe she doesn't like mario kart but
she accepted to begin with and we have
12 participants it's a perfect number i
unfortunately cannot let you shoutcast
ahmed i need you in the tournament
if we had one more participant that
would be fine she can do a shoutcast
because she's great in it but
unfortunately
you have to drive
if she would have told me earlier we
could have talked about it but but i've
been playing this for weeks now and
she's she told me uh she told her stream
first of all yesterday
so
i'm sorry ahmed but she gave me a sample
of her shoutcasting and it sounded great
so
honestly she would be such a good
shoutcaster but we are 12 members
um and that's the perfect number for a
mario kart tournament i was so happy
because
you know
um this was this was the plan all along
that after iris joined ian we were six
girls and e er id has two generations of
three members each
so that's also six girls six plus six is
twelve that's right
and you need twelve participants
for uh that tournament yeah
it's the perfect number
i i can't i can't let's go anyone
get into the card amen
yeah
actually ina is
helping me out
and like i i organized a
really cool logo that you guys might
have seen on my schedule and all that
and on twitter um but yeah
make a mix or it already made
and
cards and
hats for us
yeah
so yeah
partially partially sponsored by um
taco taco bell
yeah
yeah so sweet right
i saw some fan-made
[Music]
cards on twitter which are great too and
i want to use those too
maybe for like another round but um
uh ina is making all of us matching
cards so
i want to i want to
use those yeah
yeah sponsored by taco bells and
caffeine yeah
[Music]
taco bell's oh funny funny funny
eh
are you gonna use the sponsor screen i
wasn't planning on but maybe i should
make something like that so yeah
tomorrow on my day off on my single day
off
i will be preparing the tournament
i still didn't make a proper
announcement picture so i still have to
do that tomorrow i'll do that asap maybe
actually today after i ate my lasagna
um
yeah
oh my god i'm really like dying here
more water
more
[Music]
well
and
i think we definitely should do cooking
streams again because this forces me to
um cook and learn new recipes because i
i really don't cook much
[Music]
i know a few things and um
the things that i do know i i i do
decently well
um but
like usually
i stream
um
during the evening a lot
so
i often end my streams
around or after midnight
and then it's so late that i'm like i
don't want to cook now and like often i
don't i'm not prepared for it anyway
because i don't really have the
ingredients here but if i
plan to stream a cooking stream then i
would do it like today
i go shopping beforehand shop for
groceries
and then cook during the stream so
i don't have to be like cooking after
the stream
and be like [\h__\h] i don't have time now
it's already so late [\h__\h]
so yeah
keep the same microphone
it's a [\h__\h] shitty microphone i mean
i might get a better one that's like
like
um
[Music]
a better one a better version of what i
have right now
something that picks up everything
around
yeah no it's not the old mic it's a
really really shitty it's way shittier
than the microphone that i use for my
debut it's just
this one is like you don't need anything
like you don't have to set it up
properly because it's like just a usb
microphone it's really tiny it's so cute
it's a it's a tiny razor
[Music]
mini
microphone
you sound even cuter
it's weird because i don't have my
headphones on
so
i hear myself very differently from
usually
i don't have the feedback in my ear if
you stream every [\h__\h] day for one
whole year almost
with that same setup you get really used
to it so now i feel like really weird
without the headphones on at the
feedback
[Music]
your kitchen sounds echoey ah yeah
that's probably because
i have like an open kitchen
uh like in my living room
and uh it's like open connected
and uh
i don't have much furniture in here
uh
it's not as echoey as it was when i
moved in and there was no furniture but
yeah
it's like very a very open room
very big
i'm gonna i'm looking forward to
watching the archive because i want to
hear what this all sounded like and
what what it sounded like when i was
cooking and stuff
we can definitely improve it i
understand that you guys um
like this different sound but if we do
this like almost weekly then i want to
uh get a better version of this
microphone
something that picks up you know the
uh audio
as much as this one does but just like
in a bit better quality
cali used uh for traveling she's using a
blue yeti microphone right
which is a usb microphone but she
sounded so good with that
yesterday in her stream on this score
she had a different one and it sounds so
shitty
[Music]
i'm gonna
see what i can
improve but yeah i'm not using my go xlr
and stuff because the ghost light
doesn't even work with usb microphones
yeah the collab was great yesterday you
think so
i had a huge headache yesterday
during that collaboration
and afterwards as well
uh
actually today also a little bit
yeah it's weird
but yesterday was fun yeah
[Music]
yesterday uh we wanted to do ttrpg on
eno's channel if you missed it then you
didn't miss anything because we ended up
not really tti we doing we did like
we did like 10 minutes 15 minutes
uh and then
you know we already had a big delay
because of things not working out
perfectly and
then we finally started but then it
still wasn't really
good and cali
yeah i understand the feeling of wanting
to move it to
a day when things work better so then we
just played garlic foam garlic garlic
phone
i was like how about garlic phone
in this situation
how about guiding phone the idea that's
basically the best choice because it's a
browser game it's free you don't need
much to set it up yeah
it's so much fun i feel like the the
knockout mode is like
a knockout
no golf knockoff
[Music]
the knockoff mode is like i think
funnier for the people who play it than
it is for the people who watch it but
still because like the time pressure
really really
pressures you and
is very very much fun
uh
i don't know how much fun it was for you
guys but i i think it was still
entertaining i hope so
we had a blast that's for sure yeah
so
okay guys um
i'm gonna
uh
cut off the stream here
and thank you for being here today
i hope you enjoyed it we'll do it more
often we'll
learn all kinds of new recipes
yeah
and uh i'll be
number one cook in kfc at some point
so i can fire all of you
and i'll just run this ship on my own
[Music]
no no no no it's not going to happen kfc
is freaking busy we have friends we have
the stores
restaurants all over the world i can't
do it on my own
don't worry you'll keep your jobs don't
worry i know you have to feed the family
yes yes yes
okay guys thank you very much
[Music]
i will show you guys the finished
picture
and afterwards let me look into the oven
right now
oh i don't see anything because i
covered it with uh foil oh yeah right
hope you like the sleeves
i will bring them again next time maybe
thank you thank you everyone
i'll see you maybe tomorrow for a super
chat reading it depends on how i feel
and how busy i am
and but otherwise i'll see you at the
mario kart tournament and i think we
also have a members only string
after the mario kart tournament yeah i
was thinking of playing uh fall guys
with the members only because it was
actually a lot of fun last time and so
many people were able to join
yeah so i think we'll do that
to uh the day after tomorrow
[Music]
okay
so
thank you everyone
and enjoy what we say
[Music]
thank you everyone
thank
[Music]
on twitter and on the youtube community
board
so check it out in like one hour or so
there should be a picture
[Music]
you