[Music]
do
hello sorry for the delay oh my god it's
a little bit messy
hello why the [\h__\h] are so many koreans
here even though it's what
now it's seven hours
so
about five
six seven two a.m is it two a.m i think
it might be two a.m
um
why are you here
[Laughter]
thank you not that i'm not thankful
but i'm surprised oh [\h__\h] my game closed
now come back to me okay whatever i want
to find my wheel first where did i put
my wheel
i have so many things always
where is ma
wait what what wheel am i looking for
though i i only like do i even have a
normal wheel
or do i only have a wolfie wheel do you
guys remember me ever using a normal
wheel
for driving
otherwise we'll just use the controller
i guess you just can just use the
controller oh i'm looking forward to
that day in a million years when we'll
have this like attached to our body
although
i have some concerns with it but but i'm
looking forward to it
and not not even png's but like uh i
don't know if you've guys seen the news
but yeah 3.0
uh basically we'll get new poses uh
where it will actually not be pngs but
like
um
which honestly i would already be happy
if we were able to attach pngs to our
bodies
i've been waiting for that
but sorry one sec
uh but but uh this will be a part of the
body like the actual like
new i guess i guess hookah papa has to
draw an extra
meow
arm pose i suppose
haha suppose
um
okay then let's say [\h__\h] that but at
least i want my mario kart logo where
did i put my mario kart logo
um
let me think
mario
mario not here
mario i love the little
marios that luigi says in the uh in in
the
in luigi's game
bleachers what does it call you just
mansion
it's so cute when he says mario
mario
it's so cute
what if i just put this here and just
say mario
it will just say mario um
mario
close enough now
[Music]
a million logos why did i i should have
just changed the freaking name
which mario game well exactly well
in order to just not worry about that
i would put up this logo and everything
is cool everything's happy
everyone's happy because we're just
playing mario
we're just playing a game called mario
mario
ah
maybe in this folder
it must be in this folder
mario kart tournament
yeah that's not it didn't i last time
end up using the mario kart tournament
logo which by the way just today i was
thinking
how about
another mario kart tournament but with
new tracks only but enid
oh dear
oh my god
am i here 64. i didn't find it last time
then it must be close thank you oh my
god oh
no i'm not taking part by the way
someone else asking in the chat if i'm
being being part of that mario kart
collab whatever no because it's too late
um
[Music]
yeah it was too late
time wise
yeah
maybe another time collabs really only
work if i'm the one inviting someone
or
if it's a full member myth collab
because then
it has to somehow
work it has to somehow work so that i
can be there but otherwise it's just it
only ever works if i'm the one
initiating it which is okay i mean why
would you if you always stream during
prime time america time
why would you
you know ask
for people to join a collab at a shitty
time slot when you could have more than
enough people join at a good time slot
which means prime time
it's just a logical
logical thing logical conclusion
um okay mario cart atx logo
ah where did you go
tools
did you know that if you look for images
on google you can
search for pngs
by setting the color to transparent and
then it will not give you those fake
pngs it will only give you real pngs
such a big brain thing i know
i told you that before yeah
i found it now we'll call it mario kart
logo
and we'll put it into my resource folder
so
that we'll never have to look for it
again
meets kata
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah it is known it is known it is
known
okay
so um i have one request for you guys
today uh i don't know if this is true
but i heard that
when
i wonder if you can maybe check
somewhere that only people with the dlc
can join in in the lobby but
um i want only people to join who have
the dlc please
because we want to play the dlc but if
someone joins who doesn't have the dlc
apparently
uh
only people with dlc can vote for ah
ah
yeah but
what if you're in a group with people
who
um
[Music]
some of them have a dlc and some of them
don't have the dlc but then you vote for
a track that has a deal that's a dlc
track
will the non-dlc people be able to
race it
for free
[Music]
hey
wow for once that's actually um
wow very generous of you nintendo
wow
yo
yo what oh
well okay but i don't want too many
non-dlc people joining because then the
the chances that a dlc track will be
selected as lower okay so
if you can please join if you have a dlc
if you don't have a deal season maybe
don't join today
i know download the contents on the
accent
[Music]
my switch turn itself off again come
back to me
come back to me
there we go
yeah my batteries are really low but
it's connected so it's all good
um
let's go let's see if it works i i
download it i bought it
uh and then downloaded it
what checking whether this software can
be played what do you mean
it should be daijoubu
for
what sure i thought he said mario party
eight
i was like what
did i open the right game
mario he says it the same way
mario party hey does he maybe
okay
so but there's no change in like how you
create a lobby right
[Music]
let's uh
yeah text audio should be fine now are
you sleepy why
i'm not sleepy
but
but uh today's stream won't be the
longest because uh
i want first of all it's mario kart i
like to play mario kart where i don't
want to play too long
and i gotta i want to cook
ah
i want to cook a hirakatsu
afterwards
after the stream i don't want it to be
late i have a fillet in my fridge
you can earn platinum points uh-huh
and is waiting for me to cook it into
japanese-style schnitzel
[Laughter]
hirakatsu is a
filet version of tonkatsu which you may
have heard of more often than hirakatsu
so i want to end it before midnight my
time um
uh
how does it work again
oh god the buttons hey hey hey we're not
on the playstation today
we're not on the playstation today and
now let me hide the screen because i
guess i don't know that's how we do it
uh which one will i use
and then let me write the code i guess
in the pinned comment this time
please
only join if you
have
[Music]
okay
join
uh the tournament is currently closed
mimi me open open open them open the
gates
wow is that a translator
this is the long korean text the
translation of something
why you're trying to tell me something
in korean
i think you might be trying to tell me
something in korean
guys why are you already here
you little shits
don't join beforehand
trying to be like like those people who
see it in the future yeah wait where are
the new courses wait where are the new
courses
no no wait wait how do i get to them or
does it eh
wait what what what does it mean what
does this mean
it's random
so we gotta go for all these shitty old
courses as well
young those are random maybe random will
give us something new that's a higher
chance
oh
my god
you know what i should actually uh
first look for the
for the courses
um
uh
i should look for the courses uh in
non-online mode first that's what i
wanted to do i forgot
except that's this is just so we can uh
guarantee
that
how do i
i don't i don't remember how to play oh
god how do you do the the bounce
[Applause]
pretty decent drift though
[Music]
how do you jump again
oh it's a button for jumping
grip button ah
oh
[Applause]
[\h__\h] yeah
i wanted to
[Music]
steve
probably didn't even do anything oh i
hear a bomb
why do you get a shitty item all the
time hey
boys
[\h__\h]
blue [\h__\h] all of you
thank god today i can rage
otherwise you would have an issue
[Applause]
i mean for the first time in a long time
playing this and being really confused
with
uh
the controls because i played on ps a
lot recently
i would say
oh the diving is
[Music]
guys what's up why are you guys so tired
why is the chat so dead
what did you think of the new girl with
the cute blue new girl cobble
i'm in love like
i want to protect that girl
i want to protect her
[Music]
she is so cute
six languages
well yeah
thank you
i might get i might leave though no okay
let's just stay
i should stay and hope for the best
that we get uh
download content
um she read your tweet really
this is neil
she didn't
okay old people leave bye bye
she didn't answer me yet
she cried after reading it she cried
like laughing crying or real crying
doing the collab oh i didn't watch that
one
ah
[Music]
she said you are her or she oh don't lie
no way
nah she didn't
did she really say that
didn't say that did she
she didn't say that right you want her
no don't lie to me
eh
what
the stream is over right can you give me
a times down
what
no
don't lie to me it'll make me so happy
because no one ever says kiwawa is my
favorite v2 bar
things i've never heard before kiwawa is
my favorite youtube i mean except from
you guys
oh she said i'm her sugar mommy did you
guys miss here suga mommy for oshie
[Music]
did you say it in indonesian because one
problem i have is that um um i didn't
understand anything
in her stream but i still watched the
whole thing because she was so cute like
the moment oh my god like her voice is
like legit like not like a lowly voice
it's like a child and it's just so
genuinely a child that i need to protect
and i need to be her mommy
yeah
okay let's look at this oh my god i look
so familiar maybe
i don't know not that familiar no not
really
no this one i don't really know
[Applause]
yeah no lambie will let me step i was
also saying oh protect but now she's mad
she's mine
oh there's a secret path there
[Music]
oh
i
the first thing oh that really got me
was like i she pulled up that thing and
i was like is that a pdf why is she how
is she scrolling and then i realized
because it said that she can code
uh then she made a [\h__\h] website and i
love like nowadays you know there's so
many youtubers out there with creative
ideas and all that it's really hard to
figure out new ways to be original right
um
i struggle with that too i want to come
up with something original as well but
she legit came up with something new
um by presenting her
whole thing
[Music]
through
through through for a website i mean i
don't know if that was really like an
actual
website but it was made like a website
and she made it herself
yeah
[Music]
damn it damn it damn it damn it
yeah that was those genies i love i love
the originality of that
i didn't see that anywhere else before
someone tried to make it like that and
she put in so many cute gimmicks
[Music]
okay i'm nice hallelujah
yeah
um
she did like i don't know anything about
coding so i don't know how high her
level is
um
but i was still impressed here sorry i
was focusing on the on the on the thingy
on this this here
okay when there's no no
new road on the free choices please
choose random
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
don't worry elena i i love you i love
you more so
but what new girl is so cute i don't
understand what she says but she's so
cute and even her broken english
is like
so cute like hello
the moment when she and was that the
only one thinking this the moment when
she was introducing her mama and her
papa like her artists basically and her
ringer
she was she was yelling mama
happily and it literally sounded like
like
a child a child excitedly
yelling for her mama and papa did you
guys
notice that
was like yes i guess i'm your mommy now
are you guys on your mommy now
and then and then i'm not
at the
when i'm not already what are we getting
oh okay
i can't talk anymore i'm so excited
then and then at this point where i'm
already super hyped up because she has
an original idea to present her debut to
us
she
pulls out this video of her singing i
mean the others already spoiled that
she's like a singer
um
but
i did not
i did not expect her also to be the
producer of her song
and
the producer and she made the video too
yeah i looked at the credits and i'm
like what
what
this
she
she can't
produce as in like she composed the song
what
[\h__\h]
yeah that's that's really really really
really impressive
like she may not be able to speak a
million languages fluently but she can
do other cool things that make up for
that
yeah
holy [\h__\h] like this this is
[Music]
i don't know man i'm i'm proud to have
like
such cool people in her life
uh what am i doing
[Music]
i don't know about that you know i'm a
special type she is like
she knows a lot of things but she's not
only that she's not only knowledgeable
and talented she's also you know you
gotta be um
you gotta have a talent in order to
really be
productive and and take the initiative
first things yeah yeah
[Music]
at the finish line oh
thank you
um
but yeah the presentation was so cute
and uh the singing was really good but
but i mean the song the song was good
it's like an interest song for her i
guess um but but but but but
it was really cute even though it was
like you know i don't understand
indonesian but but even then like the
way she speaks indonesian it's so cute
and and then and then and then and then
at the end she was playing
with her acoustic guitar
and that i liked even more
than her
um like recorded singing
i liked it even more
because
she kind of like what do you call it
she
she like she did these things with her
voice
what do you call it
no no please don't choose uh
only choose random if there are no new
tracks on the selection please
don't choose old tracks choose random if
anything
why does random keep on choosing the
tracks that are already on the selection
so boring
oh my god
she yeah reyna circulation
it sounded so cute oh man and even when
she was like thinking about the lyrics
my heart was like ah
doki doki doki
[Music]
um
they got a good one there
they made a good choice there
really really cute
talent was cute
i mean
i don't know
i don't know i don't know about you know
um
how much english she's gonna speak in
her stream so even without that she's so
cute
i
i normally don't get like this okay
i look at
new girls in a in a pretty
um
in the how to stay in a calm way
i'm like oh okay interesting which is
very good
but for
boko boko
how are you so cute i was i was
literally alone in our discord
fangirling over her
um
in text
the only one who replied to me was one
of our managers
at least
least the manager also understood
that she's great
get him get him
[Music]
no
mad world was playing in my ears
[Music]
i'm trying to focus oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
go crazy over here did she say something
i know she was streaming during the
debut
so she didn't
see it yet probably i don't know but
mine and standby loves those kind of
voices
so
she needs to see the new girl
my new senpai would go crazy
[Music]
[Applause]
what did i just get i immediately i
immediately acted i did it
new let me see remember oh but in theory
yes it fits the theme i guess like nah
actually
it's not about the ocean like people
like to put uh
everything into like the same category
even if they are just like really really
really really really really not related
yes you can't even swim the rain isn't
the sea that's
what i'm saying yeah
you shouldn't be unhappy that she
doesn't primarily speak english their
whole life indonesia
there's literally no reason for anybody
to be like unsatisfied or so like why do
you have those expectations in the first
place
you you should be happy that whole life
indonesia generally already speaks so
much english
but it's not something that you should
expect from them
like their whole life indonesia and if
they want to speak mainly indonesian in
their stream then
that is perfectly logical logical
logical logical
although yes i mean
it is a little it is a little bit yes
something new it's a little bit sad
because
she's so cute and i know you just all we
all just want more
for ourselves but yo you guys are so
greedy
wait you look you guys are so greedy
we can't have everything in our lives
okay
can't just have everything
but in order to give you guys more
english speaking kobo i i will collab
with her
for the sake of you guys you know
to make you guys happy
providing you guys with more happiness
[Music]
sorry
training
[Music]
almost
oh my god i'm winning camping
[Music]
i hope it reaches
probably won
[Music]
come
i'm second here up
[Music]
foreign
you stole it
not good stealing not good no no
oh paris is new that's from the phone
game
oh the phone came i was really into that
uh when that came out
or is it not wait is it that is it was
it there before
it says tour that was from the phone
game right
the one on the phone yeah yeah yeah yeah
cause it was leading us through all
kinds of like big cities capitals i
think
um that was tokyo as well
and what else was there
maybe there was uh
i don't know what else was there
okay you gotta choose that thank you
guys no random
or is that for the non-dlc people is
that even in their selection
or do they
do they have something else in their
selection
[Music]
should be the same right
it is a narrative
[Music]
but ah they can't pick it okay
this isn't that the second one
oh
did they
they must have brushed that up a little
bit from like what it looks like on the
phone right
looks okay oh it's nice
can i go through there
uh well i can but it will cost me
something
well i did something for the others i
opened up the new path for the others
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys wearing the music family
i was in paris before
last year i was in paris and before that
as well but the last year was the first
time i did some sightseeing
and
finally it was really nice because all
the previous times i went there for a
big big big
anime convention i don't know that all
these curves man called japan expo a
[\h__\h] that's reopened
[Music]
everyone suffer with me please
while other people would go into the
city for one day
i would just
stay in the hotel room because it was
like really far away from
from the city center anyway oh my god oh
my god oh my god i'm so shaky
[Music]
whoa that was how sharp
in german we like to say
that was har shah
as a
uh uh
sorry not spicy not spicy no no
[Music]
ah
that name means bring kiara to japan
expo thank you it's so fitting for this
map what the [\h__\h] as if you controlled
that
french fan puts that in their name and
gets the paris track
that is perfect
pop again
my new lucky number oh yeah close call
buy a hair exactly
[Music]
yum that guy gave you no don't say that
that's a lie that's a lie that's a lie
that's your imagination
bye bye thank you guys for joining
thank you
i wish you could like you could um
paint purdue
it's a
it's a french toast
pineapple
or something like that
um i wish you could choose like i wish
you could create a tournament where you
could just
check one setting
that uh
you only get new dlc tracks that would
uh that would be good
was that too difficult to program
[Music]
hello hello hello
where are the people
mina doko
where are you where are you
where are you hello
you guys not have the dlc or is this
just the internet making me way to the
online lobby making me wait
kuduka
[Music]
hello trying to get in
so it's the lobby
oh well in the meantime give me that
give me that thumbs down yo give me that
time sound
ah okay perfect just
give me give me time stamp does someone
have the time stamped
maybe it's in the comments somewhere
she doesn't have a time stamper yet all
she does
[Music]
you have a time stamp
either is there a clip
what clips are maybe cut too much
i don't see it cobalt like
oh
it okay here in the time step it says
cobble favorite whole live english
member
oh wait what did you say japan
yeah favorite senpai from whole of
english
now if this is not kiara like you guys
said
um
[Music]
okay my new name is cronie let's go
hello i'm connie nice to meet you yes
okay
[Music]
is
tongue
[Music]
yes
after i
after i finished my debut
and that she said she wanna buy me a
horse and violin
and then after that you know i i cry i
cry a lot you know
[Music]
do i really have to buy her a horse in a
violin
thank you for the horse thank you for
the filing
[Music]
again
i'm just talking about lambie
wait did you think about which one would
be her mommy
speaking of crying we all cried
don't cry okay
i need to know what that indonesian part
says
is that translated in the clip ah
there's a chance really um
[Music]
that she said she wanna buy me a horse
and violin and then after that you know
i cry
translations say i was so happy when my
oshie dot dot dot
and my or she said she wants to be like
my sugar mommy question mark
she's not clearly saying that either or
she and i think i am just one of may if
anything i'm one of the few people
that are maybe at the top of her heart
but not her number one or she could
otherwise if that was the case then she
would just say it outright like i love
kiwa but um
she mentioned other people first so
but it's okay it's okay i i'll i'll take
it i'll be uh your sugar mommy
sorry guys uh all the funds are now
being funneled into kobolcanido
she even has
a name that sounds like my favorite idol
group
betty's kobol
[Laughter]
so if i give her berries if i give
berries as a present to kobul
then
i have my favorite idol bag my favorite
idol group black
revived
back from the grave
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's so cute
so cute
she's so cute she's
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
you kiara no way no
well i mean it could be oh dear
could be a small violin you know small
violin to play like a small sad song
um
yeah no
no no she does not have the kusogaki
vibe that's what i was thinking like
normally like a lot of the time these
like
younger girls
in her life
they seem like a kusuoki maybe maybe
it's still gonna like change but
she doesn't really have the kusagaki
vibe to me right now
yeah she's just a uh
like an excited gakki
a happy gucky
yeah
she's sweet
sweet
[Laughter]
[Music]
my precious precious baby
okay
actually um also um
i was
dm'd
by
zeta i'm probably saying your name wrong
because i heard other people say a
chitta
is it
or how did she herself say it i don't
remember
she damned me and thanked me
for
being so nice about the things that i
said about her on stream i guess she saw
a clip yeah
it is zetta
zetta
not chetta okay like someone swoons at
cheta i don't know who
[Music]
ah yeah kaina said cheta i think so and
since she said it like that i was like
uh she's her jan mate she
if she says cheta then it's cheta maybe
yeah i was thinking of cheese
sounds like cheese man
is that just like a way of like making
fun of her
i'm very invested in this in all of this
right now
yeah but yeah uh
she
messaged me sent me a long long long
long long long dm on twitter because we
don't even have each other on discord
yet
yeah very sweet very polite
okay here we are there are no new races
welcome back everybody
oh
the some of the same people made it in
again though the okay you person made it
back in
okay random it is
there's sonic
sonic gotta go fast it's not fair having
sanic in here
that's foul play
and hmm and
uh
uh uh kyla is not
she says she says it herself she's not a
penguin
i was watching her stream too yesterday
she's not a pangolin okay
like
she's legit a human
[Music]
on uh yeah
on her own accord
she's not even though she looks a lot
like a penguin i know i know i know i
know she accepted it later on when
that's that's a quick exception
she already changed her mind
everybody wants to be a verb nowadays ah
we're just such a
popular breed it's understandable burbs
are literally like the sign
the animal that depicts
freedom
because we can mostly mostly most of us
can fly so understandable where you want
to be oh everybody wants to be a bird
everybody wants to be one of us
we're the popular
popular kids now
[Music]
i shouldn't have gotten into that
explosion
i hate this
track because it's like so narrow
why did you do that
[Music]
i've been playing osage because i can't
control it i wish i could control it but
i can't
you like have to go with whatever
uh the game gives you
if there's nothing in the selection
you're gonna go random and hope that the
randomness gives you something you
desire
you may have gotten the double items
but i'm ahead of you
it's time for a good item for me now
come on come on really
really
oh and i saw all of these girls
all of the three new girls
are
like into
games that i'm not interested in
it's either fps games or like moba games
so
yeah our interests don't really align i
was looking also at the animes that they
watched and also
not much aligning there
yeah i mean purple kyla a classic like
uh i think she wrote
did she write kale i think there was
kaon on her list
um oh yeah and diablo yeah um some
oldies some really oldies those are the
only two things that i found in common
with all of the three girls i think
nothing nothing else i feel like they're
like from a different world
one of them was really into shonen stuff
uh
wow and and all of them
all of them i think all of them said
there they were gonna stream a lot of
fps and did all of them say they're
gonna do asmr i feel like all of them
mentioned asmr
um
i think
so yeah interests are very different but
that is nothing that will stop us
yeah yeah party games are something for
everybody ah you're back
were you
kicked out before it's your second time
no
also
am i still the one hosting this this uh
is the game still considering me to host
because only if the host has a dlc
right
well we get that as a choice right but
but i got kicked out once
[Music]
um
it doesn't really have a host okay but
i'm the one who opened it so maybe that
counts for something
oh
yeah well
now
guys uh
guys uh i want the n
it was gf one
huh
that hair color is fallen as a hair
color am i uh
fauna
farm
hey yo
what what happened last night i don't
remember something like that happening
but but yesterday's collab was fun right
yeah yeah
[Music]
i'm glad we did that
i could have just done something solo or
something small
but i was like hey how about i
we randomly spontaneously
do something bigger than that
oh no yes okay
[Music]
brakes go like
no
i don't
girlfriend give me those items that you
stole from me oh oh free
or green the shells i don't want them
never mind
no yeah yeah collab was good
that was good indeed
[Music]
yes yes yes
i had some good laughs in in that collab
was very happy
[Music]
i'm walking into everything
that curve what the [\h__\h] is that curve
it's not even a curve it's just a
corner
the hell
i hate this course is there anyone who
likes this course
okay at some point at some point
you were grinding my gear is a little
bit too strong
oh my god
just big big [\h__\h] f
no no no
[Music]
it can't be speed on here
no
so useless that item in this situation
[Music]
the chance or the yeah the chance of us
getting a
a new track seems to be pretty low so
far
maybe i should just get go offline mode
and play against npcs man
still nothing okay you better choose
random guys
better choose random okay
i don't want to see any of those three
selections on there
give it a chance
ah 64 but only eight
yeah yeah it's not even that much yet
they only added eight that is right
that's true yeah
random only picks from the free no it
doesn't i've seen uh it do
choose something else before too
no it doesn't
huh
mr incredible oh he looks like him i
choose anything right oh my god two
people commented that in a row so i was
like what the [\h__\h]
does not only choose from the free thank
you i was getting confused i thought i
thought i was wrong because
two people in a row were saying really
does only choose from the three
ah
i saw some fan art of me today
in in a
in a cow print bikini did you guys see
that i didn't retweet it i only liked it
um i thought it was too sensitive to
retweet perhaps
[Laughter]
oh it picks any map thank you okay
do you see it
yeah it's quite spicy
i mean you know i gotta be honest like
i'm i'm really not into oh my god [\h__\h]
all of you
i'm really not into animal print clothes
at all
i just find it very tacky especially
like um
uh the little
little part
what's little tiger prints and not tiger
prints not only those what are the
others called again
leo part and then
yeah i don't like those at all
so tacky to me
i mean some people can make it look good
but a lot of people
look so tacky to me wearing those kind
of um whatever shirts jackets pants in
that print no no
no no nothing for me
hey
who's shooting fire at the phoenix
without permission
oh i do have a license for that fire i
don't think you do
boy
[Music]
oh my
god austrian countryside be like
this no not really this is uh which
country is supposed to be
ireland poland
[Music]
netherlands
yeah it's probably something like
um
oh oh
it was just reminded because we were
talking about the animal prince there
was this one fanart that mamaloni did of
me before i got paris again okay paris
it is
that one was in tiger print a full body
suit in tiger print and i'm telling you
that looked hot okay
i'll i'll give you that
i hate i hate animal prints but that one
was because it was the year of the tiger
so it was basically celebrating that
i'll show you wait i just i was just
looking at it today i was thinking
uh what what do i pick as my thumbnail
hold it this one
ah
i mean
i'm looking cute as a tiger
it's like i came out of that um
out of that uh animal anime
what was it called again
uh and um okay come on camel friends was
this camel no friends
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh
imagine imagine a world where
is not a burb but a tiger i think it
still fits because orange
and you know i like my cat ears so
yeah we could just say i'm a tiger it's
in the pinned comment
tournament code is in the pinned comment
yeah what would my name be
my name would just be taiga yeah yeah
i mean takanashi still makes sense
because uh there ain't no hawks around
as a tiger i would eat up all those
hawks man
kiss my dark
time to go back to paris i honestly i
want to go back to paris or like it
doesn't have to be paris i was looking
at um
some pictures
of france like a while ago
um it was i forgot where i think it was
in the south of france
and it was some kind of huge uh wine
what do you call them again like a big
big place where you where they make wine
um
[Music]
what do you call those places again
a vine yard written vineyard why
[Music]
and they have really huge beautiful ones
in
in france
and
it was i mean i don't care about the
wine at all obviously i don't like
alcohol but
[Music]
everything was going so nicely and you
have to ruin it
[Music]
ruined
everything is ruined that was fun
what happened
oh [\h__\h] you i didn't need that i'm
already at the bottom
okay well i'll continue my story
oh
[\h__\h] you
what you changed it
um
paris overrated i hear a lot of people
say that
um i think like
it definitely is worth visiting it has
its beautiful beauty
beautiful
whoa
uh
uh monuments and and sights and all that
definitely so i wouldn't say it's
overrated but
um
no i wouldn't say it's overrated i think
it deserves
but but but there's definitely
um even more beautiful places in the
world or maybe even in in france because
well it depends on what you like i guess
because if you like like big cities like
beautiful cities old old looking
beautiful cities
then paris will be to your liking but if
you prefer some beautiful countryside
then you might like the south of france
for example i guess
but anyway there was this beautiful
beautiful vineyard where apparently
people
um like to get married too because they
have this beautiful beautiful venue at
the vineyard it's just like a huge
mansion
um like like a castle pretty much
it looked so nice and i i sent that to
my paris friend and i was like
i want to go there
it's really pretty
i i can look up where that was i
probably could still find it um
it was so pretty but like there's i
don't know why i would go there like
what could i do there just walk around
for the vineyard and
yeah there's not much to do for someone
who doesn't like wine i guess
[Music]
oh but i could combine it
by also going like to
the french
beach or something because in the south
of france it's really nice for a
vacation as well as far as i know don't
don't don't don't
why are you not choosing random how many
times do i have to tell you guys
because of you we're getting an old
track it could have been a new one
why are you not choosing
oh
my heart my pain oh man
face palm
told ya
i told you to choose random if there is
no new track in the selection
mode
okay but i have some practice with this
one
[Music]
oh but i remember this one in the
tournament [\h__\h]
in the tournament like
i was like okay i can do this i can do
this i can do this but then i got really
[\h__\h] over and i was then so far behind
at some point that there was no way how
good i would be driving there was no way
i could catch up anymore
and by the way
in the beginning of the stream i said
let's do
a
new mario kart tournament with new
tracks but if you can't really select
them wait no way you can select them in
in a tournament like
uh not an online tournament but like a
private tournament right
wait no you can i think i remember us
being able to choose
i never mind them you can do it we will
do it but we will wait i guess for the
rest of the tracks
which will take a couple months when is
the last wave coming again
you guys know that of the top of your
head
anyone who remembers that
end of 28 and end of 2023
okay maybe we can do it a little bit
earlier we don't need that many tracks
although
if there's not that many tracks then uh
the girls will have
less
to practice
it will be easier to focus on just a
couple ones which is i mean good for
yourself but
you will know that everyone will have
put in a good amount of practice because
it's really not much to practice
it will be a very tough battle
listen
like if it's just 16 tracks
as opposed to what was it before 64.
oh [\h__\h] you other daisy
because of you i fell off the cliff
because of you i fell off the cliff of
the track
because of you
[Music]
i don't want to do this anymore
ah whatever whatever whatever i'm gonna
i know i know
oh oh i thought that was gonna hit me
thank you for waiting is that your
apology was it puna was it funa who
chose this one
is that your way of apologizing to me
i take it as an apology
no esta motivada
no
okay come on give me one new track
give me one new track
[Music]
what a shame indeed holy [\h__\h] sea bunny
you are
huge
thank you for joining welcome to new
people
is this
this is where the new people are you
guys new people
you got in thanks for the race welcome
well who is that little guy looks cute
is that small on it wait that that that
suit that space or i guess it's a racing
suit but it fits as a spacesuit too
because we're in space we're literally
on earth it looks like the the suits
that we were wearing
oh
i'm welcome
you better choose random
one two three how many people is this
random random random random random
random good
good
smart
thank you
you're not going to look at it it might
really be small on it
cute i love small llamas
mommy's so cute especially together with
that staff person
oh it's mine and i've ruined it
[Music]
why why why
i smell down here
it was smaller
[Music]
it was small on me i finally came back
by the way from her hiatus
uh
she's finally back
already in full power
as she streamed what three times
yesterday
including the collab
did she no maybe only twice i think she
wanted to maybe stream three times but
she ended up only streaming too tense
i think
yeah yeah still more than enough
[Music]
i was just i was just trying to be
slower so i wouldn't be too fast
[Music]
yeah okay no one's taking that from me
oh
of course
[Music]
oh
how is this possible
okay we can change that we can still
change that
[Music]
i hate mario kart why did i even still
bother playing this game
alright so how many members do en and id
combined have now
uh
it's l eleven and nine right twenty
are we 20 now
[Music]
that's a nice number
was so crowded now we're so many now
you know
what can we do with 20 people
20 people
[Music]
10 versus 10
yeah what what kind of huge collab would
that be
what game
[Music]
double star
did that
give me more time with my star
[Music]
ignore that guy in front of me i'm fifth
among us with 20 people holy [\h__\h] kill
me please
20 people imagine a discussion with 20
people
yeah maybe we don't need to force a 20
people collab
except for maybe maybe maybe mario kart
somehow
oh there's something new
don't ruin this guys
thank you for participating goodbye see
you later alligator
shroom bridge i don't even i don't know
this one from the ds i don't play mario
kart on the ds
um you guys thank you
are these new people maybe these are new
people
are we
are we out of
people who have the dlc
minadoka
are you guys trying to join
one of the best ones from the ds ah
there you go
welcome
welcome welcome shroom bridge
why did you choose random
i am gonna be mad if it's that random
one
[Music]
two group mixed
if there's exactly two
people in the en who don't want to
participate we can have nine versus nine
ian vs id
uh
mario kart tournament
oh yeah minecraft tournament yeah yeah
there's a lot of things that people do
with minecraft
uh yeah yeah
that's true yeah wait now we have
actually a good amount of people
for
a summer festival like japan does but
only with e and an id
a little bit more cozy than the big uh
one in japan
but they do
well we can do an enid one oh and then
me and amma can organize it
me and i'm at the organizers
my coin
[\h__\h] taxi i don't want an uber right
now sorry i'm i'm fine i have my own car
now
okay i'm just trying to get to know this
course it's all good
i'm not mad
build competition no i mean like a big
festival i mean it could be anything
there could be a building competition as
a part of
the whole thing
yeah
we wanted to revive minecraft anyway
okay fine with me oh
oh there's a shortcut there
[Music]
okay
holy [\h__\h] those curves
those girls y'all
[Music]
almost as curvy as cronier
that was
close nice items
nice items
oh boy
hello
oh my goodness thank you hello again oh
two of them
[Music]
i mean for my first time on that track
that was pretty decent i think
[Music]
that looks cool
wait
is that really new because it doesn't
say one of those ds things or tour
things
where is that from isn't that new
that one is brand new
ah
well wha
the best one
is a tour track why does it not say that
join join everybody here
we have a good one here
[Music]
favorite track of the dlc oh music is a
banger
it was a mistake on there and oh okay
not a hotel so it wasn't even on purpose
not at home
and it doesn't say tour even though it's
apparent wait this is from the boat then
i must know it
was that the oh
is that the the like the tokyo track it
was it like this wasn't it daytime
is that really from tour uh maybe that
would got added later on oh [\h__\h] what
only with so few people where is
everybody no
there's another token track
oh okay okay this one's more ancient ah
was tour adding on tracks later on as
well
i think they must have
oh dear oh dear
it just came out for tour oh it's new
for sure as well oh looks good
[Music]
track mouse
how am i able to drive up those stairs
like that when the gap between is
where am i where am i
where the gap between is is
it's bigger than holy [\h__\h] this man
oh no
i didn't get an item
i see so there's gap in the upper level
so you can fall down but i guess it's
better to stay up or oh dear oh okay wow
wow wow wow
it looks really good though looks really
good
[Music]
you know it's confusing but it's
interesting
oh god
oh god oh sure
[Music]
hello oh she turned into a banana
is that like a ninja trick it's probably
supposed to be a ninja turtle
okay
i'm doing really bad but just because
it's my first time okay
it's like we're
like tiny mice in this huge ass building
okay we're going up apparently
good luck here oh i'm falling down
oh god
i'm still up there
whatever whatever whatever whatever
whatever whatever oh my god oh my god oh
oh what the [\h__\h] what
[Music]
horrible driving presented to you by
yours truly
turning into banana thank you
you were in the way
[Music]
oh blue shell
get that mpc
all these marios no
you shouldn't
you shouldn't put those cherry gummies
on the tatami
no the poor tatami mat it will suffer
we'll get holes
i don't like that spot
it bugs around weirdly when you drop
down
[Music]
thank you for waiting for me
yeah i felt like uh this map was a giant
a map made for giants and that was just
really really really small
[Laughter]
[Music]
so far how many did we see four or five
we didn't see all of them that's for
sure
five tracks or something like that i
think we saw paris we saw
uh this one just now
we saw something
with taxis
and another one
i think that's i have four probably i
think i remember for it
[Music]
coconut mall oh maybe it was five
maybe it was five i don't think i was
thinking about
the coconut mall yet
okay yeah
let's try to get
one more
i don't want to try getting all of them
but let's see let's see
it's really difficult to get all of them
apparently
[Music]
come on come on come on come on come on
now you'll see
i love yoshido
i love your [\h__\h]
why are you not getting it higher than
fifth um
because
because it was a new track okay
you can roast me when i get uh
any nothing hide and fifth on on a track
like this
which will probably happen
[Music]
we should be sleeping a time
i wonder how good a
[Music]
with mario kart maybe i should
challenge her to some mario kart
[Music]
and then she's secretly like
freaking insane pro level
i can see that coming another one
number one
yeah
oh [\h__\h] you eggman
i'll go back to the top sooner
[Music]
i just went back to the bottom because i
wanted some good
i am your empress
[Music]
one for you
oh
it was time for my comeback well you
gotta ruin my comeback
oh
[Music]
you waited for that didn't you
are you trolling me
what's happening
why would you steal my items
[Music]
go away go away please
yes
[Music]
there was a time when i was number one
oh eggman was waiting for me oh thank
you
so sad oh by the way this was the face i
was doing for the whole time of uh
kobo's uh debut
this was my face
from beginning to end
like legit
but in a happy way in a happy but like i
can't believe this
who is this girl
wait
i need to protect her why is she so why
is she so cute like
i couldn't believe it
i couldn't believe it it was so cute i
wanna i want her i want i wanna acoustic
karaoke from her
i really want acoustic karaoke
that one guy with japanese name and says
i want to save kiara
and mario kart there is some saving to
do other than that you don't need to
save me
just in mario kart
okay okay no no
no
you [\h__\h] it
is it so difficult
is it so difficult is it so difficult to
choose random
oh my god
[Applause]
oh that it's it's excite bike arena
[Music]
let's go
it's psyching and voting fashion hasn't
[Music]
i'll be mad for a while guys get used to
it
[Applause]
oh finally i need to it's sunday i need
to make the schedule for
the coming week
um i was originally planning to stream
tomorrow but i got gotta go to the
doctor tomorrow
urgently
um
[Music]
yes
so i don't even know when i can go
because i don't have a yup i don't have
an appointment
[Music]
so it's kind of like up in the air
[\h__\h] but i'm fine i'm fine
just something urgent
small
get it
[Applause]
but then i will stream on tuesday
yeah
and oh my god i have something so so so
so so great oh for april fool's
i can't wait to show you guys
i wish i could smile right now
but i'm so angry i'm just so angry
oh and i'm gonna do one snack box review
um
[Applause]
next week uh yeah the coming week um
oh dear earlier earlier
[Music]
i actually have two snack boxes with me
right now that i can choose from but i
already told you i'm doing spain so i
guess i'm doing spain
okay uh
but the other one is actually older but
arrived recently for some reason
apparently it's from way before i don't
know why
why i got this one now
uh
it's
a swedish snack box
wait twisted mansion
it's so familiar to me but this is
this is is this from gamecube is this is
this new but old
it's old
or okay
[Laughter]
okay then random it is
um
yeah the swedish snack box but i guess
i don't know should we just spat the
spanish one first but the swedish one is
older and i'm worried about you know
expiration dates i didn't check them
though
[Music]
maybe because the last one was i mean
it had some spanish things in it maybe
we should do the swedish one first yeah
so that it doesn't it's not too similar
to the last one that we did the last uh
review that we did
yeah let's do the swedish one okay
i'll do a swedish snack box review next
week
i'm interested in swedish snacks
[Music]
suzuki
if if if we get that wario track
oh thank god
[Music]
a cheap cheap beach okay
oh swedish swedish no ikea is next oh
there's so many npcs in here what the
hell
what
[Music]
please leave after one race yeah is
anyone staying
i had
a feeling but i thought it was my
imagination
some somebody looked like they were here
for a while
but as as you can see from the npcs it's
hard to get in here apparently anyway
[Music]
ah this gives me a vacation vibes
i'm excited about my vacation
[Music]
okay i normally never go this way this
is the first time ever that i went
through this way
rather than just go for the water boldly
i like to make both choices
[Music]
i don't want to go where everyone else
goes you know
[Music]
i gotta go my own way as they say in
high school musical
my own fire heard me
[Music]
normally normally that ink really isn't
much of a problem
but right now it [\h__\h] me over
[Music]
it
oh
that item you could have stolen me
something better goes to chan
[Music]
something coming for you present present
for you
yeah
how's it feel huh
blue shell right in your
[Laughter]
face didn't do anything
stars are these star items are just too
nerfed what the hell
oh my god never mind bye-bye
never mind suckers
mostly npcs but
yeah
[Applause]
you didn't see that coming did you
didn't see that coming
certainly phoenix
nothing new once again i'll give it i'll
give it um
20 more minutes until we're at two hours
of streaming time
[Music]
is that the colonel
colonel is that you
is that you colonel colonel my man
it could be any old guy though maybe
it's just a
it's a saturday okay
[Laughter]
oh what is that
what's that supposed to be right next to
me
a dragon
this dragon
okay random please
looks like a kernel
maybe he's just trying to stay uh on the
cover anonymous
by the way
yesterday before the stream
before the collab stream
ame
amen
showed us
[Music]
some
some insights into
her new office
oh exciting
hey
yeah and we all got like super excited
like oh my god oh my god this is dad and
this
[Music]
i was in the groove man i was feeling it
yes i basically met bubba yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
but yeah i feel more and more um
that i i might wanna
visit america
this year
america and maybe i don't know somewhere
else
there over there
oh [\h__\h]
um
but
i kind of want to
i want to go to a couple of cities
because like
there's like so much so much to see like
there's so many big-ass cities
in america how do i even decide where to
go
how
i have a good friend
who lives
also in america
i think
somewhere in
miami
i think we're mixing up things maybe
miami is on
on the east side or is it is it on the
east side
is it on the inside
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
miami sounds cool
wait i've been to san francisco before
but that's on the west
side is it
i don't remember
[Music]
wait maybe it was on the east side i
don't know
it is it is
i didn't see much honestly i wouldn't
mind coming back to san francisco
because of what what i saw i liked but i
really didn't get much
time to
look around
uh i really didn't see much
but yeah this is san francisco not very
nice to walk around because it's like so
so like the streets are like up and down
and up and down and i hate that
toad turn that no that's not new or is
it no it's not new
no it's not
is it no
that's the one with the annoying cars
everywhere
[Music]
um man it's just hills so many [\h__\h]
hills man
and i don't even i don't even think i
really want to go to new york because
it's just
god i feel like the crowdiness would
scare me
the amount of people there i think would
freak me out like that's
too much even though i'm used to like
tokyo
um
but i think new york would actually
scare me
what is a city you guys would recommend
me
[Music]
oh
vancouver is in canada chicago miami
boston
detroit
chicago
new
a lot of chicago and
miami detroit
boston boston
are you just saying wherever you live
because you want me to be close to
you what's in boston i don't hear much
about boston i mean i've heard it before
but what's so cool in boston
[Music]
it's not very very uh famous as
university
oh isn't there a city called phoenix
or or a county or i don't know something
that's called phoenix
probably not that worth going to
his story boston is his story oh
there is phoenix arizona
yeah
but i heard we talked about that place
before and i heard it was very uh hot
and dry
it's not even on the coast is it i want
to go to a coast
city
because then i can go to the beach
yeah always got to combine vacation with
beach if possible
if it's possible
then i gotta go to the beach
is the beach nice there
in
american coast cities or is it dirty
[Music]
i reckon that in some place like uh
well what was it los angeles is on the
coast too right
it would be very dirty
it depends
la
l.a is l.a dirty
hello yeah
good beaches in florida where is florida
oh god things are confusing me
l.a is dirty
california
our beaches are better
all right guys isn't that even miami is
in florida oh
oh
when i think of miami i feel like the
beaches would be really nice what do i
know i know nothing
well
i gotta go to big cities though because
i need to use airports i don't have a
car
my only way of transportation will be
car uh ubers and
um and airplanes
[Music]
[Applause]
for me hawaii is like amazing and
definitely a place i want to go to
someday but i wouldn't include that in
an in a
america
um
vacation
because it doesn't feel like america
it does not i'm sorry but it doesn't
feel like america it just feels like
some awesome
vacation destination
but
like when i think of
america vacation i think of places like
miami
los angeles
new york and all that you know i think
you guys understand what i'm saying i
would i still want to go to hawaii one
day though
yeah if i can
if i can
i live eternally so i have a lot of time
to check those places out
all right let's go random guys random
once again we have someone who does not
understand what i'm saying
[Music]
alaska
ah
you're right disneyland where's the big
disney world
again
i asked this before
oh i hate that bro uh
i hate that track i hate it super bowl
slippery
ew
orlando well then i have to go to
orlando
[Laughter]
and then i have to go to orlando
oh
florida i'm coming for you
not there not fair
i guess you had a bad start too buddy
i'm with you
whoa the seitan bins is even
let's go
good items hallelujah
i heard there was a secret cap that no
one's using except for me but i fell off
so no more of secrets have for me
i'll do my best to win anyway
i am power be with me
stop [\h__\h] against the wolf hallelujah
hallelujah
[Music]
decent recovery
oh no i hate this crap so much always
bald against
[Music]
who wanted to create this track oh
wow
[Music]
i'm not into seafood
i don't like seafood
unless it's unagi don or um some grilled
normal fish okay i'll eat that
i'll go up here
[Music]
safe zone
[Applause]
[Music]
apparently
ah
i did my best
i did my best hang in there kiwa i was
trying my best to hang in there
i was really trying
to why are there so many french toasts
today
it's not even always the same person
it's like they're changing faces and all
that too
why are there so many french toasts
uh still nothing new we are very unlucky
[Music]
thanks guys for joining we'll give it um
one more try
one more try and then i've had enough of
mario kart for today
[Music]
french people have home field advantage
in the paris map stuff yeah because that
is like a really realistically created
map with exactly the same roads and
corners and all that
[Music]
hey why don't you choose that road all
right wrong track wrong trick
with that smug face of yours
[Music]
mine got selected but i was not lucky
enough
i fought so i was looking at your hair
and i was like that looks like a
fountain hairstyle to me
wow
um corbett's art style is so interesting
it looks really really special
yeah
oh my gosh racing with me apparently
kobe lives in mexico
okay a reason for me to go to mexico
let's go to mexico
[Music]
i'm coming for you
don't be scared
i'm bringing you violin and your horse
horses should be fairly cheap in mexico
no
i'm hoping i'm hoping for some cheap
horses honestly like
i i kind of want a horse too maybe we
can share a horse i want a horse too
i have a friend
uh who has a whole what [\h__\h] who has a
horse um keeps it in like a kind of like
a rental stable like you basically rent
like an apartment
for your horse
and i was asking her about like
how that works and all that looking into
it because
[Music]
i may have mentioned this before but
when i was younger
i went to
a
horse arriving camp for one week
but i really liked it and i picked it up
quickly
it was really fun
and you know
every little girl likes horses you know
that
but didn't have the
funds to continue doing it as an actual
hobby this is pretty expensive hobby as
well
i want to say [\h__\h] this is how i save
myself from saying that
but yeah
horses buying horses is expensive but
even if you don't buy it and just go to
like a random place and get their horses
even then
it's expensive to
[Music]
foreign
coming out of nowhere i say that
i see you my nose is itchy
[Music]
okay yes
indecisive are you
my car is feeling very keema good at
today
my chance to get back at all of ya
come on come on no nothing can't be
saved anymore did i say this was the
last one okay one more
we're not at two hours yet wait it's
still going
what no it's not going what's happening
i i can't control my
what
she's endlessly continuing now
[Music]
connection seems dead
oh i didn't know that secret thank you
for showing me game
hey yo we can learn some things here
whoa
eyes because someone didn't but then
wouldn't i see
um
something else
yeah that one
we just passed the one person who
doesn't move
oh there we go yeah i think it's just
because i was too far behind what are
you talking about maybe are these seed
okay
last one
time out for the squid yeah
that was fun let's do it you're welcome
if you ever if you ever need something
from your senpais i know you have id
senpai's but you can also come to me
[Music]
okay last one last one i'm just hoping
really for one more
one more
of the new tracks please please please i
have a bad feeling though it won't
happen
mexico
yeah
uh
i'm waiting for you guys there you go
there you go looking fabulous okay
random here we go
come on crush your thumbs cross your
fingers
[Music]
and hope for the best wish for the best
please please please please please
[Music]
please
you're giving me so little game
so
little
so little that i can work with
okay let's make the best out of it i'm
gonna get number one today
i'm gonna get number one now you just
watch and learn
please cooperate
oh dear i missed the boost
bad start
i got an item okay
that was not enough boost
[Music]
it's horrible
oh it's one with zero out of three
that's just a glitch in the matrix don't
worry about it
[Music]
oh bananas
oh
[Music]
no
man
mario kart be like
[\h__\h] yuki wawa you're working so hard
every day but you're not getting
anything in return no no
it's like the least rewarding game
ever
that's really true though like no matter
how good you are items can [\h__\h] you over
in an instant
[Music]
just like i [\h__\h] over that number one
there
[Music]
oh
at least i got my double items can i get
one of those too yay
okay
good comeback
ah and the ring seems like a walk in the
park well i mean
that is also a very tough game but at
least with practice
you can
yeah
be successful while in mario kart no
matter how much you practice oh never
mind we have a new one this is the last
one but this one is from the phone game
this one i know
the tokyo track
from the mobile phone mario kart
thank you guys for participating
according to saigon
this is the last one for real because i
was thinking if we have a new one now
then i gotta make an exception
i hope i won't be racing this one alone
hello
guys i finally got my visa i'm finally
going to tokyo
i'll be back
i'm going i'm coming back to tokyo
but i'm going alone apparently um
no come on i believe i believe
hello
where is where's holdem myth there we go
this is holometh welcome hello myth
with a [\h__\h] ton of npcs
okay
holo myth tokyo [\h__\h] npcs you're not
gonna ruin this for me
you're
you're not gonna ruin this for me npcs
why did you pick
random oh my god oh my god oh my god i'm
ragequitting if we're not getting tokyo
hallelujah
yes
hello
no connection error please
hello please
hello
melissa
[Music]
nintendo online
please
why is my visa being the knight no no no
no oh
wow you scared me there
you scared me back here oh she's back
pedago is back
let's see
there was a time when that was better
than better kiana and then better kiara
changed their name
to worse kiara and then equal kiana
[Music]
[Applause]
as well
i'm pork chop
[Music]
i don't like these items
one plus two is four that's not true is
that because i said that at some point
is that did i say that
is that a rainbow avoidancy
is that the rainbow bridge in order
[Music]
thank you oh my god i waited so long for
this finally i can do my 3d debut in
tokyo
how exciting
[Music]
okay
there's two people so far ahead i'll
never catch up to them now i'm virgil
bye bye
bye
oh wait oh
the highway when the tokyo highway
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] no
oh
doesn't matter doesn't matter doesn't
matter
[Music]
do you have something to say
get on your knees and change your name
that was the highest today yeah i just
know my way around tokyo
oh there was a really well made guda
with a hood
oh my god
that is such a rare replacement for me i
rarely ever get second holy [\h__\h] i don't
even know that number anymore i don't
even know the value of that number
anymore
yeah it was worth it playing one more
round
you got that
nine
[Music]
finally finally some
some way of uh
showing my my my cute chimpkins how cool
i am
what do you think about the new maps um
they're they're good they're fine yeah
um but
until the end of
2023 is
kind of insane
like
eh
[Laughter]
that's a long [\h__\h] time
i mean i don't mind them
releasing them in like steps but that's
a lot of steps
that's a lot of steps
oh yeah yeah yeah it's also
a way of
yeah um
keeping mario kart atx alive which it
totally was like it's not like it was
dead before this at all it still had
good sales
but you know what that means there's
also no mario kart 9 for another two
years probably
holy [\h__\h] yeah this came out in what 20
2014 according to someone in the chat
yo
i think before that mario kart came out
very frequently like they came out with
new games very frequently
um
but
yeah i mean i don't have a problem with
mario kart 80x i'm not really wishing
for a new one but i know there's a lot
of fans who want a new mario kart
um
yeah but
but
i mean
this is fine
[Music]
i don't think it's really necessary to
put out
a new one when this one is
fine
and it has a lot of tracks and there's
everything you need
if if instead it means we're getting
other nintendo games then what the hell
i mean
yeah
i know this is fine
yeah i think i mean if
i don't say this is fine and dead in
that way we really mean it's fine it was
fine maybe maybe if there's a new
console coming out then that's a reason
to make a new one i don't think they
need a million different mario karts for
just the nintendo switch
yeah no
right yeah there's no need to be like
salty about it i guess
it's okay this is fine
[Laughter]
this is fine no it's actually fine no
really it is fine
it's always one per console is that so i
don't know about that i didn't i don't
follow it that closely i played some
mario karts in the past but you know
okay so now i will go to my office and
i'll read super chats from yesterday and
today okay
okay
thank you guys for participating today
um as i said uh if you're not staying
for the super chat rating as i said
tomorrow is my day off and i'll put out
the schedule soon maybe tomorrow maybe
i'll put it out tomorrow
and um
yeah next week
uh
please check out my april fools stream
i don't think you i don't think you can
ignore my april fools stream anyway
i gotta
um
i gotta work on my whole
plan a little bit more though
okay okay let's go to
yeah i don't need a break let's just go
to the office
hello
here we are
let me fix the chat
that was mario kart today
it was
okay
yesterday was more fun
it was decent i wish i wish it was
easier to just go through all the
um courses that i want
[Music]
vampire oh yeah yeah i was thinking just
the other day that i should switch out
one of those but i'm too lazy
making it fit into that little tv is a
little bit difficult
because i have to place it on top not
underneath
um yeah i could replace it or something
else i will do it eventually
eventually
i don't actually spoil anything oh oh i
don't think there's really
much to spoil it was just a drawing gas
collab that was really funny i don't
think it would be really a problem but
if you want to go then okay fine it's
not like i want you to stay or anything
it's not like
not like i care
no
i don't i don't care
i don't care i don't care whether or not
you're here or not
um
i don't care it's not like it matters to
me
but let me put this on the phone oh oh
you know what like i uh i put up like i
made this thumbnail
and then i put it in our channel i was
like yup this is this is the stream uh
and good uh this is not the first time
she's telling me this but kuda was like
oh kiwama i really like your thumbnails
can you make mine and i'm like yeah
[Laughter]
it's not the first time she told me but
this is a normal normal thumbnail it's
not even that special like but sometimes
apparently yeah she really likes my
thumbnail oh yeah when i when i uh for
the dance collab when i showed her this
one
she was also like
i really like your thumbnails i'm like
it they're not like i didn't do much
i didn't do much
i mean there's some thumbnails where
where i would say yes okay they look
really good and i put some work into
those
hmm i don't know what it is my
thumbnails used to be pretty shitty
though
i think good ass thumbnails are fine
like they're simple but like there it
catches people's eyes like because her
her face is usually like really big on
the thumbnail and then the background is
blurred and then there is the logo the
game logo it's easy that's all you need
um
that's all you need really um
yes that's that's good as thumbnail
style that's what also why i told uh
cronie
i
a while ago a long time ago when i told
her that she should be bigger on stream
and bigger on her thumbnails
like actually constructive criticism i
also showed her as a as a example how
good a dessert from nails she's always
very big on their on her phone things it
catches the eye
you know when people are subscribed to a
lot of youtubers you're gonna have a lot
of different faces in your subscription
box so
um
sometimes sometimes it's it's uh
um it stands out more to have like a
really really simple thumbnail ina does
that often
where it's just like a scribble or
something
like that that will stand out a lot too
in an ocean of like really detailed
thumbnails
i think that's very good
sometimes in between
but did i say this before i remember
when i
uh in the very beginning when i joined
hello live um and i was having some
problems making thumbnails i also asked
you guys to make phone calls for me but
i remember
uh
the management someone in the management
i asked for advice and they were like
sending me martin senpai's thumbnails as
inspiration and they were like you
should you should basically plaster
the whole
uh screen of the thumbnail with fonts
and all that kind of stuff and i was
like yeah
that's how whole life japan does
thumbnails and i was trying to recreate
that but i felt like it was really
difficult
um
so nowadays i don't i don't try to
plaster too much [\h__\h] on my thumbnails
anymore
um
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i think it works for japanese style
thumbnails but for hours um
it's actually
yeah most of us are going with simple
thumbnails
um
it's interesting though i i really like
the japanese style thumbnails i feel
like with the japanese uh writing system
with kanji and hiragana and katakana um
you can actually
do
so much more in terms of graphic design
maybe that's just me but from what i see
from their thumbnails um
i feel like it really works well for
uh
you know creating something interesting
looking
mmm
that's mentioned it's so much texture
yeah uh let me look at
mine channel
they've been getting a little bit more
simple i guess
yeah but usually there's a lot of a lot
of font that takes up a lot of the
screen but hers also used to be more
even more
packed i feel like
oh but you know i love i love let me
show you
i love
with japanese letters i love
uh
shut up
i love that you can do stuff like this
like
i don't know i tried recreating that
with our writing system as well
it just doesn't work as well
as of japanese writing system
i don't know
i uh it's hard to explain i think you
need to try to make something yourself
in order to really understand
and then compare both japanese and
english
yeah but you have like a lot of cool
stylistic
um choices
with japanese letters
[Music]
thank you for i'm glad you guys
understand what i'm trying to say i
thought i thought you guys wouldn't
understand
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah mikko's thumbnails are
really good and uh yeah yeah yeah yeah
let me look at them
it's like i'm looking at art like i'm
i'm really interested in thumbnail
creation
facial yeah yeah yeah yeah mikko
senpai's thumbnails are a good um
[Music]
a good
good example
yeah there is always a lot of writing on
there
with big big really thick letters
yeah and they're all like kind of like
angled differently looks really cute and
dramatic
oh that's a good one oh yeah mikko
sanfire really makes great thumbnails um
[Music]
yeah yeah i know sometimes she makes
thumbnails for other people yeah yeah
yeah
really really good stuff i guess graphic
design is her passion
it is it is it to be her passion
um
thumbnail review stream
yeah
something we could do but probably um
a little bit boring
that's just something that's just
personal interests
trying to do something there all right
we need some bgm also my nose is so
itchy
my nose is so itchy
but and what i was trying to say is i
was really flattered by gouda saying she
likes my thumbnail so much like
sometimes i still think like [\h__\h] what
am i
what am i gonna do here it looks like
[\h__\h] i want it to look professional like
so often i'm trying to
make my um thumbnails
look professional
i i can make them look bubbly and all
that but making them look professional
when it's necessary is kind of
tough
what's this
ah okay let's do this one
[Music]
accept the compliments i did i was happy
about it
my nose cat hair why are you going to be
like that
nothing i think good eyes are perfectly
fine
[Music]
there are no bad thumbnails i mean
yeah i mean
[Music]
i had fun making the one from yesterday
though
it's always a bit difficult when there's
like so many people to put on a
thumbnail i still want their face to be
big
but yeah that was uh
six
six people on one thumbnail
it's a bit tough to coordinate but it
worked out well
sometimes i have issues with like
placing the logo but still keeping
everyone's face big
but not not having the logo cover up too
much of the faces
yeah difficult difficult anyway am i
correct with the assumption that we're
only gonna read the ones from yesterday
and today
i think we are done with the yakuza
super chats
okay
yeah okay
okay nice too shouldn't take too long
and i'm really looking forward to to uh
eating hilacy today i just wish i
wouldn't need to be the one who has to
cook it
i don't like working with a [\h__\h] ton of
oil you know like a whole bath of oil
i don't like to fry things too much
surprisingly
because i i always feel like it's a huge
waste of oil
yeah you need so much oil man
it's a waste of oil
and i don't cook much with meat either
most of the time
[Music]
yeah to clean up and then like what do i
do
it's been a long time since i've used
that much oil what do i do with all that
oil
i think
i think my mom once told me i can pour
it down the toilet but not down the
drain
i don't need it anymore
shouldn't should not pour it into the
sink
store it in a jar
i know you can reuse it but
not forever
not in the sink yeah
[Music]
i guess i gotta force myself to use it
again soon
[Music]
clock the pipes yeah
buy an air fryer
[Music]
always pour oil down and sink even i
know that you shouldn't do that
even i know that and i don't cook much
at all especially in olive oil so not
with that amount of oil
[Music]
i mean i would suggest airfryer
airfryer i don't even understand the
concept of an air fryer how does that
work
don't don't tell me it's okay that was a
reverse
question
okay
[Music]
super
it's the weekend
ready for some crispy spicy chicken fun
i don't know what's crispy and spicy
about it but it was a fun clown yeah
it was kind of the game was kind of
similar to guardian phone
um
but i guess it had the whole guessing
thing was already something else
and the matching thing in theory i guess
guardian film doesn't really have that
mode either
[Music]
like i like to
uh do new games
it when possible
for collabs it's not always the same
thing also for myself though when for
solo streams as well
so
but i gotta give the credits to inachan
for suggesting the game
if it was only four people
then we would have played something else
but then we ended up being so many yata
yutang
oh and and there will be that collab
that i talked about before soon um
the four people monopoly before live
indonesia
and amitang
and oven
and uh and and honor tony tony is coming
soon too i promise a promise
i promise
[Music]
and after i have that done if if no one
has like
started
working on it yet then i guess i'll
create a wrapped collab group as well
yeah thanks spanky time
cruise thank you optimus prime
flammable thank you i'm pretty late with
this but huge congrats for the
incredible concert performance central
thank you
got me a bit misty-eyed
may you just wait until i have my big
solo concert one day
one day
hmm
rick's fellaini
thank you for the red super chat
thank you thank you with the heart so
many hearts thank you
didn't you make it into the
game today
i saw someone with a name like yours not
exactly the same name but it might have
been you was it you
was it you
did you play mario kart with me
nice
it's probably you
thank you for joining
now thank you for the red super chat
come san nida
i had a vacation to watch streaming of
my ocean oh wait my vacation is
cancelled carefree is busy because of a
lot of customers o'neil arrested
[Music]
yes but the current network issue oh no
you got in but then you got kicked out
is that what you say oh no
[Music]
oh but don't worry about your vacation
being canceled you're happy about aren't
you
being with healthy
being with kiara
as your job isn't that beautiful
why would you want a vacation
yeah
i mean
unless you mean like real life vacation
was canceled that sucks
because that would be more time to watch
me
that would suck
yeah yeah yeah can we go on a company
vacation oh
i'll take you if if uh if we have decent
enough internet i'll take you guys to
the maldives
and i'll stream from the maldives a
little bit just a little bit
and then you're basically in the
maldives yeah
[Music]
yeah
i'll try i'll give it a try i'll bring
my laptop for sure
what does vacation mean
pain
[Music]
yeah the mold is i'm going to the
maldives with raining
yeah
i'm so excited
[Music]
thank you
moody danke not your normal salary man
thank you and thank you
traveller dageshin looking for the top
duncation tricky snacks
[Music]
in america's biggest dankest spanking
oswald 1993 danke schuen hey cara
today's my birthday i would be happy if
you could say something well thank you
for the pinky first of all and second of
all happy birthday
congratulations a welcome new member
welcome thank you oswell for being part
of kfb i wish you all the best
uh one day too late but still happy
birthday
apparently i am timothaku
[Music]
this is a great collab thanks for
organizing this no problem
no problem
i need my
honestly as it's just nice to also have
some uh collabs with the girls
so
yeah i had fun
[Music]
and also i'm glad that um i was able to
collab with sana because sana hasn't
been around much and
therefore i also didn't have much time
with chances to to do stuff with her
yeah i'm happy to see her around again
she's so sweet she's such a
positive
ball of
cuteness
and positivity
yeah i'm glad she joined even though it
was a really shitty time i didn't expect
her to join but she was really motivated
[Music]
yay
cyrux
the gamer creed
sky dance
[Music]
thank you guys
now i'll be reading the ones from today
[Music]
very good very good
very good that was speed
yeah
i was doing gas gas gas
[Music]
you're just reminding me i gotta pick up
something from the post office can you
guys
tweet at me tomorrow that i gotta pick
up something from the post office
please
tweet it at me please
maybe around
[Music]
i don't know noon time
please and then from a reminder not
everyone has a tweet at the time maybe
number one at like i don't know at 2pm
my time
just spread it out for the day
thank you
motion packaging
oh you finished after your server too
it really changed my experience with
these games now when i say a non-english
item name i always go oh i must be
german yeah yeah
they've been using a lot of german in
those games not only for items but also
for character names it's really funny
[Music]
but like
german but still
like like names that we wouldn't really
normally have though in germany and
austria
it's just like german sounding
we're kind of awkward
okay
[Music]
yeah
i saw the feathers update yeah yeah yeah
i at least with oak proud i feel like um
i'm able to
point it out i just feel like if there's
no feathers in the art i don't want to
use it
because it's not me could just be any
random orange haired anime girl um
sometimes i see other people drawing me
without my feathers and i'm like that's
not me you put that in my arts of ashes
hashtag but that's not me i could point
it out
that you basically ruined a perfect
piece of art by not putting in my
feathers but i usually don't point it
out because yeah i don't wanna i don't
want
i don't know i don't wanna be so direct
when like i don't know it feels like
um
uh i feel like
what what is my fault behind it i'm not
sure
[Music]
i don't want to say anything like i'm so
happy about the cute art but i'm
probably not gonna use it because my
feathers are not in it
no i'm still i'm still really happy
about the art but like my feathers are
like such an important feature
um i could i could just yeah and they
put the effort in so
i don't know i don't wanna
i wanna be like hey thank you very much
but you forgot my feathers like that's
just like unnecessary
[Music]
um thank you thank you for drawing that
but you forgot my feathers
could you please redraw it no i i
that's like such a weird request
but for old brands i just hinted at it
and oprah was like okay okay okay okay
okay
so sorry piano
it's because i want to use that i'd play
a
thumbnail for the maldives
stream
if i do one
[Laughter]
[Music]
i know it's fixed now
yeah i was pretty tired yeah
yeah but i didn't ask them to redraw it
i just said
but you're missing my feathers
[Music]
i didn't ask them to remake it but but
they took the hint
[Music]
feather is doco
heavily implied
[Music]
anyway
stephen adams thank you oh and i saw
that reminder hmm
remind me again soon
[Music]
oh damn around
cruz i'm concerned the game recruit
i don't even know like i'm fine with
maybe doing a horror game but i'm not
sure which one i should do like it
should be a short one
i've seen a lot of people play that that
barista japanese barista
horror game
um how scary is that
is that very scary
no ring finger no no no no yeah the
closing shift
it's deeply unsettling
not scary oh
closing shift is scary
iris survived it
not that scary okay
[Music]
i want something that's not too crazy
scary
not as bad as outlets
it's all jump scares oh dear
but at least there's no wait are there
zombies maybe there are zombie customers
[Music]
are there zombies in the closing shift
i guess horror games mostly have dummies
oh it's realistic
no zombies
oh
okay
[Music]
maybe i'll just
just a little bit sneak into
one of the girls who played it recently
in their archives just take a small look
at it for a few seconds
maybe i'll play that one
[Music]
psychological horror over
there can get you get jumpscared in
pokemon i don't know i don't dare any
horror that once came
but but i was doing pretty well at the
end of the outlast stream when i got
used to it and calmed down
i was doing pretty fun
[Music]
i wouldn't say i got jump scared by
sound effects i just got a little bit
surprised okay
just a little bit
shaken
just continue outlet no i don't wanna
it's stupid it's stressful it's really
stressful
running away from
[\h__\h]
weirdos
[Music]
i don't want to go back to that
oh thank you guys thank you for the
membership
welcome
[Music]
friday nights at freddy's i really don't
know what that game is like i can't even
imagine
like
the cover of it
oh
oh well i'll look into it uh
sophie no wait
thanks spanking home thank you for the
rest of the chat thank you soon
uh
offering to the cursed gods please go
back to sleep
as a big and small cat that are hovering
waiting for cards to bat at ah
really do they like looking at the
screen when mario kart is on
my cats or like smoothie at least only
is interested in the tv screen if there
is family guy on the screen i think she
only really recognizes cartoons
uh very simplistic cartoons
then she looks at the screen but
everything else she doesn't even like
recognize it as something going on
yeah no it's interesting
yeah maybe it's the colors i don't know
i'm not sure what it is
[Music]
based cat
this movie is a family guy fan
[Music]
black ops should i watch
long uh
wait are they broadcasting that anywhere
where i could watch it like
legally
[Music]
i think like months ago we talked about
it did they say it was adapted by
netflix where
like it was that somewhere wasn't it
disney plaza later than japan yeah yeah
it was disney plus
do we know how much later
because we can wait for that i guess i
guess i already have this new plus so
good for me
[Music]
it didn't say okay let's wait a little
bit
why did disney get the rise of black
washer yeah it's a weird choice
kind of a weird choice but okay
[Music]
um
would it be on disney plus and outside
of japan that is a double good question
i don't know um
oh well um for now for now we're not
doing it let's see if uh it looks more
possible later on
ah
thank you spanky time wow
i wish the best for your cats yeah
zombie darker sun for the pinky so
attention and movement sing together
would that make them very clever now
i also like congrats on the 3d i got my
camera mug on the day of your concert it
was fate
mug oh do you mean uh
the
wait what on our anniversary was it half
year one year
half year right was it half here no what
where does the black
cups it's not a mug it's a cup
the plastic cups yeah
i don't have them yet
but they look cool did they arrive i saw
some people were receiving them they
they come in a nice box
[Music]
wait they're ceramic they're not plastic
they look like plastic
oh
another whole dog they look like plastic
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
they look like plastic to me i thought
it was like plastic cups
oh okay
okay then don't drop them don't drop
them
[Music]
i see
i'm tired
they've got way to them huh okay
cannot play beer pong with them then
okay
don't they give you any no no usually i
receive my merch too um it might even be
in the package that i have to pick up
there's a package from
the company that i have to pick up but i
don't know what's inside it's probably
those things because it arrived around
the same time when you guys were
starting to get
your uh mugs cups whatever
it's probably that
[Music]
i hope so
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
you have a weakness for features with
broken english is that why you like me
my my english isn't that broken
i just sometimes don't know the right
vocabulary
but
but but
[Music]
what is it about
hawaii uh
you say cute things like biome in hawaii
[Music]
in german we would say uh
hawaii which is really similar but
do you not pronounce it like that
[Music]
hawaii
hawaii or
oh
hawaii hawaii
[Music]
okay so this is not hawaii
wait but she could have said hawaii too
[Music]
okay i probably said it differently
because of the german way to say it
[Music]
whatever
mystic has been kissing
oh my god horse funds
are fantastic
game of thrones
[Music]
no i probably can't even change it if i
wanted to i'm too used to it
it's such a tiny difference i don't even
care about it
nah
crayons are tasty
[Music]
it says this is for the sugar mommy
budget
oh man
[Music]
you know when she when she looks at me
with these eyes and says mommy
thank you
please give me
violin and horse please thank you
then i cannot say no
[Music]
i'll be so damned
you were the one promising the moon i
didn't promise to lose but i would
probably have to give it to her if she
asked for it
[Music]
as a mom your job is on ironically to
say no
um
but i don't want her to cry
[Music]
no
let me check my dm's did i get a dm from
her no i didn't
no i didn't
she's helping
[Music]
i'll damn her
[Laughter]
he's probably sleeping
[Music]
oh god i i need to be a cool senpai if
i'm too much like this she won't think
i'm cool i don't i need to be more tsun
sun
i need to be more like cold and distant
yeah
i need to be like oh you're pretty cute
welcome to hololens
yeah right now i'm just
i'm just too hyped
[Music]
ah sana i can steal sama's name yeah
yeah yeah yeah
good idea
you probably notice it though
thank you
[Music]
maybe late to say but managed to catch
link your wish months ago i super
chatted saying i wanted to crack a uo
for you on stage someday and i finally
did
first one and two for her life
psychology
[Music]
does this imply this
person was at the concert and cracked a
uo
because in japanese it also says
it was a long travel but that could just
mean
my travel from debut to now or so
um
it could be both
they mean those really strong orange pen
lights ultimate orange or something like
that the ones that are banned
yeah your journey
my journey yeah i'm not sure it could be
even that they just did it at home or
they were actually there
in any case thank you
if you were there let me know because
that's cool
then maybe you're the one in the middle
with the super glowy orange pen lights
that would be quite the coincidence that
the the one crazy person with the
super bright orange pen lights in the
very middle of the audience
is a fan of mine who promises me to
bring to do it months ago
[Music]
that would mean not that you live in
japan though but they um donate in us
dollars so that's kind of confusing to
me
maybe
could be him could also be just any
random guys
[Music]
crucial storm xyz
domino duncan happy birthday
[Music]
new york isn't isn't scary i promise
lots of fun stuff oh i'm sure there's
lots of fun stuff but it's kind of
intimidating i don't know
wait let me look something up
tokyo um
[Music]
tokyo has
9.74 million
people living there in 2020
nine almost 10 million okay new york
has
8.4 is actually less than
tokyo and tokyo usually
[Music]
which country has which city has more
tourists i wonder in general
probably right now new york has more
because you can't even go to tokyo as a
as a
tourist
[Music]
does new york city have less people
in general living and tourists okay well
i guess that's
actually a bit better than tokyo and i'm
used to tokyo
i thought new york would be even worse
in terms of people
oh
okay the most popular city in the world
yeah because they got [\h__\h] tiny
apartments to squeeze everybody into
dangerous in the trends ah pickpocketing
oh i learned that from friends don't
worry
friends taught me to be careful in new
york about pickpocketing i think it was
friends
or or it was
or it was seinfeld i don't know maybe
both actually both probably both
[Music]
mama
don't worry i won't be taking public
transport i'll only be ubering
seinfeld was definitely in new york city
yeah
[Music]
no no i meant the show friends i'm
re-watching i started re-watching it
right now again by the way
intent there's a nintendo store in new
york city
[Music]
but yeah i guess it's really scary even
when your bag is closed some people just
steal them right the whole bag and just
run away with that holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
that would be so oh my god that would be
so [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
how do i
how do you
is there any any way of like
um protecting yourself from that
[Music]
like not looking like a tourist for
example
but even non-terrorists get robbed right
just don't carry anything
that's important with you but it's gotta
carry some money with you
don't stand out i need to look more
dangerous i probably look too
too easily robbable
[Music]
i gotta i gotta get buff and big
which means i'll be getting muscles and
and fat
just to go to new york city
so that i can tackle whoever is trying
to rob me
and and i won't even get robbed in the
first place because i just look too
strong
yeah
that is probably the only way to do it
or i guess
yeah rabbit on the back rather than or i
mean can take it back but just don't put
money in there i guess i could just put
like stuff into the like an inside
pocket of a jacket
yeah that would work
or if it's summertime and i don't have a
jacket then just put it in my in in
my uh pants um
uh pocket
you can't really
you can't really like easily just swoop
in there and take out whatever is in
there
[Music]
or in my bra
i think some girls put some stuff in
their bra
i've heard about it before
bruh
bails always talks about her bras
even though she doesn't need them that
much she's pretty flat
just kidding she does it's just not
actually that flat
just just looks like it from the front
but it's not stunted flat
oh snap
snap she always says bro
maybe she wants to go brat shopping with
me
for senpai's
[Music]
pretty pretty standard practice for
christmas ah
i guess so yeah yeah yeah when people go
party when girls go party they put like
stuff in their bra
bro
shopping
[Music]
yes in the desert phoenix arizona
doesn't really seem very desirable
[Music]
head to new pulse or lake george not as
crowded as new york city and so pretty
if you want to go to the beach go to
fire island
is that also in new york city
yes it's in new york city
it's a thin flat atlantic ocean barrier
island off the southern shore of long
island new york it's known for protected
beaches
oh they're protected interspersed with
seasonal resort communities on the
western tip rubber blah blah blah blah
it's the only area of the island
accessible car
i was in uh on a like a basically
protected beach uh during my time in
greece they're usually like way way way
way more pretty and beautiful because
you're not supposed to like leave
anything there or like you can't buy
stuff on the island so there's no waste
you gotta bring your own stuff that was
it you can't buy things there you gotta
bring your own stuff and you can't throw
it away anywhere
you're supposed to bring it back i don't
know if it's the same in the fire island
but that's how they did it in greece in
that protected island
it was really really really really
really beautiful
it looked really like nature like like
yeah
protected
yeah the photo that i'm looking at i see
some beach homes
[Music]
looks expensive to live there
now the beach looks nice though
[Music]
oh my god prime video fire island season
one
what
is
this this looks like
uh what's colgan
when you look on fire island it shows
you this prime video show
with one two three four five six guys
uh topless
in the water one with a dog one has a
dog a cute dog
and all of them have a six pack
it's a show
[Music]
the model of the show is this fire
island and then boys just wanna have sun
[Music]
get it boys just wanna have fun boys
just wanna have sun that's why they're
on the beach
[Music]
oh my god
this must be a top-notch quality tv show
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway
not lou thank you for the red super chat
wow my great uncle had a horse and a
mule in mexico never saw him ride them
though they just pulled a cart
horse and a mule
hold on
uh-huh
[Music]
and thank you for the fun stream key
well we're proud of you for sticking
with elden ring for as long as you did i
knew you could do it i was just worried
it wouldn't stress you out a lot and i
didn't want you to leave it feeling like
you didn't belong or shouldn't try this
game oh thank you
there is a reason that i
uh don't really want to say
why i
um
[Music]
i don't even explain it
uh
why it's a bit difficult for me to come
back to it immediately but i didn't
completely cancel it um
[Music]
there is always a chance for more but
yeah the chances are not very high
i guess because i'll probably get
occupied with other games
soon
no no not the backseating not something
completely different but i mean the
backseating is very annoying indeed it's
like for eldon ring
i said this to lena in a tweet because
relayna was talking about like losing
her mind about backseating in elder ring
and i said don't worry about it
it's not you it's just like really alden
ring brings out the worst in people
um the audience and the person who
streams it because
there's like
[Music]
for for beginners
we have to look at the chat because we
look for help and stuff and and tips and
advice and all that but then
oh there's no choice but to look at the
back seating and it's like insane for
ellen ring it's like oh the worst i've
ever seen i've seen other people other a
lot of other streamers complain about it
and
yeah for beginners it's
it's just
very shocking
[Music]
no i said
i said i like backseating in general
like i when i ask for it i'm fine with
it and all that but i also said that for
eldon ring it's too much it's too much
and unnecessary
yeah stop rolling stop rolling yeah use
your shoe
use lr use l r kiwa
oh
there's no reason to spam it a million
times
[Music]
it's so obnoxious
yeah but um
yeah it's still still a good game and uh
i have i have my fun while playing it
there were some good moments where i
felt
like
it was actually a little bit rewarding
after killing certain
bosses or whatever certain mobs
[Music]
there were some good moments
so it wasn't a completely horrible
experience i can tell you that
i wish there was an easy mode though so
that i can just enjoy the story and all
that and that
i know i know for people who like sell
souls games they're probably pissed off
when someone says that
[Music]
but you don't even if there was an easy
mode you don't have to play it you don't
have to use it
[Music]
just make it a bit
um more
open for beginners you know
would be i think not the worst decision
uh
but yeah
it's probably not gonna happen because
the makers of these games probably just
want people to suffer as much as
possible
and making an easy mode would um destroy
the whole concept of making people
suffer
yeah
but i want to know the story like i'm
actually really curious about it but
maybe i should just watch someone else
who's good at it play it
[Music]
maybe i should just watch noida sam if
she's planning to finish the whole game
which she probably will i i imagine she
would
and she's pretty decent at it too i
think
[Music]
anyway
thank you
thank you for the pinkie thank you for
the streams this week boss i started
playing room 535 and i made a monster
bar named kfp it is full of chickens i
saw on an irish stream stream that no
permissions for rfo but i'm enjoying it
controlling a little step
yeah didn't that come out very recently
it looks interesting who who is the
publisher
exceed games uh-huh
mixtape games
looks cute i want to try it
come out friday in your room
exceed games what what what else did
they publish
it sounds so familiar to me
ah
they published sakura
apparently
really
[Music]
mark wasn't that marvelous
and what else what else what else did i
know
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
um
just because we can't play it now
doesn't mean that we can't play it in
the future there might be a chance
[Music]
ah trails of cold steel
harvest moon
[Music]
yeah the origin of emperor that's true
sakura is the origin of am frog yeah
yeah yeah yeah
orlando is lovely as long as you stay in
the um tourist areas
oh i don't know i probably would yes
but i kind of want to go to places where
i know someone or where someone that i
know will join me to go to because i
don't want to go alone for america
maybe maybe some
ian girl
wants to go city hopping with me city
hobby let's go
thank you doc joseph enjoy enjoy gaming
alex duncan
[Music]
is that a joke
holmes had recently taken up gardening
as a hobby and have brought a small tree
home watson asked what type it was to
which sherlock replied why it's a lemon
tree my dear watson
is that a joke
[Music]
it's elementary
i didn't hear that at all
where did that come from ginger ranger
where did that come from did i ask for a
joke
did i ask you excuse me did i ask you
for a joke was a good one
black friday
and
[Music]
just play mage
yeah i guess that's easy i heard about
it all right
thank you everybody for watching today i
gotta make food now
i'm not very motivated to do it anymore
but i gotta do it i gotta do it my my
meat is about to expire today i'm gonna
do it
uh
it's not difficult i made schnitzel
before i can make tonkatsu as well
it's not difficult
[Music]
thank you guys for watching today have a
nice evening and um don't you dare order
food again
um
okay
[Music]
i will try
uh yeah
[Music]
food is at the end yeah really yummy
tonkatsu i have tonkatsu sauce from
japan
uh
genma gave me some stock the last time
we met and i still haven't used it so
it's almost been a year since i've
received
the
yeah some some of the things that she
brought to me
from japan
and gave it to me in germany
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
unfortunately we did not see all of the
new tracks i think but a couple of them
a couple of them
yeah
let's wait until the next wave comes out
[Music]
we only missed one one track yeah that's
possible
[Music]
okay
thank you guys for watching
have a nice day have a nice weekend
uh i'm hungry
i'm hungry
thank you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
bye
[Music]
sexy ending let's go
do
[Music]
you