[Music]
la
a
[Music]
la
now you
unmuted hello good morning good
[Music]
afternoon
k
k hello it's takoon again the best sales
team of whole life
English we're really like we selling so
much to S
me well I mean we are but um you know
we're going to make it as as as personal
as possible right we are great homework
doers yeah Kik welcome guys thank you
for showing up at this interesting
stream time very late
evening I believe yeah maybe kind of
yeah don't worry if it's like a really
late bad time for you guys the stream
won't be too long um
yeah we'll start off of a little bit of
a chitchat right chitchat we don't have
to rush into it yeah let's chill we the
last week or so has been that's just
like a
hurricane just mhm for real I feel that
same way like today we have the
hurricane too actually yeah today is
like the first day in a while where I
mean I don't have the day off but it
feels a little bit more relaxed yeah
hold on I'm going to go outside I'm
going to get a
massage are you jealous reminds me of
yesterday yeah yeah I got did you get it
too though because I noticed it was a
message to like me and my channel but I
think everybody got it possibly um yeah
yeah I think everyone did
too there was a spelling mistake when
Stephon sent us the message and this is
a test message we are going to send you
a message they like a massage I was like
wow free massage I thought it was I
thought it was like a one time only
mistake but they repeated the mistake
and the next time they wrote message
they also wrote this is a massage we
will send you more massages from now
on massages now let's go let's go
massages well that inspired me I thought
you were joking cuz like or like like
cuz um in studio yesterday and then K
was talking about getting a massage and
then she was talking about getting a
message with instead of message it was a
massage I was like oh is that from the
massage place cuz if they did that's
pretty smart you know kind of like a
hello I I was talking with my dance
teacher the other day about how I really
need a massage and she told me that a
certain idle company um in their like
wherever they are I guess they always
have a massage therapist coming with
them and they can have free massages
whenever they want and I'm like
yeah she was like why don't you guys
should have that well don't you have
that I'm like no we don't have that but
we should have
it
please massage therapist uh in the
studio for us cute cute Idols please
that would be nice cuz a lot of the
times when we're in the studio and we
like we do rehearsals and stuff like
we're there
for at least 8
hours and you have to think about how
our lifestyle is like sitting slouched
crouched slouched slouched in front of
yeah in front of our PCS all the time
you know we're not I used to sitting in
like a normal I mean maybe some I wonder
is your posture good Ena I mean I do get
told that I have kind of like slight
slouching but like I've never had back
problems before so like terrible you
never had back oh my God you know I
don't want to talk to you anymore
I've had back problems for like I don't
know seemingly my whole life man oh man
oh okay it's my sitting posture is
pretty good but I think it's like my
drawing posture cuz of my tablet I like
have to hunt over a little bit like for
hours yeah and your head like looks down
right a little bit Yeah I think my neck
gets a little stiff but yeah well
wouldn't it be nice Yago petition to uh
give us massage
purpose another thing I wanted to say
before we get into this you guys maybe
saw on Twitter yesterday
but I I tonight last night I slept with
a ghost plushy a certain ghost plushy
Ena got it for me I did you
did you know was funny walking into the
the studio yesterday you had so much
stuff with you usually people just walk
in you know with like very minimum stuff
I don't really need much in the studio
but I walked in with my hands full of
giant plushies cuz I I got one for my
man you got you got a lot of things for
your manager
seemingly so I had I had one for my Mon
and one for and I was just walking in
with these like giant crane game you
know bags yeah so cute though yeah
you're so cute it was cute cuz like when
we were you know going back and forth
like doing rehearsal and then to the
real street I saw my M Chan like hugging
the doll and like looking at her
laptop I was
like thank you Ena she got mine in two
tries yo two tries lucky I have I have
another penguin I got like another time
I went I got that in like one try I was
just like what just happened oh oh she
also got me she also got me this um you
know a certain fruit uh games uh like
thing but I thought like from you know I
posted a picture I think and it I
thought it's uh like squishy like a duck
like a squishy duck but no it's not
squishy at all it's really hard so I
don't know what it's for and how you use
it I don't know I think it's just for
the decoration I I was pretty sure like
in another crane game place I went to
like they had small plushies of them but
I couldn't find them in the all the
crane games I went to when I was getting
it for you so was that was the only only
fruit stacking game oh well you found it
I
saw thank
you you're so good if I find something
again that I need I'll let you
know but now I don't know how to bring
the ghost back home because it's pretty
big uh I mean you can try get like one
of those like vacuum seal bags if you
want like put it like wait wait vacuum
the ghost
exactly just like in game we
playing but in a different way not ena's
voice a bit soft you know that's that's
ena's voice but I I can raise it a bit
more that it's just me if if it was not
soft then it would not be me
exactly I raised you a bit more there we
go okay okay now I can scream into their
ears and make it play
no no no no no no let's not do that
let's what screaming speaking of
screaming into your
ears let's get could it be it has
something to do with while we're
streaming today yeah we have a little
you know announcement announcement not
announcement you already know about it
but we currently have
the reservations or so open for our yeah
the the pre-orders for our avot X myth
collaboration
earbuds no way m have you guys seen it
already have you guys been aware of it I
if they already seen it I could arrange
a forgetti beam oh if that's required
okay can you do it once so that
everything we say will sound new okay I
don't have Reverb on here so you're
going to have to pretend that is a
Reverb yeah Bo get the be
[Music]
be oh wait wait it worked on me too what
are we doing here righta did you hear
that myth is having a
with
Avon for
wireless who's myth
earon who are you who am I I don't know
am where am I oh no what have you
done too powerful sorry I forgot to
crack it down a little bit okay I I'll
just read off the script then what
script we don't have a script no it's
okay to have a script you know it's okay
this is a very natural homework stream
with no scripts
involved okay okay so uh well okay um I
guess we'll we'll go to slide
seven we have slid yeah slide sliding
down what slides are you
talking okay okay only I have slides
that's okay okay so no I'm kidding I do
have the SL but do you want to read the
the the first
thing
um
introduction uh yeah okay read
go so avat AKA I it's called proceed
right proed proceed
Japan comprehensive Electronics
manufacturer based in
Japan under the slogan something that
changes your life they handle the
Planning Development sales and marketing
of their own Brands oh yeah it's not
showing on the screen on purpose guys
we're not showing you it's it's all meem
it's all from my brain I memorized it
okay what do you mean the and the
collaboration partner
amot is an original brand of pred Japan
that was established in 2018 wow
baby as the brand of a Japanese
manufacturer it strives to provide
wireless earbuds with high s SSH sound
quality and delicate and beautiful
design M the name OT originally stood
for audio visual and interest or
Internet of Things sorry I I read that
as interest I mean I mean I remembered
it as interest internet of things but in
2023 it was reinterpreted as a Visionary
Innovation on technology so if you take
the capital of all those words it
becomes Avant wow oh yeah I think that
was a good choice to reinterpret it
because AV standing for audio visual
Internet of Things sounds funny
internet of it now covers a wide range
of projects beyond the realm of audio
visual
product yeah a Visionary Innovation
we're in
innovating innovating Innovation
Innovation yes yes yes you guys maybe
already saw some pictures it is
definitely very delicate and beautiful
uh I think we'll start by showing you
the the
product let's get rid of this beautiful
key visual we'll take a closer look at
it again in a moment um I'm actually
going
to show you special voice lines yeah
yeah over 200 newly recorded no don't
look at that yet I think first we show
um yeah the the product design shall
we I'll show you the case so
actually you know you know we can go
with this okay okay so first of all as
you may have guessed there is special
voice lines of all of us yeah included
in the earbuds yeah over 200 over 200
that's if you do your math because well
we don't we didn't all take 200 each um
yeah it's a combination of all five of
us so you divide that by five and you
get yeah yeah yeah good math but 200
that's pretty good yeah yeah yeah so all
of us are in there and uh we'll we'll
teach you everything about how to use it
and when it's turned off when it's
turned on and this and that and some
original voice lines right Ina mhm what
kind of voice lines did you take special
ones special ones well there's like a on
the website guys if you go in the
description there's a link to that leads
you to the website uh and on there you
see like you know what lines we took you
can actually see it oh the site is down
right now
okay well live whole life detoxing
websites we are talking about definitely
not a first yeah we're too powerful I
suppose but sorry Avon you you can check
it out later or maybe you already
checked it out um I think some of you
guys checked it out already there's a
list of like lines that we did and we
gave it our own little you know special
touch didn't WEA I saw like yours
there's lots of like taco taco t time
Taco
Taco I love saying taco taco t Tac T
yeah it's so fun to say yeah I have to
say one of the special things about this
is that you buy
one one earbuds and you get everyone's
voice yeah you can choose yes pick and
choose you you can just be like you know
I kind of feel like Kara
and then you just choose K's voice when
you go out or you know you're listening
to stuff or like you know what you'll be
like man I need to come down today I'll
go for ena's voice ex exactly yeah
that's that's how you can choose
anything there's an application where
you can switch between our voices really
easy really simple so let's look at this
next
thing all of English myth included more
than 200 voice lines newly recorded by
the celebrities of whole life English
myth we're celebrities we're
celebrities what and they're available
in Japanese and
English Y how was the Japanese for
you oh boyy oh
boyy this is also something you can
double check
yeah Yago will be so proud of
us so here you can take a little look at
the design it's the myth logo which is
really cool isn't it it's so cool I
think it's kind of hard to tell on this
image itself but like the gold part it's
like actually really shiny M mhm looks
very
like classy like elegant yes very
elegant people won't immediately know
that you you like to watch anime girls
in your free
time unless they know if they know they
know if if they know they know they'll
be like wait are those the whole life
English MTH collab with amot here mon
damn you got those let's go I got those
too who are you listening to who's your
current cele Li in your ear oh mine is
Takashi Kiara right now yeah oh oh mine
is oh my goodness good good taste well
thank you so yeah uh the charging case
and earbuds feature special whole life
English myth designs the golden whole
life English myth logo on the pure black
surface gives the product a luxurious
look it's very simple but stylish so
it's great for everyday use guys so use
it every day and yeah they're Wireless
obviously as you can see which is great
I love wireless earphones pretty sure
you can charge them with the USBC which
is good oh oh yes yes very very nice
okay um oh yeah uh I will show you guys
the package design I think the package
design is not in this slide so I have it
separately the packaging looks so cool
okay
ta yes you can also see it on the
website guys but here I'll make it
bigger for you cute with our
illustrations so fancy
mhm yeah man miss Lo makes us look so
cool yeah I think so too we are cool Ina
we are yeah oh I'm cool have
confidence
okay confidence yeah don't nowhere
M Okay so yeah yeah yeah and this is the
Box closed and then we have the Box open
with the colored versions of the
illustrations wow you can open it like a
little book and then take out your fancy
new premium looking
earbuds yes yes so cool they are so cool
so uh I see some people asking in the
chat I mean we're going to get to this
again but uh link is in the description
and yes you can get on Amazon uh it's it
should be you know uh not uh down
anymore so yeah I think when they first
announced it the uh Amazon site was down
but it's it's up now it's up now yeah so
go go pre-order pre-order it's on Amazon
us as well uh so go find your way to
it and I think that's that for now let
let's look at the
illustrations Che this out really
quickly
what I don't know oh wait there's there
we got to talk about different mode yeah
of the specific um the special tuning
mhm you want to give us a little
explanation about it what so hi
rain what wa wa my
wait is excited about that
okay well wait that will only work if
like one of myth is
Yosi I'm Yosi
right okay tell me about the tuning Ina
okay well so with this specific uh model
that the uh your brother based on you
can change between different
mes so you you know this model includes
a streaming mode which enhances voice
Clarity so if you're using this to watch
you know perhaps uh takanashi K or n
inter
streams outside you'll be able to hear
you know our voices a little more
cleanly that's cool yeah and it also has
a different mode for you know maximum
music streaming so oh you get that
different modes and you can change
between these in the app that you can
connect the earbuds with that's so cool
yeah nice they F about the fact that the
people who will buy these watch a lot of
streams but also listen to music you
know and want to have maybe different
kind of priorities when they watch our
streams and want to hear us more clearly
wow they consider what we need thank
you I was very happy when I saw that
this had like the different mode I was
like yeah they actually took into
consideration what kind of thing we do
yeah yeah yeah BBE consider it they they
read the air cookie
cookie they they read the cookies the
cookies no the
cookies the cookies the cookies well if
you got some cookies you know the
Takashi are always waiting for them
don't don't hide them read the cookies
cookies okay I don't think we're good at
reading cookies cuz we just eat
well I already I already showed the box
so let's look at the
[Music]
illustrations so for this project for
this collaboration there uh have there
have been created a completely new
original illustrations created
specifically for his collaboration I
already said that so we start with am
yeah so cute oh my God I love this
one
I the sweater looks so comfy and I love
her buns on ha I'm buns man those buns
like even the details down to her shoes
they're so fluffy and cute that bubble
bag I need it I love the pastel Vibe and
and she's she's just you know she's just
Amy she's so cute if you look closely
she's wearing the earbuds yeah we're all
wearing them uh mostly in our ears
partially in our hands or somewhere else
I don't know most in our ears so take a
look at that look at our ears very cute
ear fetish let's go what what next this
beautiful woman she looks so cool oh my
God a she's so cool Ka
P but also very feminine at the same
time I like it oh really goes well with
her earrings and stuff too absolutely
can we get a look do you see that your
butts guys you see him there's also one
in her hand oh amazing wa okay beautiful
I like the bag I love her what do you
call them pigtails
mhm she so cute she's so cute I don't
know what can we make her sit on us here
she's sitting on
us you're not happy with that Ina would
you want her to sit on
us was to do that on the
stream this is why you don't give
control we're doing homework K yeah but
she like otherwise she's just sitting on
air and that's really rough I think
that's really difficult for your muscles
no you don't see the spirits she's
sitting on no what what oh maybe you
don't see it don't worry about it okay
all right
next she's on roller
skates do you think she can roller skate
I mean she has uh
it's maybe that's why she has all those
bandages cuz falling down yeah this is
so
cute again very pastel really cute I
feel like her tail got a little bit
smaller also cute yeah oh so cute is
with her actually is this a
know
right
cute I really like these
illustrations I love the
I was like lowkey thinking of changing
my my Twitter profile picture to one of
these I mean you
could so cute yeah so she also has them
in your in her ear did you see guys you
see
them perceive the earphones earbuds oh
her small Hood too is so
cute cute goba all right
next is it you is that you
cute oh my God so I think all of our
first reaction was why is she wearing
amma's jacket I did not steal am jaet I
did not but it suits you really
well damn you look like a girl in a
library but like a really cute one oh my
God I don't usually look like a girl in
the library
m i mean you do carry a book around but
I feel like that's a different kind of
Library
there that's not in a normal Library
this with this one you look more like a
girl in a normal Library usually you
look like you're in some weird mythical
Library yeah I like how like the ribbon
is like not like a normal CL it's like
one of those like kind of trans
translucent you have them on your shoes
too yeah so cute oh they J me so cute
it's kind of preppy but still cute and
Casual very cute I love I would wear
this outfit I would totally wear it too
cute oh man and and as you can see uh
enan is modeling their the ear buds for
us in special shaped uh ears so if
you're also all kinds of if you're also
one of those people who have uh elf
shaped ears um you'll be fine you will
be fine you can use them as well it just
fits it just works if it fits it sits in
your
ear what a relief yeah you guys are
reliefed now are your ears weird don't
worry we got you don't worry it fits in
the taco flaps too oh
really Dam okay tacos you can try it out
go get him all right last but not least
wow so cool I got this like those shoes
like literally the same one you wore
yesterday no not the same but I was also
thinking like simar very
similar but yeah I'm kind of like
wearing like sweet sweet Street Wear and
like kind of bucket hat yeah bucket hat
it reminds me of like what all the
dancers that I meet uh like you look
like a really like dancing dance Queen
yeah street dancer outfit but it's also
like very elegant cuz there's like
Frills on the sleeves and stuff M looks
really flowy so good I want to wear this
lovely I want to wear it a little C and
breid yeah bucket hats actually so cute
I I admire people who like look good in
bucket hats I obviously look good in
bucket hat too right but honestly I've
never tried it before bucket hat you do
you do well I don't know I I I I I I
want to get a bucket hat but I when I I
think and bucket hat too really I feel
like I
don't maybe it's because I need to match
it with these kind of clothes and then
it will look
better right you got to like coordinate
like me which just wear T-shirt with
the yeah you're going for a different
style I'm going for the I'm going to the
convenient store
look it's a Vibe it's a whole vibe girl
so yeah that is all of the five
illustrtion you can see them on the
website as well of course and take
another closer look at them how I really
man I I want
like more with the illustrations it's
just so good right well Ena you might be
in luck because maybe maybe maybe there
will be maybe something else maybe with
this in the future with
de oh or so I've heard perhaps
I don't know much at all I just know
this there's I hope I hope it's good cuz
I'm I'm ready to
swipe
swipe swipe swipe right or
left for me up and down usually down oh
okay let's
go yes yes yes yes um
so let's see oh one more thing I want to
show you guys who here is going to anime
NYC who will I see at anime
NYC oh your
live oh oh oh yes okay there's a lot of
people going well there is so to you
guys I shall
[Music]
advertise aat has a boo or we'll have a
boo at anime NYC and look we're featured
on it pretty uh prominently is that how
you say it in know yeah we have the
Batters and I guess it looks it looks
like cutout of us yeah pretty big
ones so go check us out take a picture
with us and when you're at the booth you
can make pre-orders for the uh earbuds
right
there that's so cool yeah I do see other
posters that I will probably not mention
but you know you know me
yeah let's focus on the ours but yeah
we're like the biggest ones
yeah that's so cool and I I believe that
there's like a uh special thing you can
get if you show them your pre-order oh
thing do we know what it
is I think they said it on Twitter did
they say what was previously known as no
no ex previously to I still said can't
stop me what was it a art cart set yeah
art Card Set artart Card Set Beau so if
you guys already pre-ordered it and you
happen to go to enemy NYC make sure to
visit the avat
booth check it out do it do it guys do
it I'm guessing it's like this art which
is so cute so yeah you got to get it you
got to grab you one I just want to see
that art like big you
know me too me tooy I want to in can we
go in person and like sign
them oh mean that would that would not
be a question you ask me that's a
question you ask management okay
okay but any guys go there check it out
uh pay a a a a visit for us yeah yeah
we're waiting for you and what was
another thing I want to say
ah oh yeah so so so so H you may have
already seen it too but if you go to the
website there's a video from goba also
talking about all of this the whole
lineup and everything and explaining it
and it's really a flashy fancy cute
video from goody so check it out yeah
basically we talked about the same thing
um but you know you got to check us all
out so that we can brainwash you
successfully
what it's okay it's okay what it's okay
we weren't supposed to talk about that
but they already brainwash they don't
understand the word should I forget your
beam just in case okay okay do it
again for get
beam it hit me again wait I forgot to
turn down the the knob they're going to
forget about the stream we just
did well I also forgot what was I doing
here okay go back to side one starting
again
uh uh so this uh welcome everybody uh
we're we're talking about a actually
that reminds me um I part escaped how
did you first feel when we got this like
notification that we're doing
this like that's so cool yeah you got
caught off a little bit by Discord but
yeah that's so cool I said I said that
was so cool
yes yes yes it's exciting because I I
think this you know this is the first
official you know product uh in in in
terms of like earbuds in your ear where
you can hear a Us in it myth all this
yeah and like for me I'm really a fan of
like mercher collapse that we can like
use every day kind of things and I use
like like I when I go outside I like to
you know drown out the outside and
pretend I'm indoors by listening to
music stuff so you know just having me
voices in your head and then it's not a
bad thing it's not it's pretty good I
think yeah yeah yeah so uh I I think
this wasn't mentioned before but maybe
it's like pretty normal nowadays I don't
know but they are adaptive hybrid
adaptive noise cancelling earbuds and so
they reduce noise effectively very can
literally be like one of those movies
where like in in my head there's like a
you know the music and our voices going
on and I'm dancing around except if
everyone else sees me it's just like a
crazy person dancing down the road can I
yeah exactly
wow can't wait some you don't look crazy
to me
ever and so of course it supports high
sound quality with highrisk support and
here's the cool thing it offers up to 19
hours of playback uh extendable to 62
hours of the case so if you charge
everything once fully then you can just
the earbuds they go on for 19 hours and
if you put them back into the charging
case then they'll go on for 62 hours so
you can watch 62 hours of our streams
non-stop at least that's long long long
stream yeah it's really long also it
includes deep base and there's a a
certain waterproof rating I'm not sure
how waterproof that is but there a water
don't D it in water but maybe just a
little bit of liquid is okay
yeah maybe maybe yeah look it up be
careful before you dunk it in the in the
bathtub yeah
so with that I think we told everything
did I miss something you know I don't
think so we covered pretty much
everything no
M let me check m m foil stamped yeah
voice lines
200 um yeah
okay use it every day use it every day
yeah guys use these every day because we
want to be in your ears and entice you
see you at the anime NYC Booth perhaps
yeah
um yeah uh currently pre-order
so go check it out can't say much more
about that this just pre-order in the
description below yes check it out check
it out and
now we can like maybe do an outro
chitchat
Ina we can yeah I think so and let's do
an outro chitchat cuz you know I think
my kfp really hasn't seen much of me
these days so same actually yeah how's
your sleep schedule recently um it's
pretty normal here because I'm used to
waking up and sleeping at Japanese
hours that's crazy good I think I've
been sleeping pretty well because we had
so much stuffed in the last week yeah
yeah yeah so when I come home I'm just
like you I'm going to be productive and
get some homework done and then I'm just
like maybe a 30 minute nap and then I
wake up like 8 hours
later yeah nice I think yeah my viewers
don't I usually like to take a lot of
naps when I'm in Austria but um I only
did that like in the first two or three
days when I arrived and then you could
still like kind of blame it on jet lag
but after that yeah I've been like
consistently going to sleep between like
11:00 p.m. and 1:00 a.m. which is really
good and I've been waking up really
early and you know because every day is
busy every day like work and got to go
out there into the heat so the heat
makes me really tired and like drains
all my energy like you don't realize how
like exhausting it is being
outside until it really hits you I think
no so we've been so Normy last week
which is good it's unb I think it's a
good thing right it is I think but I'm
also super exhausted from it to be
honest same I mean the only time I
didn't feel exhausted at like like late
at night was when I when we had that
really long day mhm and then I was like
I feel like going to the crane games
after I'm surprised I was like so dead
you know how did you still feel like I'm
going to go to crane games and get a
million things for my friends but it was
it was like it was my motivation to last
through the day thank you so
[Music]
motivated yeah so um this hot weather
will continue and also in New York York
I
suppose I mean it's not too bad right
now this week at least it's in the low
30s well you mean New York or in in
Tokyo e really low low low 30A that is
still hot because it's so humid though
yeah but you know it's not like 35
plus it's not
bad like yesterday on the way back from
the studio I was like it's like 20 28 C
right now it's pretty
nice back home I'd be like 28 is pretty
pretty hot yeah yeah yeah yeah now you
get used to like having like 37 38
degrees and once you get down to 32
you're like oh thank God it's only 32
today no exactly not really though I'm
no I'm dying I'm M I know I'm a phoenix
but I'm melting
here well well well so anything else you
want to talk
about um not much I mean we still got a
couple of days until you know our first
world tour Stuff Plus The Kicking It
Dimensions everyone practicing a
lot I can't wait I can't wait for you
guys to see all the performances
honestly I was so genuinely shocked
yesterday we did the stream on the
official Channel if you guys saw it uh
it was in Japanese but I think it was
still worth watching even if you don't
understand Japanese but like we did like
Japanese listening practice yeah we did
like a little rehearsal going for the
script and everything and at the moment
when I read that you know the date of
breaking dimensions and I realized oh my
God it's Monday we're in the week of it
happening I screamed because I genuinely
was so
like
what yeah what oh my God it's it it
feels like it's been a million years
since our last um concert and I'm really
excited it feels like it was like
yesterday what it feels like it's been
just like we just did it and now it's
just like oh it's next week or it's this
week it's couple days there okay oh my
goodness but it's too long for me but
yeah this weekend and um obviously I
will not be streaming over the weekend
but I will put up a waiting room will
you put up a waiting room I should turn
my normal waiting room into like a
special one oh yeah yeah should or just
cuz I don't like just making a waiting
room and not streaming on
it I will do it and I'll probably I just
having one reading room and changing the
changing the visuals or something com up
yeah I'll put up a waiting room and then
when everything is over and and I'm like
chilling after the concert I will make a
I will make a little stream where I talk
about the stuff but for now I have one
more stream to tomorrow guys before I
spread my wings and fly away uh and I
leave on a Jet Plane Leaving on a Jet
Plane oh no traa going to fly mhm fly
away yes so I'm sorry guys I think both
me and Ena will be kind of quiet in
terms of
streams but we'll be back we'll be back
the busiest season is almost over no
thank God
until it starts back up again cuz it's
going to be our fourth year anniversary
yeah oh and uh don't forget to pre-order
the earbuds oh yeah just reminding you
what this stream is about check the even
if you don't order you know check out
the site look at the art link is in the
description think about it yeah sorry
guys that's pretty short I know um but
that's it for us today takori has uh you
know done their homework so we're really
really blessed and really happy to work
together with avat on this nice
wonderful project product I mean
yeah we already got our hands on them
right we already touched them we got we
got a sample yeah we got the sample wow
put it in our ear can't wait to open
pretty comfortable actually it's comt I
think like a lot of earbuds and stuff
like I don't know if my ears just shaped
really weird but they are you know they
literally are no like the inside of my
ear oh when you insert the earbuds like
sometimes it's hard to find like the
right side of the Whatchamacallit earbud
things but um these ones are pretty
comfortable when I wor so think it'll be
comfortable for many years were you also
welcomed by your own voice like and
we're like oh whoa whoa that's
me I was surprised I that to your
imagination yeah uh there you know all
all the other questions in the chat are
either too detailed for me to answer or
I I I can't really tell you the answer
um but maybe you'll find out more in the
future so thank you very much for
watching today thank you for listening
I'll see you tomorrow for one more
stream uh before I go into you know the
concert mode thank you very much
and in right
[Music]
okay thank
you bye-bye bye-bye
[Music]