[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
back to Fire Emblem
how are you doing guys
[Laughter]
wait a snacks here oh I already ate it
had like a
like an Austrian style sandwich AKA
libertas
um
papaya
yeah I'm doing okay but that was molding
so bad because I thought okay how about
we do something off screen
um
as long as it's not continuing the story
surely it will be very helpful
uh uh oh
so I did the T field Village Skirmish
and as you can see
it took me
two hours and 10 minutes
several retries
and many many many rewinds
I was so mad
I did not expect that I thought maybe
they would be like on the same level
um they just they just had way too many
units on the enemy side and yeah many of
them
heavy armor so need a mage to survive
so ideally more than one Mage because
keeping one flimsy major life through
that whole screen image is insane yeah I
tried turning them eventually I would
like put um obstructions like those ice
cubes
um
to hold them back a little bit and this
and that but holy moly that was a pain
in the ass
and here we are
here we are
as you can see post Skirmish if you can
read
seems like
maybe some people need reading
assistants by me
foreign
I guess that's okay
hopefully that gets only easier from
here well I hope that today we can
progress smoothly with the story
um
so okay um I just gotta I just end like
when I I was like you know just playing
and then
I thought I had plenty time before the
stream uh oh Skirmish maybe it takes at
most one hour right so I'll be fine I'll
be fine but it ends the Skirmish and I
look at the time and I'm like what the
[\h__\h]
ing 15 minutes
excuse me
so
Then I then I panicked quickly got
myself a
like a sandwich
from the supermarket and
here we are now what's my voice
one took me three hours to beat wow
oh but look all these places that we can
hide in
the skirmish
are actually actually
um
plantage and send English plantages no
no way
of
oh I should get all the all the animals
oh plantations well close enough
uh wait what animals did I miss with
they're also white they should separate
the NPCs from the animals in terms of
color on the map
but okay
uh I don't think there was an animal
here was there
no
something orange there all right orange
where was orange again
that's Orange
for some reason the previous one looked
white to me
oh no oh no you're feeling sick
unknown I will I will grant you a day
off
I hope you get better I hope you don't
have the sea thing or
something bad
get well soon
foreign welcome
maybe you can just fall asleep while
listening to me
um
I think that might be your first sick
day huh
it's okay first sick day is okay
everything Beyond first sick day is not
okay
just kidding
kidding
you have a good credit with me
thank you for streaming for the rest of
my shift
oh you're welcome
you're welcome it's gonna be once again
a long stream because I am the RPG
streamer as you know so feel free to
nominate me as the role play streamer or
just your favorite YouTuber on the what
streaming not streaming Awards or
whatever it was I tweeted about it you
can you can you can find it on my point
I made some more nominations way ahead
of you thank you so I I nominated
um for chess it was best
so specific best chess streamer uh well
I nominated Ollie I was like oh I have a
good idea for that I didn't have a good
idea for all of them
um but for some of them yeah
wrong kind of art people already yeah I
thought that counts so well why is there
no RPG streamer then that's important
that feels like
RPG is a whole like genre like category
chess is just chess why is there chest
streamer but no RPG streamer then what
the [\h__\h] it should be a thing yeah
that's weird what if you think about it
that's really weird
scene
so I nominated Ollie for her chess and
then I nominated
um there was um
something about best Music Streamer
[Music]
um
oh my my PC just lagged you probably
served
felt that too I can't speak what am I
looking at here
oh my God lag
robot do I sound normal again
please tell me I sound normal again
I mean I do hear crackling in the game
sound let me switch that here we go okay
yeah okay so then you know Music
Streamer I dominate
[Laughter]
Cali
I didn't dominate Cal
houn
okay but then we got these happy
accidents so whatever I guess
um
then then there was
uh
okay and there was what was there
um best FPS streamer I nominated
and
[Laughter]
he posing over Cali what else was there
at the best Minecraft streamer was you
see there's even a category for best
Minecraft streamer and somebody
argumented that I argued
foreign
someone argued that it should be fauna
and I mean okay I can see that I just
didn't think so deeply about it and I I
just made really quick decisions
it is a word okay
so I said yeah yeah I mean fun or sure
makes sense but when I thought of
Minecraft uh Ian YouTuber Halloween then
the first thing that came to mind is
crony because of her
how people like really really enjoy her
specifically playing Minecraft so
I mean I don't watch Minecraft streams
but
I mean
friends in the middle of the [\h__\h]
night for me
so
I think it's understandable but I know
that people think of her
in that case so anyway
[Music]
um
um should I um I think I was supposed to
change someone's class but I can't do
that yet right so I just go to world map
done
uh
I support I I forgot about that okay and
then what
me me as best RPS
and then I think that may have been it
because for the others I just couldn't
think of anything there were some more
categories but I couldn't think of
anything
Arena
you mean that that that training up
there
with the yellow dot dot
[Music]
I didn't put myself in Game of the Year
I think I put myself on the YouTuber of
the year because I'm in
oh in the cafe
oh
okay
X
oh yeah okay
what is that
I mean I'm obviously never gonna win
that but it would be nice to oh ah yeah
to be um not dominated but nominated
would be nice to be nominated at least
ah
all right
um
you're just gonna they're just gonna get
[\h__\h] destroyed again how about Anna
she's level five
and she has a chance
I can sell them
serious Merchant
Prius Wanderer okay
she has a chance right yeah yeah ah go
Anna no that makes you a little [\h__\h]
well 47 was pretty little
oh well good try Anna
one more I'll give her one more chance
but we might get a worse opponent now
John
oh
[Applause]
no
there we go finally a win my first win
have I got just the thing for you oh my
first win let's go
okay I think I can only do twice right
yeah but uh
one more
um
I will do her again because then she
gets to level up
come on come on come on
Saline
oh wait oh
but 46 46.
[Music]
she did good damage if only she wouldn't
have missed but she still got the ESPN
to level up nice oh Chihuahua stop
moving
so sad
this app currently always crashes I'm so
sorry guys oh
[Music]
better than nothing
okay should we do the the emblem one too
you can have a unit and an mm train
together to increase her no no cause
spawn fragments no no no no no I think
we established that last time
hmm no magic hmm
she's using Steelix I don't know compact
would be better
oh wait do they just use whatever is on
the top of their inventory because she
probably has
more than one most of my units have more
than one weapon
hello there
uh let's order me a meal
this post
office
again I crash
Crush
crash crash one paper Nothing Compares
evening alone just don't want to we sit
with this time last time we were really
like biased uh so I'll give
did I choose Chloe and someone
I would maybe go for Alfred and Chloe or
so
I can have two dining Partners right
yeah
you're not getting Selena said okay then
let's go over Chloe and Alfred
o
wait
that's a lot of stuff strength death
rest speed
yeah deep dish cup Pizza
rare vegetable I know why is this
go and confirm and then
forget about that
so naturally why do they make you do
this
let's try not to waste Nature's Bounty
thanks for letting us use you
ingredients
the fruit and the veggies cannot talk to
you
I think I saw corn on that pizza
this is so good
yummy
eh you don't need to select anything
really it looked like it though whatever
um next is reference and [\h__\h] this I
should have done off screen but they're
really short anyway so whatever
and I stop loving again hmm my sister
thought me Reckless for bolting in a
battle for the sake of my friends
what say you
my sister's always calling me a
barbarian for the same reason
a good jog puts it behind me
uh-huh see it's so short what the hell
lame
lame okay
and uh support
oh that's a lot of conversations
just warming up you know oh what the
[\h__\h] good morning
that's quite the smile
having a good day are you you can say
that I got it before sunrise and did
tons of training even got an early
run-in and the cherry on top I get to
see your bright and Shining face what a
day to be alive
who
I do feel happy when I see my friends
see me too but uh look isn't there
anything I can do for you you've been
awake a while but it must be hard
you're still adjusting to tell her
friend Alfred all about it
[Music]
there's nothing bothering me at the
moment good good great but if there is
something well I want to be the first to
know before you left lethos you asked me
as a friend to teach you things to help
you adjust and knowing you wanted to be
friends just tickled me
our friendship makes me happy too Alfred
his stub yeah his dub is okay
all right next one
[Music]
what's wrong my beloved to Chloe so
adorable when you sleep Divine one oh
[\h__\h] that's creepy oh that's creepy oh
good morning did I wake you
were you watching me sleep again yes
sorry about that oh you should just
leave me be if I nod off while I'm
sitting outside it's unnerving to wake
up on your own and find someone staring
at you
oh I never meant to do that her problem
is like it doesn't get better if she
sleeps in her own room because Dan's
just go into her room and watch her
sleep there
sleep heavenly
can't help staring at it at it I get
that
but I still must have been a ridiculous
sight sleeping here of all places oh no
not at all but I have a compromise in
mind hear me out if I'm always there
when you wake up maybe you'll get used
to it and it won't be so startling all
you have to do is set up an extra bed
for me and your chamber
nope oh my gosh shot down
doesn't matter with these people
[Music]
man what the hell
oh you're Naka you're just in time I am
that never happens wait what am I in
time for would you care to join me for
tea
I greatly prefer to have company with my
teeth than to drink alone
that sounds like on sure I'd love to all
right [\h__\h] that switching application
freshly brewed
different this might be the best tea
I've ever had you're great at this
oh you're too kind I have ample access
to high quality leaves thanks to the
Sterling tea field near my home I
started brewing tea for my family at a
young age I've had what the [\h__\h] is that
app on my PC that I don't know yeah your
family's got it made getting green tea
this good all the time
[Laughter]
possibly possibly
and your own family are they in good
health
well you see they're mostly how should I
put it
[Music]
ah I withdraw the question
I'm curious unaka have you ever tried
sugared grapes in your tea grapes in tea
sounds weird is it good I shall prepare
some for you I hope you enjoy it it's my
hometown specialty how exciting thank
you Louie I think nothing of it I prefer
to take my tea with smiles whenever I
can
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I don't remember downloading that
maybe it's one of those things they
forced you to
randomly download when you're doing
something else what the [\h__\h]
seems like an okay program though
also sometimes find
random programs on your
see were you watching me again you don't
remember downloading I was you and your
whole cotery of ladies the sight of you
all together pleased me to know him the
way you talk it sounds like you were
taking in fine art at a gallery
to me there is no greater art the finest
galleries for far short comparison there
are so many subtleties and nuances to be
seen that I could do so all day that's
really the whole reason you do it
it's no different than appreciating a
beautiful landscape I sit quietly and
let it soothe me I see no harm in people
watching and I'm sure you of all people
must agree yeah when you put it that way
I guess I do I've seen the way you drop
everything to Moon over any especially
picturesque scenes like a princess and
her Knight
so many lovely scenes straight out of a
fairy tale I adore them all you and I
are Kindred Spirits in that respect
here's an idea why don't you and I have
a little viewing party sometime we can
stand at a remove and point out scenes
that catch our respective eyes
that sounds like fun I'm getting Who You
Are no
boring
I'm so not impressed
oh man
it's an Alfred
fancy meeting everything with yunaka is
already better
if anything the welcome's been almost a
little too warm you know I'm an unknown
quantity
anybody what if I was a somebody who
would know she's cussing herself no
one's been checking on me to try to find
out true oh should I be snooping more
it's like a logical course of action
that's all I'm saying
well I do want to get to know you better
yeah we should talk more but when we get
the time
talk is
pronunciation is killing me I mentioned
it before let me think about it
[Music]
I trust you
you never once been betrayed Swindle
double crossed bamboozle
hey get that question me foreign
[Music]
why they don't make the voice actors
properly pronounce it why why why why
why why why why why why if it's
originally a Japanese game then you must
have some input and references amazing
weather we're having today huh
too true it's the perfect day for a cup
of tea especially the tea you prepare
ETA it's my favorite of all that's kind
of you to say would you like another cup
but no I'd better not if if you say so
God I can't hold it anymore they're
forcing each other to be nice to each
other
forcing themselves I win yep fair play
ETA I got no excuse although I could
swear our special workout teacups seem
heavier today oh well spotted
I wonder I had such trouble just lifting
it
nothing less let's raise our teacups to
strength to strength
sure
[Music]
weightlifting even when you're drinking
tea
using your time pretty well I would say
all right all right we did that
um
yeah I think
what's
I'm good maybe ring chamber see how many
Bond points I have complete achievements
no I'm am I not doing that automatically
I already seen like achievement blee
blah blue
in the the board ah
I have to check them on the billboard
okay
one of my morning strings you made it
hello did you guys sing what I uploaded
in my night time
[Music]
um
my shorts my YouTube short
I was waiting for a day off or so to
upload it hey hey
[Music]
I learned that one really fast you know
on the 31st I was
[Music]
um
I was I was there much earlier than the
other ladies
to do all kinds of setup and so on since
it was my first time doing 3D and that's
that studio and
um yeah
with some setup to do and then
eventually I had like what maybe like
half an hour break time
if not a little bit less before the
others would come and so on
and I was like
I want to make the most of the time I
wanna I wanna use this studio right now
if that's okay to do something and
they're like okay what do you want to do
and I'm like oh that's that's something
maybe something short and I was thinking
a little bit and then I realized oh wait
I always wanted to do the treasure box
from Maddie and Senpai and yeah so I let
them play it a few times
um so I could learn it really quickly
um and then it I I just recorded it like
on the whip
thanks to the staff for letting me do
that
it's not perfect actually I still messed
up a little bit
because like the basically the play the
the movement is with the legs is always
the same but with every
and with every of those moments
um you're supposed to put your hand
somewhere else and I kept on mixing up
where they go each time
um
but yeah a lot of people commented you
know that they've seen a [\h__\h] ton of
mmds everywhere and and I mean I thought
they were cute too
but you know it's obviously not
naturally
recorded those are all well
a fixed motion and you just slam it onto
a character and they do it
I want to do it myself
and I mean yeah I couldn't even have had
someone make the MMD for me because my
model is not
um public right so yeah that's maybe one
of the reasons why no one did it with um
myth members unless maybe there's some
good high quality
um 3D models of us that are just
fan-made but I don't think there is
one of me out there like a really good
one that looks like the real deal
uh yeah so anyway I did it myself
[Music]
it's on my channel as a shirt so if you
haven't seen it
check it out I think it's quite
addicting hypnotizing
yeah I was like fine I'll do it myself
[Music]
yes but I didn't want to like
I don't know annoy him
um again I just didn't really wanna have
it be an MMD I just wanted to do it
myself because I can
because I can
why not do it when you can do it
yourself
and so achievement on achievement screen
you can claim Bond fragrance rewards for
their seats aha you'll be notified when
you complete an achievement okay
oh
can I clear them ah said r
ude yo
yo
okay maybe it is time to go to the ring
chamber
so I saw someone writing that
um
melting the Rings together it's kind of
a waste
do you guys agree with that
should we just continue creating them
until we get all the good ones
it is it is okay cool
[Music]
oh you can save that's okay no need but
um
okay so this is how you do it right ten
here we go a thousand
uh a bronze one
oh
a golden button
well it's just pronouncing so why did
that look so special to me
I thought it was because of the rainbow
sparkles but no it's all [\h__\h]
Brown LeBrons
oh France
Castle wow whatever
is there maybe at least one guaranteed
per 10 draws
is there such a thing
Minerva B luck plus one death plus one
okay okay we have never had a golden one
though
and we have yet to see one
because my feet are so cold I need to
put on the sauce oh I have a silver one
ah we already have this one no wait we
don't I thought I guess we had maybe
Navarre scene or so
no nothing
the nervous thingy
my feet are so cold
oh cute okay we got uh two
silver ones
um
I have any plan to do another hero movie
watch along
well let's do 10 here
am I
is it okay to use my to use so many bone
fragments
um see
I can get Tiki I'm not ready for that
you guys told me it's difficult
I'll need so many rings yeah but I would
like at least one golden one
some more silver ones
cute magic and rest plus one let's rest
resistance
let's go I think that was worth it
using my
using my bond money
hey magic defense okay
HP strength and depth wow wow
why here we go
my first golden ring
[Music]
oh silk B she's cute
that's good for Louis the the golden one
another silver one oh HP plus two def
plus one oh
wow
just need four more
what do you what do you mean just for my
so that um
for what
oh for five golden rings
[Laughter]
saver a text speed race
plus one
thanks guys now we need only two more
I know three more
and then we have five golden rings
let's go
wow
oh silica made me really lucky
well also what about inherit skills
again how do you do this again how does
this work
ah
uh you guys told me to save them up
didn't you
you guys did tell me to save them up
not so urgent red okay okay
um
thank you for a look and be tricked with
a longbow
only one longbow
ah uh all right I think um
you don't get a lot unless you do
skirmishes might want to think about
using Summit chapter 10. okay
anyway
don't forget to equip the ring hi hi hi
hi somebody said Louie gets the golden
one one of the golden ones
uh
let's see is
which one said not saver right Volvo
who should I give the Sable one to raise
his decks speed and resistance
who wants this one
this one Chloe
well she has more
okay Anna has nothing right now
you're late well better late than never
okay
what no
this menu is so confusing
hi
what am I doing
everything so confusing
there's so much to do
huh
but here we go story time baby
finally
finally I want to do some progression
oh
shock
but my features are so cold I'm gonna
put on some socks really quick
I'm so cold
[Music]
foreign
let's go whoa we're going to broodia and
this is the grand Crossing let's go
cute girls inbound so we made it across
the border
we're in protea territory
[Music]
Escape here it's it's different from
Fear a nothing but rugged terrain all
around us
now
game over
under attack [\h__\h] right at that girl
just right by her head
you are the one sneaking over that's so
true like
it's our fault
cute this time I won't miss
I'm the Divine dragon from lethos not a
thief how do all people believe us
anyway though
and say I'm just in debt
Prince of Fury that's so unlikely don't
trust us no I would
like that no you would be a fool to not
shoot
there's no proof that they are what they
are
just gonna hug he's gonna hug us
bye so so so sorry
I threatened the Divine dragon and the
Crown Prince of fear Renee please find
it in your hearts to forgive me
he's doing dogeza yeah but like
like if it was like a thing of oh
because of how we looked no harm was
done then it was quite the bow Soldier
must have been hard on the knees then
originally even without saying who we
are he would have already recognized us
you know what I mean
yeah and he was within rights yeah to
defend himself but they have no like I
don't know proof whatsoever it's just oh
man hmm wait a second your face looks
awfully familiar
is that a razor blade on his hair are
you
no I'm all Crest second Prince of brodia
he's Christian so how's it going Prince
all Chris he's all Christian even worse
than usual I'm sorry for taking so long
to introduce myself oh these are my
retainers lapis and citrine honored to
meet you and your cotery
I can't say I feel very welcome
still look like you're ready to kill us
we're merely a little tense my father
King morion received word from Queen EV
that your party was on its way and he
ordered us to meet you at the border and
formally welcome you to the kingdom
oh you were told about us anyway and all
we encountered were bizarre creatures
Bandits okay when they were expecting us
and I can understand it a bit more we
had to take a little detour
still if your arrow hit the Divine One
Brody is standing seriously hurt be more
careful next time Prince Alquist
oh you must have listened
without them protecting their [\h__\h]
country and he just told you they keep
on getting attacked
Alfred
I love her no way of knowing love her
earrings was it not possible for your
party to arrive in a more Royal more
resplendent and excuse me this is the
kingdom of Warriors if you can't Dodge
one Arrow you're not worthy to enter
here are the weak serve the strong maybe
we should give you a little test wow
she didn't mean that apologies I love
how mad they are how much value on
strength I love it besides you have
nothing to prove I am well aware of your
battle prowess Prince
oh well
thank you I'm so sorry for all this
feisty oh sorry and I'm sorry it's me
greeting you instead of someone better
you can stop apologizing I'm grateful
that a prince is here to receive us
personally
really
you're grateful to see me okay
honored in fact
how polite of you to say so
Charming as well as Divine I see could
you do me the favor of being maybe also
exclusive
oh my God
it's so hard to shine as it is
no
I can show you the way to brodia Castle
can you be less dazzling
I will arrive at the Grand Crossing soon
as that will take us to the castle good
Divine one if I may
I was wondering about something Queen F
said in her letter is it true that
illusia has released sombron it's true
and illusion we thought told us as much
I see we'd heard rumors to that effect
but I didn't dare believe them
those neighbors of ours
you will need all the Rings to defeat
the feldragon right
for Generations he looks like he could
be out of a game with the initials GI a
young lion that just me it has a red
stone and a certain
Gallant Aura diamont the Crown Prince
told me he's been hearing a voice from
the room he is a remarkable person right
I'm lucky to be his brother you really
admire him don't you oh yes
strong wise humble the king adores him
as do our people my brother is cut from
The Nobles
there's no need to be so hard on
yourself
dryer
[Music]
ah there it is the grand Crossing
there seems to be a great many soldiers
out today
wait a moment
those are enemies and soldiers they're
occupying the bridge
illusion
[Music]
it took you long enough very rude to
keep a princess waiting I love you
indeed princess
the second princess
[Music]
it fits and it's not too tryhard I mean
it kind of is but that's that's second
it has to be and it's like so
it's not killing me
right
if you're the prettiest it's a dead
giveaway I always thought lumero was the
only Divine Dragon you could have
knocked me over with a feather when I
found out there was another one
wow those mismatched eyes of yours are
something to see
who else that guy
don't come any closer no come closer
look at Illusions aren't worthy to
approach the Divine dragon
this is one Aqua Senpai would look like
if her mama was a spirit country this is
invading our territory our land it's the
worst do you know how many people you've
hurt not just soldiers but regular
people we're not just invading to expand
we are keeping your vicious
unpredictable Kingdom in check I take it
you're retaliating launching a
full-scale Invasion to take your revenge
in the order of my father King Hyacinth
no she told you to do this
Fork over the goods and we'll all go
home I forgive her never I give her all
my rings if that means that she puts it
on her ring finger job
[Laughter]
Crown Princess she's going to attack
Brody a castle oops probably shouldn't
have said that
you must go right away
as if I'd let you pass my father's gonna
be so proud of me
oh
[Music]
I don't care
it's not oh my God can she join me
please we shouldn't find she should join
me
but yeah um
oh
wait
let me no let me let me let me let me
let me see first
what are we up against
oh my God
are we getting help Midway through
when we advance do they also Advance or
do they just chill over there for now
in any case is that okay heavy armor
not so heavy armor
uh-huh flying
mage
well basically they have everything but
I do have a couple
oh that oh
[Music]
yeah
classy
and she looks like she could have been
Alice in Wonderland
okay they do Advance once I get closer
Nintendo's version of Harley Quinn
I see that
evil Fire Emblem aqua
business
hahaha
or or it's the child's love child of
aqua and bells
oh
anyway
um right
so let me see they're automatically
assuming oh no wait wait wait they add
us those three new units I don't even
have to bring them
they assume like you know they're part
of the group so besides that we have an
Archer one of them is an Archer right
so maybe we don't need idea
we can bring Anna I guess because she
has the Golden Ring
and if you look closely one two three
four five we have five
five so now we have
six because that looks pretty golden to
me
damn it almost at five
two might be useful
um okay
I guess so especially if they come from
two sides okay no not fine with me fine
with me do we need the Healer oh my God
oh I can bring the Healer no I know I'm
fine with that team whatever and
um sweepy swoop swap places
[Music]
like so
oh yeah
oh yeah two Mages up here where the
solution so I maybe don't need two of
them though we don't need two of them
like this
big brain kiwawa
free Mages I got three major exactly and
return to the castle it's not a moment
to spare
of course Prince Alquist leave it to us
oh my heal stuff will be back in time
for dinner
but I'm still concerned about casualties
I will protect you both
so brave but uh as your retainers it's
really our job to protect you now then
get behind me
huh I like them oh oh Chris don't be
ridiculous yeah sure you should be at
the rear yeah uh switch switch you
should also be in the back
you too they're gonna switch
you're not gonna switch
looks like it's starting to your
positions everyone
oh
said that dragon is absolutely
[Music]
absolutely not as cute as we are right
exactly
that's the spirit outshine the enemy and
then I wanna see them like in let's do
those Rings not only this close up I
want to see the full body yes Rosado
let's make quick work risotto
um
defeat Hortense is the goal okay so we
don't even have to kill all of them
but she's very far in the back so
you know it might take a while all right
all right I'm ready
hey yo
hey yeah oh for a Smiles on them to see
the mouth oh okay
nice perfect first move what are these
for
Avo heel turn closet damn what is this
where's this risotto standing
here oh oh where's mine is here
oh
[Music]
that's a really cute design
that's really cute
no the dragon what the [\h__\h] the dragon
is like all kinds of ribbons
I'm freaking cute
I love it
wait out all dragons like that
wait there's only one dragon is there a
way I think like I saw one down here no
[Music]
no
I wonder if all dragons look like that
um
yeah yeah okay
just his oh okay
[Music]
Lance ax I don't know what what the [\h__\h]
hey what am I pressing
um
[Music]
wait did I not bring a single ax fighter
[Laughter]
that sucks I can knock down anyone
smash weapons what powerful weapons like
blades and great lines to smash on the
head driving foes backwards but oh
you can break foes by Smashing them into
units or other obstacles like walls oh
these weapons are heavy however they can
follow up and your phone will get to
attack first when you initiate combat
with them
[Music]
oh but I don't even have to stand
I oh no okay because the preview it was
showing her I thought me right it was
her right now okay
no but if that does my pleasure only do
half damage
then let me attack first with you
oh wait they can attack back
[Music]
wait a second
as you wish
I'm all ready I'm already thinking
everything through so much
[Music]
yeah yeah I was thinking too Thunder but
then I first wanted him to move away
I was thinking the same thing you know
or I guess from here would work
[Music]
from here Works to
all right
[Music]
cool music going on again
oh wait there
oh
the horse is right there
hope I can kill horsey next turn
but better oh wait no I can do it now
what now
I didn't realize I couldn't walk over
there
okay
okay am I bunks no you're not
oh
I thought the field ends like there here
on this line
um
[Music]
two archers
that doesn't kill him
what doesn't Killa makes him stronger
right
yeah it's good
[Music]
it's good wait what
I thought it was one hit
one two three four five five let's level
up though oh our channel was worth it
foreign
voice
oh yeah speaking of smoothing soothing
um I
had my day off yesterday right
and
um
on the day before or the night before
hmm
I noticed that
[Music]
um chunkers one of my ketokatos let's go
um was like kind of
I'm not sure if it if it's if if she was
like pooping blood
or
if it came from
um
her urine
and I wasn't sure I'm listening but I
saw it in the toilet and I saw it on her
butt so I was like oh damn this one
could be bad and I I have noticed this
in the middle of the night when I was
actually like waiting
to record something I was on standby
I was on standby for
over over an hour probably one and a
half hours
come down here
oh
that's emblem
yeah it's a pretty cool trick huh I'm so
glad I'm able to use it
it's all thanks to Lord sombron powering
up this ring it's called The Ring of the
princess it's pretty looks like him am I
ready engagement ring that's one of the
Rings my mother was protecting
wow
I like that voice acting just now
whoa okay here we go I'm going on on
Google
wait what's your name Hortensia
like the flower
or tenzie how far emblem
English
Amber Connor
what
damn
sometimes it's surprising
what kind of voices can come out of
people
does she have a Twitter
I think she does does she
Amber Lee Connor
[Music]
I don't know if that's her
I I I don't know if that's her
amber amber amber amber amber there's an
Amber Lee Connor and an Amber Connor are
they the same people no they look
different
you found her at Mifflin let's go
heck yeah
oh yeah
oh she also voiced a different Fire
Emblem character
Fire Emblem echoes
oh
I think I saw it and I'm on Google for a
second she voiced um
some character there
[Music]
laughing said yeah
your voice is so good for her
um
I am enjoying every second of it
any connections here you know some folks
can also use emblems and combat these
dark emblems cannot engage but they can
still use engage attacks oh
a light indicates when foes have engaged
attacks where they keep an eye out oh no
yeah that emblem is a formidable phone
nearby enemies can join in her attacks
eh we'll have to be careful
oh
he's going for her for Chloe thought he
was gonna go for me
all right all right all right all right
[Music]
weapon triangle I have no no
uh x what that's okay
because even like this I'm doing plenty
damage look at that
I mean he won't die it was
[Music]
yeah all good so now we can finish him
off
um
wait can we not walk through here
you're kidding me you're kidding me you
must be kidding me now
ah
all right I'll take that
[Music]
that's so lame
you can go over there though that's
that's good to know but
um
and now I have to squeeze everyone for
the side
yeah
okay Magic
user
um
I don't know about that
can't one hit them
can't one hit
I only have oh wait wait I have this
fist fighter but she can't reach
you could override those Majors what do
you mean override
Oh you mean
his special skill
use funder Long Poke Longbow poke on the
first
the perfect line
when I was trying to do this in a
skirmish I could always only override
one at a time
explain that to me even though they were
in a line
and there was nothing on the other side
to block me or so
my muscles are yours I was like why why
why why why why why why why
you have to be a Jason Day words look
again
well
no wait now it works
now it works
hey where Jason dumb pretty sure
hmm
[Music]
anyway
does this matter it doesn't matter
raise your sword
I don't have an open space I think but I
guess I guess something was wrong
because
but I was so confused like and it should
work this has to work now
um
better
better stay here
and now the path is a little bit clear
but not
not enough
[Music]
yeah so and then yesterday I went to the
to the vet it was so hard to carry
joggers but she hasn't seen the carrier
in a long time so it was relatively easy
to get her in
um
because I I put the carriers down in the
cellar so that they don't maybe they
forget what they look like and then they
don't panic so much but the biggest
problem always was um smoothie
she was always like
vegetable
to put
into a carrier
um
no she weighs like 3.5
chances weighs like 3.5 but
um some people wrote on Twitter to me
that the reason why she must have felt
so
um heavy to me might be because
um you know the carrier has like a
handle in the middle
um but the the cat inside will like
shift around and do like whatever it
wants to do
and then
basically the weight will be not even
and then it yeah and then you also like
try to
carrying ah [\h__\h]
you try to carry in the cat
somewhat in a somewhat stable manner
right
and that also
makes it a bit more difficult you don't
want to like shake or shake shake shake
I keep I kept on like even carrying her
with two arms or one arm on one side and
so on but I was so heavy my arms were
like dying
I was at my absolute limit when I
arrived at the vet
so the way back I I just took um
I just took a taxi back
the person was nice
it was like no problem I have a cat too
oh well you lasted hmm carry on your
head maybe next time
yeah and um the vet was nice
it costed like 70 bucks which feels a
little bit expensive but what he did was
like he looked at her butt and he wasn't
sure
he said he's not sure what it is could
be a
I guess a new TI or something like that
but when I said that she doesn't
[Music]
um
she doesn't like go to the toilet more
often than usual than he said then it's
less likely that it's that
um and then you know he was saying so
many things and I was so nervous
that most of the things he said didn't
really end to my brain
did I even move Louie
[Music]
but what I remember is he wasn't sure
what it was so
oh [\h__\h] I did need a noise I don't need
one of you over there
okay I'll bring you over now
um
Louisa tactile did he really I guess so
I
huh oh he's up there
yeah so he was like he shaved
rear part of junkers
but uh only a small area
um
and then yeah you could see I guess a
little bit of inflammation and and all
that but yeah and then he gave her an
anti
biotic through a syringe
and she was she was a good girl during
that
[Music]
um
and he gave me like
um because I have to go back
in a couple days he gave me
a
uh yeah more antibiotics like two small
ones to take in the morning and one big
one and I have to
um half give her half of it in the
evening
my cat pooped blood once I kept an eye
on the situation but she didn't do it
again she's fine now
um yeah I'm not sure either don't use
her yet
why
[Music]
why I guess because he will attack first
how how old are my cats they're
um unlimited years old
[Music]
I can't reach this one
[\h__\h] hellmate
flat junk Arena seems okay yeah she's in
Spanish today this morning I gave her
um one of the pills and she immediately
swallowed it she was so good like I
opened her mouth a little bit
and then she just immediately
swallowed it like she she's better at
swallowing pills than I was back in the
day when I was having troubles with it
I used to have big issues swallowing
pills
would often like choke on them
um
and then and then
and then it would like come back up and
then the
kind of because I already had it in my
mouth for a while the weird Taste of
some some of the pills like for example
iron pills would
go through my mouth and it would be so
disgusting
not very pleasant oh I shouldn't have
done that
[Music]
not pleasant at all
anyway yeah
[Music]
always with water always with water but
still sometimes like I had a like a long
time where I think it was just something
like set in my mind that I was worried
about choking on the pill and then it
would make me mess up even more
you know
would make me so nervous about it
yeah
mind games
see that still doesn't kill them but
since I have no Archer over here I mean
I guess whatever at least I can't fight
back
still can't swallow pills while it takes
me many seconds before I can actually
swallow it oh man
yeah the only thing that helped me with
that is continuously try again try again
try again and eventually I just finally
managed to do it properly
oh
no
now I could never swallow pills without
water never
mind
[Music]
foreign
it's not that hard I know I couldn't
[Music]
she can't attack there
you will get hit back into your face
right if you attack
yeah
a pretty rough one
pretty rough one
oh wait you still there you still there
what's up
oh Riders being oh yeah
[Music]
yeah three spaces oh no well it wasn't
necessary look at that
I forgot about the writer's vein
overpowered
yeah anyway chances has been doing
really well she's like and she's like
and then she rolls around on the ground
and she's like really happy
so
I think we're good
this evening I give her another pill
and tomorrow another one and another one
she seems mostly fine oh it's not like
she's like
like uncontrollably bleeding it was just
like I guess a little bit that one time
did the enemies not do anything oh
no hold on
foreign
[Music]
uh
attack
is that
should I bait them
stuff going all in because the others
are still kind of behind
I'll try to bait them I'll go
um
also because I want to charge anyway so
I'll wait here
Alfred would get wrecked if I do
Get Wrecked
ah [\h__\h] though I wanted to bring you on
the other side but there's already so
many people on the other side
[Music]
all right I'll take it easy because you
guys don't need so much time to come
over here
waiting goo
no
okay
wait here
changard
oh God
yeah I'm doing chain guard don't worry
waiting goo
oh wait no I shouldn't I shouldn't have
waited she has those obstruct stuff I
should have obstructed something because
that gives her EXP
wait a second I'll actually I'll
actually go over on this side because
she can walk pretty far
I mean some people on that side
and
you guys oh he could have used some
healing
for example but
um
he'll take a vulneri then
okay
[Music]
yeah it was less damage than I thought
it would be all good oh
[Music]
oh oh oh oh
no damage on either side
okay well we baited them
now he will die by my hands with my
magic
or he will not
all right well we'll finish it here
chain attack missed
no problem
yeah at least he can't hit back
it's okay it's okay
it's okay
I'm gonna use my second Mage on this
side though
oh dear oh dear
they all want a piece of me
Celine is such an MVP man
makes so broken yeah but you know they
have to be weak against something
otherwise
those
those heavy armor tanks they would be
like undefeatable
I don't know break them
I want to test this
when I do something like this
if it's poison or fire it doesn't
necessarily like do less damage right
[Music]
yeah he has something
their chain guard yeah
oh well
[Music]
win win
they has poison now
it's good it's good it's good
it's good we're good
can you not move like that so annoying
okay that doesn't kill
hmm
you can throw right oh but that also oh
wait I
got iron daggering in your eyes one on
the left side one on the right eye was
that too much
easy peasy lemon squeezy
hmm
the Mage could actually reach their Monk
and she can too how much damage does she
do on him
she does all the damage
oh he might uh get like free on me but
that's okay
74. it's like 69 74. all right
so much but sometimes in my Skirmish I
even missed when I had like 85 or
sometimes even with 90 I would miss and
I'm like what the [\h__\h]
not accepting that no no no no no no no
no no no stop
Fair
so annoying
so don't imagine that I will not accept
that no no no
[Music]
no not something over here like a
solution over here
[Music]
huh what are you doing here on anyway
hahaha
damn it
[Music]
no that's so stupid
that's so stupid let me put you here
and take this one down
I guess maybe first
okay that was a chain
with this map I don't know currently I
don't like the map angle at all
I don't like this
but it doesn't get much better
kill tank with Mage oh [\h__\h] you mean
wait which one the one I just killed
you mean the one I just killed anyway
right right right right right
I used up the bad RNG mess so we could
yeah I wonder maybe now
oh please
don't you dare
don't you dare oh one more
okay I'll take the one hit
that's
acceptable but now she's all alone over
there I have to like protect her somehow
I'll have to protect her
[Music]
so even though this is an overall very
dangerous situation
78 78 78
okay 78 hmm
she's in the range of what's that door
was risotto what where's Rosado the
risotto person
uh
okay
you wait here
wait I didn't get to charge him I mean
he's still in it but
risotto
and only you left hmm
you're gonna go for her aren't you
if I leave her standing there
oh
[\h__\h] but the only way to
get around that is if I am going all the
way over here
and this one doesn't heal it only uh
heals my age My non-existent Fire Emblem
chain guard her
[Music]
how far can we go we can go here
all right we still got full HP on that
side so
okay
oh oh oh
did they just push me off my field no it
just looked like it on the scene
I'm scared hey cutie you get to bite me
how much damage 60
days I don't know how much damage it
would have done
ow oh that hurts though
but it was important to dodge once at
least
almost coughed up on my water
oh [\h__\h] she's a mage oh [\h__\h] ouch
do I get healed by that field now no
[Applause]
that's what if I just kill her really
quickly
[Music]
does she have more than one bar probably
right
let's do a work wrapping work on oh [\h__\h]
the wheel
[Music]
I can wipe on this dude though
I think that might be worth it
I'll do it
yeah you cannot catch I couldn't walk
behind him
oh they got him it's okay
I'm sorry I could
it has two range
oh
still ax all right
um
is it my turn
the other field has to be no no never
mind
should I charge him now
was that like
I feel like I need as many units up here
in the front now as possible
I need to get this one out of the way
first
[Music]
what if I go here
to protect me
and I don't know if I want to use my
engagement already
our Arch is in range oh yeah right I can
shoot them probably down oh yeah yeah
she's in range
should we go for this one first because
we can kill him at least
but the other one is not in range I
think not at all you can get him here
though afterwards
all right
killing this one first second
one horse down
[Music]
what does she do
okay we can break this guy
can break him
I'll do that now I think I know I think
I'll just stay
no wait
she can never attack first right she'll
always be hit but that's that's exactly
why she needs healing though
don't you think
um
smash's foes
depends on the weapon
oh okay
not a whole doll
then I'll do the iron sword
oh yeah yeah it's just it's not that big
much difference actually iron sword does
more damage anyway and we break him so
okay
all right
now next up
[Music]
I'll engage once I'm in front of
Hortensia
some good stretch
I only use with heavy whips and armor
for an hour when people actually take
little damage that sentence is too long
I don't understand
now I will do this because I'm a smart
little Phoenix
very small
oh I can even start by doing some damage
with uh Thunder
oh it's not much but it's better than
nothing
unless I just wasted that and we still
had some heavy armor standing around
somewhere
oh oh she's a mage flyer oh [\h__\h] she
could hit me back home
she has so much choice
I don't mind whoever she wants to go for
[Music]
now that's dangerous
I don't think I want to do that
I don't wanna I don't want to be the one
facing her
with yunaka
oh have you left here
can't do anything with you though
what time
is it is is it go time
is it
too
[Music]
my prayers are with you
small baby
hey
[Laughter]
let's go
one HP and one one one one bar down yeah
[Music]
okay
now that we already have one HP bar down
I wonder if I should ah I can stand
behind her
oh maybe I should just heal instead
[Music]
mend
yeah
higher chances for Chloe surviving
[Music]
I think I needed to heal everyone
there's only like two people who are
injured
injured oh and then that'll be fine
[Music]
okay
and oh last but not least
ah
[Music]
I don't I don't think so although wait
wouldn't I um break her
oh oh no that was the other icon that I
was seeing from that flying horse
oh those are still around well then
what if I go over here
I can't kill them though
[Music]
nice
go here
all right let's see what happens
[Music]
oh I refuse
your offer
oh
let's go
oh oh [\h__\h] she goes for him
[Music]
[Applause]
that's okay
I didn't train hard enough that's okay
I'll friend you already got enough exp
it's time to retreat
you are too cocky
[Laughter]
ah
lap is good freaking job though holy
moly
wait is she the only one left
oh no this one's still there
okay
[Music]
um
wait the first one with the 49 is the
chain attack right
I don't care much about that
[Music]
even if it misses
oh I just need to beat her yeah but exp
let's go
chain attack is the 80 oh
oh that everything's [\h__\h] low
59 percent
is the highest I can go
oh well maybe something will
we're creepers oh
hey
that's what I'm talking about
ah she's standing on a defensive tile
is she
it's just normal floor
okay here's some exp for you
here
yo this is so much more fun than
Skirmish the Skirmish was such a pain in
the ass you're horrible oh that's it
I'm horrible
I mean she did ask was really politely
to die and I didn't say anything I was
like please please please do you will
you please die and do me the favor
so I guess I'm the impolite one yeah
um
okay I will not kill anyway
I'll give the kill someone else
Maybe
what do you think about that
yeah I'm gonna heal with you now call
engage oh she hasn't been engaged yet
oh oh
well then I guess I'll heal first
or I'll do some baby damage with others
first
do some baby damage first
yeah I'll do some baby damage
me first get as many people
participating us possible this is a
group project
um watch the crit whoa
it's p magic speech and something else
okay
one more question
one more baby damage
[Music]
y'all have horsey has like horns like a
like a sheep you see that did you see
that
but
those look like just decoration
wait let me look at her
[Music]
well look look wow yes piece of the
armor
wow and I wonder if Mika Mama also
designed the horse design
so cute
oh it's got ram horns
um
oh that would kill okay we don't want
that
we're close to the kill so let me
uh engage
and do the sacrifice
for the gray no good
[Music]
there
foreign
[Music]
XP
by the way come on
[Music]
level 10.
only level nine what's up with that okay
well then I feel
I feel like I deserve this
yeah
no I deserve this can friend break her
[Music]
um
no she can't
we can still attack with her though
we can
she'll just take some damage
but she gets exp even from attacking so
[Music]
the boss is sore now yeah yeah
okay okay
so everybody got their piece of cake
we're done with bullying by now
I think we're done here we go
houses Unite
return the rain
wait I'm the one who's after the Rings
could have done this easy way but no you
had to be stubborn I'm stubborn
does she know who I am though won't she
be on my side after that
[Music]
she's not evil right
I lost
she evil
and I want her in my team though she
knows that's why she's against you she's
Pure Evil
no
if evil like you
oh but I got her master still wait what
she will never join my team
is that what you're saying I was looking
forward to having her in my team
I can fix her
I'm okay we'll see
if cute can tolerate evil yeah
she'll get it eventually
sanded like recital
[Laughter]
Roseanne Rosado
there's a lot of damage to the bridge it
may take time to find a safe path
forward he didn't recover the emblem
ring
we didn't lose any either and most
importantly you're not hurt that's not
that good enough don't let them go
plain now that Queen lumera's stolen
Rings lie in illusia's hands in which
case we can deduce that they possess
five
yes counting the Rings taken from
lethal's Castle so many names of the
sage Lord the Azure twins the instructor
and of course the princess exalt
princess Hortensia was wielding the
latter as you'll recall I thought they
would be scattered before there was one
entrusted to them by your forebears on
the other side too if I may yeah
the king favors it or so I've heard
he keeps it in his personal Chambers his
Chambers that's odd fearness ring has a
hall in the castle all to itself where
does your kingdom keep its ring
like firenay have we store ours in a
special Gallery in the castle
speaking of which
how soon might we be able to depart now
I really am worried about the situation
there let's go the soldiers should be
back from Patrol soon
prepare to leave
thank you
if anything has happened to my father or
brother I don't know what I'll do that
was a fun fight
a little bit
too easy
but fun
oh yeah we can explore again all right
there's an animal
cute
there's an even better view up in the
somnia
Little Bub
hi up in the sky
oh well you might not be as excited
about going to the sky
as the burp is but wait what did it say
I can't
I don't know how to oh this specific
brodian cat
oh man
uh
uh here or something
[Music]
new country oh yeah I have to donate to
them donate to them
oh this chick was so rude to me I'm
confused to help me guys we're in Brody
now and those people we met first are
from Brody and they're on the other side
but the Oculus Empire isn't she also
from bronia why was she sure why why was
she so rude to me
why are they like why do they have
and they're from elucia okay
is that the top right uh on the map the
top right continent
uh-huh
what is she doing here just to steal the
Rings well what [\h__\h] I love her though
I can't stand here and do nothing I need
to know what now too fast
I'm glad before it's the illusion Army
to retreat but I fear for the castle
it's like a home to me
right I'm sorry for being rude earlier
Divine one I hope you'll support Prince
alchrist and Me hmm
that sounds like another chick who has a
crush on me
[Music]
all right are we down here I think we're
done oh no wait there's one more
little thing over here
God
well welcome
on my side you chose the right side
congratulations
everyone has a crush on me yeah
girl she's here again I'm on a chrome
girl
oh evil evil evil
almost done did you feel it
I mean
it's fighting the same things that we're
fighting
that's the last of them at least in that
moment
finally safe what you're not evil not
good enough I have
I have to be strong
just like you were
still miss you so much
and I think about what you said to me
all those long years ago
where are you
stir
sister who's her sister
she looks really powerful though
foreign
don't tell me don't tell me
although my current assumption is that
she's actually evil look at how wow
cute
oh
so this is the Sonya any yam Fields up
here uh I mean we should hurt Brody a
castle
young fields
I don't think I've ever eaten a yam
before
listen are they very yummy yeah yeah me
Illusions Crown Princess May soon attack
make preparations then we March for
Brody a castle
all right
they are very are you sure about that oh
it's just cut off
cut off sweet potato why don't they just
say sweet potato
why don't they just say that
they're like sweet potato okay
always looking you shouldn't be on the
song you know I hope father and diamonds
are safe
[Music]
self the what's the word
the the the the the the
fix them I'm not interested in fixing
him deprecating
that's it that's it
there's something down there
some phone fragments how is it when I um
like deal with you I get some Bond
fragments too right
head
do I have to do long pressing or short
press
she's petting anyway so I guess it's
fine
me
yes poop those bun fragments thank you
oh [\h__\h] no oopsie can I do it again
though
only once one action per me being
insomnia right
I think so
then hair though
milk is the option optimal food
oh
no no no no no
yes
how much was that hundred still just a
hundred though
I know dress up as well
okay
it loves orange are you sure you mean
oranges or the color orange
too bad that I'm in the game currently
um
red and blue if only I was orange then
QP would love me too
[Music]
let's see
uh oh did you guys see the schedule
tomorrow I am ironing my clothes
I guess
at 12 p.m my time sorry it's gonna be
like really shitty for
um is tpsd
and I guess CST but that's because I
have something to do later in the day
so I thought okay I'll do an early
stream
but some of you guys were so extremely
excited about the aspect of me ironing
my clothes
for whatever reason I guess it's a
really interesting concept isn't it that
some of you guys are saying that you're
still foreign
so
you will see whether or not it's gonna
be worth waking up at 6 00 a.m we're
staying up until three am or even 5 a.m
because it will take a little while
just to see
uh hiring my clothes
I've had this idea for a while and
um I was like breaking my
brains over what I should stream this
week
and I just forgot again that I could
just do a hollow backstream I forgot
that and now
now I decided after I remembered to do
it next week
so hold on banks next week I put it in
my schedule so now I will not forget
but at that moment when I was making the
schedule I couldn't remember so however
I remembered something the the ironing
streams
sure to stream too though so I think
really good we're good
kill him
oh
her legs from this angle
looks cut looks kind of messed up
hmm
but nice fur coat yeah I was thinking
the same
should we donate a little bit so that we
can at least
get those animals and stuff
yeah
okay
adult achievements
she's very rich
thank you
thank you for inviting me to this lovely
place I'm honored to host any formal
balls here oh yeah she sounds rich rich
[\h__\h]
okay
um
oh this time you're standing here
so in Fairy and I didn't know you guys
had shifts
I'm gonna dine with the newbies
um
how about
a fruit pie
one of them is a mage
extra ingredients does that really make
it any better though when I add extra
ingredients
does that make it better
option is usually best oh
it doesn't look so much better
it's what they like maybe
it does
Chris's success
uh-huh
I've got an F and it's a massive debuff
what I'm pretty good at cooking F at the
cooking
so I add this you better not [\h__\h] this
up chop it clam wait
what
please oh don't look at it I may not
like it but I'm gonna finish she doesn't
like it but support is up wait did they
[\h__\h] it up
my goodness
unique flavor just as we talk about it
well what rank is it
hey ah a b c d e it's not f
oh okay I get I get no debuff but at
least magic plus one
you little [\h__\h] Clan you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
Osho why don't you focus on the cooking
man
where are you [\h__\h] idiot sandwich
foreign
what's up you're looking at me kind of
weird
sorry I didn't mean any offense I just
couldn't help it it's rude something
wrong with how I look
[Music]
and that's so creepy imagine someone
walking up to you
and just randomly starting laughing at
you just randomly out of nowhere and you
you always look the same it's not like
you have something on your on your nose
or so
just laugh at you because
it does it again
wow you're always so confident huh I was
thinking about how plain it is on your
face
there's confidence all over you
it's kind of inspiring to look at which
is why you were staring
I remind you of your school days as you
all stop oh no I don't mind I'm actually
a little honored to help out the Divine
one if staring at me lifts your mood go
ahead and stare all you want
but a quick jog will help get my mind
off it see you around to find one
I said podcast is another word I had in
my mind was
something else but like with some
letters mixed up
uh
we're good then good that I didn't say
it even though I would have said it
wrong
hahaha
like trimming a deck but the
it starts with
ah
now that I've turned over a new Leaf
tend to devote myself entirely to you
Makaya no need for any of them
I'm glad you were the one to find me
one more and then we can continue with
the story again
I have two Master Shields he's
captivating where is it from a farming
Village known for its single origin tea
it's a favorite of mine so I'm pleased
you like it
hmm
okay
ring cleaning ah
what does that do again
I have to go to the ring chamber for
that right
and the training I am okay okay
more Bond okay okay
uh
ah
Apollo strings there we go
[Music]
yeah ring of the hero nice and shiny oh
yeah oh today I saw
because someone sent it to me
that person always sends the best things
to me
there's
um Lord of the Rings
it's already clean well the Rings
keyboards
much better oh
with like uh three different like
patterns
one of them has Elvish on the keyboard
one of them has dwarfish on the keyboard
what am I doing here
oh I did the wrong ring
I just went with the first thing I
thought it was connected with whatever
they're wearing
um and one is uh what was that let's be
thorough
was it dark speech or quite
what the [\h__\h] I'm not quite not quite
black speech
that's what it's called I didn't even
know that has a name I didn't even know
they have their own language thanks for
always taking such goodness
I guess it's like an evil version of
Elvish
Uno keyboard
so cool they look so cool
well two of them are like kind of like
darker ones and the Elvish keyboard is
like green white
nice
be thorough now
um
really quick work of that she's so nice
have to go to class now I enjoy have fun
thank you for stopping bye
[Music]
Alfred right
huh
yeah
this ring is filthy don't you think
just like me for real for real but is
that not a waste of time you are a
strange one shush now what a waste of
time let me Focus this is serious work
polishing Rings thank you now I can I'm
taking this very seriously
okay beautiful little guard ring uh so
that's mine now
that's the right one that I have to
polish count on you
sorry for cheating on you
what
much better I appreciate your efforts oh
that's all it
solid maybe use the seal too what do you
mean the seal I see you're used to hard
work
see you Claude oh oh all these three
belong to me so should I just all do
them with kiwala
oh the sale yeah
yeah yeah
you know that's clean right oh oh it's
the same ring okay
okay uh
what did you guys just say what was I
supposed to do the master suit
uh how do I use
how do I use
I didn't know I did not know that it was
clean
inventory
and we wanted to change who was it uh
and Anna
I think
but hmm
will she really get much better if I
change her class will I want to use her
a lot
oh and not too low oh who are we
changing
to be level 10.
without an issue me
oh well that would make sense
where is it
where is the master seal
show me the mouse I can't see it
ah it's this change class
so she would uh become a Divine Dragon
because I'm a dragon child now oh well
now I can really call myself Divine
dragon
gets harder well [\h__\h] that I already did
a skirmish so whoa
whoa
I can sense a new power I will use it as
I fight for everyone as a Divine dragon
let's go
sick
really really nice
um
I can use Arts now oh
[Music]
there won't be some regret later
that's okay
um not the scrumptious then until
another time
I guess
they were already tough anyway man
I have two more Master Seals yeah I
don't know who else you knock on maybe
she's level 10 plus
yeah maybe I'll do Unico I want to see
what she looks like when we promote her
um
oh wait she can't oh
cabinet
Chloe okay okay gladly
because I've been using her a lot too
but wait she can't be
she can't be anything
why not
[Music]
you know how perfect the way she is
and somebody said I still have two
monster seals
huh
where are my master seals
wait doesn't someone even like have it
in their inventory
no
I guess we were wrong none left
okay
Let's uh oh yeah one last thing the
training
uh
huh
was it the one in the training yard I'm
confused
Arena ah
training and
the thing oh training yarn but actually
it will actually it's not the training
yard
okay
and I will not
fight again go Anna why you just have a
second
the mysterious Merchant you have to
catch up I'm citrine a daughter of Brody
and nobility a mage
[Music]
it's sad to look at that
very sad
if I win
I win I swear against challenge
ring
my loss for your game
wall
yeah
change her weapon too
which one
iron
compact
oops no
leave back what if I give her one of the
better ones not the pole ax or the
hammer or so
okay
so if I no I want that to be uh at the
top and then
order
I can't
wait issue okay but hey does it work now
that I can't make it any higher than
that it seems
it's just on the
oh a clip
[Music]
uh-huh okay okay
well depending on who her opponent is it
might not
help at all
but we'll see
hi there you can call me lady Anna
let's have a good match
[Applause]
[Music]
but hey my new
um container for my sword is really cool
yeah and I can't catch a break poor girl
to try so hard
when you try your best but you don't
succeed
when you get what you want but not what
you need
your support
okay
ah those two
yeah yeah we have to talk about what
just happened because that was [\h__\h] up
Kiana
and I was just trying to train go easy
on her what the hell
hmm maybe I'm coming at this wrong what
are you thinking about Anna
oh that's lady Emma to you wow to answer
your question I'm brainstorming new
products more stuff to sell huh yep
sweethearts day is uh
it's where couples give each other gifts
right that's the one unless
but the same old gift every year
two weeks I'm out to Market something
mind-blowing that'll bring and I have
nothing planned birthday wow that's a
pretty lofty goal oh quit treating me
like a kid and help me out here Divine
One nothing I've come up with so far has
grabbed me so I could use someone else's
input maybe I'll make chocolate again
what on stream here
something new for sweethearts day
how about necklaces
you have your finger on the pulse of the
average sweethearts day participant I
cannot unhears just played out his
flowers
it sounds like iron Mouse the whole time
to me customers don't want something
they can get anywhere they want
something one of a kind ah the constant
need to come up with Goods like that is
what makes my line of work so tricky got
it I'll keep thinking we'll come up with
something good eventually
right
oh all right all right all right here we
go
um maybe it is iron Mouse
um
yeah time to depart is
[Music]
world map
or should we do a Divine parallelog what
was that a candle
oh shall we check the shop too
the DLC oh that's the tiki no no no no
no no no no no
guys keep on telling me don't take it
but I don't want to
cause I've been told it's difficult
sorry
and do you sell the Vines
um Master sales
no
um I think I don't need anything else
that you have here
because
I have the healing of 15 healing 14.
I have a lot of vulnerries in my
inventory still I'm pretty sure so oh my
God we're good we're good
do come again
ah
what about you
oh oh you're just that dude
uh wait he said he has something new
that's new I guess
oh ah it's the brodier close
oh
yeah but you know I think none of this
makes sense if I can't wear it on the
battlefield just see it here it's kind
of lame I want to see but
no I would like to see it on the
battlefield I would like to have it as
an option to see this on the battlefield
I'll be here
I know
well
you know
okay there's no master sales anywhere I
looked everywhere
I say don't have one right now
[Music]
okay
item shop fun on the list oh well no
need no need I don't understand anything
don't eat them
I'm good I'm good I'm good
we're going to the castle
it's a long path to the castle but we
can go without interruptions oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah bye
um
[Music]
I'll give you another one
who will I take with me anyway
usually one
set of vulneries is fine but I'll give
you some extra
can he not use a javelin by the way
ah I don't have an extra travel in any
way
he can
hmm
oh wow so far he's always been like fine
without though
um
oh you might need
another set of only just just a single
one and then we're good
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
what am I doing no no no wrong buttons
okay here I go
I can get the armor flyer to Chihuahua
[Music]
wait who had it her armor Slayer you
mean like a soul
yeah would be useful
[Music]
um
and I guess we can buy a javelin for
where is he
Alfred come here
I got something nice and pretty and
shiny for you
and you go long distance attack
now goes for YouTube
hmm
would be good if he has a mini ball
right
[Music]
s from you ah true
for new units
all right
you can have
speed and luck
another Golden One what's the other
golden one I know they're all taken
you can have magic and resistance
perfect
silver one
and then you may have
HP and defense oh that Flex
for you
you are easy
gotta go for a bit later
you're going now or you're going later
traveling for Chloe oh
we're here
brodia Castle
it's really cool
I don't see any Aleutian soldiers
oh thank goodness the attack hasn't
begun
wait there's someone in front of the
gate mm-hmm he doesn't look like a guard
is it an enemy soldier no that's that's
damn hot he must have come out to greet
us German for diamond in case you
wouldn't have guessed
oh
hi
it's dude I've been waiting for you
divine one I greet you as the Crown
Prince of brodia
wow
I'm dearmont
oh
his armor is cool
I like the armor sounds I've heard so
much about you I'm honored to finally
meet the legend in person it's a
pleasure Prince diamond
and Prince Alfred welcome
queenev's letter explained your
situation thanks for coming all this way
it's good to see you
likewise I'm sorry it took a war for us
to meet again after all this time we see
now who is the better Prince thanks for
escorting our guests from the border I
know it's quite obvious it was nothing
really I bear ill news however
illusion forces attacked us at the Grand
Crossing is that right a battalion led
by Princess Hortensia
fought her off but she said something
troubling the Crown Princess intends to
assault brodia Castle
if they're after our emblem ring we may
be on course for a dangerous
confrontation we'll have to prepare our
defenses thanks for the warning all
Christ
gum father will want to hear about this
you guys should have sent a dove
first thing once you find out about that
so that they could prepare earlier you
[Music]
may have this feeling my boy
thank you Father
I wish you'd stop finding excuses to
leave the castle it's not safe out here
please diamont not another lecture
where's the harm in welcoming my dear
boy back remember the flags in the back
not moving at the top we best not argue
in front of our guests oh it's all right
please pardon my rude now you don't see
them anymore
Prince Alfred I don't mean the ones on
the
wall King
for a welcoming duel there's no time for
that we have an important matter to
discuss
as all Chris was escorting our guests
from the border illusion soldiers
attacked them huh Illusions because that
the crown princesses feel empty a castle
already making their move huh soldiers
go now Shore up our defenses some more
NPCs would be nice in the background
to make it more lively realistic
I'm done getting that information
please I don't deserve such kind words
humblers ever son
excuse me but I need your Kingdom's Aid
you want our emblem ring right
yes please
yeah
a ring of the Young Lion
fun Alfred
nice this is the man who's always
invading hallucia
it's more intimidating you're seeing
morian friend and family man he's known
to be a big-hearted guy but in battle
the demon comes out he's not someone you
want as your enemy
sometimes
Divine winner I've got the ring for you
thank you what will you do with it
I will give it right back to him the Sun
probably
rise up
oh
oh sorry didn't touch the controller for
a while
Roy
that's the red Marv
I'm Roy really summoning me that can
only mean War has begun there was a
person in there
how about that all along this emblem
dwelt in our family's ring and now you
have released him is it seems Divine is
no exaggeration huh
what can Roy do you lose your majesty an
illusion wyvern writer is approaching
[Music]
it can totally fit to the person inside
that's totally fine but with all that
armor on top of it it's funny to hear
that voice from that from that night
what
may I call upon Roy's help to defend the
castle of course
oh
foreign
[Music]
I underestimated how far you could get
into broadian territory Princess Ivy my
soldiers are on the way
I will give you a chance to surrender
before they arrive
two kitchen for that fight
go back to the castle what why if
something happened to you our country
would be devastated
please leave this to us right right why
should the king get a say in the matter
I'll do as you ask but diamont allcrest
don't you dare get killed
we won't well we'll try not to
do
you must be the Divine dragon
that's right you really are as stunning
as my sister said
I'm pleased to meet you
as is my ring oh but that looks like
lemonade Lord a gift from my father Sage
power I am sorry to say I must kill you
so nice
I won't let that happen not even you who
will fall Princess Ivy you won't
surrender them
in that case my forces will prepare for
that as will ours
how cute I'll stop at nothing to get
those Rings back
please penetrate me with those gloves
just kidding
she's so pretty and polite and evil and
nice
I mean I mean poke me
cold
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] uh
[Laughter]
do we bring where is he
oh is he not
though is he green
what
[Laughter]
do I watch the whole cutscene again
we have free
treat what about where do I get this the
the ring but not the guy
okay Skippy scoop
just keep all of it really
all of it
a ring is on here okay
that was a cool scene her flying in like
that
just let me skip
seven cutscenes in a row yeah what the
hell
okay here we go
[Music]
um
unit selection when will I need wait let
me let me first look
uh wait he's all deployed uh that's
that's him that's him
I have a trebuchet no a Ballista
I have some flying units here some here
okay maybe two archers
lady is here and she has an ax
but she's also flying
oh okay that also seems like some
special person this person too salkov
okay
um but I
don't see that much heavy armor maybe
two units no or one
only one
some Majors though
[Music]
okay
says the real boss in the map
are you
ah I said two archers
but I'll bring this Mage I think yeah
definitely stronger than the clan thank
God
don't bench best boy who's best boy
you mean Alex
hey Tia I mean she if we have two
archers you know one can be on each side
and they'll take down the horses but
besides that it is pretty weak
and I do kind of need Alfred don't I
[Music]
um
give him the longbow
you can oh wait what no wait what why
why why buttons I still only have the
one
bench Chloe
um but I love Chloe
okay
[Music]
but then I could give
well never mind never mind
okay
that's all okay
[Music]
this boy could take on another Pegasus
in a dog fight was sent me
cool event and Alfred nanny
from though cause I have yunaka she can
do that big ass AOE Hill when it gets
bad
and Fran didn't do that much healing
last time maybe once only and the rest
was all chain guarding
the rest was all chain guarding
we'll try we'll try it this way
hmm you
you okay
let me see
so do we have two arches now yeah
one will go here
um
one will go
here
I'll have to part
teams
but this one by the way
we should send someone on this one right
I forgot how this works again
um
what kind of units do you normally send
on there any any archers only oh
but then they can
eventually go through here right they
can open it up and then they can shoot
these people over here
we'll see maybe I don't know how far
that reaches but maybe it reaches
something useful
[Music]
I think the rest is fine
I'm kind of nervous but hmm
oh wait
Kiana is defeated or false Rich area oh
are they coming no no no no
no are they coming to me rather than me
coming to them
do I really have no ax user again
Mamma Mia
okay
then okay
uh yeah next user would be good in this
case
[Music]
um
should I bring Vander
his ax and horsey
[Music]
Anna kind of weak
you have accidentally engage the true
foreign
we didn't need an ax last time either
oh
you're helping to
where were you taking me huh wait uh
is this the castle is that Prince
dearmont
Amber what are illusion soldiers doing
here
they've attacked us
say amber
where are you out fighting beasts I was
but then horsey got spooked and wouldn't
listen to me I kept getting tossed
around on its back and next thing I know
here I am shut up and help us
I'll never understand how you end up in
these strange situations but this time
it works in our favor
I was just wishing you were here maybe
horsey sits this this year
so close
ready to defend the castle together
I was born ready
okay
[Music]
that's nice
if our enemies reach the gate the castle
will be there okay we can't allow that
to happen of course not
trust me I'll take care of it
defeat Ivy whoa
whoa here we go baby
my brother voices Diamond what
hi
is is your brother also kfp or just you
you should get your brother to join kfp
yo that's cool
[Music]
Stephen Foo his name is jofu
all right all right all right
I'm gonna send it here to the balista
and then besides that don't show Maybe
are they gonna try to come through here
I'm only gonna go up
[Music]
I will I'm ready assume that
they will also come from the sides
get the Archer ready there and let's go
let's go
on the left side are lancers on the
right side are sword users so I don't
have any ax people but still I'll send
um
and
I'll send you there I've got this I'll
send you
send you there
together we will defend the castle
don't split too much
okay so should I really just oh uh keep
some people in the middle here emblem
Roy's excellent offense and defense
making well suited to the front lines oh
the sink skill hold out allows the unit
to survive most combat with one HP
sync skill hold out
okay
wait is that like a passive skill
the engage weapon Lance Reaver unlike
most swords is strong against lancers
and weak against axes
[Music]
oh
cool
he just refuses to die
okay nice
the engage skill rise above temporarily
raises and units level and stats wow
the engage attack blazing lion strikes
several spaces in front of the using
against the terrain and flips
[Music]
okay well
well I was here for now as long as I
protect these stairs
I think you can step down a little bit
power blooms in me
[Music]
understood
all right you're also Frontline my heavy
armor boy
[Music]
okay I'm ready how's that looking
is that looking
uh I guess you're just gonna
for now
um
should I use an obstruction where would
I put it
it's everything's so wide they can't
really
even if I abstract something it doesn't
really do much does it
yeah
okay so just wait
very well
let me see where they go don't don't
know
oh he really goes for that right away oh
no
no oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] they all want that
am I
ah
[Music]
we will not relent until the castle is
ours
okay
um these enemies all come at once our
defenses won't hold
our Castle has a Ballista we can use
that to pick them off I'm on my way to
it
yeah sand
you can use a Ballista by placing a unit
equipped with a bow on it and you and
selecting fire but let's still have
great range and power so you can deal
serious damage before enemies got close
ballista have a limited number of user
Towers to plan carefully oh yes uh this
one has seven
not a hotel
all right bye
[Music]
it's not AOE damage though right
for this horse scene
[Music]
yeah
oh yeah okay here with the long long bow
it kills
hmm
all of the steel bow
yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
that one is never recovering again
[Music]
that's a decent level up too
okay so on this side
um
I'm gonna
go for him
[Music]
75 75 is my highest
but yeah if we missed and we don't break
him either but he would still do only
zero damage
hello
oh no please don't miss please don't
miss
up
[Music]
oh I think oh tribe of Amber or wait who
knows more damage
it seems like Amber does more damage
all right
he's got an I run great Lance oh that
was cool
like a balance overnight yeah
and it does demand the most damage too
oh but we first have to take
ah some damage is that one of those
weapons where they have to attack first
on the other side
[Music]
oh that's okay
31 Chris
wait this one has one percent
[Music]
are you calling his Lance the killer
lands because that didn't kill at all
[Music]
foreign
use a different lens on use a different
person
[Music]
there's a literal with killer lens oh
okay I'll I'll use a different one
me
okay there is a literal killer Lance
hahaha
ah 73 31. all right okay
okay one
and yet we didn't get that crit
it's okay he's broken now
and we'll finish him off but I'll finish
kind of I know this works I have another
Mage in the back okay oopsie
yeah yeah we're already clearing up that
first line easy I'll clear this one and
then the other Mage players the one in
front of me
no need for Echo yet no no no no no
calm down guys calm down calm down
see
[Music]
I have a fire
I beg your pardon
I like defending for once because we're
always so far we were always
um the one
the aggressive ones
so
just this once it's quite nice
who wants to go first here
ah
oh the flyer oh wait oh wait you're in
reach of the flyer
I don't wanna
[Music]
I don't want to move him that far over
there but oh well
[Music]
100 percent
this FB is a callback to many pass
installments where there was more than
kill everyone as a Mapco
uh-huh
Odo
[Music]
um
they said with his engagement that he's
strong against lances so let me engage
right away
and then he can
soon later oh he looks nice with that
costume
later he can
hey Lance revert that's what I mean but
it still isn't killed but
they said later he can charge it back up
okay okay
oh
yes
beautiful
no it doesn't kill
this doesn't kill either
ah
a
[Music]
oh yeah they will burn anyway at the end
of the turn right
okay
I know
demo damage
I also have to Flame Gambit but I don't
even need it now
okay
[Music]
we started a fire today
I burned them she doesn't kill oh so
okay well then I guess I have to use him
with the javelin
good that we got
traveling before the fight
burn damages leaves too with with one HP
anyway even if you're at one
more damage
I was just uh beside the Divine Dragon
actually
okay I also I also get damage from the
fire though as far as I know so I'll
stay over here
um
oh these people [\h__\h] I didn't think
about that
I have to protect
let me move over here for in case they
come over
let's just I'll just wait here
I'll just wait here
attack for 18.
oh
you bastard
intense
they just fly up there through the fire
but you get damaged from the fire too
it's not that easy
[Music]
foreign
don't kill my wife I think they're done
now with me doing damage
okay okay okay she's alive but she needs
healing
uh your knuckle Can You Reach Out She
can reach no she can't
reach well she we can we can let her
come there uh okay
I'm close enough
why can I not break him is it because he
has a shield
the other one doesn't
[\h__\h] hellmaid
how's it looking down there okay
okay let me
take this dude down with the bow
armor Slayer okay we did give her that
one mine's still alive
foreign
[Music]
let me see
okay okay okay okay I will take some
damage but yeah
[Music]
should be fine
come at me bro come hit me bro oh that's
what you get
when you let your heart win whoa
oh who the [\h__\h] is drilling someone's
Drilling
yeah I'll keep oh no wait
we uh have to move her away
I think
so that she can get healed but uh how
far can you go you can go here okay
no
this channel
doesn't even need a Time Crystal
God damn it
nah we have plenty
okay so I just I just go here okay
although I'll still be in reach better
go here
still in Rage but
maybe don't go for someone else who's
closer actually well actually
first
of all
highest percentage is this one still
though
first of all let me know then yeah
I'll have to up my weights
okay that makes me feel a bit more safe
she can attack from here
who told me wants to send out to take
care of the mage
actually it's really only those two
majors who can do it from here because I
have to send her away for healing for
safety
the Mage still would wanna go for me
yeah okay whatever whatever
[Music]
oh citrine
from free
what
wait one two
they both can
they oh wait that's fire
if
that's the train right
oh yeah okay okay because maybe if I do
this first then maybe the illusion
Soldier won't be able to
fight back when I attack her with fire
from Celine
I know she will because I first only do
10 damage
yeah okay but she won't do that much
damage to me
[Music]
mama
we missed
you were beautiful while you lasted I'm
too op
P I'm too op
okay now I'll
go here with him
because I think that ax guy
he might go straight for etienna next
right
yeah bye
and I can't protect her
when when the ax guy hits her
I wonder if she'll survive
both of them are not if I stop him right
there
[Music]
hopefully
matching outside
oh
I feel like I want to send him down
there so they
see it as an option to go to Diamond
instead
at least one of them
you know what I mean
[Music]
wait to access
it'll be fine
[Music]
he will be fine
okay and then last but not least we have
to heal
thingy where he will survive right
thank you Maxwell thank you soon
enjoy the VOD
I'll just let him
here
it's hard to decide if I want to send
them to the middle or to the side okay X
goes for Alfred
and breaks him in the procedure
here we have
[Music]
I was a close call
but that's how far that goes what is
that view what is that view no damage
for the illusion Soldier
only a win for us in this case
bad decision on the side of the enemy
take wait will they send endless amounts
of flying horses
because I've noticed several times that
the horses they will
not endless
I need to advance
[Music]
it's not endless that would be infinite
XP
how much though
yeah I can end it but
currently I wouldn't say that's an
option because
right now I feel like I'm still being
very much
um
aggressively attacked and I have to keep
my defense defensive
you know
this horsey is going a little bit too
fast for my taste
[Music]
I'm sorry
I'm gonna prepare for a lot yeah bye but
if only keep on adding is the horses
then as long as I keep my archers alive
I should be fine
[Music]
Maybe
Lily is doing a great job too look at
him look at them so your tail is
all right all right what do we do about
this situation here first of all we need
to heal
ETL
Can You Hear The Shield
hi handana
my muscles stay fixed foreign
being useful
and Yuna got two
sentence for the enemy hell yeah
I mean it doesn't have to be your death
sentence I offer only this lady to join
my team
[Music]
I mean maybe those two who are standing
beside you as well
although I'm not really interested
no I'm not really interested but if they
have to join when you're joining
then I guess
I'll take it
[Music]
just to this once
um he can't get anywhere except here
okay but that works oh you still got his
lands Weaver let's go last round last
round last round
[Music]
20 damage oh he'll he will take 10
damage though
you keep my shot
take that
[Music]
oh by the way I'm having a collab of
moment this week
and because I needed to fill my schedule
of something so I was like Hello can
someone collab with me I don't know what
else to put in my schedule
and then Moonlight replied
uh and I'm thinking either a Nintendo
switch Sports because I haven't played
that as a collab or solo either
should I wait here
actually I'll throw a javelin over there
um
or Minecraft together because I guess
you know why not but if you guys have a
better idea let me know
um I'm not sure
did you just miss
bastard
chasing it
chihuahua cannot accept that also oh I
might have to
[Music]
say fire
so I can't attack the one right in front
of me anyway okay that helps my decision
making
um
okay
but for good streaming options
are so too
yeah I was I kind of wanted to do
Nintendo switch Sports in case mume also
hasn't played it before as a collab but
she has but I still kind of want to do
it because I haven't done it yet and
um so many Ian girls have already played
it as a collab so there's not really
many options anyway
as to who hasn't played it yet
you know here until the end uh
doshio
should I engage
to make sure he dies let me see
now I feel like
like not necessary
so we got
100 percent
[Music]
all right probably deliberation
yeah that was also what I was thinking
and maybe then with someone who can do
home 3D like me
yeah maybe we'll just do Minecraft then
but um I don't know I'm not really
feeling Minecraft right now you know
hmm
you don't really move your body as much
as you think really
well I think it would still be more
interesting though
yeah that's the stuff what's wrong with
MC nothing wrong with it I just don't
feel it at the moment
I can't just suddenly snap my finger and
be like all right
I'm totally into Minecraft now I don't
want to play Minecraft Let's Go
[Music]
um ah she can't heal
it's too far
[Music]
no it's not because mama told you left
the server but
I'll stay up here
but I don't know
it's just
whatever like I don't I don't feel like
I have a real purpose right now there
you know
[Music]
hmm
oh one of them has arrived
a person why is he also so polite he
doesn't sound it looks like the polite
oh [\h__\h]
Andrew
shouldn't have put her there I'm sorry
my name is
to meet you it's not beautiful
circumstances
sounds so English
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
no let me skip all of this
oh okay
undo
I mean I'm fine with like some people
dying but not right now not this early
no no no no no
um
here she should be safe
[Music]
now what am I doing
so now he goes for Amber
and that doesn't do as much damage so we
could
[Music]
save yeah
do you crit again you have 19 yo
[Music]
yeah Special animation it's a crit
iCal
okay that's beautiful that's beautiful
so many flying horses but that feels
like it might be the last round but who
knows
eventually they'll stop coming
um
I wonder how much damage that does
to this dude oh
my choices
um
I feel like I can kill a flying horse
even without the ballistom
all right I'll do some other stuff first
we'll see how it goes
[Music]
so now an ax would be nice
I think
no a Lance would be nice oh
but even he doesn't do much damage but
he will he will break
ageu it's a it's a lady right
pretty sure it's a lady
[Music]
it's a dude oh okay I wasn't sure
I thought it was a strong looking lady
look at those eyes they look so female
to me
the bangs a little well
yeah could be a lady
um
[Music]
a very flat chested lady but those exist
I mean look at you know
anything
[Music]
engaging lend me a strength
talking out
[Music]
okay you shall
attack
first and then I'll he'll walk away and
then I'll put kiwawa in the place where
he is
[Music]
all right
oh it hurts
no the the far away horses I can't reach
I think it didn't seem like I could
oh no wait I'll actually
I'll go here
[Music]
and now
it's a beautiful
beautiful
devastating kill
so okay
I am defeated will they have killed him
anyway
Gotti
teamwork guys teamwork
hmm
my turn oh yes
no no you know what no you you know I'll
let you you go first
and how about I'm getting
[Music]
it doesn't do it all
but we also don't get hit back
yes I'm playing happy engagement it's
already the first episode
you missed some stuff but
you're also playing the new
probably already know the story
you're welcome to
watch me
playing as well
all right
chapter eight what I've attempt to Aid
right now Oblivion we started at chapter
seven right
we start at the beginning of chapter
seven today
[Music]
what Hubert
I remember he learned
good old Hubert
and I might not want to waste this shot
on this horse right now because
I can't kill the horse with anyone
[Music]
yeah
close those long distance shots are
precious with still so many horses to
come flying horses I mean
um
okay
well then
chill
you you could maybe make your way back
trying to charge I guess
you
[Music]
um
I need to sneeze
here we go I'll take in all my bacteria
on my beloved chickens
my my sister sent me uh that mean
picture today
of that super Round Chicken and she was
like and I said this
have you seen this chicken before
okay
that funny Round Chicken everyone knows
that funny around chicken man what's why
why when did that is that picture in you
or why is that going around so much
recently
[Music]
okay okay no damage this round for us
nice
I like that tenacity
what
I'll stop oh here we go she's advancing
now nothing and no one will take me down
I mean she didn't take a step forward
but I feel like that sounds that
afterwards she will
move and I can stay where I am or at
least that means there's no more
reinforcements right
[Music]
so
first of all
that was the perfect position to put him
in actually
[Music]
spreading
apologize later
so polite yes she really seems polite
the Butterball chicken meme what well
just uh I don't know what that is I mean
a really round brown orange chicken
not me I'm not round
[Music]
yeah you charge over there
and uh
yeah okay now how hopefully we can reach
can we no what
we can reach this one
but only that one okay no that's
okay
okay did I lose a unit so far
I think I didn't I I went back right
when I lost one
so looking pretty nice
I want to do something with Chloe though
I want to break this bastard
there's no one else who can come and try
and get me oh yeah don't only break him
I kill him too
go Chloe go Chloe go Chloe go Chloe go
Chloe go Chloe
she's aggressive
she's she wants to show off you know
she's looking kind of special right now
you on the other hand oh wait you can
also kill
oh
62 percent though
really low might wanna instead
do an atrocity I know I will lose one
round of this flashy thingy but
I think that's okay 77 also pretty low
though
I risk it
Fallen star I can't use it
is it because I need to be one one in
the back
oh yeah
also 77 though but let's use it let's
see
that's a cool weapon
found out not
working
enough
27 it was gonna Bumpus on me
but no no no all right are you are you
gonna comfort me now all we have left is
a few mage users magic users and yeah
okay
okay then I will welcome welcome you
women will die go for the middle
I should just
leave everyone in this position or
I'll put you down here
[Music]
she will probably go for the middle
maybe the rest will go for the sides
[Music]
the hill of yunaka now
well their HP isn't looking that bad
yet
[Music]
wait she flies actually she might go
straight through the middle like for
real
[Music]
Tristan's bow don't know Tristan
uh
[Music]
huh engage ioe heal without sacrifice
what quick James
what
is this an AOE Hill everyone who's
adjacent
it's a hill
oh I kind of want to place
I'm sorry I'm gonna actually go a step
back
and do something smart I didn't know
that
uh amber amber amber
and I can heal all three of them
ah it's pretty good
foreign
I was just gonna file a complaint at you
guys because it only healed one
[Music]
okay okay okay well then
wait
she's like citrine I'm so sorry she's
surely useful but she's like not doing
anything
they're approaching
oh
[Music]
well thank God I still have some shots
I can't reach this lady though but she
will reach me
outrage
ous
I can't
ah that was the different range okay
that's confused
all right
it's a mistake that you're choosing to
stand right in front of my face
you're right in front of me I just have
to shoot straight that's the easiest
thing ever
this emblem strength and my own there
will be no defeating me
oh
it gives a real boss vibe that we have
to shoot her with the ballista I mean we
don't have to but
it makes her feel like extra big and
strong oh
hmm
and then
[Music]
I thought so it's strong
heavy armor
don't call Heavy Armor
that doesn't look heavy to me
I see so much of her skin
all right
[Music]
I'll take care of what I can take care
of then
which is this
[Music]
uh her emblem
her emblem gives her heavy armor
oh hello
[Music]
I don't want too many people to leave
this area I
although Hill
we'll be able to take it but
no I think I want to defend yeah
take out the mage
I can't take him out though I can't
oh no I can't
never mind
you were beautiful while you lasted
take him out to dinner
take me out to dinner
we just have to take out everyone to
dinner
[Music]
oh
what if I do override on her
who doesn't do much
is that worth it
[Music]
already plants great
it does less damage
[Music]
um
check normal with brave plants
oh
not a whole
uh six plus two
I'll do more damage from the other side
wasn't a thing in this game
[Music]
huh
but she just turned around to me
oh
momentum
oh if I move forward
what
oh my God big brain to whoever told me
to do that now
oh my God
by the way I have an energy drink today
although I'm feeling more energetic than
last time I'm gonna open this up now
and round two baby oh I did all the ride
okay well that's fine
I'm drinking
Red Bull blue Edition
um I don't know if you guys have that
overseas
I would assume you know normally Austria
we don't have all the nice things but
since Red Bull is from Austria the one
thing we have is I guess all kinds of
additions from Red Bull
oh yeah but blueberry I guess is very
common
okay I'll move over here done
in case the Mage wants to take me on
can't take me on because
you'll be down
down for you can come
[Music]
down
[\h__\h] I'll take damage if I want to kill
him maybe he'll miss
eighty percent
[Music]
worth it
weapon weapon
well I will probably won't even drink
the whole can I'm really oh
I really can't no drinks like
or I don't feel I never feel like
drinking the whole thing and even like
only three sips energize me perfectly
well
one out of five odds yay
yay Elio let's go her name is kiwawa
substitute have you not been paying
attention or what
um
[Applause]
[Music]
I wish I could hurt you from here but
like
back
what do I do with you you still have the
great sacrifice but we don't need that
now
[Music]
what if I obstruct this place here then
she can't go straight for your idiom
Maybe
I can probably go around the corner
though unless I move
my girl there
should I obstruct here
is that actually not a bad move
struck
wait is this aoe2 when she's in this
form
no okay
big obstruct
it what it is
it only looked like one
I'm such a genius that was my idea but I
didn't even know it would make three of
them well I'm so smart
[Laughter]
nothing she's just doing nothing which
would be maybe more useful on the right
side let me see
only uh one flying unit left and that's
it
[Music]
and
two units over here
[Music]
oh how about I leave him here right
Amber
no better leave him
Mikaya makes Dave so busted yeah I I I I
I I did not know about this
[Music]
yeah too bad either he's a mage
you think she'll just cast some magic
right over that there I guess yeah
[Music]
oh whatever I think it was a cool move
anyway
oopsie
[Music]
what I could do I could like bomb her
right now
please
[Music]
what do you think of them
then the obstruction is useless because
she'll focus on me
I'm back how's it going it's going well
we're almost done
[Music]
reverse is just Amber too did Amber was
Amber able to reach
if Amber wanted to I didn't look over
there
[Music]
opposite
does anyone know for sure
they could
might be worth it though
oh yes
[Music]
where's the iron great Lance
but do we want the kill for Amber maybe
sorry sorry guys I keep on you know how
it is with Fire Emblem you want to
optimize everything you know
[Music]
how it is
I'll show you how it's done
what did she say I strike through I
strike fruit or I strike you
[Music]
is that it is
don't fail on me now
is that a killer Lance doesn't kill
ironically but the I run great Lance
ironically
kills
[Music]
him alive
seven times I feel like that's a
a record for me especially considering
how it's a boss fight and I instead of
going aggressive I was defending I was
waiting for them to come and it's still
only seven turns
[Music]
oh last stage was seven two really
but this one was a I was waiting
I was waiting
on them they should have let me struggle
a bit more
how is awkward MVP they only covered the
ring but the emblem is Tainted with
feldragon energy I'll have to summon him
again myself
emblem of genealogy
oh
yellow
it looks like her looks like Alia
same color theme
Pokemon Leaf
letting me swing a sword with these arms
again I will do what I can to retrieve
that which has been stolen
hey thank you leave
[Music]
brown head oh it looked red
could I have
a fake it's okay
I forgive you Princess Ivy surrender I
will not
there is more for me to do
no
you left us leave you can't just leave
you can't just leave leaves from the
border because you can't just leave
leave what is it because Evolution
Battalion stands at the ready
King Hyacinth is acting as general
he's leading their army himself what
leaving or leaving and she is demanding
to see King morion
I must face him anything less would
bring dishonor to brodia father he's
baiting you this may be a trap of some
kind go back inside ah I can fight my
way out of whatever trappy Springs I
urge you to reconsider listen who's the
father and who's the son here stop
trying to protect me so this has been
happening a lot lately
what's it all about are you worried
Brody you might lose this war or lose
its king
you're not ready for any of this brodia
to lose its king
or me my father dearmont from a young
age I was told I would lead brodia after
you died
dude he's the king
you have to let him go we have to first
of all prioritize or understand that he
has to prioritize his duties you can't
even see him as his dad
you know normally in the Medieval ages
the kids of kings and queens most of the
time they didn't even like talk to their
parents yeah they barely had like a real
father son relationship
and and their dads would die very very
early in their ages and often they would
become Kings
at a really young age like 10 or 11. so
you Diamond are already
if that happens
so don't be a little baby
imagine
a boy forced to anticipate his father's
death
think of that empty throne and that's
exactly what you're supposed to do is
returned war is here
future because it's uncertain
I'm not ready we are the assassinations
if a guy I die brodia will live on
it's not good but it's normal in this
After I'm Gone
I'm offended you expect that day to come
so position
I think I'm gonna lose
you know why you don't understand that
because you will never be in Royals
Royals
[Music]
let me be your ruler ruler
okay I'll stop
risks of Youth that's not what I meant
King Hyacinth awaits me on the field of
War his army at the ready if brodia
hides then what after years locked in
battle with the Lucia will we reveal
ourselves as cowards listen to me I will
fight bravely for brodia I do not fear
death being known as a king
exactly what do you think about this for
your country
me
who will take the throne
[Music]
don't say that
I will not let that pass
I will protect Diamond to The Bitter End
oh Christ
do you mind you could learn a thing or
two from your brother you sounded like
me when I had bronchitis
that's how he sounded me when I had
bronchitis if step into fear then we
step out of brodia
now then to the Border it seems I can't
dissuade you from this path
all I can do is walk it with you come on
everyone let's show illusion why we're
called the kingdom of Might there's no
way that the Red Bull kicks in that fast
right
with our strongest Warriors
yes I want to see you transform into a
mighty Dragon
they'll find out it's all fake I'm an
imposter uh nothing you're right yeah
she actually has never been to a dragon
turned into a dragon sure I'd like to
spar with you two Divine One
after a father gets his chance but
that's for later now we should prepare
for our journey to the Border she
doesn't know how but let me tell let me
let me help you earlier so in anime and
our picture games and all that kind of
stuff you know
you just need to be in a brilliant
dramatic situation in a dire situation
where it feels like if you don't turn
into a dragon now everyone is gonna die
and then your feelings and maybe even
your tears additionally that could
really help the whole
process will turn you into a dragon
before you know it yeah
power of friendship
power of tears
yes you can I have no idea if I can
or how just dramatic situations think of
it think of it
hold
thanks
[Music]
wise words yeah that's just how it works
the rules of anime
this reminds me of
uh at one time when we played fly emblem
free houses
in the very very end game
it was like kind of like a area that
looked like this in our our
um at school Castle thingy
or you could talk to all the NPCs but it
was like right before War you know what
I mean where we had the last chance to
talk to everyone I think it was right
right at the end
this reminds me of that it was dark
though I think it was darker than this
ah that felt so
no anxious news
it was cool Epic
Good Times
wait that was just chapter 12. maybe it
wasn't at the end it felt like the end
I guess that was just the end ah that
was the end of the like the school time
and then there was a time skip
right
Calm before storms yeah yeah that's just
so
ah riveting
oh that was it okay
the time has finally come when
preparations are done let's head
straight for the Border
oh we're already leaving brodeo huh we
weren't long here what's the
preparations are coming we will head for
the illusion born about like oh yeah no
problem for me I mean I wanted to do
progress today and I guess that's what
we're doing of course
a battle of Volusia
I can't let anything happen to my father
and my brother I have to stay focused
okay cool but before we do that sorry
guys we have to go back to Heaven hey
seal the Divine dragon is such a thrill
to meet you I can't stop stop shaking
oh I'm Amber yeah nice to meet you
thanks for the help you actually did the
last hit to die
it's pretty impressive
some meal time some nail time some meal
time all the way
oh what fun it is to go to the thumbnail
all day hey hi
Lisa in the Royal Guards
yes your majesty oh you can count on us
done a fine job protecting it all these
years new life for Vander he's slacking
off just because you're not around are
you staying excellent and when we return
you'll be treated to a victory Feast I
am coming forward to it how about some
of you soon
body strong of heart all right
here we go
they're wrapping up their goodbyes
yes Mama onto the Border
bye-bye
[Music]
I mean the Skirmish was a pain in the
ass but uh the normal story levels are
fine
so far
um
Bond conversations available how shall I
put it
I did not expect the floating island
this world is full of mysteries and
surprises hi Dimitri I don't want to
bond with you
one still shows me yellow how shall I
put because of the bond
age
views sorry sorry I was confused
hey Claude I heard you're called The
Master tacticians
set your sword aside for a bit we'll
walk and talk oh he took me very
seriously
[Music]
what
what is that a buck what
what what
no
yeah but why did it
what
yeah but what
I talked to the Matrix and I talked to
Claude and it tells me that I increase
the bond of Dimitri but I talked to
Claude in my vision what what
[Laughter]
it should say that my bond with all of
them has increased
what
oh that's funny oh man I'm so confused
I'm in a weird mood right now
time to pet this little
weirdo
somebody said milk but I don't know is
it real I'm gonna give you nuts let's
see if it's different
oh my what if it doesn't like nuts
I have so many nuts
ah
that really is a big difference but a
second hundred Bond fragments
so same amount of bond fragments but
hmm
it doesn't like these nuts
why don't you like these knots
ah
I'm a pet
sound like Ollie for a sec
and away
you happy now
are We Done Yet
hmm
just follow me now
yes it does
it's kind of slow
okay follow me come on
eh it's so slow do I have to wait for
him
it's like
I'm gonna wait for you
Master it's like a diet oh my God
oh
even though I didn't even give her the
swimsuit and this dude's
adding
oh I'm actually like really impressed
hey
I'll make sure to Splash loudly that
will ward off any dangerous animals up
here in the sky oh
the most dangerous animal of them all
QP mayonnaise
that was a great time I heard it coming
I was like oh this is gonna be great
I wanted to pick up this [\h__\h]
okay
where is it oh it's coming it's coming
can I do all my
tasks before it catches up with me we
will see quick talk to me right last
time I visited Samuel uh you were asleep
it's an honor to finally speak with you
like this
you're welcome thank you hi hmm and it's
so strange being away from broadcast I
hope diamond and Alchemist can adjust
quickly okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's stalking me
it will eat me
what do I do what do I do I'll have a
lot of pasta through first
this is a legit technique I'll come over
here
don't touch me don't touch me don't
touch me don't touch me
no quick travel is not allowed in this
game
this is the rules
it's not loud
okay now I will get a big big
advantage
he'll never find me he won't even know
where I am
nuts oh [\h__\h] the nuts will oh he's mad
at me because I gave him nuts and I'm
picking up even more nuts he'll know me
from the nuts sent
I don't want the nut scent I want the
innocent
[Music]
what is that where is it where is it
oh where's the dog
I think I dodged it I think I dodged it
no the dog is still there
what's really confused I think I'm done
with my tasks no wait there's some more
items
uh
awesome a good point oh yeah it's stuck
the dog is stuck
stupid
too stupid how do I get there
it's a normal Red Bull but I guess
um one thing I can say is that the
Japanese ones are weaker than the
Austrian or like European Red Bulls in
general I don't know about America they
probably have the same like
um amounts of taurine
I would imagine
like you guys's energy drinks aren't
that much different
attention
foreign
and 0.3 coffee in
cough cough
okay I would say I won because the dog
is stuck
I'll take it as a win
should I donate something
are we good
[Laughter]
quick
escape to escape to the arena
he was he was running up to me while I
was looking at the achievements
okay I think I'm gonna give up on
training Anna because
she's so low level that she's never
gonna make it
Maybe
she has no chance
you know
[Music]
sneaky boy very sneaky
best as a mage need to make her mage
um
you'd better buy something
I'm lapis get ready
um
[Music]
your game
I feel like she had a chance for once
but
it's okay though
it's okay well we're close to a level up
[Music]
there
someone these again I'll be your partner
um
oh yeah
[Applause]
oh my God just the thing for you
good for you oh
we want magic though because we're gonna
make you a mage someday as far as I know
she only has magic too
oh well
we have one more try I'm gonna go back
okay I'm not gonna up on her all right
all right
hi there you can call me lady I can't
use the sale on her yet that's stronger
than I look this could work too
yeah let's go girls
next time guys
finally yeah the kid matchups she's
she's good with those
[Laughter]
foreign foreign
yeah yeah I do I do yeah but she needs
to be level 10 no
to be changed
into mage
oh that's for promotion
oh should I change for now then
uh inventory
promotion
no yeah
[Music]
the dog is on the loading screen oh my
God I didn't see it
change Clash
no mates
in the second seal
foreign
do they sell that oh God
okay how many one I already won
we're not playing anymore dog go away
welcome probably not here
not here pretty well
the last time I looked I didn't have
anything
at least it looked like they didn't have
anything wait
uh huh
ah now they have it I can buy both of
them I thank you
I thank you
I thank you I'll get them well maybe one
more
I thank you
do come again
going
go away I'm a cat
[Music]
Ford I'm safe here
what was I doing God I'm so confused
um inventory
Unleashed him oh Lord he coming
needs proficiency what's that now
[Music]
she can be other things now
but not
not a mage
uh Base Class requirement how do I give
her that
now I wouldn't run from corn on the
senpai
needs a bond of Celica ah
go to Arena and train are still like
this is
with
uh
silica
gives me magic plus free
I need I need to go to level five or
six
all right let's do all of them then
[Music]
if I win
you'd better buy something does she
actually have to win the warrior it's
just the activity
down
oh my God no okay thank God because she
has no chance
in honor of meeting you I'm holding a
special sale today I'm gonna rake in the
cash
when you're selling oh what a cute
little shop you've gone to so much
trouble that I have to have a look sweet
ah so how do I get to six now the
maximum was five
tone position
skill and inheritance
[Music]
can I do it again oh okay
oh
okay so we'll just go up to six
[Music]
I'm lady Anna the mysterious Merchant
I'm Celica are you my opponent
[Music]
oh it hurts it's okay Anna you'll be
strong soon too
soon you'll have a chance
okay here we go we got it
and a training Ike yay
I can't wait to see what she looks like
when she's a mage
I really like seeing the differences in
like everyone's outfits changing by the
class um yeah that's there's a Dunkle
it's really a dog we will never know
[Music]
it's okay it's okay I like you
you you you you too
[Music]
hmm
it's lady Anna sorry
lady Anna deserves to be very powerful
too so
we will now
change her class demo
here it is everyone says she's stronger
as a mage so we'll make her a mage
oh changing
oh thank you Riley
[Music]
but I've also been playing engagement ah
nice
and I am together don't fall behind
you have some time tomorrow to catch up
some more but the day after tomorrow I'm
playing again and you know my streams
along don't fall behind
thank you
cute
she looks like a V Trooper
I wonder if I could offload my old gear
secondhand at the shop
[Music]
sorry at the same time as you now with
chapter 16. well but obviously you play
off screen
AKA you don't stream so it's always off
screen
um
hold on I want to look at her
how do I look at her
I want to look at her properly
can I look at her minus doesn't work in
this case
how do I look at her
I want to look it up give her a bond
ring for magic
[Music]
um
not until I enter a map okay well who
should I take away the
which one was it the silica ring I
really liked Celine with silicon too
oh I need more Bond rings
[Music]
I can give her Mikaya too
all right
we'll be able to focus again on killing
that healing look at her skill she's
trained to kill she shouldn't be healing
all right I'll do that
um emblem rings
I kept her with Celine okay cool cool
cool cool
swish
what else would be good for her
do we still have another Golden Ring no
but
go do some more cats and get another
Golden Ring
oh
oh your lips not taken right now
look at this both red-haired so it works
wait leave it to me
[Laughter]
ah
leave it to me that there
oops
where is she
[Music]
Anna
Makai are not belongs to you
papaya
ah cute okay I think we're ready to go
unless wait a second and I think that
was another
Bond conversation
talking to the emblem who watched over
the Divine One a film unstable okay I'm
in a fairy tale
I enjoy our chats
being around a pegasus site always
reminds me of someone very dear to me
who
sounds titty
[Music]
his wife oh let me Google does she also
look like him because then I would be a
little bit concerned
Fire Emblem
oh
[Music]
some of her like new artwork looks
really printing wow oh the one from five
of them Heroes
oh
and and the legendary kaida
from Heroes wow
she pretty she does look a little bit
like him has the same blue hair
[Music]
but let's not comment on it shall we
kind of a huge flirt too
oh no so many conversations over there
[Music]
the way they Leaf pronounced it kills me
a little every time I hear it
is that your name live
Peterson
I'm guessing it's not leave
don't worry I got you
took me a moment though
my goodness is my face so funny that
you'd laugh as soon as you see it again
forgive me Chloe though I wasn't
laughing at you rather different people
the first time we met that has me so
amused oh yes how could I forget my
first encounter with the princess you
are at the harbor with your face
scrunched up in tears it was adorable oh
yeah crying people tears oh adorable
women to board couldn't sit sail and I
was grasping at straws
that's all which is when I
[Music]
met you if there was some place you
wanted to get to go I could
sis and off we went to the tea Farm I'd
snuck out of the castle Incognito before
but this was something altogether
different enough of this tea talk now I
can remember my excitement like it was
yesterday the first of many Grand
Adventures that day is burned into my
memory forever
when they told me you were the princess
I nearly keeled over with shock I mean
how many people make friends with a girl
who turns out to be royalty
I'm sorry I hope it wasn't too hard on
your nerves oh it was an honor like I
was living a real fairy tale you might
say I started a new life that day
indeed you must elaborate oh I'd be
happy to sound like the only thing
that's going on in this world besides
war time if that's your concern
the audience wanting more
it really makes you wonder said all you
guys can talk about like you guys need a
TV or something
man
hey you knock it yeah Tio watching
people while they sleep what's your name
pumpkin seed don't say it's tea stay
real still I need to give you a
once-over oh wait uh what why what are
you looking for and what are you gonna
do if you find it so many questions
here this will only take a second
I didn't even consent to a Shakedown
you're searching me like you think I
stole something good guess how did you
figure it out
excuse me
I happen to know that you did
trouble
starting to run meal I feel like this is
oh great then I'm out
yunaka
hey wait Polo
[Music]
but if you close your eyes
Emma
you can see Anna properly Oh no you're
lapis right why is she wearing those
clothes for you because it's your casual
clothes making neat stuff out of
whatever's lying around
um yes that's me yes
I smell profit to be made the name's
lady Anna I'm a merchant who's just as
good at cutting wood as cutting costs oh
uh all right oh it's a pleasure to meet
you Anna default armor you don't have to
be so formal
maybe Anna is fine bottom line lapis we
should be in business together
I am not sure I follow that's lame why
don't they adjust it you'll be in charge
of supplying cute Goods
make a killing I'm happy you're happy
the customer is happy
win-win-win as labor you'll get your
share of course
come on please oh don't make a little
girl cry he would slow down do only a
fake crying I know you Anna
I'm a winter tide Village so some some
related to that would be nice
[Music]
or you'd want something that reminds
people of your hometown
apartment once you have a product I'll
work my sales and Market to support some
free recorded tour
okay that makes a lot more sense
[Music]
clears during her daily training beat
down
yeah as you probably did try to think of
something to make
it
all right Fran and Anna
I want to get my parents something but
what
hey friend oh hey Anna what you doing oh
Anna is so formal call me lady Anna
right
sorry I meant hey lady Anna yeah there
there you go so what are you even
watching really insists on I'm looking
for an anniversary present for my folks
a merchant do you have anything like
that for sale
Fram Fram of course I do
[Laughter]
she's gonna scam you'll find gifts
cheaper or better than these anywhere
don't trust her these knickknacks are so
cute knickknacks I bet the statue ever
looked good in their house
like
underwear raving of their names for free
hmm that's tempting you're pretty good
at this lady Anna I got separated from
my family no being on my own has really
put myself Snickers
but look close enough stock is rare and
valuable your parents will love their
gift guaranteed in that case I think
I'll get this statuette some engraving
would make it seem extra special thanks
for the business I'll gift wrap it for
you too if you wait right there you may
be young but you really got this
Merchant thing down one thing's for sure
I'm not gonna make the mistake of
calling you plainly I want to do voice
acting for a game like this I feel like
I could do this
I feel like I feel like dude did just as
well
it's not like they have like really like
super
natural this is like like anime style
voice acting you know what I mean
I don't trust myself like voice acting
like a realistic Hollywood movie or so
but this
I'm gonna do it
I feel like oh my voice could fit some
of the characters right right right yeah
maybe that's one thing I could
do
one day and
10 years
I will not say the word
cook
need a good director oh yeah yeah
definitely hell yeah that reminds me
um
actually when I was in Japan
you know one time I was recording some
songs right like free songs at Cali's
place and then it failed so I had to
re-record it in the studio but it was
like the the same room where I was like
streaming so it was just me recording
alone and then because I was recording a
lot of software that I wasn't so
familiar with of course I messed up and
kind of uh saved it in Stereo apparently
even though I recorded in mono so I had
um I needed them to actually that was
that was the reason why I had to
re-record anyway because apparently I
saved it in Stereo so they told me can
you please re-record all of these free
songs and in monologue and I'm like oh
okay so I did that and then right before
they
um like showed me and everything and I'm
like okay so can we make sure that
there's a small no and then I guess it
was recording in mono but then when I
was like
um
saving the files I guess I've failed
filed I saved them in mono in Stereo but
like in my mind it's it feels like
yeah that shouldn't be like such a
difficult thing like what an impossible
thing to change stereo from Mona
especially if it was originally recorded
in mono anyway because I imagine that
it's just like a force stereo kind of
thing well I don't know I don't I mean I
don't know it's maybe there's some audio
Engineers out there but yeah it sounds
like an easy thing so anyway then
um
I guess you know
it was like okay no way we're gonna make
her record all these free songs for her
time so they
um tried to bring it back to mono and
they did and all this good but then
there was another occasion where I had
to record something again or something
different
another
um free songs
and um
I this time
was in the studio with some Direction
audio
there was an audio engineer and there
was
someone
something like a director or so who
would give like they would mostly
actually the audio engineer was giving
um like
um
guides yeah yeah and I was like I walked
in and I was like oh man
oh man
I think I saw a clip where Bales was
talking about a similar experience I
think it was Bales and she was like
overwhelmed because it was like such a
you know real professional big recording
studio
um it was her first time now to be
honest it was not my my first time to be
in an environment like this
and so it felt like
so nostalgic and familiar to me
and it was kind of cool and I
immediately felt like comfy and
at home
um
so then I went into the recording booth
and you know there's a camera they can
see me in the recording booth and I can
hear them and you know they got those
those First Take
kind of headphones and there's like a
thingy with the all the it's like a like
it looks like a mixer where I can change
all the audio that goes into my ears and
there's a tick tock tick tock Tick Tock
sound the whole time
and anyway
so I was recording in there and after a
while the audio engineer she asked me
Chihuahua
this isn't your first time doing
something like this right and I'm like
okay actually this one's why and she
said oh yeah because like you seem
really like familiar with this and like
you're used to this and it's easy to
work with you and I felt really happy to
hear that because I guess I felt the
same like it's it's nice to record
things alone at home
at my own pace
but at the same time it's also nice to
record with someone there who can tell
me uh this this one's out this take
sounded a little bit better than this
take or this vowel wasn't pronounced so
clearly so let's redo that and can get
some other people's opinions and it's
also easy when someone else just
controls the program and and they can
like quickly delete takes make new ones
sit around put them aside and so on yeah
so
yeah and it was really nice it was a
good experience
and when I said like uh if they have
some honey for the tea because they had
some some tea hot tea but I asked it
because they have in all the places they
always have like milk
and sugar
and the brown sugar Maybe
also in airplanes but they never have
honey
what this needs to be more normal like
ever since I started doing this
streaming
job I always put honey in my tea I mean
I think I already did it beforehand
every now and then
but now that I always want
uh to do something good for my throat I
always put honey in and yeah they need
to normalize honey
it's a good sweetener yeah it's
sweetness and it helps your throat and
then uh when I asked oh you guys won't
have honey huh that's okay but then the
director or whatever
that was went out to the convenience
store to get me some honey
a full new bottle of honey so nice
so sweet
and then at the end of the recording
um
the audio engineer like said kiwawa
I have to tell you something and it
sounded so serious and I was like really
worried about something like what does
she gonna say oh my God I'm just gonna
tell me something and got really nervous
I'm like Nani
and then she tells me
you know if you take in too much honey
you might gain some weight you might get
fat and I said
for a moment my heart really went down
you know sometimes when people say I
need to tell you something like in a
really serious tone you really get
worried
okay it was totally fine but then I told
her I was consuming so much honey for
the past months and years and and many
other shitty things but so far my weight
has been always looking the same so
worrying
was very serious to her
anyway it was nice recording there
because then also nothing can go wrong
I can't accidentally record everything
in Stereo even though they needed a
little mono
and also it was cool that like for one
thing they asked me like for my opinion
what I want to do with it and
um what I think is best and so on so
it's nice to like
be looked at as a professional and as
someone who's involved with this not
just like
oh
as a vessel
hmm
yeah
Tony honey
not as a sound dispenser yeah
that was a lot of fun and then and then
and then like uh you know when I would
listen to it in my headphones that I had
in the studio everything would sound
fine and then I would go outside the
recording booth and they would after we
were like done and connecting all the
takes
they would like play the whole thing
uh through the loudspeakers and we would
all just sit quietly and listen to it
and I would like write down on my lyrics
sheet would I feel like maybe we should
switch after all but then once you once
I heard it in the big speakers
everything sounded so different to me
and I was like no sorry I'm
we don't have much time left but can I
please re-record this part in this part
in this part because I think I need to
do this differently and then since we
only had like only 10 minutes left
I recorded
so many lines again
and I went into the recording booth I
took one line I it took like 10 seconds
I went out the recording booth I said
please play it I don't even want to
listen and listen inside I want to just
listen outside and let's listen Okay
okay next one and then go in again and I
record something and I go outside again
and I listen and I go in again and I
record the next thing and then I go
outside and
so on until the very end and then
everyone was satisfied
[Music]
yeah
that was nice
yeah unfortunately I can't do this that
often because I'm here in Austria so
most of the time
um I can't
I always record everything on my own but
with like hinotai and heart Challenger
because I was still living in Japan I
recorded it in Japan
and with the producer
and you know gojo-san gave me
instructions and all that back then
I think for especially for like
um singles
when I release not just like sun covers
or whatever
if it's a single I would like to have
those kind of directions I mean whenever
I did some takes for like Sparks and do
you and so on I would send it over and I
say if you need anything retaken don't
hesitate to tell me and I usually give
them like three to four different takes
for every every line
I tell them just just let me know if you
need something done differently let me
know let me know
um but usually they never tell me to do
something differently retake something
yeah so there's never any retakes but
then I wonder like if we would have done
this IRL like together wouldn't they
maybe have had somewhere
some more directions maybe only because
you know it's kind of a bother of the
back and forth back and forth by doing
it online that's why they don't say it
I mean the the song is all turned out
great like do you lose box and so on
favorite night too they turned out great
in terms of vocals I would say but you
always wonder couldn't it have been even
better if I would have done this like
IRL and the proper recording move
oh well
who knows maybe maybe now that the
um whole
sea thing is pretty much done here in
Austria and Germany and so on if I ever
do a song again with Kira since Kira is
in in a decently reachable distance
I think Kira told me he's got like a I
think
somewhat of a more professional
recording environment than I do
maybe I could
record it there with some direct
feedback from keto hmm
but I don't know
and if we do something together again
but let me tell you one more thing
before we continue and focus again on
fighting I had a meeting to
about
my album so now we're like really going
in there for real
and I mean it won't release
anytime this spring or so I'll tell you
it will be in summer okay
need some time for everything
um but yeah you'll hear you probably
won't hear about any details because I I
think I guess for once I should probably
um keep some things
like quiet so it will be a bigger
surprise
that's much sooner than you expected eh
the album well ideally I already wanted
it to be out in winter originally like
this winter
well stuff like that yuria I will not
tell you yet
you must wait
but it's actually set in motion now
motion mentioned
um so look forward to it
is
foreign
[Music]
make it happen it's going to be awesome
thank you
yeah I want
[Music]
um
I really want an album this year I don't
know if I can do any singles
definitely not before the album
Maybe
maybe at the end of this year I can
squeeze in another single but
for now this year I will focus on the
album mostly
and then after I'm done with that I'll
see what happens I think I think I can
squeeze in another single after that
before the year ends so ideally one
single one album this year
[Music]
hmm
see when you know the thing is like I
would love to have as much of an
song output as as like Calio Iris but
you know they
they have like uh like they're they're
being pushed to to do that Cali is with
a label iris is a v singer so that's
their thing that's what they're being
pushed to do and they get all the
support they need for it
um
I mean I also get supported by janma you
know but everything takes more time and
uh
it's obviously not the focus so it's not
that easy I can't just blast out all
those signals and all that concerts and
whatever endlessly even though I wish I
could well I'll do I'll do what's
possible and what's in my power
soon as nah
I'm excited I'm excited
looking forward to it
now off to the Border oh it's freezing
here wow it walks so far there's like
basically nothing in Broad here what the
hell
there was like so much more going on
here
why is Brody so empty
what's about what what's that on the
left side that looks like a like a
colosseum
are they still gonna add some things
later
when I continue on the story that's for
later okay that would be weird if they
didn't use that
oh and down there there's also something
um
they're nine
nine
not done yet
okay uh I think we're ready to begin the
ah no wait you guys said something about
the tombs for
uh uh for Anna
soda Anna
um I mean I think if I optimize her
then it will just give her everything
she needs anyway but I'll see
oh okay uh I'll I'll take yours sorry
you're officially retired I think I mean
it was good to have you in the beginning
but I don't think I'll be using you
anymore
um I'll take the search one too thank
you
I found that one would be nice can I buy
that in the marketplace
and the state right
do I have do I have another Stave
[Music]
um
um who is that oh yeah
ah wait I can take yours
oh
do I want the obstruct Stave or do I
want to give myself
um a thunder tomb
yeah thank you guys there
I think I found it too might be nicer
she can't use it
it's search with him can she get
the opposite
wait let me check this job
I don't know
item or Armory Armory right
uh
sorry all these menus still kind of
confuse me I keep on like using
r for example so I'm trying to be
careful
are to switch like these things oh
there's fun one is like okay so for
founder I understand the special thing
is that
um the range is bigger
oh wind is effective for flying I didn't
know that what's the special thing about
surge it can only be used in clothes
come ah
so it's it would be stronger using it
right in front of a person than when I
would use fire
was it really be
church only has one range search name
that misses it's only close comic but it
hits harder it never misses really
even when someone's like in a Thicket
well that would have really helped me in
the Skirmish that I did
it's right
Unlimited
infinite
what does that mean
what does that mean though
I can hit infinitely
wouldn't help her squishy oh okay well
then we can get rid of that I guess
and get Thunder
and then maybe or the staves oh stapes
are items
ah
uh I tell my shopping
[Music]
wait I don't need to buy it though I
could just take it
it's always the setting up yeah we made
it now
what she was cute with her ax but
everybody said make her mange make her a
Mage and now I made her arrange and
we'll see I guess I'll bring her along
right away
store that and then ideally I would want
this one
this one okay perfect
I didn't tell you that
okay
I think it's probably the right choice
of everybody
tells me to do that use up that Master
suit while you're at it
wolf right oh that's cute
Master sale on on on her
anyone level 10
um
uh three eleven
he could be
Maybe
I'm Chloe Chloe too okay I wanna I wanna
Advance her
Griffin Knight
ah
is she gonna be a griffin Knight
that's so cool
[Music]
cool no more Pegasus
oh by the way I I watched Energies
mokopee stream
oh cool it's like it's like where the
World of Warcraft
oh
nice
and the more copy
um I'm gonna be honest like from the
advertisements it looked so much better
than what it actually is I like her new
outfit too
um
[Music]
so what I saw now I must say I talked
about this for a moment with Amit too
uh
what why what we would en has for home
pretty is better
because
first of all no finger movement
second of all it also can't really like
capture jumps well
which is also a problem that we have
with our home Freddy though
um but also like other things like
um bending the knee or bending the arms
or so on
those kind of things our suit does
better at home
so mukubi really got my hopes up but
uh no you I don't think you can hook
them both up at once I mean you can you
can but you can only use one of them at
once
um
if you look up the
video or so you can see it it has like
six trackers I think or so
and it's not a suit it's like trackers
that you attach to what you're wearing I
guess
um what's what I have is a suit which is
not as good as the suit in the studio
that for example I recorded my new
YouTube short in
um so definitely not on that level
and honestly our suit isn't much better
but I see definitely it's
somewhat a little bit better than mokopi
at first I was like oh my God this is so
nice hey yo what I can't get it because
I'm not in Japan and it was a little bit
like whatever but now that I see it
wasn't that good anyway I'm like okay
whatever then
didn't need it I guess
okay are we ready now
are we ready now
[Music]
I'll just give you this one
here we go
like everyone got so hyped over Moco
beat because that advertisement looked
so good I really got hyped we got hyped
in our Discord someone posted it and
we're like oh wow wow this looks really
good
Diamond where's the king that's not
something to the front line dancing
either to wait here with the rear guard
will do
oh ring you didn't give it to your
father
another ring
tried
you wouldn't take it
the king said that if anything should
happen he wants you to keep my ring safe
but what if he needs it
father wants a fair fight not to say
that using the ring is unfair but we
brodians have a particular sense of
Pride he wants to stand in his own
strength and thus just to respect that
ah I understand
I'm just not sure our enemies will have
the same code of honor let's be at the
ready
push comes to shove I want to be able to
help it a plan agreed it looks like the
battle has begun
oh
is this Game of Thrones
[Music]
hmm oh
cool cutscene your invasions of my
country come at a very high price
now
now you'll pay it
do you really think you
think you had the might of protea
yes my Army he's amazed and you're heavy
armor dude you should know
he'll wreck you
[Music]
[Applause]
he's letting you play with him though
well then is that all the power Your
Dragon's got
the Healer he is not yet at full
strength
not until the ritual ritual
reach for the one by which we all
reignites his True Glory she's gonna be
Invincible in a second
Sovereign blood
it's sauron's power flowing from him
what
no no you're bad at that whoever you are
seen you before maybe no
no
she looks like a good lady
Evelyn father come on there's still time
to rescue him
Evelyn her new name will be Evelyn
I want to do your majesty see you later
heavy armor Gothic Lolita
okay
whatever the cost you will hold them
here I need them to one day track my
kissy mouth
don't forget that ring was given to you
by our Lord sombron
your failure to protect it was a brief
it is your duty to reclaim the ring now
I take my leave to illusion the snow the
winter area is so cool
so
you want me to buy time for you as I die
here oh wow there
I die for you father that's your dad
you're not going to stop us we have to
get King morion back from them right
before unless she wear them
she is the microphone
[Music]
we're all feeling very funny today
aren't we it keeps getting
dragging away father like that
what could King Hyacinth be planning I
don't know but with so many of the
corrupted this will be a tough battle
foreign
[Music]
are there any more joining me later hmm
um
wait
let me see what are we dealing with
uh-huh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that Jade oh that's our
assistant
I mean she's all alone here
and whose side is she
was she all alone there
is she gonna be okay
we're like all alone like it's are they
not gonna go for her hopefully not
a little house
a lot of lances and this this this Trio
again a lot of accents
that's this axis but I see basically no
swords except like
this one dude he might be the only one
of the sword
oh
which means
uh what's effective against sword lands
right so what we don't need is lances
one or two
well so I bring swords and ax
and
um
one Archer one Mage or two archers one
mage
because I don't see
heavy armor wait well
okay that's heavy armor
That's Heavy Armor but I don't know
oh wait are these also
oh these are all legit heavy armor oh
okay yeah I'm definitely bringing Anna
oh that's a lot
I want to bring two pages I think
[Music]
and maybe then if I bring two Mages then
I might have to chip out on the archers
[Music]
okay
everyone is armored as hell down there
yeah I do have the uh oh yeah armor
breaking weapon whatever
still with so many
Who Would I bring I guess oh yeah so
Citron
who am I gonna leave behind I just
recruited her but she's Lance and Alfred
is always
also kind of helpful but maybe no Alfred
this time
what do you think guys
he's a sword we need ax Stone so Louis
actually this time
I'm leaving behind and I'm bringing I
think Vander because his ax and Cavalry
I mean
keep our friend remove Chloe
Alpha will be better than our Cavalry
okay
so Alfred instead of instead of Chloe
what's she again she's she's sword okay
Van Der Hart no it's not worth using a
van at this point
who else I have uh push your own is
level five that's way too low uh maybe
lapis then I have at least a sword
fighter
uh my other choices
not looking that good because I have so
many Lance users
now this is not bad yeah
the blue is removed under
[Music]
restores and ax in disguise
uh-huh
oh I know
yeah I don't feel good about benching
her because I just promoting a turn yes
but they said Alfred's better in this
case
really good don't touch it
well I got a bench somebody
can drop you know for growing
you know
you're not coming
who's Yuna
I guess
yo she has a killer ax in her inventory
where'd she get that from
should I
hmm
okay
well you guys are not sure about Chloe
or
Alfred but leaving yunaka behind
[Music]
um
I really need two archers
maybe not
okay this is the team
I'm going with two Mages there's too
many but I think I can drop an Archer
and uh
what the hell had that
killer why do we have to kill ax give
that to someone else
trained
x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x x ax
doco no ax users except Van Der and
Pusha is this for real
I need ax people
oh it's part of the Ring
and the slaves ax ah okay
[Music]
it can be in your inventory I was
wondering where the hell did you get
that from
um
[Music]
okay okay time to go
give Chloe is tough
there's always something uh
do I have one
I'll just buy one
uh
why is it in items
[Music]
great deal okay mending
reward what's that
space weapon Mana magic will teleports
the user up to five spaces away
Lumi there's some new stuffs here
hmm
cool
and yeah I think
um
what it
no all the special emblem rings are on
the people who are going to battle so
we're good
foreign
[Music]
I wonder if I'll be able to find her she
has an ax couldn't be a worse time for
meditation
but I've got to clear my head
I hope she joins my lineup afterwards
ah
sneeze Google because I really need a
really and especially because she also
seems like a heavy armor
I really need that oh [\h__\h] I didn't
switch the
lineup but okay so I guess you're going
that side
[Music]
anytime
you're going that way I guess we're yeah
this time we really have to split
[Music]
I don't know
I'm gonna come for her if I'm just maybe
better off just letting her wait
should I go aggressive mode I'm
listening
oh look at her
[Music]
wow
Fluffy Bird
lion Bob
[Music]
they will come for her but she can hold
up for a few rounds
okay okay okay
ah
um
[Music]
I put her in a bush
let's go
I want to balance out everything so that
I have
one lands on each side
one horsey on each side one Mage on each
side oh okay I'll stay
here
well by the way in terms of healing
was my halo right now whatever you need
it's not you not gone anymore
oh Anna oh yeah okay you
was more of a mage but she's also a
Healer so she's a Healer Mage for me now
she can't do the chain link though
that's only for real Healers
so some
okay balance I guess so all right you're
going over here then let's go
oh I can't control the green lady anyway
that's good this will not end well oh
self-awareness did the king perhaps
Grant you
you heard him didn't you
if I want a ring I must reclaim the one
eye made unless this time with no
reinforcements we must make do if you
want to leave
I'll understand oh what will you do
Stars choice but to stay
even if I know it's hopeless even if I
know I will die
oh that's that's kind of sad head to the
northern and southern Force the
corrupted are standing by there
so much for meditation now
think you can get through my defenses
you're defending up here all alone does
she even know that she's getting help so
sad but damn Shield
and your armor WoW
that does sound like her
no way that's perfect
she must have been asking herself why do
I get all these like strong Shields
wearing heavy armor blonde ladies as my
jobs
calm down
what
foreign
so this was really not a nice encounter
here that's really not fair
[Music]
oh wait that's the ah
see right now
the Archer would have been really nice
this will do
you'll have to
alphan destroy too
see they really need more good voice
actors in uh for like anime and games
and so on so I am kindly offering my
services
kindly
should I engage him already
I might emblem engage
while having her that's so mean
you're so mean
not like I care
why does that not kill you
[Music]
um
I'll go for you first
I will win
oh that was a waste of an AOE
you're right I forgot about the AOE God
damn it he's new in my team
[Music]
um
and I might rewind
maybe if I do it uh it might not be so
much of a waste if I do it like to the
the soldier on foot
because
there's someone standing next to him at
least
or even the one flying next to him
[Music]
I'm so indecisive
I can kill this one and maybe with
engaging I can kill this one
so what about you what about you what
about you oh you can also kill this one
but
um oh you can do a lot of damage to that
one too
oh
my problem is though that Chloe can't
really help because she will have to
heal herself and maybe even like retreat
a little bit
foreign
[Music]
take down this one for now
was that too much
[Music]
but he couldn't even get a kill with the
engagement
she can though
all right
let's see you dodge this
for breakfast
okay I had to stop
so so we're cleaning up though so I
think it's not too bad
again
okay
and then we're done on that side
ah
next up okay at least we have an Archer
here
that cannot one shot the horse
no you can
to the steel bow you can I would have
been surprised if you couldn't because
you were pretty strong last time
just don't miss
thank God apologize later
his movement is so funny oh
strength magic decks speed
[Music]
okay
I guess I'll break this one even if it
doesn't do much damage
where can you get this on PC I don't
think it's
on steam or so Fire Emblem engage
is that switch only
[Music]
um
do you think the other mange will wreck
Celine
Nintendo is so stuff there you go
I mean yeah I guess I'm somewhat playing
it on PC because I'm looking at my PC
playing it
Capture Card Capture card
s
I think she was gonna be fine
okay
[Music]
fire
melts that snow
we want to see the beautiful nature
again although I mean snow is beautiful
nature too I love snow
you know what I mean
I want to see them flowers
[Music]
so close but I mean
it's okay because we'll just end it with
Anna
[Music]
congratulations good for you
I hope that's not your whole race wait
is that a race I guess is like a a
monthly raise right
well thank you so much
very kind of you
okay
here
one time is a bonus okay
well hopefully
use the race for yourself
although I'll take it
thank you so much
mama
[Music]
stomp stomp stomp stomp
imagine her saying
some
Mystic art from kisara by accident when
she's supposed to acting oh wait sorry
wrong job wrong wrong character
feels the same for some reason
sorry I met mixed up some some of my
scripts
Chloe's suffering so much now
oh dear those
[Music]
I won't be much use in the state do we
just accept that I don't know if I have
to rewind I have to redo so much
what do you think guys
um
[Music]
rewind
cool
still pretty early yeah
[Music]
Chloe
wait she wasn't attacked by one of the
single one remaining no she was attacked
by two people
where did the other one come from
um
thinks the train was fine
you guys said I should just finish off
someone with her
but you know I healed her how high are
the chances that she'll survive when
she's not healing herself and instead
attacking because I could have [\h__\h] I
thought we only left one person behind
but don't you got attacked
no it wasn't one unit that attacked her
twice
or was it two units I'm not sure anymore
move her away
okay here she is safe
yeah I don't think she'll survive
otherwise she needs a break
everyone's just bullying her
okay so what did I do before
did I engage kiwawa
dying cage
thank Cliff you're not dying I killed
this dude
for me
and then
hmm
oh no I did yeah I kept two of them
alive
nah
I engaged with both of them lend me your
strength
what you doing
so what you doing
[Music]
this one
hi it's jumped up on the table you're
welcome here and you can lay down
what are you doing
[Music]
good chunky monkey how are you doing how
are you doing
you're getting comfy yo yo
wow
is that what I did before
[Music]
is that what I did
stand down okay
oh [\h__\h] did I do it the other way around
did I keep this little
oh yeah I did
yeah I kept two of them alive
[Music]
foreign
blocked a soldier for citrine
[Music]
yeah okay
I'll
come over here
um
[Music]
first
this
just retracing my steps right now
I have no choice but to win
no Chloe should be fine over there
pretty sure Chloe is fine oh he still
gets the same level UPS even though we
changed the rngs didn't we
was that set in stone
oh what did I do next
hmm
[Music]
I think I broke him first
fixed for this battle
Naruto
so I did that
then I'm since I can't reach that dude I
guess I attacked with Anna
there's some fire
kill the movana
damn it she could have used those EXP
changed up the order
can reach it that's what I did that's
that's indeed something I did I remember
that now
all flowers eventually wrote
um
now I guess Alfred gets the kill
it's all right
[Music]
now let's hope that everyone will
survive I don't wanna rewind again
[Music]
oh please no more playing around with
crony
[Music]
oh
did she just use
Thunder on me
[Music]
foreign
after
[Music]
after this Victory Hallelujah
all those special characters are coming
for me now okay
okay okay okay
damn it
um
I'll go from the side
[Music]
can we okay it's roasted tea
or uh possibly even if I go from a
distance actually
the arrow attack
[Music]
Fallen star
would work too but I wonder
what happens if I attack normally
okay
then
I'll do the following Star Tech
wanna see archery
[Music]
huh
oh my good way good way good
oh [\h__\h] is a flip and we got a critical
nice flip
I saw Emma's waxing stream by the way
she did a flip there too
[Music]
um
we're almost there kisara
[Music]
can I walk through here
like is this just
um can I just not walk further because
or is it really blocked off
canva reduces the movement not a hotel
hmm
so I'll just go from the side chunky
walking what are you doing just lay down
good good turtle dove your
I think I'll use the
the vulneri
[Music]
consider it done and you also need a
vulnery
I'm gonna come back follow up again
and also use a vulneri
damn
she can heal everybody else she also
needs to heal herself
you know prioritize it's always going to
take yourself
take care of yourself first before you
take care of others they also tell you
that I think in airplanes put the mask
on yourself first before putting it on a
child that's next to you yeah
[Music]
yeah
it's not worth it
I think
I don't know is it
[Music]
can you one hit
that's the protocol
ideally you would go all the way here no
maybe not
decisions just
what the [\h__\h] am I always pressing
okay I'll do it
maybe I'm in 72 percent
actually uh 70 in this case maybe maybe
he'll miss
come on come on
[Music]
I'll apologize later
Longbow on alcress
um
no I guess not
[Music]
maybe next time
no he said apologize later we'll get
through this
[Music]
probably on ATM we'll have to switch
around because I guess
I wonder if later there will be a better
Archer to replace
etia with
[Music]
you
maybe I'll engage
uh
yeah okay
yeah I mean besides out Chris like a
second one because sometimes would be
nice to have two archers is what I
trained for
maybe like not a normal Archer but like
a Archer on a horse or so
uh Pegasus
maybe it would be nice
for some variety
don't replace it here
[Music]
stand strong
reinforcements are coming
Believe in Us can you hear us
in the distance oh they go up on those
Towers
all right time to attack eh
bring out the corrupted are you playing
AOE or what
are you vampires
there's people in the tower how many
only those two are
what if I would have stood up there
would they have been on my team
spawners
like what how many
car seat car seats
uh
if you're still there they can't spawn
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay what's effective against these
thieves
just first time I feel like that's so
weird
only reach this dude
oh never mind I can reach him so it's
better probably to kill the top one
first
or is it
this
would take down
one unit
better to let them go closer
[Music]
guys if I kill this one will it just
spawn another one
she would be Invincible there hmm
[Music]
no double spawn don't think normal spawn
okay
[Music]
it's good
you're saying I should bait them
then
say the word
am I ready yet to fly over there though
[Music]
not
but I told you I just wait
[Music]
let me see which one is the closest
if I do that
I'm in
so close then
[Music]
this you guys always tell me to push
that but you guys I think you need to
tell you to stop telling me to push that
because it will never really help me
somewhere okay
I'll go through this way
came over no what are you saying
no game over
hmm
if I stand up there even though I don't
need charging will it still like charge
me regardless and and like use it up
because I don't want it to be used up
oh hey this doesn't really do anything
anyway never mind
although I guess the announcer would be
nice nonetheless
no okay
allow me
[Music]
okay
I thank for the rest
I'll kind of just wait close by
what's our move
although I need I need to come I need to
have I need Hatton
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I need
them to come over so
[Music]
guess I'll just be chilling here well
not here
maybe here better
is this Emma in the woods I guess not
ah
come in this whoa but I'll go in with
yunaka
good luck lapis oh
it always has those
Asterix Asterix
Asterix and Obelix Princess Ivy stays I
stay oh
[Music]
Precision
that's a crit oh
think I'm going to rewind that I'm down
that if I stay alive I can keep on
fighting why are you sure stinky chunky
monkey
um
why you're so stinky
now
it's really stinky
I think when she went to the toilet she
may have fun peed herself a little bit
that's okay I don't judge
it's a lot of fluff that you gotta like
push aside you know not like she really
can push it aside
happens to the best of us a satisfying
ending oh she actually managed to kill
one this time
so you didn't need my help after all
uh but I'm going back
and
who died lapis right
uh no what
lap is died
short time memory
hitting strong okay so in that case
you think she would survive if I put her
in this this Forest oh she can't okay
well you know what I'll
I'll just put her here then
what did I do with you
I want I know I know
[Music]
was she not properly in the woods I
thought she was but here is the woods
I think I didn't completely Place her
there after all
she was she wasn't she I don't think she
was
now that I look at it again I don't
think she was
and now he goes for
diamond
and achieves now
and I also achieved nothing
oh let's see how that goes
30 and he still hits
30 percent
sure sure sure
[Music]
oh yeah
oh one two three six
it's like I won in the lottery
midday
that was so worth it I won't forget this
yeah yeah yeah
alrighty
no I thought I would like come over here
with with my Mage too to help you but
you don't really seem like you need the
help
[Music]
no oh sorry what am I doing how rude of
me I am Jade a royal Knight of brodia
she's cute
may I join your ranks Divine one of
course I just
last week I'll show you why they call me
the Iron Wall oh
that's a cool title to have you
definitely seemed very sturdy there
thanks girl
no problem
foreign
[Music]
I won the lottery because I found you ah
yeah yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah it seems like we get her as a unit
I mean you can always kind of see
that's the better designed ones are
obviously units the ones who have an
actual name
engage
[Music]
oh
it doesn't kill
all right I'll I'll I guess I'll bring
him down to one HP and then I get the
kill of someone else
but then I feel like we could just do it
without that
because if it needs two hits anyway then
maybe I shouldn't Waze
it
[Music]
I'll do this my prayers are with you
oh ah he can charge right there
you can stay there
finish him off while he's at it perfect
placement so cool thank you for putting
yourself
in that situation
[Music]
I appreciate your cooperation
Oblivion if you want you can join kfp
AKA I can't take any Chihuahuas back to
princess fire
emblem
charged again
meow
meow meow
ah
um
[Music]
and get you again maybe
questions
how much do we do then
oh
thank you chaos fire platoon
interesting oh is that where the name
Splatoon comes from splattering platoons
or so
[Music]
foreign
interesting
[Music]
now I wish that would like crit or
anything because this is so
regrettable
we're so close to Greatness
I know to take more damage when they're
poisoned but this already is taking that
in account right
[Music]
hmm
oh wow
now
he'll die when I counter him
it will be like that sometimes so now we
have
this little battle over there all those
minions
take him down
[Music]
how many of those spots are there by the
way one two three four
okay you're charging here
uh I don't think I can recharge all of
them right because I have like I think
five emblem rings and there's
four of those charging
plates here so I think the one I'll keep
for myself for a little bit later is
Celine
Food City
uh also
you didn't use his override yet
should I use it now but it doesn't
[Music]
I want to use it on someone that gets a
kill out of it
um
what do you mean one turn left to what
oh yeah I know it's multiple online but
I can't use it in this situation because
I can't get past this guy because
there's a a mountain wall
I might as well use it
[Music]
I wish I could go diagonally because
that could work here
okay
if Princess Ivy stays
hello
I put myself on the title title thinking
I could recharge but wait afterwards I
can still move right now I'm on the
other side
hello from the other side I can't walk
over there now
I might rewind that
[Music]
I was thinking about you know I want to
be on that tile
I had that in mind
I have enough rewinds we're good
[Music]
if Princess Ivy stays
one strike will decide it off
um
[Music]
whatever it's okay
we're staying here now he was gonna make
himself confident also you know the
other Advantage is that he'll be in the
woods you know
in case someone wants to hit him
hmm we can definitely take that dude
down just wondering what combination I
want to do it
I think I decided
I think I did
I'll fire first and then I'll shoot with
the Archer
I'll get some crit and coming I'm not
letting him touch me not a single time
not a single time but one second but
before I do that
checking
yeah okay
um
77 81
. so either I just accept the fact that
I'm getting damaged anyway and then in
exchange just do more damage to him
however
here he has less chances of hitting me
also 85
.
decisions decisions
oh I'll take the chance
[Music]
go ahead hit me first
that's what you get in exchange
I pushed him back
so strong
Lumpy's so strong
defeated
Anna Anna gets the next kill
I must protect Princess Ivy
it's the next one
TM
[Music]
um
what's today engagement
because I said I'm keeping
her anyway what about her yeah and Kaya
Kaya engagement does not help me
if I stand here if I just stand here
will you just leave me alone and hit the
other ones
foreign
[Music]
don't think such assumptions that are
gonna make me cry
level up
as long as I do something one two three
instruction
of Justice
look at that would you look at that
no one went for my baby I went for
Alfred and they missed and they go for
lapis and it's not
looking that bad Eva
what's that get behind me effect
all right all right all right all right
you need to charge right so let me um
put you here
Shield canvas would only it says first
long range of texture no damage but it
would only be for the upcoming round
right if it doesn't
like if no one hits me it doesn't like
carry over to the next round right
okay
well then
okay Anna
Anna do enough damage
you you sure okay then we need someone
weak enough to not kill either oh
[Music]
they're all too strong
something weaker
no
no they're strong
I'll I'll get some damage from it though
yeah
for you Anna I'm letting lapis take an
extra amount of damage
for your exp how nice is that maybe he
even misses Lucy
foreign
[Music]
well thank you
nah
I'm pretty tough you know
sure sure you are everybody else could
kill that enemy in one hit but you
couldn't but sure you are tough very
tough you are
foreign
don't waste it on me why so why so
pessimistic oh one two three four five
six seven don't make me feel like 11.
I'm gonna make a burrito today by the
way after stream
oh it's already 10 p.m holy [\h__\h] I think
we're ending after this because it's
almost six hours of stream time and
tomorrow you know I have an earlier
stream so I need to wake up early
prepare early to hand cam stream so it
takes quite a bit more preparation
[Music]
we're just going to show around to you
stream ironing time
should engage Anna and use great
sacrifice and we'll move
oh yeah I know about that but I don't
feel like it was necessary just yet
um
oh yeah this also isn't necessary
because you have to wait one more time
I should have healed him though
what am I doing
what am I doing with my life
well uh
[Music]
I
on it
I guess I'll put you up here
feels dangerous though
and then
hmm
I already talked today
we're running out of ownery
[Music]
I don't know how I feel about this
um
but
if it goes bad then I'll just redo it
she doesn't get the terrain bonus oh
[Music]
okay but I have oh
I have my Mage buds
so much
the Mage can't do all of the work
they're coming from both sides
nothing
okay okay okay
girl it's time to go back here
I guess
very well
oh
take
care of
give me an order
ah
fine
heal
Mommy
[Music]
foreign
have her kill the Mage the Mage killed a
mage
[Music]
Diamond AOE
interesting also she can do a lot of
damage them
start
but on it
okay wait wait wait wait wait
I want to redo
yeah I'm gonna move
um
[Music]
okay that was maybe unnecessary because
if I want to want him to go up there and
then first one of them
or both have to move like but I if I
move Chloe I also want her to attack but
wait wait
[Music]
never go here but once you be
affected by the fire What if I
should be affected by the fire then
might be but I was gonna heal in the end
of yunaka
where should I go for
so if I do the the fire with
um diamonds I wonder who gets more
damage from that
[Music]
yeah confused I guess Anna is healing
sorry
[Music]
mage
I'm sorry
[Music]
sorry for L search oh that's like a
better search I assume
okay engaging again
very busy
[Music]
oh
a steel sword
Lance river is okay
there's my opening
yeah
oh for [\h__\h] sake
now I'm making more mistakes again
oh well well well
a real problem is
oh maybe I should actually
kill
first
I was gonna go closer so that the the
one in the back
stays in the fire but I guess the fire
is only for one round two
so whatever
[Music]
oh Shield
I can do some damage with the killer ax
but that's
although she will survive with one HP
and then if I'm gonna heal afterwards
and I guess it's okay
[Music]
there's no crit's chance maybe he even
misses oh no okay
I'm healing it okay okay okay we want to
make use of that killer ax a little bit
um
[Music]
I guess they don't really need that much
help down there anymore when I arrived
they're already dying like the flies
anyway
so
all right before I heal with Anna
let's see if we can you know get some
more out of this
we'll take down this dude
yeah I will not forget your looks
oh sorry should have checked the echo
Maybe
thank you
[Music]
that does a little bit but
yeah bye
I would prefer to do some magic right
now on them because that's what
I need I'm prepared
[Music]
that's what I really need maybe I
shouldn't have risked that stunt down
there
oh yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
ah
I wonder how much damage override would
do
Emperor engage
yeah no I but right now I need her magic
is what I'm saying to kill that heavy
armor dude
it's like nothing that's not worth it
I just put him up there
on the mage
oh yeah on the Mage it would actually
make some sense
the iron lands
good job
this is what I trained for over right
behind Mitch oh
that way I would go back on the fort
spend the grand magical stuff to use it
permanently cool
[Music]
was that even possible though
I'm already down to five everyone's
now it's four
hey but no that's what I saw that
there's no spot of it um ah wait he can
go further never mind
okay
I'll do it if that makes you guys Happy
raise your sword
very cool thanks for the flex
[Music]
uh okay
not just stay on there
okay
I know I wish I could like
put someone here to protect
um my Archer
I guess the only thing I can really do
is put the archer in the wood
um
[Music]
I think I'll
foreign
[Music]
like that either
the constant shall be left with one HP
is it that camera everyone's healing and
they just focus on kisara
and I need
her to fight in the next round though
what should I eat for dinner kfp
of course what else
your only choice anyway okay
um
hmm
oh unless you're screaming all still
I'll still stay
you're done charging
you go
where's the dinner they're right there
look in the mirror
it's in the chat oh oh oh
you'll pay for that
bastard one more
in your face
all flowers eventually wilt
yum yum yum
oh another one oh [\h__\h] that might end
badly
for peace
[Music]
I don't know if I can even do anything
about that
if I rewind simple enough
I think I might just accept that one
[Music]
uh I think we'll be fine losing one unit
but we gotta be careful now
[Music]
I'm not going back now we're almost
there it's like five units left
unfortunately oh that means we
can't
do the warp bomb
but it's okay and that fear and there is
acceptable exactly
[Music]
now here's the problem that I saw coming
I would desperately need her magic I can
kill that dude but the question is can I
kill the others with these three units
Powers unite Powers United
[Music]
where to I don't think so
and then he will go on to kill her
afterwards
[Music]
you see my issue I saw this in the
future
[Music]
and then ended up sacrificing it yeah I
hope you weren't playing on classic
not if I body block him for you anything
yeah I can do that
oh my second yeah okay okay
[Music]
writer's pain
go for a Rider's Bane so it's actually
gonna do some damage me first
I think the the
path is considered blocked now
right
not give up
put some fire under his ass
[Music]
work
level up finally for Anna what one two
three four five six six
look
hmm
what's the word
[Music]
uh attacking with her
ah next he'll just go for her I'll heal
her then
I have to
hold out
yeah I have to survive if I heal myself
up then I'll probably survive or he
might go for the Archer who knows
in any case oh wow
that does a lot of damage to him
surprisingly
[Music]
that's really it
is
Welcome to the
[Music]
um
that you guys just um
how far can we go
this far
okay
go ahead uh I'll send you here we're
done on that side right
yeah okay
uh
she has a staff right
yeah okay then let me
um
put five more down her right next to you
foreign
I'm making it weird
no not me you can put units on top
because for free healing there's healing
on the castle
[Music]
oh yeah well no I don't need we're ready
to advance
how's that
hmm
no okay
[Music]
meditation enemy face are they gonna do
anything
oh yeah this I
still exist
good job lapis good job I'm so proud of
you
so proud of you
[Music]
now
we can give Anna another kill but I
honestly just want her to heal herself
so that she's ready
I'm sorry guys you might not like it but
uh actually I moved here first
I'll put her up here
huh
wait wait wait wait wait
ah there we go
because the vulner is so weak but at
least the castle will give her some more
[Music]
um
she heals up there yeah but only ten
only ten
oh cow Chris all Chris can get some
exp too
I guess I needed protecting
I should have moved first
anyway
using a lot of owneries in this harsh
harsh
winter oh can go so far
hi
oh
here
oh wait it's oh oh
we'll just we'll just cover everyone
first
[Music]
I will run out of his thingy oh wow
allow me
[Music]
and you can just fly over there
um
okay next turn I'm going for real
[Music]
for real for real for real for real
trust me
[Music]
maybe I could have already sent some
people there now but oh well here we go
here we go it's time baby
to say goodbye and then hello again and
join my team Ivy you'll have a better
life trust me you can you can live in
the in the sky with me
I'll treat you real nicely
oh
that's interesting that it does so much
damage because
they're effective against me
do you do you kill
um
checking out my options oh
[Music]
put you here
's so scared here I goat they're all
kind of late
[Music]
struck
die oh wait maybe that's
oh maybe I wanted to send someone there
but uh no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no I didn't I I didn't
think of such I can go from the side
it's okay
okay
I feel like koala might die there I'm
scared
I'm scared
I'm scared she's like so close to
everyone
15-0
[Music]
she's a tank she hasn't been feeling
very tanky to me
Dream well
why not put someone else because
eventually we will all have to go there
I'm gonna give them some more options
don't worry what's going on oh
[Music]
I'm giving you options here here
I don't care about casualties now
this is just a part of the procedure
it's a part of the of the bigger picture
you know also he has
little below 50 chance of hitting back
so let's hope for the best
I like
distance not a whole door
[Music]
okay
free rewinds left it's getting close
one
[Music]
someone is gonna die
I'm very sure about that too
question is will I want to rewind or not
um
I could finish them off here but I'm
so worried about what will happen after
that
sacrifices
have to be made yunaka at least you get
some exp before dying
was that too much
it's an exchange
I'm just a Body Exchange
two devs next enemy return at least
that look I can even attack this dude
never mind let me take a step back
[Music]
go with javelin
hmm
[Music]
do I offer myself on a platter or do I
walk back a little bit I'll offer myself
no platter
see we have reinforcements because
they're lagging behind I see them
basically as reinforcements
okay let's see what happens ah
Donald oh she goes foot no okay those
orders we're plain you will not pass if
once you prioritizes the icicle oh but
she goes for kisara
I could
oh defend
she stood out for us for so long and
that's how we repair I think she
appreciates us she sees it as an honor
I think this is the only way she would
would have wanted to die oh
boy
foreign
to me on this level also
that kisara death
I crawled her I recruited her
all right
um
[Music]
let's begin
oh
19 damage back
[Music]
let me see
okay okay okay okay ah if we do this
first
then uh Alfred might not get so much
damage back
hey maybe we can even kill her in this
turn
okay one HP bar down
[Music]
foreign
I want to see
what we can do here
[Music]
's a funny HP
more casualties
pretty sure I'm pretty sure
[Music]
who wants to kill
we have um
some good options down there I'm not
giving it to kiwawa this time
[Music]
so we can give it to citrin which she's
level 11 he's level 11.
um
even Chloe could reach if she but wait
before we kill no let's give Chloe a
kill down here
Advantage Pizza
throw a javelin at him come on baby some
Revenge some sweet sweet revenge
just once it's stuck in there go back
and then turn it turn it while it's
stuck in his chest oh
hmm
one HP and a dream yeah just like
just like Ivy right now
okay Diamond just joined us and he needs
to avenge his father because
we all probably know what's probably
coming after this
all right
please don't kill my golf girlfriend
don't worry I am just
I'm just pushing her off her cute ass
dragon
I'm sorry
to take her home of me gonna carry her
level up
we're nice level up that's a good one
[Music]
did it it was a bit of a struggle this
one but the other two fights today were
easier so
I'll take this
one needs to be difficult today
so
we're already over 20 hours Play Time 23
actually
great Victory Divine One
please no
kill me no no
I will not take your life just like me
for refereeing naive
if I live
what's to stop me from hunting you down
you can't return to illusion after this
your Kingdom's through with you what
gives you that idea
if King Hyacinth had wanted you to
survive he would have given you an
emblem ring well damn besides he had no
need to stall us the weather alone would
have slowed us down I don't understand
it but smart the King used you fire
emblem for you to survive smarter than
me
suppose you're right your father has
already sacrificed your life no that was
honestly her first smart statement grant
me the release of death in the whole
game how cruel in my opinion
you are my deity
and I respect your will huh could I ask
you to forget that oh
exchange
I will tell you where King mauryan is
being taken and why huh
my father intends to perform a ritual
that will restore the fell dragon's
power oh no her ritual you see it though
the fell dragon has been freed his
abilities are diminished right normally
she's
he is exhausted and can't transform into
a dragon ideally he would have all 12
rings but securing them will take time
in the interim
some Braun decided to temporarily regain
his powers through an ancient ritual in
which he consumes softened blood
you can't mean my father the vampire
King morion
yes
my father took him as an offering to
sambron
that was his aim for the start
is that horrific the ritual will take
place at destinia Cathedral
you must hurry and do be careful
since the fell dragons return the father
has not been himself I see
that is the extent of what I know
come zelkoff forgetsu why are they still
alive let us leave this place what are
you going to do
whatever I can without taking sides oh
if we meet again Divine dragon
I pray it is not his enemies let's head
to illusia yes we have to hurry
don't go come with us man
no
no really be careful next upcoming
chapters are tough
[Laughter]
she remains a neutral party
can I like
like hire her for like single battles or
so I wonder that would be cool
emblem
leaps skill
with a variety of weapons allows him to
adapt to any combat situation
the sink skill arms Shield reduces
incoming damage when the user has weapon
advantage
uh-huh
the engage weapon killer ax lands
Critical Hits frequently the engage
skill adaptable automatically equips the
most effective weapon when the user is
attacked
the engage attack quadruple hits strikes
with a sword Lance ax bow increasing the
chance of breaking an enemy
like kiwawa who can also attack with
like every weapon at once almost almost
only free though wasn't it
ah sorry for letting you die but
I should make a proper introduction I'm
kisara I won't rest until King morion is
safe again
might never rest
wait that's again like
a night cool
it's desperately what is that
a marmot desperately wants to protect
their King
and then fails at it and then is
probably like really [\h__\h] sad I think
kisana had like a similar
similar thing
looks like an otter
okay
I can't believe King who wasn't updated
father we have to get to Destiny a
cathedral hurry the day after tomorrow
if that's okay
I don't know
you're not looking good right now you
must not let the fell Dragon regain
power let us make haste for destinier
Cathedral
yeah as I said
the day after tomorrow tomorrow you know
I have other things to do I have to iron
my clothes
guys
I have to iron my clothes you understand
right yeah
[Music]
this is the way to destinia Cathedral
I don't know in this snow it's hard to
tell where we're going
we don't have time to get lost
hold on
see someone up ahead
is that you
eat a while
[Music]
she's a friend
Vale
how did you get here Oreo time
I don't know you don't know how you
cross the border into another country
well how about you you look worried is
something the matter we're trying to
reach Destiny probably worried about
having so many stalkers in the snow and
just realizing that Oreo is one of them
if it's the cathedral you're looking for
head that way
you know where it is
you're close see that really tall tree
over there use that as a landmark I
appreciate it real I owed you for
patching me up the other day that was so
kind huh
were you wearing that ring before yes
it's very important to me no I switched
it
I think I switched it pretty really last
time we talked Veil
um
oh
fail
I'm sorry I better be on my way spooky
[Applause]
where are you going it's not safe
there's no time to search for
I wanna watch Lord of the Rings again
let's hurry fail
what in the world she's gonna catch a
cold
hahaha
look at them running
yeah extended edition
I guess we could do that
swing here again
you're supposed to be on your altar how
am I gonna talk to you if you're here
oh well
um
so it's 11 p.m now I have to cook
and I also
have to like sleep at a decent time
I hope we don't have too many like
super chats that I would be leaving
behind let her cook
where is that for
that
wait no I recently figured out where
that was from didn't I what
on it
[Music]
good stopping board that's for sure I
think today we made a lot of progress we
went through all of brodia
foreign
of course it's a meme it's from Breaking
Bad oh there's a lot of memes from
Breaking Bad that's what I what I should
be watching
um
[Music]
foreign
yeah yeah it's a secret to Malcolm in
the Middle so as someone who grew up
with that I should totally watch it
okay now you have two archers I should
do Tiki
before chapter 10. hmm
but it's still difficult right I wonder
if I can do it off screen but you guys
probably want me to do it on screen
on on the Stream
he fell asleep
when is he going back to the altar
is
yes yes I wanna is there something some
cute dialogue or what
okay so next time maybe we start with
Tiki and then we go back to the
main story
gets more difficult the longer I learned
so
really
okay
you're playing tails off all right
an item I need to get on the map
for Tiki
Tiki who's Tiki anyway
outfit is cute which one
my daughter characters oh they're
probably the characters
yeah yeah everyone has one of those it's
like a hakama made outfit cute
everybody always asks when are you
getting Tiki nobody asks who's sticky
except for me I ask who is sticky
it's a Divine dragon from Marv's game
wait there's
always Divine dragons
like free houses
I don't remember Divine dragon in free
houses
free houses an exception
sometimes
oh Ria was the divine
really was she called Divine dragon
I think all right dragon
I don't remember that being used to that
word
hmm
I loved surface
the substances
I love I miss her so much
you know I I like the characters so far
that we've met here
but so far I think I still like
um
more characters more from Fire Emblem
free houses
especially with like the early crew that
you get
um
to be together with but I guess soft is
you know
um cute girl who is mysterious with long
hair
and is Barefoot kind of here gets
replaced by oriochan
seems like they understand
uh what gets our gears grinding what we
need you see what they're doing there
and there are they are manipulating us
they know their audience yeah
but that's I guess like I don't know
this office was just ah
I love her so much
I miss her I really want to play free
houses sometime
Kelly told me that she's been playing
[Music]
um maybe she's mentioned it on stream
too but she's been playing
um this game
for hours and hours and hours and hours
and hours offstream
I actually tweeted it I guess maybe she
tweeted it and didn't tell me about it
yeah so since she's already been playing
so much off stream I don't think she'll
be streaming it but
I wonder
but maybe maybe I once I have
um once I'm done with this fire emblem
on stream
I probably will be like I want to play
more Fire Emblem and then maybe I'll
play free houses different routes
privately
because then I'll have the the itch
the itchiness
play more and then I'll actually have
something I'll have I'll have plenty
options huh
can play
the church one I can play Dimitri or
Claude
the DLC for free houses oh no I don't
think I ever did that blue lines
insanely long
free houses card classic no [\h__\h] no
DLC route
of course not
that already took so much time back then
and there were like so many other games
I wanted to play I feel like once we
were done with that you know we were
ready to move on but
um
yeah
oh yeah I know that my route was an
exception as it was like a little bit
shorter than the others
oh yeah Mercedes okay
oh well oh well
tear duck the whole time today
you hear that
in the background
have you noticed
it's like a oh no mostly not
it's like a spooky
ghost opening my
my creaky croaky door the whole time
opening it closing it and opening and
closing clock
ghost it's a ghost
hurt oh yeah I guess it also sounds a
little bit like an armchair rocking back
and forth back and forth back and forth
I think it's some
that specific sound that might be coming
from my um
uh
air vent
think
and I've been hearing
loud loud noises
uh
so much last night and then I
um I fall asleep so fast these days like
I can't even finish a whole Gilmore
Girls episode
I fall asleep so fast which is a good
thing
but then this movie has been waking me
up every day at 8am which makes me think
my brother myself
uh just naturally woken up at 8am and
always feelings moving at 8 AM for like
one month and now she's like [\h__\h] give
me
[Music]
let's give it now after one a month and
she doesn't let
wait and I wait and just like please let
me sleep
and she just won't So eventually after
waiting for 20 minutes of her
I get up I make her breakfast
and then I try to go back to sleep
um but then I'm partially too awake
because of smoothie annoying me and then
I'm also partially too late because of
all the sounds that are coming from my
vent
like from outside
because then then I can't help but pay
attention to it and then I have troubles
falling asleep again even though I'm
super tired so messed up
I've been thinking you know if I ignore
her long enough she will surely stop but
and she kind of does if I ignore her for
half an hour but by that time I'm like
so annoyed and so awake
then I can't sleep anymore anyway and
then I just end up making her food
and so the cycle continues and continues
and continues
all the feed America now the thing is
like she's asking particularly for wet
food she will not let go until she gets
wet food
even if she has dry food
she wants wet food in the morning
ideally she would want it all the time
but she gets it in the morning
I love her I love her so much but she's
annoying me so
[Music]
just like my cat forever
he's a very special one yes yes she is
tried feeding my cat nothing but wet
food for a while he got really fat oh
I guess they do do that too
so I'm mixing it I give her a
dry and wet food
never eat that wet food oh yeah well
well you know chunkers doesn't eat wet
food either
[Music]
um
cutest alarm clock
yeah but
a broken alarm clock because I cannot
change the time and I cannot turn her
off
she's broken I need to bring her to the
repair shop
but it's okay I don't have to deal with
this much longer because I'm going back
to Japan soon
the alarm clock can annoy my brother
again he didn't really seem that
bothered but he said that like she would
do the same thing to him and he she
would like step on him and be like right
in his face like one centimeter in front
of his face really close and be like wow
and he wakes up like oh
but he's he's more
I guess cooperative
he got used to waking up early through
um
what was it called
you know the trip that he did
oh
oh I'll look at it
what's in English
the pilgrimage yeah
anyway
huh so
um see my I'm pretty sure there's at
least
half
half of my energy drink is so full
now it's a small bottle it has
250 milliliters
sounds like there's it sounds and feels
as if there's more than half of it in
there but now I don't want to drink
anymore because I'm gonna sleep soon
anyway
so for next episode yeah
no but that's the day after tomorrow I
don't know but
I don't think have you guys ever like
kept an open energy drink and
drink it the next day what about the
next next day
I don't know about doing that with
energy drinks
it's probably delay they're cheap as
dirt anyway
um
one more quick sip this one's actually
pretty yummy
hmm
I think I've grown
fond of Red Bull didn't like it that
much
like a couple years ago did I say it
already I did right
um
it
kettle
one or night
blueberry Red Bull is bearable yeah
that one's okay
[Music]
they had three unlimited red bull in the
world
in the studio
sponsorship thank you uh Bhutan Center
and I think Aqua center right for those
of two
what time Senpai for sure
was the other one across senpai
yeah those two thank you thank you it
must be because of that sponsorship
not very healthy but surely there's a
lot of people there who are sleep
deprived working night and day every day
or weekday or weekend day
so yeah
okay so tomorrow short stream relatively
short stream at um 12 p.m my time
and later in the day um
I have to get some things done
I really hope I do get some things done
because
[Music]
it's lacking
might have to vote it that's okay you
can valid while you're also ironing your
clothes I also have a
you call it
whatever you'll see it tomorrow
let's hope it goes well so far my
ironing when I tried ironing it always
I don't know it didn't really iron so
I'll use this opportunity to get some
ironing advice from you guys
although I do everything that you know
seems necessary like you know I go in
circles and all that and then go back
and forth and I use the water and all
that
and yet no it doesn't work ironing back
saving yeah please
ironic advice you guys probably
have more experience with ironing than
me I feel like I feel like you guys
would wear things that need ironing more
than me
Maybe
all of you of course
oh well I need to go I need to run
myself and I'm saying hey I'm gonna cook
now
should I just throw in a pizza oh wait
today's Tuesday
only then I should have another hello
fresh delivery actually
I don't work
I'll think about it
when you shop still open oh my God
it's not much longer
hmm
foreign
[Music]