[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I have a problem
help me
help me keep me
I have a problem I think I need to go to
the hospital
I have gaming hands but I have no gaming
arms
it hurts
so I'll try to stay down
as much as possible
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] are my arms no this this
one this this um prop is pretty old and
comes from ancient times when
um yeah when when we couldn't use like
paintings on our bodies yet although
that is very recent
um
uh I will if I would
may I kindly ask for
um gamer hands with arms
[Laughter]
it's really difficult to use
I can also add them myself but I feel
like it's got a little bit disrespectful
to the artist
um and back
instead of saying can I get a hand can I
get maybe arms oh yeah Raven style I
have no problem with Rayman and I don't
want to discriminate Rayman he's like
really cool and all
um tilt controls
yeah
uh sorry for being a bit late no worries
oh God I'm tired like oh I was I was
cuddling with smoothie watching some
uh TV to pass the time
after having a really late lunch and
I feel like I fell asleep for 10 minutes
which is surprising that I woke up
naturally
without sleeping for 10 hours
that's that's however my second nap
today but at least it was only 10
minutes
it was only 10 minutes you can't even
call it a nap in my world okay I just
dozed off I think and then I'm like wait
wait I have a stream wait what what time
is it what time is it
but that's not that's not enough thank
you thank you thank you thank you my
naps normally take two to four hours
so it's not an amp
[Music]
you want to know what means movie have
been watching
okay don't laugh okay
oh I think there might be a surprisingly
big amount of support towards me
watching when I'm watching
[Music]
um so recently
since I've um you know I I always need a
brain dead show where I don't have to
think uh something relatively light and
funny
you know to fall asleep and to pass time
um
and normally my to go shows for that are
like Scrubs and Friends Big Bang Theory
um what else
um Modern Family although not so much
stuff like that okay
uh
how about your mother to your office yes
the office oh yeah how could I forget
that but I've already rewatched all of
them look a million times so what did
koala do kiwawa went through Disney plus
hoping to find something there's barely
anything good on Disney Plus
barely and anything
uh
and
my my Nostalgia demanded of me to watch
wait one is even the
what's the English title
okay Malcolm in the Middle
welcome in the middle okay okay so
what's your reaction
okay see see I was I was thinking it
might be a surprisingly good reaction
from you guys
yeah starting from the bottom uh from
the first season I'm like re-watching
all of it I used to watch it like
randomly on TV back in the day but I
never watched it in order from beginning
to end never
that was always a show that I
um would pick up on TV on on Austrian
German TV
um
yeah yeah and I I think I always liked
it but
um I was back then I think I'm enjoying
it more now than I did when I was
younger because I don't know I don't
know I don't know like now now I get the
I understand
Lloyds and how a little bit more I guess
uh and and I don't know the kids are
cute
and I I understand more things I guess I
mean now I'm kind of too old for it but
at least the stand more than I did by
then
yeah
and
I don't know there's still some some
parts of the show that are a bit weird
to me but uh but it's fun yeah 80 of
America's joke swing past me yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah it was like too much too
I wonder really what the the appropriate
like target age group for that show was
because I feel like it was supposed to
be for younger kids but
I don't think I understood much back
then at all
he's pretty 50 since I've known him
hey off topic
Family Family Show
but I really really gotta feel for loise
sometimes right damn
it's tough being a mother of three to
four wait four to five really obnoxious
[\h__\h] teenage boys
oh my God one of my favorite episodes
was always when they turned into girls
felt so sorry for her
man
hey hey don't make fun of my th don't
don't you dare make fun of my DH
[Music]
all right all right four to five
yeah
all right so we're gonna play uh
unexpectedly some Mario Kart for people
who are coming in here expecting GTA I'm
sorry
you're really late to the party because
I already canceled GTA to play rest
and then I played rust and then I
privated the stream because it was not
fun and I
don't think I want that stream on my
channel
yeah probably not
and now here I am trying to make up for
that disaster with a Mario Kart stream a
little bit I I I just I you know I was
like I need a game
I need a game that is enjoyable and fun
and that's difficult I know I know I
know I always suck at it but you know
still in fear it's not too difficult and
um what happened well that's the thing
nothing really happens
that's the problem I guess
um yeah Mario Kart is like
you know comfy and the thing is this is
absolutely big brain genius
in less than two hours
is uh the Mario movie trailer or
whatever coming out that Mario movie
direct or whatever which I did not
really care for but now we can connect
it and do a watch along
which is so perfect because look we're
playing a game that's called Mario Kart
and then we're gonna do a watch along
which is not on the uh not written on my
thing about whatever uh we're gonna
we're gonna you know connect one to
another they made the channel
[Music]
cast retail all the tanks for us that's
what I've been thinking like [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
should I reach out all my tangents from
rest as if nothing happened
man now I have to retailmen thank you
you you're sharing one brain cell with
me
so that they are actually um archived
you know we have to Archive them also
one more thing I think there's um since
last time I played uh there's a there's
four New Roads right
so we're gonna try to play these
together
the Divine horse honestly
um
I almost want somebody to clip that
and we're just gonna re-upload that one
part of my stream
the the horse part to my channel if
that's okay
does someone does someone want to clip
it like into an actual clip not just you
know something funny
looking at my kfb clippers
I will give you if you don't have the
data I can send you the video data the
whole archive
I no it's okay I will give it to you
I'm private
I don't know it's such a depressing and
disappointing stream
[Laughter]
I don't know Senpai should be in it too
um no I don't know maybe maybe tomorrow
when I wake up I'll feel differently
about it so
um let's wait until tomorrow oh okay
okay
um
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
put it put it there uh okay we haven't
done this in a while online play okay
put the OBS screen away now lady
and look at your capture card
uh uh tournament Disney
and
I will choose one of my tournaments
don't look
also don't you guys like the thumbnail
on the title today
I think I think it's beautiful which one
which
which one maybe
right
I was going for Christina manzanita's
um Twitter because I was I was hoping
for something Derpy something good to
use for this no no like nothing too
serious you know I found the perfect one
okay let's see I'm joining my tournament
I'm probably unreal unless I was
thinking about unlisted too yeah
oh well anyway uh
uh-huh uh-huh
doesn't [\h__\h] matter okay uh
hoy
here is the code when using
um that one okay master and
um please
as a rule please always try to go for
the newer ones
um
I should wait I need to I need to pin it
please please if possible try to go try
to choose uh one of the New Roads not
random
but if the new words are not available
then whatever
Minecraft updating I should have [\h__\h]
prepared
rainbow now I will I will [\h__\h] eat
you if you choose Rainbow Road
where's everybody
okay
oh wait screen screen screen game screen
hi hello everybody so I would go for
Ninja Hideaway in this case do you
understand no this dude apparently has
not understood this dude has understood
this one too this this yes you girls are
understanding everybody understands
except that one dude who chose random
wow I expected more people wow
okay that's actually a pretty impressive
I don't think people have ever listened
to me this well
[Laughter]
maybe he has no DLC I don't know what
happens if you don't have even my own
was chosen unbelievable okay anyway it's
quite a [\h__\h] quiet why is it so
[\h__\h] quiet guys oh no ah wait I know
what here Iran
I don't have a switch what go [\h__\h]
buy one or buy my old one because I want
to kind of buy a new one one of the OLED
ones
you know I don't know if that's worth it
[Music]
[Applause]
where are we going what okay so far
actually uh I'm playing like a
professional I would say
yeah okay okay uh that was you know it
happens yeah
[Applause]
oh what the [\h__\h] hello I was
I wasn't sure okay well this map is
really [\h__\h] difficult
was there a problem
no no no
no no [\h__\h] hate you
[Music]
I hate you guys so it's okay it's not
your fault it's not your fault it's not
your fault oh God no no oh oh where did
I get mine my golden thinking again
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm not doing so bad
oh [\h__\h] where's my trick ah
I can't make it all right
okay please wait for me okay we both
suck that's beautiful
we have one more round
can still change right
[Music]
I don't know what I should be using the
star for but let's oh [\h__\h]
hello
his name is donations
my Deutsche points
good morning
what the [\h__\h]
not aim for the rides I was going for
the left like 100
drinks game but okay oh nice safe but
that kills the booster
well that sucked
foreign
[Music]
once you may leave the race thank you
good warm-up yeah we have to warm up ah
are these they they're both new but I
want the other from the same or is one
of them newer
um either way I'm gonna go for this one
oh I shouldn't be so fast you know
that dude Oh I thought you were new
I was gonna say I think that dude looks
new uh
that one is newer okay
hello everybody
[Music]
how you doing
how are you doing
hello
well are we a full group okay
um someone didn't get the memo but
that's okay
Castle game one of the possibilities
there's gonna be a moo moo Meadows oh
well that's okay too I will forgive that
how do you do do you it's almost at one
million go go go guys play it on the
side play it on the side while watching
my stream playing on your phone while
watching my stream on the TV okay okay
trying to get in well you will have a
lot of chances
oh even the participant from South Korea
hello
of course many many Americans good
morning everybody how's it going and
it's also one from Norway
my Zhang I'm gonna go to Norway
[Music]
here's some tangents well just in case
that my archive from rest is not going
back up
[Music]
I like hungering
games
[Music]
isn't coming back I will first start by
repeating owl what the [\h__\h] what I'm
necessary
repeating my tangents ah
well that was on purpose did you guys
write down the name of that person
that was so aimed at me
[Music]
so blatant what the [\h__\h]
yeah Deja Vu time I know
[Music]
so okay first of all I I was really
productive yesterday
I uh I I I I I I I got like four
packages from the post office that for
some reason I didn't even get a notice
that you know they tried to get them in
not even a notice what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
boom
why am I not driving
yeah one of them was a snack box
uh finally I'm I'm uh missing one more
snack box
should come like this month or next
month
[Music]
I was using hers and still had free of
my own yeah
um it's a France the snack box that you
guys we'll see on my next
uh oh wow
not so bad
so bad good night
beautiful wow
what a good idea what what fixture
probably my highest ranking today I
won't get any higher than that
so okay
uh
Twisted Mansion no Twisted Dimension has
always been here right
and let's do random in that case let me
should do random guys
uh
no no I don't know what you're talking
about there's no Rainbow Road here I
don't know what you're talking about
so so next week uh next week I'm
uh France snack Box review I'm really
excited for it um
hey looking forward to the whole talk
aren't ya
okay who's understanding the memo we're
listening to the stream to what I'm
saying there you go there you go there
you go okay a couple of them okay
everybody who is choosing rainbow road
is [\h__\h] sadistic
um
that's the word right
oh okay well oh that's fine I don't I
don't like that map I do like that map
from France oh hey
all the friends came here
sometimes it really surprised me to see
how many friends can be there are so I
think I think you know we'll see a
couple of them at the
at the snack Box review
[Music]
in France as well
I'm soaking my head this map makes me
tilt my head oh oh did you see it did my
did my life did you show it
what's up
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
I [\h__\h] hate you guys no okay that was
my fault everybody
[Music]
oh
yay
for driving slowly I love you
oh
okay okay okay
bye bye suckers
let me win this as well
[Applause]
this is
[Music]
oh my voice holy [\h__\h]
oh man
oh wow
sorry I was really excited there
um okay okay so I picked up packages
the packages was actually a chair and I
built that chair so that I didn't even
mention that in the rest stream I built
a chair it took me
um eight minutes approximately it was a
really simple chair but
I built
because I got myself a makeup table no
it was not an Ikea chair no no the paper
was Ikea but yeah makeup makeup table
um
I got like a a makeup table from Ikea
and a big big fancy round mirror yeah
going for a round mirror is the fancy
sophisticated Choice there yeah and then
I bought a chair that
um you know one of those makeup table
chairs the typical ones where you would
like you know it's like a it's like a
round chair with no back to it and you
open it up and you can put something
inside the chair so I put my my hair
dryer in my hair iron in there yeah are
those NPCs
[Music]
oh yeah a stool okay
okay I built
are you happy now hey no French person
here why not
that one guys with a fancy name dancing
guys
that's a really cool name to choose in
German language somehow all right
can we go for the middle someone has to
go first right you guys go first go go
oh you guys suck
I would not go for the middle why would
you not sacrifice yourself for the
greater Goods
[Music]
speaking of France I'm sorry but um I'm
kind of unrelated but since I'm thinking
I'm traveling uh did I tell you guys I'm
planning on
[Music]
yeah
I'm planning on taking
um my mom to Italy uh probably
[Music]
in November I'm thinking what the [\h__\h]
come on oh I need a I need a I need a
mushroom there
yeah yeah
did I tell you I don't think I told you
huh
[Music]
yeah I don't know I was I I don't know
why exactly I thought of doing that I
think
like I talked about never having been to
Rome before
and then that's a while ago and then on
I said it on stream and my mom was
listening
oh [\h__\h]
and then she was like I don't know
oh Rome is nice blue really nice I have
been yeah yeah and I'm like oh Mommy
maybe you should show me around and my
mom oh yeah that's right I I remember
one more thing I was uh I think on the
Italy snap up stream I was saying that
like I don't my mom used to take me to
Italy a lot and but I don't remember
uh how good her Italian really was I
remember her speaking with some Italian
but
[Music]
maybe as a child I was just imagining
that my mom was really good at Italian
she's really not that good but then my
mom was like girl I
I feel no Italian a little bit and I
will prove it to you eventually and I
could prove it to you in Italy then so
so yeah basically this is
uh yeah basically I'm taking her to
Italy so that she can show me around in
Rome maybe and then she can Flex her
hopefully existent Italian to me
okay uh ah this one's new right
[Music]
yeah Bullet Bill amazing I have tangent
buff maybe a little bit
um
hello
you're looking as creepy as ever
foreign
[Laughter]
guys you need to leave the room
unfortunately we're here already
oh
you look like the NPCs
for understanding
[Music]
please choose this new one thank you
thank you
how many are we
one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten ah okay
one person missing why are you chosen
ing
[Applause]
please please please please please
please
it says the tournament is closed
really no no
oh that was close that was close
ah ah don't have the new moms okay okay
hi hi
guys be careful of the Japanese drivers
they're really good
we have to gang up on them guys okay
okay
trust me bro
so uh the truth is on my second day my
best
okay I hope you got the screenshot
on my second day of the Comic Con that I
went to I told you guys I went inside
Ryan and I [\h__\h] you I played a little
bit of uh Mario Kart there because I
walked by a Nintendo stand and I saw
Mario Kart there and I was like you know
what I guess we should enjoy ourselves a
little bit oh bye
it's ruined give me another chance
please do chats
oh yes thank you that's also a chance
but anyway so what I did was uh play
Mario Kart a little bit and we played
the new map so this one I already have
played before a little bit
Marshall so I know I know about these
bouncy mushrooms
foreign
one try for each new map so it's not
like I'm like super pro okay
I swear to God I will find you're
enjoyment Germany huh okay that's not so
difficult for me to find I will find you
I will find you
I will find out where your house lives
as we like to say in German oh beautiful
look at them go get them go get them I
need the red gel I need the red oh
what can I ruin it like that
I swear to God I will I will I will
become a witch and put all curses on
Earth on you
you sucker
yeah definitely fruit I could have been
fifth I could have been fifth
[Music]
I'm disappointed in my Japanese Bros
why did you not get number one ah are
you out of practice that's not the right
word
has it been a while since you touched
your controller huh
I expected more from you I was hyping
you guys up so much
[Laughter]
or maybe maybe
uh did their best to get a gang up on
the Japanese Bros
was it correct okay oh no I don't know
what to choose for this one I'm gonna go
for random
okay
give them some slack no no no no no no
no no no oh hell no no no they're they
are supposed to
being good at any given time
they literally like Camp to to find
these Mario Kart streams
okay well well
so
oh yeah so in November I'm going to
Italian
[Music]
it's probably for like two nights three
days two nights or so you won't even
notice
I'll be back before you know it
let's go
[Music]
look
since my mom really likes wine I was
like thinking of maybe bringing her to
France instead for like going to like
one of those wine chateaus and Vineyards
you know what I mean
because I saw some really oh
some really beautiful ones
uh like on social media before they look
so beautiful the thing is you know I
I've enjoyed that at all would I they
said for me to enjoy there unfortunately
so yeah that didn't make much sense
oh my God
okay well actually that's not so bad
because I would have I think that would
take a month about the same time as if
you just fly through normally
[Music]
Miami
is uh Italian huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
God
coming from
[Music]
okay okay
that [\h__\h] wall
[Music]
foreign
hey it's just
oh I guess it could have been worse
could have been worse
concern considering the circumstances
uh thank you
[Music]
all right I don't care let's just go
with one of these let's go with chief
chief Beach
laughs
all right
oh you little [\h__\h] Shopkin
[Music]
you know what we call you in German a
little Besa Visa mm-hmm
know it all know it all aren't ya
a little no at all seventh is good yeah
yeah yeah for me that's good
yes I am yes you are yes you are
[Music]
wait I have more tangents so what I I
made a chair
I got packages and I sent a package to
Bales finally sorry for the delay but I
was trying to perfectionize it
and it costs like 140 bucks oh I like
that map so in whole I spent like 200
bucks on on the stupid snack box I hope
she likes it I must say
most of the things in that snap snack
box that I chose are things I will
you know buy for myself
all the time
so
[Music]
I think they're really good
let me try to go on here and then I'll
go up here oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
the crazy shipping crisis Australia what
the [\h__\h]
what the go away go away
I hate you what
what
I didn't realize it was okay to fall
down here already so early
oh
[Music]
okay
okay what else what else what else
massage on my way back that was really
good but it is partially really hurt and
I was
not courageous enough to say sorry that
[\h__\h] hurts can you please stop
yeah so I just endured as much as I
could
okay
wait
[Music]
not so bad not so bad because I missed
that I
said
[Music]
[Applause]
at the end I was believing I was [\h__\h]
believing
up so many
yeah of course Austrian makes the top
three in the in the winter Championship
finally
oh my God
yo this is really helping me cheer up
wonderful all according to keikaku some
people say I can't get in so you know
what we'll do one more one more run in
this tournament and then I'll try to
open up a new one okay but I think it's
probably
Not Really Gonna help
well I'll try I'll try
[Music]
ah
okay now let me go through some new
tangents
um
I want to tell you something exciting oh
but I shouldn't use up all my tangents
because we have GTA tomorrow
um
um wait okay
oh let me tell you I did not get bonked
for the autograph thing so don't worry
that some people have been worrying
about that I guess I did not get bonked
okay I
that's all okay
[Music]
one tangent in members huh wait what was
on the ball what do they tangent about
in members
[Music]
what was that
I remembered it was something but I
don't remember what
I hope he looked you up you know what I
I hope so too it wouldn't be so funny if
you did well
nice
[Music]
I'll open up a new tenement in a second
um
they're recording oh maybe I'll talk
about that
huh
oh what was it what what tangent do you
mean
December travel oh
[Music]
December traveled
Oh you mean the fact that I'm I'm
planning on going to Japan in December
yeah okay
um
but honestly just for like myself to
enjoy myself
oh interesting oh
but I mean while I'm there I'm surely
gonna do some up clamps
and hopefully if I get some studio time
which I doubt so don't get your hopes up
then I will record something if I can
found it
holy [\h__\h] I'm actually not so bad today
am I or all my all the participants just
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh oh okay okay here we go this is
difficult
[Music]
yes I take it back
you know what I will I won't I won't and
I didn't follow so far behind anyway
either
today
[Music]
look at those tricks y'all whoa
small small
go go go go
oh I hate that part I hate it oh God oh
God oh
oh
what the [\h__\h]
oh this curve is fine this curve is
quite all right
okay let's go no time to waste
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah play Johnny I shot this too and shots
oh
Chihuahua
newborn
number one
these PM's in the worst possible oh no
way hey hey we gotta do Tokyo blur okay
and then I'll change map Tokyo blur took
your blur
Ry
thank you
just be wearing the crown
wait what what map was that Chihuahua
what what flag
oh yeah time to visit Japan as I as I
was saying
after this after this tournament after
this I'll make a new tournament after
this one after this one
what Japan oh that was Japan oh
yeah
[Music]
I bought all the kebabs I could find in
the artist alley which must have been
only
once very specific
laughs
oh
one very specific
um
shop wasn't it because I think there was
only one
you must have hallucinated though I I'm
visible you know I I am very why is
you guys didn't join what the hell
attending for fess
well not not as a guest no I don't think
so
room is bugged oh okay
okay well thank you thank you very super
chat you must have seen um
[Music]
any plans for meeting Navi oh yes
uh no not yet I want to but no not yet
and also also also a certain scientific
rail gun no a certain Japanese whole
life member
uh has contacted me
and seems to be very serious about
finally visiting me in Europe now who
might who might that be because the
thing is many Japanese members have
given me that record that that promise
right so who Could That Be
[Music]
what could that be I was really
surprised to see that
we have to
do how our schedules work together but
hopefully it's gonna happen in the
coming buck in the coming half year
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
ing members
this is
just wait a little bit for me
[Applause]
please oh what the [\h__\h] well I guess I
can't tell NPCs to wait for me
[\h__\h] empty seats
[Music]
your guesses are from what I'm seeing
not very correct
[Music]
dummy
You're Gonna Hurt Me You're Gonna Hurt
Me What is love baby don't hurt me don't
hurt me
[\h__\h] you and [\h__\h] you and [\h__\h] you and
[\h__\h] you
hi
whoa oh wait I feel so sorry for the
French person at the very bottom
now because
so sorry
okay let's leave this tournament uh oh
hello everybody I'm so sorry guys I know
it's really hard to get into into the
tournament but we're making a new one in
hopes of uh
in hopes of it going better what
ah delete an existing one
which one was I using this one right can
I delete it
oh yeah
okay
I just got in I'm so sorry but we always
have to cut it in and cut it off at some
point you know
sorry
okay
choose a symbol for your tournament all
right Daisy
and your name
when
the [\h__\h] is Winkleman
angel
[Music]
no teams no items no CPU oh Vehicles
smart steering no what smart steering
active
daily
start time it doesn't matter right
oh this is
it doesn't matter right
races I don't know man I don't know
Christine
all this doesn't matter
code required okay there we go
[Music]
uh five four seven one
okay let me in though let me in
let me
[Music]
I'm in
baby
[Music]
one match per person
choose New Roads when possible place on
okay
ah did I tell you
when did I tell you I probably told you
but I told you did I tell you
holy [\h__\h] who's that is that a gar uh
that I went to I went to the arcade the
other day and I played I played um I
played um some that that that that
um Olympic
Olympic
uh Olympic Super Mario whatever Nintendo
game on in the arcade yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah my Olympics yeah with rnt yeah and
of course I chose Daisy my beautiful
Daisy what the
what that one orange-haired woman looks
weird
are you trying to be me
[Music]
which one is it ah are you trying to be
me I always says it always gonna be
Daisy love Daisy
love oh it's Yoshi map
what is this yoshima it would look like
right what's
[\h__\h]
wow the music I never noticed how good
the music was on this map whoa
whoa it's so good what a bomb
oh
[Music]
wait this makes me happy
laughs
[Music]
I'm coming
okay
it's so chill and I I it really feels
like I'm driving
through a beautiful city in the summer
time all those summer is in reality over
so sad so sad where I'm wearing all my
winter clothes
I want to go shopping for winter clothes
oh but that's I want to go shopping
somewhere where there's actually nice
clothes like in Korea I really like the
fashion they had in Korea I I bought so
many things
snow from my tangents my
um my suitcase was absolutely overweight
by like
I don't know eight
kilos or nine kilos or so or ten I don't
remember
hey I deserve a Bullet Bill now too
please thank you
[Music]
no [\h__\h] you
yeah
[Music]
I did not pay it uh put it overweight
because
they were really nice to me yeah
the guy at the counter the checking
counter he was like okay well did you
enjoy Korea I said yeah he said are you
coming back and I said well I think so
and then he said okay no no need to pay
well I wanted that was if I would have
said if I would have said I didn't I
not coming back would I have had to pay
oh look at that waiting for me
[Music]
this is a bag
oh it's a hand with you guys
the hang of you
Nintendo use charm it was affected
turkey blur let's go that was good in
Tokyo play it was fun it was fun
Ging
now tell controls you should not use you
should not be used until controls
I would have wanted you to earn your
Victory blah blah
blah uh anyway what was I saying where
was I okay oh yeah I want to go shopping
style from cloves of clubs in Korea
um
I bought quite a lot I would have bought
more if there wasn't a limit on one
[\h__\h] suitcase
yeah
shopping list
but I mean I guess I guess our
Zara I guess has fine fine clothes so I
guess no no hello where's everybody you
could bring two no
no not in that case no
no no no no no no just you know
okay why you guys not understanding
what's in the paint message
it was a miracle the first time I want
miracle
oh God the chances are pretty low here
yes
yeah okay
let's go
yeah there's an Iron Man there huh
[Music]
I'm gonna if I go to Japan in December
I'll I'll buy you some some clothes
again I think although I feel like I
don't know
[Music]
it's hard
to
uh judge right now it's been a while
since I've been shopping in Japan I
wonder how the trends have changed in
terms of girls clothing whoa
stay calm
oh
the cards at the convention uh tangent I
was gonna say you know I was playing
against a friend who was absolutely
[\h__\h] at the game you know
really not an experienced player and
against
my friend I was actually doing pretty
well I would say
but then
[Music]
cart laws gave me the shittiest islands
and the shittiest opponents NPCs they
were I think on like really difficult
setting
and yeah I don't know I I lost again
against my friends
but I don't know it was I think I was in
the final ranking of the four matches I
was four for fifth
versus first
can you [\h__\h] believe it I cannot
[\h__\h] believe it because I was
thriving
pretty beautifully okay I
saw well
and then I get paid back
oh you little [\h__\h] oh okay good timing I
get paid back
with I don't know being [\h__\h] on but
again what
what this
I was first or second what
happened in the last one second of
this match
huh
wow wow
my wrath is unmeasurable
it's unbelievable holy [\h__\h]
what did you guys do
while I'm talking about being scammed by
Mario Kart I am once again being scammed
by Mario Kart
okay our Channel
here several times
[Music]
survival for gifts but you know
if the other is some
space
yeah what the [\h__\h]
yeah
oh the funny thing was that my friend
um didn't know what to do so
they just chose the same exact same
setup as I had Daisy with the same card
with the same Wheels with the same
everything so it was actually like
pretty fair in terms of that
hmm
in the end it was really hard to
distinguish which Daisy was who and
which one was first place and which one
was fourth place but
I had to admit well I was fourth place
okay I was fourth place okay I'm sorry
yeah
[Laughter]
huh oh this one is that that's that's
new right on it am I going crazy
pinball I think it's new
baby winging
it's the colonel hobo are you making fun
of the cocoa
wait is that
it's an old man
well there's your pinball recently added
right
[Music]
that reminds me
now this one is old
what is it it's old
oh wow it looks beautiful it looks new
[Music]
but I love paintball so nostalgic all
right don't leave me behind
[Music]
I don't know where to go
foreign
[Music]
of course yeah yeah we all saw that one
coming
oh
[Music]
I'm just enjoying the big jam now
I am so far behind
there's absolutely no chance for me
that's okay
[Music]
for the middle speed for them oh
yes
no help for me
[Music]
oh no oh
first round pinball music
awesome very funky
[Music]
foreign
ah okay well that was terrible what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
oh all my French French friends so many
of you guys
what the [\h__\h]
could be worse
[Music]
um
wait no these are all old
these are all old
so let's go for random
[Music]
yeah they also called the French people
let's win them
[Music]
oh okay I was I was looking at it and I
was like
that looks new but at the same time it
looks like that one that one map
uh you know where you bounce
yeah yeah and you fly yeah yeah you know
what I mean so we're going for Sky
Garden I hope some more people will join
us
it's not that new yeah is it from uh
oh thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank you and the first
couple of people who chose the wrong
thing I forgive them because they
probably were thinking I was gonna go
for random
that's okay that's okay
[Music]
huh no no okay but this map is not so
bad
it's okay
hey Sans is playing with us I I think we
have some fans some Sans fans and chats
couldn't be me
because I don't know anything about the
game and the fandom
first first
[Music]
take this
pumping so the trainer that I'm watching
later is that just a movie trailer or
what what is that gonna be is it just
something short
something to be hyped about
[Music]
movie trailer okay so it's probably not
gonna be very long huh
it's a teaser
oh I live in Japan in December I really
want to go to the Nintendo World
[Music]
I hope I can go to the Nintendo while
it's in Osaka not in Tokyo so it's quiet
it's quite far actually but oh well
I will make the trip I'll jump into a
shinkansen
and make my way to Osaka yeah
[Music]
to the right side this time you know
what I'll never go to the right side
never
mind
coming oh wait did the star just save me
from falling down
can you start do that
I thought that's where it stops
[Music]
here
baby yeah
a decent save at the end an arcg I saw
you waiting there at the end you're
going in my good chickens book yes yes
oh oh yeah I want to talk a little bit
oh coconut milk a little bit about
um
I want to talk a little bit about the
meat and greens I feel like there was
something I wanted to talk about in the
meet and greets
[Music]
something I wrote something down
there was something I want to mention
you know great meet and greets
when I remember is someone flexed to me
uh in in the first um slot of the meet
and greet which was like around noon
time
um
[Music]
someone Flex to me and then they had
lunch with them the first thing I did
when the meet and greet started was
bringing out a plate of schnitzel
I think they were Australian or German
I'm so sorry but yeah they were flexing
some schnitzel at me
some schnitzel
and they said like literally until three
minutes before their meeting great
started they were still cooking
perfectly timed no it's not rude it's
fine it's fine
I was killing but it was really funny
how it was so giddy-gitty that second
because everybody got like a time slot
at first I first I let everybody choose
between two different rough time slots
uh one was like at noon for me and one
was late at night for me
because I wanna uh to be okay for you
know every time zone
uh
[Music]
and then after you chose one you were
assigned to
um like a Time
oh what the hell
I didn't see that one coming
so like really exact time
however my my staff person not janma who
assigned it
missed one important detail okay
a piece of meet and greets
so
closely and exactly times for every
person who is attending
that
for some reason this staff member forgot
to assign me a break like not even a
five minute break was planned
and I'm like
yeah something there you see there's two
hours of meet and greets yeah you know
what five minutes per person okay
there's something missing there what
about my five minutes
but it was fun it was fine
I was like no no problem we're gonna
power fruit in so I don't wanna
I don't wanna you know mess up the whole
time schedule
[Music]
yeah but stepson was like okay um I'm
sorry I I really forgot that next time
next time
but overall the meeting rate was really
a big success and I think
definitely want to do it more often it
was fun talking to everyone it was
really comfy because it was not like at
a shitty time for me because like all
the other meet and greets were often as
[\h__\h] like not only the meet and greets
but like conventional appearances where
the meet and greets would often happen
where uh usually at like bad times for
me
um and this time I could choose my own
times and they were still relatively
comfortable for me
oh it was fun
it was fun I want to do it again you
guys are really sweet to me it was nice
listening to everybody oh yeah yeah so
many people tall oh wow
Sydney is newer I think
everybody told me like what kind of
games they
um like like seeing me play and how long
they've been watching me yeah yeah and
they showed me their merchandise
and uh yeah I look cute I feel like
there was something I wanted to talk
about
one person
one person Korean bro was
um asking me about my like if I ever did
this like personality test that's really
um popular in Korea I didn't do it yet
but I think that was like what 16 17
personality test or so
I need to do it I need to do it
do you guys know that test that person
is on the fifth round
huh the person with a crown Maybe
and bti yeah yeah yeah yeah you know BT
okay
please leave
the round
by the latest after this one
one round only place per person
okay
[Music]
it's more for entertainment
I mean you know good I have done it
have they done it on stream how long
does it take how long does that one test
take
[Music]
and if you don't leave then I'll have to
kick you out
I don't know how to do it but I'll
figure it out
I will forgive people staying for two
rounds but not four or five rounds okay
[Music]
I was doing such a nice Dorito
coins
money money money oh makes me funny
[Music]
oh I like this map oh it's coffee
this is supposed to be Sydney
[Music]
impression
I feel like she just said
[Music]
behind us oh okay I think they're around
I think they're grounded
[Music]
foreign
please please please please
[Music]
well I mean overall I'm not
it's like [\h__\h] these
[Music]
for my standards okay okay how do I kick
someone out uh for real
for real for real
you guys know please tell me well
um
[\h__\h] I don't know let's see if they
leave I think they left
thank you
wow why is there no function to kick
someone out that's actually a pretty uh
ridiculous
[Music]
maybe they thought that Mario Kart is
such a peaceful game question mark
question mark question mark
peaceful game that you wouldn't need
something like that
well also that person that any unlooking
person has been in here several times as
well
not consecutively but
[Music]
I think that person's like their first
time at least
is it a new version of the calamari
desert
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
Kiana for the Japan Expo
oh that's already over isn't it
that's gonna take a long time until the
next Japan Expo
[Music]
this is
what what
I guess it's a different version
[Music]
thank you
we're all so close together
come on banana come on banana oh okay I
guess
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm sorry
it was already in the game
about question mark
foreign
[Music]
was amazing
Donkey Kong
[Music]
oh
ah the head Anya is a Korean fan maybe
they didn't understand in English
my nose is Twitchy ah
[Music]
okay let me
committing but you guys might be so mad
sometimes okay
[Music]
so angry
foreign
smoothie tonight
[Music]
please please uh
I think you have to go I think you were
many times
can you please let's go
let's go on Sky High Sunday
thank you
[Music]
it's starting
Nintendo Direct starting now I thought
it was wait it's starting now
it's all Nintendo director
in 30 minutes right okay okay what the
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh it's just ah the countdown sides and
it goes for 30 minutes what the [\h__\h]
that's like
about as bad as the whole life English
Cube okay
[Music]
okay they always do that wow I didn't
know they started Dead really
um
Sky High Sunday this map looks so yummy
yum yum yum
only practice thank you
do they cut out the 30 minutes after the
stream is over
because that archive must be really long
otherwise
they don't no no I don't
know
wait but they're doing a 30 minutes
countdown for a trailer a movie trailer
or is it more than just a trailer
[Music]
okay you all suck all of you suck
you suck so much
[Music]
cool that was dangerous
tricks on point
on point
foreign
[Music]
except for the very beginning
[\h__\h] cat hair on my nose
that night
now should we go slime
okay it's okay I only had one left
that's fine
[Music]
yeah oh nice nice nice little the
smaller Bin My smoothness no
so far oh [\h__\h] missing all the tricks
and yet I'm only six can you guys
believe it
[Music]
oh
okay blue shell coming through
it's really dangerous but for some
reason I'm going left now even though
I'm unfamiliar with it
[Music]
it went fine now get your nose itchy
nose
foreign
[Music]
so well and I only played this map once
before okay only once
I swear
but why ain't you guys surprised by how
skilled I was what a gamer what a driver
what a driver what a racer it's it's all
the GTA that I've been playing probably
that's why I'm so good today it's the
GTA
[Music]
believe it or not
biggest game right now
okay what do we have
um where's the baby Park oh baby Park
Waits Nolan wait no one is new isn't it
okay never mind let's do snow land
there's no land this uh
[Music]
yeah honestly it might not even be so
much [\h__\h] GTA may have really
improved my driving skills
a little bit I mean it's in GTA you
gotta be really careful to not bump too
much into other cars when especially
when you're on the Run
wait that one
that that one pop team epic character oh
and the Pokemon Bronco
Roku character
I see you guys I'll see you guys
I for faster
I don't I I know thank you
[Music]
well whoa those
Graphics no actually looked pretty good
Daisy looking flawless and beautiful
oh oh I really like um how the items
come in into this map
I think I really liked that previously
to go the right way
[\h__\h] by these [\h__\h] then you can
actually manage to get two items
you just have to follow the trail
[Music]
yourself get hit by my bananas
I'm gonna leave some yeah okay okay
no one oh okay at least I got a coin
nose itchy nose itchy
[Music]
yeah well I got two items I got two
items
[Applause]
oh and a Bullet Bill okay
foreign
[Music]
is fine for me okay
but I'm I know I'm gonna [\h__\h] it up
somehow I know I know I know I know
[Music]
and maybe not
oh
[Music]
um hello
you you could have given me that
Rory
what the [\h__\h]
to me that one
huh
[Music]
I mean okay still amazing look Rory I
never want to see your face again if I
never say your face again I don't care
that's um Maroon 5 yo
oh no
oh my my [\h__\h] throat
it of course it would be dessert because
it was so close
I I I got to first place fair and square
okay I did not cheat
I was just a little bit lucky okay
yeah lots of yelling I need to stop I
need to stop
huh
[Music]
um
mmm
[Music]
but that felt good
for once being at the [\h__\h] top
that it was just all everything all the
circumstances
kim chicken
kimchi and chicken
all the circumstances just to stay they
all fell
all together in place so nicely
thanks for entertaining while I'm at
work you're welcome
good luck at work hope you're having fun
[Music]
let's go I like this map
it's challenging but it's not that
difficult for me
I have a feeling for this map
this is what happens when you're not
sure which item to go for and you just
go for the middle and then bake where
Granny's spaghetti right oh
I was so close
I need to wash my nose it's so itchy
[Music]
I keep on touching my nose it's not
getting better
[Music]
no item oh no I didn't get an item from
the previous one that's okay
[Music]
getting the triple mushroom
when I'm like fruit forth is insanely
lucky these items are fine too might be
fine might I say
[Music]
oh
come at me bro come at me bro come at me
bro come on
[Music]
come on
we're seeing unbelievable skills
Chihuahua as if we've never ever seen
her like describe ever before holy [\h__\h]
she's like a different person is it
really her driving
she's doing amazingly well we're so
proud of her let's go girl
oh that's fine everybody everybody gets
hit by the Thunder this is okay this is
okay no don't don't don't don't
lose hope everything's gonna be okay
Chihuahua
she won't okay
oh
[Music]
boy
can't
I can't believe it
downfall of a legend
whoa whoa I did not deserve to
[Laughter]
served
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] was that
also that that dude with the spiky hair
I think he's been here for a while I
think you gotta leave if I'm wrong and
I'm wrong and also the dudes with the
small eyes and the big nose
you you've been around for a while I
think
I think you guys gonna go
it was a cute girl on the left oh
[Music]
well I mean we're missing people anyway
so in this case
in this case I forgive you but uh
dudes
[Music]
Lobby is not letting people in
um
[Music]
oh what the [\h__\h]
so who are these two Blaze
Blaze and Lucas
you little shits how dare you betray the
rules of kfb
you should know better this is the last
the last one I think by the way because
then I will prepare for the watch along
oh this might be yeah I knew it I knew
it was too early
if you guys are so addicted to Mario
Kart then you guys cannot stop playing
and then go to the public Lobby
huh
I know playing with NPCs is not fun but
I'm sure there's public lobbies that you
could try out
[Music]
nice driving skills koala
whoa hey look at me
[Music]
me playing today is the first time in a
long time if you ignore that that couple
minutes at the at the Comic-Con
normally I'm like really
Rusty you know when I haven't played it
for a long time
so we're Rusty like it's so [\h__\h] look
today
oh
you gotta say I'm oh my impressing
myself
whoa whoa
you're lucky that blue shell didn't get
you
[Music]
someone tried to kill me with a green
shell I am not surprised
I know you didn't want to do that
reclaimer I know that wasn't on purpose
it's okay
you know I will I will say that that one
time the previous match where I got
second I deserve to be first so let's
say today I got first okay because I
think
that was actually legit
legit scale unlike the other time where
it was mostly just being really lucky
[Music]
oh
what the [\h__\h]
yeah thank you thank you for agreeing I
agree with myself too
whoa
thank you
so this is what you do
when you win cookie wow at the Finish
Line you party together all right
[Laughter]
pickle you sweet potatoes
love you guys
no no I don't think they got impatient
that was not on purpose I think hitting
me with the green shell alright guys
[Music]
thank you that was fun that was nice and
we played some Mario Kart together and
it was the first time in a long time I
think it was first lives except those
people that don't wait yeah yeah yeah
yeah those [\h__\h]
[Music]
so okay now we're gonna go
Don't Laugh at My Hand hands okay
oh my God
oh what is going on
man let's get rid of everything
oh no mom oh you don't really see it
that well that's fine
watch along
everybody is welcome to stay and watch
it together
we're going to connect this perfectly
to Mario movie trailer and I'm gonna put
the link
oh whoa 130
000 oh there was also a new Pokemon
trailer today I saw that one I mean it
wasn't too special I wonder when the
hell are they gonna show the evolutions
huh
okay
[Music]
the thumbnail today is amazing isn't it
yeah we saw one Evolution well that's
pretty much it
smell here later onion
[Music]
it was cute though that Evolution was
cute yeah
um so now we need um
where's my screen
there it is
[Music]
can you guys look away for a second
no of course you can so let me do it
properly
okay
Point okay here I am here I am once
again I turn into pieces can't deny it
can't pretend just
[Music]
I Cry
behind his hazel eyes
can keep the music for now it's just
fitting
no no no no
playing myself
[Music]
anymore
here I am once again
baby
[Music]
I'm so excited for the karaoke on on
Saturday
I'm so
[Music]
excited
that's it
[Music]
wait never mind
um
I mean
no man we're playing a Nintendo game
with permissions from Nintendo how much
of this can I show
I mean
Mario is literally in the game and you
know I'll just I'll just keep it without
anything
the timer
oh
do we need a timer
I mean in a timer I guess but then we
start we started I don't know where do
we even start for the Vlog launcher
[Music]
okay shut up game
chat app it's not live yet not really
um
online stopwatch oh [\h__\h]
foreign
let me get this from my movie chamber
what
oh I'm gonna stop wondering though
and put it into my launch party thingy
oh my God
amazing all right reset and I guess at
the
um
um isn't there another countdown before
it actually starts usually
for all the people who watch the Vlog
okay if it starts right away
then we're gonna start
when it starts
uh oh yeah I need to
um
[Music]
do it so that you guys can't hear it
okay I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready you
can start now
ah I'm gonna start oh wait I should
tweet maybe that we're doing uh watch
along
uh we are done with Mario Kart
now let's do the movie lunch along
for for the Mario movie is there a date
for the Mario movie when it's releasing
oh
[Laughter]
sorry never mind ignore me ignore me
April 7th oh wow that's still still a
while to go
so they can still change their mind
about the voice acting and get me for
Mario instead no
hmm
what do you think
taking screenshot for
Twitter
ah wait it sounds like we're doing a
watch along for the Mario movie as if
it's already out in my tweet
let's go
with bird View at the Mario movie
stick big no not sneak big we're
watching the full movie now hope you
guys are ready and I hope you guys have
popcorn
bird View
birdview yes Birdville
you guys are lucky so lucky you made the
right choice of being here
reporting made for piracy it's not
stop saying no I got a deal what a deal
it's not such a deal is this a whole
movie yes yes of course it is
no no it's not
no they're such a movie does not exist
yet
which is
surprising I guess if you think about
that no actually I guess I think I think
have you guys ever thought
in all these years of the Mario
um games being a thing also what the
[\h__\h] is that nerfed ass on Mario I feel
of you for real for real just like me
for real for real but have you guys ever
thought of oh why is there no movie for
this
eh there's a live action movie overlay
but have you guys ever desired and
thought of you know if this needs a
movie
I I never thought of that
you know never
never
had the the hustle is
maybe as a kid really
I never really thought that it could be
possible or that I mean I mean it's not
it's obviously not impossible but it's
just like huh it never felt necessary to
make a movie
it's weird hmm
maybe in Pokemon or Delta but not Mario
or Zelda movie oh
wait after the Mario movie who knows
maybe in five years we'll have a Zelda
movie oh oh wait you know what I feel
like
I would I would be so behind a real life
action movie of Zelda
oh
I feel like they could nail that
they could ruin it but they could also
nail it
that would be amazing I can totally see
it you know like in the style of Lord of
the Rings
with some pretty elves
oh
link doesn't speak well we'll make him
[\h__\h] speak
oh whoa whoa and they have so much story
that they could make into a movie they
could do a trilogy
or five low G
wow no not we don't need Chris Pratt in
that one please
do there were rumors about them really
no way how old are those rumors
they have a tell them what black I don't
know that one
and if we move more than freezes series
like I I don't want to see Zelda moving
in you know 3D Graphics like this I
legit want to see it
in live action and that's kind of I feel
like
um rare normally I would want to see
something like like Pokemon for example
in its original like Graphics you know
what I mean in the original look
what I feel like Zelda has a lot of
potential to work as
as
[Music]
um
as a live real people hmm
I hope I hope someone does that I want
to be alive when
when they bring out a movie like wait is
it is it starting wait what the [\h__\h]
for some reason I had it like on pause
is it starting
no okay I've refreshed okay okay okay
okay
how much longer
four minutes what five
okay
okay thank God
thank God
000 viewers wow wow wow
oh now I seen the recommendations that
there's a near automata for a Nintendo
switch which now really makes so much
sense and I understand now why I got a
new automata uh
um
um advertisement in on YouTube like
yesterday
[Laughter]
yeah it launched today apparently a new
version I didn't even know about that
happening or maybe I've completely
forgot it
watching this Mario movie night with
something huh
wait why are you why are you
on future why in the future
hey
wow doesn't have premium
um no no I have premium on this account
but
um
on on my I was watching on my iPad I'm
not logged into any account on my iPad I
really should
because I can't even go through like my
previously watched videos
when you don't have an account you can't
go for your previously watched videos it
sucks
but I'm too lazy to log in
um
the part where he Mario is all over this
guys well so is Mario gonna talk in this
movie
oh yeah right because Chris Pratt is
going to talk right oh that's what Chris
Pratt is here for right he's not the one
in the in the trousers and the Red Hats
and
would have been awfully small Mario
weird weird body proportions for Chris
Pratt
okay I guess okay what the [\h__\h] does
Chris Pratt sound like I don't remember
is he gonna do an Italian accent because
I'm I'm gonna be honest Mario without an
Italian accent would be so wrong but
then if they're gonna give him an
Italian accent they should have just
casted an Italian person I'm sorry but
what
he said no accidents
oh
all right guys
we're not watching this no no good night
everybody bye-bye
why is he is he gonna say Mamma Mia
Elise
Sammy is gonna say Mama Mia
and he's gonna do
what
what the [\h__\h]
also has Daisy in this movie please tell
me Daisy's here probably not only only
Peach probably huh can we at least get a
side Cameo of Daisy
hey why did they not cast me
oh man what a disappointment
oh no
what kind of decision is that you have
to have an Italian accent
ah
what
so so Mario is American now
Mario is American ah
European presentation
Italian oh oh we should watch Italian
dub when the movie comes out yeah I'm
gonna travel to Italy and watch the
movie in the Italian movie theaters
[Laughter]
that's that's the only the only time
ever when you would want to watch
um the dubbed version of a movie and
rather than the original oh my God
he's always been American Italian well
okay but he's also always had an Italian
accent
okay Italy I'm moving my trip to Italy
starting right when the Nintendo logo
starts uh um yeah I'm going in in March
instead just kidding mommy don't worry
hello
Mamma Mia
oh it's another Comic-Con right now how
long are you coming hello
when I wonder are they watching this I
want I want to see the reaction of the
New York Comic-Con people
are they watching it in like a seminar
room or so
Daddy
Zelda build up fell down two please
on
oh
wait am I the only one who expected
crisp
a
let's go
is that a minion
but it's green why is it mini and green
wait there's a blue one too
copyright
mm-hmm
when his his homework deadline is in 11
days
while they're getting special treatment
can someone mention takanasi kiwawa
hello I'm streaming too
Chris son
subtitles
Chris my son didn't know he had a son
does he have a son
it's me
Koopas he had to think hard for that one
face Docs
don't look at me so closely please
it's me it's me don't don't look
um
Bowser
oh
Well Jack Black is cool
but I want to hear his Bowser voice
though like how is he gonna make a
Bowser voice
this voice sounds so normal
no hate but you know
I want to hear your evil evil voice
oh let me do full screen
oh
is it an original story or the story of
the first
Mario game
which is basically just rescuing Daisy
holy [\h__\h]
it's like a Marvel movie oh not anymore
it's so intimidating
oh
oh my gosh like Lord of the Rings
it's like Lord of the Rings
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God the penguin King
oh
my that's so good
needing the cuter voice
what this looks so good holy [\h__\h]
that's what all of Nintendo's budget is
going
oh my God
oh my God it looks so [\h__\h] good
oh
oh his it looks a bit different and
where's the butt
butt Mario your butt
what a little girl where did your
diapers go
his face is rounder than usual
how cute
oh my God
it's amazing
look a little girl
whoa Charlie Day Charlie day it's not a
YouTuber
ah
oh that was sudden
he's gonna get with Daisy uh peach sorry
you're not getting with Daisy and
Luigi's getting with Daisy
kiss kiss kiss
[Music]
that looked so high quality
can we watch it in 4D
4D please
exciting
[Music]
I mean Mario's face looked a bit weird
but I can get used to it at the rest
looked amazing
holy [\h__\h] like
wow
that was that was way more than I
expected I expected actually something
way worse than that
right
I want to hear Mario talk a bit more
though I guess hmm hard to judge now
it would be so funny if it was an
Italian accent don't you think
you know the whole charm about Mario
but besides that besides that is amazing
oh oh the sceneries
the locations looked so cool and so so
detailed so much
so much I don't know life and and beauty
so saturated
um Jack Black I mean he didn't speak
much in the trailer but it sounded
fitting yeah
the Penguins
I guess those are the penguins that you
know in my Super Mario 64 you could you
know drop down the world right
ah
oh wow I'm excited for the movie now
actually it's good that we watched the
trailer because otherwise
before that I was absolutely not
interested in the movie
watch along but once it gets released
it's only in the in the cinema though
how am I gonna do a cinema launch along
huh
I'll have to wait until it's like
somewhere available online for all of us
on the DVD or something like that
Blu-ray
IRL stream and could bring my my phone
into a Twitter space but that's probably
pretty illegal too
I'm definitely gonna get blocked for oh
yeah oh yeah I guess yeah we also I'll
just go to cinema yeah yeah
at the same time and then just share our
thoughts
afterwards I guess we can't go at the
same time because they're all at
different times but you know what I mean
you know what I mean
um
yeah three to six months until you can
watch it at home probably yeah
um
that was dope that was really convincing
really convincing
hmm
that's that's that's that's that's like
even even higher quality than the last
Pixar movies or so that I've seen
hmm
but it has that charm
it's like good 3D good Freddy
hmm
exciting wow
nice okay
hmm
[Laughter]
son toad toad that's good you think it's
good that he had a more down-to-earth
normal voice I don't know
um and I was listening to Toad's voice I
was hoping a little bit more for like ah
kind of voice but oh dubbing the whole
movie like that um would probably
destroy someone's throat and I guess it
would annoy a lot of people
in the cinema this way it's more like
mainstream I guess
for mainstream viewers
told boys told boys Mario voice
not quite as expected but it's fine it's
totally fun I'm a tailed voices pog
oh Army toad oh yeah they should have
casted Amish told on me as as Chris
Pratt no as Mario
yeah cast me as Chris Pratt who is
cousin as Mario I will play Chris
Pratt's role
as Mario you can still credit me as
Chris Pratt that's okay
that's okay that's okay
okay
um
I'll see you guys tomorrow tomorrow for
GTA 5. yeah yeah
yeah we're getting closer to the end not
finally tomorrow but we're getting
closer so let's have some fun tomorrow
and then tomorrow after the uh after the
play time I'm gonna read some super
chats okay
okay okay
I screamed too much
for Mario Kart I think it's better to
just chillax now
almost same time same time
I think same time same time
all right then oh wow crazy day I had a
free hour recording I'll play it rust I
deleted rust and now I played Mario Kart
and watched the movie trailer wow wow
wow wow
so much holy [\h__\h]
uh I'm a bit exhausted a bit tired
I'm gonna eat some lasagna now
roller coaster it really was a roller
coaster day but the the recording really
went really well it was really fun I'm
sad it was my last
shoe but I hope they invite me again for
some official programs
but it runs so well three hours of big
fun and you guys don't even know yet who
the the Newbie is right because every
episode there's a newbie
I don't think you guys know right
still secret but look forward to it
I need to get these cat hairs off of my
face
so and in German we say
[Music]
yes
I'll see you tomorrow how I feel about
rest
uh yeah
let's see I'll see you tomorrow
[Music]
thanks for having fun with me
and cheering me up with me
in Mario Kart
bye-bye love you
[Music]
foreign