[Music]
just
hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
hmm
uh
oh
let's go
[Music]
where's my btm
wait
i still have the chicken in my hands
[Music]
thank you callie well you also reached
100k
we all did we all did all whole ibn
members
have reached 100k
uh either during the stream or shortly
after
let's say congratulations
we amazing
i'm so glad that all of you like
welcomed us so nicely and enjoy our
streams
so far really really i'm glad i'm really
happy
[Music]
so today um i want to celebrate i want
to party
with chicken of course with chicken in
my hand
i thought since i really like to
interact
with everyone interact with my fans
communicate with them
i really uh enjoy talking to you guys
so while doing some small talk i thought
we should do a a q a kind of thing so
we're doing martial
so during today like a couple
hours ago i opened the mashima
and i asked you guys for questions and
you'll send me lots of questions oh by
the way
i i changed the
some mic settings because i told you in
before stream probably some of you
missed it but i told you that i actually
have a really good mic right now thanks
to cali
but i think these settings are kind of
wrong but i
i played around with it is it a bit
better today or no
it's better
really and the echo thing that you guys
talked about uh some people
i noticed it too i noticed it too but
some people said um
like it sounds like i'm like
uh blasting music from my speakers and
the mic is picking up but the spooky
thing is
i've been using uh noise cancelling
headphones all along
so raise the mic volume
it's already at the maximum right now
maybe i'll
turn down the music a bit then okay and
that's weird but do you hear the echo
again
that weird spooky echo
is it is it did you hear today i really
don't know
why it does that it sounds mapped still
but no echo at least oh what
i can help you with volume okie dokie
we'll figure it out eventually but at
least yeah that's that echo
really ugh it annoyed me so much i don't
know i
kept doing that
[Music]
at least that's something that makes me
happy okay
well done oh
what you do hear some weird noise
i'll check again after the stream i'll
check my own stream i feel like i know
what's best
oh
anyway we'll figure it out but i hope
it's a little bit better today let's go
well today i'll be asked l and not be
asking questions i'll be answering
and since i got you guys to send me some
martial they're not open anymore because
i had it open for a really short time
and we got
hundreds of questions and my manager was
like
can we close it soon i don't want to go
through anymore
and i was like yeah let's close it it's
already so much holy holy [\h__\h]
is
you guys oh my god
so i realized you guys really had a lot
of questions to me that so that's
it's good that i'm doing this now
all right let's go
uh i'll answer as many as possible
let's see can i answer this one
[Music]
maybe this one
where is the one that i wanted to answer
this is difficult there's too many oh
yeah first let's go with this the most
important question
i mean you would think i would know the
answer to this question
okay i think i know the answer
i think i know the answer no no no no
the answer is make yago
proud
[Music]
jago is not alive then
what is the meaning of life the answer
to that would in that timeline the
answer would be
to bring jago to life
so you have to create yakult and
yeah there always has to be a yahoo in
every timeline
all right we got that one
i think that one that was a good answer
i would say
oh yeah he's he's one more
wondering what kind of streams we can
look forward to in the future
i will have some nihongo no banco
streams like cali and amelia was
planning uh i am i don't need
i don't need frac i didn't i don't need
to practice japanese like
cali or
i don't need that i can teach you
japanese possibly
uh
[Laughter]
should i should i teach you one um
important
let me teach you a good one
all how does this work i gotta make it
bigger again oh there we go
i okay this is this is the
this proves that i don't need to
practice japanese this means
this is chimimorio i don't know
it means something like spirits
uh evil spirits from the woods or
whatever something like that
i don't need that i can teach you
something
[Music]
i will do in the future um
uh like i'll play like rpg games and
stuff
if you enjoy those two and uh i'll play
some fun games in between just like fall
guys
and i actually i was thinking of playing
this game that i saw uh
oh my papa thinks i'm i'm speaking bad
japanese
because i i i said some bad words in
yeah oh yeah i'll play against an impact
when it comes
comes out and i want to play atelier
soon for tails off the thing is like i
played all of them
pretty much so i don't really like to
replay games that i already played
and but oh yeah the
thing that i wanted to play i wanna play
uh
the game where uh you're a chicken and
you have to carry
what was it an egg
do you guys know what i what i mean egg
is broken hearties too
we'll play that this week probably but
other than that
uh yeah we'll also do some karaoke
streams
and um oh yeah minecraft yes yes yes
i saw a certain senpai i shouldn't
mention her name too much
and so a certain senpai played a lot of
minecraft and that made me
interested in minecraft before i didn't
care at all
generally not maybe not the best gamer
but i just really enjoy
rpg games yeah um
but if you have any suggestions on good
rpgs especi especially like
um anime style rpgs
i had to leave but i heard you were
roasting
bye i heard you were going to buy more
alcohol are you so frustrated about not
being able to speak
proper japanese that you need to get
drunk
oh ninokuni i never played ninokuni yeah
that's a good idea
next time next time you have problems
i'll be on standby just call me on
discord as your joker
all right
savage bird
all right good question we have a we
have a good question here closer to each
other
[Music]
um
all right let me get this no questions
[Music]
i was wondering what you think is the
best way to learn new languages
it's something i've always wanted to do
but it was never
never really sure where to start thank
you and i'm looking forward to
all your future streams so much
and what japanese
and i i did start learning
i tried to start learning another
language recently
chinese but then now i have the problem
i'm too lazy i'm just too lazy to
keep it going but it was going well like
especially since i already know japanese
chinese is um not so hard because you
can like
kind of guess the meaning of the
characters
um but one the most important thing
that really helped me when i learned
japanese
is uh communication each one doesn't
know your body communication
and how to remind
um
so i actually when i learned japanese i
i
i bought some books and stuff but
i never used them and i didn't take any
lessons
i just taught myself and and talked a
lot
with japanese-speaking people
yeah yeah now the books i don't know
where they are i had them i bought them
like ages ago
and i opened the first page and i was
like ah
blah no burn this book
[Music]
i learned in bird school uh so
for many years so there's nothing
special about me being able to speak
english
from where i come from basically
everyone speaks fluent english
[Music]
um
there was a time when i tried to learn
latin
but the thing is now this is important
i sucked at latin i was
so bad at latin well you could say latin
is just a horrible language in itself
there's no way you can have
fun learning that language but
um i think if i would have had interest
and passion
in learning latin then i might have
had done a better job at it uh
so this is important i had passion and
interest towards japanese but not
towards latin
it was so hard oh my god
[Music]
is
so uh to
summarize you need passion and
communication
passion and communication passion
yeah and of course it's also easier
the younger you are the easier it is to
learn languages
and i mean even if i didn't have a
teacher for japanese um
[Music]
i it's probably better to take lessons
but at the same time you shouldn't only
rely on lessons
you should also talk to people who speak
that language yeah
oh but what's really easy is that like
going on a
on a exchange here or something like
that
[Music]
i never did an exchange but uh
i would really recommend it really go go
abroad for real
well that's that's such a serious advice
for me
[Music]
okay
yes
wow that's a long oh
what's this okay this person made an
effort to also add english so you guys
can read it with me
very nice
[Music]
one of my favorite streams of pekora
senpai
was the stream that she did when she did
like a
minecraft rta not not the recent one the
one
where she tried to get the trident
i watched it all in one sitting even
though i was watching an archive but
i don't know what it is like i don't
know why
i i can watch
like she can entertain for hours and i
that's
one thing i really look up to her about
like she she'll also just do small talk
while she's gaming it's just so easy for
her and it's so smooth and she's so
funny
yeah so oh
[Music]
i wonder what what would be a good
collaboration between me and pecora
senpai because i'm
i'm not the type who wants to make fun
of her or so
i'm the type like i want to do
everything for her
i know
that would be the bestest
the bestest
oh i want to do a pretty collab with her
but that is still very impossible
what's the point if you're not fully
fekora uh i have to say i mean i guess
it's funny
um i i i do laugh at when people are
bullying her sometimes teacher elite
english
ah i guess i could do that
do you have any ideas guys fall guys
oh yeah yeah i still have to get the
chicken costume so i'll be playing some
more for you guys this week
but uh yeah we could eventually do a
vlog i just call up but
does that will work as a collaboration
not really probably ah horror game oh i
guess we could do that because i really
hate horror games
horror movies i've never ever played a
horror game before
and yeah she should maybe introduce me
to that
japanese minecraft server that would be
great
[Music]
but if she'll show me the server i hope
she will not blow me up
[Music]
in a horror game stream i'm really like
a big
uh how do you say a big chick chicken
oh that's funny i'm a big chicken when
it comes to
hurricane that's funny that's quite
funny
hmm
i didn't even mean to say that
i just laughed and and something popped
in my chest that that's
very concerning oh here's a
here's a deep one
what way some of your last time last
minute thoughts before
or during your debut do you wish you
could have done anything differently
um before the debut
oh my gosh especially the 24 hours
before the debut i was
i i don't know if i should say but
i was very let's just say i was very
emotional i was very emotional
and worried and um
there's however one thing that um really
cheered me up
on the night before the debut
i really um couldn't sleep at all
and i was maybe crying but
then i saw um a fan art
from hikosan and he goes and
does a lot of fan art of piccolo so i
always was watching he goes on some
fan arts and he surprised me
with a fan out of me did you see it i
retweeted it it was so amazing it was
like
oh
i saw that and i started crying again
but this time it was more like happy
crying
i was just so happy
[Music]
i said no
and strength from that so thank you
everyone for the fan art really it
really cheers me it makes me laugh it
makes me happy
yay thank you and what i look at all of
this thank you so much
and about what i would do differently i
would maybe like to um
i would have liked to have a bet no not
a better microphone this microphone is
supposed to be good but i just had
have the wrong settings i don't know it
should have been better
yeah yeah but other than that i think i
did well
i think like once i once the stream was
going
i i i thought it was going well for for
what i
actually expected especially
next next door kiara if the rest of the
whole ibm members were your employees
for your restaurant how good
do you think they would be as employees
oh that's a good one that's a good one
okay
she has tentacles so she can she can
really help out well i think
um she like carries so much so many
plates and stuff
yeah no no i'm not talking about making
her into food
we we don't sell seafood in my
restaurant i don't like seafood
is maybe a bit too small to serve
the customers i don't know
i wonder she could play
she could sing an acapella the
background music of our restaurant so it
could be constantly her singing
and um kelly
i don't think she should be working like
in my restaurant because
as soon as she's like unhappy with the
customer i feel like she would kill them
i'm a bit worried about that we don't we
don't want any customer complaints i
mean
i mean we probably wouldn't be getting
them if she would kill them
but still
probably not a good idea amelia i think
she would do a good job because she's a
really good girl and she
she knows what she does she works hard
so
yeah i think i think probably amelia
and ina would work the hardest
and the bestest amina is a chef
oh can she cook i wonder
maybe if gouda can cook she could be
cooking
um but callie probably shouldn't work in
my restaurant
convince
[Music]
oh
there was a similar question to them
to the previous one
saturday was an absolute marathon for
people watching and must have been very
intense for the five of you yeah yeah
yeah
indeed how were you feeling throughout
the day
and would you say there were any
particular highs lows or general
my memory memorable memorable
mem memorable
moments and
yeah i originally didn't plan to stay up
so long
i really got crazy after a while
uh hi hi
was when pagoda senpai commented on my
stream
and i'm i was glad that i was the second
and not like the last one because having
i'm i'm glad that i
got it over so quickly and then after
that i was just really relieved
so yeah uh and other than that i think
we already spoke about
everything so um
[Music]
now i would say yes
is it true that kelly only wants you to
stay dead so you can live with her
forever in the underworld
i will say yes um
she probably will say no um
maybe ask her when i'm not around
ask her in another round then she might
should probably still not admit admitted
but
she'll probably think about it
i know she does
[Music]
oh
what was your reaction when you knew
hookah was going to be a papa
i was like what
what what
are you serious because like i know
all of his works and and i've always
like
thought he was super super cool
tonight
i just felt so blessed like oh i am
going to be
my papa's daughter yeah and he's so
supportive too like he's been
especially you know my papa is a busy
busy man okay
but he's been watching uh all
our streams since the debut
which means like during in japan it was
night time
okay he stayed up all through that then
also watched the collab
and also watched my fall guys stream
after that
so he stayed up the whole i mean i guess
he took
a nap probably in between because he
wasn't as nervous as me
but he stayed up for all that and even
after that
he's still showing up and everyone
streamed not only mine
and he's tweeting about that he's such a
supportive papa i'm so happy i have such
a sweet papa that like even in his even
though he's busy like he cares so much
about
this and i'm i'm really really thankful
[Music]
so yeah it's a huge honor yeah he he
likes feature but he's been
in tv series for a while like especially
on tony
[Music]
next
where did you learn japanese there are
many famous tourist attractions in japan
but where do you want to go
i'm looking forward to the future
delivery
delivery am i delivering chicken no i
know what you mean
um well yeah i already mentioned i
learned japanese by myself
and they're famous many of them
i like even though i'm on fire i like
snow so i want to go
to hokkaido in the winter time and see
the snow festival there's like a snow
festival
in um in february i think
[Music]
i um to see more of like
not not so much the the the busy
tourist places but more like the calm
landscapes
uh happy birthday no this michaela it's
my birthday happy birthday
wow i picked that up well
and what was i saying dirty brain what
was i saying
i
happy birthday
[Music]
i'm sorry there's a bunch of questions
which are quite similar so i'm trying to
[Music]
find some that are not similar wait wait
there is some that i want to answer
congrats on your successful w you're
very successful
i'm excited to see this chicken and her
friends grow me too
are there any of your senpai's in
in particular who you would love to
collab with besides becca of course
and do you have anything in mind that
you would like to do thank greetings
from germany
[Music]
um yes okay so
there's a bunch so i really like a lot
of my senpai's
i i love i love so many that it's
actually like
if i don't if i mention like 10 and then
don't mention the others i feel like
that's please
please don't think anything of that if i
don't mention a certain name
but recently especially recently
for like uh people who have already
interacted with me
i would love to collab with poga senpai
because she right from the beginning she
was very supportive of us
she kind of sang a song for us on
youtube
she uploaded a video kind of dedicated
to us that was super sweet
she has so much energy and well she's a
fennec fox
and i'm a phoenix yes yes not the other
way around
so collabing would be really fun with
her i think
as well as nana senpai i really like
that by we're both orange and she's so
bubbly and cute and she sings so well
i really like her and let me say but i
really like all
everyone from the new generation nami
said but it's really calming she's also
been very supportive
she's been also i think on all of our
debut streams in the comments section
yeah
of course also put on senpai she reminds
me of of arc knight's characters
and uh oh like maybe like uh kirio koko
uh i would love to be uh in a in a
reddit review with kiriyokoko senpai
or i also love madden senpai i love her
singing
and she's so much fun like i i really
also enjoy her her art streams
and she her talking is always really
nice to listen to
and she's just really funny really
entertaining so i'll collab with madden
senpai with us
i love madden senpai actually from whole
life fantasy fantasy i love everyone
ah there's so many know that i wanna but
fubuki senpai
let's say the last one there's so many
but phobic is senpai
[Music]
to be honest
to be honest um
i love fake senpai but fubiki senpai
is kind of the reason why i wanted to
join her
life
could have
i want to thank her if possible in
person
um for like motivating and
inspiring me
yeah she is such a good senpai she's
also super supportive and
uh i just love her she's such a
sweetheart and she plays arc knight so
actually we could do like an arc nights
collab maybe
something like that um because i play
arc knight
too she's really a nice nice senpai
let's move on
what time is oh we only have 50 minutes
left
[Music]
oh did i save that three times
oh yeah pick what happened by stream was
so funny today
that's a really long question
[Music]
where is that one question
there it is
there we go if you had to bring one
person or a thing
to a deserted island that had enough
food and fresh water to live until you
got rescued
who or what would you bring no cheating
by flying away from the island
i think we all know the answer to this
question
guess it
no you guys don't know my priorities yet
you are saying cali you don't know my
priorities
[Applause]
[Music]
especially since it says we have enough
food and enough fresh water to live
so it's kind of like a vacation
to go on
[Music]
in a nice environment at the ocean
with swimsuit i guess
we would be in swimsuits right um
yes
i mean with cali i think it would also
be fun because
if it's only a student she probably
would uh speak a bit
more openly about her feelings she she
would maybe
give in
especially if it takes a long time i'll
just i'll just tell her we have to
procreate
i don't know if you can procreate with
the death
well we gotta try you know i'll just i
want to tell her that uh
i will not tell her that we're getting
rescued we'll just
we'll just not tell her we'll tell her
we need to procreate
[Music]
okay i want to answer this one
love your streams your hats and you oh
thank you
timmy you're soaring for the tears of
top 2d
wife is like a majestic flaming bird
just like a barbecue chick
well you could you could you could write
a book
your choice of words is very good
anyway to help your papa with ideas
what's the next type of hat that you
would like to have
okay i still let me be real
i have a certain idea
for a future
outfit
i did not tell papa yet
actually i would like to
show how majestic a phoenix could be
by wearing like a really sexy sparkly
golden dress
can you imagine
can you imagine you know what i mean
like a like one that you would wear to
some
award show can you imagine
like a tight a tight one a tight-fitting
sparkly golden dress
maybe maybe if it could go up in flames
would be even cooler
so i know
it should oh yeah it should have like a
slit uh
for for one side of the leg
[Music]
oh yes please
but okay i'll also take more hats
[Music]
um
anything that my papa will give me to
wear
i think i love it anyway no matter what
it is
[Music]
actually i went for this pretty quickly
what joke
i also thought of this actually because
i've seen some fan art as well
of me and subaru senpai and subaru
senpai
is also one of those senpais that are
really sweet
in my opinion and fun and yeah
team bird yes team bird
we shall definitely collab if i'm really
looking for it
when the band is lifted and i can collab
with everyone
[Music]
i want to collab with everyone but the
question is also
do i ask my senpai's or should i wait
until they ask me because piccolo simple
probably never asked me
she's just so shy should i ask them
or should they ask me i don't know
it's hard it's a it's a hard thing you
know
how how do you get that happening i
asked them
i guess usually i'm the type who like
um you know does the action
that is necessary i'm the type who
reaches out first
when it comes to these things
[Music]
foreign
yeah oh yeah definitely i'll i'll try to
make a good impression
by like talking to them every now and
then first
and then and then i make the final move
i'll be like
please collab with me senpai
i'll do anything for you
i'm looking forward to all the collabs
in the future
[Music]
be
i'll probably do a singing stream this
week maybe
possibly after getting this microphone
to work better
so many so many comments
karaoke yeah when you do the chicken
dance when you 3dw
oh there's so many things i want to do
when i do 3dw but
i mean i guess i can do the chicken
dance whatever
use marin to get back
oh yeah minecraft stream possibly this
week
possibly isn't but i really haven't i
don't know how to play it but
we have a priority we have to get the
costume and fall guys first i really
need that costume i forgot
already when when it's gone but probably
soon so i really have to hurry up and i
also have to do an arc night stream
if possible my my account is [\h__\h]
that's not good enough for cc
chicken asmr what the hell is chicken
asmr
22 days 22 days oh maybe that's maybe
that's enough time
maybe that's enough time backpack ah we
could that
we could do that but this chicken is
broke
this chicken has no money to weigh you
i don't have money to whale
bug piper
i think tomorrow we'll do
some gaming stream not not a karaoke
stream yet but
um okay i think that's uh good enough
with the question i still
many of them were pretty similar and i'm
sorry if i couldn't answer your question
but i'll be doing this again probably
soon maybe
maybe maybe if we get to 200k soon
we could do this again for 200k and
again and again
and again and again
free to play gang actually no
i did already wail but it was too much
it was already too much i don't want to
whale again
yeah 200k let's go friends chicken
family
yeah all right guys let's move to
another screen
wow
for watching today i was really happy to
answer some of your questions i hope it
brought
some light into your life and
german stream
[Music]
no one will understand me
why are you holding those chicken dice
because i i'm hungry
i didn't eat dinner yet
for today see you in next year uh and if
you didn't do it yet please watch the
video that i uploaded on this channel
today i uploaded my version of the
book intro and which i played in my
debut stream but in the debut stream it
was cali who was uh reading the book
[Music]
it's not gonna take it's actually good
microphone quality in that video because
i didn't use this mic i use another mic
so
i still didn't decide on the ending
greeting
[Music]
you guys have ideas for ending greetings
i could say i could say in in
in german i could say outfit
can you guys even type that probably
most of you don't know how to type that
it's uh ow
probably if i write it in the chat i'll
be gone so fast
okay from now on and then greeting
is german it will be
one second at source
auf wiedersehen
will be saying this okay so everyone
learned some german for me today isn't
that nice
three two one
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
bye
oh stop to my channel subscribe
[Music]
is
i still
[Music]
wow