my change
[Music]
no one expects me to rise
foreign
[Music]
no one is the day
thank you
[Music]
if you wake me
a thousand times
[Music]
hello
hi
hi I mean a song tonight
hello hello
I'm always here hi guys
oh it's been quite a day
I've been I've been running all over the
place oh my goodness
all right
um
I skipped work for this oh Lord I hope
you're ready for some real high level
gameplay
for some high level gameplay I think
we'll get to maybe make a character
together because Vivo said that
um I can go ahead and like start and
like launch the game and then others can
like join in but I have I have the room
it's like open and ready I just need to
invite kikiwawa
um and then it should be
good to go but some of you may wonder
why did I start this up early
um because I wanted to do I need to do a
lyric dive
um I'm making myself do it now because I
I have to
um if that's not your cup of tea uh if
you're just here for Baldur's Gate
Boulders Baldur's balders
uh come back come back in like 45
minutes ish
um and then well actually you know we
might I think the lyric dive is only
gonna take about 15 to 20 minutes it's
not going to be that long and then after
that we're making a character
um which of course Barbarian Berserker
and I'm trying to figure out what the
best build to start off with is but
I I got you guys here I'm sure that
you'll you'll give me some advice but I
might need to kind of look it up as well
um I know character creation can take a
while I'm not really like that that's
why we need to kind of do it beforehand
but uh anyway here for the whole thing
welcome welcome
um I I probably should put like some
kind of memo or something like hey chill
we will be playing Walter's gate shortly
uh just so just so people are like aware
I guess for those that drop in it's like
it's like a little intro thing you know
it's a nice little
it's a nice little appetizer it became
daytime
it became daytime while we uh talk about
these lyrics
because
um because wow what a bright and happy
story
yeah he let me smell your feet people
are still gonna ask why where's Baldur's
Gate where's Baldur's Gate where's
Baldur's Gate where's Baldur's get you
I'm aware but I gotta say I gotta say
something hold on a sec somewhere uh I
have a no child's
thing that we used before uh for what
was it the arrow game we played treble
days
you play
aller's gate
soon
that's all the why no Childs why do you
think
why do you think
you can turn off nudity you can you can
and believe you me I did
um here's my question though even if we
have nudity turned off I get the feeling
that
um like our are the special
quote-unquote scenes still going to show
up but the only difference is they're
wearing clothes while while performing
The Acts because I actually haven't like
I said I haven't seen any of them
because I don't want to look at them I
don't want yes no yes yes yes
no yes I see mostly yes
I I see mostly yes
I think it fades to Black they have Lee
I think I think some of you are freaking
messing with me here
um
bare percent run seduce the bear well
since I'm not gonna be playing as the
bear I don't know man I don't know
[Music]
you you can do the deed with your no you
can't you can't you can't romance your
own party
you can't I mean that would be sick
don't get me wrong like that would be
hilarious but you can
I remember I looked that up
I looked that up they actually have
leaves okay well I believe that
hey how about how about like a DLC
though is what I'm saying
don't break your this is hard already
well okay here's the thing we can in our
hearts we can role play it out but you
know only to a certain degree it only
goes so far
Anything is Possible
Gore
no no no my my character is not
interested in any of those things
um anyway I think we were gonna go ahead
and yeah do a quick little uh lyric dive
here until 30 ish right about the new
song Left for Dead lullaby there's a new
EP that came out brand new EP if you
guys aren't aware
um if you guys are not this is the
appetizer to before bothers Kate
this is the appetizer to before
poulter's gate
um but this is the new EP release
um if music more music is something
you're all interested in we're just
gonna talk a little bit about what I
wrote here
um and then we'll get into you know
character creation right
um I meant to finish this the last
stream during the lyric dive stream
there just wasn't enough time in fact I
actually I hung out with several other
members today I'm not gonna say who just
because everybody's privacy should be
you know uh respected uh unless they
give me the okay but I hung out with a
ton of a ton of holos today and had a
lot of fun
um went to went to uh have it relaxing
chill day with crony as well that was
cool um we had a lot of unhinged
conversations as per the usual he showed
me this really messed up food
um I'll probably talk about it later I
should get back on topic but uh it's
crazy we were like sitting down in like
the Spa relaxing area and we had like
this partition in between us because
that's just how the place was made up
and we were just talking about unhinged
stuff like back and forth with the
partition in between us and just dying
laughing because like we couldn't see
each other but we were talking about the
most messed up stuff
I I can't even repeat most of it on
stream
it's always an unhinged
crony found some really cursed stuff
actually
um she sent me like some some gifts of
like
a future possible like romanceable
character in Builders K3 and I was like
this can't be real this is the most D
and D stuff I've ever seen in my life
the fact that you could make this happen
anyway Left 4 Dead left for dead lullaby
I'm in the mood to talk about lyrics
today I'm in the mood where to go
oh scroll back up
Watermark that's the harmony
um it was the it wasn't the bear believe
it or not it wasn't the bear
all I'm going to say is
Taco I don't want to talk about it
I don't want to talk about it
um instead I'm going to Taco Bell
um the Left 4 Dead lullaby uh lyrics
[Music]
I'm not gonna talk about it
just dying laughing um
so this song Left for Dead lullabies the
last song on the EP I hear from a lot of
people that it's maybe their favorite
that they really like it a lot which
makes me really happy
um
that it's a lot of people's favorite
um I've been hearing a lot of like
really high praise about it and I'm
quite happy with it because I didn't
think too hard about it when I was
recording it like if it was actually any
good I just hoped it was and I write I
wrote really honestly about it
um so yeah in the beginning let's rod
and treachery somebody asked about the
treachery line in the last stream the
treachery you know meaning betrayed
trust Maui trust has been betrayed a lot
in the past not not just by you know
various people like around me but you
know people in the past and stuff like
that but it's it's not something that I
dwell on too much but I do put into the
lyrics Here make a mention of bury me
and irony
[Music]
I feel like my life is pretty
there's a lot of irony here and there
especially with being deaf and searching
for meaning in life
so bury me in irony
[Music]
o is like not a thing that you say
actually in Japanese unless you're like
shushing a sleeping child
right
um which was kind of I guess interesting
to use in the lyrics because I guess
it's me trying to lull uh the The
Listener into like a a sleep but it's
not a very happy sleep flesh dream at
least not until the end right go to
sleep
go the f word to sleep that's a good
book
um with a song of Love go to sleep
um I feel like there's there's a bit of
like cynicism here you know it's almost
like you can hear the the sarcasm but in
the beginning of the song it's like very
very isolated I like to imagine I'm like
lying at the bottom of a pit singing it
you know up to the sky trying to find
the light or something like that the
void that was the whole image right
final level of Hell Etc When I Wake I'm
born again no one left to mourn my end
shout from the other side sync me down
below
um is meant to kind of display this
feeling of being in an unreachable void
on the other side in a place where like
no one can really quite understand how
you feel and even if you try to explain
it like I'm trying to with these with
these uh lyric types it never quite hits
correctly you know quite the way that I
I want it to the when when I wake I'm
born again
um part kind of refers to coming out of
a deep dark rut I guess uh which happens
often you know whether you're
whether you're having like writer's
block
um I have days
where like I'm really kind of like
I don't know it's not that I think that
I should stop it's that I don't want to
do anything streaming's so fun though I
can't help it
um but I do have those days where I kind
of feel like
hmm
you know just to keep it real with you
guys yeah fed up with various things
creative blocks
um not everything is going swimmingly
right it's not really a beautiful day in
the neighborhood
um
it's like that you it sounds like burnt
out yeah exactly you only write when you
really feel up to it right exactly
definitely which is why it took me so
long to make this record
um no one left to mourn my end talks
about feelings of Abandonment
um so you know coming out of a rut even
when I come back I'm like okay let's
keep doing this let's keep streaming
let's keep singing Etc
um I feel like because I can't like I
guess how do I phrase this because I
can't stay consistent I always I always
worry that
um you know people will kind of like
fall away I think that's a normal thing
there's like nothing really unhealthy
about that only if you get obsessed with
it I guess I think it's a pretty common
worry for a lot of a lot of creators
these days but I'm at work
hold on naughty deadbeat hold on a
minute
how to slap you in the mouth for that
I'm just joking I'm just joking feel
free to watch the Vlog
um and then we get we get into like um
the actual verse so there's like a
H which is kind of like an explosion of
feelings
um after we've kind of drifted to the
bottom of the Void
um how we've come so far away since red
tomorrow red today I know a lot of
people really liked that red tomorrow
red today line um because it it kind of
points back to your Mori which was my
second EP and I feel like that was the
EP that came out
um right when like
right when I feel like I was kind of how
should I say like peaking
in a sense people were really like
surprised by me I think and I think
people were like wow this is kind of
kind of it was like my first my first EP
that I made while I was really in hello
because my debut EP of course I made
outside of it so I had like a lot of you
know feelings and like I wanted it to be
as good as it could be right you're more
you're more is so nostalgic I think in
terms of that record there are some
places where it lacks polish but overall
I'm really quite happy with it that was
another EP that I was really quite happy
with for its time it was it was the best
I could do at that time so it's really
special to me um and so red tomorrow red
today is a lyric from Red if you guys
haven't heard the song Red that entire
record actually your Maury was produced
by tenuoa who made this song so I I
thought it would be perfect to call back
to your Mori specifically on this track
yeah
my favorite release of yours I'm glad
that you like it thank you very much
still love red it's a nice song I still
like red a lot too
um in the ash of what remains lies the
demon no one could same
um this is kind of a sad this is a sad
line
um it kind of makes me feel like maybe
there was a fire that raged that isn't
raging quite as hard
um any longer and just leaves behind Ash
right and what remains uh the demon no
one could same
um a stubborn person who wanted things
done their way
um who Could That Be maybe it's your
Mori
um then we've got hollow smile dull
disguise Idol lies still idolized um I
think some people thought that this is
like Idol Eyes right it's hard to tell
putting these two words together right
because there are various ways that you
could read it
um
but you know
Hollow smile dull disguise uh is kind of
like going through the doldrums of day
to day pretending everything is very
very cool very normal again we're about
to go into that freaking Katy Perry
that Katy Perry meme you just gotta you
just gotta say that you're fine but
you're not
yeah
um
but yeah when you have like a hollow
smile you can kind of tell that there's
like
there's like some some not necessarily
this honesty but like like you're hiding
something putting on a brave face rather
um and it really is it comes off as like
a dull disguise trying to be
um so like front-facing and disguising
yourself as somebody who's just you know
going in the going through the motions
day by day doing the right thing I guess
being the way that they should be not
really showing your true feelings
precisely that that kind of feeling okay
until you make it you know
um idolize still idolized I think I kind
of want people to interpret this in
their own way
um instead of kind of going out there
and just saying it outright
um but there are always
I don't know a lot a lot of times in
Show Business right as like a little
like lead-in I guess in Show Business
occasionally there are
sort of like I guess
small dishonesties and mistruths right
just becomes so normal it's like it's
just something that you do
or rather the entertainment industry
does instinctively like idly without
even thinking about it you know and it's
like
people are like cool
you know like all right this is accepted
or rather even liked
um however how you feel about that is is
up to you maybe that's fine for you
you're okay with it because it's an
Escape maybe you prefer to see things
completely crystal clear as they are
um it's really kind of up to you it's
just a statement of fact not necessarily
an opinion amongst the dead there's life
the sudden change Cuts Like a Knife
um
so amongst all of these sort of like um
Fallen Dreams and things that I wanted
to do that kind of didn't materialize
there is still like a flicker of Hope
and kind of like hanging on to it right
but the sudden change the way that
things are now so drastically being so
drastically different than they were in
the beginning
um can sometimes feel painful
you know the reality is Harsh indeed
um time seldom heals your hell is all
it's real a lot of times when you mess
up or do something
um that like you're like oh man I could
have done this better I could have
written this better this could have been
better
Etc
um and like you feel a deep cut from it
in various ways in your life
um sometimes you're just told give it
time you know people tell you oh just
take some time you know in time it'll
heal but some things can't be healed by
time
crony's doing her best out here but
there's only so much she can do
you know
cut my life into pieces
this is my last resort
suffocation
no breathing
um anyway continuing onwards we gotta
keep moving
um
let's see oh um yeah your hell is all
it's real they lead you on they lead you
on with pretty words and lies
um so this can refer to like people that
maybe hire you
um people in your friend group etc those
that you know compliment you in excess
uh give you like pretty words and lies
um I guess to like show some kind of
comfort because they're just trying to
like be helpful be kind
um some sort of comfort when you burn no
it's uh when you cry you may have heard
that I think they may have heard that
wrong I got these lyrics from uh lyrical
nonsense because it's just very easy to
copy paste them shout outs to lyrical
nonsense for all of the translations and
keeping of the lyrics for holo songs and
JP songs in general really appreciate it
um
so yeah a lot of times I feel like um
sometimes when I ask for advice from
Friends Etc they're very kind to me
they're super nice
um but
not all of it is rooted in honesty
because I think you know some people
just want to be kind I don't think it's
a bad thing but it happens pretty often
what is the bgm chat it's uh the
instrumental for my song Left for Dead
lullaby brand new song on my EP do you
go six Left 4 Dead lullaby title drop of
the song led to rod and treachery bury
me an irony
already talked about this when I wake up
born again no one left more man shot
from the other side sync me down below I
wanted to gradually ramp up the way that
I sung the hook right so the first hook
is like very somber
um and like but it has an extra Darkness
to it you know it's somber but it's it's
dark and still has some strength in it
this particular instance of the hook I
decided to sing a little bit like
lighter more Airy a little more like
Whimsical
um and like I guess an idealistic sound
I wanted it to ring clear through like a
bell right so that it would drastically
contrast uh with the second or rather
the third I guess rendition of the hook
and then uh the fourth which changes the
lyrics which gets really intense and
gets into screaming uh Etc do you plan
to ever race the instrumentals for the
umj songs I'd like to I need to speak
more to the team about it I just
recently got a lot of them as background
music for my streams we'll see though I
think that would be really nice to hear
um others you know tackle the the songs
as well I think that would be super neat
your control of intensity made this song
thanks a lot I'm glad that you think so
because in the studio I really thought
about it and I tried to kind of like go
back and forth um like I could do this
more intense and I tried to focus on the
flow of the the hooks and how they like
change in the intensity
um because it also changes I feel like
it changes the meaning
um and uh existence of the hook in each
instance so I really I like the second
verse lyrics the best right here week of
heart but sound of Mind friends I found
but left behind
um weak of heart but sound of mind is
referring to myself feeling like um you
know I've been through quite a bit so my
heart is it's been weakened but I'm
sound of mind I keep moving forward uh
trying to do what I do friends I found
but left behind is pretty
self-explanatory because there's a lot
of those a lot of people that I was
close with before um entering my my line
of work outside of being a Reaper right
um this part gets a bit nostalgic they
speak of me like a ghost vibrant vibrant
memories colorblind there should be a
comma here a speaking me like a ghost
vibrant memories color blind right there
a total at that part
um sometimes I do hear occasionally like
um you know friends that I had in like
the art community
um that like May occasionally like uh oh
this is not that was not that part okay
it's fine
um talking about me like oh yeah you
know you hear about what happened to
Mori
um like all this happened to her and
stuff like that and like it makes me
feel like a ghost you know I thought I
heard the voice of sheriff Tonica again
a vibrant Memories colorblinds the
memories themselves are like vibrant but
I feel like I've become colorblind so I
can't really perceive
um how vibrant they were and remember
them perfectly tragic words last
goodbyes on my soul like a faded
Watermark I feel like the sin of itself
is
it's pretty self-explanatory
um for how I feel about
um my relationship with my friends of of
those days
um Etc
and uh it never really goes away but
occasionally
I feel like um you know it the memories
like like the watermark it fades away
but it's always there you know no matter
how much it fades it's it's still there
goodbyes I shared with people
um even the fights that I had Petty
fights amongst my friends
edifies between my friends and I anyway
a wistful wanting the narrative unwinds
basically is kind of referring to a
nostalgic longing for the past and then
in that longing
[Music]
um the story the story kind of unfolds
before me right a quick one guy start
the character creation otherwise the
others can't prepare oh I have to do it
first
okay hold on a sec
I didn't know I had to be the first one
to do it
all right guys quick pause on this
quick pause on this
one moment
can I invite I actually need to invite
really quick
uh invite
let me just invite
let me invite do I not have
Kiara is a friend
on Steam is who what hold on a second
it can't be
I think you do see when I try to invite
you it does not show up sadly
click
I can't scroll
online friends search friends oh and
people also left
Ara
it's not online anymore maybe we're not
but how have how did this happen how
uh restarting the PC gotcha
okay
well let me add really quick
uh I hope you guys are cool with the
deadly silence
let me add
this is organizing DND
no no no no Ian curse yet I'm able to
run the game fine first of all I noticed
that when I opened so I opened the game
and I started running it and it was
already on Ultra
and I'm like thinking to myself Baldur's
Gate is it really okay is it really is
it really fine with you if I run if I
run the whole live thing uh OBS the
YouTube Chrome
Ballers K3 all this stuff
and the computer's like I got you what
do you mean this is no problem
all right
I sent the invite successfully
don't trust it
Ultra dear
I don't know man the PC is nice
it's a nice one
can it run crisis
all right I don't know about all that
I don't know I have to look into that
maybe we'll try all right I invited
now let me invite vibou and then I'm
gonna launch it
I'm gonna launch it
um
please
invite friends
get in here everyone
oh the kitty cat
I'm sending invites left and right
what class are you gonna be
Barbarian Berserker
um let's see so
I'll wait for them to join before I
launch it because otherwise
people thrower there is you Wawa
here let's let's get a little bgm in the
background anyway because the silence
makes me feel strange it scares me
all right uh it looks like uh just
waiting on waiting on I think that she's
yeah restarting something
um
I entered the lobby still figuring
something out okay in the meantime I
guess I'll just explain really quick
this here Japanese part yeah I uh I
don't know how many people got the
translation but actually
um
right yeah ping me when she's back
please yeah that would be cool thank you
thank you uh so there's actually like a
translation
uh that you can view on lyrical nonsense
which is awesome but yeah it's basically
correct uh Hey Mama I don't know where I
went wrong
where did I go wrong I don't know where
I went wrong
um
and then I'm gonna fall and Catch Fire I
love this part mama
[Music]
that part's so fun to say
some clever word play well Tenny woe is
basically a master of word play when it
comes to JP lyrics honestly
um
yeah I'm gonna fall and Catch Fire is
what that means just like that uh
the other world is already full
um
100 scenes of hell is actually a famous
painting I believe it looks like an
upside down birthday cake that was a
lyric too but I changed it
I changed it from like an upside down
birthday cake a downward spiral to where
I belong because I just feel like um the
image of an upside down birthday cake
perhaps falling on mori's head uh might
ruin the imagery or rather the mood of
the song to where it was where it was
going I guess yeah
um so it changed it but
hmm
yeah
but you're not Mama you're dead is there
a song of yours you'd like to hear
narissa cover I would love a new reason
to go back to unalive oh man I just like
people to cover what they like to be
honest
you know I want I want people to You
Know cover what they what they believe
they're strongest with probably a
singing heavy song I bet that nurse
could hit the high notes of unalive and
a robber us as well I could definitely
see that happy birthday to the crowd
it's kind of funny but a little out of
place yeah I thought I thought it was
cute though
um and then resentment Grudge is
jealousy
translates to resentment grudges
jealousy uh Envy right
um
uh becoming right
um and then this is really cool no
reincarnation uh Reincarnation of course
you guys know The Reincarnation uh is
right uh being reborn right
um but the Carnation here is meant to be
like an image of like flowers like
carnations
I think I actually gave that imagery to
Tenny Wilson like avoid where I'm kind
of floating and then like pedals slowly
start to like fall down and like you
know flowers and stuff like that it's a
reincarnation Carnation what incarnation
that's how it is in ramaji yes correct
um so yeah time never heals when hell is
all it's real kind of already went over
that no wow
in on us and yet you start to hear the
desperation creeping to the vocals
um the walls are falling in on us and
yet words like regret won't wet my lips
it's it's kind of similar to a feeling
of like um
I don't know um how do I say
when the walls are falling in closing in
on you uh and you feel like kind of
choking and whatnot um even though
perhaps you know how did we get here
surely I did something wrong
okay Mama
Where'd I go wrong
um I still you know won't talk about
regrets no regrets it's better to not
have them
um there are moments that change if I
could
searching for atonement does not ensure
good
[Music]
um so like of course there are moments
that I would go back and change as I
think anyone kind of feels similarly
right
um but you know searching for all that
at home it does not guarantee that
things will just fix fix themselves
right you turn around and say oh man you
know I messed up let me try and fix it
let me try and become good does not
guarantee anything
you know
the next step is how do you live with it
I think expecting expecting things to to
go your way is uh
after that is nothing not the greatest
idea right it's normal yeah I would say
so left for dead lullaby we go back to
repeating led to rotten treachery bury
me and irony
When I Wake I'm born again no one left
to mourn my end shot from the other side
sync me down below
um yay all in character creation start
to please
launch
uh okay uh Wawa got it ready up
let's go click ready
and then I'll click lunch
um yay lunch
all right now before we finish up the
lyric dive
um watch okay now we're skipping the
cutscene
oh
I'm sorry who was that was that a shout
from the other side sync me down below
I don't know guys are we gonna make a
character
[Music]
are we gonna make a character
um I'll go ahead and let them work on it
I think that they're like working on
their characters right now
um and I'll quickly finish this up
uh so in the second hook of that song
right
um
I kind of like ramp it up ramp up the
vocals and whatnot but there's only one
one kind of little bit left here in the
song drifting deep I realized no one
expects me to Rise
um
oh but in your selfish eyes catch and
let me go uh I think actually that is I
think that was that was misheard
um it's born and you're selfish eyes
like the image of an idol uh born within
the eyes of someone you know to be
perfect Etc
um catch me you know um be you know love
love me in some way and then let me go
and move on right
um
yeah drifting deep I realize no one
expects me to Rise
um it's kind of like feeling like there
aren't a lot of high expectations
um for me to ever kind of like make
something of myself
who's hosting me I hope
[Music]
Sandlers for a Shrek
um and then when I wake recall with
Dread
see who you had left for dead about from
the other side think me down below
um
I think this is another really
this is an intense one this is an
intense bit of the song because I really
start to like
the vocals really kind of go nuts here
um
but you know when when it is when it is
that I ever do kind of resurface and
make something good of myself and do a
good job
um I guess it's it's a little bit of a
cynical remark like I want I want those
who gave up on me to look at me and be
like ah
you know
but it's more of like a
it's not that I really
feel a certain way
maybe I do
maybe I did
never mind
ah forget it it's not about it's not
about owning anyone or anything like
that it's nothing like that I guess
let me put it in a way that maybe others
can kind of
understand a bit
maybe sometimes you feel like um if you
worked really hard on something
um and you're like really proud of
yourself and you like
how far you've kind of emerged like
you've made yourself better you feel
like you've improved and whatnot
you kind of want people that like
didn't expect you to make something of
yourself to see it right
not just proving something to them
you're proven to your something to
yourself as well
you want people to tell you did well
validation
I guess there is that too
right
huh
yeah
you had left for death
um shout from the other side sync me
down below now despite all of that there
still is the line finally reaping what
I've sown
which
in a sense is taking responsibility
after all of this like you know you're
gonna see me when I better myself and
you're gonna be like oh man
laughs
maybe I should have stuck around Etc but
at the end of the day
finally reefing what I've sewn I had
some missteps you know
sometimes
sometimes you gotta deal with the hand
that life throws at you because you made
some missteps
down the river it's not the song we're
talking about the final line of the song
of course is um bring me back uh to live
again you know it's not capturing that I
don't know why notepad isn't capturing
that but it's bringing me back to live
again
um and that that meaning is twofold
right you know resuscitate me bring me
back to live again take me towards the
light again where I can produce things
that I like make people that I care
about happy make the deadbeats happy Etc
but it's also referring to one of the
first songs I ever released Live Again
live again it's pronounce it again
because back then days were really sweet
you know and I want to find a way back
to that satisfaction that I felt in the
beginning right anyway uh that's about
it that's uh left for dead lullaby a
song I'm very proud of honestly
um
now it's time to make a little character
I hope you guys liked it though it's a
song about moving on it's a song about
reaping what you sow accepting your
missteps and um and hoping to come back
someday stronger and be better that is
uh that is that song at its core there's
a lot of emotion in it there's a range
of emotions Nostalgia sadness anger
Etc but I'm glad that so many people
like this song Thank you so much for
enjoying it I really appreciate it
um I hope you guys will listen to it
lots stream it lots because I'm really
proud of it
um now I think it's time to game
I think it just might be time to game
behold
here we are now I'm by the river I kind
of turned down the a little bit um
yeah uh so we're not gonna play origin
characters we're playing a custom
character
I want a large Madame let's randomize
some characters oh cool I think I might
find something fun and random
let's freaking go I'm sorry
I'm sorry
oh okay
well we're gonna we are gonna have to
change
um
I kind of like human well hold on
it'd be more fun though
uh We're Not Gonna Be barred
um we are not barred
what here we go
but is it gonna change my my beautiful
creation
please don't change my beautiful
I kind of like this chill Dragon though
but you are a Bard I I know but
if I don't be a human
I'll be a human
you acquired the following
[Music]
um and then how else am I going to do
this hold on
um oh yeah it's that it's that one okay
not a Bard not a Bard hold on um you
wouldn't mind I'm going to scroll
through uh
Barbarian
yeah let's go
you can edit the body I can yes I can
but why would I oh can I can I get
larger
dang it but that's not
foreign
[Music]
all right hold on
um
three is the buff Madam I like the buff
Madam but this is so good
I think we need to let some things go
[Music]
I need to let it go let it go Mori Let
It Go
yeah yeah
[Music]
pink dragon's kind of cool
let's just be huge madame
that's what I want to be
um instead of
now I can pick maybe I want to be elf
maybe I want to be
I want to be huge
this chill dragon's kind of cool though
work after work
yeah maybe I'll be half work that's cool
um
barbarian barbarian half orc yeah
I think tiffling is really cool but I
I'm already playing that actually and I
think we have um I'm playing that on my
my lonesome and I think we also have um
we also have somebody who's already
playing see fling Soldier
urchin
uh nah we want to focus on
we want to focus on stuff that'll make
me strong Outlander you grew up in the
Wilds yeah group in the Wilds
nice yeah strong right ability points um
I don't want
charisma's so fun though
I think we have other charismatic
members
I'm very stupid
but I'm really struck I can't I can't
add more points to strength okay that's
fair look fair enough fair enough okay
wait can I
you know why did I just take off to
oh no I didn't never mind hold on
I can't I
can't it will not let me make myself
stronger oh
let's do bonus to strength
plus one bonus to I wonder what would be
good
the Yeet build try to figure out what
the eat build is
the Constitution
I don't know 17 is Max all right let's
go yeah Constitution might be good I
just want to hold on I only have 26
points to sign
might as well put it
I'm just not very charismatic
um but I like being
can I be really dumb but Super Wise
I see there are there are uh limits here
Olympus all right fine fine fine fine
fine fine fine
Charisma just so I don't completely fail
every Charisma role
um
then
fine fine fine fine fine fine fine fine
fine fine fine fine fine
[Music]
High wisdom equals Street smarts oh well
I have those but it won't let me go
uh skill proficiency
[Music]
build proficiency uh definitely one
no hold on ah how do I want skill
um if I want to throw someone
I'm guessing Athletics would be good
well I can't I can't choose it
I can't choose any of these actions
actually I have to choose looks like I
have to choose
[Music]
I guess perception Etc
not letting me choose Athletics though I
think my Athletics is already pretty
good
yeah but there are some but it's just
it's not letting me
you already have high Athletics that is
true maybe my perception would be good
all right uh nature is pretty good I
like trees
animals oh what if I could talk to
animals super good
yeah
okay you can go into extreme detail and
appearance yeah oh okay
body type
yeah let's freaking go well
kind of want this one though
um Madame where to next oh just a very
deep voice
the friendly
Health be wary it's open is that like an
old man boy those wretched things
there's magic where to next let's hope
the locals are friendly hell I want the
deepest voice
more of those wretched things yeah let's
go it's pretty good health
[Music]
very like very
scary looking face
and we're not here to mess around
um let's go find a crazy skin color
[Music]
like a green
green
um
[Music]
see eye color is
pink
and tattoo style is
[Music]
um
yeah yeah
it's not Shrek
this is not Shrek
so you know not Shrek to color black
makeup style we don't need makeup we're
a born raised Warrior
big big scars because we fight on the
battlefield
that's kind of cool I've seen some stuff
hairstyle
um
where is the where are the Buns the twin
buns
where are they let's find them
take me to the yeah
cool that little little like ogre Billy
eilish look here
foreign
yeah
yeah okay
open The Score though okay
Oh yay no problem
understood we're gonna go back to
you know don't proceed
appearance appearance appearance
yeah we're looking good
maturity
old
very old
yup I read it
yup
I read it
210.
[Music]
no man
I will quantity now we're pretty much
almost like good to go here in terms of
hair
[Music]
maybe red I just want some ridiculous
colors
highlights
all highlight colors let me see them
blue is kind of cool maybe like a teal
I want something bright
space buns yeah
pretty neat
[Music]
character looks terrible
I love it beard
[Music]
pretty good
I want it to be too long
ice cream area it kind of gives that
Vibe huh
I like this little
[Music]
this little ponytail this facial hair uh
ponytail
good your sings uh
yeah that's good
I think that's that's about it
and to the character name the
character's name
is moriope
okay
[Music]
I need water holy water on my eyes why
my character's perfect Fiona
stop
it's well let me see let me
hey boy
me out Fiona stop
you should work
Jolie
Jolene
it's all over now
or Shreks
no Shreks it's moriope we need a
guardian I'm just gonna randomize
I want someone small
yeah that's too that's too similar to
biboo
just a little one yeah that's cool
it's also too similar to
oh now we're cooking
yeah this one's pretty cool
yeah I'll take it
[Music]
nice
hey pretty cool
it's nice
I'm pretty good
the guardian is beautiful too yeah I
think so as well
looking good
too perfect Too Perfect for this world
I love it oh I love it
[Music]
is that a Yeti
I'm gonna go ahead
and hit the loading screen
and when I return we start the game
with everyone okay guys
so I'll be back shortly
be back shortly and I'm gonna load
everybody's
everybody's pictures in as well okay
guys I'll see you shortly enjoy the
Beautiful music and until then okay
bye I'll see you soon see you very
shortly
um I will be muting the EP teaser
moment um because I want you guys to
hear the down down down by the river
sounds so good if he's using oh it's
already turned down excellent
it's already turned down for what okay
okay JK if I want to add them I have to
I have to click out of the screen and
the music isn't going to play so listen
to the teaser sorry sorry
[Music]
no one expects me to rise
playing games
[Music]
nobody's life
no one expects me to rise
[Music]
playing games
foreign
we are
starting shortly
hello again
I am playing with a controller but I
think everybody's doing like character
introductions I guess
introducing their characters and whatnot
um on their own
did you see did you see everybody's you
guys seeing people's
welcome back welcome back welcome back
welcome back new day new stream uh I
think I mentioned this before but we
really are wanting to finish uh The
Campaign which I know is going to be
really difficult I hear that like the
first chapters like Adventure Mode
which is the easier mode I guess
oh oh not yet okay
well we'll start around 10 I think
um
it's gonna be a long ride we really want
to though but we're gonna have to be
strict
we're gonna have to be strict
no a beautiful character oh this is my
guardian
yeah you guys you guys haven't seen my
uh
well if I go back I can show you right
this is moriope
my my beautiful beloved Queen
[Music]
um moriope loves nature
um and doesn't like people
and likes to throw likes to throw small
beings
um
iope uh beautiful queen not very smart
but super strong
super strong
um
I would like her to tank
but I don't know not like I'm bare over
here
um
in terms of Rome in terms of romance uh
moriope has no no time for that
unless unless a very specific a very
specific type of being
shows up in the game which is
um yeah moriope is only attracted to uh
to to the demons
with with really bright red skin and
fire inside of them
and will not romance anything else
nothing else no
yeah
and that's it
it's It's All or Nothing
so Little Nicky I swear to God
I should beat the snot out of you
hey Graphics looking pretty good though
I mean I'm only I'm only stuttering very
very minimally and this is an ultra
Graphics at Ultra I want to keep them
this way hmm
I can tape I can take a couple of
dropped frames on myself you know
only only so much that we can do
look up you can see the details the
pores the wrinkles
Vivid details
the the Tomboy Supremacy oh it looks
like we're about to get started
moriope smash no one smashes moriope
right I might need to do a little volume
adjust here
whoa Guardian whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
hope hope is that okay caliope nuts
moriope actually it's my character but
morio hello hi hello oh man it's
Baldur's time this is the Gang
it's from the store let's go let's go
we waited down Cali we were talking
sorry big smash voice
yeah
I have to ask you first
because when we were creating characters
yesterday people said it might be good
you know to like balance out everything
so that we are have ever like you know
uh we cover everything uh you know what
I mean yeah yeah and then they told me
people they told me uh just now that I
shouldn't go with magebreaker because
true strike sucks
they kept saying that to me too but then
other people said that true strike is
fixed now and then they fixed it I fixed
it
yeah what was wrong about true strike uh
I don't know I don't know too much about
I think I think it's hard too because
it's just like everyone always has their
own play style on things that they like
and dislike
um
[Music]
true strike sucks
okay then let me just ask you people one
thing did we say somebody is gonna have
investigation as their thing or uh let's
see if you guys look at your abilities
and look at your proficiencies what do
you have because we should cover our
bases okay yes
let's do that all right uh I'll go first
I'll go first okay so I'm playing a
barbarian
um as like my class I'm a huge huge half
orc
um Outlander and my abilities I have
really high strength 17 strengths uh
dexterity is pretty good 13 Constitution
is 14. uh stamina and physical endurance
of course because I'm big and girthy uh
intelligence nine because I'm just not
very smart uh wisdom wisdom is pretty
good
um smarter than me
it wouldn't let me put it into other
things so this is how it has for me
Charisma is uh is 10
um like it's it's fun wait how is how
Shrek smarter than my heart
valve okay what the don't call her
that her name is not sure okay get it
straight first of all
um but yeah I guess I can kind of tank
because I have high Constitution as well
um and then I have plus two bonus to
strength one plus one bonus to
Constitution uh my skills in particular
I've got plus five to Athletics which is
really good
um you know most standards oh that's
good I have a negative one on Athletics
Good Luck running away
um and then animal handling plus three
oh that's three
um and then Insight plus one medicine
plus one perception plus a survival plus
three good Survivor I'm pretty
intimidating so I've got plus two there
um yeah that's what I'm good at
where do you have all these weird stands
I'm so happy um if you go to abilities
and skill proficiencies and you can hit
change and you can see what you have
oh yeah
I can handle a lot of weapons so so Cali
what's your strongest points then in the
build in skills skills uh let's see so
the highest my highest role is Athletics
um well I don't know my Athletics is
plus five
um okay let's see and then survival plus
three animal handling plus three
okay our strong Windows I'm
sorry excuse me
I got plus four in those but
hey what's your strength
uh
uh uh 12. okay well you can't beat me in
strength so in an arm wrestling match
you're gonna suffer anyway continue
onward your turn your turn
well I don't really know if I should
change any of this um you you don't have
to so just read it off okay we're right
now
[Music]
um
uh stealth is plus five
oh that's good yeah
um another strong one is animal handling
inside both a plus four perceptionist
plus four survival is plus four
um I don't know what do you want to know
people should I tell you my weak points
too then we can cover those or so
um yeah sure
um I'm weak in history
and religion oh yeah we wanted someone
to cover religion and history huh oh I
have plus one in history I have negative
one oh no I have negative one in history
I have plus one in religion okay okay
okay well we don't have to cover
everything I guess but
um okay and then yeah basically my
question was if it's if it makes sense
to go in uh you know bounty hunter that
gains me Proficiency in investigation do
we have anybody else who has Proficiency
in the investigation because of yes then
I won't do it I have a negative one in
investigation negative one in
investigation yeah oh okay so go ahead
go for it go okay it will only bring me
to plus one but okay
then then I'll just stay with what I
have now uh yeah
I think um we'll be fine what does
narista focus on uh well I'll read my
downsides first with all the other
skills I don't have so my Athletics is
minus one aerobatics plus two sleight of
hand plus four stealth plus two Arcana
plus one history plus one investigation
plus one nature and religion plus one
animal handling zero inside zero
medicine zero perception survival zero
deception plus five and then imitation
and performance and persuasion all plus
five but then strength is eight wow
dexterity is plus 15. Constitution is
plus thirteen intelligence is plus 12 so
I'm smarter than all of you all right
I can tank that wait does does anybody
have deception on a decent amount
because me and the rest are on zero
let's see exceptions
well maybe you could instead choose to
rule persuasion or intimidation instead
of deception I don't know yeah can we
choose and it depends
it'll give you multiple like dialogue
choices and you can choose what you want
to roll on yeah okay okay five in my
deception two oh okay yeah you're the
charismatic one oh wait you have plus
five interception oh then there was
something else that I heard was Zero
yeah okay
do we have persuade persuasion covered
by someone yeah
good me and people want to do the
persuading yeah we'll do the talking I
think both of us uh scale on Charisma so
we will be the Wizards you guys do that
I think we do The Killing yeah the only
stealthy one well I'll kill two but yeah
yeah yeah it's good to do both oh yeah
you're also healer right Bijou cleric no
oh you're not clerical anymore I am
swapping to sorcerer I'm only going to
cleric for about two levels and then I'm
swapping to sorcerer uh for extreme
magical violence
um I do have heels and narissa should
have heels as well as Bart so we should
be okay okay just have some potions with
you well then I really didn't need to be
a Healer okay good good
um yeah uh did everybody show everything
off on stream then I think so yes
yeah and they're Guardians oh wait I
forgot to tell the mine
the what my my thing right yeah you
haven't introduced your character yet oh
yeah ah yeah Google Google yeah okay hi
they forgot about me it's okay no no
never we need you you're important
what is it yeah I'm
not cleric
um strength is nine
bad strength uh Dex is 13 Constitution
13 intelligence eight I'm not very smart
or strong but I have Charisma and that's
all that matters
um and also wisdom is 15. here's my 17
and then my proficiency
I got persuasion plus five performance
plus three intimidation I'm very
intimidating plus three deception plus
three survival plus two perception plus
two minus and plus four inside plus four
and we're handling plus two religion
plus one and then nature investigation
history Arcana all negative one but I
got still flight of hand acrobatics and
yeah
there you go
I can't
uh
oh they're telling me to add one
Constitution but I can't
yeah yeah you have to take away from
something yeah yeah I did but the plus
is grayed out even when I have one
ability Point extra I'll do I wait like
this okay
wait what but it still has no no where
was that where did uh where did I go
thank you for the reminder it's okay no
need to panic we have to worry each
other we got your back
but
but they really want me to have more
Constitution
and I can't I've gotten the constitution
for the group
um
oh wait no the picture I think was of
something else
[Music]
now I don't know what to do okay hold on
well I think we just have the
recommended because we didn't really set
them right
um
okay oh it was okay okay okay
you keep recommended yeah
okay okay we can start then maybe
awesome maybe right so we're all gonna
like as our characters
but yeah I think we're all just us
except for you oh yeah
[Music]
did we make a sexy a sexy love interest
and I already showed it off but mine is
my mom oh mine is just me grown up
mine's just a random
ly
yeah mine is literally just the old
fellow bearded lady
hello wonderful lady let's go all right
are we ready to get started
fourth
okay here we go all right what's gonna
happen look oh
yeah
Pirates of the Caribbean yeah the Kraken
oh uh Davey Jones
wow he's got alien feet
Paco is Taco Time
is he single ass later in the game
absolutely what's happenings
world we're on a big ship
yeah
cool yes oh I think you may have missed
the first cutscene yeah we are all next
year we are oh
we don't like it there though we were
there against our will yeah that looks
very evil that doesn't seem right we did
not choose this life hold on a sec
that rendering is great on that that man
no right really high quality Graphics oh
wow
that's grip strength man
I like where the world's all over again
oh they're getting captured I thought
they were getting disintegrated
hello
Dad suffering let's go
well technically they're not dying
they're getting teleported
oh
that's good
yeah did you hear did you hear it
The Wilhelm scream
classic why do they have dragons
they're the targaryens obviously oh my
God they're not blonde though it's fine
let's go I guess oh the other the other
ones weren't blonde right I don't know
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
all right well Cable Management let's
blow this Popsicle stand boys
on the Frosty
chat is the audio and the visual is fine
is it lagging or anything
it's pretty loud
yeah because it was crazy loud oh good
nice I think it'll turn down when we
exit the cutscene
I'll have to pull up are the dragon
people here to save us specifically or
to save all everybody
is that cat who wants that no that's not
my character okay
she's always angry all the time yeah
she's kind of cool though kind of based
your character still seemed much more
stands out here than that one even Kelly
oh yeah you think from when I checked
yeah she's a star muriope is a star she
knows it
wow
don't save people Dragon people hate
tentacle people oh we're waking up
it was slimy
we will not be joining forces I'm sorry
you're going straight to the camp but it
was nice to see you anyway beautiful
rendered and also whoa excuse me
I like that
you like what that was not enough but
oh and it's the number three yeah like
Ballers gate three yeah
[Music]
did everybody miss the part where they
put a word yeah yes when that happens
just just know there's a worm in your
head because that's very important okay
there's a worm we got wormed yeah you
got worms in your head
dialogue off
yeah I look great
that was awesome
looking real good let me oh we're all
together so let's freaking go hello
where are you
hey I'm playing with like a much
if you guys don't mind I'm very going
I'm going to very quickly turn my
settings to best or extremely good
instead of ultra just a moment please
um yeah I want to see Cali face hold on
let's take a look at how you can zoom in
let me really quickly change the video
to not be ultra
how how do we do that
if you go to settings you got to press
the start button
for me right guys
okay wow wow do we have the same hair
who all right yeah
oh
nice sisters yeah
I'm sorry where are the genitals you'll
eat me later no none of them yeah I get
to throw you later on where are the
generals the genitals what do you mean
the genitals because I them off from the
beginning of the game but apparently
it's not really turned off so I need to
turn them off we're at Agenda oh go to
settings it's
be careful
okay okay uh maybe I rejected instead of
unchecking it yeah we're all scared what
about cinematic genitals
I would probably
head off too I would probably
I don't know yeah okay is it an
accessibility
yeah in gameplay and then scroll down a
little bit actually you should even see
something about scrolling down
cinematically off share private moments
off yeah none of you guys are getting my
private moments yeah
none of mine are checked so I think
we're good you're going for
that I wanted to go for the demon lady
too bad she's so cool
we can fight for her you can have the
bear the bear yeah
you were so excited about the bear what
are you talking about okay look the bear
is cool all right don't get me wrong but
oh
look
should we turn off karmic dice oh my God
karmic dice avoids failure streaks while
keeping the results mostly random no
that feels like a good thing to have on
Dynamic right
say it again
I would just have it off turn it off
they say off off off okay
wow are we ready wait wait he's trying
to turn down some things
medium is good actually
it's better than whenever I was playing
on the other computer I don't know how
to do anything by the way what about
narissa
oh same I don't know what let's go
what's going on okay bee boo and Cali
you will have to like uh tell us
everything sorry yeah I know a little
bit that's about it though I know a
little bit too
just a little mm-hmm
uh okay wow it's so pretty though the
game is pretty yeah yeah it's very very
detailed we're moving I love how you
move like you do in League of Legends I
thought that it was gonna be like I
could play with a controller oh yes
you're the league player where's the
karmic dice by the way
uh I don't know hey chat where's karmic
dice
or McDonald's here also on the first one
gameplay
we're turning it off right they say turn
it off
okay
I should look for that too no Lisa is a
league player yeah I like League are you
ever gonna play those kind of games on
stream uh it's kind of hard because if
you have more people to play with but
some people just don't like want to try
it at all but I feel like you would be
filling a niche because no other Ian I
think is playing those that genre on
stream I'm not good though
last one
I might try it I want to do Dota 2 too
because I haven't but I I'm more
familiar with League than I am DOTA
because it's been a really long time
why whoa whoa whoa I think I need to
change this
resolution to not be white and then we
can start and we can start okay Prospect
ratio gotta change the aspect ratio
this is called sphincter I don't like
that
what else
we're in a thing we're we're in it
what's wrong with it
though you you hurt me look you can heal
you can heal there's a healing right
here all right we've already got some
party conflicts
in our faces people
all right
oh man
off
avoid failure streaks okay anyway back
to the game
hey team I mean okay let's go let's go
we just go through it or do we yeah we
go go through this thing yeah
I know it's gross what you have oh
okay come up here come up here
well I need to get used to those
controls okay get on the platform oh
yeah you guys okay
someone go talk to that person right
there
we'll draw Charisma people
oh okay I hit it done and then I'll loot
them afterward who is he
oh no he looks dead no he's still alive
barely
it's fine
yum yums
yummy
expectation
[Music]
those are the yummies they return yeah
turn the music up
uh
is it important what I say whatever you
want what would your character say yeah
um
uh yeah maybe so high-res
the high-res brain I realize you're
talking
no don't destroy the brain it's good
it's good let's ask more
peace so many memories
okay
oh okay I see you guys I'll fix it in a
moment
let's
Rock them soccer no before we destroy it
we have to you know cover all options
free free the brain it sounds pretty
nice it sounds nice
you sound very nice
it's nice to us it's a nice little brain
well my strongest one would be the
dexterity one I say I say investigation
[Music]
definitely prize the brain from the
skull bro
I will I will do that let's take a look
at it skill checks some dialogue options
require skill check a dice roll at most
meet or exceed a target number your
character skills add a bonuses right
okay okay
oh good luck
yeah
oh it has to be minimum 10 right
if it matches it it's fine too
I don't want to touch this strange
creature
prove a threat
what am I looking at
uh yeah let's move the lights the brain
yeah
what happens if I fail
something bad
oh no do I does the brain take over me
oh you just wow you just
killed him dude
sorry it was so wobbly
look at his little legs
we got a runner
we have a pet now it's cute
it ran it ran away oh it's running away
all right I destroyed
uh I don't destroy today hey we lose
them I I knew we should have killed that
thing
yeah
I'm sorry I don't know it will follow
and haunt us forever we'll be back for
sure
oh we left we
La I
uh
where is
okay I'm here wait um do you have do you
have it do you have improvised melee
weapon use it
I mean
on you improvised
yeah improvised weapon yeah
improvised melee whip I found it okay it
says two habits to pick up
oh
yes I can't hold on a sec
hold on improvised melee weapon
yeah
over there
[Music]
and over oh wow
let me help you I'm sorry about that
yeah it sucks well anyway you'll get in
Rage thrill later and that's the big eat
cool I'm back for that that's the one
yeah we're gonna but we're gonna use
that
that's pretty sick
I thought I'd provide some some
background Ambience for you guys it's
fine why is thank you I like yours
laying tiny horned winged one wait you
don't have wings tiny horned
displacement okay guys
okay okay I changed my whole uh layout
in OBS I'm ready now
my name is good luck fighting whatever's
over there ah just kidding
oh man it's gonna be a long journey
let's go okay let's go
whoa
ready to Bonk them in the head with my
the hammer oh
oh
my gosh
yeah
orange I like it oh no oh no no you
cannot join our party yes you cannot
join her is she your sister excuse me I
am much more beautiful wow she's so
insulting
uh we share a brain we share a brain
cell
s face seem to the
lucky
you cannot join my party
sorry what is this they all want to join
us yeah so bad we're just we're just
that cool they want to join the squad
party's full yeah squad's full sorry
together real sorry about you guys
survive
okay well you gotta go to the camp
um
are you making these decisions now who
are you what do you suggest who are you
um
who are you who is you uh
what made you think I was a thrall
parasites
unless we are cleansed
bodies and Minds basically if we let the
things stay in our head we turn into one
of those tentacle people mindful oh yeah
so we don't want to do it I mean that
could have its upsides too yeah
okay Escape
getting the the snacks the munchies
the dress is the matter of a cure for
this infection once we reach the
material plane
okay okay
bye all right go to the camp and wait
teach us combat
let's do this
oh so angry
oh look at that Bloody smile General
wait I kind of get it all right guys
around you during combat so you have
time to plant eh
is there
uh wait who is there an order
[Laughter]
why am I playing this I can jump
right well anyway never a dull moment
we're pretty strong right off the bat
get over it I can't move pieces of dirt
nice yeah
and ax I don't need that I could sell it
though collect everything sell for big
money
right well take it I took it all right
next oh we attacked we have too late for
all right everyone have to end their
individual terms
ah okay Luke Goblin engage
nice
okay our tank should shall be in front
of us
I guess I'm also playing as
to you
can't believe they're giving me this
responsibility I got gold yeah Luke
Goblin yeah
they're leaving all this nice mood
around here what a shame we left it for
you because we know you you would want
oh
mindful I'm going ahead so I can yeah
he's got so much good stuff hey
hey
no what's this restoration
what's this I want to go up there we go
let's climb up this nasty yucky climb
the thing yeah
people took all the loot
I did oh yeah that'd be faster than that
but you'd better share the money from it
the revenue yeah you split the problem
no
climb
oops
why
oh there's a girl in here
oh yeah there's a map they do not react
okay
uh-oh then we still started to come and
see what about this one oh
button
I'm sorry let me see it closer it's okay
oh what happened well how are we all
missing we're killing a guy
I guess it'll take us some getting used
to team but that's okay
um
it was still alive here oh you okay
not enough movement I guess I'll just
move forward these boots
range ranged attacks all right
unless I could throw
do something to me dummy nice Miss idiot
here we go no I want to do something oh
I'm Barbarian
oh oh hell this is
crazy no I will not help
okay
the brain the brain you told us not to
kill let's get him
let's get him oh
hello
now there's two
die
all right I mean that works
we must have already died oh wow wow I'm
so powerful you're pretty strong
already
is there any loot left
let's see what's over here how about you
what are you holding why do you guys not
want to see this
oh thank you hey I saw you before my
eyes
what's this do okay I'm gonna go free
Shadow heart I'm gonna push this button
which button
what what where is she oh all right I'm
gonna freeze
what what's happening the console
appears everybody needs a ranged weapon
there's a socket
insert it well
comes to life Freedom I'm late
free here I'm freeing her now
place your hand on the console just let
her out let her frame
you took my key why didn't you take my
key
locking everything else you load Goblin
I was gonna share yeah sure
I don't even know what to do with this
I'm wise this is dark mine
what are we doing
critical friends
Shadow heart gonna die
what
it just rejected me feel the bite no
it's over did he die
yeah no she's super dead
tear it open I'm not giving up this is
all my fault
it's rolls
oh what the
are you kidding me
I'll show you Shadow heart all free hey
no I would have free Shadow heart I
wanna free I won The Rock
didn't use a reaction shocked
already Limited
already in use hurry up for your you
gotta free your nurse
critical failure I haven't even had a
critical failure in my game that I'm
playing right now
okay so I need to get for you it cannot
be held I'm still trying to open our
thing
it won't work
only one and it's open yeah only only
one at a time
do you need the key
incredible
I guess Rick Shadow heart it was nice
while it lasted
oh poor oh what's happening to her oh
why do we want this anyway because she
can join her party oh my God she's not
gonna be so dead yeah she's super dead
I am so dead
that's a shame okay she's still alive
you can use that key that you got to oh
you already emptied it all right you
know how to play this game I guess we
should just move along ladies no I don't
no what he's a romance option well it's
not like we'll never see her again if we
don't free her okay you got this you got
this you got it yeah people are saying
it's almost that chromatic dice are off
[Music]
yeah we both got ones well how did you
only get once
beautiful
then there's four of us am I right
ladies
critical success
we look so good together
iconic Duo
you know she pretty good I'm so glad I
could free you wow thank goodness I
freed you from the Pod wow good thing I
freed you myself
all by myself
[Music]
no no it's fine got a pro do you gotta
Pro do you feel that just now dangerous
companies what you need in a fight looks
like there's plenty of fighting it says
moriope let me come with you
got a heart beautiful no you're on your
own if you're if you're wiping if you're
wiping already uh we'd make for easy
double lady I want I want Shadow heart
okay you can have Shadow heart that's
fine okay I'm taking Shadow heart yeah
conspicuous she is good yeah
don't wait don't worry no I said there's
a very nice vampire dude no no we will
not allow him on the team he will never
be anywhere near any of you why not you
can't tell me
all right
Live Your Dream I'm a bit lost too
live your dreams
yeah yeah we came that way let's go uh
to the right
so we have a big party now yucky vampire
out of our camp
but he's yucky
[Music]
that fiend
what's inside do as I say okay
you got it
then we step on the fire get in the
butthole space button I don't want to
I'm ready
oh yeah yeah oh you know it the soul
squad's here
the whole Squad
pop up this one oh
I mean yes wait okay
I'm here now
do it we must escape
so we got it we're on the tentacle
dude's side for now Gotta Get Ready
no who am I right now um
Lily killed everything that we see yeah
I'll probably do some other stuff
oh yeah I forgot to rage
oh my God
so angry
oh that was okay
who's alive here
I mean okay we're pretty strong Jesus
yeah we can try and shoot let's go oh
that was
so dumb I mean it hit
oh
yeah
oh yeah gotta get to this let's take the
transponder I'm gonna new new
people
oh I'm not sure where the transponder is
it's on the other side hurry got a dash
was that oh there's more there's more
bad guys here can't get there can I Dash
dude the attack was resistant energy
took cop damage exception what if I want
to fight the devil
is level eight it has a hundred HP okay
never mind all right never mind
kill everything
he's resisting everything I'll wait for
you
wait we have 14 turns remaining by the
way
oh I see so that's how the race is I
should probably use it up beforehand
what I'm about to hit I'm about to
strike my rage ended I need to find a
way forward flute
oh
trying to strike
it's so clear I only have these two
chats that I should be using is that
correct
are you guys still shooting at him yeah
for fun yeah you're going for the
transponder bro there's three enemies
right now okay
I'm getting hurt okay
because he's super powerful dude yeah
okay yeah let the tentacle monster men
fight we gotta get those guys but I'm
just very slow I need some assistance
no I'm just very slow
I need your help I'm dry I can't reach
everyone's dead now
everyone's dead
well who's Dash do I have Dash yeah you
do have Dash It's on your it's on your
other side how did I miss it okay
people you're too strong
well no one was helping me so I was like
fine I'll do it myself
there's some fighting yeah I just killed
everyone here that was all me oh he's
dead oh oh it's okay I can take it oh oh
I'm gonna go for the thing I'm going for
the thing oh go for the thing
transponder
made it in time
already I don't have a pet yet do I
are you surviving on your single players
in fact I'm playing on normal mode
however I have not really played much of
the Barbarian class yet
I'm really good at Magic but I'm not
playing Magic this time
can you guys see the cutscene yeah okay
good
yeah big old dragon
oh
that looks painful
wow
people be careful
what's happening to everybody else while
this is going on
who's the witnesses you're watching me
struggle no one is coming to help me
sounds about right
get ready this is the rest of the
campaign
it's okay I know how to dash now
good I I don't know how to do anything I
wish I had a con say I wish my
controller worked because this is so
confusing that like I have to use my
mouse to move and then to turn the
screen stuff I have yeah
to wrote I'm like what
yeah
I'll try it
I mean I prefer a controller personally
oh the Goblins I know those guys I know
all your other your friends no no
they're not
definitely not
foreign
s are never good guys in any medium
can I say the thing what
stuff
I saw it in chat before you even said it
[Music]
Darkness will fade away
life will guide your way
oh oh
yeah
who did save us I don't know
let's go man that was clutch
then you are so beautiful thanks I know
you just Bella the ball
oh what's up sis
we look good what what me oh nice turn
back I mean you can be my sister too if
you want
being through
you need a cue I love the narrator's
voice so yeah it's very soothing very
ASMR
what'd it do bagel
okay
please teach me where the dash is
um it's on the left side of your bar
it's like a foot with wings
I just don't think I have eyeballs all
right
with wings is very important and jump is
also very important you will need to
jump oh yeah definitely nowhere to jump
button is all right leave it to me
I'm not dumb one second ketchup you guys
keep moving I just gotta take a sip of
water real quick hey
oh what's that oh
it's the it's the cube from that one
scary franchise
tesseract
give me some and Pinhead
oh dang it dang it one scary
franchise like I don't know the name of
it oh people what were you doing
oh I checking to see if you're okay of
course she's in love right away
speaking of
how are we alive
I saved you obviously
uh
we made it doesn't matter
judging by all the cops and strain about
I remember the ship
I remember falling
than nothing
damn uh I love the deadbeat inside jokes
uh where are we
I don't recognize this place
Sheila good
I suppose
no I want to steal her clothes
no ban
no stealing clothes let's go together
and we both know no it's fine you can
steal their clothes as long as you don't
steal their underwear
overburdened with Hangers On already ah
excuse you kill at the camp that's all
you're good for is Chill yeah I am just
stay at the camp there you go bye peace
all right ladies let's Bust a Move yeah
oh we leveled oh I'll click on your
character portrait to level you're gonna
need to level it to level up hold on a
sec all right excuse me level up
oh
it increases a lot and spell slot
nice and I'm getting tankier
oh I have to choose the Spells now okay
and I'm gonna have to read these to give
me a moment I got destructive wrath okay
I'm good
choosing spells man takes a letter
reading
oh we're gonna lose these bodies while
they're busy leveling up
um
[Music]
everything everything foreign
thank you chant
are you a man do you have a man voice I
do but I'm a lady excuse you
sorry excuse you sister
you're so cute and small
yeah I'm perfectly eatable yeah oh we'll
be doing lots of throwing yes and then
he throws away at us both
the Waypoint discovered let's go
oh money
I I guess I'll just
what did you just find oh this is a war
Point warp on the map oh so you can fast
travel here
and this is our first one though so we
can't go anywhere yeah
where's everybody oh look we're over
here
waiting no you never split the party
that doesn't seem like we know uh I I'm
exploring so
yeah this one's a little brain guys did
you guys get all the fish too are you
okay are you fighting oh my God
you're gonna need help you're okay
it's not worth checking anything
just just throw insults at them yeah I
need my turn I need my turn
emotional damage it's fine
oh as far as possible uh oh okay help me
oh I can bonus action there's nothing I
can do whoa nice nice
that was good
[Music]
are you okay the return I guess yeah
she's fine she's fine she's okay vicious
mockery
yeah we just kind of we just gotta kill
this guy
uh they said biboo apparently you hit me
yeah you were in the way
so there is uh friendly a fire in those
guys yes there is
correct careful
I got it
you can run so quick why yeah all right
I got you I'm gonna throw you a potion I
can be useful heal here I'll heal you
here why yeah how do you have so many
attacks
I need a help
I need to help
do not throw uh it's we're fine we're
fine someone smacked this thing right in
front of us
excuse me yeah did you miss oh no you
didn't okay good it didn't it didn't
feel sad okay yeah I didn't hear a
Smacker that was weird
oh God
oh
that's good what's going on too late I
want to go up here I Will Follow You
Marissa oh yeah wait never said come
here don't you wanna be a nice elf man
ew I do I do want to meet a nice
elephant come over here will he join my
team and help me yeah a lot of things if
you want him to
look up the hill
go just go talk to him
I don't see anyone keep going just keep
walking yeah keep going how big will it
be oh I see a man yeah
we gotta kill frog let's go tune in he's
got a printing corner
uh you girls are so fast like you can't
look at anything
um
what are we doing right now
oh you're listening that was so based of
narissa right there whoa whoa whoa whoa
kill me
ooh he does that I did not see this part
oh good luck
and I'm wrapping I'm gonna die
yeah
[Music]
it's lunch money because he's playing
hard to get an eraser you're playing
hard to guess dressing up but whilst I
was trapped in that pot
[Music]
how it is
this is chaotic I like it though why
does he think we belong to them you are
we're obviously good people
share a brain cell walking out of
Paris
um
he likes you yeah
that's why it's how he shows affection
the Mind flayers were me connected us
that sounds uh
whatever they did whatever they put in
US
just no he's annoying
let's go
whatever just happened the typical DND
slash world of Darkness vampire ready to
decorate isn't even a vampire
look at those teeth spoilers yeah
you just gotta gotta learn I'm out of
line of flowers so I hope it looks very
much like one also it reminds me of
Victor
yeah but a little bit less obnoxious
still yeah true
um
oh baldorian option ah are we all are we
all valorians
various ways are we yeah I think we are
all of us yeah I think we we all got we
all got like joints from from the city I
think is that so
we clearly move in different circles wow
this guy in the face
he's like Bernie no GTA 5.
can I kick him out I don't want to talk
to him anymore why did you guys make me
do that
you like him no I don't like men
I like evil men not men
oh what's the difference
a big difference big difference
yeah I can't come out
no thanks uh
it won't let me stick to what you want
I'm leaving don't
hilarious is it gonna make you
send him to the camp
it won't let me pick any of them
no it makes the sound but nothing is
happening
it's like a double
click a triple he's never gonna leave
thank you so much I'm clicking so much
guys help maybe bye
uh what if we stop listening
yeah guys get me out of here time to
save it how do we stop listening X on
the top right
excellent that's all
right bye Marissa
did you find this Kiara I I summoned it
I have I can summon like five six
different animals I just realized it's
sick this is don't work numbers aren't
working you guys can we knock her out of
combat yeah can you like him I got you
and I'm sorry guys
that was awesome you better heal me too
oh my God this is so dangerous
can I even save and reload is that even
possible
I got a different option I got different
options oh okay uh wait no no I'm stuck
again kill me oh let her back down put
it back down yeah do we want her to
survive no kill me
I don't wanna that's Kiara sorry
let me help you
okay did you get it you get an option
now
I'm staying in safe distance
at this point I'm just having a good
time having a good time
across the sky just they even reload
apparently okay all right let me see I
don't know what data it's gonna show
hang on let me you got it yeah I got
your back let me save the game real
quick
new save with Mario can I help oh can I
help you okay
food game
safe successful okay
okay
did you did you get into a loading
stream or screen yes okay why is my game
not sure
a bit late to save
now I'm safe after everyone got hurt I'm
sure it'll be fine we're new at this
okay
we still have my game I'm dead because
you killed me
you'll be fine we can
we can save you oh you're back down okay
let me help you out
you're good yeah dang just stop by
talking to this freaking guy yeah yeah
what someone else I don't want to hello
okay well we
I can't move can I kill him what
I I can move my screen but I can't I
can't move oh
God they're broken
oh do you have an earlier save do you
have I have a quick save I think here
let me yeah maybe go back to that
earlier save before we met this freaking
guy he fell apart ruined everything all
right let me see auto save all right um
there's us on the beach
but you can just grab it again it's okay
we can get it again better than better
than whatever's going on right now yeah
whatever whatever this is thank goodness
for autosave it looks like pasta
oh yeah save save Lots because you know
something like this might happen
[Music]
back here oh I think we have to level
again yeah that's oh no I'm good I don't
need to take so much time
I can't level oh oh Shadow heart hi
let's go oh we talked to her again hold
on let me I'll let you go faster you do
your thing booboo okay uh
yeah
go into the camp
so I don't have the leveling thing guys
yeah I don't either neither do I I think
I already left it's already after we
leveled it since yeah
because mine's only at 13 and I thought
I was at like 20 something oh you're
right oh there we go there we go we got
it just popped
okay
let's get those levels
no problem free hats yeah let's save if
we decide to talk to that guy again
beforehand yeah since he broke the game
yeah oh yeah well you know there are
always other greener pastures like uh
maybe halson you know I bet you'd like
animals next time
is a great kind soul I think you'll
really like that character and maybe
you know
yeah well no why wouldn't you trust me I
mean I feel like he's just a very
Charming character that you'd like
that's all that there is to it there's
no no tricks no trickery no anything
just give me different clothes yeah
you don't like your gray gloves that's
why I wanted to get a steering because
the stereo has nice clothes too it does
have nice clothes but I don't I don't
want him I want to steal his clothes
oh okay now we're all here for the
battle let's go okay
uh can I walk around this
uh probably gonna have to move around it
okay how do I need to equip something
long range pretty sure I have a short
bow your frog is so cute
can I
um
why doesn't it hurt me still that's
pretty evil you stepped in like the
little corner of it
snack
hey can I not how do I can I not attack
when I dashed no because no you can't
yeah I can do this
I can at least leave a Hunter's Mark
nice
it will do more damage if you if you
shoot them throw axes oh I can throw
axes oh you're so right Chad I didn't
know that because I don't play barbaric
oh boy
you're good you're good on the way good
I'm good can I control the Frog
you should be able to yeah it's not the
Frog's turn yet
oh okay you want a party
oh yeah
oh angry
uh
get him Froggy's friend
wow
give me brain frog only one HP
Nani oh there's another one up there
Maury smash
triangle
my turn I love the Frog's portraits ah
okay wait now it's frog okay now it's
froggy time what can froggy do
some things
can froggy attack no not enough movement
okay froggy just follow oh cute he can
be butter you know cannon fodder or bait
awesome yeah I guess so let's go I can't
do anything special ah wait wait A Touch
of creature can I do this no not enough
movement I guess if I would have dashed
but it's okay you're good
oh you need help
ouch your HP is only that
am I gonna be okay okay it's not bad
yeah it's fine
good shoot the other one girls he has a
hunter's Hunter's Mark on Hunter's Mark
nice yeah
oh oh how oh
that sucks
you had to concentrate to keep the
Hunter's Mark active
yeah you're good you're good all right
good luck it's only for me
nah hey can I do anything else
and rage nah there's no reason to end my
rage
yeah keep raging keep raging I think
it's over though after this turn
um
there yeah this one
I need healing
um you have some uh oh yeah
oh that was on that was on the wrong
person
[Music]
thank you
let's drink it
oh thanks
[Laughter]
smash
and only smash
all right time for you to go kill that
guy
all right I'm not talking to him again
this is up to someone else all right I
don't want to do that
you were so cool when you like when you
like got him to the ground and like like
him up that was safe
talk to this video
mine too okay
so yucky
kill the others help you got it he's
used to kill it yourself he's a useless
don't worry what else I got um you want
a Tango pretty boy he got you on the
ground too yeah good luck
push yourself to your feet can I add a
bonus both at the same time inspiration
is that okay
I want to be cool
ah let's go
wow
yeah success
apparently he's good at picking locks
yeah he's a stealthy one
um
in the chat
sorry I haven't done anything to you yet
he's kind of he's kind of jerk you know
yeah
get out of here Dollar Store victim what
was that what's going on
yucky man the knife away and I'll tell
you any everything I'm not an idiot
it has to be this I'm only eye resting
chest something they did
they took you too
I saw it during
whatever just happened
I was ready to decorate the ground with
your Innings I would like to after this
cutscene rest for a moment but I can
heal my HP apology accepted oh yeah oh
you can press shortness yeah I just need
apparently everybody too please tell me
you got it impressed I can't rest
through this guy's dialogue yeah we just
need we don't care we just need him
go to the camp dummy all right we can
rest
there you go oh much better yeah I feel
rested let's go ahead and do a save here
oh yeah let's go it's like good good
call yeah it's popping off in here hello
let's kill it yeah kill it
beat him up
you guys talk to him
yo little it's serious
I don't know
right for that yeah that was kind of
Awesome
all right I think we need to go this way
oh because it just suddenly die oh
Goblin scimitar
oh The Bijou Caleb during the cutscene
nah no Cuts yeah I bonked them right in
the head cut scene was too good for it
what is that
that looks uh crazy Marissa do you
really want to stand so close to it
yeah yeah
well apparently Marissa was stuck
because of a party boat I don't know
what that means though oh I don't know
because every other time when people
were voting it didn't get stuck like
that if people didn't vote so I think I
think the Voting is just like a
suggestion isn't it yeah yeah exactly I
don't think it was the problem and give
him a hand there was um
luck
that's all
that 20. wow
critical failures on this whatever
you're doing
now our pool should do the trick
go to help him out I don't I don't have
any I don't have any strength so
okay
it doesn't really look like you're
pulling that hard there is some wait
who's he oh oh this is what you like
he's a wizard I don't know I want to
know who he is though
apologies oh
he's Mr Magic Man
yeah
a bit shocked but I'll be nice to him he
doesn't seem like a mean guy pleasure to
make your acquaintance
say but I know I like his fluffy hair in
a manner of speech
the wizard of waterdeep
you two were on the receiving end of a
rather unwelcome insertion
worms in our brains
it is there a conditioner
the wizard he's a wizard apparently
I ship it there is that and that's the
wizard
is really cool you know
[Music]
soon to be something else
hmm we do have one few enough can it's
not exactly a common Affliction we're
most certainly going to need a Healer
I'm a really dumb cleric though I don't
think you would trust me to like get
worms out of your head
I trust you
oh
okay
we're traveling with plenty of company
already
perhaps I can join you later instead
go to my Camp stay there forever if you
play solo are all these dudes like
joining you yeah yeah and you play solo
they they join up and then you can like
hang out with them and do their like
story quests but we have our own we have
our own we have our own party which is
so much better I wonder how we get their
approval though if they're never on our
team like out in the field with us
oh this way you got to get their
approval if you want to raise them up
but if they're always in the camp you
can't get their approval
Marissa why are you walking like that I
don't know
what are you doing
she's like and now that's back to normal
okay
talks what's here when you see
hello
hello there's so much to look at
oh there's people here hello
should we kill them
yeah sounds fun I just saved the game
uh Taman and wooden uh gimbal Bach
gimbal box you're real nice to him oh my
God hey what's up it looks like one of
my old cats
I am not impressed looks like a raccoon
I summoned a raccoon oh really
honestly it looks like a raccoon but
it's supposedly a cat
attack
able
meow I love
I have a meow action and what else just
meowing attract the attention of nearby
creatures to draw them closer to you
um cat cannot move too much
distraction no one will hurt this cat
I heard the cat I will destroy them I
will destroy them
wow well it did attract the tensions
are you kidding me
bye info
all right hold on right I got you
wow put your nostrils
what's with your nostrils
you in fact my eyes the nostrils
I was trying to throw a potion at you
sorry oh she did
yeah I killed two people though I killed
two people so it was worth it I'm in
danger too never says in danger too we
only have Cali at full HP sorry
[Music]
what's happening right now
um someone's turned oh oh
God oh
let me
hold on a sec
thank you you're welcome now let me see
if I can
do I'm like a sweet
how dare you do that to narissa
so rude
can I use a Potion No I mean at least if
I'm knocked out I heal right if they
make me sleep that's how it works in
Games
bad news
oh
I'm gonna try to wake you up okay
next time I kill him I am not the team
baggage am I doing this right to chat
dang it
um all right can I help you wake up
oh wait um
how much 80 I'm dying still
no don't range
that's not what I want to do yay oh you
guys
make me auto do that
haha nice damage yeah yeah do something
I am holding a ranged weapon now
oh wait this always are still alive okay
okay let's go down
sit down beat her up oh wow what what
why did you do that when we're like
right we're literally right here oh well
she is arranged no don't freak
it doesn't matter it doesn't matter oh
wow oh thank you no
stop taking the gold right before my
eyes
hey
rude yeah
Point Blank Archer show oh oh oh are you
okay you want a ground
hello
it's a crazy brother
oh boy oh let me jump back oh dear okay
hello oh this is like a dungeon oh Jesus
okay um
oh that is a lot of people that's a lot
of dudes that's more than one okay we
got this who are they
oh my god oh good yeah insult them
insult them more oh my God tell them
they're stinky
oh oh
it's fine tomb Raiders okay I'm gonna
try to blast all of them here we go
let's blast them okay anyway I start
blasting how many can I get oh okay
yes look at this
I blew up how many I got I got nobody
what's that even though you did good I
tried my best I did not have good rolls
it's the matters
push this person
yeah give Neal one too shove them okay
somebody set the oil on fire do it oh
who has a fireball
you can shoot it
oh
I don't have fire but there's oil on the
floor now I don't know if this really
works I also do not have fire I don't I
don't have a fire again
How's It Go five five light to fire a
brighter higher as you desire
chasing all that weight is fine or
something something
all right
of course they don't enjoy
of course they just point blank ignore
the tank
wow
I don't know what that means but I think
you call him stinky yeah he is stinky
he's smelly dude what are they doing
wait what's that oh they added more
pizzas
if I go here and then
I do this
let me get off this oil
just in case
wait don't leave me
please
I'm still in retail I'll apply haunt
this Mark on him I'm going to perish
I'll find him next turn
[Laughter]
hopefully they will attack me please
let me take the damage
yes go for our tank what do we have our
tank for don't attack the the weak ones
please not the glass cannons
help
oh oh man y'all oh dear
good luck
somebody I have no spells
ow
it's like they know
I'm about to die wait let me use this on
him can I not
he Dash
gonna be fun looting this place
afterward
s and live ah there we go oh we
definitely will
oh
[Music]
don't worry Bijou or taken Downs
I bought him on the head and he took
zero damage
yeah
seven damage on your mama mia what's
that mean
um well you're choosing how to react
oh
you can react yeah you can react
sometimes you can like sit back to the
counter spell
go go
yeah
wow oh I didn't know I could do that
okay
[Music]
okay well that's one person
was your father a flounder oh wow
what's the flounder isn't that a fish
it's a fish
it was your father a fish wow
to you guys no no no we'll revive you
I'd love to revive you but I do need to
do something about this yeah no no no
you do something I I'm on my way don't I
have a Revival thingy oh yeah the attack
right there ah
uh I'm gonna try to revive her then
the only thing to remember is when she
comes back it'll be at one HP so gotta
make sure
oops
[Laughter]
it's fine it's fine no win uh oh now I
can't can I take path is interrupted oh
I'm in the way
shouldn't you be able to aim over her
head
come on now why is it only 42 of me
being able to throw it properly because
because throwing throwing is difficult
it looks hard yeah can I oh wait is
there anything else I can do like they
say just touch her yeah there you go
okay it'll give her one HP though so you
gotta heal pretty quick after that or
someone will just knock her out real
fast
all right
uh for retreat
your little look at that Tower
he knows what he's doing
he's using real strats wow I mean smart
man I should play like that um
do I have any do you have any problems
okay ah if you throw the potion right at
her it would hurt her because it's an
attack roll so you have to throw it
right to the ground next to her is that
what happened to Cali before I don't
think so thank you like the Polish is
made of glass so you're throwing a glass
bottle yeah so that's probably on the
ground when we want to do that thanks
for the help chat on the ground so I
can't do anything
um oh except uh perform yeah okay yeah
do you know Ragnar the red
no Ragnar the red gotta learn Ragnar the
red
it's my favorite dinner this is this is
all this is this is what you're getting
does that even does that do anything oh
good okay
okay it's fine
um
oh how I'm helping
thanks
oh nice nice nice nice hi Luke no I
can't thank you
I want to change back to my other weapon
was it team if
you
oh there's the one person no hello sneak
attack
ow is that coward yeah
I think that didn't do that much then
um
wow oh gosh wouldn't have a blast yeah I
don't know how I feel if someone called
me that uh
owie
okay
okay yeah yeah yeah
thank you okay
let's go
um I suggest we all take a long rest yes
wait how do I do that who's over there
the race that come come to us yes
long rest wow I sit like such a lady oh
do you want to end today oh no yeah I
just wanted to sit down
we're doing long rest right hey what
were you able to say
we should we should end the day so we
get our spells back yeah no be sure to
sit on Cali's uh oh what are we wearing
yeah
okay how do we steal how do we steal
their clothes
Gail has like our clothes
we look like
nice everyone's everyone's backside is
finally crafted in this game even ours
I wanna close
why do you want to take off her clothes
so badly
no I don't I want to wear her clothes
because they're nice what does she kind
of wear then huh
I doubt that they will fit her
uh just FYI says somebody in chat I
don't know if it's a one guy situation
you can't steal their clothes with four
UPS four Co-op players without killing
them
oh
brief so loudly I don't need a stereon
right something the matter I guess I
could just murder him how do I take his
clothes by killing him
with anything no what's your damn mouth
for yourself like just like blonde
murder in the camp just
okay
slap his cheeks around a little bit
roll initiative
yeah I'm saying it literally
crimes certain actions are frowned upon
by others like I give a let's go
yeah I killed him oh my God yay
[Music]
what are they doing
we're so messed up wearing the right
outfits
clothes yay
take his underwear
I just always happening
oh well you guys are crazy you killed
someone yeah it was sick
why
I wanted his clothes now I got like
fancy clothes I'm pretty sure we can
just undress them I don't think we have
to kill them no we gotta kill him you
want their clothes
sadly with four with four player
okay well I I'm happy
okay put them on
I did
well
would you like to go to bed yeah sure
yeah let's sleep you can't resurrect
them back apparently
canceled what what me not me
what is this oh yeah
somebody canceled again why not your boy
is currently choosing camp supplies for
long rest yeah yeah okay so something
wait I think I think Kelly has it too
surprised choose it okay okay can
players denied the request
yes okay yes
I'm sorry
noodles who is trolling
fingers in your skull
I don't think anyone's interested
Force the tab pull out of your mind I'm
not very intelligent so I'll just wins
I'm smarter than all of you all right
well I'll use wisdom I'm Wiser than that
you focus I'll try it too oh whoops
I succeed you know it's our first meal
in the game big success maybe maybe we
want it you can make it clear that you
are what
you know what is there to fear yeah it's
the one stuck inside you it is a minor
oh there's a brick but why is this a
mountain enough exactly I mean it's in
character right
then character
[Music]
no understand oh I can't wake up because
you guys are in a country
wouldn't I get to sleep if I failed this
what what would have done what what did
that even do the fact that I succeeded
and what would it have done if I failed
oh no no idea
[Music]
somebody says you you said you wanted to
multi-class
yes apparently we can't on this
difficulty
what yeah it's disabled on the
difficulty because it's fairly Advanced
oh come on what should we do lyric
um it's okay I'll just wait
when the reroll happens I can re-roll
changing difficulty and menu option I
can change it oh yeah changes are normal
yeah change normal we'll be fine oh yeah
we'll live we will live yeah
I don't know about that you guys
we've already been a little branch of
dying a lot of times
it's okay we're pretty we're early on
the break of dying because we don't have
stuff yet exactly
okay
if it's too difficult yeah but then the
multi-class thing you know
French multi-class then go back
so
really
um
[Music]
moriope love Liara
oh
oh yeah maybe you need extra you take
like two spaces
there we go oh look at us nice but
there's always going to be one girl
excluded why is our our poster so
why do we sit like that how do I steal
people's clothes without killing them
you can't
[Music]
click on the bed click on the bed roll
the bed roll the bad the bad thing
I'll leave Camp okay
all right
are you trying to end the day
again
ladle wait no I don't need this stuff
open this
already
dust
yeah
I'm stuck
where are you stuck oh okay I'm good now
is there nothing left in here did we
already kill everybody yeah I thought
there was gonna be more there's a
there's a thing over this way
why would I need the cutting board
you guys are still inside yeah
yeah okay I'm on the other side oh
stealing all the money from here
why does the books have HP that might be
worth a look oh
is there ever something special I did
something
did something happen
you do not recognize the language on the
plaque
oh
there's a door I opened over here
I'm on the way
mm-hmm
which door
this way this one yeah this one
where is oh no we saw yeah why are you
giggling
why are you giggling
[Laughter]
did you go
wait where'd you go
so I'm just exploring some more she's a
little thing let's go
take what okay this is mine
there's like nothing of value in there
did you already steal everything in here
Bieber
oh oh where are you going oh
what's gonna happen
what's happening
I think we're fine
what what's happening for you girl I
ended my turn I uh I think yeah I think
you have to end your turn
oh but there's a button apparently
what button
go back to entrance okay I can't go so
far
oh okay
[Music]
no maybe now it's it's not as dangerous
anymore because it's shot once you think
it's gonna shoot again oh
maybe it'll be fine no it's not safe
it's not over okay okay uh let's leave
the treasure
yeah oh okay
assumes you
I'm not until you turn out of the turn
boost mode
exit okay
whoa whoa okay
oh
they're like
oh are you guys fighting something oh oh
we're fine no it's fine it's fine it's
fine it's fine oh oh uh people does it
ever stop yeah you're dying I'm dying
yeah
oh
you're never gonna be able to push that
yeah there's a bus I mean do you want to
walk into that I mean I mean I already
got the loot in the thing in the middle
you did is there more of them done I
don't know if I can shoot the buttons
I I earned it I earned it I went and
grabbed it and survived I earned this
I turned it off
okay we'll go find them
oh oh is it good now yeah I turned it
off
go oh
we'll try you guys oh I found something
with 71 health
oh he's dead though
but his chemicals are still kind of
moving
look
Ed oh
you know
is there anything oh anyway
is this better than what I have oreop
only Fine Dirt
Holy Dirt the text on the planet this
we're too dumb to understand what's on
the plaque yeah not very smart
equip the shield
are you guys still down in that uh Place
yeah we didn't finish exploring it
well there's something over here
oh
there's dead people with loot oh cool I
love that
my aesthetic
that statue religion failed
oh they have so much money
press the secret button oh
nice mine mine Memorial past things
maybe it's a trap again
I missed you guys okay I'm gonna look
very happy to see their Maury
fighting time where is it okay
um there's a person next to me oh yeah
one right next to me too
somebody
oh get him deadbeats whose side are you
on
boy
all right
oh he almost died I wonder how tanky
these guys are I need to see their
health
nice shot
there
oh oh you missed come on the Crypt it
looks so strong though sheesh I have the
same final go help my friends but
where are you you lose this area
where I do I'm gonna be I was having a
good time
on a little solo Journey
yeah I was alluding looting things on
the beach the beach
rattle them boys oh he's dead oh
um another one
[Applause]
you've been frosted
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay
yeah bye
hi dummy I love that spell
um
okay
this is what yes okay one HP left hmm
use the other one
oh
back off deadbeat you don't want this
you don't want any
oh
I'm too lucky
they never hit they always miss
oh angry hey let it all out it's good to
let it out
let the aggressions out back off did
beat back off
deadbeats have a bad aim yeah
out of things do I already use my bonus
action I'll live through this surely
oh yeah yeah it should be fun
uh-oh I forgot about him
whoa
yeah six
[Music]
how many enemies are left
but they're all pretty beaten right
yeah yeah we got this
boom
oh he died he did die
hey
yay
what you gonna do oh what you're gonna
do
with you
is there there's one left Gun there's
still one dude on the right behind
people who kind of get behind me let's
see him I see him okay
I'm here for backup yeah
oh money
they have money
a lot of effort to hide one sarcophagus
all right
what's in there what's inside big
treasure beyond my wildest imagination
oh
oh huh
foreign
oh you're talking oh
he's got pretty eyelashes oh my God have
we found your Romance
[Laughter]
oh it's the weather
Supreme deadbeat right
heal that nose you're curious
just got a little beaten up
no I have a question
question
it's a test from sensei okay um oh let
me see the multiple choice questions
they're crawling out of a tomb peaceful
Undead interesting why aren't you
attacking me
no attack Mario
yeah
away again
this is on the quiz I'm trying to
remember the real answer this ogre is
having a harsh time answering the
question what matters is mine
Deeds
I am sure they'll believe this was I
right sensei there are different ways I
can phrase it
money Jesus
[Laughter]
we used to see each other again no join
our team and place oh he will he will
look we'll see each other again
[Music]
no no yeah oh Lord I got magic Missile
magic Missile
[Laughter]
oh actually
do you want this Amulet of lost voices
unless you speak with the dead oh yeah
that sounds you can speak with your
homies okay here okay cool
you hold on what is this oh Soul coin
the coins can power infernal engines
um do you want magic Missile
I'm not gonna use it
oh sure I can hold on to him no wait I
don't want to stop I don't want to use
it
but still the controls they still Escape
me okay sorry I remember how to do this
hi Lisa hi
does this do anything
for white cool armor poorly there's a
ring on my finger
Yahoo
oh
girl why are you holding a starion's
underwear what did you just do
ladder way out it's the same
all right it's a little weird but
alrighty Alan come to us wait who has
the sterions underwear Kiara's wearing
it what
no yes you are
what do you mean I'm wearing it wearing
it I checked your inventory
what
what I didn't
consciously equipped anyone's underwear
and you're wearing it
there's a ladder
I'll find you oh no shovel
I'll find you guys don't worry
Ollie left yeah there's some stairs oh
because all half elf on the way is the
same okay
I didn't know that that's a lot less fun
oh wow oh no vampires
so yeah it was going yoink his underwear
I believe but I don't know if anybody
did that
all right I'm out I'm on the way
where shall we go next team
good question can you do a short rest
you were here before
oh so I gotta I gotta do the short rest
huh
as those
okay no worries okay
we came from here now
where are we going
lead the way okay this way I'll follow
people okay I've been together strong
Abba together strong no you never split
the party
[Music]
where are we going
um actually no not this way not this way
we've been this way we didn't go up this
way yet
um
left or right
oh well this way
wait actually actually where wait hold
on there's someone over here uh anyone
can short rest but it's good to talk
about it gotcha
oh there's a being oh it's the it's the
girl yes
it's a different situation
uh
Zoro was right oh yellow is a toad
prisoner
and if it escapes how will you
oh hi a guest s
what do we do in Liara
a lipstick that's up to you yeah what do
you think is right
good luck
get rid of them well
foreign
but am I saying this to her
yeah I think you're saying it to to the
the people yeah
but I don't really have much persuasion
and deception at all
I try to talk to them because I have
both of those
I'll
I guess I'll try do your best
yeah no one can get
over 10. come on what yeah
yeah
get out of here cheap links let's go
we'll check out that blast tea flings
tea
German by the way for for deeplings oh
really yeah
they just make it sound fancy
I'm good so we came for a look mm-hmm
I'm in dire need of healing I don't know
not really but we'll find out please
help to get to get the the things out of
our head yeah
oh okay
uh five okay
totally doable
let's go yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
where is
look for Nettie whatever you want
say whatever
even the worms so cool they're pretty
nice I killed these dudes
no wow yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh hi well then you're gonna stay up
there
too bad observe and listen
s
you can just kill her and then you can
shoot it
we accidentally shoot her
to YouTube
we throw something at it what this guy
came up with a panda
bro
for us is there oh what did I do what
did I do
as interrupted release me and she will
share it okay bro go
now share the tadpole hasn't yet
scrambled all your senses
talk to her my people possess the cure
for this infection
you will join me oh hi that was me
right uh we'll go our separate ways I
thank you what is a crush crush it
sounds like a French food
a shelter it does yes they're chill Camp
when infected with a gay tadpole we must
report to Augusto for purification
all right we'll journey together
dismiss your weakest Warrior all right
who's the weakest Warrior
anyone
get out of here
go back to the camp you you're the
weakest oh very nice we're all very
strong ladies yeah
also her armor looks like plastic so
yeah
okay and we're so cool
the thing
yeah the thing they just told us about
before they left oh the the area the
campsite they came from we're like
Nettie I hear you're shouting up ahead
we'll get we will get there for sure I
think okay
oh something's happening quickly save
hold on
little save oh yeah okay this is I think
this is the right direction
I'm for gorblins what's going on
tail
more like get janky
the yucky one
nine Hills over the gate now you open
the gate yeah when the when the when the
bad guy is there
no yes
a lot of facts let's go well maybe if
you open the gate sooner yeah true yeah
right
that's a that's a life they lost for no
reason
can we help him yeah we can let's do it
I love will will so awesome oh
yeah Mr Hero man
oh I'm sorry
in front of me okay right back yeah I
can't I can't do anything we are pretty
far back I I might need some help what
is this well you should be waiting for
us
am I dashing I want to dash yeah we are
pretty far away Dash might be in order
why does it even start when we're so far
away should I get on the hill or stay
here I I either use it go on the hill
oh wait no no oh that's I thought that
was one of us
okay uh
um
oh
hmm
wow
good luck y'all are really far
these guys look like they can handle
themselves
yeah
Cali is this one we never split a party
yeah this would be the reason
oh
[Music]
ha ha
oh we're doing a little dance
[Music]
oh I get better accuracy the further I'm
away with bows oh
interesting
yeah I thought I I thought that was
another one of us that's why I got so
close Okay
um
horn from back in the day
the old things the medieval days
wow
wow Miss twice
right can I push this person
I pushed this person oh how forty
percent I also I will risk it plus do it
speed
dang no it's too bad double your
movement speed
I
am good I'm not gonna use it
whoa whoa I'm sorry
okay cool
nice I don't know how I did that but
so you can push and then also attack
still I guess maybe I'll try the same
thing
[Music]
um
chat if he's like down here and I'm up
there
can I shoot him because like
realistically I don't think I could
I mean The High Ground is an advantage
you have The High Ground I mean like
down yeah oh right there yeah because he
wouldn't be what do you mean do you see
what I'm pointing at
oh
because I follow you yeah yeah it
sounded like you know what I'm pointing
at I mean right below like right it
doesn't matter if you aim at him and it
says that like he doesn't say your past
obstructed and it just gives a regular
like percentage it would be okay oh got
him oh oh nice well done
um
all right
and now we shoot
yes
we get him
and turn
oh you can paint hold out and right
click please almost in the battle I'm
almost there
Dash was helpful
good to know
[Music]
you girls know how to Ping because now I
found out
I think yeah like that
this is what I meant here I see I can
see it on the map yeah is it right click
or left click right click and I click
okay oh okay
yes yes
go help them
go help hold on they're really far away
yeah I think you can scale down the
mountain
or the hell that we're on
there there she is see there I am yeah
Kawaii has arrived
[Music]
um
hold on we'll reopen our way not
throwing
uh let's see
I'm shot
oh good crit let's go oh he's Manny
works as scary I know I can throw the
knives but I feel like where do I know
works from
oh
yeah he hated that he's mad wangy
[Music]
pop
uh hold on
uh
wrong so I guess throwing would be nice
what was that
oh
[Music]
um I don't have any attacks left so late
I know I know the order is wrong why go
down yep because they're still far away
I did not see them
thank you
yeah right I love the Rings thought so
parts of
these guys and they're they're front
lining I'm in the back
I'm still behind them yeah you're
feeling it oh that person's dead yeah
and we couldn't save them we failed them
we will be revived surely
okay I'm gonna go stab this thing oh I
can't do this more accuracy for being up
High
um
okay oh wait
wait I stabbed him okay I'll stab this
one then oh yeah do your thing yeah one
damage let's go awesome let's go not a
stab that was a poke
but good job
better than nothing
[Music]
I'm gonna put the mark on
it oh
[Music]
um
is it damaged uh well now I know that I
have any damage on that one
two guys left I think pretty much
outnumbered I think we'll definitely win
[Music]
yeah
we need to fight more things so we can
level one more time yeah
I want more stuff yeah we're weak oh oh
that guy's dead too oh oh oh
no
okay all I can do is stab so I'm just
gonna keep stabbing
let's go
[Music]
that was one time use
no stop saving everything
angry
I didn't do anything to him
I didn't I didn't either the battle
isn't oh what what happened that was he
doesn't like you Looting again the
goblin the goblin wasn't the guy I think
you may have accidentally looted one of
the dead people oh do we okay can we run
away
uh is he temporarily hostile or Perma
hostile maybe we can like download the
Dead Island oh he's he's temporarily
hostile I'm sorry
let me see no I think I think we both
did it Bijou I'm not sure oh I don't
know I just thought the goblin wasn't
bad that's what you get from being a
little Goblin you guys can talk with
non-lethal attacks and we need to fight
him I think so oh yeah how do you turn
that off yeah there's like a switch so
like you know where you have all your
spells and stuff like go to the first
wheel and it's like at the top wait not
available can we just can we just
disengage
I'm sure
goodbye okay sorry will sorry
one person toggles it for the entire
party oh
yeah
he might resent you but they won't be
actually hospital I'm incapacitated
okay good okay
come on be nice pretty let's go nice one
can we just okay Enter
I'm leaving yeah
don't worry I'm hidden he'll never be
your friend we just gotta run from him
don't enter they say one person says
don't enter
charm just means he won't attack you you
gotta run away and then flee to Camp
uh-huh okay okay I'm running away if you
answer more people might try to find out
oh so you have to run away and get far
enough so it disengages from combat well
we love will I want him on our team yeah
cool he's awesome will you stop being
mad
ah I wouldn't even lose it wasn't even
me
he's not up for reasoning
okay just just run oh I remember I
remember that yeah I should have
remembered that was gonna happen
it won't work on him he can't be an
enemy please
poorly no no no no no we'll just have to
run away for a far far enough
doesn't like the green pink
Marissa it looks like a heart I like it
run away can I disengage now
yum can I can I flee from combat
am I far enough
how do you how do you tell if you're far
enough I don't think there is a far
enough
get out of the battle
I'm trying
to be maybe we all have to bear yeah
27 meters isn't so much okay well I'm
far enough now of course
whoa leave me alone
it's fine
HP and a dream
I spam the red button the red button
didn't work
see all right I should be okay flea
combat yes we combat flea combat yes
it's not working right
is it working for you yeah I flew I fled
to camp how come how come it's not
working for me I'm like are you not far
enough I got pretty far away I'm using
oh you're using dashed yeah I'm like
super far I also have fled the combat
eyes are open just keep keep running
keep running you can flee from combat
and go to Camp if you are far enough
from your enemies and it's it says it's
fine enough
how many camps are there
and why what this one's for me
can I buy arrows here
yeah it won't it won't let me press the
button okay I'll keep running I guess
maybe again please I mean
ice arrows oh
it's okay I'm still in combat too so
wait oh he's coming after you
people are you pressing the disengage
thing yeah
the bottom white red one because the
bottom white red one but it I think it's
bugged because it doesn't say how many
meters you're away from him because for
me it said I need 27 meters
I was out of his range because it didn't
say the 27 meters anymore but now he got
closer so I don't know
but he's chasing me
well they say that he likes you when he
chases you so oh yeah
more because I'm far enough but it won't
let me disengage still
I am going to perish going without me
remember me
got something to say about what I'm
doing over here no I'm just concerned
um
how do I volunteer without killing him
is that even I think he's gonna kill me
hi I can hide okay
[Music]
we meet again
has predicted
I shall be here
we can reload if you want that battle
was easy so we can just do it again oh
you want to reload must be unarmed or
using oh I can maybe I can Bonk him I
fail yeah hold on I'll try to I'll okay
I'll try to Bonk him hold on one second
yeah as long as the embarrassing not
lethal
yeah
knock someone unconscious okay I need to
be unarmed so I need to take off
weapons okay come here I'm gonna Bonk
you
I messed up Marissa
I'm chilling you you look so beautiful
they're in Basking in the sunlight but
also partially being covered by the
beautiful leaves above you thank you the
sunlight doesn't just work Wonders on
you you guys Romancing each other
you guys having fun I'm sure glad you
guys are having fun
well well well you shouldn't have
Bluetooth
[Applause]
[Music]
dirty loot Goblin
oh another chance
oh my God why
why did nobody nobody carry away the
dead body of a Starion no at least it's
hilarious
[Music]
to another camp
look at this look at his underwear what
the heck okay well
I'm going to die
oh no okay well I am actually deceased
by to bring them back to life well maybe
my skeleton friend can help for a prize
um yeah hey buddy can you help me bring
my friend back to life
[Music]
um
yeah uh resurrect someone I think she is
oh I'm gonna bring you back oh thank you
so I will
surely he'll forgive you
right I'm a new person that's me
really thanks for noticing let's give
your upturned bats now is any better
thank you hello hello there you are you
back at the battlefield or where are you
girls now I'm in I'm in Camp now okay
okay I'm talking to a lady I don't want
to rest I have one HP
we have one short rest left but maybe we
should just sleep we should just do a
long way we'll just do a long one oh
that
oh
ah gotta wait for the comments
oh oh this oh he's still here yeah huh
we just keep bringing his dead body with
us together
I guess so that we can one day bury him
which is very respectful exactly that's
what it's all about the respect
are we ending the day yeah just yeah
okay okay
all right
bonus burning hot someone in Camp still
wishes to speak to you go to bed anyway
yeah
Marissa if you want to speak to me just
speak to me
I mean I don't know who would want to
talk to me
I can't wait
[Music]
and now if you're too sad you can DM me
you know
every day I spend in your DMs yeah
all right good morning everybody okay
good morning good morning dead person
good morning you guys ready to go back
into The Fray
yeah let's go back into The Fray I
really hope he isn't still mad at him
well we'll find out won't we quick save
hopefully
fingers crossed shall we here
there's a lot of blood in here nice oh
yeah that's that's where I died
that's my blood
[Music]
it's bagel's blood right there for
whatever reason the the loot is done
being angry yeah is he is he done is it
safe now
hopefully
oh
yeah
who do I get to choose a subclass now I
wonder
I think subclass additional rage charge
nice
okay I get to choose a subclass gonna go
Berserker okay okay I will need to take
a moment to maybe look at the Spells do
what you gotta do oh yeah everybody okay
no more cleric I'm done being a clerican
yeah I think the one I wanted to do was
a college of lore oh
should I go for this one now good one
you guys wanted me to take this one
[Music]
um
yes okay
so is it even with animal enemies like
the work just now that I could speak
with
or just like random doubles and so on
yes also with the words
don't mind me I can now speak with
animals let's go
be helpful I take Shield or magical
magic mentally useful I gave you a one
magic Missile scroll so you could test
it out and see well not now obviously oh
or I'm taking orb nevermind I'm getting
an ore or
yeah
Thunder damage lightning damage okay
ignore okay
you're not do not the bear the subclass
was already the one I wanted to be I
think
eh
[Music]
that was what I already chose
I think beforehand yeah I remember that
um
[Music]
cast speak of animals but is there an
animals friends are strong
okay until long rest
so until we rest I can speak for any
animal are there any animals here I
haven't seen any of you
are you animal
s Chad I can use frenzy without using
rage first correct
Pals
hmm
let's do this
oh wait why do I have to press this
again
and can I speak with my own animals
frenzy replaces rage
I see
a better rage okay that makes sense
I'm taking this
following you Cali because it's my best
friend
sorry guys I walked into something oh oh
what let me listen wait what happened
what happened I don't I don't know
we in here oh I see you're in the hollow
I was gonna talk to the shopkeeper
anyway so
can I talk to
your crab
I'm not wait you also have to speak with
animals so yeah I'm uh I'm a gnome so no
one's can speak to the animals
maybe then I shouldn't have taken a peak
of animals
good
hello
I'm talking with a cow that's really
nice
uh I haven't done for someone
oh the cow didn't want to talk
let's freaking go
[Music]
I am going to bring in our sun
new good armor whoa that's sick you know
what actually all right narissa I stole
your Raven huh
you're Raven's mine
Savage
Raven likes me
can't help it uh you know I I understand
it because I like you too it is what it
is
[Music]
your bird cute you can talk to these uh
you can talk to these cows I'm doing it
right now
be gone I'm hungry eat my eat my Raven
Maybe
I know which one's good
oh my god oh yeah you're right I don't
need armor cause I'm a barbarian I Gotta
Get Naked okay bye I forgot oh God I
forgot uh
Callie can you do me a favor what's up
uh when you have time can you save and
reload the game I'm stuck in combat
music probably because of the whale
thing oh
you got it
no prob actually I'm gonna get one
what's wrong with this one really quick
hello
oh
what I just rolled a success
oh all right quick loads
[Music]
is a cow being mean to you oh I had to
quick load the game it's okay I should
have said something I am very sorry I
should have said I'm quick loading the
game
pardon me
pardon I'm sewing I'm Rose
I don't know what's happening
I'm like I've walked away with people
there are people like praying and they
were really mean they did not want to
let me in oh are you fighting them no no
one's fighting me I'm just talking to
people
oh good the music's back thank you no
problem
ah wait this one's good
come on give me a good roll
they're gonna eat you cow you better
tell me yes
Battlefield with blood not resist death
but Embrace good job
that's my job
I'm here oh hello it's a pig hello
oh
we're winning
the confidence ox
apparently animals in this game are
jerks
I believe it
this this this
um this pig wants a mate
[Laughter]
hello shadow
yeah that's the one I summoned I can
summon two Apparently one one word
familiar and another one
there are different choices I can have a
boar I can kick the Border excuse me
let's not kick the bird Eliza's
following me in this thing
fine I won't kick the bird we're down in
the Grove
I love these random animals following us
what'd you guys get down in there
they're kind of guarding the way I just
I just walked in they were like cool
all right
must have done something right
oh
[Music]
I still kick it don't don't hurt the
bird heart attack be nice for the birds
I think that the Druids won't like that
yeah it might get a little bit tiny key
though I'm gonna yoink this key from the
birds
the zucchini
no I'm just borrowing stuff thanks bird
foreign
[Laughter]
oh gosh
oh and beat that guy up you have started
a conflict
yeah oops
okay
yeah that sounds like a good idea maybe
we should just reload the saves really
fast they're starting an actual
hold on there's a little a slight
spoiler though which is why I'm confused
in the campaign there's a child that
steals it
oh yeah
well today it was me
huh
it was supposed to happen
I mean I can all happen regardless but
maybe maybe not it's just a difference
of who does it I think the child tried
to steal it and she failed
apparently it just tried okay we're back
to here
um let's try pumpkin
why are you trying to defeat the cow now
I fee failed before I before I didn't
finish my dice roll this time well I
already saw the oh yeah
I feel like I'm stuck in a Time Loop man
this is the first time I'm talking to
this cow
so why don't we actually uh doing in
here no I'm looking for someone looking
for the looking for the Healer we're
looking for Nettie
because of this you said she told me
where she is if you talk to
applicous over here
uh-huh
and the dragon they had Marching In the
real YOLO
hmm
Witnesses
oh
wow
but his Superstition oh
God
square square
oh I found I found another barn
Timber nice
yes
I'm talking to his Queen room
[Music]
what
I didn't do anything
oh
no
don't start the kick her huh
it must take then I am strong did you
stole from the bird
wow
[Laughter]
I killed the squirrel because I had
critical success he's kicking it
well that's chaotic
so what do we do didn't even have any
loot
oh my God I only we only have to kill
these two people okay
no it's only two you guys were fighting
I see five above me there's five five in
my battle
you can't steal things wait where are
they you can't steal things
you gotta tell me hey Maury I'm about to
do a really risky action save the game
so shall we reload another time okay
I know you you really were proud of your
critical squirrel hit
maybe you could do it in the next life
one more quick load okay well
then we lose the bear because we just
gotta play forward okay okay if I if I
lose I won't steal the key okay listen
it was the birds key why did humans get
mad at me for stealing the bird's teeth
I don't understand they love nature
they're Druids no yeah don't steal
anything don't steal you want to be
friends with these guys we can steal
from the Goblins okay
it seems like they're being kind of
corrupted they're being kind of like
racist for the thieflings and stuff you
know like they're they're yeah they're
bad yeah yeah so I think
um
you know yeah they need a bonk on the
head okay
I can tell you where Nettie is listen to
me she's in a room through the carved
door deeper in the Grove yep so that's
what she says
and I not touching the bird because I'm
scared okay I'm gonna talk to the bird
yeah again
oh my God I'm Gonna Save the game
oh thank God no it's okay I won't I
won't you like it if I fail
I'll I'll be good
and for the sake of plot I'll be good
yeah I know how you really want to play
it it's fine don't worry about it
okay I'm gonna add guidance
I'm gonna go find that barred lady again
she was cute okay it's good I beat the I
beat the roll there is no way you're not
just looking into a mirror
I mean cute fart lady I only know of one
so this is another tiefling she's
another tiefling Bard so I'm kind of
curious I wonder if she can join us
[Laughter]
okay save it so I don't have to kill
this bird all right ready okay
we're good now and
yeah I'm chilling by the stone door
what's going on here where we can find
the Healer inside there's so much lag
here wow hello there buddy husk oh stone
door yep right over here
once we go inside the healer is inside
okay I'm waiting
ready to enter
save the game
I saved the game
yes
all right into the stone door
shall we follow yeah sure that'd be cool
I got the cutscene
there's a small child here oh no
please
oh it's a snake
it's just a what
a poison heck of a threat
no wait I will impress like a dragon
snake and I will cast out every stranger
that's a child I do not
uh what is the girl's actual crime one
of your guards outside said you wanted
the scene here I am first
judgment
in thanks
Wrath
all right well that's a little messed up
I do have a moral compass devil
Tila is restless
ah she's so mean come cooker
back the idol surely do it
do it right um
let's go Mario pay mad all right I got
these added so let's go please work
let's go let's go
I can't see her roll
I got I got 20. it works okay
Let Her Go nice persuasion my Grace has
its limits thank you oh that was really
cool Mario
yeah the house is great I think you guys
will really like Houston
mm-hmm
um
here I'm not gonna open it of course
because that would be thievery
what a pretty dog lots of nice goodies
in here that I will not be taking
because we're friends
I'm a friend guys we lost I went to
Romeo Valley well what's up narissa
where are you guys oh we went into the
where you said Nettie was yeah I didn't
uh
I don't I don't know where that was okay
I'll leave and then you can see where my
icon is and then just go there yeah yeah
yeah yeah
okay all right let me know okay
all right I'm outside the follow where
my icon is
okay okay wait yeah I see it okay I can
get there you can go back in thank you
all right you're welcome I save game
every two seconds
yeah just take it a little bit better
because I accidentally steal the idol
again
oh did you find the Healer yes
oh
I'll start a conversation
she's healing a verb good woman oh just
give me okay
excuse me and more important than some
birds whoa rude is there anything I can
do to help
us
why the feathers like so weirdly what a
weird bird what was it you needed
um
need help now
[Music]
do you know anything about mind players
I've got plenty of them
I have a tadpole in my hand I
took a mind flayer type bone
I wish it was a frog tadpole
um I'll be kind of gross too though oh
yeah what other kinds are there it's not
like a frog hopped into my head
oh yeah help me
I'll do what I can come follow me but
there's four of us can you help all of
us please
let's go oh we need to follow follow
this way oh all of this stuff that she
has I can't pick up sad she'll get mad
at me
you should you should have expected to
be a thief
I really should huh
take a closer look
what was that oh
can look at him I stand on his butt
letter
they track the door and find whatever
bro he runs to and report back to me
remember you are only a scout do not
engage not kill anyone simply observe in
return I shall decide what we do next m
what who are you talking to I was
reading a letter on this person's body
I'm hoping for less grave cures so you
killed him and laid him on the table is
everyone being captured by minds and
didn't think it was a common experience
um
why is she not answering me
ignoring you given the other cold
shoulder
it's got a stick is pointy
at least that's what master has oh she
does have a stick what are you gonna do
with that
he hit me with a pointy end
still
we have I can use the amulet to speak
with him oh nice idea you don't have to
be here for this oh the bird does look
like Shadow let's see what we can do
right
oh God Jesus what are the cats doing
all right okay
I don't want to be so rude baby
of course I'll take anything no tell me
what's been happening oh baby I need
symptoms strange events
um
oh I have a bug
you see that right
I wonder if what I click is actually
though not what it seems to be
um I'll just victims okay okay not that
the others know they're victims of
course how'd you pick up the parasite
halson was desperate to find where all
this was happening
okay
um
should I go for the first one I think
that yeah I'd go for the first one no
yeah they're okay they're safe they're
just not just not been over but Master
Houston was sure
so I'll be straight with you
you're dangerous I'm dangerous
he's gonna poke us
yeah you deserve a chance to save
yourself
how did she pronounce it was it wyvern
or wyvern
why I would say why all right wyvern is
correct all right let's go
I swear to me you'll swallow it if you
feel any symptoms
I thought you could kill me what about
that branch of yours coated in a fatal
toxin
you're funny
you said I was gonna kill you but she's
very honest though saying that so I
think she likes us now at least she's
nice versus like the main lady outside
yeah
yes
[Music]
I hope it doesn't come to that but thank
you I mean
we can use it on people yeah
we'll be useful later I never once saw a
mind flare infection
suddenly there's dozens of you is she
Irish a lot of us Master Halston and I
were tracking a pick up a hint what is
all what the hell I like it
apparently we can kill shut up
the jerk lady which one that one that
set the whole Grove against his side I
don't know
I think we could I think we should kill
her
I mean I agree that she's well
identified
what do you mean it should be changing
uh
first
I yeah maybe maybe we get we get house
at first and then we can we can murder
her
yeah I mean I I love violence yes I
agree some days later we only have seven
days oh the thing in your school we need
to stop sleeping
it's already been
these right because we slept very nice
place right
it doesn't seem like we're turning into
his mind players
or maybe it might be more than seven
days
[Music]
um
hard to say but there's a lot they were
special infections of course we are I'm
converging on an old Temple of saloon we
have plot armor we're the main
characters
he saw a chance to get answers oh okay
let's go find him whatever he found okay
didn't make it back
um
get him
[Music]
um
but the place is rotten with goblins
it's okay we can kill the Goblins yeah
we got plenty of us yeah yeah
technically speaking I mean
discover what he learned and perhaps he
can save your life
okay how's that sound okay no they'll
find him thanks let's get him it would
mean everything to the
Grooms let me know what happened out
there
remember
hi
okay let's go let's go
save the game well four I accidentally
steal something hold on I'm sorry guys
just a moment my cats are batting
something around out there and I don't
want them
they might try to swallow so just a
moment
is this so should I you keep this
because it's single use is this like
yeah you want a new outfit
yeah help me seems like I could use a
keep it
drink it
I can call it a weapon with it yeah
amazing the syrian's armor too oh oh
yeah
apparently there's this room if we check
behind a book yes
all right real fun I don't know I took
it away from them we're good I don't
know how they found a little thing to
play with a new toy let's get out of
here
wait apparently there's a secret thing
apparently behind the book behind one of
the bookcases
but all the bookcases are red meaning
like yeah meaning if we touch them we'll
uh we'll get into college the game oh
wait I got perception what is the
perception for
open locks or maybe
read Stone top
[Music]
yeah there's there's apparently a chest
so it'll lead us to her room and there's
a solution oh
all right who finds it first
oh apparently this this door can open
but it's red
oh does it say locked or is it just you
can yeah it's locked and it's also red
ah
yeah maybe maybe if we go save we can
lose this stuff yeah maybe I'm gonna
tell you through anything not this room
negative five bagel
what I do I didn't even do it I didn't
even do anything at that time are you
yeah it's just randomly angry
I just readily making people angry
that's a bigger wolf
I'm sorry it's cute no one no one fought
me though so rats I want to talk to the
rat yeah the rats surely have a lot yeah
can I kick this one too did you find it
oh take on the servants course is that
what about you
boring I wanted to kill the rats
I can't I can't they won't let me
do anything a little cruel
I mean I think you probably can you
probably could kill the rat if you well
I know you press square
I don't think okay
are you oh you found it I don't know how
to get into it it's locked oh
maybe you could pickpocket the key oh
oh wait how did you guys get up there
walk around yeah you go from up here
I thought I picked up a thief kit
I mean if no one's here I see us too
um okay buy the hand fail
oh
yeah my sleight of hand uh only got six
oh I can roll
okay
nice
oh you succeeded
okay all right Luke Goblin it's up to
you I just want to see what's in it I
just want to see what's in it yeah same
yeah okay no one saw me so yeah that was
big yeah and they can't just sense that
it's on you right so we're fine yeah
yeah okay let's go let's go what did you
take what was inside uh let's see there
was a movie there was uh
yeah okay I'll read it okay
the Mars crisscrossing the page don't
look scribe so much a slash uh kaga
swamp dogs tree meet me alone olodan
okay I don't know where the swamp is oh
no Don wasn't that one of the rats oh oh
we got a quest though we got a quest for
it we knew Journal updates
well done all of that is one of the rats
hmm
okay
Brad talk to me
rat Whisperer
do we follow all done I don't know I
only heard the last word all of them
that's all I registered in my brain
laughs yeah I remembered one thing and
it was oh maybe it doesn't say anything
it's not actually a rat
maybe we can make him say something
cool
um
I'm beginning to feel like right
well done
oh let me talk to you again
yeah speak to the rat
now okay really doesn't want to talk
okay I guess we gotta go with a swamp or
something yeah I think yeah well let's
go okay
they read leader and they she's like get
them out ah yeah that's right get them
out yeah we could just like escort the
tifflings out of here but I think it's
great the book I have to read the book
he heard what happened to the squirrel
understandable
balance is a myth where any clowns trust
nature struggles Unity is a fiction men
of mere flesh seek only to tame beast
and raise Flora we are the Thunder and
we are the rain we shatter Mankind and
grow new life in its place okay it's a
mate
I'm looking at your outfit before I just
realized can you give me your cleric
outfit
oh can you wear heavy armor I don't know
I don't think you or can you wear medium
armor I just I just want I just want to
change out of what I'm wearing now here
I'll give you I'll get oh oops oh
I'll give you
a sirion's clothes here you go okay
I don't know where they'd go my items
perhaps yeah just checking your bag yeah
apparently oh my God
I thought I did too I don't think did I
need to pick them up I don't have it
wait who did I give it to
eh
I I give it to you right
yeah you have it a padded armor padded
arm okay okay yeah there you go I was in
the wrong I was in the wrong
uh
can I uh live for uh two minutes or one
minute
I'll I'll be right back you barely yeah
yeah yeah go for it
eat some chips too
Cali yeah you're in um underwear yeah uh
so the reason for that is because
um as like a bird as a barbarian I I
yeah it's better that you don't have uh
armor
oh okay are you sure about that is that
an actual thing I may have been this way
I may have been LED astray here
um they're basically they don't count as
armor okay your normal clothes don't
count as arm okay well I mean okay this
is bad I mean
it's not bad
we can well you have you have like a six
pack
yeah you know she she works out it's
almost an eight pack you know we'll get
it there though we'll get it
oh is that does that look better are you
happy in New Clothes nurse they look
good on you I think yeah yeah I feel
much more comfortable not in the ugly
default clothes
I could I could play a little ditty
they're not what I meant to do
you can have that Tyrone it's not it's
just the equipment armor you don't need
gotcha
well I can work with that hey nice tune
sick thank you I like it okay
what the
did you what was that what was there
she for a pot
do anything there was nothing in the pot
you could throw the pot
yeah
well I just wanted to show her God oh my
God
[Applause]
oh my God I'm not getting bad
away look at that D string mine are way
more decent than yours okay
isn't the top so cute like oh my God it
is but put some pants on please
that these panties are the ones that
that guy was wearing I doubt yeah yeah
maybe maybe not yeah
uh what why are you so scared this is
just the natural body of a natural
person my underwear is like Warriors
underwear you know firmly I like it
yours I'm gonna see what my underwear is
how do I take my clothes off
you look like you're about to go to
Coachella
the hair the Buns the colorful buns and
those clothes you look like you're ready
to go
play likes Coachella once
oh really correct oh that's actually
kind of cute that's kind of nice yeah oh
wow oh I heard you would look Bijou but
not at me okay
oh no I don't think it does unequip my
my instrument because
wait wait keep it on keep it on
look at those ladies
what is the stream turning into okay
we're supposed to go beat up goblins yes
um fanart please of me and Marissa and
this okay thank you and Cali too in
those Club yes I don't think they're
unfashionable
yeah protected yeah they're very strong
I need another vase to throw at you guys
okay how do we make progress where what
are we in yeah oh yeah we got distracted
no not at all very very distressed no no
no no okay
um now here's what we can do
would you guys watch the goblin Camp
yeah let's go yes all right follow me I
really want to see the idol again you
know
okay wait let's save let's save let's
save and test our power level what's
going on here right okay
get get close so we can all be better
together what what are you why no why
wait wait wait wait I want to talk to
Polo okay wait okay tell us when you're
done okay
I I won't grab it I won't grab it until
you guys say you're ready
just want to see if we can take take the
idol you know all righty wait can you
hide
widespread
oh
I succeeded in history let's go
unbelievable
um
yeah no they're they're questioning
they're like why are you sneaking around
you're watching
this is a legend
he's a legend
oh
I'm gonna throw this oh I have an idea
okay
are we ready to do this ready I saved
again no no okay hold on yeah we need to
wait for kiwama to be ready uh
he's a lore important NPC legendary
figure in DND
okay uh
there was no drunk room how do I how do
I play my songs for some reason I only
have the option to do bartic inspiration
and I don't want that I want to do my
actual song playing is there no like
regular I I think I broke performance
because I don't remember how to get to
my regular performance
hey comment check the absolutely what
does that mean this is a little like at
the bottom part okay yes I found it I
found it you're so smart thank you so
much okay take the performance check
playing as a bar the NPCs will come
watch you play your instrument and then
biboo can pickpocket them from behind
it's pretty cool oh yeah for the future
I think they're big people will leave
yeah just for the future might be kind
of oh someone's here
maybe don't pickpocket him maybe maybe
everyone can see
okay here let me see if we can distract
these people
maybe probably not but
we'll just see I'll Stand between these
ones
okay I think they're busy I think so too
but just yeah just we're just doing like
their blessing you know
I can't wait to see yeah but I'm a bard
um
[Music]
don't ignore me
oh the boy likes it oh
[Music]
yeah so adorable look at him look at him
dancing he's taking his little butt cute
pocket that is so adorable
I'm done okay save are we actually
trying this okay why not okay
come here and I'm gonna do something
okay okay what are you gonna do
okay
okay go get it there's a flower Cloud go
get it
huh
nice
okay
I mean they were blessing it like two
seconds
move The Outsiders
well
you gotta watch this guy get beat up
again yeah yeah let's just go get bashed
in it was freezing pretty sick
oh yikes you know that man
oh yeah that's gotta be painful
ow
but like feeling it wasn't it was his
fault
they're just leaving the tieflings for a
lot of things apparently I don't
understand
[Music]
so are we battling why are we running
battling of course we have to fight
something right did you just shoot a
bear
the poor Bear yeah tough it
okay he's gonna try to kill us
[Laughter]
we're gonna fight so many people
yeah I don't know man I I don't think
there's a way to win
we could always just reload again too if
you guys really don't know I guess yeah
then since our since our plan to steal
the idol didn't work with the with the
smoke cloud
what was that yeah I don't think you can
steal the Idol without getting everybody
upset sadly
oh
attack a creatures eyes and blinded
about the Bears
yeah well we can't
we can't kill the bear
what's happened good job shadow oh you
love me Kylie's still naked yeah
bro
I feel like a photo
nice
bro bonus action I already used it knife
fly somewhere safer
no probably not
game
hope that's cool I'll throw them
apparently they kill all the tieflings
when you do this so even if you beat it
oh yeah it's a little messed up I got
silence
I have a good idea if you guys want to
kill a bunch of stuff we can go to the
goblin Temple because they're yeah
I was trying to win a battle we are
going to lose against the Bears did I
drop my ax
a voice of reasons
I I remember where the goblin Camp is by
the way
make our way up there yeah I remember
nice I follow I have only ever gotten as
far as the goblin Camp past that I do
not know what happens
okay let's see so let's we gotta exit
the town first I'm following you yeah
just follow follow Mario Pez lead
get Cali's butt while she's walking up
the stairs let's go let's go oh yeah
there's a shopkeeper by the way if you
guys want to buy items like healing
potions Etc wait which one which one the
Amic up here uh past these cows there's
uh a merchant
does he have ice arrows selling stuff
here
oh maybe I think I saw ice arrows really
I'm pretty sure that I saw some in the
inventory but you might want to yeah
grab some stuff really quick
oh from my dude over here uh what are
you selling
oh
he does have ice Arrows by the way
I think there's another bye well
can I sell all these weapons uh guys I'm
sorry yes what I'm stuck oh wait no I
got out I got out it's fine it's fine oh
one at a time yum one at a time that's
too realistic I know this way I'm just
gonna open up this part of my map I can
actually we can fast travel there and go
there instead let me know yeah when you
guys are done shopping okay I'm just
selling stuff okay
oh money
how do I get him to give me money oh
give me money
give me all your money
oh oh he refuses my offer I think
you can do that please
I won't leave them behind we're going to
get us killed he's right
definitely has a frost Arrow I think
can I okay it's a good idea
make use of your services please yes
where is Will okay only one person talk
to him at this
doesn't will normally appear around here
you guys
uh doesn't he like show up and he's like
hey and he's like teaching the the
teacher yeah is he gone he's not here
he's gone
it's all very bad
surely we'll run into him again we
didn't kill him guys if we don't have
will can we not find Carla
wait I don't know who that is but I'm
down to find whoever oh no no no you
don't need vote for Carla okay I don't
think about your preciousness
yeah no you just care about your stupid
apprenticeship
um
do I need any of this I wonder if these
were I wonder if he's where like he
killed me
mmm
Vengeance first
should we go look I'm gonna go check
around where I died
yeah I really hope he doesn't agree on
me if he's there though
we just need to have a chat with him
yeah
oh if you go to Carlock first he will
find you apparently oh okay
so we could we could go find her yeah
what's bartering I kind of
oh yeah he is there oh I'm scared I'm
scared maybe just go talking to him
maybe yeah say the game say the game
first hello
hello are you okay
hold on I wait I have no money oh I
can't even click on him yeah I can't
interact how do I have no single money
how is that possible
I got gold
but didn't I did I I feel like I picked
up money before
you remember opening like a chest and
having gold yeah several I mean I
thought it was gold
oh well I'll sell things gotta loot more
yeah mostly yeah pick up stuff
I dug that up that was my treasure thank
you I'm never helping you again
yeah I'll give you I'll give you some of
the loot you wanna uh
someone special yeah I'll give you
something
how much gold is it money is shared in
the party it looks like it is it
was on zero okay did people use up all
the groups money oh I didn't I didn't
buy anything yeah
anything
well it was definitely on zero and now I
I made some money but
um
apparently so
we can but we don't have she has to send
it to you
party gold is 329. aha nice I guess
technically we can use each other's
money yeah I mean if you guys need some
gold I'll give you some gold we have a
shared bank account okay right now I
could just take y'all stuff
but I could is the thing
I get it I'll buy it so next time I see
oil no I can make it go boom
I can I will I will punt you so far over
the mountain if you steal something else
[Laughter]
it doesn't do anything huh
anything else that's worth buying here
can we stop shouting it'd be calm and
drop sparkly really
okay
oh yeah they have an amulet I gotta talk
to that I totally forgot about it yeah
I'll talk to him later
okay I want to look and see if I can buy
anything
uh uh yes uh green green gold rainbow
sorry I'm blind uh uh
there's a great great I'm blind I'm so
blind
um
[Laughter]
this swing okay okay that's that's okay
cool insufficient gold
oh that's expensive I'm not reaching
that money uh
yeah
yeah maybe another time
calm down
behind I wonder if she'll notice
maybe you never time hey what did you do
what are you doing here
I did something good go check
yeah what'd you do is this to stuff look
in your inventory
and I don't know what's different
look at Cali's inventory I see gold
I don't know how to even look at other
people's Instagram
press tab I love this it's just mine
okay
do you not do you not see my message
is there a message
[Music]
oh it's not reflected oh man man too bad
I spelled something for you in your
inventory but I guess it doesn't uh
oh that is high yeah
yeah I don't care about your stupid
apprenticeship why are you fighting I'm
gonna take your word for it
Hi Well Kiara
that's very strange yeah I mean it's not
like she she just placed the items in an
order that makes it look like a letter
Kelly's playing on Console oh no I'm
using a controller but oh it's different
with a controller oh I'm I'm ready okay
we got some goblins to kill let's gobble
those goblins up gobble gobble
why not they're huge they're
terrifying nothing could body you boo
I'm sure all of you have seen a turkey
for Thanksgiving I love it
cakes they make me feel so powerful when
I eat one you know I have some big ones
that used to live near the old my old
place
I remember seeing some cross the road
once and I was like holy
oh my God
before we go to the goblin place
make a little detour I remembered
something okay
there's it's combat though okay
let me save and we gotta go ah already
saved okay let's go we gotta go this way
oh we gotta see the dog too hold on yeah
the doggy the dog the dog's over here
what was his name where are we here
before no really but I see dead bodies
yeah we were just acknowledging them
we're like just dead
[Music]
wait wait don't don't loot the body
accidentally okay stranger
you just hear the sound
so uncanny
crazy
I can make it I can make it yeah
I believe in Bible power
there's death in your scent yeah
my friend is injured I think your friend
is dead
to him
he's with his God now I'm sorry he'll
wake up
oh he will and then we'll return we have
a Revival scroll
Revival I have a skeleton that can help
here here come with us come with us I
won't leave him oh he's hot and cool is
he hot Chico
his name is scratch
[Music]
um here
follow my son
atiku never leaves the side office
okay now now he may show up cool
okay another detour we are going over
here there's combat it's the combat
detour all right let's do it
I'm ready to fight
always ready
me too me too I want more fights um
spend too much time in that City yeah
yeah it's okay soon and then we got this
yeah um
I need you to kill the mom and not kill
the child oh I remember this oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah kill them kill
the mom but not not the kid hell of cash
okay
yeah don't kill me don't want to kill a
mother well she wants to eat us oh okay
yeah that's that's okay she's really
mean
yeah this paint maybe you guys should
wait for me me and Wawa oh yeah yeah
yeah the minute not enter without
so we're not like spread out super far I
love the little animal family
a girl I'm hiding
I'm hiding yeah okay let's go oh
okay Wawa you can talk to her actually
because you can talk to animals
uh okay have a little chat uh how do I
talk without uh killing Oh no just walk
up to her oh okay okay oh it's never
said though
I didn't mean to
oh you have animal handling
well time to get eaten it'll be fine
so lunch time yum yum yum yum
is the obvious so pretty Out For Blood
how bear
I thought
oh we have to call it I know
oh nice striking while the iron is hot I
guess
up in the air like she just don't care
oh is that awesome
you just ascended
[Laughter]
oh oh
um
can't go so far so go as far as you can
oh fly to Target position
um
I wonder if I could throw you a bird go
Shadow you probably could you have
enough strength for it
don't forget about it baby
[Music]
okay
don't worry
um
on my way a baby is coming to defend his
mommy
um this is a bonus eye and then I can
also do a race attack
[Music]
oh
I feel like you're scarier with
underwear on intimidating
she's cute here goes nothing
oh let him bleed
mama mama
oh oh
god really angry
oh The Voice came out of it
who killed the baby still alive
I don't know but the baby's still okay
okay good crap crap
or something
crab crab no crab attack crab cannot
attack crap oh maiming pinch I'm like
one step too far away
uh
well crap Maybe
maybe act as a bait
that meant that would have been so epic
if the crab would have gotten the kills
dead mother
[Music]
and now I now listen to the
baby yeah someone who can talk to
animals preferably where where's the
baby where is it
yeah let's save let's save real quick
before one of us accidentally kills it
don't um don't act
supplies by the way okay
strike will end his suffering don't do
it
let it live okay come back and kill us
someday it's gonna eat the mommy is
Ageless because the Cub begins
[Music]
why do we have to leave him here oh we
will we will find
and again later yeah he'll come back to
kill us because we killed his mom no no
we we we'll take him as a pet oh so
there's a shark back here isn't there
yeah yeah we can't do anything with it
because it's sealed by Magic
I want to go look I remember correctly
I see a chest yeah it's sealed by Magic
so if you try and open it
yeah
I think me and uh oh yeah now also
Bieber we might wanna you know heal
no problem
oh we already did one
so when you try to open the chest is
that when you got damaged yeah
oh really does that happen to everybody
who touches their chest yeah I think so
I want to touch it I know
they're dedicated to Saloon imploring
all to accept the moon maiden's blessing
and sharing her Bounty just an old
prayer I like her no religion failed
yeah
wait I think I have religion there's a
prayer behind the statue
how do you jump again
it's one of the actions on the
um the second one in the first row okay
right I'm gonna give you a check over
here I took I picked it up I'm gonna
send the prayer to one of you guys to
use it because I could not do it so who
has good religion
so proud
did you get stuff oh
what necklace Bloodstone Idol pendant
okay now we can go kill some goblins
cool okay they were all right goblins
goblin killing time
yeah go mm-hmm
you don't have to pass the check if you
just know what to do and there's Clarity
wow
pretty nice
that's true just an old prayer a dummy
well I mean I'm not smart I might be
dumb I'm not stupid it's okay
do we have who's the smartest one in the
in the party again me in terms of um
James stats
okay
up there is Goblin yep up here across oh
wait yeah that's right across the bridge
and then we go that way yeah I will wait
yeah I'm trying to catch up
um any charismatic people want to lead
the way oh oh yeah I'm charismatic hello
we're both charismatic
yeah you guys can you know take the
charge
oh wait wait there's no one here
look what why did they get mad I don't
know so they didn't even give you a
chance to anyone
oh they're all tired yeah
ow
I am here now I did not have to fight
this so I'm not sure how this will work
we'll figure it out who are we fighting
now get him here and help us goblins not
goblins goblins okay well we want to
fight those let's go
um where are the memories
yeah huh or the house right next to us
yum what what
um
Alex really don't see them
okay we'll see where I am
go to the left
and in the middle of that roof
ah and then there's also one at the end
if you go down just downward
with the arrow
okay well we want to come back here we
are
I guess
oh well okay
guess I can't do anything
ah let's go bird let's go
through the front door
can I not
what what does that mean not enough
resources okay oh it means you are used
in action or something yeah
oh there's another guy
oh
can I get some from oh can I get them 65
percent
[Music]
um
let's go
it might have been a mistake
yeah that's all right I couldn't handle
those guys we'll handle these other ones
[Music]
thank you
oh you missed
[Music]
um
yeah
why why twice
because they got good songs
I'll be fine I know what to do with them
there's one on the other side but um and
there's one inside the house
oh that was good too
none you really couldn't take me talking
to him like that yeah I love your
insults insult me please I could never
you're perfect
[Music]
don't die
I'm on fire
um we can get them let me get a bit
closer
[Music]
oh nice nice
okay
take him down take him down
all right
go burp go
no why not rip go here
oh
burp getting closer
okay
if this this person has a ball right so
that means they won't attack me if I
move behind them right I'm not strong
okay okay
building below
here we go don't miss
it yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
beautiful that's so good
and I feel myself
a couple left I think two goblins left
now that we got the Waypoint we can
return to Camp as well if you guys want
yeah
okay
he's wow your words are very strong my
words are hurtful
it's my job demon of words not soup or
song
oh no I said if you go too far into the
village you'll aggro more people oh okay
I'll stop moving in I thought I needed
to get by the Waypoint to unlock it
yes
nice okay there's one in the house and
then one by narissa oh there's one in
that there's one by me I have that yeah
there's one right in front of you
um me
oh yeah inside the home
almost forgot about that
I'll fight you fast
that's all right I can survive this
you got it
oh
are you okay okay I have one HP okay how
do I
how do I get this person
can I like shoot it from the
oh holy guys he only had free HP
that's why I didn't do it I'll do it on
the next Target
hmm
Cali only one HP what the yeah
that's okay I'm good don't worry about
it it's not okay I'm good
you're bleeding because I've been taking
damage I guess it's the adrenaline
oh well I'll find out I'll just chewed
him from the window yeah
oh
I'll show it I don't know where the
other oh there's one in there
excuse me
so you can get XP for her
um
we're literally about to go rest at the
camp
so I'll just chill here
you guys might need some help though
sorry
maybe I will pop up
bum
take the shot get them
oh
nice all right
and I wanted to check out these bodies
oh maybe I should have moved a bit
further out of me oh
go shadow
let's go try Shadow good try
okay
I have endless responsive this is nice
oh we're done we go to the camp Camp
yeah all right we've got this uh already
all right so let's let's go back to I'll
take us back to the camp go to Camp yes
and let's give us a ride
oh I think you guys got a return on your
own
oh
uh so it's in the scroll wheel at the
same one where you like go to your
inventory and stuff
look at that
dlss what DLS
I'm Gonna Save really quick
victory
just chilling with one HP at the camp
all good I'm just hanging
living my best life okay
okay
let's all take a little nap I'll wait go
to bed come on the camp wishes to speak
to you oh I want to speak to us they
always keep wanting to talk to us why
are there too well no wheels
yes why is there two of them
yeah
and Kale's twin I talked
what is going on
what
same cook I don't know what's going on
but I'm into it
what's he gonna do with himself
make an army out of himself
oh Shadow heart wants to talk to me
really
oh no I gotta talk to Shadow heart
something's wrong no are you hurting
I'll protect you always Shadow heart
oh Gail where are you doing here this
has nothing to do with you brother
Let Him Live oh oopsies I failed stop oh
yeah he's like right behind you
you made her mad how deep is this
inventory you can talk to her separately
can't you
arrange it
did I aggro her forever
no she's she's fine we should get to
know each other a little more yeah
make her like you
can see it
um
zero is
fresh you
somebody said don't don't put the silver
and open oh I think I'm raising her up
maybe I'd like to get to know you better
what if I do
hold on I kind of want to watch this
what happened to you I have to go what
happened to a stereo I'll show you wait
uh wow whatever she's wearing is very
sexy okay
for now I'll leave her B for now I won't
press how do I oh see because that even
work she approved of me okay hold on
nice you're getting it it's you I'm I'm
doing it I'm doing it
um thank you
there's no story
none that you're entitled to hear okay
I'll I'll talk to her again later when
when we have more time to buy yeah I
don't think she wants to talk to me she
doesn't want to be interrogated right
now so leave him alone forever space you
know yeah gotta give her a space
all right ready for sleepies mine
yeah
yes sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep
sleep
Supply pack we're gonna need to steal
more of these from the Goblins yeah
saving her ribs for the real prize you
caught me
what's up
oh
who's a good doggy
[Music]
so cute that's so sad catch all right
oh he can talk to me
um how about your master
friend
oh
[Music]
baby Master
for pets pets you can pet the dog 10 out
of 10 games you can pet the dog
I mean you're small enough you could use
the the dog's speed right into Batman
yeah I can ride the dog
everyone approves when you pet the dog
pet him again
more pets
hey stop that
I wonder
maybe not you know over stimulating can
I keep petting him
we get tired that's nice oh I can only
leave now
um
well he liked it yeah
okay
shall we save now that we're all full
health yeah good idea good game
um
goblins
crab all right I'm in another another
crab
how about this whoa oh
that's so cool that's a big one I didn't
expect it to be so big I did wasn't
expecting a spider
that's a big body no it's just another
crab look they look so similar
same amount of of legs and hands right
yeah
just green green crabs are just sea bugs
see spiders yeah yeah you know you've
got a good point
an armored spider
aren't shrimps the Cockroaches of the
sea or is that crabs
and it's definitely not crabs excuse me
yeah no I didn't I didn't mean it I
didn't mean it I didn't mean it I'm
sorry crap
crabs are cute they couldn't be
cockroaches of the sea
at it again
oh yeah play music for me
throw something at you again I like them
oh the NPCs like it
oh
they came over everybody's into it it's
like a big party now look see everybody
likes me
amazing everyone's gathering around
thank you
and why
I thought Advent was like really
friendly with each other
it's always going
oh my God
I guess we're gonna sleep one more time
because y'all are injured uh no we can
just slow we can just we can do short
rest
I'm learning to save
Joy me again be looking the same don't
make me shoot you with my lightning
Dylan
you you're with me first it was a
lifetime it literally did one damage
after we just healed down and down down
by the river
[Music]
[Laughter]
all right what do we want to do you guys
okay fine
but like actual enemies wait did we end
the date we did okay yeah yeah how do we
leave the camp so I'll leave well you go
first uh it's the scroll wheel where I
don't know how it is for PC um
like the bonfire again
ah okay um all right we're in the
blighted village which okay this is
close to where we're supposed to go
follow me and we'll I know where the
camp is from here oh wait
I press the I pressed the uh the the bed
right no no no no no no no fire so go to
the scroll wheel
um where like you have like level up
inventory Etc click the bonfire again
wait I can't click anything right now
it's waiting for other players oh yeah
cancel can somebody cancel this oh you
just have to wait till the timer runs
out oh okay yeah
sorry
[Music]
leave Camp okay gosh I'm so hungry
all right okay these guys I recommend
not really messing with the blighted
village right now
we gotta cross this bridge over here
[Music]
it might be
I'm gonna cross this bridge I believe
okay well let's cross it okay Crossing
is there a reason you're letting me go
first
waiting for Wawa there's a there's a
there's like ogres in in here yep yeah I
don't think we can take them
yeah they're really strong and there's
three of them but don't worry they
haven't noticed no yeah
let's just they're just going keep going
so what's with the leg
are you sure we can't kill them
maybe keep going for now maybe later
okay come back later yeah when we're
really strong we can beat them up
beehive
hi honey
now if you have high enough Rays you can
persuade them that you're cool
okay I have race hello I have oh good
you saved it okay hello hi
just boxing casually people go alone
first yeah
can you convince there's like poop on
the ground yeah
what did you just call me
okay we don't need to hire those big
ogres we can yeah
I feel like that was a mistake do I have
[Music]
perception
oh I have deception okay let me add
guidance oh give it a go it's like yeah
oh I made it I made it nice yeah yeah
nice nice
days hey what's that supposed to mean
that's kind of rude now you're one of us
across the mug
how did we get here
absolutely do it do it do it or you
follow them dead
all right
um let me see is there one close by I'll
just Dash into battle
and the lag
o let me do the rising next time what so
you were gonna put poop on your face yes
why would you need to when you could
just kill them
we need to make good relations so we
don't have to fight so much why not
yeah oh ah
[Music]
um
fly as far as you can
and speed down
you can speed up also Dash okay
there is a large dark monster up here
that is very frightening
um
dark monster
I don't know what it is it's like a
pitch black spooky thing it took some
damage already
oh
oh there is one monster behind us indeed
you're spooking me different one
okay well sharp-eyed nerd what a name
probably spider
um
the icon didn't load at all no it's
definitely there I see it it's very dark
um
pitch black portraits are from my cat
hello goodbye
goodbye
classic
come over here
thank you for taking that damage for us
wow
that's a good thing
yeah
please and damage good good good
okay
yeah oh
oh that really sucks
no yeah we're not we are not thriving
I had some better accuracy
oh can I talk to the work
even in the middle of a battle
hey oh oh no
one for the alarm
Knock Em Dead
what's the matter no the one that is
behind us
oh bird is gone too
okay Shadow is dead there is a no bird
for you anymore
what would you like to have next
I can bring you almost any animal food
not kitty cat because I just don't want
to see how that ends ever again
anything else
I feel you
see
[Music]
ah are you gonna kill him yeah okay
I was about to say Jesus
[Music]
get him
I'm gonna get him
that's my girl
nice
it's my little one over there okay I
probably should have walked outside to
walk around
wow
very careful of the daggers
it's fine and the water uh the water is
electrocuted
huh
dad uses non-lethors I don't know it's
not why is it not toggled why does it
say non-lethal damage I don't understand
I can't I can't take it off
I have that too
I think no I guess if it's grayed out I
don't have it
is grayed out for you oh
my God there we go it's fine I don't
know why it was Revenge me avenge my
desk please
oh
God mediocre loose
and then I think I can actually I can
bring you back
nice well because I got an extra turn
I'll try and be like kind of bait I
guess this guy hopefully targets me
instead of you
got anything nice on you
and taking a shot
okay we just got that one left nice yeah
always going
oh I got you you try to run don't let
him leave
or
oh
yeah holding back this whole time I
can't believe it has been electrocuted
nice team
is that it I think that's it
need a short rest I'm worried about
narissa maybe
okay I gotta be get that short rest real
quick and I'll save the game
yes
come on
he's popping off over here I need to
bring my babies back I didn't go up
there what do these guys do
people scared you go I mean like a style
what what's happening
I don't know the goblin the temple is
over there the Temple of Love okay is
over there but then there's these guys
what are they
radical
you're probably gonna want to fight yeah
it's too big but the rats are too small
simple time
I'll quickly change some graphic
settings oh yeah what happened oh sorry
whoa uh brain worms
oh
control yourself
Temple of Silver Saloon
the Temple of the Loon
whatever it is it's irresistible
Shadow Escape
can she speak up I can barely hear her
louder
why can't we see them young woman
with even pain
oh yeah
[Music]
the weapons
come back stove
[Music]
actually let me turn it up elsewhere
what is happening
oh it's the tesseract
let's go bring me to the underworld
the needles in my face go
wow
I raised volume
um
oh of course those visions
uh put the artifact away
put it away
put it in the old pocket okay uh this is
another situation where I really think
you guys should go I'll stay close by in
case it turns into a battle and I need
to tank but I think in terms of Charisma
wait wait it's The
uh
oh he's performing for them
or even more lags challenge him to a rap
battle
back
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's go let's let's go guys outshine
that big silly
Street they all came over when it was me
I'm gonna crank a brand new move
it's so cute backup dancer
thank you to move uh
okay shall we move on yeah yes I mean
you've really captivated them I don't
know man
I know I'm distracting them wait I found
out
oh yeah
I'll bear cubs you remember turn this
off again I think it was better before
Oh yes
wait I want I want I want out there
[Music]
used to
how do I get out of there
roasted dwarf leg
oh good eating oh what did I miss anyone
play the game
[Music]
Lauren before we go into the temple
wait can you can you talk to the people
about the owl bears give them a chat
games okay
they're only talking about volunteers
chicken
it's so cute oh chicken chasing sounds
fun Count Me In
respects mates are they gonna burn him
is this like a steak
oh I hope not uh we gotta get rid of
Volo first if you want to do this I
found a waypoint
I want to talk to the out there okay we
gotta get rid of Volo then okay
do you mean kill no uh
in
come on to us dialogue is moving pretty
quick
Goblin Kind
reduce them to cowering yes
sir not a whole doll let's go
yeah very cool tell it how it is wow
okay can you leave now
damn those rhymes
amazing
oh come on I'm just telling you how it
is
boo you stinks
I'm busy here you lying uh oh he's gonna
fail the deception check she's so
British
why is he here
[Music]
um
sorry all right
sorry guys I tapped out uh you're crazy
nice chicken chasing time
good night
no tomatoes in the chat for Volo
no extraction time
well chat I don't know if it's normal
but it's taking up 38 49 of my CPU and
7500 of my Ram I don't know if that's
normal
at least a bet
that's fine
I saw it too it wasn't always this bad
but now it's fine wait
wait where's the bear going wait
running
what's he doing oh wait how did that owl
bear cub even come here
was it already here before
oh no
the requirements are responsible for
your pain kill them yeah persuade them
let's do it yeah yeah
okay oh I can't use both okay I'll use
guidance okay yeah
yeah come on oh sick baby very angry
uh-oh hey we're not involved in that
battle right
I think I think it was a Straight Arrow
the hitch you might want to get out of
the way
our baby gonna die
[Music]
well there's gonna be a better way to
save him
[Music]
later apparently but yeah then we'd have
to bring him back to life
yeah
this little guy
I don't know how long ago we we had to
save yeah I don't either
yeah
weren't we supposed to get something
super cool for leaving the mom alive
we're leaving the Baby Alive take the
egg yeah but yeah that's what I mean I
guess right
um
yeah sure are you sure we didn't save
recently
hold on a second I'll I'll give it I'll
check it I'll check it out alrighty
let's see uh
last save
a load game
um
have to do the Volo thing again but
that's fine
should be okay space bar through it
oh bear safe scum I mean yak
I mean yeah well we'll definitely tone
it down as we get more of you know the
game some people are saying you could
group them with a performance and then
use all the AOE attacks on them
oh nice that's huge yeah that's a good
idea it's actually really awesome
but so should we throw a ton of goblin
spur or yeah because they're not
fighting us I really don't want them
yeah you really don't need to I don't
think we should enter the temple
yeah okay
Albert is worth keeping around chat says
by the way
um I guess we can kind of skip this part
because we've already seen it yeah
put it away all right cool
nice
let's Jump Right In
I'm gonna Boo this guy off the stage
real quick okay
do we have we do we have the wyvern
poison remember
tub
I'm down to try
uh but we should save before we do this
guy first get off on stage
where's their beard okay I found it I
found it it's right here I see it okay I
just need the poison because I don't
have it um I think
[Music]
um
I'm right here
crab looks so cute so what do you do
uh just poison you gotta put put it in
the the Boost tub how do you put it in
I I'm not sure but there's a ton of
goblins around so maybe what if you did
a performance over around this oh yeah
do performance do a performance
[Music]
won't even chase a baby we
wait another one's coming over so
oh
no wait there's a guy right behind you
guys yeah one is watching you directly
Paddy likes it I didn't do I didn't do
anything he's got a sharp eye
yeah it's a good thing
yeah it's an extra delicious it makes it
makes it tastier she's talking to them
myself yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay he's happy with it now uh
okay are you distracting people
I'm not paying attention
let me let me try a different song
[Music]
why is he watching you like that
I mean
maybe you guys why don't you walk away
from it for a minute and see if they
don't maybe you know walk away and then
you can try yeah nice idea what is this
still watching me
yeah is he he's like the potion guy
looking at it it's like Fire Emblem
oh he ran away
hard to be The Bard
still just a babe
yeah yeah
okay I'll walk all the way over here
don't even think I'm over here
they're they're taking some booze
they keep seeing me yeah there is
there's a guy okay guys over there yeah
oh now he's gone oh my crab made it up
but not the wolf okay what if I oh wait
this guy's leaving this guy's leaving
this guy's ah hiding successes okay did
you get it no there's so many people
you're really thirsty
cool
[Music]
oh I think you can
does this mean that they're not seeing
anything that's in here
okay it's poison it's poison now okay
okay it wasn't even in the red before
huh what's happening
ah no thanks
what's happening
um
oh are you guys seeing what happened how
come I didn't get a cutscene
um
okay well may I bet each and every one
of you before the sunset that's crazy
tell me what happened okay
[Laughter]
drink up I'm like uh
do the bartending drink oh cool I I'm
stuck see how this goes
why do I have two cutscene yeah it's
okay
you make them drink it I trust you
yeah
surely it was a success
yeah no
do your trick
I want to see it too that it's a banger
they go I see him I see him oh wow
drunk it up
a drink
[Applause]
what are you talking about I literally
just like danced I did a jerky dance
over there I did the stanky leg that's
literally all I did
I should have your arms ripped off
please please work because I need to
roll a 20.
good luck
let's go nuts
it's fine I'll take critical success
so many of them are still alive yeah oh
wait is bear okay now there's only
there's no better I should save the game
yeah same
time to save
that was gangster
um
nice okay save him
he runs away oh only time
[Music]
oh we'll definitely see you again now
yeah now we save okay
yeah we'll see what awaits Us in here
yeah I'm quick oh my God okay get out of
this leggy area
it's a lot smoother inside the temple
okay
hi guys hello hey get away
it's a big idea
business oh what's your business guys
a great question you should figure out a
story
but our story straight
hmm
I've got an audience with the one to
charge into it you have good deception I
think yeah
a master deception
oof oh it's okay you still got it you
got it you got it you got the you got
the boys yeah yeah yeah I've got skills
some
right
well
you ain't the first foreign type I
suppose us gonna have to be a bit more
specific though mate
absolute's got a few favorites around
there oh oh
audience is right she said nothing no
mistake but she knows her business she's
in telling the WarChiefs what's wrong oh
next ride is gonna be a bigger game oh
yeah
yeah the journey began and it's only
going to get crazier we'll tackle the
goblin Temple next time
no problem it'll be fun
um yes I'm hyped to see where our
journey takes us from here on out
yeah that was fun um oh I'm also kind of
playing on my own as well at the same
time with a different character so so
maybe next time you'll see some improved
gameplay I don't know
I think you did pretty good today though
yeah I'm learning the Barbarian ways you
know and I mean look at this master
putting it down
he's after my own heart
you never put those clothes back on
confident lady you know it better
Shredder stuff
um so yeah everybody take care hope you
guys have a lovely day wherever you are
please hope you guys
you guys are uh doing well and have a
lovely day yeah yeah are you all ending
the stream uh I'm gonna talk for just a
little bit and then end so yeah I'm
gonna I'm Gonna Leave the call here
bye bye bye
[Music]
yeah bye bye and peace
if you wish
[Music]
they're all set
yeah
[Music]