[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
okay yeah abc okay what does that first
name alphabet
hello everybody um amelia watson hello
live and number one detective at your
service
[Music]
you don't use that so often do you yeah
i thought is that amazing
i like it i thought it was new
yeah
[Music]
howdy i'm next hello this is claymore
from whole live english what's up
shitsureshimasukashinde
go all that good [\h__\h] hi nice to see you
guys welcome
i am recovering i was i was a bit uh
under the very under the weather
yesterday i'm doing a bit better today
though and very excited to play with
some ladies yay anticipating whoo
yay
who knows who is that
happening no
soon my name is
i'm on black garden phone i draw with a
mouse
same as your mouse
but you're good with your mouse drawings
so
i don't want to train
with a tablet believe it or not
i find that hard to believe oh no i
really understand that yeah i really
i really feel like i'm not used to it
then yeah
wow
where did you get them from um
oh macdonald
[Music]
[Laughter]
for introduction iris maybe it could
also be inaudible according to
discord is
oh okay okay discord um
hi
it's iris i am
i am the
somewhat new um
hawaiian project hope v singer they made
it uh last month yeah for those who
don't know me hi rice
uh i'm very excited this is my first
time collabing with almighty and
senpai's stop laughing
[Laughter]
how confident are you in your drawing
skills
ah
ah yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm i'm just as
good as dina seems to be a mystery
yeah i haven't i haven't drawn yet
actually but i've i've been telling
people my streams that yeah i'm i'm
godly at drawing but that that's just
that's just me um you know put giving
putting a really um strong face in front
of them i want to tell you guys the
truth no uh
oh i i i draw with mouse i mean i do
have a tablet too but like girls and pie
i can't i can't draw with the tablets oh
really i'm using the mouse
expect awesome art yes okay
looking forward to your masterpieces
yeah masterpieces
[Laughter]
are we gonna like when we play it we'll
mute everyone else like uh it kind of
been among us oh
that's a good idea
i think
but since it's like the first uh holo
full halloween collab since iris jordan
i think for the sake of having
conversations we should not mute
sometimes we don't like give away what
we're writing
yeah yeah exactly yeah
all right ina introduction
wow hello i'm you know my innerness from
whole life english
um
uh welcome back
[Music]
welcome back oh
yeah i i like to draw
i'm looking forward to drawing a lot
today
yes okay yes
that's it
and meows
hello
uh i've played this game a lot
now today even today i've played it in a
separate stream
and i'm playing it three times this week
so i would like to say i'm the master of
gardek phone um let's freaking go
let's go
indisputable
with this stream i think we would all
like to give a big big warm welcome to
iris welcome to hello live english thank
you
[Music]
i'm still i'm pretty nervous but yeah
i know what you're saying
no no need to worry about
um
i think we should start it off with
normal and okay if we want if we want
all we can because which is six people
so the rounds should probably be pretty
short we can try some other things too
but normal i think is the best
[Music]
yeah
yeah oh
[Music]
um
oh shh i'm really on the spot now okay i
already thought of this one
[Music]
i have mine ready
a hint by the way i feel like like very
wide broad suggestions make for funnier
outcomes
when they're open to
but mine definitely is not
the phone
oh my god
i wonder who was that
okay wait did i just oh god oh god
did i
you didn't i don't think you gave
anything away wait we got we gotta we
gotta go
oh god i've never played this sorry i
don't know what i'm doing i didn't do
anything i didn't say anything
what we heard nothing you didn't do
anything
i heard nothing i really heard nothing
yeah i was too distracted by my lack of
time
i was talking about my roomba i think i
left my roomba going in the uh
the kitchen
right
you're using a room huh
i have a roomba
i like to sit on it
[Music]
oh dear
i don't know what i'm doing
i got i can't know what that is how much
time is that
[Music]
almost half time
oh sh
um this is the warm up round right
yes the more
we have so much time to draw so many
different things don't worry about it
right okay
i gotta warm up my
my drawing skills what the hell is this
what do you mean what the hell is that
i left my drawing brain somewhere i
can't find it
no way you're gonna do the best things
anyway come on
this is a hard one
five thousand years since then yeah i
feel so awkward drawing this okay
oh yeah yeah
beautiful
um
what time is taking girls um
if you add a little bit of color it will
make it so much easier to recognize who
you're drawing
i hope this is enough
[Music]
also don't don't write anything to your
drawings writing examples okay okay no
writing okay
god damn it
i can't put like an exclamation like oh
no
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
okay this is easy this is
um
what is this
oh this is adorable
this is what i get from dads
you guys don't get to see what i wrote
hero one second we'll see it at the end
i'm just kidding i'm excited why is
there so much about me
oh what the hell
interesting
i see i see
oh
[Laughter]
hmm
on the right side you have some tools
you can erase and you can also go steps
back
oh steps back okay oh you have a you
have a custom edge picker as well that's
nice i'm gonna use this
by the way today i'm playing christmas
music on live stream
oh no
christmas music is so nice the bells and
everything ah
made me feel so nostalgic because it's
music that i went that i was using
during the christmas time
so nostalgic
usual oh god i don't have time
yeah not a lot of time here huh
not a lot of time
because this music makes me sleepy
uh
fan artists love this
oh
[Music]
it would look like okay so there would
be fingers okay
um
wow this is rough this is rough for you
guys
[Music]
oh yes artiste
i i mean uh i forgot what what uh
nice weather today isn't it
what nice one is yes it's very dark
outside i can barely tell
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait this
this cereal
now everybody will know who it is right
here oh yeah oh my god
oh my god this is pretty good
who throw this
i mean i like it
you don't have a problem with it
um
thank you
[Music]
what does this mean
i always felt this way is there like
points
are we supposed
no in this mode there's no points no no
oh all right
i am confused
so iris
how how does it feel after one month in
the whole live english yeah finally
getting used to conveniently getting
used to everything yeah
uh but everything still doesn't feel
that real
oh
yeah is actually not real it is all a
dream irish oh wow this is one long
havoc of a dream
don't wake up the dream is so nice i
also don't want to wake up i've decided
to never wake up
uh
oh my hair yeah it takes a good two to
three hours styling it yeah get ready
yep i woke up super early for this yes
holy damn
sounds rough i thought that was like so
set in place you don't need to like you
wake up like this i wake up like this oh
it's even it's it's worse when i wake up
it's all over the place it's what it's
all over the place
so you have to like oh yeah struggling
with dangling yeah my my hair brush my
hair brush it gets a lot of yeah a lot
of hair just gets wanked off when i'm
brushing it yep
i've seen those videos where people
clean their hair brushes out after like
two months or so and the water is like
brown
oh my god
well i think i'm done this is a
beautiful island no one will understand
it but yeah
we should do auto so we all see it at
the same time normally i do manual but
okay okay
honestly
[Laughter]
[Music]
is scared of hope
[Laughter]
what do you mean stick figures are godly
wow
that's really good thank
thank you
man
you guys can um save save the album if
you click on the button to save it oh if
someone wanna be on save duty or i will
do it okay okay
okay shall we go to the next album
santa missing suspect descendants enough
of him
oh
[Laughter]
i couldn't think of anything
posing
i'm wearing a
leotard was even still about um iris but
i just put her in there
so i guess i was right by putting her in
there
okay
in between
again oh
in between some bells yeah yeah made me
think of christmas and i was like hmm i
guess i'll put iris in there
because she loves christmas so much
doesn't she
yeah yeah
yeah
you will like it much more once you get
to know these five santas
well you're all centered
us yeah yeah become santa
oh no that's santa yeah
[Laughter]
that is very poor
oh
it's nice it's so cute
[Laughter]
sorry my cat walked in front of the
camera
i see i see
that is so cute yeah we really enjoyed
that beauty uh manga that we read
together i liked the
you came up with that idea
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
escalated a little bit let's go
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
i thought it was kelly oh god it was me
out
beautiful there's a dolphin there what
is that
it looks like a dolphin
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
ads you wanted the chaos
oh no
i got that one yeah
what does blessing mean
i don't know what black thing
oh my god i love this beautiful i love
the face on the banana
beautiful it was really good it was a
nice first round ladies nice
nice fast we shall do more
new turn
should we do another normal one
i don't know what are the other modes
well
the others are partially pretty
difficult um for example um i think
maybe sandwich could be interesting
people have been suggesting should just
suggest you
sandwich a lot yummy sounds delicious
want to do that one we can try it
outside and keep drawing until the end
finally describe the last drawing we
will understand when it happens
oh is it gonna like hear all of our
drawings on top oh
yeah sandwich oh i see
i get
okay
um
[Laughter]
i think that's good that's a good one i
think it's good
i can't think of anything yeah that's
the problem i have that a lot too
[Music]
i'm excited for your prompt everyone
yeah
let's go something simple
screw it let's just let's do something
fun let's go wow great that was
something crazy
okay
oh yeah
god the time the time is ticking so
quickly quickly
i has idea
okay
[Laughter]
shut up kelly shut up
don't shut it up kelly
talk i can't like i can't wait i'm
rolling
uh-oh
i just feel like making it cursed
curse is fun do cursed
okay you betcha girl
you betcha
so how's that different from
oh yeah art skills coming at you
[Music]
yeah
oh i'm so
oh yeah
you're good
why doesn't i let you save your color
you should have like a custom color bank
you can save yeah
oh no fortunately oh no i'm not gonna
make it
i don't know uh
don't worry other people will finish
your drawing maybe
oh
oh that's a good idea so maybe we should
leave room for others oh probably yeah
i'm not sure
okay
oh my god
oh no no no no no no
wait no
eh
okay okay at least it's recognizable i
think but all right
yeah okay okay let's see what happens
oh [\h__\h]
this is nice
oh god everything is going to turn into
stick figures
uh this is really cute this is adorable
thank you thank you
wait what
all right i got it we're going point for
point here
okay yeah
oh okay
i forgot the whole drawing okay
i think i remember
oh my god i don't remember i already
forgot i have a heart brain okay
how am i supposed to remember that
also i don't even know what was going on
there
oh oh yeah
oh no oh god
um
i'm so sorry
if you wanted to control z
you can i can't i can't draw so many
people in that short time
oh my god i've been doing it
i couldn't i think i can't pick a custom
color
you can
you have to click the big big swatch
oh okay
you taught me something
there we go
learn something new every day
there was some something like that in
between with one silver one
i don't have space
hey this isn't bad i think i'm improving
i think we're seeing improvements
now you wait for me game you wait for me
or i'll be angry
i'll be angry you don't want the no wait
oh what's happening
couple more seconds
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god what is this wait does this
time count as well oh my god
[Music]
what
what okay okay okay what
all right it's a no-brainer
what
oh i didn't notice there was a
bucket oh wait no it didn't work
um
something like that
this is really difficult
i like this game
i also enjoy this game
it's simplicity it's implicit
there's like someone missing
oh man
oh no i actually still have time damn it
we're supposed to be this like
as accurate as we can
or yeah
yeah as much as we can remember right
and your artistic interpretations of
what's
good
i'm so done
[Music]
i captured the essence of it
i don't know about this one
i actually had it
in early because there was no no more to
say
i guess the reference was just so simple
oh wait no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
i really want to know what the what the
title to this piece of art is oh my god
oh [\h__\h] the time gets shorter and
shorter yeah it seems like
i don't know i'm pretty sure isn't
sandwich i think sandwiches like that
okay
all right we're we're going in we're
doing the best we can with the tools we
have
that's adorable i don't understand what
okay okay
it's hard to be able to talk about it
because i just want to make
jokes about what i'm seeing
okay you can make graph jokes about it
also afterwards we see it anyway so
write it down
remember
yeah looking good ladies looking good
beautiful and then there was a
taco
oh my god
who's asmr
you can all do it if you want if you
desire that something
maybe later
something
was it like this
i don't know what happened here
uh oh yeah
can we get like a pur
a different color
nice
i feel like my drawing skills are
evolving through every single round
yeah
aren't they yeah
[Music]
don't doesn't have enough time i can't
stop time
just go back in time and you're going
good
[Music]
oh
okay
wow you're fair you're a fair player
nice
she doesn't use her skills like that i
respect that i was
irish that's not even mine i'm not gonna
steal that you know came up with that
it's beautiful that was a good one
beautiful that was a real good one
it is pretty accurate
although i don't know what happened
there's one more one more thing to do by
the way five out of the six so
then okay
everything
wow
i hope you know that
that's my heart and i
love it what
oh
oh god
i wanted to hear that now that was my
hip bone
a headphone yeah
[Music]
i have the same issues though i really
want that brace that you were talking
about i want a brace for my full body
yeah the shoulder brace to make sure you
don't punch over like the hunchback yeah
yes that would be nice that's a good
purchase
you can get one of those gamer rigs
[Music]
should i go manual because it's been so
fast actually wanna go for it slower
let's do display mode manually okay and
you can open it up on your own timing
okay
i see
i was detangling her hair but getting
stuck
okay okay
i think i did a pretty good job
oh it's so cute it's so cute
wow
that's pretty cute yeah she has a lot of
a lot of stuck in there a lot of mascots
stuck in there
so did we all get the same
i think we didn't get all the topics i
don't think so oh and maybe we did at
one point some people's images had to
memorize it and then like draw it
yeah
yeah oh oh let's let's check out goudas
that's good
hey did you know gooda what was going on
when you saw that image did you have an
idea
i know i just thought it was iris
oh singing
she has that hopeful expression in her
face yeah
beautiful expression
all right let's see watsons
okay you're all going for the singing
female now it's just
the music notes made it look like it
yeah oh
all right and iris draws herself
[Music]
beautiful
oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
how about for each album uh each person
who led the album says next next next
and we follow that person uh you know
what i mean yes
okay
next is inna
what did i write comments
tomorrow
shouldn't tomorrow it just start today
again
you know what happens when taco time
ends what why oh wait wait wait
only i can open it
[Laughter]
[Music]
nice interpretation
[Laughter]
i see you around all the time there
oh yeah the paint bucket continued to
betray me over and over again
opening i can see them
if it was alive or not so i ended up
drawing it dead
oh no no that makes sense according to
the first one oh
[Music]
i know what's underneath
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah very confident
i did it perfectly yes believe it oh i'm
sure
[Music]
[Laughter]
and what i thought when i saw that was
good i killed them
a beautiful progression of events
this is beautiful
[Music]
launched
ready for takeoff
is a missile missile
missiles
[Laughter]
why do i look like a manga
[Music]
yeah
i didn't
[Music]
well i kept it very simple
[Laughter]
the whole rocket thing just disappeared
about the orange underneath
i thought it was pac-man
an artistic edition of pac-man
wow
[Laughter]
yeah i love the face on on all of them
oh my god especially the amazing yeah
that is accurate yeah accurate very well
next one
cali oh lion pillow hello ian pillow
fight show it to me
show me what you've got
i had a hard time drawing this
oh
[Laughter]
hair
from my head
obviously some pillows
all right i had no idea what was going
on all right
i tried it was
it's okay i think i think i saved you i
think i saved you kind of what happened
to apex predator
apex trampled predatory
okay
[Music]
how am i supposed to follow up with this
i don't know
maybe don't make
i mean technically that could be correct
because
um
that's not good though oh no
what battle all kinds of battles all
kinds of that yeah yeah i have i have
magic powers
how many people have been killed until
now i have no i'm hope i don't kill
people
oh
alrighty next up iris
please read your bro you're a suspect
i'm an investigation
um i missed the trident i think
if you missed it
you didn't recognize yourself okay
oh it's in color
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
that's so tiny
is that your power we got so close i
wouldn't i thought somebody would
interpret it afterwards so i just
because i don't know
[Music]
minus the power of the sun
yeah science
exactly saved them all i will send them
to you all afterwards thank you we have
them
we have
stores
we have ten
a bit more i think we can squeeze in
another normal round
okay
um
i think yeah i think
[Music]
chad got any ideas
suggestions submissions
i hope i hope
so someone
really good gets that prompt
this is gonna turn out amazing thanks
chad
okay thank you all hydrated
party time
[Music]
oh
i'm on it
leave it to me
okay
i ran out of time my prompt is possibly
interesting
no problem that's just that just makes
it better you know
okay maybe i left it really vague we
have to see
[Music]
oh boy what does this look like
um
so we have this
um oh gosh
uh
and then
this one it's okay to write a letter in
this
since this is a topic right
like this this is pretty much true
though
beautiful i feel i feel i feel it i feel
it i just feel it it's beautiful
[Applause]
[Laughter]
did not think about the composition of
this picture very well before i started
trying it oh my goodness i can't wait to
see everyone's streams after this
oh
first
maybe add some more color to this
oh there no
no it's not that chat
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
yeah well i mean
pretty easy
this might sound better does this sound
better it sounds better
that sounds better
beautiful all right wednesdays here we
go
what does that word
what does that mean
oh easy i just described what i saw
um oh geez oh
i need to google someone real quick
uh
what is that
what is it
[Music]
tell me what is that what is that i
don't speak this language of memes ah
what
wait okay i'll grab what
okay um
i think i know who this is maybe
and if i could draw this could be really
cute
what's a turn
oh
um
[Music]
i need to draw my circles perfect
okay
okay uh
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you good
you're good
clara's not good
she's gone she's gone he's gone
she's disappeared forever
oh no
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no
the phoenix is dying
[Music]
oh
what what
wait i don't recognize who this is what
uh oh
just playing my cards real straight chat
check it out
who is this
this is okay
um
is that a sword i don't know what this
says
oh no i didn't have enough time
oh what does this mean yeah what does
this mean
oh my god don't make me try so many
people again
that means oh
yes i do
of course
[Music]
um
okay we can do this we can do this we
can do this
[Music]
help i'm right
okay okay
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
i have given up completely
never give up never surrender
this is what this animal looks like i i
don't i lost help even though hope is
right next to me right next to you right
next to you girl
did you just say i'm next to you girl
yeah
oh wow that wow that's i don't know
that's kind of charming
why is that so charming i don't know
uh-oh
[Music]
there everybody's gonna know what this
is right yeah
yeah oh no
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my god
well we started out with things
i expect greatness from this
oh my goodness
that's good that's so much
[Laughter]
i
dead in these things
i was dying
good guys what's up
realistic
very real is it oh my god
[Laughter]
oh my god did you practice that okay
god damn
that's sick you're gonna say i can hear
this image and it sounds exactly like
that that sounds like that sounded
perfect
oh man okay next okay
sesame street character
muppet
was a little weird
the lego looks like it's about to
dominate yeah
this was the one where i started dying
by crying oh no
i also didn't know what tea bagging
meant
this is what happened
one big [\h__\h] place
what is that
he's putting his teeth
oh laughing when i was i
[Music]
[Laughter]
like you bank a turn
[Music]
car banking
it's okay this is what the cardinal
phone is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
yes
yeah that's your background basically
good stuff
oh
[Music]
it became so hot that they melted into
one box oh
god that's a babysitter he's like a
monster
i miss interpreting
return to monkey
i love that i love it i love it monkeys
look like that's so cute
[Music]
i like the sensors
the right person got that one yeah
good job
[Music]
when
anyway
i mean
same thing
oh that's a good one
same thing you understand each other
this is the the telepathy that we have
after almost a year
yes
wow
the bucket works all the letters
capitalized
so
uh know that there was an eat a pun in
there i just guessed oh wow
my intuition is
trained
trained for planes
tackle world domination with halloween
yeah
with the homies
[Music]
[Applause]
that was a lot of fun time very good job
i had a blast
wow
i will send them to you afterwards
everyone can pick one to upload on
twitter or five or two two how many ever
you want yeah they have a lot of lot of
gifts gifs about okay by the way how do
you guys say give gif
just gift
oh no oh no yeah yeah wow
i'm a jiffer
i usually say gif when i speak german i
think and when i speak english i tend to
say jeff
what does jeff even stand for many years
ago yeah
it was it was the pineapple on pizza
before pineapple on pizza was a
we do have an announcement
we have one long time long awaited long
long awaited announcement from uh hold
on hold on actually
we haven't announced that that's
everyone
shall we open it
two one
bum
oh no i can't break everyone there we go
[Music]
they're adorable
it says happier though it's already been
way over half a year might as well be
one year
right
it's definitely ready yeah
[Music]
uh
very soon like
what's 15 minus nine
uh
math wow that was fast that you did that
mathematical g who are you what have you
done with gura
sorry is taking over
[Laughter]
imposter well uh the the booth and
geekjack page is got going up in
approximately five minutes
this time the tweet on hololive english
twitter is coming out in i think 20
minutes if they don't decide to put it
out earlier now but it should be coming
out in 20 minutes right mm-hmm yes yes
quite big yep yes they're very much very
big i have seen them
seen them as well show their details oh
yeah show you
your your ones
guys i got yesterday
check everyone's streams for the
individual pictures check it out
35 centimeters that's big you guys 35
centimeters
yeah they're huggable totally huggable
they're soft i can confirm i have
touched them before
yes good question do we have a picture
of yago holding them i wonder i don't
think i haven't at least not yet
not yet but eventually hopefully in the
near future i think definitely oh wound
yeah
only because we need it for scale for
for imagination
no other reason
we have a picture
some people don't think in centimeters
we have a picture we do really i thought
you guys were talking about
[Music]
no it does not come with jaggle
unfortunately we're sorry but yoga could
honestly like just quit his ceo job and
become a model at this point
true fact
is calling
is that what it's called thank you
thing is that i'm not really sure what's
kinky
i thought it's like a like a magazine
i was thinking
dairy queen dairy queen
[Music]
i haven't had dairy queen in
yeah that's a good point when uh when we
all eventually meet we need to have a
big pillow fight with these
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
you need a lot of things i don't really
want to put them into my luggage because
they're going to be big can you are you
getting all of them are you getting yeah
of course
your hair will probably carry one as a
carry-on but then they'd be questioning
you
yeah they're going to look inside
they're gonna open them up and be like
what did you hide the bump inside of the
map
no
no no i'm going to cut them open oh no
don't dissect the plushies
i cannot risk that dissection oh no no
please no
i wonder if it's just cotton in there
though
is there anything else besides cotton in
there
all right we'll find it out i guess at
the airport
cotton
and distort it yeah i've touched those
as well they're very soft very nice yeah
all right well iris how how did you like
your first collab with live english it
was a lot of fun i love to play gartek
everyone's art and art levels are just
out of the world
thank you
some figures have a ton of personality
actually and that's not me being ironic
or
sarcastic thank you you did a very good
job thank you yeah
we're so glad to have honored you in
this collaboration thank you i would
like to collab with all of you guys
again
yeah of course yeah let's keep doing it
yeah
hmm yeah i think some of us just like me
have not done a one-on-one collab yeah
yeah let's do that today was the first
time for me to collab with you yeah i
still haven't collaborated half of you
guys oh wait yeah
yeah yeah
that still is so nice yeah that's good
that's it minecraft minecraft
minecraft
give you an official tour of the eon
server yeah i haven't got a tour yet i
was just like looking at everyone's
buildings it's just like what is this
i'd love to show you around yeah
yeah let me show you phoenixten
you might have actually already stumbled
into phoenix i think right is it isn't
it like the restaurant the restaurant
no no that's kfc
oh i heard you stumbled into a big
village oh yeah yeah yeah that's phoenix
oh yeah the one with the with the golems
yeah
oh oh by the way iris the hole that you
fell into
now that we're all here um i fell into
that hole uh a few months ago several
times and lost a lot of things and i was
always wondering who dug the hole yes
who dug that hole
is that no one has any record of anyone
ever digging that hold on
on stream yeah we need i i kept it open
because i was like well
well i want the person who dug it to
fall into it but that iris fell into it
we need to know who the suspect is
yeah who was it who did it
who did it oh okay couldn't have been
maybe it couldn't be
or something like that you were like
reacting suspiciously biscuits
suspicious we need an investigation
sauce maybe one's hatchimal who was it i
wonder that hole of death
it's like it's like a whole lot of
nowhere too it's so hard to notice
like if you go through kfp back to like
spawn
yeah
i mean i'm responsible for the the
stairs uh in kfp i will open up that
hole
not that a different pole that i don't
know a different different hole that's
like one block
wide but it goes straight down yeah feet
yeah it goes straight down it's out in
the middle of nowhere yeah and when it's
really hard to notice
yep
but he dug straight down
[Music]
and they were trying to maybe just uh
make a landmark or something or
no it's like really close to my house
[Music]
no no no no i knew nothing about this i
like this conspiracy this conspiracy
theory
[Music]
are we going to cover that hole are we
just going to leave it there for more
victims
yeah it's a memorial
it's an important part of holo en
history
emma what were you saying oh does
anybody have any like uh individual
announcements like maybe a stream you're
gonna do or something like that
oh yeah
uh so tomorrow um i have a karaoke
stream with a special guest a guest who
is not in holdo live so i hope you guys
will
check it out we're doing uh archived and
also unarchived streams oh
i'm excited nice
thank you
that's all i have anyone else
um
i'm gonna play
uh
police officer officer gouda
yeah and now we're gonna continue devil
may cry finally so that's all i got
yeah
[Music]
all right um all right then i'll say
next week i'm playing minecraft with my
real mother uh
heartwarming and it will it will
actually be amazing because for the
people who don't know my my mother is
better at minecraft than all of us here
she's really good and she will teach me
um some stuff and we will go get never
right together
[Music]
unless you'll keep me how to farm never
right it'll be fun so my momma will be
on our server for one day
you guys are you guys are welcome to
join in for a minute and introduce
yourself to my mother
yes
mama
oh phoenix god i want to say hello
i didn't say you guys would want to do
that oh i didn't think so okay go ahead
please please be welcome
my mom knows about all of you she uh
checked all of your streams out
let's gotta think of some embarrassing
stuff
no
i didn't have many feathers back then it
wasn't naked
[Laughter]
okay anyone else with announcements uh
[Music]
i'll be streaming subnautica later on
today
and tomorrow ring fit finally got my
switch oh boy
yeah
exercise no no not your virus just some
healthy exercise
so we all know that right we all need
that help healthy
health
no help
that didn't work out anything anyone
else anyone else
i have a
morning show that i'm going to be doing
a week weekly but uh
we want to do it weekly sunday but i'll
be gone for two weeks after that and
then when i come back we'll do another
one
okay yeah oh exciting
big commitment
good night
is the name
that's a club
[Music]
i will be watching it it might be
archived but i will be watching it yeah
i'll definitely check it out yeah i'm it
i mean you and me we are on mexican
orlando this weekend
yeah thank you heading out to megacon in
orlando florida in the us of a uh you
can meet or talk to us or uh show up on
our panel i believe um
minus tomorrow and kiara's is the day
after
yeah i'm on saturday on friday and uh
oh yeah if you if you can't attend it in
person if you have a ticket then you can
actually watch your stream of it so you
don't have to be there in person but you
still need a ticket there is a stream
so everyone we're looking forward to
seeing you that is the first one that
kicks off the halloween in america
conventions american canada conventions
tour let's go let's go
on a tour i can't believe we're going on
tour guys
[Music]
okay
thank you for coming thanks guys
[Music]
peace
goodbye okay
darkness will fade away
light will guide your way
hope has descended and you are not alone
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
darkness for you
you