[Music]
oh my god i'm so nervous
today i eat i i think i ate too much i
think
i got sorry whoops i had my thing open i
got it
i ate too much chocolate and my throat's
kind of hurting
there's like
i don't know i don't know
good afternoon yeah there was echo
because i have my thing open
yes oh no
vito
thank you
d vlogs uh gonna start soon
hopefully the heart eyes will be able to
seduce
nintendo
what
[Music]
ah
i'm nervous
[Music]
here
we're here for you thank you that's your
reassuring i'm so nervous i'm so nervous
i know what to expect
also i feel like you know because
nobody's nobody's talking
i'm alone here
and it just gives you the uh
ah but you know
i'm gonna travel oh everybody's in the
lobby
everybody's in the lobby so let's go
hopefully um let's just do our best and
you know
oh look the two twin tails on my screen
are socializing that's very cute
actually has a slightly identical oh
look now we're socializing
that's cute
that's real cute
uh everybody you can tweet with the
hashtag below holo
oshogatskop202 as well as um there's
also an english hashtag
oh okay i think um
uh right now uh they're interviewing the
winners from box c
so who won in bloxy who is the winner
who's the winner in block c
[Music]
ah
very nice
cali because she wanted to be last wait
i thought she didn't want to be last
[Music]
night
okay
be the card
[Music]
i feel like i don't know i don't usually
talk like this
but
i don't know if i'm even gonna be able
to talk normally
oh my gosh you haven't won the whole new
year's cup ready yes i am
oh no
[Music]
believe in mushroom no mushrooms are the
one that's gonna betray me oh no should
i should i not have said that
yeah
don't worry about it oh thank you for
the support i will i will try my best
you sound like you're debuting again i
know
i know i know i know
[Music]
[Laughter]
mushrooms will save you no it will not
i mean maybe it will
[Music]
i hope i don't get
mario kart too hard today
i feel like if you guys saw i was also
watching the other uh i was also
watching the other cups and then
basically anything can happen
anything can happen like i know like
every because everybody's really really
good right but
it all just
it all just depends on like the rng and
everything so
it's just wow there's been lots of mario
karting so far yeah i see i i was a
witness to some of them i was like oh my
goodness
[Music]
every race has been crazy
yeah yeah yeah
let's wait for more players
wait did you see the opening uh so
they wanted us to
uh get our you know like oh if we have
like catchphrases or things we want to
say
you know
oh and then apparently they're using it
for like the video thing right and then
mine's like hello i am wayne i'm
commonplace and then somehow they put
japanese subtitles on it and
it's kind of like yeah
[Laughter]
before you're waiting
no no because listen like i didn't know
what to say this was before the mushroom
arc i would have said something like hey
is brainy the mushroom farmer or
something but um
yeah
i submitted it before um the mushroom
arc started
like i didn't know what to say so just
like okay yolo right
okay
[Music]
did you eat your breakfast i ate some
pasta leftovers
i feel kind of cold though but i don't
know if i should turn on my air
conditioning because
i don't know
if it's too hot i can't concentrate
either
so it's like
[Music]
pasta sauce
at least i ate before the stream that's
true
i just turned off the air conditioning
for now
[Music]
ready for sweaty oh no now it's starting
no no it's sorry come on i turned up the
ac and now it's starting my god um
i don't know what i should choose
where's um
guys okay
i don't know i'm gonna choose this one
whatever oh no no baby park please i'm
gonna die in baby park
don't read chat i won't
i'll try my best not to read
[Music]
how many people are here
oh
baby fork oh god what a bad start
oh god i'm so bad oh god
oh
[Music]
oh my god okay i'll try my best well
i'll try my best in baby park
oh that's kitsu very very kiss me
because
no
island
oh no no no no no no no
[Music]
please
bananas
[Music]
[Applause]
oh bananas are you freaking serious
are you freaking serious
[Applause]
[Laughter]
that's cute
[Music]
oh no oh no oh no
nice
[Music]
that was so lucky
nice oh nice nice nice nice nice
[Music]
nice nice nice nice nice oh mute city
everybody wants new city
i admit i don't have um the shortcut for
mute city down but
i'll do my best
this is banana peel beach
oh god royal raceway no
and why we why do we keep getting the
mouse that i'm not familiar with
[Music]
just don't choke i get it okay
you want to be good just don't choke
classic
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't really want to be first in the
very beginning
[Music]
i just said don't choke i just said
don't choke
it's okay it's the first laugh there's
still hope
see the the second i got mushrooms
that happens
so i hope
i hope
oh god see are you serious
as soon as this happens
you know you know you know what's gonna
happen if i start getting mushrooms
that's what happens
[Music]
oh god see are you freaking serious
it's the mushroom curse
haunting me
[Music]
bananas i mean i guess that's better
than nothing
[Music]
[Applause]
i hope
i hope i can redeem this somehow
[Music]
[Applause]
oh god yeah
mushroom curse
[Music]
please something please happen
i need a miracle i need a miracle
i need a miracle
[Music]
i need a miracle i need a thon or
something
[Music]
foreign
let's hope we get something better next
time
let's go let's go let's go
i'm gonna keep pushing for
i'm gonna keep pushing for wario stadium
[Music]
yeah still number one but the gap is
kind of closing you know
so honestly anything can happen
[Music]
i wonder what's next
bye mute city
dang
[Music]
i'm not really good at mid city oh let's
just do our
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my best
that start whatever it's fine
it's fine
we can still salvage this somehow
[Music]
the first lap we focus on much and all
my shrubs god mushrooms what the [\h__\h]
what's wrong with you
what is wrong with you
[Music]
i don't know what is going on
i just want
to be able to
do okay oh god i missed the item it's
not good
that's not good that's not good oh god
no no no no no
that's great
i can't use the shortcut
because i don't know how to use it
[Music]
i don't know how to use the shortcut
if i have a mushroom i will have more
confidence oh crap no no no no no no
please
head to me please
is right in front of me
ah mushrooms more mushrooms is it really
okay oh god
is it really okay to give me mushrooms
oh no items this is bad this is bad
ah this is real bad this is real bad
two items
ah five okay five uh five
five five five
twenty five
oh super senpai is number one
i'll keep pushing for wario stadium
[Music]
okay okay oh there's big blue oh my gosh
look at senpai really aiming for the
scary scary maps
[Laughter]
[Music]
are you serious
gonna cry
dang it
[Music]
it's okay we're gonna try our best
oh god yeah i can think it takes it i
don't have the items there you can cute
sweetest yes yes yes oh my god oh no
oh no no items can you believe it i got
no items
oh gosh
somebody saw the two items not me they
all got bananas
[Music]
uh it doesn't matter because i'm holding
banana
[Music]
i can't do that okay whatever it's fine
let's go
[Music]
we can still recover
we can still recover if we have the uh
we have
um as long as there's a will there's a
wig
[Music]
like this
[Applause]
haha
[Music]
foreign
dang i should have used the mushroom i
used the mushrooms too early because i
got too
nervous
that's okay
[Music]
oh
ah
dolphin stupid dolphin place
dolphin shows
um this is the fourth race is it
is this a fifth
so this one and then one more
[Music]
mushrooms of course we got mushrooms
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no i missed the
oh whoops
ah i should have used it at the back
i accidentally pressed it
yeah that's what i get we're missing
that's what i got for missing
[Music]
oh no
it's awful
i hope there's still a way to redeem
this
the thing is if you get um
if you'll be behind you're gonna really
get mario kart at heart because
everybody's just like huddled up
together
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
i'm behind i wonder what should i do
i hope a miracle will happen
here's me hoping for a miracle
hoping for a miracle
hopefully boo steals something nice
mushrooms well
i guess
i don't know
yes two
[Music]
six
ah
[Music]
six so ah silva is gonna be the first
yeah
hmm this is dangerous i might get kicked
out
i might get kicked out in the last if i
don't do well
[Music]
i might get kicked out uh it's fine
though if i get kicked out it's fine
um i did i feel like i did my best
and um if i get in then i'll be very
happy but if i get kicked out is fine
you know i mean like to be honest
everybody's like trying my bit i'm
trying their best
and it's just um
like
see the like if i got first they got
second it's just like a matter of rng i
feel like
everybody's just trying their best
so um
that's what i'm gonna do too
really though the maps that are chosen
i'm really bad at them like
i'm just
i'm just really really really hoping for
a good rng
like if i got like crappier rng i would
definitely be destroyed
rng has been like um
kind of nice nicest to me like even
though like it's you know in math that
i'm not
good at at all
[Music]
no
like it's a bowser castle or like
whatever place
[Music]
i feel like whenever the maps get chosen
i was like oh god why is it this map
[Music]
nice
she just banged the blue shell out
ah she's aiming for the
[Applause]
she's aiming for the oh god why do i
have banana
why i don't want banana
[Music]
higher than me
i think she was pretty far away huh
[Music]
oh god why
i'm gonna try and pick up
[Music]
okay kkk
let's go
[Music]
i got in
nice nice and nice
the money senpai similar to senpai and
me
hey
oh
dang i was so happy about this
[Music]
i'm excited
yes
all right guys pays off um i think uh
that is it uh i think the winner uh yeah
communication has occurred
so that's it uh they're gonna interview
the um
the winners and i'm gonna stop the
stream uh i'm gonna see you guys in the
pro cup later i'm gonna do a new stream
so yeah thank you guys for coming and
bye bye see you soon
[Music]