[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
Fae
[Music]
hey what's up sorry for the wait I want
I was going to start on time but
everything was being weird
um
it will lay out after looking yeah the
chat box is a little bit smaller now
doesn't stand out too much
very good Disney thanks for the update
since I'm gonna be using it more in the
future I should put it in my description
afterwards thank you
[Music]
Mamma Mia guys
I tried
before the stream you know guess some
Gaston was
it that rarely happens to me that I mix
German into my ankles yesterday
um yesterday
[Music]
um I
um streamed so long and then I cooked
and well that was pretty yummy
and then I slept and so did I do my
starting tweet
I am I don't think I did
maybe if I did end about doing it twice
starting now I don't think I did uh but
yeah I didn't have so much time but I
really needed to get some
I did
well double is better
but I really needed some more of those
sunflowers man
foreign
because I don't know how many do you
guys say we need because I I had at the
end of yesterday I had maybe nothing
left
and I collected like 19 but that that's
me collecting for two hours basically
trying to find places that have it you
think that's good enough
no way
at the same time you know I was visiting
some new islands and doing two shrines
at least
nine is good really oh you can have his
answer no I still don't have that one I
only have the normal one
um but okay if you guys say that that's
already good then we'll get a couple
more
uh and then we can Oops why do I always
take screenshots but I found a really
cool Island Shrine thingy
um
so I flew around it was really hard to
get up to the islands uh up here
um because the the little pieces the
island pieces that fly up they don't
reach that actual height
well it sucks so I had to go over to an
island and had a waterfall and then from
there on I had to fly over to the
islands I wanted to go to and I found
this island it's the the light
um Tower Island thingy
I was like oh this looks cool
yeah because it shines into first you
have to get rid of the water because
like this uh Stone thingy is surrounded
by a lot of water so you have to get rid
of the water then you can go into the
cave then you blow up the cave uh inside
so you can go in then the the light
shines through and there's mirrors and
it's dark in there so I spread some of
my light flowers
um and then yeah you keep on sending uh
the light around and around and around
the inside of the cave it's pretty long
and then eventually you light up the
final point which is this there's also
some dude protecting it and there's um
oh yeah then there is as a reward
a donut Helm
pretty cool kind of late for me to
receive it though
yeah that's so cool though
something really special for a special
Island yum uh oh and then I was fighting
I just fought a
level free
construct because of another Shrine and
then this one I was trying to fly
because he was like protecting the stone
and I was trying to fly it up
but
it's
really difficult and so I flew all the
way up there and then and then I I
couldn't I couldn't land properly so I
just thought okay I'll drop it but
because of the light air here it did not
fall straight down I didn't either and
so I lost the stone and that's where I
am right now and I have to go back down
I've in these two hours I've wasted so
much tonight
because I kept on making vehicles and
then they didn't work out well and I
kept on losing them
so annoying oh but
oh
that's the exact vehicle that I made and
it's like over there for free I didn't
see that
okay I'll use that is there some
sundalians
let me see they actually they blend in
so much don't they
the sundalians do you guys hear the game
audio Yeah
because like they're really golden and
they don't stand out it's really mean
actually
when you're actually looking for them
yeah you hear it okay when you're
actually looking for them they they
blend
yeah it's like I feel like it's the one
flower that blends in to the
surroundings the most
and this is the exact vehicle I used to
get up there but it was really [\h__\h]
difficult to land it was impossible to
land
the sensor helps
I don't have Santa Clauses you guys
think I have time to quickly get sensor
Plus
I don't want you know I I don't think
and I don't want a situation I don't
think we'll have it though like or
Skyward Sword but if it really looks
rough that I can't finish it then okay I
will not force myself we'll do a part
two
you think so
okay yeah no I I want some more
sundalians you got some of you guys say
it's enough but I don't feel secure just
yet
because you guys say it's like so much
Gloom
okay please let me land properly
it's like
okay
let's drop it immediately when we reach
that right side and uh
[Music]
hey hey
wait no now the free vehicle's gone
this game
[Laughter]
uh whatever whatever yeah I I have a
reverse time this way
also uh I have a energy drink but I
am afraid to use it because
if I drink it now already
uh I will
probably already break down before
the important test stream on Kelly's
Channel at midnight for me
yeah so I'm not tired right now anyway
uh I actually slept relatively good for
once I was I was sleeping so wild that I
slept over a lot of smoothies meows
surprisingly
but she was very very very
strict she would not leave me alone So
eventually I had to give in yeah but I I
was surprised like I was like falling
asleep in and out while she was meowing
really stubbornly at me
okay attempt number three
I almost had it though
I'm almost at it
I tried it uh
actually no no not this one but I tried
something similar with the bike too see
now now it reaches too much height
and what the [\h__\h] am I supposed
to go
and I can't let
see and I can't select it
I have to let go earlier
am I having a DSP moment
I I would still say this is not too much
um look it's this not it's not a DSP
moment yet no no no
only my
my um my fourth attempt
I'm not that bad thank you
oh man
I don't know why this is funny to you
to me do you hmm
your boss really
well you know what it's good that it's
funny to you I am here to bring you guys
entertainment as post even likes to say
we love to entertain you
miss a German popular
TV
Channel
for Zoomers
that I also used to watch a lot
and their slogan is we love to entertain
you
jump it
wait
[Laughter]
no I wasn't
just leave the land on there anyway I
just
foreign
actually maybe it would be better to
have less of those fans because
they're kind of too fast
don't you think
would it help me with glass fans but
they they're putting this here telling
you the player to use it
so
that'll be unbalanced but what if I take
the like the diagonally the the ones
that look at each other whatever
okay
if this doesn't work I'm going to cry
you know this this whole
Moon
uh like uh uh air
thing situation
pretty cool at first
but now I'm sick of it
everybody's heartbeat I can hear it I
can hear it
everybody's heartbeat now
yeah
[Laughter]
okay somebody
looking at cow carrot needs to make us
clippy clip compilation
of me finally
bringing this stupid ass stop to the
shrine
hahaha
shut up
blessing Shrine or else
I will hurt you I will rip that [\h__\h]
Stone out of the sand again and I'll
break it into pieces and blow it up I'll
blow it up
press track don't stop first try
these people oh yeah it better be
it better be a blessing
big ass blessing
[Music]
such a big ass blessing that you think
somebody's like having allergies and
sneezing
so much that their eyeballs are popping
out that that's how much blessings I
want
bless you
ah okay this is good though because now
how many do I have
yeah I can get another heart yeah I did
um
one or two shrines off screen so in a
really short time where I was looking
for sundalians
that's safe
um
oh yeah is she done it's Corner Senpai
done did she give up or did she actually
end up finishing jumping
because I I saw yeah she was like doing
a long endurance stream
daily and don't go
oh she really should sleep if she's been
streaming for 24 hours she really should
sleep at all
little paws how much is she going to
sleep
she doesn't sleep I will I will slap her
butt
I'll spank it
I already checked this area
where which island has the most some
billions also do they regrow
um after like a night or do I have to
make a fire place or
that way that's a sundelion
how how fast do they regrow
blood moon
um
after blood moon damn
I haven't seen a blood moon in a while
though
uh okay I checked out I did this island
I did this island
I had to fight on this island I think
yeah
I didn't go to this island yet I think
is it lower I think it's lower
how low no wait it's not
thank you
so I have to build myself another
little contraction huh is that it
that way that's something else
is it
I don't know it's hard to tell
I guess the sensor let me just check out
this island and then we can
try to get the sensor hmm
you could drop to get the fly okay what
from
I mean down there
but now it's gone no there's so some
materials but
wait
[Music]
with this air
I can at least reach this little piece
and then
that doesn't look so easy
you should have respawned really
okay I'll check it out
don't see it yet oh there it is
[Music]
man I don't know how I was able to get
enough sleep eat breakfast
play some Zelda
go swimming
yes I went swimming again
probably gonna go swimming tomorrow too
because like honestly right now
Austria is [\h__\h] suffering
uh-oh
okay we don't have to land it we just
have to end up on the island
no sunburn no no I'm always like putting
plenty of Cream
oh interesting Island
it's just a hole why
[Music]
is it telling me to jump through
yeah like it's been around 30 degrees
Celsius like
days
the hottest days of this year so far in
Austria
right now I feel quite okay
oh that's the first time I find this
room what
uh sundalian though I need some billions
I can beat that 33. I said around 30.
I think I saw in the
um
weather uh what's the word
the thing yeah I think I saw it say up
to 32 or something I don't know
humidity oh well it's not really humid
in Austria
thankfully
[Music]
so that's the one
upside I guess
but we also don't have AC es uh you have
to remember that because apparently in
America it's pretty common to have ACS
but here
it is not I don't have a scene
what do we do about this hole oh wait
oh
holes are meant to be
jumped through
no new ones what is all of this
what is this island trying to tell me
why
why are they they're bouncing pads
[Music]
how to
get the sensor Plus
oh there
data from five times a month oh I just
so have happened to have taken a picture
of
a Lionel actually the other day but I
don't know if I have five pictures let
me
just
go take some I think that was a dragon
down here
we're back in Normal
um
can never find this word
ugly yeah there it is take a picture of
that one very special picture
it's the file one wait Lang we already
fought a fire one didn't we
but this one's also looking like fire
gravity thank you
finally
can't take a photo while you're applying
it looks like fire
oh they're multiple oh
I'm bearable Heat
okay bye
actually
[Music]
we fought them yesterday but a different
one so no needs today
I like the music though
[Music]
maybe those
maybe I didn't take a picture of I
probably didn't take a picture of the
white one I generally never took
pictures so chances are high that I did
not take a picture before vocabulin
and
huh
silver blend
yeah wait did it save the normal one
no
now it did that's
the Lionel that I took yesterday
I mean I probably could not wait it's a
stick
yes
first
[Music]
probably five by now but just for ah hey
horsey I left it there
for the sake of being extra secure
huh my Majora's Mask oh yeah
creepy [\h__\h]
ah
oh and then before we go you know do a
story I also want to find one more fairy
ideally
to upgrade
one more time
if I can
would be nice
I swear the horse just went to the right
side huh
is this horse on the side of the enemy
Shrine below
Punk
and normally you can like Ram into
enemies now this one doesn't want to do
it
[Music]
I need to find one more enemy maybe come
on
maybe if I find a cave if I can find
different types of enemies in there
because I left them out for too long
yeah that might be why it's angry at me
it's not that long though because I used
it before the Stream
in fact
okay two red ones one white one again
that's nothing new
bye-bye horsey I'm gonna look for a cave
have fun making friends with the book
blends
it must be a cave here
100 percent
there will be a case
what is this place have I ever walked
through this
circles
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
oh wait we can take a picture of him
oh my god did not find it did not find a
cave
uh
yes sir with rope sounds like we're just
taking a picture of his clothes
[Music]
okay and then
we just go to him right uh
uh out there
no
we have Sunday oh not right now but
can I take him out of the inventory and
then take a picture like that
okay
easy
but we have to go up to the sky again
anyway
is there any shops that sell sundalians
I guess no
wait
I can enter From Below
it
yes let's make it really great
sorry
sensor plus please
sump
there's some pumpkins
um
there are two of friends Sonia's grave
oh I don't remember ah wait was it that
that one
where the map is of all the
locations
hey hey
[Music]
after the mail quiz oh I never finished
it because I never could find the last
person
uh no I'm not gonna buy any stupid
pictures
why would I want to
finish my album with pictures
especially what I don't understand is if
you play breath of the wild why would
you want to do it again
why do they make you do it again
I feel like it would be so fair if
you know breath of the Wild players
if you have the data
on your switch
that the game trtk recognizes it
that would be really nice
speaking facts I know
I know as always
okay
um
so we have 20 sundelions now
actually they might be easier to find at
night because they kind of glow
so how do I set the thing
I may be in the album or like here
Target of Center
okay
now we go to Island
but I already
checked out a couple of these ones
and now I've been like around here
let me that's the dungeon
maybe I'll go here
at least horses carry over oh yeah
that's true I am tutorial in the worst
I've I went to the tutorial Island
I ran around for a little while and I
found nothing and I was wondering like
maybe because
you don't the game doesn't want to
spoiler you yet with these flowers
because I guess it could imply
the amount of Gloom that is on the
ground I don't know but I did not find
it
um
maybe I'll take it actually I want that
one
okay so far nothing is pinging
wanna get up there
I shall
catapult myself that looks right Dad
[Music]
we could also use the platform thing
over there but no it works
there must be some sundalians up here
sensor Sean
it's not working
it's not showing me any sundelions
you're kidding me
ijer now
um
[Music]
okay are there really some on the
tutorial Island
because I didn't find any never saw
something right
no no I actually I didn't go to the cold
area before I went to the left side
where the big water
Pond is
I just went now here because I don't
know I wanted to go somewhere else
but
just quickly check in the middle here
not a ton
but some
[Music]
um
nothing here
nothing at all and I ran out of
wow one shot
I ran out of stamina
most in the ounce above the golden area
yeah maybe I should go there there's
nothing here
for real I don't I wonder what the
reason is why they don't put any
sundalians on only the tutorial Island
do you think maybe it really is what I I
was saying
like somehow not wanting to spoil her
because like the description
of the sundalian maybe is the spoiler
maybe probably
damn I'm so smart
okay
um let's see where could can I go
[Music]
I don't have any teleportation marks I
have to go up on those stones or
I could try flying over from
here
Tower I guess
the sun's aliens I need them because uh
apparently you know if you want to
finish the game there is a [\h__\h] ton of
Gloom
that you will have to face
hmm
you're bright
where is new boy
[Music]
I think I see one
oh yeah I see it okay here it stands out
but on all those like grassy golden
Islands
it does not stand out there okay that
might have been it here but I'm
surprised we found anything here at all
now
I could try I don't know how high it is
but I could try to get there
[Music]
yeah two for one that's that's pretty
sweet good deal
laughs
wait that chest I want it I can only
open it if I kill the mobs right
I don't have time for that I guess but
um
no time no time
I could maybe reach the lower one what
do you think guys
oh
whoa
[Music]
[Applause]
come on come on do it let's go oh
yeah wait wait that looks good
hey I have to go there come on come on
yes
see it
anymore
yeah yeah
different Island wait ah
two with a two again
oh
there's so many I'm looking so much at
the sensor that I'm barely seeing them
on screen
well this one is oh
oh Golden Grove
ah
wow
yo if blood moon hits soon
we can get all those again
but nothing else here it seems oh
there's a friend here that I didn't do
[Music]
let's at least activated so I can
teleport
do you think I got plenty now really
you think so I don't know I wasted like
when I look back on how many I had to
waste uh with the Lionel Colosseum
I feel like with how much people have
been exaggerating
I feel like there would be even more
used
wherever we're going now
I think it's gonna be okay
[Music]
should I only make like full five ones
and maybe fours to
it's the end of the game I might as well
use all of these that I haven't been
using
no I'm doing it on purpose because those
are the low level ones I'm not using
them anyway
just make four five ones okay oh
constructed
steak
steak um
did you guys see on my Twitter [\h__\h] me I
want to do this one can I can I
oops
where's the opening
uh
where's the opening this one doesn't
turn
have you guys seen my salmon
[Music]
I had to actually Grill it so much
longer than
it said on the recipe it said two to
three minutes on each side
but then
I grilled it for that and then it said
until the inside is not glassy anymore
um grilled yeah grilled salmon and I I
put it out of the frying pan and then I
looked I cut it open in the middle a
little bit and I saw it was still very
glassy
I was like okay I put it back for quite
some time it was very good it was very
soft and and the outside was a little
bit a tiny bit crispy and I I took off
the skin but now in hindsight I'm
wondering maybe I should have kept the
skin because actually it was really nice
and crispy too
huh
did it come out of the fridge oh yeah it
did I guess you know
oh
wait are we turning the inside or the
outside
the inside right
but I'm so confused
cold eye
ah
play it out
we're turning the outside
and that's on the other side right okay
so like this
if I shoot it there is it really gonna
land where it's supposed to land that
sounds really scary but it has to do the
same
put this whole construction here
do I shoot myself too maybe afterwards
[Music]
that's the fun part took you some tries
should I go together then
to see where it ends up at
this was finicky for you yes
or maybe it has to be in the exact
middle
kind of
what
wait me me I have to
[Applause]
I have to get up there too
[\h__\h] hell
ah damn it
anyway guys how are you doing today hmm
did the crystal make it it looked pretty
good but it was kind of going to the
left I'm not sure
but to me it looked pretty good wait
could it if it fell down then it
wouldn't it would have respawned inside
but if it landed then it should just be
here now right
no it's inside
okay
my hole was reset too
no because I am
um
because I teleported
[Music]
launch yourself to the ball
oh
my snack it's
um okay German people will understand
you know no bears
so there's actually
Columbus is pretty yummy there's a like
a Mana version of knoppers
I don't know why numbers isn't suing
manner honestly because it's so similar
normally Mana waivers right they're like
really normal wafers
but knoppers add like a layer
of like chocolate hazelnut cream of some
nuts and uh like some white cream
Layer Two in between the wafers
that's not first for you
raise the hole here
and yeah so manner actually has when you
guys know Clippers
you found them in a store oh
amazing what in America
we duchy's no two let's go
that cheese
cute
what
is this
no they're really good
you know I like normal chocolate
sometimes
but other times
I really crave
um
some chocolate with a crunch like a
cookie to it
yeah yeah
[Music]
try number two
what that's
whoa where'd it go
that was very good very straight
nice
I'm back welcome back second try out
not bad
next let's have space
Ohio
yeah yeah I also pointed it like with
this uh spiky bit towards the front so
maybe that helped as well
um
now we'll have five
uh blessings so now I'm like hmm I want
three more
because it's so
so
OCD
yeah the plot I know well we'll probably
get to do
some
um
shrines on the way to the finale like I
mean with temples on the way to Temples
we had to do Shrine too
no we're doing the finale of course
of course we are we just started okay
you don't know about it really okay okay
but I want to also upgrade my armor
I don't have much time to him uh
uh
not much time to do other things
armor yeah upgrading armor good idea of
the show
where is the where is the another the
next last
one that I didn't find yet maybe
maybe in akala area
you guys know
where I can find
another one
um
oh
wait they even marked the ones that I
didn't find yet
thank you
[Music]
there's no one yes I have to wear it
down
um
that one most likely to I don't know
which one I didn't activate yet
um
this one I did
this one oh maybe I didn't do that one
maybe I didn't
there's a chance I didn't do that one
uh-huh
yeah I'll have to do another question
um
mmm so good
ah
I also have a sandwich for later
it's um
sandwich
foreign
should we ask here what they want
I feel like I I heard it before Sam
Dalian what do you mean sundelion nearby
what
wait on these
on these parts
look
um
oh
yeah weren't there like ah a lot of
ruins over there oh
yeah
wait it's getting less
ah here
hmm
well this tree is crazy there must be a
court of no
no eggs
wait wait where are these two millions
so far are there maybe
um
I see Splash fruit
all right my my bling bling
yo it's even growing on the ground
right next to it
mmm
[Music]
hit your brethren two new members
welcome
okay so let's ask the stable really
quick what they needed I feel like I
asked them before
damn it
I maybe already finished the quest
wait they're playing I finished it
I just need to transport them yeah I
know I finished it
yeah yeah
I'm sorry triply though I am making my
band members worry about me that way
what they really ought to be worried
about is our declining audience but the
Beating Heart of the stable truck just
pulls us once more three cheers for our
own beats
are they salubrious Beats
damn sometimes I make jokes with your
guys's names
it's funny when that works out
it's deliberius beats here
where are you
I don't see him
what's the one time I can Implement your
name you're not here
he's here
and there you're shocked
shocked face Facebook
I'm talking about you I'm talking about
you
I remember it's essential for our
signature soundtrack together we're not
just disable Trotters and my heart will
always be the stable glopers
I thank you
did Elsie lapping
get himself of membership or did he get
one gifted what
um
yeah I know I know
don't I have to bring you guys over
there
um yeah yeah
the bridge
ah
yo if the bridge is no good how about we
cross the river
YouTube YouTube is streaming in normal
European hours yep that's that's what I
do I always stream around this time
to the river all together now okay
do they not need help from me
[Music]
where are they
huh
are there
I am blind
what is it you need help of course you
need help
tell me
I thought it might not be so hard to
cross the river I see now that I was
mistaken
I've talked if we took off our braces we
also floated across the river the
current would run that planet around the
Great Fairy so new year yet so far
you don't know what to do
um
I mean
huh
I make bot
uh
how to make bot
ah
I make cupboard I think I try
uh
which side
points
[Music]
what does a boat need
this one sucks you just all hey I was
thinking to do that can you really do
that
why I pulled it really straight
huh oh well it doesn't fall over
we just use the fans
[Music]
um
uh question is
where will I go
okay so wait are these okay to be
underwater I don't remember
my pink yes
use their planks as a raft to put in
this
they work on the water okay
wait
then
I think the small one works
I'll just like put it underneath
I think
I don't know how that helps but somebody
said I should do it
um
the steering wheel I guess
I'll freak out of water touches the
bottom oh okay
steering wheel for me
that's gonna sink
well I mean I can't give it floaties can
I
make it wider so it doesn't tip over me
okay
I need one more of those
[Music]
um
not the small ones
huh
now it's lopsided though but two of
those don't make the other one the same
size right
or does it
no nice boat nice boat
[Music]
downtown
um
[Music]
quinoa was so depressed his things
so where exactly do I put the fans hmm
isn't this boat too wide at this point
that I can't even link
maneuver it properly
[\h__\h] what is it
why did I do that
you broke
put the fans on the wings
okay
you bumped the boat once oh my God
you're not the hero of Hyrule
well this is quite something I mean I
used everything
that was given to me
it's more than just save okay this is
this is quite something Let's Get It On
I overcome cute no
this is fine
yeah
[Music]
yeah they're sitting in it comfortably
why is it oh
it shouldn't be moving
can I still attach things
why does it move
okay oh it's not attached everywhere
sorry guys well you can just
go ahead
well [\h__\h]
yeah only one little spot to touch but
maybe it will still be fine maybe it
will be fine
guys
calm be calm
no no no no no all is well it's okay
just let me get on there and control
let's go
to the right to the right
oh man
why is it not floating guys
[Applause]
and did they destroy my
my building do I have to redo it
no okay
can I please attach it to
like four spots not just one
I don't know if I can
there's always only one
planks closer
the [\h__\h]
well man this is starting to annoy me
you guys too
stop overreacting
black monster
[Music]
I'm just preparing it
cooked it I hate if I cook now yeah with
the sundalians
sorry guys one second one second one
second one second
now right is that okay
plus 15. that's more than it usually
would be
I did that on purpose one less that's
12.
thank you
it's too much should I make less
yo yo perfect perfect
get some variations going
oh this is perfect blood moon is helping
me a lot here ah too late
hey
we're all of those crits can I still do
it because it's still red
probably not right
the music is gone
[Music]
15.
ah
[Music]
magical
no more meals
foreign
and make this last one
if if I'm like in between like oh [\h__\h] I
ran out of food can I like leave
wherever I am can I leave the place and
then
you know what
you guys are really annoying me
in there and I'll carry you
I'm not gonna run out of food okay
okay I do have portable stove Studio
okay okay okay
so I'm kind of doubting that it will
ever work so let me just carry you but
how do I get to the other side
it's not rocking it's very smooth okay
[Music]
some some said they did it like that
let me let me
get um
okay okay it looks good looks good looks
good it's working
yeah yay so I just have to get over
there
and then they will recognize where they
are
yay
[Applause]
so on necessary uh
[Music]
pretty we're getting more and more is
this the last one
another favorite task was harder than
the final boss
then I feel confident
[Music]
don't ever separate from your group
again
[Music]
I was the last one
oh wow
[Music]
we've done it
I think my heart just picked up the
tempo
who tried to try to cure for anyone's
malaise and mayonnaise
[Music]
a token of thanks
oh
yeah thank you
I'm inspired I'm beside myself of joy
thank you so much for not giving up and
forging on despite all the obstacles
obstacles every time the great fairies
emerged in response to our music it gave
us all in this troop confidence in our
plane
if you ever want to hear my beat stop by
a stable
if we're there I'll give you a rhythm to
remember
the show is not over far from it we're
just getting started we'll keep playing
and make audiences smile all over the
kingdom
it's up to us to pour all our thoughts
it's Felix into a music when we play
from now on I want their music to soothe
every traveler who comes to the Stables
not just the great fairies
I consider you would honorary member of
our
might I know your name
oh link oh that's what we can call the
hero who saved a grand trap
Holly will remember our grand Trope will
continue playing for one and all under a
new name where do stable Trotters no
more in order of this genuine hero we
will be the stable Heroes
huh
we finished this question
on the last day
of me streaming it What a Feeling oh my
God uh intoxicating the beat of the drum
has lit a fire deep in my heart
what about you can you feel like are you
ready for more allow me to enhance your
clothing
to the maximum min max my clothes yes
let's go ah
so many bugably more I shouldn't have
fused so many oh
[\h__\h]
okay I can't do a full set huh
chill
she's taking me
is this the set you want I mean it's the
one that I already have the furthest
ah
let's see I mean because otherwise the
only sets where I have like full sets
are like the heat one and the cold one
and the desert one
so I feel like for me the smartest would
be to just do the basic one
you know but I can't I don't have any
more vocal blend horns
will I need the Heat and the the cold
one at all and the finale
um no hmm
hmm
Helen is enough
well at least we could do one
I would need
four more horns to get this one up to
maybe we can
I don't know if we have time to kill a
couple of white vocal Blends maybe I'll
find some on my
Journey to the finale
okay all right then let's focus on the
finale
even though I don't want to
uh what are we gonna do
which one this one I guess
um
do I talk to
Tower in the Lookout Landing
where do I need to go
ah oh follow the ring ruins Quest oh God
damn it
I am close to the end I can finish it
today
I've been told I can so I will
the thing with the lighting area I did
that and I I got something
sandalia nearby
oh I think I know where but no it's okay
now
five more streams can you guys
believe in me
it's a for that there's
another like quest for the quest or
how do I know where to go next
foreign
no
this one
okay
and you don't have to charge the tie I
found in the dragon pillar runes and
offered to nitrage at the altar a fork
of lightning heralded the appearance of
a new Sky Island okay
is it close by
I'll just go here
okay
go to fair and Scott where is fair in
the sky
the ones that look like a dragon on the
map Islands
that didn't
uh
I didn't notice anything like that
[Music]
oh okay
how did I
huh okay
uh can I get there through the Skyview
Tower or do I want to go to the shrine
because I cleared the storm oh
I use Skyward Tower okay
these ones
well it looks like there's still some
cloudiness there but
besides that
let's go do we start at where do we
start there's a like a lower one down
there but I'll try to get to the pond
one
it's stormy here too do I have to wear
my like special helmets
this one
oh yeah probably
Thunder head aisles
wait
[Music]
I have shock resistance but should I
still take off my
on a feather helmet you mean this one
it doesn't nullify it oh
I have the tights too
um
I'll just take off everything
but just got the helmet from the quest
before I feel like I should be wearing
it I don't know
yeah why is it not daytime
[Music]
should be daytime
I can't see
what I do here do I just go to the Head
probably
is this the head no
yeah we'll probably have to go to the
eye
it's the eye of the Dragon it's the
friend of the fights
let's draw something cool on the way
some islands are higher
can't see
oh
why would somebody put that here
it must be constant lightning strikes oh
Mama Mia
thank you valuina
hello
does the lightning not affect you
lucky
lightning is so scary
bad weather is so scary
those are interesting structures
these things
am I going back no just looks the same
as the other one
Lily
I hear
thunderstorms are the best times for
naps should be so loud so scary
it freaks me out
sometimes it gets really really scary
and I can't sleep
oh
okay what the [\h__\h] is this
I have to do something with that
I should charge it maybe or is it
charged right now
oh wait electricity has to be sent over
here
Maybe
hit it with my thing
purposefully wait can I do it really do
though
[Music]
huh oh I should be on it I guess
I need you need to read you
should
[Music]
yeah okay cool
you know generally like I guess
this could be compared or is a similar
thing
um
like the
oops I think that all the paths too
uh shrines not shrines but temples
dungeons
have been really cool the paths really
nice truck for it also is oh really ah
oh boy I can fall down here and then
come back up
how nice
yes the foreplay
yeah don't you agree like some of the
paths were really cool
the the one for the how do I make this
jump
one for the groans
even had like a boss fight which was
really easy but still kind of cool
and the the path for the the water
dungeon was better than the water
dungeon
oh
it really gets your hopes up
close one I thought it was long enough
there it is
half up to the winch exactly that one
too it was really hype jumping bouncing
I felt intimidated
does he want to fight me
but I don't want to fight him
maybe he thinks I would appreciate
the ownership of his
stick
I think my my chat is broken again at
least on my side
probably because I'm using YouTube chat
not at a studio chat not the normal one
today
oh yeah they give those all of that was
really cool too
um
what is this
oh it will open up I guess
all right let me try with the shock
fruit
I never use it anyway
this one
ah
okay that one stays open
[Music]
oh I wonder what you get for this one
uh
[Music]
um
I need to get back up
oh your balcony plans doing my they're
not doing so well
I don't know there was like it was my
chat is still dead I just read off of
OBS there was um
you know I was like taking care of them
properly I was pouring enough water and
then after I poured a lot of water on
one day
immediately after it was like this big
big big
rainstorm
and it added so much water
to my balcony plans that it legit killed
like half of them so sad
I'm trying to keep them alive
desperately
um
yeah they got drowned literally
let me open different YouTube chat
because this one's ridiculous YouTube
studio YouTube chat is ridiculous
YouTube hello
what
okay
enable
there we go
usually pots have holes yeah I mean I
think mine do that I have that too
um
that was way too much water
but
one of them is
the one that was already carrying fruit
it's still carrying fruit I mean you
know the tomatoes
still there
resilient one yeah I don't know if it
will continue
changing its color from green to
red eventually I hope so
ah give me I want uh I might hey
straw right he attacks of his head I
actually never saw that before oh nice
wait but come here because I
I want your material no oh wait that's
good
[Music]
oh my God that's the one thing
that is sometimes like really not
helpful with the
with the it's not the Saints
the Sages
they just push the important enemies
down
did I do that one already
yeah okay there's more enemies on top
there's a rail
that I probably have to take
aha but oh there was no cart here was
there
oh
I'm just gonna build my own
um
[Music]
and did I never save like a card a
proper one
yo
am I blind I don't see a base card
you don't think a cart works yeah
I mean there's this thing hey
well how does that I don't think that's
gonna work
oh there's a construct over there
you know what
um
I will
cheese
that's the hint oh I should do a tea
again
yeah I'm gonna
I'm gonna fight well I could make it
without
possibly
wait look at that isn't that the eye
already the eye of the Dragon
also isn't this a level one
how much damage did I do hi I'm here
hello
[Music]
oh that's a level three one
yo I already did so much damage
he's stomping
he do that enough
oh oh I almost
I almost misused it
thank you
ah wait I'm I'm like fumbling I'm
fumbling I'm fumbling
hello
[Music]
[\h__\h]
no no let me go
um
where's the downstairs must be on the
back of his head
wait uh
I know I could I could unbuild the whole
thing
I got it eh
let me get one of my good weapons so I
could also use this one
the pulverizer unfortunately it's not on
a donut weapon
because I didn't have anything else
oh oh oh oh
foreign
I remember still when I had like no idea
how to deal with this phase
so lost whoa this does a lot of damage
too
this weapon
hide under it and let the light oh wait
that's an interesting genius idea
wow I didn't think of that
Sam oh
another map
um
maybe in my free time after I'm done
finishing the game
okay now I have something to fuse it
with
this
is hell yeah that is powerful
oh wait no it's not even that good 47.
thought that would be stronger
oh well oh well it feels strong
ah okay
they even like do it for you here is
this already complete this is can I
really use it like this
I think so
or do I have to attach the side ones too
noise
okay
but
couldn't I already reach the eye easily
by flying down there or is this just
like extra for exploration if you want
to see more
you could probably shorten it
there's a shrine nearby half Ascend
ready oh
oh wait
[Music]
thanks for telling me
should get me in
oh
thanks for telling me
The Joker that's using shrine
yeah just in time yeah
you took an account that there would be
some delay oh
blessing no no okay ah
we are the naked people again
we only get two sticks
them and there's so many okay let's try
to be sneaky
ah
okay come here
no sneaky
no sneaky for me
at least these two they know me oh
maybe I can feel something
I know
yeah that's fine
he already forgot me violence is the key
yes yes I have enough Hearts to just oh
yeah true but I still don't have a
second bro
I mean I'm gonna wait until he wait
where is he going
[Laughter]
yeah
I want to do a sneak strike
got good ears even though there are no
ears
so far
[\h__\h] whatever
I ain't got time for this
easy a lot more damage than without the
attachment to
cross jumping is silent oh
[Music]
wait there's still so many
oh my God
okay
we can't reach the materials right now
oh God
oh one hit
that one's so strong though
oh
whoa wait that was a decent weapon maybe
although wait it's weak but it has shock
emitting
ah
okay that made him lose the weapon
what you gonna do what you gonna do oh
you're gonna call your friends
oh we got a uh the banks of a sword
sick moves Wawa
one left
Oh I thought there was more
this is the one up there yeah
I got no shock fruit so let's see if we
can get in with the horn
yay
um
I got this it's been two years thank you
man bye thank you
FPS boob
[Music]
oh yeah in this kind of game I I enjoy
the FPS
there's like a practice officer no no it
doesn't I'm just good
I'm just that good
[Music]
27 FPS version
will I need this
it just takes up space in my inventory
should I you guys recommend me bringing
it with me
nah
as long as I don't carry the
metal weapons and stuff
probably good right
okay
I would have appreciated I don't know
a speed or a defense or attack boost
anything
really
any advice how I did it honestly I
really just forced myself
I brute forced my knowledge I I gaslit
myself and everybody around me
I faked it until I made it I'm really
not a good
example I always say this
I was just like reading things and when
I couldn't read something like a kanji
I would just copy paste it
because I was too lazy to learn like
purposefully
so I just like copy paste
what I couldn't read
put it into
like a room odomaji fire
um
and then pretended that I already knew
it
so really not a good example
what do you get in this machine this
this must be a special gotcha machine
but you know maybe I could compare it to
me learning uh hunger Korean signs
is that worth it is that worth the
trouble probably not
oh
I didn't know it does that
wow
um I can swim past them
yeah yeah so with hunger
I I couldn't do the same thing that I
did with Japanese
and I I definitely
had my my struggles my fair share of
struggles I tried using some apps where
you can where it's not focused on the
language study but just on the Hangul
study the the writings are you
[\h__\h] off
I'm just gonna leave
[Music]
foreign foreign
yeah I don't know you just have to brute
force it
it's easier when you're like really
motivated
when you really have a passion for the
language that you're learning
space me out you little [\h__\h] Mike
star Shield okay
it's on
can't see it
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what is that
give me back my
and where's my shield
cool but where's my shield
wait let's go
why link wasting my time like that um
[Music]
did he spit it that far
is it here
just give it to me
[Music]
sorry this is really painful for me too
I actually just went back inside because
I wanted to go up here
mm-hmm
okay where do we want to be
sent to
but honestly I'm
gonna go straight to the eye at this
point
because we don't have that much time and
I all the items I'm receiving
so far I don't feel like I really need
them
I'm just guessing that the eye is where
we need to go
was it sit on that just got heated
uh
[Music]
yeah I don't see it but I think it's
below
[Music]
here
so I would think
that that's where I need to go
dark
there's a shrine there oh
I'm dead as Spirit oh oh where will it
land okay
just a little bit of light is that a
cork no
whoa
what a weird bird
send aliens oh and it's finally daytime
we can get some extra sundelions here
that is the stand bulb
more meat more meat oh what's this
[Music]
big hearty radish I never got it before
why kill fellow burp that was not a
chicken we are allowed to
take non-chickens for ourselves
hey
stream hearty radish
okay what do we got here
[Music]
it's magical mysterious music here
trying
was it a shrine or is it something else
it's nice that they give you a couple
more sundalians here because
who knows I might really need them just
chill out
those burps are so panicky oh
another one
they're preparing you for the finale
generous yeah
what's this
[\h__\h]
good job good job
that's exactly how you do it
hmm
you guys clumsy
[Music]
oh
tumbling oh
[Music]
swine
you thought I wouldn't find you huh
behind those Vines oh no that's actually
not where you're supposed to come from
okay okay let me do this rhino
yeah
we broadcast those fun thank you guys
for always tuning in to the rebroadcast
yeah
big task kalu I'm glad you enjoyed those
two I think my my set list was really
good for that stream personally at least
you know I always try to give it a
variety too because I know like
some people
you know don't like certain kind of
music and I I see sometimes some
chickens are like I don't like the songs
you chose
some the other day I even saw it on
Twitter like when reply was like I'm
gonna skip this one because previously
you never sang songs that caught my
interest so I'm not coming to this one
and I'm like okay I'm not gonna Force
you but really is it that bad like I'm
really trying to mix all the songs I
don't know so many new songs but I don't
think that's really necessarily what you
want try to mix Angie songs and Poppy
songs I'm not gonna sing heavy metal
but I don't know I've been trying to
sing a lot of songs that you guys would
know
um but I don't know if that's not
still not satisfying and I don't know
what to do man
also nice um
a shrine just a blessing
no I don't know I want to make it
enjoyable for everybody but
um
rap and meme songs and some legendary
songs oh there's a statue here yo wait
can I get a heart I think so
I don't know if I can get two though I
might be able to get two
I have one more
is this the last
Shrine I'll be seeing hopefully not
can't please everybody
for blood yeah some Vocaloids and J-pop
some non-j-pop some K-pop
boys back strings back all right
[Music]
um
can't satisfy everybody yeah but I don't
understand
what's wrong with my karaoke I like my
choices
hello open door please
is this because I skipped something
am I not gonna be able to open the door
or do I push
walk up to it
nothing's wrong with it thank you oh
yeah there's hands there
oh and they even look like my hands
but only like my one of my hands
link you need one more
there's no that no it can't work on the
left side wait what it takes my heart
you guys didn't tell me that
how many
can't be that much
one two three oops oh that wasn't so
much cute
Vitality check
hmm
oh oh is that a new headdress again
I thought I was gonna be wearing you
know
this one oh no yeah or another this one
I thought that's what I was going to be
wearing
um
Spore law a lot
oh
Birds Eye
uh-huh
just like the shrine lights
link
Zelda's house
Sonia
better
well I take this too
oh
how
like the shrine stones
well can I wear it
guidance from ages past
pick up
I guess I'll have to put it on a glider
there they are there's so many
oh even like put up so nicely for once
foreign
I know I could Auto build but I don't
know if I have the thing that I want
to put everything ready for me yay nice
I did not tell you to do this
you should have it yeah I probably do
build my own things one last time
fire
memories sake oh and there's another
Godzilla machine here too I didn't see
oh there's a um wait a second
um
we must take these opportunities to get
some free Rockets
now that we don't have to
carry
those anymore I can put on my normal
Shield again what am I doing what am I
doing what am I doing what am I doing
what am I doing
um
here
rocket Shields get oh yeah free Rockets
hmm
what do we have here
must be pretty
high-end stuff steering sticks okay I'm
high-end but the stuff that I use a lot
well literally just fans in the steering
sticks
why did I get like a million of those
two things and not whatever else should
there uh be
let me check
yeah I love the steering sticks you
always need steering sticks
oh gliders is literally what they have
here ah Anthem the carts
okay
take off
we're going down
those tiny islands are interesting
foreign
take off
takeoff is now
my batteries I really don't have so much
batteries huh oh
let me go to spend aliens bye-bye
wait I still need this thing I just
realized
can I
I'll wait
is this
occasion that I once showed you
but I was like I wonder what this is
this looks like it'll be important later
you guys said yeah it will be important
later
oh
okay it won't move
wow that was very much later
a lot later
[Music]
foreign
um welcome to later now is later
it is the future and it is the past
take it take it
do I really have to place it
properly on my own
the shrine Stones also always get like
place
for me
wait which way anyways
[Music]
ah okay
decent placement
guys by the way um in the description
there's a link to my merchandise that is
that you can keep up seeing on the top
right of my screen if you're interested
the link to buying the merchandise is in
the description it would make me very
happy if you would buy my birthday
merchandise
just saying
you know YouTubers and streamers they
always plug their [\h__\h] I should do that
more often too
if you already did then you're the
greatest I love you thank you
you are paying my rent and you are
paying for my music videos
thank you and at the same time you're
getting some really cool merchandise
that you can actually use for things
like taking a shower because I've been
I've Been Told
oh that's my the bath towel is not as
big as I thought it was gonna be and I I
didn't realize until now when it's way
too late
because I asked for the biggest beach
towel they have and I just you know
Gemma told me the size once and I I was
just like I don't know I was probably
tired at the time and I didn't pay much
attention to the numbers
I just thought they would follow my
instructions of a big beach towel that
you obviously want to lie on
um
yeah now it's just so tiny
presenters hmm
where are we going taking me
I must hurry because I have a stream at
midnight yep
it's overnight weekend I know
no no one reason I that Gemma told me is
because the blanket was so big so they
want to have a different
size obviously it would be a different
size anyway even if you make it a big
beach towel because the blanket is
really wide it was never gonna be as big
as the blanket but that was an argument
like oh because we want to separate it
from the blanket size of course
are we in the underground oh yes we are
can you find this by accident
or is it like closed off I would hope so
um
oh we did keep the shipping uh decent
price like not only for this but also
for the anniversary
nice
trying I'm trying to keep the shipping
small that's why uh
I think it's it's it's actually uh not
too expensive right yeah yeah
even though there's a big plushie in it
um
2 000 Yen for you oh nice nice nice
there's a white vocal balloon
[Music]
thank you
I want to kill him
and where's uh he's so far
I need to kill him
it's my mission oh I still don't have so
many good weapons
what
blurry rush out of nowhere
oh yeah slap him slap him silly nice
reflect I was 100 on purpose yeah
did it have
did it drop when I wanted
yes okay I think so
um
might want to go back to the the thing
but I'll probably still it's not so
urgent right I'll still get more chances
right
seven thousand five onion shipping
oh but honestly I'm actually like
I want the yen to improve itself I'm
waiting for it
it's been very long
because my my my salary comes in and Yen
and then gets a
uh changed into
um Euro right I lose so much I don't
want to complain but it's been like this
for like I don't know how long a year or
more
um
it's nice for other people but I I'm
like not assumed amused I mean I'm not
amused what the [\h__\h] are we doing how do
I place it there again right
I know it's okay
I placed it again
okay I thought this was where it has to
go what the [\h__\h]
no I I wouldn't mind just keeping it in
the end but it automatically gets
exchanged when it goes on my bank
account
um
and then it's so sad
I'm so sad why is the Yen so weak for so
long
can you go up there
what's the matter what like is there a
reason
shouldn't it already have calmed down by
now
oh they're trying to devalue it
Nanda and I don't know
it's good like when you travel to Japan
I guess because you get more value
but the other way around is rough
my name is
geisters
those pieces
well I am not the fifth Sage
for me
build
say put those clothes on me
that is me the headers
gas lit myself into
it
when Bank of Japan is keeping interest
right now and the fed and European
Central Bank hiking rates
the yen is Diva okay I do not understand
that
can we build her stacked yo little [\h__\h]
usual room horny Bonk
wait where over there there's something
where the green lights are
basically
[Music]
luggage growth even going into pandemic
so they were hit especially bad
just trying to keep a positive Groove
interesting
the rootlets I don't know where they are
yeah it's been so long left leg it's
even cold look at that left leg the pole
oh excuse me um do you have stock of
like one leg for some robot lady
just one yeah I get the other leg and
the right leg the PO thank you
nothing there
where is the leg
give me
you only have right legs left well I
guess I mean that shouldn't be
yeah it's not ideal but it shouldn't be
complaining right about having two right
legs at least you can walk I'm sure you
can walk with two right legs
of course you can
we'll make it work I mean that shouldn't
stop us
excuse me where is the leg
going on
what am I moving
on this way
that's so slow I forgot the leg
and then see it
huh
by the way
is that the leg
on the inside of it
doesn't look like a leg
Acy on him
what
wait
come back up here please
just a weird box that's all it is oh
okay we have to fix the the other Bridge
part
why is there a steering wheel
and that
rocket
it's not rocket science
wait so they want me to get something
out of here
[Music]
the gliders oh do they want me to fly it
out of here what is the bridge for them
yeah
but I feel like you could place a glider
on top of the bridge
and fly off
yeah okay yeah you just have to
like the wrong direction
oh yeah I get it
Rock should I use Rockets
hey I don't wanna that's so I don't feel
any control over what I'm doing
all right
we can use it for the other parts too
reuse
one rocket works
I guess
okay
[Music]
wow away maybe this is too heavy
actually I don't know
whoa it feels heavy somehow
well let me try
foreign
[Music]
maybe it's stuck
come on
and it's suddenly so quiet
it's so quiet in my ears
okay
oh wait what if I add Rockets
not only Rockets
Adam
I'm scared
of how far I will fly
let's go okay wow ow
uh
where's the body
wait where is the body
why that's where I came from
I am so confused
there it is
can I use it again
wait why is that there what is that
look at that
wait does that work
that was before why is there a laser
here now
as extra
oh for a chest oh
I don't need it
huh my
my staring stick is gone
or did it go why did it break off
it's in the water oh
it's too late
here we go again I'm surprised the
Rockets are there
I stopped it before they could break off
amazing see this is perfect service
right at your doorstep I deliver your
left leg take it
oh
it's blue
I feel like I'm playing this doctor game
but like the other way around I'm not
like extracting body parts
and putting them in there is
like a temple because you have to do
four things
it's basically a temple no
a dungeon I mean
in German it's Temple I think
um
I mean you can't really see it like a
temple map but you know
okay where's the other one over there
now I can't take off properly
can I
I want to take off
[Music]
wait I'll just put
um
one of these underneath
easy
I remembered
let's go
let's go up to the Green Room up there
nice
oh there's also one there
uh I'm
fat
I wanna keep it I put ah
ah
I put many materials into it I don't
want to lose it now
um
guys random topic did you guys watch uh
this anime movie called Blue thermal
what let's go I saw it a second ago
no I watched it in the airplane they had
like anime movie and it was called Blue
thermal blue anime
God I really like that blue thermal blue
salmon blue formal
yeah I'm speaking anime to you
fascinating
in here
left arm
it's about
um this girl who joins like a university
and in a university
uh there's clubs and one of the clubs
that she wasn't really planning to join
[\h__\h]
um is is a a pilot school but not for
normal planes it's like what do you call
those planes that they don't really take
off on their own they need to be taken
off by some other machines or another
play in a proper plane
yeah the glider yeah yeah
and she joins the university and she
goes to this like
uh in the beginning it's still very
beginning so don't worry it's not a
spoiler but she goes to this
um
like Festival where they introduce it
they introduced all the different clubs
that you could join and she was
interested in some but then she bumps
into uh or like well something happens
and she breaks the glider
basically
really [\h__\h] expensive new glider
and she's devastated she's so
embarrassed and they are really pissed
off like why would you you little [\h__\h]
yeah
wait ah
wow
and then because of that she kind of you
know joins the club and then you see her
journey of you know Finding Love for
something she didn't know she would love
and
um
hooks
yeah getting really freaking good at it
and it's just a really heartwarming
sweet interesting inspiring
little anime movie no
can I still use my uh
my my my my my my glider
I wonder
this thing is huge
numbers
now let go of the glider
but what do I do then there's some stuff
here
I wait
okay what does that mean
I don't know is it doing something
I was thinking yeah should I use the
this box as the actual base
for a boat
and then should I turn this around
though
oh wait now it's like not moving it all
because it stopped at a certain spot
is this what I want
I don't know what I'm doing
how will it move
I need the I need the fan in there
I mean I can use my own fans
yeah look at the wheel
oh the wheel
that wheel do I need it
[Music]
okay
yeah speaking of movies
so actually it's not about another anime
movie
I was talking to Ina
and she told me that next time she goes
to Japan she wants to
um
check out this
week
check out this new anime movie I'm like
oh one one one
and she tells me let's keep please
does this work
it's releasing a new one
foreign
no idea and then she was like also like
telling me Oh yeah the thing is
they
um
did not use any money
to advertise it at all
because I guess they ran out of money
yeah
from
making the movie in the first place what
the [\h__\h]
I would say so too they're famous enough
to not even need promotional style but I
never heard it's about to come out and
then there's not even a real teaser of
the movie guys
because I looked it up on
on YouTube
I was like well okay I'll look into it
that's interesting maybe I'll watch it
too when I'm in Japan
sir
they're just I don't know relying it's
huge risk right they're just relying on
people who haven't heard of it and maybe
telling others
um
I would have had no idea
what am I doing
[Music]
I feel like it's like almost working but
I
hmm
help me please
I've been waiting for it for years
I did it what
they did it on purpose he doesn't want
to promote it
why why
we have a memorial
production yeah but doesn't Ghibli have
done money for it
so then um
wouldn't he want to promote it
especially when it's his last one
set box vertically
yeah about this
how is it gonna dry
help me
one guy I was looking for that
I'm talking about the movie you know
just one person told me the solution
which is not
like that then wow
90 what's 90 degrees I don't know what's
90 degrees
huh
well which way
I don't like those red oh my can it be
easy
somebody said something
like do this
I think that's what you meant
oh
the band put the wheels in its place
okay
like this
or shouldn't it be
isn't it like rubbing on the ground
I don't get it how's this gonna work
not like this
[Music]
oh man
I did not place it there
you saw me guys you are my witness
game is trying to decide for me
multitasking I was telling a story
anymore so I'm I want to watch the
Ghibli movie too and I'm thinking you
know because I I watched the movie with
uh coyote and kanatas and honey
before last time
in like February I'm thinking maybe I
can call them again we'll be like our
own movie watching gang
I'll ask them if they want to watch it
again on like different movie obviously
but
if they want to go to the cinema with me
again huh
I see
um
a movie club yeah
yes yes we're gonna watch the gameplay
but like because
but I think it's based uh you know I
said it's based on a novel no Nobel
Nobel
so if you read that I guess you would
know
did I guess this right
who's that for anyway
thought it just drives over to me then
it will open the gate huh
what's that for us
ah wait something like where I took them
from I don't remember how that was
yeah like this
reverse
Shane is just a train that doesn't open
the doorbell so
um
Ultra hand to recall on the door what
Wheels
all right
it doesn't get higher but we'll keep it
keep it keep it keep it keep it keep it
keep keep
up
yeah I'm not gonna um
the game is bullying me
okay and now the rest we have to carry
it
oh oh wait ah
um
what
huh
no floaty
when I come with you
what I thought this would be a water
slide experience for me too what the
hell
I've been bamboozled
yeah
it's so
shallow
s what is it
ah where did it go oh it's there
it's gonna end up at its destination on
its own right I don't have to
I didn't check my
stamina
but this is how you for free get a full
wheel of stamina bag
nice
so does the water flow oh
where I wanted to go
by the way do I have like
some speed food
because I'm concerned wait where's it go
I'm very concerned that I mean I will be
stressed out by the time
it's in the water ah there's my piece oh
it died off but I at least found where
my pieces hmm you'll be fine I thought
the Red Bulls were no no no no no I'm
worried about the time not about my
tiredness but yeah that'll be um
useful too at the end because the stream
is let me down I am counting that by the
way as my Monday streams
yeah I look yeah because I'm not
planning on really streaming tomorrow uh
I have some plans for tomorrow
um
but I'll stream on Tuesday
yeah
but so for the Bingo I'm wondering
can I get seven days in a row if I count
that as a Monday stream
we'll see I'll have I'll have to like in
the end they said that we can be very
lenient about it I can basically decide
for myself if I I think that I
uh you know finished something then you
know
and I'm not gonna cheese it you know the
funny thing is when they were explaining
um when we were rehearsing and they were
explaining this thing to us this Bingo
thing I haven't been there right
um they were like Yeah so basically you
can decide it on your own and for
example when it says barbecue if there's
a game that you play where you play
where you do barbecue then basically
that counts too
so
you can be very creative you can be very
you know whatever
there's a Bengal thing yeah um for the
summer for the whole summer they created
for us and for you guys too you can do
it too
like a bingo sheet with summer themed
things partially
that if we complete it apparently we're
gonna get a reward that has not been
decided yet
yeah
it hasn't been decided yet
apparently
but it'll be something nice they said
that's what they said
so that's that's not motivating isn't it
apparently there will be something I
don't know what
General it's also just fun I guess to do
it even if there wasn't a reward and
yeah so they were explaining it and when
they were saying like oh yeah you can do
basically anything and if you say that
counts and it counts We're not gonna
like check everything
We're Not Gonna check if you guys
actually did everything but there should
be proof
like on the stream or on Twitter you
don't have to do everything on stream
you know
just try to have some kind of a proof um
yeah
and then Aqua Senpai started
anything together they started like
pointing at every they were reading
everything off and they were like oh oh
I can do this in Minecraft and I can do
this this is
[Applause]
they kept on like ah Minecraft this is
also Minecraft there's also Minecraft
that's awesome
not Minecraft
Roofing
unbelievable
stop changing Jason try to do some bangs
outside of Minecraft come on
foreign
no no I don't have to do all of them
right just five that are in a row
business
this is
what is this
who's this
okay
I gotta give it to them this is the most
difficult dungeon
so far in the whole game
yeah I have no idea what's going on if I
have a thunder helmet then it's a oh
hold on I'm so strapped this one
can I use that
foreign
mine not working
I don't know
I went
oh oh
let's go it is a bridge for me now I
have three pieces actually
grab the arm which arm is there an arm
what time local
where's the arm
did I miss it again yeah
is it here
it's so dark for me
at the start
and on the other side
oh no then I can't really use the bridge
can I because I can't carry it on top of
this
put it on top
wait is it down here or is it just in
case you fall down because there's a
where's the where's the arms
oh
this is not the first time that I'm
ignoring the body piece
oh
oh can I launch it on here though
that's not enough to launch it is it
did you carry it can I really
please
link
suddenly he just walks over it with ease
cccc
outside
while we're turned on God mode
okay how are you supposed to do I don't
know I don't wanna know I will never
know
is there some uh-huh they want me to
build a car
to roll it down
more muscle cars the more the merrier
I have a strong affinity
to building cars since my childhood
I used to be a car mechanic when I was
five
yes you don't believe me
why there's nobody believe me when I put
one on the wrong way
yeah they didn't compute the game yeah
one of my favorite games for my Johnsons
it's it was so fun you you repair cars
that look like [\h__\h] and then you drive
them around this village where you and
like help people and then you bring it
to the car show and then you can win
prices
if your car was cool
um
wow
please
man children games so fun
okay let me add a steering wheel
I like how even though it's kind of
annoying to me they make you
now at the very end
like build again build a lot of things
that you learned that you supposedly
learned throughout the game
make you solve riddles
in ways
that you should have adapted over the
time well I obviously didn't because I'm
trying to cheese everything
but it's cool yeah yeah
if I had more brain cells then this
would be amazing
but I don't so
that's what you get
oh yeah muscle car yeah yeah look at my
right baby hi
what are they doing there
excuse me I am on a business trip I have
some business to do if there's a white
you guys then I could consider fighting
you
put the family yeah cause I heard um
um um an opinion about the finale being
really emotional so I'm having high
hopes for it
and I mean a lot of things already felt
kind of emotional to me so I I can
imagine it living up to
that expectation
[Music]
um
I'm just assuming that I will be very
sad not only because the ending will be
so good but also because I don't want
the game to end
um link
foreign what if she's manipulating me
and actually once I activate this thing
it will try to kill me
hmm
what do we do then also where is the
last one because I went to that one
oh right down okay there must be like
one here right
blue light
wait it is that one it has to be
No One spoilers chat please
well I can go backwards incredible
can I reach about my car
I obviously don't have a license
it's so dark where are the other rude
trout fruits
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
that looks like it could be an entrance
[Music]
await it's activated
because of the arrow
ah
one big turn around
nice driving boss thank you
it was so fast
I mean we gotta get up pretty high huh
oh
I wonder
that thing should I just fly up
but they always give you materials
for
what you need so
normally at least
[Music]
should I just make balloon
there's a root there
okay I make balloon
which one
this one
[Music]
it's very cheap
oh but it needs fire
I can go to the root on the left is
there a path up there
okay
it's up so high
fire emitter Dooku haven't used one in a
while
but then I can't
far from the entrance no
I fire weapons you know I think it's a
scent for the yeah but um
but
to wear
I'm gonna try to get to the
root uh
I don't see it anymore
on it
is it up there
ah and I see the bones
nice shot oh
goodbye balloons
I've been making so many things and just
immediately give up on them and drop
them
today at least
it's okay it's
It's The End
do I have some more speed food I don't
think I do
damn it
should have made some sweet food
if you want to finish today you might
just start want to start hover biking
am I am I doing that bad
no
foreign
no okay
but you know I I wouldn't mind I doing a
second part but I just um I just don't
want to
end it at the spot where maybe I only
have an hour left of gameplay
but then I guess I'll just do a lot of
side stuff and then finish the game
but you know for as a streamer I just I
don't want to just do a one hour stream
you know
I can easily finish in free
that's a [\h__\h] weapon
before giving me confidence
super chess
maybe Super Chat stream on
the [\h__\h] was that
project stream on Tuesday dad opened up
a big part
wow
and it heals me
well that's why that is is that not it
must be cut off right this this black
part
surely it's cut off right
from the rest of the underworld
Underground
but just make September a superchargery
month
because of September there's my
anniversary so there will be even more
Super chatos
uh no I'll get these ones done until
then
[Music]
I reached the entrance
super Super Chicken
[Music]
I won't read it on Christmas no I I
always like get to it pretty fast don't
I
excuse me do we have a right arm or leg
I don't know I think leg
for me to pick up
this time don't worry I will not just
leave it there I see it I acknowledge it
it's right in front of my eyes I will
carry it
this one is easy to cheese oh more
cheese really
that already looked complicated to me so
I appreciate the cheese
foreign
this is the fan one
I see this
I acknowledge it
but
um
two
I mean okay maybe two can carry it
better but how is it supposed to go over
there
oh
where does it go
and but then again here's another one of
those spots
[Music]
wait give me give me give me ah
I have an idea I don't know if that's
the cheese idea or if that's the
intended way
probably not
we'll see we'll see
okay
I have many ideas
I know it fell down
I won't have one's enough
I want to put it on like properly
oh that that that's perfect
let her cook guys guys about my salmon I
wanted to say one more thing yeah just
you saw once again I made buttered
parsley potatoes and I just once again
want to say please please do yourself a
favor and try it if you haven't had it
yet it's so easy you cook potatoes
where's your peel potatoes
first you peel the potatoes
you cut up some fresh parsley
and then you
you
cook them yeah
in the water and then then they're done
right so you add you you get rid of the
water
okay
okay that's my problem I thought that
that wasn't there I was just gonna hope
that it stopped that that I can pick up
pick it up here you know what I mean
[\h__\h]
oh
yeah you put a lot of butter into the
pot after the water is gone yeah mix and
mix them add the parsley and then also
some salt you get perfect buttered
parsley potatoes so yummy mmm so good
actually I was surprised
that um the
the recipe for some reason it didn't ask
for
butter I don't know how the parsley that
would be so lame I don't know how that's
a premium recipe when it's just parsley
potatoes not buttered parsley potatoes
what the [\h__\h] we're in Austria we are in
Austria if you make parsley potatoes
they gotta be with butter it's just
it's right there
in front of your eyes
so much more yummy flavor
smooth texture on the potato
anyway apparently I didn't successfully
cheese it so
how does Jesus
I mean
I have like an ultra cheese idea like
you could take the the floating
platforms make yourself some stairs
probably that way you could bring that
thing up there too
or alter chase you could of course make
yourself like a flying thing and then
fly up there with it also
the Gap needs to go to the side ah
oh
[Music]
what
thank you for that very obvious
solution but this doesn't seem like it's
cheese necessarily
I saw wait
I hope I can reach it because what I
wanted to do is just grab
grab it here
that's what I wanted to do but that
seems intended doesn't it
oh okay
and now
why would you choose that it wasn't so
bad nintended
[Music]
cheese was more satisfying oh really
so happy and I'm I guess I guess I guess
I'm pushing against it
was that it
oh
is that it
[Music]
now there's gliders
I think this time okay that was it
okay
why does that one not go up so high
I want the glider
okay I'm too lazy to go up there
I'll just I'll just make my oh wait
because
broken well whatever I'm gonna make my
own glider [\h__\h]
[Music]
fine I'll do it myself
um I don't want that I just want the
simple one
no I don't have the one I want to make I
think no
but it's under the water or over the
water
okay that's okay I already took
everything out
then yeah
it is what it is
oh man that
[Music]
um
the time we played
isn't this too heavy it's the time we
played uh jackbox party games
I like the games this time more than
usual
hmm
do I need Rockets
why are there two tracks anyway
it's interesting to hear you know you
know because for the one where the
audience was voting
it was interesting to hear a lot of
those things
t-shirt one too I
I I just wanted to point out that I a
lot of the phrases that were chosen were
actually more afraid as I was pretty
proud I thought I was like doing so bad
generally generally with Jack books like
coming up with the things
fan is dragging on the ground oh okay
really I'm always so bad with coming up
with
[Music]
um
like witty things
but this time the sufficient
suffering or whatever and the other one
the other suffering one
Volvo Bells were from me and a couple of
others even some drawings from me got
used apparently because I got the the
top artist thingy
yeah with that game somehow I was like
really stressed out I was like I don't
know what to write I don't know what to
write I don't know
I just the sufficient suffering that
that one I typed in in like the last
second when I had two seconds left I'm
like I don't know
this is here sufficient uh suffering ah
that sounds like it works
yeah
even though English is not my first
language
[Music]
I'm finally
finally finally finally
I can
take part properly
[Music]
um
do my part by adding some funny stuff
I was so happy it wasn't to me when I
was frustrated about you know not
winning something it wasn't me being
frustrated about not winning
not really it was more like
I don't know I'm not really that
frustrated in these situations I often
just play it uh I have to say I play it
up what's the word
not like that obsessed with winning you
know I don't care that much
trying to
I know joke around the
oh my God I suck so much
but I was happy that I actually
got some things done quite well it's got
a cleaning sign
yeah I found out later on that there's
um in the in the newer party packs
there's some games where you can set no
American prompts or whatever
American focus problems
so I'll do that in the future I didn't
know about it oh my God
[Music]
I didn't know that
that'll be so helpful and then I
mentioned that after the Stream and then
I think gouda or someone they were like
no don't take away our advantage
that's the only reason why I'm doing so
well known
the stone
captain
[Music]
foreign
fighting machine
because I so far never created something
like this
a vehicle
[Music]
they can ride on minerals construct
oh I have to press let's go oh
that's really funny guard
left hand right hand back part what does
that do
and then attach things okay can I
okay
just checking if it can Dash work as it
can
so you want me to attach some things
here huh oh like that's supposed to be a
shield
the weapon so you can draw forth the
true power of this construct attach one
to a hand and your power in combat will
be magnific magnified several fold
the road to the secret stone is long and
I do artists
I recommend that you make stops at each
Armory along the way okay
get accustomed to operating this
construct so that you are prepared for
whatever you may face whoa
you can attach things to the hands or
back of minutes gone to the back too
the attached objects can augment the
constructs movement or combat abilities
yeah oh uh how ah
well
right hand I guess do we need the shield
so
and then on the back too
then I'm just shooting how can I even
active ah okay that's what the back part
though that's what Y is for okay okay
so I can shoot
from my back but doesn't that shoot
backwards
batteries
ah all right
why don't they see me as one of them
wow
this is very interesting I feel very
weak though
yeah yeah I did it I did it
wait is it reloading how's recharging my
batteries
also I can walk over the bloom right
foreign
still with three charges okay why are we
bothering with him
yeah that's pretty cool my original idea
at the end oh no hey
they're strong what is it
what
wait wouldn't it be cool if I could
catch
that might be pretty strong
oh I'm done okay I thought it was up too
high for him to get him I don't do so
[Music]
is this something you guys told me to
get some aliens for no right not not yet
right ah yeah
I'm broke actually oh
well
uh wait uh attached uh yeah
ah what did I attach something no
nothing sorry
[Music]
all right
can you get off and fight on your own
that might be faster
oh
[Music]
wow that's all nice
[\h__\h] I can use my ball oh
wow nice shot
all right
finally
[Music]
um
oh I can replace it easily though
[Music]
um
here this should be stronger I think
right
first I was trying to refuse it to this
but you saw how that went
that took some time you know too much
time
[Music]
all right they want me to do some stuff
here is that is that
is that build air
I stole my device when attached to a
concert's back can greatly enhance its
Mobility oh will we be faster
we have far to go before we reach the
temple with the secret Stone speech
would be wait if I attach a rocket does
it give me like a
boost
I can only do one right
okay
rocket hey let's be Rocket Jump
oh
okay can I fly doll
oh I don't think damage wait what did
that do for me I don't think what that I
don't think that was helpful
not right now at least
um
the fan is probably better right now
yeah it's like a little
boost so cute
um
there's a route close by so we can heal
[Music]
okay
takes so much
it's faster yeah should I just get off I
don't know like like the game wants me
to use no but it takes so much time
especially if I keep on bouncing these
enemies away from me
I mean it sucks in combat what do I have
her for then
oh wait am I all my all my things are
empty
my my
minions aren't helping either
okay
hmm attaching the proper weapon to this
concert will enable it to attack distant
enemies oh
take careful aiming the tide of battle
will turn in our favor
[Music]
but it's so close I don't I [\h__\h] help
hmm I don't want to use my Foods
all right 15.
[Music]
let me out
for my armor what do you mean
ah [\h__\h]
let me off
come on
[Applause]
I have no idea what's going on right now
like where everybody is and I'm just so
disoriented right now
wait there's a stone fused to the master
sword
when did I ah is it because I made it
into an X
[\h__\h] yeah
she used my
she used my rocket
oh right Shield
again
[Music]
I want to make a new one but these are
all
currently
not fused
let me use something right now oh
perfect
[Music]
um
wait wait oh why are you rolling down
[Music]
maybe a good time to reload
into the unknown
[Music]
because then maybe maybe I get some of
my hearts back too
hmm
where are we
oh
oh we're at a point where the enemies
have yet to really notice us
then let's change armor and be more
successful this time shall we
um
should I still try to kill them all
[Music]
Majora masks can skip them
I could I guess
but I need some I know
ah it's okay we can fight
what's my weapon oh
all right
wait a second
too dark for my taste
going back to work I'm working too what
a coincidence oh what's going on
let's use The Rustic Claymore I I saw
that coming actually
leave me alone
let me guess
[\h__\h] bastards
sometimes it's so annoying get the right
thing
okay
we'll make another one
all right
silver the silver coin would be good
uh
oh
it's like this
okay
is this
[Music]
wait let's add some stuff
oh nice Mountain
because currently there's nothing okay
you guys said
oh wait Cannon there's also cannons here
[Music]
let's attach that here and this
is it better on on the hand
Cannon is broken you mean in a good way
right
where did I see this uh
root
I once again don't see it
oh yeah
I guess I'm going this way oh whoa look
at those horror Blends am I supposed to
walk through there
ah
oh at least these they don't do Gloom
damage huh
here's my eyeballs for fighting the king
glioc in the future
and meters are best friends because she
doesn't do much damage those Springs are
funny
uh-huh
I know I don't want to fight with her
she can just
fight on the sidelines
follow me oh there are the horriblings
um
let's do another pot room
but we're in the Gloom can we get out of
there
Michelle
oh that was it nice
oh
I I have yet to see what it actually
looks like when she uses the the
cannon not the cannon I guess
whoa let's go
I can't answer that area
refuse something again
no blue horn it's probably not that
strong
oh well for now
best option
able for what's today what do you mean
to dig we're not trying to dig anything
now we already learned that yesterday
I kept on switching between universe
my bow
the root
let's go to the road
oh
get some healing too
whoa
on you
[Laughter]
sheesh
wait that felt extra strong because my
bow broke
I only have like Lino bows and some
shitty Soulja Boy Soldier ball
oh
ah that was not my aim okay
okay
yeah nothing but Savage lion balls well
you prepared well just like me
we'll be very very
prepared when it comes to bows for the
finale
you didn't bother to kill a single Lino
in the whole game
are you perhaps a chicken
yes you are yes you are a little chicken
I know I know it
nah I'm got him oh there's a he knocks
over there gloomy Knocks
oh they really want me to face
everything now huh
how nice of them
as long as they're placing the roots in
between for me to heal myself there
then we could
always throw you around now
which which color is that
Maybe
how does it a blue one how does it work
to do a sneak strike on a hemost
can I do that
no
why keeps on turning he's so confused
all right it's time to show you guys my
aim again
that video cow carrots
that was damaging my reputation as a pro
aimer and Pro Gamer okay
because my aim is not always that [\h__\h]
just saying
where's the eye
grab him grab him he's still occupied
with my my babies
very good very good
yo these two weapons I've had them for
like a million years
oh that's it wow
it's on my channel oh yeah I guess I
uploaded it
well I mean
I mean free clip I I should take it
but but it's hurting my reputation
Boomerang do you guys use the boomerang
weapons I
tried before but you have to throw them
and then they just
you just go everywhere
never
mind
but now I picked one up
big Boomerang best weaponing game are
you sure about
[Music]
you want more stuff huh you're so greedy
we're close to the secret Stone
draw four of the hidden power in this
concert and press onward
hell yeah
oh wait you still got one Cannon here
I'll give you another candle
show us those cannons
let's go
enemies don't go
so break this is there like a bone
thingy underneath
supposed to be broken
wait how do you
are you awake
is there
why am I why am I breaking this
what's for
mining Mecca
oh am I getting a path
can she climb because she's not in ghost
form yet
so yeah but if I go too far away
how will she catch up with me
can't climb okay so I have to do this I
suppose
and get a ghost
I can just go around it all well
can I open it up
I did it just for you mineru
for you
can you make it
oh yay
she gambled her way out of it oh
that is
a huge
mountain of sunlight
I mean
I don't think I'll be needing it anymore
[Music]
is somebody attacking us
oh yeah
let me get off
with the Cannons it's hard to fight them
look
it almost feels like subnautica oh that
game
I always was like a little bit
interested in it
I want to try it
and I still want to play rap I still
want to make a raft group
I'm playing Rap too
um
I never got to play it like everybody
got their groups I feel like in the end
there was like no wait could anybody
create a rap group in the end because I
saw so many Japan groups and ID groups
ah like mixed branches
yeah I know it just doesn't happen why
we ignored the the raft hype when raft
was fotm
yeah
nice so much so not holy [\h__\h]
um my Cannon broke
that's what he wrapped uh yeah well but
the thing is the four people Max and
horotoly is more than four people now
and then I always feel bad this is the
problem this was this was always a
problem with myth like there were so
many when it was only myth
and no console risk
um
it felt bad because there was only five
of us I felt bad to like
not include only one person you know
oh
now that it's more it's
uh something you can avoid yeah but in
the beginning there were so many games I
wanted to play
but I felt bad about you know excluding
someone
and why are there barely any five people
games that's why I think we should only
have four people Generations like The
Gamers gen
link that is the spirit Temple but this
construct cannot climb a share Cliff
face
okay okay
we well do I need more than one
maybe I need more than one
oh no
I have angered them
um
or did it count as a sneak strike
[Music]
and another one this is like if you have
a big group of enemies in front of you
just do this this is the easiest way to
clear them because the snake strike is
so powerful
thank you
right
damn
oh that didn't hit it
pops room small buds yeah both
well I played a lot around in the
beginning with the muddle buds but then
I thought well it takes so much time for
them to do significant damage to each
other
so in the end the the pap shrimps are
still open the op is Pink
but in my opinion
she can't do
fire can't she I hope so
rap supports up to eight yeah
really I thought it was always four
because people always played it in four
what
[Music]
get him get him gang up on him
nice collaboration
speaking of collaboration I saw that
whole look here they're already working
on like Kobo for example oh my God
[Music]
oh my gosh green was filled with water
on that screenshot
I wonder how long it will take them
and wait didn't they they didn't even do
they know yet though for example today
the second gen
so maybe they're doing 2nd gen and third
gen together
that would be really cool
[Music]
so we cleared that wave
ID patch wait wait they didn't have
first one either oh oh right
oh well that's super exciting
they said August oh that's so soon oh my
God I want to play ID gang well they're
working hard huh
they must be working hard on that
it's nine new characters right
guys this is not what we talked about
oh back rocking [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay back rocket
um
yeah I remember now that I was using
it on my back too yeah yeah yeah
let's go faster come on
can she really close this whole cup she
must be able to
oh
no comment try from the bottom okay
wow that was so close that's so mean
even more
kind of annoying well
that was the path to the spare tip what
about all those pieces I added to her
body those were like old little things
you have to activate in other temples
too for me
Nani
I don't upload the light for here
this is already the end
maybe it's the end already
okay it's all the spirit Temple okay
okay yeah yeah yeah
what are we doing
we need the tear right and the thing
the tear of the Wawa oh
a Scenic walk no no I did that hey let
me activate that
hmm tears of the wild one
sad one
and oh there it is
it looks so easy to grasp we did not
have a boss fight yet and that looks
like a big area for a boss fight but
it's all gloomy and I don't have
good weapons on Mineral now
is this what I needed the food for
for this for later okay okay
my weapon choices don't matter
weapons on the ground huh
yeah yeah
it's me
but gloomy this is
glue
let's talk to my phone it was once
poison
um
what what are we how are we
which is
just punch each other with our hands
[Music]
I don't know about that
what I don't do damage
thank you
what am I doing
[Music]
sorry panic panic hands
oh terrain fight
but if you get it right once it really
does it backfired on him
she really does good uh damage there we
go there we go
there we go yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh
yeah
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh I see some stuff there
oh
my God
wait I'm coming
and another one and another one yeah
okay
oh there's more spiky balls
okay I I get it now
we're just gonna keep on repeating that
huh oh face too
phase two phase two
I thought I finally figured it out
longer arms
more arms
[Music]
you think that's fair
it doesn't matter same strategy works
oh
um
oh okay that was already enough
[Music]
oh no oh no it's right diagonally
oh it's making it too easy though
[Music]
yeah the face too doesn't change
anything about my strategy that's a
little bit of a
oof moment for them
oh my my spike is gone but that's okay
[Music]
and the Lefty and the Lefty because
that's all my God
with the power of Lena I demand you to
die
kind of cool though that you know this
is also quite the original idea
you get to do Mecca fights
if you weren't building huge meccas at
this point by now then at this point
this is where you probably get inspired
to do so
[Music]
that's why you guys were weird in the
chat when I was asking like
whoever I end up like fighting her
because turns out she's not my friend
she just used me you meant I was like
fighting her opposite her old intention
I guess
I take hot container
yum yum yum yum
oh second row finally
wait we were already a second bro oh I
didn't see it oh
second row second heart
I have to leave soon thank you for
watching though thank you oh that one's
so purple
let's look at it
examining
it's for you meaning
come and get it
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I need to get a massage maybe tomorrow
[Music]
oh
do it just do it
don't let your dreams be dreams
you guys should get a massage too but
warning once you get one for the first
time you won't be able to go back you'll
always want the massage
[Music]
yeah
and please
yeah finally
mysterious
constructed
foreign
[Music]
can I get the ability to float please
huh
oh
baby
constructed
so you guys said she won't turn into a
ghost
story again
I guess they finally understand that
after four of the Sages
I've heard the story plenty of times
that with the last Sage I don't need to
hear it again
I could have tell me it told me a
different story at least
[Music]
I am one who lived in a distant past in
the age of hyrule's founding
the circumstances forced me to forsake
my body and become a being of pure
spirit
long thank you
have I slumbered within Zelda's purepad
in order to share what I knew when it
passed into your hands I apologize in
our meeting has been so long delayed the
Demon King's interference is to blame
nevertheless I ask your pardon
now on to the topic at hand
in my own age the distant past
from your perspective Zelda awakened as
the stage of time and appeared before us
thank you guys
what I must relate to you is the tragedy
that occurred in Hyrule uh are you gonna
tell me about her becoming a dragon I
already met her as a dragon
at its Crooks was Zelda who held a
secret Stone and traversed time
she made a momentous decision in those
days gone by
I would have I would have you know of
the results she poured into that Blade
the master sword
for longer long outside
foreign
[Music]
they listen to the same music on their
ears
foreign
[Music]
mm-hmm
I will come from
their tails look like peepees
that is
the way
[Music]
wow
it's the moment
[Music]
awesome
this is
admitted so guys
[Music]
oh so cool
whoa
that's crazy though but [\h__\h] Epic
spider monkey
s yeah
foreign
[Music]
thank you wow
link more like stinks
wow wow
Epic
sukuli candles
crazy [\h__\h]
you know this tragedy as the imprisoning
war
though it took all we were able to give
we succeeded in imprisoning The Demon
King
but I was wounded in the process my body
was soon to expire
that is when Zelda came to me bearing a
decade and broken sword
yes you will recall how the master sword
vanished from your hand at the Temple of
Time
from there I traveled into the distant
past appearing in zealous hands and now
you hold it once again
nope
is
in Vietnam
hmm
foreign
[Music]
you
I immediately
[Music]
the West
foreign
[Music]
for her personally
you know how she does this because she
wants Hyrule in the end to
continue in its beauty or be beautiful
again and and peaceful so as a normal
human in her normal body she wouldn't
even be able to see its glory for a long
time but if she turns into a dragon she
lives for thousands and thousands and
thousands of years so she will see the
effect of her restoration
that she was in charge of for many many
years she will be able to see the the
peaceful Glory of
her
her endeavors
yeah for a long time and in some way
that will probably bring her all the
happiness she needs and will give her
all all the makeups
for the things that she gave up
by becoming a dragon
yeah
I mean yeah yeah she might not you know
be much of herself anymore yeah but
still still though she'll be protecting
it she'll be flying over Hyrule
forever
you know
it doesn't matter somewhere deep in
there
there are Slumbers at Zelda and her
heart and her soul and she will see
a high roll that she always wanted to
see and she can make sure
for many thousands of years that it will
stay that way
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
trust me
trust me bro
afterwards Zelda and I discussed
strategy We Lay the groundwork for
guiding you in a distant future before
the gloom's Affliction took my life I
became a spirit and entered the pirapet
denzela did what she felt she must and
began the Forbidden process
she believed you would use the Master
Sword to defeat the demon king and
restore peace to Hyrule
you have already you already have in
hand the hope that Zelda left to you the
sword that seals the darkness the master
sword
but could you come here without
I'm not sure
go now link
with the sword of hope that Zelda left
to you you will surely Smite Demon King
Ganondorf you could oh
she tells you to get it
good that we have it
[Music]
state of spirit
[Laughter]
I'm glad I guess that's not me because
that was a pleasant surprise but yeah
trail of Master Sword
new objective and complete ah
not link but stink no no
issue follow me
yeah
follow me
[Music]
um
are you remain here
also I do have to call you with the
huh
well okay so what now
what now did we get all the
oh
we got them all
yeah we got them all the memories
[Music]
okay we report to Purell okay
so [\h__\h] hot again
um let me find my remote control for my
fine really quickly the fan is behind me
but the remote control is not
[Music]
hey should I put my energy drink back
into the fridge maybe well that's so
loud
because it's like not cool anymore let
me put it back
[Music]
ah
y'all know I still feel pretty energized
but that might change
like yesterday I was feeling so tired
because of the Heat
right now it's okay-ish
um
it's been four hours let's see I have to
end the stream in
another four I think because Cali said
let's get together half an hour before
the Stream
can I make it in four hours guys
the end of the game
plenty
okay good then I can probably even eat
dinner before the stream maybe that
would be nice I already cooked it so
I have the remains of the salmon and
really good stuff really good stuff that
was good food because I added butter to
it that's the sole reason
[Music]
hmm
I wanted to cook some more
because now we have a couple where's the
cooking thing what we have a couple more
sundalians
did they get rid of the cookie no there
it is
nearby
off right
salmon should be bigger uh it was plenty
big to me in like real life
maybe it looked small in the picture
generally it was a big portion
[Music]
um
uh what am I doing I
aliens
also new free free more if I want one
more armor upgrade I feel like
we could do it
yeah I still got potatoes too of course
of course
there we go how much space do we have
four okay let's make some normal Foods
um
is it worth it making food with um extra
Hearts there's like nothing like last
time where they immediately get rid of
all of them
make defense food
just one
I should make just one you yeah just one
well I already I still have some left
over from last time all of these
so okay
I can make defense potions how about
that let's make if you've guys really
think I should get defense stuff and I
can make defense potions Maybe
foreign
normal food wait do we have enough more
normal food I mean yeah full recovery
I just always feel so bad about using
full recovery stuff
maybe one normal
one normal thing
um
what could we make
could I make
everyone can't make the pizza it's so
sad I made it once and I could never
make it again I was always missing
something
um
that could be good yeah that's good
just one and the rest I'll make
beef and
I could have mixed this in maybe no oh
well I had to make defense potion again
we need a
monster part
yeah
and a crystal speed
fire
Thunder wings
uh
do I not have the thing I need
I might not have the right critter
I'll make defense food
wasn't this yeah I run shrooms
pretty rare Beetle I barely collected
beetles
oh that's good triple
oh baby you triple
okay now I think my inventory is full
yeah
although
I will not need this anymore
so I could just drink it all
these ones too I don't think I will
regret it will I
and just fill it up with more
more stuff more fun stuff
I could sell them oh well
oh
I already have Bloom recovery stuff I'm
out of materials anyway for that
um
no we can
banana no I got bananas too
where did the bananas go
oh
Manny banana
[Music]
oh one more
alrighty we're prepared with food what
about my weapons I'm not happy with my
weapons
oopsie drop it
um
yeah hopefully we'll still find some
more I mean in the in the castle we also
found a million
cool weapons but let me just make
something out of this
[Music]
um
wow
I might as well use these things right
that's not even that good in total
hmm
powerful attack swinging down to you I
would never like be at my last heart I'm
even dead or I have a decent amount of
hearts
I never saw myself
at my last heart never
um
for now it's okay
don't
[Music]
um
okay
how many
one more Shrine one more Shrine I want
to do one more shrine
the master sword is infused yeah true I
always forget that because you can't see
when it's fused and confusing me
um
I don't know what the fuse maybe this
oh wait it's already fused right now
what
else like that
how why are Stones yes why does it keep
on fusing itself of stones
use the Lionel blade
um
this one
okay
because I reloaded is that why oh
no you can't see it looks good though
whenever talking to you
Joshua no
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
my God yeah 30 plus 55
85. wow math sugoi
you found the site of spirit
this is
incredible that means we have the five
sages fantastic work link I can't
believe this is actually one of the
sages who faced off against the demon
king alongside Princess Zelda and now we
have news about the princess there's
some relief on that at least so in the
ancient past Princess Zelda went to
restore the decayed master sword and
return it to your hand trusting that you
would defeat the demon king in the
present day she did so much all on her
own she wasn't all alone
don't give her all the credit
the master sword was restored you say
when when were you planning on telling
me and it was found on the head of a
white dragon of all places that's hard
to believe
however
wait that's a flute that she's carrying
the whole time
this was Princess Ella's wish once she
believed and so strongly that she gave
her life to see it through
for us
thank you she's she's barely emotionally
moved I think by the news that Zelda
sacrificed herself to turn herself into
a dragon
I feel like she should be more like eh
no way
huh
thank you for finding the sword link I
have to say you really don't quite look
yourself unless you've got the master
sword at your side
[Music]
now then it seems you have all you need
you're prepared to face our enemy
[Music]
there you go
we need to determine where the demon
king is lurking yeah maybe she doesn't
quite understand
it seems unlikely he'd still be in the
Hyrule Castle I can't think of any place
he'd be here on the surface that must
mean a zebra on the ground or overground
but the underground is probably more
fitting for him
that's it the deaths
well wouldn't you say there's a high
probability that he's in the depth
do what you think best of course but my
suggestion is to ask Joshua for any info
she may have
she's enthusiastic about investigating
the depth so I'm sure she'd be happy to
help out link the rest is up to you
destroy
dove
will do
somebody told me though I just
remembered to talk to them about
learning
what you fixed Laura Lynn all on your
own within one hour how did you do all
of that crazy [\h__\h] man wow
oh food you want to give me food Mighty
salt grilled crab no I don't have space
for that
okay
I need to Finish Master Koga
yeah but I don't know if we have time
for that
do we
[Music]
no
okay
that won't take long really
it'll take me 20 minutes tops
oh
really don't kind of want to do it
um wait
I will risk it oh where's the Koba Quest
oh
yeah I got time a lot of people seem to
agree okay I trust you maybe we go here
maybe we're lucky and find a horse oh
and we just fly
[Music]
then
I go to original Village
oh
the chasm that's like here underneath
okay
let me eat some more chocolate it's
probably kind of melted so I have to uh
it is
to eat it out of the package
uh
only the top layer is melted where the
chocolate is
um
creamy
so
where is it somebody said it's weird
how is it weird
look for smoke
or underneath
is that smoke
hello there
what are you doing oh well if it isn't
linked oh you recognize me I haven't
seen you since we met oh wait are you
gonna hint I
wait oh I thought you meant smoke for
from like the chasm but you did mean
actually just smoke okay
um
hmm
okay wow how did you see that oh dude
[Music]
um
well that was easy
[Laughter]
oh the music here is so nice
ah
everywhere it's so nice
I did it without Chan
I mean okay I looked for smoke okay I
admitted
um true
foreign
[Music]
that's why you gotta do all the quests
by order and everything properly mm-hmm
ah
there should be
a root oh
ah there it is
[Music]
amusing oh
ah hello welcome to the team
um where did it go I'm here
the Army is growing yeah
my Army
of sages
wasn't there in taze of Symphonia isn't
like one of the characters called sage
I always thought that was weird a weird
name
the boy the little boy wasn't he called
sage
oh wait I know that was the last name oh
yeah yeah yeah
ah
oh yeah but generally the first name is
kind of weird too
it's almost a genius but only almost
kind of insulting he's like the genius
I've just given him the name genius
their names in Japanese were Dumber
he's called genius in Japanese where
it's hentai or Gene genius
like that
probably yeah
ah and they felt they felt it was too
tacky
to give him the same name in English so
they just take away the you
I don't know anyway
you little [\h__\h] I'm here to challenge
you
so face me or else
I even got my slipper resistance on so
your stupid slippery jokes
don't do [\h__\h] to me
oh he's doing yoga right now sorry to
disturb you I respect your Yoga Passion
I've been waiting for you
it is done
we have enough crystallized charges at
last
and I still don't know what to do about
this voice
where now
our gift to the demon thing
that you were about to challenge but you
almost forgot about me what the [\h__\h]
a weapon Beyond Compare
you
oh yeah today you will go down for me
as a day of our ultimates weapons
resurrection and today the world faced
its end behold this feat of engineering
but look at my feet of engineering did
you see Meadow oh wait
wait
I'm glad I'm not that's why you got
where you go
or like wait for the next thing in the
story
ah
this Unstoppable donut cut that would
have been so lame if you finish the
cougar Quest before getting minnow
because then you see me in a little and
you're like eh
this is the same thing
[Applause]
wait what do you mean you have your own
that's impossible no way may I wanted to
be the first
then I'll go take my rightful place
anyway and the Darkness below the castle
where the Demon King now dwells
ah yes swearing and of all things will
begin in the deepest reaches serve the
death's fire redeem spiral Castle
oh
no no
this time I'll bury you unless you're
already 100 know how this fight works
for whatever reason
although it would be interesting to try
uh fighting him uh as a normal link
wait I forgot how to fight
I forgot the buttons I was pressing why
thank you
left hand
oh wait it's a bit different than what
oh wait I saw on
okay your little [\h__\h] your little [\h__\h]
you did it without the mecca I would
love to try that too
okay okay
[Music]
um
I'm purposefully choosing one of my
weaker ones because
maybe I should stay off of the
no because it takes so much time
[Laughter]
let's go
School
where is uh let's do it again
[Music]
it's for fun
oh he doesn't give a [\h__\h] only to lead
you uh strategy
seems to be worth it
[Music]
do what I'm doing right now
and I guess you could still also if you
have me noodle
use the same strategy as you did before
or
what do you do
you know what about me
it feels more appropriate yeah I mean me
too I I feel like
I prefer packing off of her back
different though because see
he weapons wow
now how do I
um
I had to
ah [\h__\h]
I don't know here
[Music]
can I send those back
foreign
yeah I can
eyes is he awful oh yeah okay let's
let's get a stronger one
yeah much better
you want to try the same thing again
I would make it very fast for me
yeah no
you don't wanna
get up
get off of your High makeup wait my abs
died I think it's upgrading and
upgrading updating
can I do something about those too no
[Music]
[Laughter]
reopen it in a moment when this is over
yeah this is what I was waiting for
thank you
oh
[Music]
wait
come on
well well well
interesting outcome
Adam doesn't do damage
okay I have an idea
[Music]
good
Ness
yeah there we go
what
hmm
hey I should be back in a moment oh my
beautiful weapon oh my word destroyed
yo Lego [\h__\h]
I was as close to destroying the world I
[\h__\h] all those hats
because I restart the app
can you not
add a million things to my head
and even changed my hairstyle
he makes squeaky sounds
okay
I was this close destroying the world
with the Demon King you think I'm just
going to let it stands to you do you say
think I will let him stand
[Music]
time to bust out my serious moves a
brand new technique
darkness of the darkest dips I will
destroy you
no no he'll self-destruct won't he
trampling for you before my rocket
This Is the End
now fly cocoa
[Music]
oh back onto the surface you're welcome
friends come on
oh my God
well thank God it didn't take so much
time huh
Great Danes
and welcome to you please wait a moment
don't worry I'll I'm on my way
[Laughter]
the first uh until the bling at the end
I was like it could be but is it really
but the bling
it's definitely solidified it
um
thank you for driving out the trespasser
he must be a huge Pokemon fan to be
going out like that
I watched near Battle closely it is
unlikely that he will appear in another
abandoned mine his manner of departure
attests to that Minds similar to this
one can be found on the thriving surface
settlements and other places of
Distinction
oh there appears to be some connection
between the Surface and the depths very
curious perhaps you find this equally
intriguing it may be a good idea for you
to explore this connection
there's another other thing before you
receive your journey
might associate over their managers
schema Stones you may want to ask for
one wonder what it is does it have to do
with rockets
[Music]
do I need batteries in the finale finale
finale probably not right
no okay because otherwise I could have
probably gotten some more now
but if it's not necessary then whatever
ah hi
I'm well equipped okay
here I have some rocket science for you
I always wanted to say that
uh okay
nice
I will also prepare the parts required
to it to test it if you want to go back
up or what
what are we doing
where would you want me to go oh up
there
I don't care I don't want to go I don't
wanna I don't want to go
catch
noodles Revival
I think you know there was a Instagram
cat or so that I found
dad uh whose name was noodles or YouTube
shorts I'm not sure it's so cute so cute
so crazy
reminds me of chunky wonky but way
crazier
um
uh wait what am I doing oh
just give me as much as you can
[Music]
now that the dog you still wants not
another dog I'm happy you do
cute
very cute Nala so cute
okay it's time to kill Ganon
let's go guys I'm glad we could finish
the Koga thing though thanks for letting
me do that
uh where do we go I uh wait we are in
the depths right now so
uh but I should probably talk to Joshua
again after killing Coco she might now
have advice
for where he might be
oh well yeah below makes a lot of sense
but yeah where is the chasm did I see a
Chasm somewhere
about it
wait maybe I did oh maybe I did
but I will go to Joshua first to tell
her about Koga yes
oh apparently
it's not chasm
apparently it's chasm
terrible
[Music]
Jazz and better
just makes more sense in my in my
opinion yeah
[Laughter]
the wonders of the English language
[Music]
um
did the music change again yeah
[Music]
we don't call it chocolate a coconut
yeah
exactly
thank you oh but then there's chaos yeah
and you could argue maybe that chocolate
maybe comes from French or whatever who
knows
who really knows
archive I wouldn't compare it with
archive because there the CH is not in
the at the beginning of the word and
that can change a lot of things I'm sure
English they just don't know what
they're doing
you look like you're in a good mood did
you discover something
um
well of course you did You're The
Swordsman so did he have any close-up of
Princess Zelda
um oh no nothing huh well even so that's
one less danger for the princess I'm not
even surprised you did all this you're
The Swordsman I'll be hard at work here
with my research into the depth so just
come let me know if you find anything
else Swordsman
oh there's got to be a connection
between Princess Zelda and the devs I'll
continue with my research but I will not
help you I will not tell you
because you probably already know deep
in your heart just look deep in your
heart
yeah true thank you
[Music]
you are right I don't need your hints
because I got a chance
I expected her to tell me something but
yeah
it's not like I needed
[Music]
I wanna just even though I don't need it
just for completion sake I want to get
some more batteries if I can I've never
used this one before
[Music]
we can get a whole new bar
let's go
okay
[Music]
it's new jeans is Coca-Cola
advertisement song
somebody wrote Coca-Cola in the chat
just had to think of it
[Music]
super shy
chat chat oh Chasm chat oh there you go
Chasm is correct
ah yeah you too you didn't realize too
yeah I also just recently realized that
that dude is there or remembered it
because I
completely forgot about it oh
um
yeah and I also just went to other
places
to get my batteries
you're not the only one
I'm also at the end of the game and I
just realized
oh [\h__\h] I should have left a flower huh
I feel bad now
sorry
you never saw that one the construct
ever really
okay guys it's time to finally open the
door properly
wow hmm
okay and then underneath
maybe like
in the very middle
could have probably ported somewhere but
yeah under the floating part that's what
I'm thinking I probably saw it already
before
[Music]
jasm has a unique by Omi are you trying
to
make me say
funny words in my funny way
um
[Music]
do I have no more chance of doing one
more Shrine or do I get another blessing
on the way or so
safe now even though I don't have to
by only
cute no no blessing to men
no shrines just fights okay let's go
this is
[Music]
what happens if you jump in here like
super early
so anti-climactic
climatic I don't
know that's awesome word that I
have many questions about in my head
gloom's approach
very interesting it's actually very
different here
oh
the mobs kill you speed one really
becomes a challenge
I want to watch someone speak right now
live fruit not here right where is there
is there
hello
oh
music
kind of far
we can repeat that I don't mind
interesting oh it's me
oh wait there's a lot of them
oh there's so many
oh wait I
marinos
oh
okay yeah yeah this is where I'll get
triggered by a lot of loom okay cool do
I don't have to fight them huh
oh maybe yeah let's try to not land and
just swim through and fly through
hi
come on hey I'm just hanging around
I'm down
oh we are under Hyrule Castle we are
gonna end the game let's [\h__\h] go
let's try to not get hit too much
let's not waste too much food
let's have fun no let's go
game
what what the [\h__\h] was that
your YouTube name
let's not talk about it don't explain
don't explain German French ah there it
goes my first heart
I'll pick it up
better to avoid fights no okay
um where am I going though
that's what I felt a moment ago always
in the white one
go down don't talk to me
[Music]
no no no no please don't touch me
oh oh no
yeah should I should I should I do I
have to
thank you
[Music]
let's not fight let's not fight
I remember something
I am a genius
see you later silver boy
let me go let me go let me go there's
something that's so mean that's so means
to freeze me on the globe
that's unfair that's so unfair
okay well he picked me up from the Gloom
that's kind of nice
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no
um
no that's not acceptable okay
I'm panicking
hey
no go away
did I get my
[Applause]
yeah I just realized I can just walk
over but we're pretty slow that way and
that's so easy to move
um wait I wanna can I I can't open
chests huh but I got back my weapon
right okay
but yeah Big portions of Boom oh I guess
I could
laughs
skip put that way
also I wonder how much cool stuff I just
skipped if there's like you know
wait that's the Majora's Mask oh
could I skip a lot of the enemies too
the power of sage they left me
wow
yes oh my God why are we not doing that
no
why did I immediately changed my mind do
I have to fight this
it's getting handsy
blocking the Wi-Fi do I have to fight
them
I can run
uh where where to there was actually
like a path to the left and I went
straight
I wonder what there was on the left side
is this the right path
wait wrong hello
wait could I fly up I'm not really I'm
like disoriented so it's like where do I
go
oh
too late they're gonna touch me they're
gonna touch me they're gonna touch me
they're gonna touch me
you need a hand shut up laughs
yeah I'm thinking switching quickly
uh
what's the button for shield again is
that l or l
is that l
no
[Music]
can I like
I don't want that
[Laughter]
we have a safe ride before that
um
I don't want that no no no that's mean
you thought I'd kill me yeah that's the
problem when you have no idea what's
going on on your surroundings
okay
cute blob
oh no
wait let me think though
ah okay what are we doing what are we
doing where do I land uh wait here here
might be good can they go up here
probably
[Music]
okay okay this should be safe I think
yep
okay
oh does this path
lead
there in the end
because there is
that's okay
man
it's too bad we don't have our
friends to help us
Maybe
[Music]
I should make a cannon Shield actually
because I'm running out do I have a
cannon
still never Cannon
still don't have a cannon
no I'm Canon Ganon we're gonna fight
Ganon without cannons so we're non-canon
Ganon
the donut bombs how do they work not on
like can I fuse them to an arrow
yeah they still no
they're not ideal
man
well that's just stupid
he was Canon to any weapon
a cannon you're meaning bombs right did
I read that wrong
oh wait
could this work
that
yeah
[Laughter]
what those were so far away
huh
that was funny
oh it's staying pretty close
it's a lot of stones
[Music]
here we go
thank you
I feel it we're almost through
just got a waste all my materials
oh
it's not a two-handed sword
ah got it
I found the exit
hi hi
there's more let's go
this one surely won't be as thick as the
other one right
right and we'll just focus we'll focus
on one spot here
foreign
would have been fine to just do like one
layer
man is there something to fuse
why nothing too fuse wait maybe I have
one more
oh yeah this one I have this one and
another spiky one
going the wrong way
College we don't have our stages anymore
they took them away we're too deep
apparently the Wi-Fi connection is
really bad
that's what they said
I need to get a new provider
deeper and deeper
will we eventually reach the part where
Zelda and me were exploring
or
forgotten Foundation
we must
that oh wait
oh hello
how many over there I could wear my my
mask when I walk over there
is this already like the gloomy part or
does it get worse
it gets worse
okay and then I'll try to maybe
do some damage control
I remember this music no I don't but
it's really cool
I mean part of it
I remember but now when I was fighting
it sounded a bit different
uh time to maybe feel some things
because
um this this one I want to use the Royal
Broad Sword
um too
[Music]
yeah that's fine
I wish I had like all these cool weapons
from before
I have so many great base weapons
lots of sword
it already has the Lionel saberhorn
okay
they're all sleeping on the ground are
they gonna notice
oh they're gibdas
but I have to blow up the the wall over
there apparently
hi
uh
okay okay we're good
[Music]
oh I will uncover this part now
let's go we've come full circle
so many bombs
I'll prefer I would prefer to not use
them all up because I might need them
for combat okay this one's not so
difficult to break
oh yeah oh yeah wow that looks crazy
yeah master sword oh
I was gonna ask how do they know but
yeah because she time traveled oh my God
and dragon that's her yeah
oh
[Music]
wait I thought that would maybe trigger
some kind of cutscene
should I did I go the wrong way
cook food here
why
do I still have more Seth aliens no
all right
more rocks these ones I tried
right now
oh
a door okay
wait
where is he down there
huh
I'm scared I'm scared
feels like we're really close right to
where it all started
I'm scared
I mean it's gonna auto save a million
times but
I climb
imprisoning chamber oh yeah and it fell
down oh we're going even
what did I get all this
Sim
s
[Music]
armor oh yeah thank you thank you thank
you thank you
well you think Donald maybe won't notice
me with the Majora's Mask
died with a what a sad way to go down
about to kill Ganon about to save the
world and I just accidentally don't open
my parachute
[Music]
that's the the torch that Zelda dropped
by the way
um
foreign
to heal
Oh I thought I thought because because
that was moving the texture was moving I
felt the Gloom hands were spawning
but no it was just a texture bug
[Music]
well the light has changed so much
[\h__\h]
time to change the bow anyway to my
strongest one
finally
[Music]
I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared I am so
[\h__\h] scared that's gonna fall off
isn't it when I stand on it
oh no I have to jump
I don't wanna this reminds me of Metroid
well I feel at this point we're gonna
end up in Australia
after diving
so deep I think we'll be on the other
side of the world
vibes you know what I mean
foreign
[Music]
time to panic like [\h__\h]
I have sweaty dance
kind of thing really oh
foreign
[Music]
thank you your Shield actually might
help me here
[Music]
they're all like busy busy busy I'm
trying to get to reach you thank you
foreign
thank you
Master Sword
okay okay we can use one now
and eat one of these
should I really use a monster sword you
know maybe not yet you know monopods
could be fun oh true really it doesn't
work here
thank you
yeah I was gonna save it for Ghana
because yeah well this has to charge you
know
wait
let's play it smart
cool
quick music
[Music]
oh well we're cleaning up pretty nicely
the flip
I only see oh is there a second row of
second
wave okay okay
okay
all lined up
[Music]
oh man
what do we got next okay give those
give me those give those
give those give those
[Music]
please I just did that because I wanted
to change it up a little bit but I just
remembered while I was doing that that
they like Elementary things
Elemental
things
oh
give me some distance
foreign
[Music]
but you need to attach some Elementary
stuff hmm
unconsciously smart
oh partially partially
also it's not unconsciously it's a
subconsciously
toilet is so cracked for real like last
episode I think we all saw
how much of a help he was for me
[Music]
sorry dildo
are we getting liners too no way right
we're not getting another Lino Coliseum
here right
I swear
oh wait um
nah okay thank God
that's where I draw the line
yes
friends need you
right there
hi well this is the last uh
the last
Brian
thank you
what what are they done I wanted to
fight some more and pick up some things
and now what
stuff is
right now we're running away from them
right
[Music]
oh I'm leaving them behind me
I'm leaving them behind after all
okay
[Music]
thank you
oblique
[Music]
oh no
no I didn't pick up all the items
[Music]
oh
Lord why
yeah wow I mean that's such a typical
Trope for RPGs and in the end your
friends are staying behind and you're
gonna do a one-on-one with the big boss
I saw that in tails of games too
although we have to fight on Gloom
please say no
on top of it
no okay
both feelings
it probably saved anyway
so you should have used night cream
Ganon
fighting alienate style I started
understand
give me that back it doesn't belong to
you
last stretch before the fight
now how long will it take me to figure
out these gimmicks
and the best strategy oh
didn't Skip Leg Day
[Music]
four ten
oh man help me
patriarch mine and villain farming not
perhaps
kernish get built
the Menace Unleashed
and noodle arms
face each other now
[Music]
um
Gloom swords
[Music]
for 100 you still have to take a picture
of him right so mean if you forget
only just like a Skyward Sword oh Mommy
where's my highly I'll do it
sword equipped wait did they
automatically equip my master sword
because I don't remember equipping it
if you bought all the photos uh
ah Mamma Mia
let's get the nine
and maybe a defense up for now until I
understand how to fight him
[\h__\h] I'm so scared what do I do how do I
do it okay just focus it's a one-on-one
fight he walks slowly so you just gotta
look at his moves he probably has the
same moveset as in Skyward Sword
honestly
just don't panic just don't panic easier
than any Lionel okay
see I'm already panicking
oh
express it you'll be does it go away oh
I think
okay okay yeah he definitely has like I
don't know two free phases
right okay next time I know
okay I waited too long no I wasn't sure
how long it was gonna take
local
[Music]
cool
oh okay
she's too greedy
she does not know I expect I expect of
course more that's too easy
phase two
oh we say how [\h__\h] have missed their
house just relaxed
Spanish
oh it's gonna be spreading Gloom
everywhere I think he looks so gloomy
hey hey the screen ends there you know
left side too or what maybe after this
phase you spread to the left side no
no
[Music]
Batman
oh thank you
is it worth fighting the ghost
do I have to can I use like these tools
do they no they don't work
but maybe this stuff works that probably
doesn't
maybe the only thing that works is like
bombs I can't imagine being able to
freeze them
[Music]
yeah I prefer one-on-one fight because
um then I know where the [\h__\h] he is okay
here we go uh no no that one that would
focus on this one
but
do I have to um
[Music]
spaghetti spaghetti
spaghetti focus on real one okay
[Music]
well phase one was way better
for me personally
[Music]
um
ancient blade when if not now but what
if I miss
yeah that's not even that much
what
I don't know what I'm doing guys do I
look like I know what I'm doing because
I don't
hello
[Music]
I've noticed now that everybody's back
nice oh
[Music]
oh what an opening what an opening
use the bullet time that is perfect
moment to do some damage
and calm down
you take parts now okay
didn't he already
isn't that what the kids do
scare me
face free baby
you can't scare me I am the hero to save
the world and make Zelda's sacrifice
worth it
I shall not let it go to Vain no
I'm not
[Music]
this field is saving my ass
[Applause]
let's go away at some point
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
counter flaring me
there
wait what did I do
I just got up
[Music]
I I'm taking everything my shield
broke
oh that is very sad
[Music]
[Applause]
um
I thought I could like healed myself
from the um
you know what I know about that uh punch
the balls punch him okay
um I'm gonna run out of shields
[Applause]
wait wait
you meant
happy disappear
ah oh
[Music]
oh that's what you meant
okay
okay okay
okay okay okay okay
thank you
Mommy
[Music]
I'm always on yeah it's not so bad it's
not so bad it's not bad I can use all my
food I can use all my food I can use all
my food
yeah they just go in one go he he sees
it as like zero or what just like the
liners in the in the Coliseum
keep it attacking aggressively okay
Chihuahua Chihuahua Chihuahua
Chihuahua
I got my sword on so far
okay yeah just keep on shooting is that
it please tell me that's it
I know Facebook will use my bow 90 of
the time
yeah
for stress
face four
oh no but my sages will come back right
[Music]
here
what you doing what you doing
[Music]
um
just like Satori oh [\h__\h]
I mean
lies that's clear lenses
[Music]
foreign
with her help on her back at him
don't don't tell me I have to like buy
myself walk up there find my way up to
her back again please tell me the game
brings me there
almost oh no
no she's not inside him right
like are they combined now
no
and then I have to hurt her but then
I'll set her free
set her frame
[Music]
set for free
oh
oh that's what a badass dragon looks
like baby oh oh those eyes are like you
know when cats in pictures
have those shiny eyes not because they
really look like that but because of the
reflection of the phone
also I think it happens with other
animals too but
it's so freaky with
cats oh my God yeah
this is like Ghibli
um it reminds me of some Ghibli
craziness
the old old lady I think whatever old
lady
thank you see you guys said she lost
herself but if she would have lost
herself would she really come to my
rescue
this
no
she would mind her own business like the
other dragons
thank you
best girl
I told you he likes looking over Hyrule
seeing it's peaceful
wow
[Music]
I need like a saddle or something
otherwise this is very unsafe
we're much smaller
[Music]
geez
very epic how do we how do we do this we
just stand on her head
we think it's like a fancy bow
the face
or just meet the master story
you did
[Music]
what what am I supposed to what do you
want am I fixed on it okay I can jump
off though why would I do that
how do I how do I fight what oh I'm
controlling the dragon
how how how
am I really
where is he how do I
I was holding on to it but not not
anymore wait what the [\h__\h] is going on
what the [\h__\h] is going on
good what what
what what
died
is she gonna just pick me up whenever I
need a ride
oh wow
okay
not what I expected
oh wait I see okay
[Music]
to Lindo
the land please
I could wear my
got skydiving armor but then I have to
keep on Switching around
I could
I guess Skye what am I doing but now
it's too far too close I guess
[Music]
maybe I should land on him may I kindly
land on him
oh
okay
Okay so
they want me to do that so
um Zelda
oh cute
thank you that's I was like about to ask
how how can I tell her to pick me up
hello and then she brings me all the way
up again so that we have a good distance
can I give her some head pads scratched
watch
switch to scratcher
this is so cute this is so sweet
I just wish to Lin could send me flying
straight forward a little bit
[Music]
no I just want to get to the side
Zelda is an elevator now
but I guess I don't really get no no the
Gloom gives me some damage hey I got my
hearts back by the way
down
[Music]
so can I really not hit it with the
arrows
how much does it need
oh
nice soon
nice so nice though
[Music]
I'm waiting for my Uber
I'll give you a big tip after this don't
worry it'll be worth your time
Bella pick me up
I doubt that I'm here
I'm here
hey
there she goes oh so sweet man nice game
development she knows exactly where I am
go straight towards me
good game
okay
let's go see you later pretty eyelashes
by the way
[Music]
okay I'll switch
blind forever blind
let's go to the one that's really close
to the Head
yeah this works much better
[Music]
there we go
big damage
I feel like that did no Gloom damage to
me though interesting
where where was the bloom damage
pick me up
perfume
uh humans on the back not at the actual
eye
oh it felt like it was happening on the
on the on the zip
[Music]
we go again
I can learn somewhere to the
fight in the Birds Temple Sky Temple
that's okay it feels really free
and refreshing oh God
to be up in the air like this right get
a toothpaste bone
cold air ratchet
oh oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
this girl
I'll get you out of that Dragon buddy
don't worry after
Thursday
are we doing what I think I'm doing
we're gonna hit the tear
foreign
[Music]
I
really destroyed this epic moment please
help me
[Music]
thanks girl I'm sorry that was
embarrassing I know
oh God
I think that's high enough actually is
it
ah yeah
[Music]
okay calculating
I wanted to do a cool strike like while
falling
[Music]
it's a Blood Moon it must be I saw it
just now I think
[Music]
oh
yeah final attack
[\h__\h] you Ganon
sincerely
and not even seven hours just six hours
and I was like wasting time in the
beginning for a whole hour at least
[Music]
foreign
Let's Take It All In
[Music]
thanks guys
uh is the ground okay where did that
beam come from
now about you Zelda
destroyed Canyon dove
he's gone dwarf
what
a dragon GF
Skyward Sword we're in Skyward Sword now
this is though
the sky of Skyward Sword
trust me
connection is right there
[Music]
can we heal her can we extract her
feel better be
[Music]
sure
let's come battle together
distract her with magical friendship
power
her her lashes are so yasified
[Music]
it's working
always works German always works that's
why I changed the game to German in
English you can't do it if you set the
game to German you can freeze Zelda
that's why German always works
to Zelda and she will come back yes
Germany always works
[Music]
can someone catch a stone now because
the the dragon is gone so who Catches Us
[Music]
thanks bro
I buy
you're not gonna say anything huh
maybe it's all in my head
maybe it's all our dream
but that was in a different cell again
oh
[Music]
what if you fail
catch you and will land in the water and
we'll be wet together let's go
[Music]
she's got her arms open for me reach
hold it was it wasn't red even
[Music]
can I let go now
would that hurt in real life
is this RPG logic
yes
I thought so
hmm
should have just sent some magical Birds
to catch us
happy
Zelda you good
[Music]
hi hi
right
a paper
[Music]
ah
precise they didn't want him
it was busy
[Music]
that's just how
about we finish
[Music]
foreign
I'm not crying I'm just happy I wanted
to cry
okay
[Music]
tell me more
so how's
[Music]
good for you
okay that like two seconds at the end
moved me but it cuts off immediately so
it doesn't get me to cry
close though
very close
Keith
oh
I didn't jump down
baseball membership
here is off the kingdom
they're just happy tears now
[Music]
wow wow that was so much
big journey and
could have been even bigger
[Music]
I don't know why but the ending screen
is giving me tears
nothing's happening
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
foreign
Nintendo
it was so good
I don't wanna suck up my snot
[Music]
whoa
whoa whoa that always tears
oh
foreign
[Music]
to say my thoughts right now I'm
enjoying the
this moment
sound was crackling really I don't hear
it crackling
[Music]
but if it was then I fixed it now
oh
wow
oh the voice actors
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so good
[Music]
so
this one
is definitely
one of the
free
[Music]
it's not two
best games
I've ever played and
feel regretful for not
I mean I don't care about the products
but I would have liked to uh
really enjoy it a bit more but it's like
one of the few games that makes me feel
like
very open to and looking forward to
the future where maybe in a couple years
I want to replay the game
carbonara
sorry
um
[Music]
yeah like not many games make me feel
like we're playing them after finishing
them once
um
it had
so much greatness to it it had a great
story it had great characters I like the
graphic Style
um
the whole like building aspect
sometimes
like it's not my favorite thing about it
therefore maybe breath of the wild is
actually more my thing
but
I mean it overall it was worked into the
game very well
um
and it gave it
definitely a lot of freshness and new
aspects and new things to work with yeah
the story was really good and ah the
music was good
oh
the I thought the temples besides the
besides the water temple
I think they were all great besides the
water temple
[Music]
water temple is some
the weird one
um
oh yeah and then shrines were
fun I think like I I hear from other
people critique that the shrines are too
easy but I feel like it's a good
balancer some really easy ones and
there's some medium ones and there's
some more difficult ones and well I
think they're fine
[Music]
the bosses
of the temples were pretty good like
that I think like the boss from the
water temple
actually elevates the the water temple
overall
[Music]
um
played breath of the wild but I watched
full 100 flippers several times as you
may know
uh this really like makes me want to
play breath of the wild in the future
not on stream probably just privately
the fire for a future but damn
like Zelda games are always epic but
the breath of the wild game is just just
use all the potential that Zelda games
have and make it shine
good job Nintendo good [\h__\h] job take
your time
another five years or six or seven or
eight to make another game although the
next one I really wonder what direction
they will go to we talked a little bit
about it during the playthrough at some
point like will they continue with open
world will they continue with this style
of 3D
what will they do it will be very
interesting to see I'm stressed out that
because the credits are over
yeah I'm very curious if they don't you
know try to recreate all that then maybe
they'll take less time for a new game
[Music]
yeah but we will see yeah this is the
norm going forward oh really
open world too I wonder then it will
take a long time
good luck Nintendo the end
but post scene coming in
but will we never have like an OG style
zeld anymore then I think both are nice
to have you know
[Music]
is this
after all is done
oh
foreign
giving her a tour
getting everybody a tour
I always say goodbye
foreign
[Music]
hmm
mine had said
it's known to come
outside
[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
me neither
until my Liberty
streets
[Music]
in the future yeah
foreign
my arm is gone so he can no longer build
things huh
too bad
could have rebuilt the robot
minero
aunt devices
foreign
[Music]
reminder
look at that little chicken
[Applause]
[Music]
s
I'm now starting screen over
oh
where's the New Game Plus
we don't get New Game Plus
ah
not until the DLC oh your play versus
Real from just one as one of the best
games I've ever played yeah mine did
laughs
and if they're still seal I I'm sure I
will play it on stream yeah I'm looking
forward to that
damn
man
leaves me speechless it's it's so good
it was so good I'm I'm so glad that I
went through with it the whole game from
start to beginning
and don't don't only do half-assed
things no we play full games we do that
we have to
um
let's check how much I have where
in continue
where do you see that
well there's a star
means both games
well I don't expect too much because I
didn't do that many friends and I didn't
do that many codecs at all
[Music]
I didn't really like
purposefully like
aim for 100
um
oh yeah I'm sure this will get game of
the year it has to
how could not
okay where is the where do I see that
here what
where do I see though
[Music]
oh free hmm I mean how much do kodaks
alone
make
probably a 20
that's not so bad that's not so bad if
Clorox make up like 20 percent
collects are 60 uh
zero zero zero point zero four per Kodak
oh
I don't know
I know you need to have food well
sometime before the coming stream I
guess
yeah which is starting in one of uh no
in two hours but we're gathering in one
and a half hours now
um even 40 is insane I think so
I mean you know if I wouldn't like feel
like you know as a streamer I don't I
don't want to like torture you guys for
too long
then I would have dragged it out longer
honestly
and done some more stuff I just wanted
to finish it today so that we can you
know move on to other things on stream
but
yeah I would have totally and maybe I
will off-screen when I got some time I'm
currently very busy bug in the coming
months I think I'll play quite a bit
maybe on Plane Rides Again I'll take my
switch and I'll work on that but wait so
if I use this save file
those percentages they'll keep on going
up up right but do I have to kill Ganon
again
no right
use this file oh okay
okay nice nice nice nice so Ganon is
already in there right okay nice
all right never again I'm happy
I'm happy first try I don't know is
there anyone here in the chat who has
not seen my suffering in the last stream
of Skyward Sword the very end of me
playing skyward Swords
I've seen it
is there some people here
oh I ca oh yeah right I cut it out
because it was so embarrassing how
I lost my [\h__\h] mind it was a dark day
yeah like people you guys told me oh
it's not that but you can keep it in but
for me personally that was like
something I don't want to be seen like
that's that's a side of myself I don't
want out there
yeah
um that was it was a sad day yeah I was
just so pressured because of the time
and
I could have done it if I wasn't so
pressured
so some kfb were maybe because concerned
that today will be the same thing but
you have to take in account uh or
whatever that for Skyward Sword there
was
um
motion controls
so that played a lot into my failure
hmm
that was rough
mm-hmm
so you know yeah I did the Lionel
Colosseum yesterday maybe that was good
warm-up for today we did we did a lot of
like big fights yesterday
um
it did really well with this thank you
you know I had so much fun with the game
ah
I I don't know it just made me very
happy it gave me very many happy
memories
you know
off-screen and on screen
I really enjoyed it was a good time
I I'm glad this happened I want to say
thank you to Nintendo for creating a
never Banger game
foreign
games of all time
like it's hard to put into words which
ones are the others
it might even be my number one game now
in my um
you know yeah there's some other other
contenders that I really enjoyed very
much but if you if we don't only speak
about enjoyment but also quality of game
you know you know then it's it's it's
rough but there there's just like this
is the the dimensions of this game
are just something else
that it's hard to put it under any other
game that I enjoyed
um
yeah
it's just not a fair comparison
near shaking tunic yeah you know that's
what I mean the dimensions of tuning are
so much smaller it's like one of the
best games I ever played but and then I
really I really
Charming game that I have closed in my
heart or in my heart deep in my heart
no no no no no hate for tunic I love
tunic so much
it's hard to say so I don't wanna like
give clear
rankings you know
but if I have to give this game a rating
out of 10
.
even though not everything was perfect
the good parts
elevated so much that I want to give it
a 10 out of 10.
you know
if I see it very objectively maybe I
would give it a 9 out of 10.
but I want to give it a 10 out of 10.
um
yeah
the highs there's highs and lows and
mids but the highs are so high that it
makes up for the lows you know
so
that's that we finished another game and
I will maybe maybe it's good that we
didn't do everything on stream like for
overall for the whole playthrough I've
been doing a lot of things offstream but
maybe it's good that we didn't drag it
out much longer because this gives me
some more fun time with Zelda uh tears
of the Kingdom in my private time you
know
when I just wanna
no kill some time
on the airplane or whatever
and I have something really really
joyful nice
high quality to play
um
[Music]
yeah if you ever find the King Dragon
you should record oh I can
okay okay
does it say how many how much time
say where does it say how much time you
spend
in the switch menu right
oopsie [\h__\h] I made a video hahaha
great great video
wait I'm scared then I show something
weird
I don't think I could show anything
weird but where is it oh
in my profile
[Music]
play no
um
made up here should be up here and there
I think I found it oh yeah
yeah it's so ah it's vague it says
played for 100 hours or more wait do I
have to close the game for it to update
properly
so vague
oh okay now it says blade 410 hours or
more okay
okay so I guess that's really around
where it is
before I started it was about 100 hours
and now that I'm done for today it's 110
hours that's that's compared to other
people not even that much I guess
ah good amount of gaming yeah you played
more than me really
well well I told you guys I always
showed you so money so many Recaps
imagine I did a stream on all those 110
hours damn
but I showed you in my recaps of what
I've been doing off screen I hope you
enjoyed my recaps
eh Fire Emblem
well it says
I played
lost epic for 10 switch sports for one
cue remastered for free five lemon gates
for 95.
Metroid Prime remastered for 25 Pokemon
Scarlet for 45.
Mario Karter looks for 90 hours
what
how the [\h__\h] did I get 90 hours you're
telling me I almost played Mario Kart as
much as I played tears of the Kingdom
no way
I am ashamed
what am I doing with the time in my life
lucious mentioned 15 hours
Mario Party superstar has 10 hours
oh that's that okay I have a couple more
like games that were smaller hours but
yeah
Uno 15 hours
ah yeah well well
wow wow wow I don't I don't know man
this was amazing
this was life-changing this was
beautiful
it was amazing it was a pleasure it was
a pleasure to play this game
in 95 hours for f e t h
mm
sounds like you liked it I really liked
it it was exquisite Splendid marvelous
super
califragilistic whatever
Divine indeed it was quite divine
spectacular
um
it's always sad after playing a game for
a long time
with you guys
to leave it behind man
not always
I remember there were sometimes where I
was happy to leave something behind but
usually it's sad to leave it behind
um
yeah you feel empty yeah but I don't
have to feel empty I still can I can
still play the game I'm not like 100
finished
yeah
we don't talk about those
it doesn't mean that they were like bad
games I just felt happy to be done with
them
oh yeah DLC they're still gonna be DLC
surely
um
well then I still have a stream upcoming
so I should probably take a rest
and then wait let me take a look at my
schedule and tell you how it's looking
there's not much
I didn't I didn't plan everything out
yet but
so Monday
I mean Monday is the the collabo stream
right
myth mythical lab
coming soon in two hours that's after
midnight for me so that's Monday
um okay I can do Super Chat reading on
Tuesday we should probably start maybe 4
P.M my time
whoa
what are these almond hours
I've seen my schedule that Alma has
really early starting times what's going
on
what what's going on
I'm leaking on my schedule but this is
looking crazy what what she never
no like overall not only on Monday
maybe it's just roughly maybe it's just
this like really roughly reserving
her schedule and she won't actually
start at that time hmm
yeah okay and then on
um
I have uh probably Korean lesson here
yeah
[Music]
um
oh I should book a massage for tomorrow
I gotta do that okay Tuesday is super
chats Wednesday I'm thinking Minecraft
on the weekend
I wanna either do double FF or
we're doing Saturday GTA and Sunday FF
and
I mean that could still change I'm
waiting for some things
first day and Friday on one of those
days I'm doing a member stream
in the evening I think oh and oh [\h__\h]
wait that's already next week oh
something's there's um there's there's
maybe two special things happening next
week I just saw in my schedule
you know
oh
[Music]
hey
um you will see when it happens
Chihuahua leaks
yeah it's not 100 clear yet I might feel
kind of a vague schedule but since I'm
taking Monday Loki off besides the myth
stream I might not do the stream until
then
the schedule until like in the evening
of Monday because maybe I'll have some
more
clear thoughts until then
I'm leaking Diablo four not in the
coming week I think
we haven't talked like nobody brought it
up I guess I gotta bring it up but um
yeah
[Music]
Isn't that cool out today yeah but
technically it's after midnight for me
and also in Japan it's already Monday so
for me it's Monday
and that way I can definitely keep up my
streak
seven days of streams
hitting that Bingo well let me check I
streamed
I stream today I assumed yesterday a
stream I did a re-broadcast which counts
too
on Friday I did a stream on first I did
the stream on Wednesday
okay that's one two three four five
uh Monday six yeah easy okay I'm hitting
the seven day streak for Bingo
it does it does
it does if it counts as
counts at my contract in whole life
then it counts uh on the bingo
[Laughter]
technically correct yes yes I streamed
it I streamed it I did
yeah yeah aqua's Minecraft fireworks
count for fireworks I guess wait is
there a watch fireworks on
on the Bingo sheet
I'm not going to be watching fireworks
in our summer like in Japan watching
fireworks in summer is pretty
um
pretty normal but you know another funny
moment when they were explaining to us
the Bingo sheet
in the rehearsal time
it was so funny they were like
explaining the Bingo sheet and they were
like you know like leading up to
something they were going on and on
about the Bingo sheet like oh there's so
many ways to clear it you can do this
and that and you know it's your own
judgment in the end
also this time we have uh English and ID
versions of the sheet you know because
like they they showed us the Bingo sheet
and we looked a little bit added and
some things you know like 47
pre-factors of Japan learned them by
heart seemed kind of difficult for
overseas uh talents and then you know
the the higher reps they were like you
know kind of like you know talking about
that too and then so they say the so
therefore
we have English and ID versions too so
I'm like oh oh so we have different
goals and they're like well actually no
it's the same it's just translated into
English and Indonesia you have the same
goals
they so did that on purpose it's hard to
recreate that in moment on my own for
you guys but it was so funny they were
like going on and on and on about the
Bingo sheet and then leading up to
like purposefully leading up to trying
to hint at our own versions but no no
it's just translated good luck
foreigners good [\h__\h] luck
time to play Geo guesser oh
I don't know I'll do my best yeah
translate it not localized
[Music]
yeah when he when they hit me with the
ACT well actually I'm like
oh I
[Music]
oh
well get attacked yeah
how many prefixes do I know
a couple probably more than you know
Gouda
but I asked her are you gonna actually
attempt it and she said yeah
Oh Come
on yeah I thought maybe the equivalent
would be learned American states or
whatever even though I am European would
have been just as bad but yeah
maybe I'm better off learning the
Japanese prefectures than learning
American states oh I might be I'm a beat
um
yeah okay so some things are still
unclear but there will be like two
longer streams that are either FF or GTA
or both or what something like that uh
member stream Super Chat reading on
Tuesday Minecraft on Wednesday
and some special stuff going on
hopefully I just need
yeah
to be sure
packed week indeed very packed very
stressed because I also got some
private stuff to do
[Music]
um
yeah and my Japan trip my next one is
getting closer
oh actually I have to learn on
choreography somewhere
um
yeah
we'll see how it goes
no extra day off well maybe I mean maybe
I will I don't know
I'll I'll I'll see how it goes and yeah
yeah yeah
don't forget to think about sure take a
break two hours to go I have to go eat
food and just chill for a moment
I'll see you again on cast Channel
um
[Music]
yeah so thanks for watching
the playthrough of chihuahuas tears of
the Kingdom
it was so much fun
I'm glad you guys were joining me on
this adventure help will have more
and yeah I I I'm I'm partially
speechless it's hard to
say words but I had a lot of time uh fun
I can't speak I am confused
I didn't even drink my energy drink I
think I might be fine without
can't wait for next yellow flavor oh
yeah yeah right until the next one comes
out the new ones probably many years so
in between I do plan on playing
Twilight Princess Ocarina of Time and
some others
um
yeah
I'll be doing that
mm-hmm
my dress mask yeah sure let's go will
freak me out but yeah
foreign
hopefully they will be as much fun as
tears of the Kingdom
um
this hoodie I said yeah I'll miss it
this was a great asset I really loved
the assets that were made for me
and also the thumbnail art everything
thank you for providing that it's really
sweet how okay your feet whenever I have
like a big series like this going on
often they create stuff for me
you know to make things a little bit
more
um fitting for me and that I can
um immerse myself and you guys can
immerse yourselves too
so thanks blue and thanks John Ian
Ian I'm never sure in my head
thank you you too
um
for creating some cool stuff for me
it's like each Series has its own outfit
yeah right hey
this ass was ten times better than the
original orange potato chips bag what
what potato chips back
all right
with potato chips back
huh
do you mean my my soft drawn hat
or oh no you mean do you mean the not
the soft drone hat but the the other one
hey hey no roasting now and that one is
cute
oh Midnight's helmet for Twilight
Princess I'm sure there will be a
midna's helmet acid
if I play that yeah
um
okay I should probably go I'm like
stalling because I just I just want to
give this game as much time as I can but
yeah I gotta go I probably should go
yeah good that we didn't have too much
time pressure good that we could end it
comfortably so
um did you see whole grass oh yeah guys
if you see if you have nothing to do
until
um
the upcoming stream
I will link ah I can't do that but yeah
I will link you guys
um
here is
the um hologram that I'm part with with
the hollow live summer theme song group
I guess
I have some
thoughts about kfp in this hologram
[Laughter]
um
yeah watch it watch it watch it
I'm in it
I may not be in the thumbnail but I am
in the video I I didn't realize until
you guys
um tweeted at me
no well not tweeted at me but I saw it
in the kfp hashtag I'm like oh wait I'm
in that one because I saw the
reservation uh and the the thumbnail and
the Tweet about this hologram and it was
still upcoming and I'm like
Muna is in the in the Hologram with
Japanese girls oh it's nice to see that
apparently they continue to use overseas
members photograph every once in a while
and then I didn't realize that it was
the summer theme song group I didn't
realize that
until you guys told me no I remember the
lines now that I watched it I I remember
it now
but it kind of also blended into my
brain with another holograph that I
recorded for
where I'm really curious about the
finalized version because I
I
channeled my most insane self
for recording
that
because the script demanded it
um
yeah
you guys will think that I am absolutely
broken when you watch that one I don't
know when it comes out but
I was unhinged yeah
I just had to laugh at myself when I
recorded
but I went all in because I thought
that's what they want mm-hmm
yeah yeah on his tall girl
okay so enjoy the holograph I'll be
going I'll see you on Cali Channel and
in Germany
foreign
[Music]
bye bye
yay
[Music]
thank you
thanks for the membership thank you
foreign
[Music]