[Music]
you
my
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
we're kicking and kicking off the wig
and it's pretty genius isn't it i'm a
kikkity kitty that that actually is yeah
it's like it took me a year to think
about that one
well you know better late than never yes
yes we look like on my screen we look so
nice with the colors together your
orange fish and then
the yellow and you skirt with the yellow
in my hair we have some matching colors
going on there
yeah yeah nice composition oh wait i
want to try something
stay still oh man
stay still
okay i'm waiting
oh
i'm putting my head on on your kimono
okay your hair is kind of in the way but
oh that looks cute i think yeah that
would look cute i knew it like i love
the color combination of yours it's ah
ah it's nice
let me try to put you on my
you
cut cut it off nicely
at the neck
just like this in medieval
[Laughter]
it's not perfect but but yeah there it
is looking good and we got the matching
twin tails today
isn't that lovely
oh
did you did you ask nami mama for that
or did she just decide to give you twin
tails on her own
uh she just decided yeah
it was just like oh you get alternate
hairstyle and this is what knobby mama
picked i was like hell yeah oh
she's she got some good taste some good
sense
she knows what the people want
uh yeah i specifically asked for this
very specific shape of twin tails like a
spiky
fin type of twin tail
i was very specific but the other
hairstone that i got was was his idea
yeah
oh cute
so
amma is actually last minute not even
last minute last second also streaming
yeah don't don't worry about it i'm in
the back up in case the main one goes
down oh no oh are you
are you trying to sabotage me by making
my stream go down
no no
i'll ground the youtube satellite again
oh no you're not gonna do that
wait i'm it from the from the um screen
that we're in now the party screen will
i leave the party if i go back to the
main screen
for a moment no no no no you should be
fine yeah because look look look guys
here look
it's amelia
oh my god what the [\h__\h]
point five games to elect amelia watson
back what what what look at that look at
that
[Music]
what is my favorite
what did you say what did you say what's
your favorite
huh
well i can listen to you already oh
there's a russian oh oh there's that the
language announces here oh listen yeah
quadra kill that's five in a row that's
five in a row oh my god holy [\h__\h] i'mma
can count
oh
it's even called amelia watsonville
million celebration
it is it wasn't on purpose but i think
it's perfect timing that we're doing
this collab today because uh i heard
that like in one or two days this is
gonna not be available anymore
yeah yeah it'll it'll uh
disappear yeah forever this is the only
this is the last chance to get it if you
ever want to get it nice actually i'm
not sure exactly what yeah actually nice
timing thank you yeah you're welcome i
had a feeling
what is that oh that's somebody i don't
want to talk to you guys are you
messaging is there a dm on my bottom is
that at the end of dms show up at the
bottom
yeah so there's system and party i think
it's nobody's damning you hopefully
you know what happens
party
oh no
party you're still you're still in the
party i think oh okay i can only open
the party chat i don't know how to get
back into it into the screen that i saw
before
oh that's okay i'll just put us into a
game okay
uh oh yeah so this is uh my first uh i'm
allowed really this is my first um
pc fps my first online fps and my first
time doing an fps with the mouse so
it could yeah we have to play five
matches and then we can yeah five
non-black pictures
are these really
are bad
yeah uh there's bots on the enemy team
so uh if you pick your character that's
the character you get for the whole game
you don't get to choose in between some
games you can do that
wow okay oh i see they have some kind of
classes the plus one is probably some
healing class or something yeah
yeah the plus one is healing so if you
want to try healing um
you know i mean whatever you pick
whatever looks interesting to you uh
i'll help you through explaining it
um they're all not looking very cute um
the only one looking cute that's
available is a girl called cassie
oh
yeah uh she's a sniper i think she has a
bow so it'd be pretty interesting if you
want to try hell yeah i like a bow i
like me a bow i have some experience in
minecraft with a bow
lock in oh she's good
she has a bob
um maybe i wanted to pick somebody else
but okay this is this works
on you're you're uh you're a a cute
world of warcraft looking dwarf
uh yeah yeah he's not well he's kind of
tall but why is he saying paladins above
is that because you're an announcer
oh no i i think i got a really cool
frame i just spent some money and bought
some school things oh is it you look
very special there
okay what is this you kidding me
did i hear a chicken uh
uh wait can you speak again actually is
is i missed a last test
a little bit
uh
okay
i'm getting thrown into the cold water
i'm feeling but what is little ex
exactly okay eight seconds after using
dart roll your next weapon shots damage
is increased by thirty percent uh-huh
what
okay so
don't don't worry about it for now you
get it just shoot and get a feel for it
uh so yeah you have four different
abilities one of them might be a passive
or so and then you have an ultimate
which charges throughout the game and
your ultimate carries over to the next
round three so you'll see now
you get on a horse and we're gonna ride
to the point
just just try to shoot the enemy let's
try your best okay they're bots so
uh it's not it's not too scary right now
but on our team they're also bots
because they look like real people oh no
on our team they're they're not bots
okay so they're also beginners who still
have to do the bot match
yeah
who are oh that's from me okay is
friendly fire even possible
uh no not in this game though okay
of course i got a kill
okay and then i have to stand in the
control point
yeah so you just stand here until that
little timer or the little bar at the
top reaches 100 and then we get the cart
which counts as one point in the game
so once you get four points you win the
whole game uh-huh okay uh-huh
by the way everybody the game is free to
free to play
yeah it's free to download yeah
how many of you got announced uh amelia
watson
uh six
six i guess i think they're assist so i
don't think it counts she's cute
there's like a pink bunny girl with us
she's excited that's
the character you're playing is perfect
because you have a bird right above your
head
really
i think it's a phoenix actually yeah
what really yeah wouldn't that be too
perfect
i have some attacks don't i what's
what's a double kill
i'm natural you get confused about what
your attacks do you can press k
and uh it brings up
like uh the descriptions
i'm carrying on it
you are you're you're uh our kill leader
probably
oh we're already dead with i'm just
pressing buttons without really knowing
what they are right now
what's going on as long as you're you
have somebody who like just shoots stuff
and you're just shooting stuff at the
enemy that's pretty much all you need to
do okay
i think your character might have like
movement abilities
like that i just did a movement
oh nice
it doesn't matter where you shoot oh
chicken
um
yeah it doesn't matter you always want
to aim for the head yeah you'll do more
damage like that oh
we got the point
wait what what purchase items no no no
right oh so uh it's gonna be on
automatic purchase right now but there
is a mechanic in the game where you're
all just like well back here it's
connected we're all back in the base
oh yeah yeah so once you capture the
payload and push it all the way to the
end on their side
then it starts again because now you
have to capture the point again okay
then try to push it okay 15 seconds
uh
disengage blast shot fire and then
fire an explosive crossbow to blast away
enemies in an area dealing 450 damage
the famous announcer of paladins emilia
watson that you can only get like one
more day or so so download the game now
otherwise you'll miss it
actually guys this stream was uh oh [\h__\h]
i done
yeah why did you use the ultimate
vivi and you [\h__\h]
gotta i gotta cuss like a like a fps
player you [\h__\h] yeah
how would you do that how do you what
kind of swearing do they do um help me
out here
oh uh you hacker it was the [\h__\h]
thing yeah are you happy and you're
hacking
where is that hacker i'm going to report
you to the gm's or so i don't know
it's all day
so yeah now we capture the point and a
lot of times if you can't finish pushing
the payload all the way to the end we
have to capture the point again but
we're obviously going to get it though
okay
obviously not a match for us
nice push it push it apparently the
champion that you're playing people
think is like a little opie or like
broken so she's really good yes what
who's op
the the champion that you're playing
i don't have much choice so
double kill
i want to hear the armor voice actually
so far i must say
um i'm i i'm what are you doing
oh oh that's that's the uh this is
dragons ultimate i thought so i must say
it looks pretty good visually i'm liking
it visually this game
yeah yeah yeah
that's crap yeah it's not bad
it reminds reminds me of a
a pretty uh world of warcraft
oh yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
what i'm stoppable
seven kills is that what you're saying
where do you see your total kills a nine
straight you press
tab oh
[Laughter]
we did it was that the first game
yes that was the first game and four
more i unlocked adorable that's me i'm
adorable
cute
so at the top like where it says
everybody if you click on the last icon
at the top you can see the scoreboard
what where where everybody um uh oh did
you exit out of the
victory thing where it shows everybody's
poses i know i'm still in there
ah so at the top there's like these
little icons that you can click on
ah
oh
yeah so if you go to the last icon it
shows the scoreboard and you can
see you know how much damage you did or
if you're a healer how much healing you
did
oh
oh but i'm still i'm still
looking the weakest
out of all of us i need to become
stronger i'ma teach me the fps skills
teach me
uh
okay okay i'll try oh my maybe we should
damage go over this oh what actually no
my damage is higher than yours what was
your class was what was that class oh i
was playing a tank but i kind of wasn't
actually playing
oh i mean
is that your excuse summit
no no i'm excited
okay how do we how do we continue
um
how do we continue oh yeah so we'll play
another game but i wanted to talk if you
click on that champions uh tab uh on the
main menu
cassie yeah so here you can look at the
champions and then also like say if
you're playing cassie you can click on
her see she has a bird
she does and she has kind of orange red
hair like me
yeah
like the perfect character for you hell
yeah um
so if you
you can see all the abilities on the
left side and if you click on um
uh hold on oh yeah if you see at the top
there's like a little cards thing this
is maybe a little complicated for now
but i'll just explain it briefly so that
you understand because when you do start
the game it asks you like what abilities
and what cards you want to pick uh-huh
um so if you click something like create
new loadout and click on an empty slot
there's like different cards that
enhance different abilities oh it's a
card game
yeah
sort of yeah it's just like for the meta
gaming abilities and stuff you don't
have to look into it now but just so you
understand how it works yeah so you just
put different points into the cards for
the abilities that you like and then you
like build your own loadout sort of
thing so even though somebody else might
be playing the same champion as you you
might have it built like differently
just built different
oh cool
interesting like yeah well wait actually
i want to there's a champion that i
wanted to unlock hold on
worried
cute cute cute
can i use that or is that do i need to
unlock it
is that the sign for
needing to unlock it
check you see it right now
look at the skins skins
here skins skins
cassie
oh
cassie why does she change her voice
why is she becoming a different
personality when i give her a different
skin
oh yeah sometimes they do that there's
like some robot skins where they they
get they have like a robot voices oh
that's cute
that looks like me
timber timber and tinder what
why is it's the same outfit but it's a
different name and it sounds very
similar what does that mean
cute cassie
dragon cross dragon she got a dragon now
oh my god that's a valley girl outfit oh
my gosh she's sunkissed now beautiful
she got a freaking parrot on her hand
cassie it's funny how she changes your
voice i like that
oh dark cassie
what can i use that one
cassie the
i want
i want the
i want the timber i guess
yes
she's yelling timber
i need more oh i don't have enough
crystals i thought i had money that was
not the right money what about this
three thirty thousand i'm close no wait
i haven't okay i can be coral cassie
yeah yeah the other ones are
unblockable in a different way okay
and a coral crossbow let's go
wasting all my money on it let's go
well if it's if it's at least the gold
coins you get those pretty fast okay
while playing and stuff so all right oh
i didn't equip the last one okay
okay i'm ready ami
i'm ready let's go let's kill some
people
we're cute there we go
two out of five cassie cassie
i shall be the bird lady once again
yeah
amy
oh my famous announcer
if if you could have me be a a narrator
or announcer in the game which game
would it be
which game would it be yes it doesn't
have to be fps game this game
[Laughter]
i don't think they need to hold a lot of
people in this game
ah
i don't know
neopets
a fortnight they have a they have
announced their packs sort of and like
halo and call of duty oh
oh by the way uh i mean you are aware of
my
of my deaf loop um
adventure right you know that i was
playing that right
aren't
it was on on the ps5
um so it was with the controller
this is already like a lot easier to
play than on the controller on the ps5 i
gotta say
yeah fps games are they're kind of made
to be played with a keyboard and mouse
like me it just feels so familiar but
yeah you do have to get used to it but
you've been playing minecraft so you're
you're pretty used to it by now
okay let's go oh she's cute
okay
oh
it goes oh let's kill him let's kill the
bots
i'm already scared of
playing without oh god
playing without the bots and playing
with real people people are not gonna
have mercy on us are they it's their
okay they're not much better
can you
when you get matched in this game does
it only match you with people who are
like as new as you are
not sure actually maybe cat will know um
yeah i don't know what the i would hope
so
they can't just match you with
oh
with really good people when you're just
a noob
yeah we'll be going against people who
are new to the game too i think
it depends sometimes it looks like a
really high level person partying with
somebody who's that their base oh my god
we're camping at their base is that okay
it's fine there's not acceptable
oh god
oh what the [\h__\h] i got too close to that
weird fairy
she does a lot of damage because she has
like these fan projectile things that
explode oh
and they do it it's like a wide area
that they cover
oh
okay i'm coming back wait for me i'm
i'll protect you don't be scared i'm
coming
[Music]
i saved you i saved you it's
don't okay about it i'm here for you i'm
here for you
blue magic i need healing i need
oh thank you
i can i can she talk [\h__\h] talk you much
harder than this uh man be careful do it
you little [\h__\h]
you uh you suck at this game you can't
shoot you don't know how to use the guns
you probably shoot yourself in your leg
all the time every morning
[Music]
right in his heart
yes oh my god chad i know it's
incredible i'm playing with d announced
that's her ultimate she does like this
weird bounding thing
oh i thought that was your head oh the
bot is stuck like in the map
oh
[Music]
boom headshot
eating carrots of your crunch sorry
full free
to
push successful
we we got the baby out of it
boy or girl
uh
but i uh both
it's twins it's twins but wait my game
is not moving am i still in the game
um
it looks like it
oh [\h__\h] it crashed
oh
i was too good at the game
yeah
the baby was too powerful
oh what should i do you're back i'm back
really
no i guess it's the bot i'll wait or you
oh okay i got kicked out i think
i'm out mm-hmm i'm back in the starting
screen
oh but i'm about
[Music]
help me i don't think i can rejoin i'm
not in the party i
think you see that that party message
uh
yeah yes i saw it i saw it really oh so
i'm in the party we're about to finish
the game um in like the next few minutes
ah
because if i just leave i think i might
get like a cool down
but does this count as one game
probably not there might i thought you
could reconnect on some games but maybe
because it's a bond game it doesn't let
you damn it
damn it well that just means more time
with the uh paladin's announcer
you know look at um the different
champions if you want to see like
yes a healer that you might want to play
or like a tank usually i have somebody
in like every class sort of that i like
to play
what is that what is that one
something new
i don't see where chad where is that new
thing
something new cassie cassie
yes yes yes yes
paladin's announcer yes chad i know
mm-hmm
weapon skin ah weapon skin
oh oh there's a new one
oh did i look at it it's equipped
i'm still there i don't know
all right let's see who there is she's
cute
i s i see character nala hodor where's
squishy
uh-huh inora
cute she's cute i think
cute cute cute she's cute she's cute
or you can unlock them with the gold i
thought you have to unlock them by
playing the game but i guess
at least then you can
decide who exactly you want she's cute
thirty thousand hmm
sarty
where you are you're invisible sati
what
satin yams over oh well almost sarty
there you are
oh looks like a night elf
mm-hmm
who is this
oh cute
cool
wait which skins just you have herald
oh yeah you're still my party okay let's
play
letters
who is this lady sequin sati oh the girl
i just looked at
she she has a
uh
beautiful beautiful shoulder pads
it goes oh
did you notice chat that i was only
looking at girls has absolutely nothing
to do with anything
nice
i i made cassie now
so no one can take her away from me
i mean her
hey how are you doing oh
i got a gift intelligence somebody might
send you a random gift it's just like a
gay skin or something in the game what
you can just send it to people that
you're not even friends with
yeah i think what
oh christmas
kfp
i i i will gladly accept all kinds of um
skins
and
but uh
i'm not i will not be accepting any
friends requests just gifts okay
i was born ready i'm going impulse oh oh
my bow looks nicer now
i can't move can you move
five
four
three
two
oh yeah yeah oh this is weird we're not
in spawn okay
yeah this is
this is a different game mode than the
one we're playing
this one where should we go where do i
go i think you just get kills in this
one follow you
just get kills is there no no base or so
to like the [\h__\h] thingy
oh really it's just um i don't know
where everybody is actually oh [\h__\h] i
think i felt not follow me
[Music]
oh
how do you do the the zoom again
oh my god oh my god i in the tutorial i
learned that i can zoom but maybe it's
only with certain
weapons right clay probably usually uh
maybe maybe it's not possible of the bow
oh
yeah it might not be possible with the
bow because i think the bow might only
be hip fire
yeah chad is saying it it's just hip
fire but if you play like a character
that has a sniper there's a few
characters that are snipers uh you can
zoom in
okay
dying so much right now you need to be
more careful
i should have played a healer i forgot
that i put a different game lesson
no problem do we have any healers at all
right now
uh
yeah we do
it's the treat
okay it's all fair he's using guns i'm
using a bow is that fair
probably cassie is like not so much
close range because if you get close to
that guy his guns are pretty close range
yeah i felt that
huh oh
oh oh the tree what the [\h__\h] was that
tree oh my god there's that tree that
guy is an art pin
he's a healer okay
cool you stand near him you'll get heels
uh not my best game
are these bots because it looks like
they have real names yeah exactly
yeah but i think the bots might
oh
is this you is this you guys
are you not that there was five matches
against lots but maybe they changed it
oh [\h__\h] i'ma protect me be my meat
shields
okay
oh
i'm gonna kill you yeah
get wrecked you get wrecked
it's a job we just need um like 20 more
kills 20 more kills are we winning we're
winning
yeah we're winning i have a carrot in my
mouth
mmm yummy carrots
i like carrots too
gonna kill you i'm gonna kill you gonna
kill you damage dealer oh
yes that's me
i i want to use my old tee
comedy and friends let me use my old tee
what does it do
i don't know am i doing something
i think it's like a auto locks on to
people probably no
i have no idea what that did
what did that do chat
this is
fire
[Music]
enemy killing spree
yeah
[Laughter]
i'm dead
oh no it's okay you spawn instantly you
just need uh six more pills to win six
more oh my god yo
thank god i'm working
wow
[Music]
i feel like most of the time i was
shooting air but i tried
you know you hit some stuff what's
important for fps games is to make sure
your mouse sensitivity isn't too high or
too low uh-huh okay
uh what's also important is that the
healers do their job and adjust they're
too slow with their healing honestly
it's their fault
every time i die their fault stupid
healers
can't do [\h__\h]
um so if you want to open any presents
that you got if you click on store
it won't open anything weird and then if
you click on the top icon in the middle
it's a chest and you can there's a thing
that says open gifts
huh
wait uh sorry uh
a store
uh
chest
opening i got no gifts um
[Laughter]
it's okay put them soon
next game let's get let's see
next game until i can get i'mma we're
gonna we're gonna play this until i get
the i'm a voice pack i need it
it's gone
uh hold on that quest
assembler
there's like a second icon you can see
your uh progress on the amelia what's
that announcement three out of five
noise we don't even need to do 10
apparently
i think they changed it when i played a
few years ago
you used to have to play five games
against bots but i think it counts now
just like any matches that you play okay
i i don't even think the last match we
played was against bots i can't tell
what do you think i don't think it was
bots
but i don't know anything about this
game anyway
uh
but if if it's only two more then i
guess after getting the voice pack we
can play
a few more because i need to listen to
the beautiful voice of amelia watson
double i want the double experience
okay i'm gonna be sandwiched in between
amelia watson and amelia watson
yeah that sounds good
[Laughter]
are you still
using the same oh you do you do the
train out is that the tree from um that
marvel movie
um
no it looks like similar you know
similar his name starts with the g2 yes
grover yeah
oh it's not the same one
sad i like that three
match era
what do you mean
someone didn't our team didn't pick a
champion so we we have to look for
another game
it should auto select
yeah but then he's like oh this person's
probably afk so might as well
smart
let me see
okay
my iron mine
i got freckles i like freckles
i mean my character has freckles i feel
like yeah
the freckles would look really uh cute
on us don't you think
freckles on uh yeah i don't think i've
really seen a vetuva with freckles
before
there must be
we have freckles or uh cute
freckles hella cute hell yeah
hey i'm using the the german announcer
pack
i'm learning you don't need that i can
announce for you
guys
oh
baby i'm
tripled
record this right now put it into the
game directly
it doesn't change much to the
to the english words i guess we're using
some yeah similar words
[Music]
i don't know i don't want to read i'm
just gonna
i'm just gonna go with it oh it looks
icy here
oh yeah
we were here too
this is a king of the hill map so
there's just like a point and you just
have to capture it yeah look he would
think
are you a vegetable
did you manage to become a potato or
what i've heard you wanted to be a
potato what is what's that about
yeah i became a potato but now i'm
sprouting a little spud you're a
broccoli now
bland
four
three two beautiful you're looking a
little bit
to say
uh no like yo your your skin that needs
some skin cream because you're like uh
oh i'm dry yeah you look very dry fresh
gloves
yummy
hey that guy does a lot of damage
it did i ran right into the middle
that's okay
i like to fly
there's other characters that like you
can fly around sm or you can jump really
high or
holy [\h__\h]
they're in control
okay okay you're here with me yeah
healer is adjusting oh don't die you're
not adapting
inhaling
how about not dying man
but they have a flamethrower
[Music]
he is unstoppable
his dead body around in front of me how
traumatizing
[Laughter]
oh my god
nice uh wooden butt you got there uh man
thank you
this way okay
there's a guy behind us
get his nuts
okay we'll finish one for you i i i'm
avenge it
wait is that 149 kills the [\h__\h]
we're losing almonds oh so this is this
is king of the hill so it's like a
control point and so whoever has control
of this area
number goes up what is the matter with
you i just woke up
i just
look i have awoken from my sleep
spawning in 15 seconds oh man
oh man
where is the party here is the party
don't you hurt my baby
it's okay you got the tail you got to
come really i did oh my god
i did
oh
wow there's a lot going on man
yeah
sometimes it's kind of scary because
there's so many abilities and characters
that you don't know what they do
yep yep yeah
what's your favorite fps game
favorite uh
maybe cs go i really like csgo
[Music]
but uh it's it's kind of
it's a little punishing like when you
first play it but it's like a a good
bare bones fps because there's no
abilities and things like that you just
have a gun and you're just a regular
person
i i i have heard a lot about the game
that has been around for like a long
time right
yeah it's like the game well counter
counter-strike in general has been
around for a long time but yeah cs go to
has also been around for quite a while
ultra ammo
oh inside no no no you can't you can't i
did not give you permission yet
do you see their their blue guy that he
puts totems down on the ground and
that's that's what that was
can we kill the totem too
yeah you can shoot the totem and you can
also uh it's good it's always good in
these types of games to target the
healer
and uh
damage and kill them
they have no idea that they're dealing
with two gamer girls right now
if they knew that
cuties
if they knew
uh so this guy's ability
[Music]
yeah yeah oh man
hello
i think we are playing against enemies
i think every time you play like another
game they increase the difficulty
stop shooting
spawn camping report
what do you call the thing that you used
to look at people far away
oh a scope oh yeah 30 60 no scope or a
360 no scope
what's that what's that mean what does
that mean 360 no scope it means you make
a complete circle with your mouse and
then shoot without scoping in
what does this scoping mean
opening this leg
uh scoping it means like when you zoom
in you know how like
you can zoom in with that
damn cool i want to do that that's my
goal
your goal is to get a 360 no scope
no it's a 360 no scope that's my goal
okay
i killed the totem
yeah this guy's on the
electric guy
he's a healer
[Music]
real people i don't know
i'll
damn there's no mercy on noobs like me
huh
now that you know they don't know
they're just playing
[Music]
[Applause]
okay now i'll play i'll play for real
i was just playing like you're gonna
play for i hope yes please i need my pro
game my girl emilia watson what did i i
called you for this collab because i
thought you know
fps games who could teach me that is not
a question it's only one person that i
can ask to teach me an fps game and it
is amelia watson the announcer of
paladins it can only be you
you can only have you made it you made a
good choice just
you know i'm warming up i'm warming up
warming
i wanna buy a champion really quick hold
on hey you got an eight kill streak oh
man
holy [\h__\h] uh
maybe
whoa
well then i'm getting more crystals wow
[Music]
wow
where are the presents
where are the presents where are the
presents friends requests where are the
prisons men what what
where are the prisons lame
[Music]
oh is that present
oh no that's
what i bought
i'm too low level for president your
level is too low they were trying to
give me presents but i'm too low level
uh sounds like you're too low level yeah
i know that was the thing what is my
level four ah okay i need to be level
ten apparently
oh
okay that's okay they'll all come in
when you get to level ten
i'm waiting for it
are you buying something right no yeah
i'm ready oh yeah yeah i'm done
i'm just uh
wow plus zero percent
the event pass gives us and uh
unbeatable plus zero percent exp
[Laughter]
look
that lady
i'm gonna try to get some
more headshots this time
seems like some people can survive a
headshot though not very realistic got
to say
yeah i think most people can survive um
because your health is pretty high um
we don't have a healer but oh neat trick
for this is for paladins if you walk
away there's like this little cool down
bar underneath your health
if you're out of a fight and not taking
hits you'll automatically regenerate all
your health back okay
okay kill your enemies hold the
objective to gain points first team two
ah so another four hundred points okay
oh yeah i'll put on these for the next
game instead
okay is this the last game for you for
like uh to get the announcer back
probably yeah
oh
oh you see are you ready for this the
announcer back
oh my god
oh my god there's a lot of money here
i'm gonna take some of that home all
that gold oh i was so shiny
shiny
which one is um that's you oh
oh you're also healing as well or
what is that what kind of character is
that the battle yeah this is a it's
called a flank character so i just i
just do have like machine gun
applause so that you can pounce with oh
you when you scratch my back with dog
i'm feeling a bit itchy
oh
wow that's so cool man
i don't think i've ever been on this map
before it's like haunted or something
it's oh it's like a cthulhu map
honestly everything looks like world of
warcraft to me i don't know why
where's everybody
i see you
oh
take cover
oh [\h__\h]
an enemy
well that was a mistake
[Music]
[Laughter]
shouldn't press f uh f is really just f
what is your f
it makes me shoot like four dash forward
while attacking i suppose but
yeah
the smartest thing to do when i'm trying
to stay away from them
ah
they do be dead though
oh nice we didn't it was a nice combo
you finished it
i was doing damage on
is she behind the wall sometimes i'm not
quite sure where they're ah
they are here dragon
i feel like someone in the kfp has that
name are you from canada oh somebody's
about to get fired yeah
is it easy to like snap someone in this
game or is
this pretty tough
i i feel like it's pretty tough because
there's just so much going on but i feel
like if you're sniping against bigger
characters it's easy because there's
some pretty big characters
oh [\h__\h]
she built the wall
oh i can shoot the wall you can break
the walls
uh i don't think you can right
[Music]
stand behind me okay i will i'll try
oh no no
we're waiting at the moment
beautiful that's what i like to see
what's in what did you just do i saw
that
i didn't know the hole right there
in the sea
[Music]
i think i revealed people to the rest of
that's so useless
at the moment that's very useful
don't die
okay i have expert movement abilities
they have more kills than we do now oh
no we're falling behind
i killed ghost
i killed the ghost
but they were already dead but i killed
them again because you're now a double
ghost
what is that
magician looking lady what does she do
oh
um
lady this the one with stones or the one
the one with the dress
oh yeah i think she's a tank so she has
like a wall and she's pretty tanky
she couldn't do too much damage i think
a tank oh that's why she took some time
oh we're winning this is a nice match i
feel like we're we're more equal than
before in the previous one
yeah yeah especially because like this
type of game mode a lot of the times
people don't pick like a real
composition from the team and usually a
real composition for a team includes
like having a tank for a defense you
know and then having support healer yeah
[Laughter]
we don't have that here
that was german
did you watch the did you watch the
whole talk with jaguar
yeah i watched a little bit of it
he he was praising you amen without me
even like really
initiating crazy he was talking about vr
chat and how
where he studies it and then i'm like
yeah mimi
is all possible because of her and he
said yo ahmed she's like so impressive
wow wow
yeah yeah he's got he got his eyes on
you um
it's sweet i don't know it's kind of
embarrassing but no
not embarrassing i feel like very proud
to have you
okay
well as long as he dies uh sooner or
later
i'm happy
you should try um like another character
because sometimes there's characters
that like they have uh area effects
which can be especially like for
somebody who's new to fps can be a
little bit easier oh cause you're kind
of like hip firing you're like a hip
firing sniper
hip firing sniper
yeah i know it sounds weird
well yeah my hips are on fire can't help
it i mean i can't stop that
where are they
where are they and there's fun
oh god i'm saying
[Applause]
how do you undo that
are you dead yeah oh man
my lt's so useless man
oh
i guess i could uh
try out more
characters when i have like a bit more
choices and and like time to look at
every character
yeah
some of the characters they like rotate
them out for
like who you can play and stuff during
different weeks and things like that
not
let's yet yeah good question
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
thank you
thank you very much
i have cute and right yeah i've been
using human right click chat just just
uh
maybe not that often but
i try i just
jump off the map
what you jumped off the map
no not me oh damn those are you saw
someone jumping off yeah
[Music]
where am i okay they got it
my hero
amelia wanted
i always said
i think it's really cool that you're
like part of the game like that i wanna
i wanna do that too
yeah
if you ask me any kind
my song is in the ribbon game
yeah i think there's like a little tiara
pixel like
shouldn't have been so close to all of
them but we're winning let's go come on
nine more nine more
go go go go
yeah go go we got it
horsty go go hoisty
what
victory
that's a win
yeah that's a pretty challenging game
he is sniper what do you mean oh yeah
you mean because that was too close yeah
i unlocked a million once in one million
celebration legendary you're legendary
um you're legendary equipping cover
copyright 2016 cover corp they had to
write that on there didn't they come on
yeah on that tiny picture
i got it i want to listen to it you
play game play
[Music]
what does objective time mean
uh objective it's like uh how much time
you spend on the point so the point is
the objective during the game oh
no don't rover's my favorite
i heard you talk louder can i turn you
louder
uh
i don't know
maybe audio might be in the volume
[Music]
notification
i'm gonna turn them a bit higher maybe
that helps
hey how are you doing what that was not
ahmed who was that voice
talk to me not you amen
okay
i mean frog aisle
oh yeah this one's pretty good i mean
not you
oh
i have here in on my screen in obs she's
a she's a shiny
shiny rare element and the one in the
game is the legendary armor can i
i don't know what is big game
we do scroll down
oh no i want to change it
did i already select it
oh well
wow
cute you look fluffy
hello
about do you have your own voice back on
too
no i i i i changed it i don't know dad
you should listen to yourself
i can't
but uh i hope you enjoy it if you get
three kills you get that
baby
let's go first time
[Music]
i'm gonna like really rock this i feel
so strong now
and i immediately died
[Music]
maybe i was flustered by the
overwhelming amount of ammo
yeah
i'm a sniper i'm a sniper
i'm supposed to be the only one here
faker
he's a different character boring
oh my
objective lost no
what objective
[\h__\h]
oh yeah so there's a point over there
that we're supposed to it's like the
other one of the other games we played
where we get the payload and get the
push it
do i have to shoot the payload
uh no just uh try to kill
uh and stay alive okay
ha ha ha ha it's again the cassie that
killed me oh what did this guy just do
he fell off the
cliff not the smartest boy but he got
the spirit
did you see that
i eliminated thank god oh oh what the
[\h__\h] they're coming
yeah that spot back here is pretty good
that's that guy's ultimate it's an
important kill it hits you with it
damn
and uh there's like some abilities you
can get to help kind of kill the other
team like there's one of the items that
you can buy
that uh
reduces the amount of healing that they
get from their healers so right now they
have two healers so that's like oh
oh no
that lady that killed you is actually a
healer too
unbelievable
where is i'm in here oh i got it yeah i
just died but i got two kills with my
ultimate
oh
good job
where are they oh
are we are we winning we're losing right
now
um
either
i guess i know we're losing a little
bit six seconds remaining 30 seconds
remaining says amelia watson
[Laughter]
[Applause]
30 seconds remaining
oh no
eight seven
six
oh
okay they're in overtime right now but
they're yeah they're dead okay
i did something good okay guys oh
actually that was uh us together
[Music]
this is
pretty fun i could do this more often oh
i wouldn't mind playing this more often
with you on there yeah
because i think
you'll probably like if you try some of
the other champions and stuff you might
find somebody who's like a bit easier or
so for you to play but yeah
you know it's good practice for you too
especially for aiming and things like
that true yeah
i i
but with this one where i have to go
slower i can take some time to aim
properly
yeah it's better in the long run because
then when you do switch to like
i'm
a bit confused i thought snipers were
the ones who can zoom in and i'm a
sniper and yet uh it won't give me that
a few different types of snipers in this
game because she is a sniper but
yeah she has like a crossbow so yeah
uh
it's just different
oh we gotta get on the point that's 70
percent ah
stop it
[Laughter]
oh damn
bird lady i see you there i see you he
does a lot of damage i guess he does a
lot of damage
they're about to be right around the
corner
thank you thank you go on go amen
are by the way are the flowers dead by
now the ones i sent you yeah they dried
out yeah
how long were they alive
for like a solid 10 to 12 days i think
damn that's that's pretty good that's
decent
yeah i think it's pretty good yeah nice
oh
thank you again
do you have a favorite flower
uh
yeah i like i like um sunflowers are
pretty
true
i don't really know too much about like
flowers to be honest
but me neither
the
flowers they came with like a little
tiny bug and i trapped him i captured
him what
on purpose so it wasn't just like
chilling there
uh well it was just chilling but i put
it in a terrarium
because i have a few and then i gave him
some seeds and he's he's killing
and i messed that up
it's nice that they sent an extra pet
yeah
there's nice of them
as if they knew that uh
as if they knew that you like
these kinds of
insects and yeah
you should get a frog on me
i've been thinking about it
i've had a frog before it was a fully
aquatic frog yeah it's called a african
dwarf frog and they uh oh they're really
cute you can keep them in like a five
gallon tank is it as as toxic as uh you
are almond
i don't i don't know
i wouldn't be surprised
hey can you get
toxic frogs that easily
uh actually probably not i think the
only
i think there's like poison dart frogs
you might be able to keep as a pet
but it might depend on where you live
because sometimes not allowed
beautiful announcing um a good job
wonderful
oh so if they capture the point uh this
game then it's game over she yeah we're
losing a lot
they don't know who they're dealing with
oh why did i jump in here
oh
stupid cat it's always gas
bird lady always attacking and a bird
lady
they just have so much
or they don't really have too much
damage just they have a lot of heels
because they have two healers it's the
hooded lady and the little fox looking
guy
they both do heal so it's kind of hard
to do damage against them sometimes
would you say this game is paid to win
or not really
no no not not at all i don't think well
i mean you don't have to unlock
champions and things like that but it's
oh wait we have the point
it's not like a pay-to-win thing because
it's not like you can only unlock
abilities with money
nice
good to know
yeah
and you can uh if there's like a
champion you want you don't have to use
real money to get it you can mm-hmm
we got it captured
[Music]
what a kill what a kill as if i got a
hawks eye man
nice
actually uh before the stream
i took a little nap because that was uh
getting cozy with my kitty cats
yeah and i had
a a weird dream
oh
what about what
i
i had a weird dream that i
was lurking
every night
and they were talking about me and i
i
uh i didn't realize i was using my real
account
and i i i answered something
and then it was so [\h__\h] embarrassing
it was like holy [\h__\h] they 100 saw that
how can i
how can i get out of this mess
it's like it's like when you have a
nightmare like people that go to work
and stuff they're like oh i had a
nightmare i went to my office naked
[Music]
related but then i woke up and i was so
happy that
it was
not real
do you remember your dreams a lot
yeah i do i usually do but uh i don't i
don't know if i dreamed last night
what that's possible
yeah it's the the fox guy on the other
team um
his ultimate ability turns
people into chickens in like a certain
area
that's so cute
yeah maybe i should practice that uh
character
yeah he's pretty good he has like uh
he throws like potions on the ground
sort of and they heal or do damage
fun
what's his name you know the name
hip hip okay i'll try to remember do we
still have the the thing the objective
thingy yeah we're still pushing it but
the person who's on the point
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
capture
frog
apparently intelligence is in the chat
what they said
they said that you shouldn't be able to
play any champion maybe i don't know if
that's for me or for you i'm sure you
mean they just unlocked me some
champions
maybe no way
for me
paladins from the game paladins where
emilia watson is the announcer of
paladins which is only available for
like one more day so get the game now
it's free of free of charge is that that
palette this one
they're a person i thought it was a game
how is that possible how can a game shop
thank you paladins this stream is not
sponsored this is just me trying to
learn learn the fps game
yeah and be really shitty at it yay
some characters that i wouldn't mind
getting one or two cuties as well and
just kidding she's just kidding excuse
me she's kidding she's kidding this
sounds like um
i am like
oh over time over time
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's the pink it's the [\h__\h] thing
oh i got an epic skin
you got an epic skin what did i get
an epic weapon
got another epic skin
oh a champion pack
looking pretty empty here
oh coco
nice that's good for you
they probably want to send me stuff but
they can't because i'm still level six
oh
yeah i think it's because you have to be
level 10 to get the gifts
[Music]
i'm an independent business woman okay
i'm the owner of the worldwide biggest
fast food franchise kfp okay
nothing can stop me
nothing
you get him i believe i want to play
another game um
okay
this is fun
yeah it is it gets pretty addictive
especially when you start getting like
kills i love the sounds
really satisfying i like the the red
color in the text when it says i killed
the enemy i like that it's beautiful
yeah yeah it's a little like symbol
that's that appears when you get a kill
oh someone in the chat asks how much
does that voice cost it's free of charge
you just have to play five games and the
game is free of charge too it's like
this is the second sponsored stream of
yours
i've never done a sponsored paladin
stream so oh oh yeah i guess that was
just uh
yeah normal stream but you were i guess
kind of on your own advertising it's
like paladins you know it's fun
i've been enjoying it too
actually we chose this game because i'm
uh i asked amma for a collab like one
day ago two days ago one day ago yeah
yeah and she was doing a members stream
and then i was like
which which fbs game could we play
together for a beginner and then she
asked her members so her members decided
that we play this
nice nice yeah it was it was it was it
was fate it was destiny
that was playing this
yeah because i asked like which out of
three games would be best for somebody
who's new to fps to play and paladins is
pretty easy to pick up because there's
just so many like abilities and
champions like one that'll probably
click with you
um yeah [\h__\h] your abs um
[Laughter]
wouldn't mind getting covered on by a
bubson again
holy [\h__\h]
oh yeah you did you did right
yeah i'm not surprised
yeah
you're putting so much work in these
days it's showing
you yeah i've been trying i've been
working hard um chat what do you think
is the best one uh does anyone know what
what's good here i don't know which one
i want i don't have time to read who has
time to read nowadays huh this looks
cute because it has a big big boob
i got the big burp one oh it is like a
if you ever like want to or take time
yeah you can if you know your abilities
you just read them and you're like oh
this does that and blah blah yeah it's
kind of like a meta gaming sort of thing
where you just boost the abilities that
you like to use like say if there's like
a movement ability there's probably a
card that boosts that movement or in
some way
everything you said 100
entered my brain while i was looking at
your buff arms and abs um
how does it feel to have so many muscles
i don't know how it feels after noodle
arms
uh i feel like rainbow oh one got first
blood
i panic
you panic don't panic it's all good so
good gonna be okay we're gonna win this
i believe yeah
i have yet to hit someone i think
it's okay it's not good not a good arena
for me
are we are we uh
are we pushing something
uh we're capturing the objectives so
it's just like the last game we played
where there's a point in the middle okay
and then uh yeah you capture the payload
and then push it okay
okay
paladins unlocked everything for you
just now are you sure where do you see
that
why would they do that that's so nice of
them
i might have a typed it in the chat
maybe i wasn't looking at the chat
paladins hooked me up
i might play your game more often
[Music]
[Applause]
where did she go
our healer is pretty good she's good at
keeping you guys up
[\h__\h] yeah
wow nice shot
hmm
what the [\h__\h] what was that
oh we got it yeah
[Music]
wow i kind of feel bad for the team
they're getting rolled a little bit
i mean
we got paladins on our side so yeah
we're kind of too strong right now
what should we call it amen
oh yeah push successful um maybe like a
mix of our names yeah because we both
you know helped and
i did it
like um
congratulations you're gonna grow up
into a strong strong child yeah
beautiful
15 seconds
your voice could be a bit louder
honestly i would like to hear it louder
yeah
maybe there might be a setting to turn
it up maybe
this is like
you gotta imagine these people are gonna
download the game just for your voice
just like me
so we're like
we're we're a whole life
fans looking for a oshie that's all we
want man
we want to hear her loud and clear
yeah okay that was that was uh
i knew that was gonna happen
i like
that it's like kind of little
fantasy style fps game
yeah yeah it's like a you know you have
magic abilities and things that can't
really be explained yeah
because other other fps games they they
look more i don't know stale
they look more
um gray and and sad
okay not all of them but with some of
them that i've seen so i like i like the
look of this one
i got her butt
[Laughter]
guys yeah it gets addictive when you get
the kills yeah also yes yeah i'm using
the german announcer pack because
i thought it'd be good to learn german
you know oh really i want to learn
german
it's been taught
it's been told amelia amelia your name
pronounced in german is amelia by the
way
amelia
you're like flexible no bad
oh i picked the wrong ability that's
okay
[Music]
who is this guy
bird lady assistant
no wait that was you killing someone ew
uh if you get an assist that still
announces it for you because you
technically did damage you were doing
damage and you helped
even though you didn't get the finishing
glows
oh baby
i got the assist ah
christy
i'm about then so while you're watching
how about putting the amelia and kiara
skins into the game oh yeah that'd be
crazy
you could totally see like a kiara skin
for cassie
i'm a phoenix by the way paladins if you
didn't know i'm a phoenix she's a
detective i'm a phoenix just saying
just kidding just kidding no pressure
man i'm just joking okay
that must have hurt
i'm sorry
what am i getting these kills who am i
what what's happening it must be the
paladin's buff oh my
i got
maybe uh yeah 50 damage buff
that's the true power that was hidden
inside of me
getting used to the game i think
i'm just i'm just gonna i'm just that
good good get on my level amen
[Music]
i didn't know you could climb walls with
the person i was playing because i was
build the phone oh whoa whoa unlocked
blood one whoa
is that the sexy
oh wait wait oh let me look
maybe i need to restart the game or
something
you shouldn't have to if you got it um
and you should receive it like uh
because you're not
you can't get something right
i i don't know if i got it from the from
playing the game or from uh
from them but i got a sexy new outfit
how do i have all the champions unlocked
maybe
how do i do it just click clear all but
then
and when do you
ah thank you paladins thank you
dragon crawler ninja
son when are these things go do i have
to click
oh my god belly girl cassie i got her
really
what holy [\h__\h]
what
the way she says cafe like as if she has
gum in her mouth
[Laughter]
berry
bark is that a champion
yeah he's really fun he uh you can build
turrets so you can put down like two
little turrets and they shoot people
within a range and then you also get
like a shield that you can open up and
uh you have a shotgun and you have like
this really fun movement ability with it
okay
thank you paladins
i need to get used to like the whole
interface i don't know how to do things
at all
yeah kiara's gara is new to fps games
and things like that very new this is
literally my first online fps game yeah
literally the first
i don't know what level are you right
now uh six
cassie
[Music]
i don't know if you have time but we
could play until i don't know how long
it would take to get to level 10.
but then you could get looking pretty
slow
yeah maybe
i think there's uh some questions but oh
it's too late
i don't know what the there's sometimes
daily quests that you can do to get more
xp and things
if i write in the lobby chat uh
only our team can read it right
yeah i think so yeah
somebody stole cassie from you let's do
that did i not walk in i don't want to
be
no okay the other cute girl but she's a
healer i don't know
now
yeah
um
how do i use the dragon
uh i think the dragon has like
projectile missiles so you shoot from
from pretty far okay
and then uh you can also fly around yeah
like i can fly
yeah and your ultimate ability is like
as soon as you hit somebody with it it's
like an instant kill so if there's
anybody you really dislike you can
target that
your your
grover card looks really cute cool
very fancy okay what is this fusilli
mamma mia damaged doubt when hitting an
enemy directly with rubber laundry
resolve was increased by 25 movement
speed
fire spit applies
and knocked ideas additional 300 damage
i don't know i'll use this oh i can't
okay
oh
the battle is about to begin
okay whatever
you're cherry blossom tree now i
think sort of yeah
you're so cute
what a pink tree you are
look at this i'm spider-man
okay very slow shooty shooty okay
uh yeah so i think uh because it's a
projectile it might do damage in like a
small area it's not like a sniper where
if you shoot specifically ah okay so i
don't have to be so exact
yeah you should try to be but
there's some
well that cassie just died in front of
me so i think she needs to give me the
character bag
she's not
it's a little difficult because we don't
have a tank oh no
that's all right
who has the killing spree
oh why are the doors closed
what the hell
no
all right
oh no
oh where do you like my daikon
what was that
[Music]
just trying to do my part here
the door's open when you get closer
[Music]
i guess rejoining is not really an
option
i think
you should be able to um
let's see
it's okay a lot of times when you have a
game
you're getting rolled in the game goes
pretty fast
like uh you look at the top it's two out
of four so it's just one more round of
them winning like that oh
[Music]
windows update can you read the room the
air in the room windows please i'm
streaming and playing a game i'm gaming
yeah
what the hell
playing paladins i'm not gonna update my
windows now do i look like i got time
this is beautiful 15 seconds yeah that's
pretty
wow nice garden
me like oh you can go over here
oh swim
oh [\h__\h] go on
no time
no time for taking a bath
okay
oh i need
you're one
stinky yeah playing fps games makes me a
little sweaty oh i'm not sweating at all
maybe uh you need to try a little bit
less hard
no apparently there's like this thing
you could take it's like some deodorant
pill
the older one
yeah if you take it it like makes your
sweat smell nice what
yeah
that sounds
really
weird
is that even healthy
i don't know
i i heard about it and i i don't know
too much about it but i think it's real
it must be real because i know somebody
who takes it now i know what now i know
what to
send you as a birthday present next year
yeah deodorant pills
my aim is so bad right now they don't
happen
i also noticed a
strong difference in the way my
projectile
acts
compared to my arrows like my errors
were like super fast but my shooting
shoot now it's like it arrives way later
then yeah yeah yeah when i'm a lot of
times like uh when you're playing fps
games people talk about the difference
between a hit scan
a weapon and a projectile weapon so
projectile usually has a travel time and
hit scan is usually
you know almost as soon as you click
yes yes my understanding
professional talk amelia watson
i just say pew pew and shoot shoot
and ouch ouch
wow i keep thinking i keep seeing our
cassie on our team and i think asu
enemy can't see bad cassie
she's almost dead okay
i mean you need to send me like a fps
dictionary is there is there such a
thing i wonder like as a joke item maybe
there's an fps dictionary yeah i think
it might be well yeah there might i
could totally see that being like a joke
item
joke
thing uh
yeah
nice
like something that some people will say
like when they're communicating in fps
games is like oh that enemy is lit like
the
uh
i don't know what what is the name
what's the name of this guy we're on day
huh
they're coming
predict i can't remember the name
oh look i'm lit i'm little
[Music]
waste dope super lit
like a lot of times if you just died to
somebody but you didn't damage them you
can say like uh they're lit they're lit
they're lit
they'll win tommy
i can't vote
i would like to write a formal complaint
i'm gonna pull uh an amelia watson at
the end i'm gonna say the game
disconnected and i'm just gonna
close the game on purpose
that's called an amelia
it just crashes you know like that
it just happens i know i know i'm in
oh
it's just it's it's kind of difficult
when they have somebody who's really
tanky and we don't
it just means they have somebody to
absorb all the damage
like a sponge like a spongebob
yeah
i could have played tank but when you
have to pick between playing a support
character to heal your team and like
tank you're probably better off
picking a support oh
ah i unlocked a champion pack
sorry almond that way
why not sorry to me hey
what about me
[Laughter]
what what happened so someone wrote in
it
yeah
i don't know what you did oh is there uh
are they apologizing because we lost
probably yeah they tried their best they
tried
oh the normies must be thinking like
what are those idiots talking about
lamb
okay let's see let's look at this whoa
the sniper has seventy
six thank you paladin
oh that pack gave me all the people
yeah so you can uh go through
i got them all i got them all
oh my god she looks she looks like
natalie dorma what the [\h__\h]
she looks like that's the dormer in um
uh you know when she has that
what
am i thinking somebody else sorry in in
the in the in the movie uh um
she played in that movie where she uh
had her hair blonde and and shaved on
one side not in vikings but she does
also look like that viking's chick how'd
the game stand actually dormer in the
hunger in the hunger games
the the lady called tyra
she looks like her eyebrow
tyra the untamed she said
she's pretty good too oh she has a it's
not a sniper rifle it's an assault rifle
so i guess it's kind of like a maybe an
ak or so
yeah
understand what you're saying is that
pew pew or pew pew pew or pew pew pew
pew pew
pretty rapid fire
fire grenade i'm sure you've seen it in
um one of the games we played but it
does like a fire spot on the ground and
it does quite a bit of damage
uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh and then uh her
ultimate has like super rapid fire where
i think you have
you don't have to reload so you just go
blah blah blah oh
good to know
yeah
i was a favorite
for the paladin's community manager yeah
she's really fun to play i like her
voice lines a lot too
she's like don't run that sort of one
who's who
all right
still talking about okay
russian tyra
is that russian tyra
i think she has a russian x and i don't
remember
oh
it kind of sounds like it yeah good
obsidian
whoa
cool obsidian timer is cool
cosmic tyre
has some good
good looking outfits there hmm
yeah she does
tyra i like that
i saw the fish one like on the screen
and i thought oh is that a new champion
but it's a tyra it's tyra yeah oh she's
cute what the [\h__\h]
what's her name io eel
the shattered goddess oh
she should debut as a youtuber
oh yeah she's a she's a does support
yeah she is cute i could totally see
this like a being a youtuber
so she also has i guess it's a bow or is
that no that's not yeah
it kind of looks like a bow
can't tell
oh you see have you played her before
yeah it is a boat no i haven't played
her um yeah she does a lot of the
supports actually can do quite a bit of
damage like uh
she probably does quite a bit and then
uh-huh
uh ying yeah she does a ton of damage
too he's also pretty
oh
man i don't know who to go with i want
to play
one more one more match one more minute
who should i try somebody new on
chad who should i who should i go if it
must be a girl
i i recommend tyra because uh yeah she's
like good for especially for practicing
shooting and things like that okay
okay let's go with tyra let's play
thank you thank you belgium
speed running the game right now
it's pretty fun yeah there's like a you
know you could play with five people in
a party so
it would be pretty fun
i feel like i have unlimited
possibilities right now of all the
champions this power oh yeah
who is your champion
oh what what did you say
who's your favorite um
grover
oh okay oh wait where is she here there
she is
tyra
look customize your champion customize
your champion
uh oh i think like oh i can't wait i'll
have
not enough money right now that's okay
we're looking at default tyra
grover is my favorite
announcer keanu would be cute
imagine
the hunt calls
i'm trying a cute v tuber i
want
looking forward to
how you're gonna play her
i've never played her before zombred
gaming that's so that's so damn right is
all these fandom right
in the uh yeah enemy team
there's at least one sniper there
i mean you know what to do yeah
yeah mob pop the drum rate
bully that's all right
has three charges but reduce the damage
of h2650 only 100
[Music]
can only do this one anyway okay
ordered his skills
auto rifle fast firing automatic rifle
that is 105 damage
a grenade that explodes on impact
okay okay the only 700 fire bomb heroin
incendiary device leaving a pull of fire
mark your parade to gain vision 50
increased weapon damage against him oh
and hence
wait a minute
wait
what uh she already
uh in-game um started counting when i
was still reading
oh oh oh okay this is where it is okay
oh did i just did they place that
is that a wall yo that's cool
continuously push the left mouse button
or do you usually
um
go pew people move your finger
so usually like with uh when you play
with guns like that that continuously
shoot you can hold it and pull down
because a lot of time there's recoil so
you want to pull down to account for
that recoil
um i don't know for tyra you can use
first so that's a good one so just like
click and hold for maybe like a few
seconds
okay a short amount of time
thank god for auto reload thank you game
dev loop did not have that
no no that was pretty difficult man
especially with the controller
yeah i think if it's your first time
playing it's probably pretty difficult
um get used to like some mechanics if
you don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
become fried chicken by my hands yes yes
super
oh she's doing the naruto run whoa
who is that oh pink-haired chick was
doing a naruto rack
yeah she does a she does the naruto
i knew exactly what you're talking about
such a
believe it
believe it enemy killing spirit they're
doing killing spree no
they can't kill like three of us i think
unbelievable
yeah i have a little fox pet that i
spawn on the side oh i think it's oh
okay it's like emanating heels okay
cute
yeah it's like a spirit box
it looks a little bit confused like why
my hair what am i doing here
we have like the ultimate base set up
actually because we have this uh
engineer on this
fight with his parents
they got no chance against us
but sad a bit sad yeah i think their
tank is scared of us we shouldn't push
oh my ultimate does let's see
what is that
oh
i tapped out of the game what the [\h__\h]
i killed him
who
the tank i think i he got mad at those
talking [\h__\h]
i want to hear more of that i want to
hear toxic i mean i really like toxic
ahmed
ah but balance has been so nice i don't
want to give them
i heard her saying pickle pickle pickle
while she was running there
people
did you kill two people
yes
double kill
i was just
spamming you definitely
oh it's right click right here
oh
okay
this is fun
yes yes
fun
you caught they're calling that a kill
yeah
yeah yeah
i'll forgive you this time only if you
give me back a kill
all right
we'll make a trade
[Music]
you know the tables are being turned no
no
no no no you're on the point
no no nothing's turning
everything is stable
okay
[Applause]
sorry get out of here
spray and pray that's another
slang term it's used in fps games
i think you
[Music]
some right buddy losing on purpose just
to make us happy
[Laughter]
[Applause]
i got the russian skin
yeah
i want to wear the
the russian skin [\h__\h] yeah
there they are
sorry
i've been focusing on the game i have
barely seen them
now i see you
oh i learned how to say happy birthday
in russian but i was like
ah
i know i know babushka
match everyone no
look yes again
yes
i don't
[Music]
thank you happy birthday to you
oh
she looks cute
what's up
oh my god why is there a cat
who is that cat is that yours it's me
you have a pink cat oh my god oh my god
is that the same character as before but
with a different skin yeah yeah it's a
different skin oh
i like it
[Laughter]
what did you say before i'm your
huckleberry yeah she she said that i
just quoted her
and she said something like you need
some kale so i'm like a huckleberry
but that wasn't the abandoned skin
what oh okay that's your american accent
it's her american accent no more
american roxanne
oh that's here
okay hunter hunting party
has been unlocked
uh mew-mew
well you're so cute
i'm it's not not okay to be so cute you
look like a magical girl
that pose is very elegant too
oh yeah i do i do feel like i look like
a magical girl apparently
cute
we can't stay here we need to adopt this
cat
[Music]
oh it's this map that's the oh it's
what does that mean you should lock on
[Applause]
my personal space i don't think that's
okay
[Music]
that's cool i like the movement ability
on this
and there's chicken
fire fire
okay i see it i like transfer my heels
what the hell
what
i just
found
uh
i found a gap in the matrix or something
oh did you fall through this
yeah
yeah there's a there's a
there's a little area here where you can
fall off i did not see that coming
yeah it's kind of hard to see because
it's like a little foggy but
once it once you know it's there you
know you learned your lesson
or did i
yeah
i wonder if i can click on people
through the wall
no okay
wow
don't let them
[Laughter]
they're scared of our cute outfits we're
too cute
yeah we'll get another close-up it's
definitely a buff
wow
oh they're behind
oh i think
i thought it was a friendly but she shot
me
oh what's going on i hear people dying
everywhere
if they fell into the hole
i need you here
[Music]
smart smart very smart
but
i keep pressing the remote death is
inevitable
oh oh
tried to shoot the bird but she was
already dead
oh he's killing my steelers
[Laughter]
i want some kills too many
yeah but i don't really have a target
right now so i wasted it
[Music]
that's okay you get it back pretty fast
um
we are
too
our dominance is too strongly inserted i
mean they're too scared
yeah i think that's it
i like i like the
characters have a lot of moving
abilities and on this
this lady you get a big jump it's really
fun
yeah maybe a snack like a milkshake
milkshake
huh
what's a milkshake
uh
you want a milkshake that's three and
four
yeah you should try this that's really
you should try the oreo shake from
a
burger
yes
burger thing yes
yes they have oreo ice cream and oreo
milkshake it's like i guess it's not
really a milkshake it
feels very ice shaky
but it's so good it's so addictive
i've had it many times
i have to go to the i have to go
shopping later i'll get some oreos and
make a homemade oh are you making
yourself i'm sure there's a [\h__\h] ton of
recipes for that online
yeah well it's pretty easy i think you
just put oreos in a blender with
cream
it's the milk hell yeah
i'm dead but we only need a frame oh
winning winning winning
[Applause]
[Music]
i don't hear you
hello oh hello
do you hear me in game
no
not enough i'm gonna need some more
ahmed so what do you say about that was
that ggo went
uh that was a good game yeah i had a
seven kill streak amazing nice wow but
you had a 14 kill streak damn
[Music]
further away from enemies they're like
pretty close up i mean right now because
of the map i feel like i was
like on the
normal in between distance
yeah
there was not really like
so much space to
go further away and still do damage but
yeah oh that was fun
i couldn't i could play forever right
now
why you want to play another one
last one last one last one last night
i'll put
you can try tyra on like one of the
payload maps okay
where is um is she gone oh because i
already have it now the advertisement is
gone
how about it yeah i think i see
i guess i'll i'll practice some more
tyra then or should i try someone else i
don't know who is who is evie
if he looks cute what does she do
oh she has like ice abilities so she
flies around on a broom
and uh she can go into an ice block to
heal
she has a blizzard a blizzard ultimate
which does quite a bit of damage
hard to play evie is really tricky oh
can i switch oh i already locked that
thing
yeah she's kind of difficult to play
because
the types of abilities that she has and
she's kind of supposed to be like a
flank but
you know you can still play and try i'll
try evie is the hardest character what
hard for beginners on you
oh well it's all right
get on your broom a lot you can you have
an ability where you can go in your
broom and you can try to get away from
enemies so just run away when you take
damage or something
they're probably like the enemies
probably looked at our lineup and
they're like oh she chose evie she must
be meeting her and be really good at it
yeah and playing her yeah
increase the distance uh-huh i have no
idea
i have to go through the cards and pick
a
like a nice loadout
oh oh that's teleporting cute
link magically teleport forward short
distance
uh
[Music]
we got the point really nice i guess
that was uh
but that was a short distance it felt
like i i went so far
all right
all right we're 90 on the point sweet
[Music]
oh captured
you feel the power i may feel it i feel
it
where are they they're hiding
yeah i think they're still coming at a
spot
come here oh there they are
you can mess around with the cards to
make the teleport reach fighter or fly
faster
[Music]
is she difficult do you feel like she's
difficult very difficult
successful though and i did almost
nothing
i mean that's all right you know you get
to try it and fly around i like playing
uh eevee and like just going on a broom
and flying behind the team and
and i'm trying to mess with them a
little bit that's what she's good at
like poking that's probably why she's
difficult to play because oh that's kind
of how she's outfitted to play in some
cases maybe uh-huh uh-huh in a while
since i've later remember i like her
voice line evie
[Laughter]
are you
more like you'll be sorry
oh
[Music]
one
attack
target there's like a
different horses and things you can get
like an ounce or whatever wait
i'm on ice book
i just can't do anything it's just like
a shield where
i turn into an eye because
it might be like on default uh cards and
things like that you don't get heals but
there's like a lot of times when people
play evie when you go into your ice
block you also generate
health in there but you might not have
it equipped maybe okay okay
and where i have my heels on you
oh
that was not my kill really it feels
kind of like
um
disappointing when you think you killed
someone but then you look on the right
side and it says someone else killed
them
you got an assist it still counts sort
of but yeah it is more satisfying just
yeah your name up there i'll just
imagine it was me
yeah finally
one kill
probably my only one
got it
i'm learning yes baby steps
thanks a bunch thank you for
uh playing with a noob like me
we got a seven field hill street
i was on the two obvious
uh point i just wanted to ride the
the
[\h__\h] thingy i love it
you know like in the supermarket when
when
mom brings the cart and you're like
mommy i wanna i wanna ride the car
please
[Music]
victory
that was too fast
that was really fast
you want to play another one
and i'm gonna end on a satisfying game
right yeah yeah i'm gonna oh seven wow
i'm gonna uh do a different character
though um
who did i
play the best with i had i guess a lot
of ex experience with cassie so i got
used to her
i want to play the valley girl cassie
yeah yeah do it okay
you hear that guys
oh my god
the phone
oh
last one for real last game
for real
we want something more challenging you
know
holy shish that's a
what's quite though
why the chesticles you have there me
lady
[Laughter]
oh cassie
the bird is so cute holy [\h__\h]
it's so cute by this new tank
never played them
new tanks oh yeah like a paladin oh you
got wings
yeah
okay
got a strong tank on our side looking
respectfully yes yes only respectfully
what did you just say did she just curse
she said something blah blah [\h__\h]
oh maybe she said beach beach
a beach ah
b-e-a-c okay
oh oh that skin is really cute yes
beach episode
a sun on the beach oh
run on the beach oh okay i feel like she
purposefully said it as if it's uh
as if it sounds like [\h__\h] okay
cassie it's you and me again
okay
hello
you want me afterwards go for a drink
you want me
oh
sure
nice sunglasses thank you you see my
bird
oh yeah
that's purple it's like oh it's like a
parrot yes i'm just looking at my okay
this is a oh what is that your wall yeah
i mean is that how you so now you turn
me away first you say yeah sure and then
you build some walls up man
i thought we had something going on
there but all right
okay
where am i oh what i do is portals oh
it's this map i like what's up we don't
map i think they updated this map it
looks different when i first played it
i did get a nice kill there
very sniperish
[Music]
okay
where are the enemies
oh no oh no no
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
oh that's what was behind me
that's yeah
you wanted to put it in front of me nuts
behind me i know it
have two healers you should get
cauterized
eliminated
is that thing in the way
oh eliminated
okay
nice wash i think
are we pushing
eliminated
i think the whole team just got wiped
now it's ours no
uh no well they already captured it so
now we just defend for the next minute
and then we can capture it on the next
round
you little [\h__\h]
if you're sniping if you're one of us
then you must go to the original room
afterwards sorry
i don't know what my ultimate does okay
it does something oh [\h__\h] okay
is it powerful uh
does it do something nice
yeah i think so i don't know i don't i
didn't kill anybody with it but i think
it's maybe it's more like a crowd
control thing
i guess one one thing to learn as well
is like how the maps look how they're
designed yeah to know
where to shoot from
where to take cover and all that
nice hey
[Music]
oh my god
defense successful hallelujah
yeah now so when you defend on like a
payload see how we have one and one at
the top on the score yes yes so when you
capture it and then you get it you get
two points and then yeah when you defend
you only get one
it's a little complicated um but you
can't actually win the whole game like
say you have three out of four points
and you you win in defense even though
you get a point usually you can't win
the game like that you have to capture
the point that makes sense
sure
you'll see it's kind of hard you'll see
when you when you play might happen this
game i may speak very fast like a
machine gun
three i'm sorry
i guess that's the
pro gamer inside of you
oh yeah you've got a gun
yeah that's true
infiltrating the system
oh nice wall okay so this is a circle
okay
do you remember when you recorded these
lines
yeah i do oh shoot
i remember remember
killing spring
enemy killing spree
i wonder if there's any randos who just
got you and then tried you out and are
like yo who's this cute girl it's kind
of kind of cute man yeah
who the [\h__\h] is amelia emilia watson
oh they got it
again man
[Music]
how do they keep on doing it
oh god
this is scary what the hell oh oh oh
whoa whoa
so wow
oh i used my old bite oh okay oh i can
do this
uh okay
wow
wow wow that was just a lucky shot
i'm spectating what ozone
oh yeah what are you doing
trying to hit people with my slow hammer
oh then i'm gonna get on the point
[Music]
said something in the valley girl accent
about the sunburn
uh
you need some help of playing some
sunscreen maybe
yes
um
yes uh gentlemen uh
did you bring some of that
milky
some lotion
uh you know i don't have some but i know
where i might be able to get some
the store
five
four three three two two one
run
[Music]
defend our honor we lost too often but
at least this is a good last match where
it's not too easy
yeah
you get to you know play the character
that you like
watching you awesome i see you
all right i distracted them for quite a
while
he's kind of good at getting behind and
taking out a healer maybe that's why
we've been losing ah
yeah we always forget to buy items wait
you can i don't know it's on auto she
has an autobuy which is fine yeah what
items am i using
uh so it's just items that
i feel like i've been missing a critical
information here
and it's kind of important but the game
also takes care of you
ah how sweet on the point
paladin's stupid taking care of me oh no
almost almost
[Music]
[Laughter]
like this you can y'all bad easy what
yeah the person on our three on our team
was probably throwing oh
[Music]
oh let me look at the
scoreboard
kills but uh i have a lot of assists
you know this guy that guy was playing
can't really get kills with him too
easily
oh wait a kda killing defense assist or
what was that again yeah uh kills death
sentences
ah deaths are my own deaths
yes ah
holy [\h__\h] nine deaths
um
six sisters
oh yeah the i mean that guy was roasting
us but he can't he can't even properly
name uh put a name uh
in on the keyboard he just rammed the
keyboard grounded so honestly
i don't care what you think about us
we're amazing gamers we're the gamers of
ian's
live ian okay
yeah you did really good for playing
your first i mean your first time i i
think you did really good yeah it was
fun it's uh i think it was a good choice
from your members to
use this as the first fps game for
someone they didn't know who they were
choosing it for though right no no i was
just like oh it's somebody who's new to
fps what do you guys recommend
[Music]
yeah it was a perfect choice i really i
really like the um the game it's fun it
has a lot of different characters
oh yeah and and and very colorful i like
the the graphics beautiful yeah i'm a
sucker for cracks
you play like jrpgs and things like that
because it has some magic elements i
feel like
might have like because of that
yeah yeah yeah
indeed
and now thanks to that you know i don't
think we would have gotten so many uh
supportive
items from uh and characters
from paladins uh i i don't think we
would have gotten that from the other
games that were an option yeah yeah
now this is so sweet especially uh you
know a lot of people like to play and so
it's nice yeah thank you thank you thank
you
but most of them it was an honor i was
so nervous to play with the the
announcer the famous announcer from
paladins amelia watson that made me
quite nervous that was probably why why
i was not doing
so good i could do better
um but she made me blush and uh just
listening to her gave me butterflies
that announcer
yeah it made your hands shaky i'm sure
you know so made it difficult
uh i like that that's kind of like a
like a meme
funny yeah
who funny maybe one day come on kiara
skin
one day i will
i will take you down amen
oh
i will become a professional fps player
that is part of tournaments and i'll
take you down
we should do more training yeah you
train me and then i become
i become the teacher
like the
pupil overtakes the sensei
yes yes
so you gotta step up your game to um and
practice a bit more i don't think you've
been playing enough fps games these days
yeah yeah i've been meaning to now that
i have my pc is actually fixed
it's kind of hard sometimes to stream
some fps games and play them at the same
time
i see i see
i can see that i've been i was also i
feel like i was
uh around the end focusing and not
focusing on streaming but focusing on
the game rather than streaming
yeah
and awesome and i guess
i've seen you getting sniped a lot
maybe that's the problem too
yeah they feel like they're
they're targeting you a lot
yeah that does happen that's why you
have to practice so that you know when
people try to do that to you you just
you know
roll them
yes yes
although they kfb
supposedly has i think a lot of respect
for their attention they know what
happens if they bully me too much
yeah um
well i think i'll try out some of the
different champions uh if i ever
uh stream this again and try out what
suits best
uh for me
thank you for accepting the spontaneous
request of teaching me amit thank you
very much
maybe there's something that i can teach
you
another time oh
you said you wanted to learn german i
can teach you german
oh that'd be fun
yeah
jeremy in my memory
you'll be fine
you got a talent for it i'm sure secret
hidden talent
maybe
i'd like to find out um let's do it
all right thank you everybody for
watching today
and
[Music]
oh yeah
next stream on wednesday schedule is out
on twitter check it out
thank you
thank you thank you paladins again it's
really fun
so nice of you to help us how did they
even find out i guess because they maybe
they have their eyes on you yeah maybe
on the player count because i think a
lot of people also start to play
and we're playing because they want to
play with us well maybe they should
always notice and they're like yeah
maybe they're sitting in the
headquarters and suddenly they see like
a huge spike and they're like what the
[\h__\h] is going on
alarm service going down almost what is
happening we need to find out the source
what is oh oh is it because dear famous
announcer amelia watson is playing right
now ah that makes sense
oh that is super cool to get like so
many cool skins for people that we like
to play
yeah thank you so cute
alrighty uh and in german we say alfina
[Music]
goodbye
thanks for watching everybody have a
nice evening
thank you
i was fun bye bye bye
[Music]
do
you