okay
I was talking and then like wait wait
aha
oh
my God oh my God
the mission started
why
hello everyone
good morning are
[Music]
um I think
um they will be doing promotion first on
their stream and since we already did
our promotion yesterday so we're just
gonna chit chat right now I guess yeah
yeah we're just gonna chill together
if you guys want to hear it again
um it's on our description it is on my
description yeah and everyone's
description oh oh I kind of wanna wanna
hello
yeah so apparently uh I did an oopsie I
said that oh my God yeah pre-order is
closing an inner sloth and a hollow life
website no it's actually only closing
for the whole website yeah that's only
for the whole life website okay yeah
inner sloth merchandisers you should
still be able to get them yeah even
after today yeah for the whole life one
you can get it until 11 59 PM GST today
today
today November 28th
today is your spot it's just still going
so you guys can chill
yeah um
[Laughter]
oh okay
okay
oh
yeah
inside for the Ians right now yeah yep
oh in the game
foreign
[Music]
oh but here's the question for you guys
from all of the merchandise that hollow
life and Among Us is having right now
which one do you guys are most
interested in
oh um I like the keychain with all the
IDS and Ian's like the game
um
[Music]
the key holders
yes I love them what about you a little
bit
foreign
order in that one
yeah remember you guys you guys you guys
can get any OC from hololive Productions
yeah down to i-be and even Stars ain't
that cool
I actually haven't seen the Stars One
the Stars merchandises oh it's cute a
lot more like a charm yeah yeah
um I need to check them out
I think it's if we're talking about
merch I like the plushy
oh my God
she's like oh my God the real picture
it's so good
right
I wonder if we can get like the Airship
if you buy the whole thing
whole thing
that will be spicy
yeah get them all before
wait
uh-huh before what before tomorrow all
right
oh yeah yeah the whole life one will be
gone
sale no it will be gone by today if
you're talking about like Indonesian
time
all right
so until this night until tonight until
tonight
11 59 p.m jst today
[Music]
I kind of want it but they don't ship to
Indonesia unfortunately you know what
you gotta do you need tip
um
[Music]
she's giving up tips and tricks
um
[Music]
wow oh my God oh my God you're
soundboard
I love that sound effect
just tip tips and tricks
[Music]
um
thank you
uh okay should we just play the the
basic the most basic one for for the
first one oh yeah sure yeah
okay okay
basic it is
already had a moga stream like this
right like four hours ago or so yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I had it yesterday
no we're kind of promoting and chatting
at the same time just now wow
um
inside before me oh they're in the room
oh there's a room oh gosh
because the other because the other room
closed
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
do we want to do like a you know a
classic introduction of everyone yeah it
can also be a soundtrack
let's start by the top
hello everyone hello it's on your mouth
is second generation how how's my voice
whoa
I really love that it's so very nice
okay Bale's next
what's up it's me the red I'm tired um
the rat I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
to being the best sauce rat that I can
hello
[Music]
oh no you silly
in the room yet I don't sit here in the
room no I'm not isn't it oh yeah
okay
next we are hiding what are you hiding
coconut I'm shy do you want to hide with
me yeah
ventilating
cameras
I just didn't know what you do right
trying the whole life Cosmic kid try out
somebody's dog
naked compared to everyone else oh
beauty beauty is is you're just
beautiful fauna you don't need yeah
that's all natural
yeah
you were born naked the national Beauty
I'll join you've convinced me
tell me
sound effects the sound effect is
sending me
they say crony's love but I have her on
Max I can't do anything else
it's just her voice
louder or something yeah
speak from the stomach crony be tired
diaphragm higher you said you're too low
yeah
well I think that needed it but but then
nothing happened I'm sorry
[Music]
oh say again crony this is this loud
enough now yeah
I hear you okay yeah
thank you
um
[Applause]
oh
yes she brought the whole audience with
her
yeah ready amazing
thank you for bringing the energy that
we need yeah we need that caffeine help
by your energy I felt that in my
eyeballs I know how did I whoa how do
you feel living here
in your eyeballs who's panting
yeah bye
now
[Music]
[Laughter]
from her life Indonesia generation
we did not only
[Applause]
getting the boys amazing incredible
amazing
this intro
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you for waking up so early I love
you
hello oh hi I'm nasty movie from Whole
Life English I have a stuffy nose to go
men
registered to me that you're saying oh
hi I thought you were saying Ohio but
then you just cut it halfway because you
could be bothered today
I also heard nashimum instead of Nana
she's just saving letters I am saving
time here come on
take too long the room is gonna distress
[Applause]
excuse me
[Music]
all right let's go let's go
are you ready
what
what that is that is so chaotic
uh okay how's the volume
oh I almost pressed the emergency button
oh this feels weird not playing with
um the proximity but I guess what can we
do
Muna senpai
oh oh oh waterfalling why is she
following her oh oh oh
ah everyone's here
everyone's here yeah I don't want to be
alone I've learned I'm gonna Channel my
inner
um detective skills I'm gonna borrow
some detective skills
okay everyone's there so
I'm gonna go to Communications
I have never streamed that
6 a.m so
I'm a little out of it people
you would probably never see me stream
on 6 a.m regularly
huh
oh oh oh oh oh are you gonna kill me are
you gonna kill me
Anya Senpai is probably like
right now I can I can tell by the way
after the manga's collab
um
me ah
me and
Kyle isn't it
um
was talking in
CC until really late
somebody's gonna kill me here
oh
oh oh no two people
hello
buddy
oh two bodies yeah there's yeah oh yeah
where was everyone at
it
I
[Music]
think I just arrived on the shield
in case you're trying to speak your
muted
oh sorry
um
okay um
storage and there was a hallway to the
left you know the hallway that leads to
electrical and then yeah yeah yeah
go in that direction right before I
discovered the body
oh
would you like to explain why you were
there right before I discovered the body
wait but like I've been traveling like
everywhere else like I've been traveling
the right side of the section so I
didn't really notice anything like I was
checking samples
three seconds before that I when I found
the body why did you not report the body
if you were there
since we've already lost two crew
members
[Music]
yeah
we were on the right side
I keep wanting to press the button
all right I'm gonna go down I think I'll
stick with Anya Senpai but to be honest
I can't be too sure to be honest
uh everyone's here
okay hi
huh
no
oh no
in front of everyone in front of
everyone
okay so so there's this report where are
you guys
it's literally either the two of you
that's so fast is that because you're so
near to the body because you just killed
her
okay
did you all see it no because it was
like it was like yeah
in front of my eyes oh okay I we were
all there together so cronies kind of
sauce yeah
she has an obvious
um reason to do it
oh
yeah we're together though
well goodbye crony wait can I undo mine
well you know okay fine I'm just gonna
like yes I am the Imposter podcast
[Applause]
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
all right
really right really
she killed when I was
um they know Nino
and then she killed me
well quiet
I don't I think Kiara Senpai is innocent
I don't know I feel like she's doing her
task properly so
I don't know
but
all right
let's see if she does it I'll do it
for
eh
yeah
the oxygen really calculated so
embarrassing oh my God
there is
someone doesn't know that's kind of sad
someone is being choosing as imposer and
the Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it
yeah
yeah yeah
[Applause]
the thing is I heard everybody I already
said Anya and Zetta were in the room
which means that they're gonna be
innocent the only two people around me
were Kiara I had to choose between the
two
we both did so much work for us to win
that round Right
double kill he had no hesitation to kill
anything anymore
[Laughter]
yeah but thank you for not voting me out
appreciate but there's one person
missing in the room local
Ollie like when I was about to walk over
and Anya was there and I was like crony
you just got me in so much trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
man I was like when you guys were in the
discussion and Courtney was like no it
was like people were there and everyone
else seemed not convinced and I'm like
[Laughter]
and like I was like I was hoping I was
hoping that Zeta would say something I
said that people wouldn't ask me I
didn't see it she was doing tasks yeah
look at that ran the funny thing is that
I was like I was about to go out from
that room so if only you had waited for
like a few more seconds I probably
wouldn't have thought that you know well
you learned your lesson or crony learned
her lesson for next round right yeah
well one day we can get imposter twice
um
I jinxed myself
why why do I always get imposter I
always always get imposter
okay let me think
let's sabotage.com
never mind
see
it's a good thing I didn't kill them no
no because Kiana's there
Ah that's a good thing huh I almost
killed I almost killed them
foreign
[Music]
honestly I I was at there at the scene
too but if you wouldn't have just
admitted immediately that it was you
then I wouldn't have known because there
was so much going on
you don't you shouldn't it right away
I was in there I was in there because
electrical was out and everyone else was
yeah yeah yeah how could we know it was
her we don't know if it was her
there were so many people there
too much
yeah
so because like I saw it the way I saw a
movie like I don't know I just arrived
no no it's not Mommy I saw Grande in
front of my eyes killing it really very
unfortunate
that is oh no oh you know besides what
Luna said crony just incriminated
herself by the way anyway
[Music]
who knows
ah
all right uh I don't know
Umi is here but my kill countdown is not
done yet so
I'll be an admin
all right let's um how about we close
all of the doors so that you can get out
okay my kill countdown is here oh
help
Anya Senpai saw me there so I can't you
know
yeah Ollie said by zombie as well
it's really bad everyone stick together
oh holy crap okay okay this is really
bad everyone's here
foreign
ly press the button
should I kill or not
this is really bad
everyone's together everyone's working
together
Okay so
no Chad I can't kill because they
already saw me in navigations and then
they're gonna be like well last time I
last time last time I saw zit that was
with all enough all right so
holy crap I should be venting
chasing me and then she went off to the
right side of the map okay can I be
running around yeah
I thought he was the Imposter because
she was chasing me but she saw it sounds
so suspicious right now I know I do but
they're used to me and chasing me around
the table but I almost called a meeting
because I was like that's kind of susp
and I was like oh it's mume so it's just
probably just being normal yeah it's
probably move me being mummy yeah
why did Ollie called a meeting just to
check
actually I want to do a little promotion
did you guys kill him and
um
collaborations
yeah sure I mean today
um what if you go to the electrical for
like one second and then you went out
immediately oh I was just checking to
see who's inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there um
yeah yeah if you don't have any tasks
like inside the electrical then why
would you go inside because I just want
to see who's inside and see if I could
stick to anyone
I mean Ollie and me were like going out
of the room why why didn't you like go
with us instead where is sorry where is
this intense
are you going to the electrical just to
make me and like I almost were like
going out
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
why didn't you go with us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
um
okay somebody stick with me then
foreign
this is so hard please
crony I need your help
come
okay I can't be with all Ethan by then
because
why
why are you here
's
here as well
I can't kill Ollie because Moana said by
already saw me with Ollie
oh 202
foreign
I should have killed fauna
uh
ah
let me think let me think Chad since all
of them are together in admin
then
[Music]
they're all here so
it's so hard everyone's together
when we were all in the admin room and
then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
teleportation it wasn't the three of us
who were in the admin room and it was
well yeah it wasn't me phone and Kiana
you know what what's interesting is that
Zeta came after that
yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't I was
like going walking I was walking I don't
know I didn't see anyone teleporting
though but that uh Zeta was like yeah I
said I came to admin I came to admin
because I saw you guys I think I was in
security we were doing stuff
interesting sounds interesting I'm I'm
suspicious interesting
so can you describe the the how many and
you took to arrive at your destination
I'm just gonna say I finished my tasks
there's only a bed left
the wiring okay so so it could be a task
one yeah let's let's pick up those who
finished not yet I was
with those who haven't who haven't
finished the task
me I was gonna go do the card but then
oh two happened sure sure okay I'm gonna
I'm gonna go with Moana Senpai then uh
okay with you guys too I can
are we voting Anya we need Daniel to
vote oh yeah I'm sorry can you go
skipping I I avoided I believe no no I
hope you like space accidents
laughs
let's see what happens
game over here
[Applause]
wait who was it dude
sauce okay
yeah cause that was so sad I didn't
teleport by the way
I was actually walking
poor thing it was lag
it might have been the pain
can I just mention that in the in the
ghost chat they was trying to sing a
Taylor Swift song
I thought you were just ignoring me on
purpose I have no idea how that song
goes I didn't even know that was a song
until later on oh my God
I'm standing there and you're my jump
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
[Music]
okay let's try okay let's try paulus I
guess I don't like it that much but sure
might be fun okay all righty
code there you go
thank you thank you
y'all see nothing one second one second
goodness
skills that they don't know the map well
so they didn't know where to go
exactly but I'm wrong with truth I never
know where to go um
so like I'm gonna get lost a lot yeah oh
yeah
[Music]
what are the chances
what are the chances you get it three
times in a row right
but to be honest everyone has already
gotten I feel like they're for every
Among Us dream there's someone who gets
it three times in a row so I'm guessing
I don't know
weapons let's go to weapons
um
oh no
oh hi
me
Communications maybe if I go to I
she's not the impossible
um
why didn't you report
oh yeah you say you saw it but you
didn't record it
yeah that was awesome nearby I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left room of the
office I think so I was in the office
and and then I go after you knew and go
after a new Lightroom Anya yeah and then
you saw it it was like it was dark so
like I didn't see it at first like I saw
that I was right behind you you seemed a
bit sus
I was right behind her oh she was like
acting a bit sus in that hallway right
before she entered the right office so
um
yeah but I was behind you
so I was yeah
was actually on the left leftish side of
the of the office I saw her I was in the
office I was in the office and then
going away
I saw you I went I didn't go in the
office yeah
I saw you I think go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think yeah I
think mommy is in your Communications or
something yeah I am your communication
may as well yeah
I don't know man I don't know like
Senpai was like around there but how do
we know that if she didn't report
because I didn't see it first yeah they
and Anya are kind of teaming up against
Muna
oh my God are we folding well I don't I
don't know I don't know if there's
enough information or anything
um
foreign
that is so sad
uh so basically I don't know I don't
think it's Mona
I don't think it is but I don't know I
wasn't there
I wasn't there so how am I supposed to
know
I
nobody's in a laboratory
uh I just want to
me
when it's dark like this
somebody's probably
oh
oh hello hello
I don't have anything in Communications
why
I'm probably acting so sauce I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry
laughs
let's go let's go let's go
let's go
and then where is that security or two
oh
[Music]
okay let's go let's go let's fix it
let's go let's fix it
oh
see Ollie going around
I don't think it's mermaid
why would she be in Communications all
alone if she's an imposter right in the
beginning she could be looking around
for some food
the task is increasing
foreign
what is she doing
what
is happening
wait let me see my task okay oh two my
only task is O2
O2 and then I'll be done I think we need
more tasks I feel like
huh
comes
is it done
ah what the heck
oh okay okay
Phil canister still
all right I'm gonna check to see the
meeting room because I left foreign
so where's where's office right should
we should I go to office
ah I see Moana coming from the top
let's see
I mean my task is all done so I can just
go around
huh
oh hello
foreign
maybe I should call a meeting
oh my God
where is it where where's the body
where I wait where am I I'm here uh
security electrical
security
[Music]
yeah I didn't go there
yeah yep on the way to the
Bay was suspicious of Muna and I didn't
see her the whole round no I was with
Mommy before but uh I go with Mommy
before yeah I didn't see nothing but I
know not at all I was in the boiler room
still doing my tasks
but hmm
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but wait
what side are you guys on
um
I was in the in the with Walnut before
fauna only and Zeta we made right
and we just like standing there yeah
in the emergency I think yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
oh yeah and then and then final went to
the specimen room and then we met up
with Anya and then we went to the
laboratory
I was mostly on the right side of the
map the whole time yeah me too so I
can't be on the left side of the map
where are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah wait you said right side right oh
singer
and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win
so I'm already done with my test so I'll
just follow people around
oh yeah I have like one more
all right so let's go
[Music]
um mommy but mommy was alone the whole
time on the left side so
if
if they killed two people wouldn't have
to be a double kill
then wouldn't they be in the same place
okay so movies and all these together
foreign
oh my task
but I didn't see how you didn't get to
see who it is
[Applause]
movie she was chasing me at the end
anyway
yeah
I'm not really good at being imposter
guys no I'm not either
I was thinking wait or can we not kill
again do I have to report before we can
kill again so
I didn't know
we can only do one would you like to
explain
yeah it's a new mode haven't you
explain why did you miss it you should
have prepared and you wouldn't have you
wouldn't have missed it
all right gaslighting is the victim's
fault okay
two intense
I have a missing one person
oh who gave up two good friends who is
it
get in here
I'm sorry oh that's okay I am learning
the game okay I don't know the strats
here
[Laughter]
I think we can at least squeeze in one
more round yeah maybe we can do one more
okay hide and seek yeah
wait this one is
ah
wait
I will sleep afterwards
I'll fix O2
[Music]
yeah I was wondering why she didn't kill
me the whole time while we were on the
left side I think it's just because she
doesn't know the game
[Music]
what okay
thank you
why do I hear away
oh no she's gonna kill me
oh no there's three people never mind
okay
here
here okay
sorry if I'm not talking much
my mind is not fully awake yet
upload hey
self report no
what
why did you not record it then no I was
on the security cameras I saw it what
was it what what was it how could you
what was it
again
I see your body
I saw her on the security cameras it was
mermaid standing over crony's dead body
away
earlier to creep around that was
fun when she died why didn't you report
her right then and there wow
[Laughter]
I didn't see her body so
I didn't leave the lights out I know
but there is the report button even if
the lights
a little bit yeah I didn't see me so I
don't know I have no idea um
because she was running she was like
there and then she went the opposite
direction so I don't know if she really
didn't see it or she knows I don't know
another double M nothing
just keep impossible keep it you know I
didn't see crony die so I I think it's
Bae honestly but okay
whoa then we can just go to three of you
out and it'll be it'll be all okay
oh
that was nice knowing you yeah
who keeps spawning who keeps voting for
fun
that is so sad
all right let's do
I hear the radio in the back
it must be the Imposter The Imposter is
folding
okay let's go to office no no no no no
no no no not office is it are you almost
incriminated yourself by not doing stuff
there we go
security electrical hi
oh we all got stuck in the same place
all right let's find the spaceship I see
Anya Bay
um and the world okay here you go
I saw
I'm gonna go up foreign
by then where is she
oh
okay
okay that's a hard vouch
hi
somebody they keep sabotaging hold on
I'll go the other way then
let's go let's go let's go
foreign
Dropship
man
okay
it's literally four of us five of us
is unjust invited oh where is she does
anyone know where she okay she is here
this is I feel so bad for the Imposter I
feel so bad
I feel so bad okay I have to do task
let's go
task let's go
is it here
I feel I feel so bad for the Imposter
huh
oh my God
done
task done
okay
no no no no no no no
no no no
help
I don't know
I feel bad for the Imposter because like
we're all sticking together it's
technically impossible oh I don't want
to see the stack
foreign
emergency
should I
emergency meeting
no
oh no never mind
that's like gonna be like is not doing
the test
another memory again again
so hard to kill everyone yeah everyone
was together
[Music]
and I was like bro this can't be real
pee that you can see people's names when
they're watching somebody that's no I
just saw your your character your colors
yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah I think you
should be able to like see the colors
well why are you looking on a camera Bay
that's creepy
I was like I was like
walking with them
but but you guys instead not in like one
step but have like a different style so
I just like oh this is hard even though
I do it
it is hard okay I think every everybody
should be off on their own and isolated
at all times honestly
easier yeah
there's always one can we just maybe do
one more round and in case someone gets
imposter who already got impossible
before we restart or just yeah but it
feels like yourself yeah
I'm going to kill all of you okay so
someone who gets it again
okay
yeah if someone gets it like I guess
maybe we already got it okay but once
that narrow down here
oh yeah oh yeah
you want to play one more round it
doesn't matter who imposter is if I get
it again I'm gonna throw it
let's do that well like if we get a
little imposter again either Muno or me
we could just do the emergency meeting
and cast okay all right imposter I'll be
throwing it
oh
see the title is correct non-sassy time
at 6 00 am but yeah to be sticking
everyone sticking in one place it would
be super hard for the Imposter so
what
oh yeah yeah by the Rockets
I I was stalking fauna and then it got
dark and I lost sight of her but then I
saw crony come from the opposite
direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again I don't think yes
the rocket oh it's nearby the laboratory
oh no that's so far
I've just been in weapons all I'm saying
is that I'm like on the left side of the
map
did whoever was did they cross paths
with you or did you see them escape to
the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interesting
oh I did see crony run however I don't
know I I don't know
so okay I will fess up uh-huh I I did
get it again what what but like
should you cast me out now
but I didn't kill anyone so I don't know
what happened
yeah
if someone else give me give me the Hat
of imposter and we'll just continue like
that give me a hint
I have an imaginary kill people I will
just act as if I did it
so like if I'm impossible should I just
out myself and just ever have too many
people I mean like it narrows it down
too much so I'm not sure we can really
do that I mean we could just keep crony
around
well at least she's honest she's very
honest at least he's on a very honest
yeah
we appreciate the honesty
well she hasn't
just keep going around for fun
and then like find out the other
imposter first and then leave her last
and it's like I wonder who the last one
could be
no no no no
ah
I jinxed myself
oh no
it was bae
that rat
isn't my first time dying oh no no it's
my second time dying
wait is it
foreign
killed the cat
huh okay
we have to go
in the hallway on the left side of the
map like which was like like a tree
[Music]
not that bad but like on she's in like
the middle left okay in a hallway who
was with someone was with me at
stabilizer so they're also safe
um I I was walking up with you but then
I went to the left and I met crony she
was coming from that area but I guess
she didn't she didn't touch it yeah
every time I see crony I won't lie
it's okay
yeah anything can happen it must be the
other imposter
fish are friends not food God I I have
no idea you go skipping
no
[Music]
honestly I choose fauna at this point
what what
hold every single round
and amuted herself immediately
[Music]
my death was in vain
all right I gotta do task
I gotta do tasks
two imposters
hahaha
okay I'm gonna go to
wait this is not O2
what are you good at let's see what
she'll do let's see let's see what is
she doing let's see sabotaging
okay they're together they're together
look at them they're together
all right let's finish tasks
[Music]
oh once I'm done with Tesla I'm gonna
stalk people oh I'm done I'm done I'm
done time to stop
time to stop people
where are they
I didn't see it
and me and meow meow they're ganging up
on me
foreign
what is she gonna do
oh no
uh oh I have a I have I have a theory
like Romeo and Juliet
what romantic
I have I have a very big Theory so I was
assessing uh Zeta
um and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since crony came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that then came
back
isn't the type that would be
um going on herself please just to get
in anyone's stress if she's in Pocket
that couldn't be heard it couldn't be me
so it's either krsn by or Bay
right
or maybe your cooldown was not done yet
oh
no I feel like I really
because we're kind of dwindling to the
final people so if you waste a if you
waste the thing we're gonna we're gonna
lose by the way the body was at
um beside the weapons is that weapons
like you better choose somewhere like
between weapons
you better choose someone
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
twice
for existing
I always get one imposter every man
every stream for some reason huh
uh guys I'm so hungry I'm watching oh
[Applause]
let's go
I'm sorry
in the Back Bay you stopped me where in
the back
they was on a killing spree
yeah I felted in my spine when you did
it respect to the ones who stayed alive
and finished the tasks yeah yeah
honestly I was dead and had to finish
the tasks I think it was me himself
if that's possible since it was hard for
the other imposter
one red but I wasn't looking at my
screen I was like were they someone's
head
oh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
one more round and then I just want to
do hide and seek
if we do one more around and we should
remake the room though
actually you can just you can just
change it to the morning poster and the
killing time is like 10 like the lowest
10 seconds and pretty much they have to
try and kill every everyone before they
finish the talk
yeah yeah so you have
[Music]
you have okay and you've set the the
running speed to the fastest whoever's
making the room and then okay you count
to ten if you're the Imposter and then
yeah okay I have the player speed on Max
oh my God that is so fast
and
no reporting the body right
in the reports okay
10 seconds it doesn't get any lower do
we have okay we have to do task yeah
yeah yeah yeah so the point is to finish
all the tasks
[Music]
yeah
so wait so how many should I do
should be good or two to four yes
possible so no recording though no
reporting um which oil do you want to do
do you want to do the normal one for now
go wild yeah okay oh we can hear each
other screaming
let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
oh wait you're not supposed to do okay
you're are you faster
I'm meant to die
I have no idea
oh God I'm gonna die here oh
should we do a test
oh
yeah let's just say yes
[Laughter]
all right
everywhere
[Music]
oh my God oh my God oh my God
play the elevator music oh my god oh my
god
let's go
I mean I haven't killed anyone in a
while
oh
yeah
come on
is everybody oh carrots invited about
the downloads yes yes it's a dangerous
place
everybody
out here where's everybody
wait is it only is it now
what
yeah
everyone else is dead I can't do the
tasks
[Music]
go grab a coffee
time
[Music]
I don't think so we can haunt her
oh
no no no no no no no no no
repent for your sins
[Music]
oh no it's actually harder than I
thought
[Music]
let's go
thank you
one more one more one more yeah
possible
wow wow amazing I think that would work
so that we would win what what
good job
[Music]
okay
should I change something any
Improvement advice was actually okay
sometimes if I hadn't messed up I would
have won so it's okay I think okay
School issue all right play well if you
want to win
it's possible
who is it I don't actually don't I don't
actually want to be it so please no
thank you wait we should restart
okay okay
this game is so broken well we could
just do an emergency
um yeah yeah
and kick her out
right goodbye
goodbye oh we have to wait
just you know doing the marketing
merchandise the links are in the
description and for the the whole live
one you only have a couple of hours left
so if you wanted to get it but didn't do
it yet then go do it do it do it yeah
let's do it
do it
dude do it
is incredible
me
all right will it be fun again or help
no we weren't easy
oh yeah
yes
everyone there
oh
it's not me there's me
oh my God
we do tasks during the countdown or no
no no no
wait yeah
okay accounting please wait what
started
doing you guys are confusing me
it's okay okay
oh man
I have no idea what should I do but
ah the screen
what is happening
the Keystone is broken
well this is peace
right now you don't need to go looking
for me okay I won't
come on
I can't do the card
God damn it
no
hmm
you're so smart nope not in the
cafeteria at all
[Music]
um
foreign
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
there's only a few people left yeah I
got two more towels I already mentally
gave up on that movie
[Music]
thank you
you are scary
everybody
[Music]
I'm so sorry
that was fun
did anyone besides me never get imposter
I didn't I never I never got one only an
onion me we have cursed yeah it's not
fair
oh cute I'm going to sue someone I don't
know who but I'm going to school
probably maybe Susie
or hello
he means milk in Indonesia
please give me
how do I say please give me
uh it depends that you can at least give
uh you can at least just say
uh something dong
[Music]
mama
oh my God
I will marry you or something like that
I'm sorry so so anyway guys
right now it's gonna end soon oh I'm
gonna show you
yeah in like 12 hours I think so much
guys
acrylic stand yeah
t-shirt
[Music]
cheers
thank you for joining so spontaneously
especially to the IG members who already
did their homework
thank you
[Music]
so much
fun for you guys too thank you yeah it
was really fun thank you
[Applause]
bye bye
[Music]
um I forgot to
end
okay
[Music]
also
um
so
maybe a little bit of an announcement
[Music]
okay maybe not really announcement but
um
I am supposed to do the ASMR tonight
right and I really don't want to
postpone it but I feel like I think I
might
depending on my condition I might take a
break for
a day or two
because I am not feeling healthy at all
I've been having migraines and it's been
a while
it's because I keep postponing my break
I'm just like oh okay maybe I shouldn't
take a break and then I don't take a
break and then I like last week I was
supposed to take a break but then I
streamed twice every day and I was like
uh okay maybe next week which is
supposed to be this week and then I
didn't take a break either so
um
we'll see we'll see if my condition is
better but I can still push it but I
don't want to be I don't want to do ASMR
while I'm like
dying because then that's not a pleasant
that's not like a pleasant relaxing
experience
uh
[Music]
dying it somewhere dying you somewhere
is kind of sad
don't you somewhere is kind of sad not
gonna lie
um okay well that's
that's
um my announcement my only announcement
you know what makes you well
yeah don't worry don't worry
um it's just I feel bad because like I
kind of already postponed my ASMR
because it was so late
yes like
um yesterday
huh
and because I also have this collab as
well so I had to postpone it to today
but then if I postpone it uh
[Music]
it's okay
all right well I guess I'll see you next
time
I'll just talk with the others now