[Music]
the marketing department huh weird that
they'd have this file oh man what a
weird place to put a photo set up what
are they even shooting in here I really
make myself smaller to get
it it's almost like I'm going through a
mouse hole man I don't know where to
look for this thing there's nothing here
why does everything smell like chicken
marketing is really embracing 3D
Revolution maybe a little too much oh
are there mice in the ceiling man how
Department's really not going to like
that wait what is
[Music]
whoa who who are
you what is going on
what what do you
[Music]
mean I'm so
lost how do you know
about no I'm not lost I know exactly
what I'm looking
[Music]
for I
what FP SV
001 I I found the
files I'm uploading them
now
uh I got to go