[Music]
for
oh
k
[Music]
k hi
everyone I'm
car sparkling J of hard life English Al
and
today it's been one year this rock is
one extra year old
in Hall Live question mark I should have
thought about that sentence before I
said
it hey happy
anniversary to me and to you literally
one year from today B debuted yes
7:30
2023 was B's debut and now it's 7:30 202
4 or 31st if you're in jsd but yeah be a
debut today and now I am here to
celebrate it with all of you thank you
for
coming
um disclaimer and I
am in a completely different setup right
now uh as you may have noticed my stream
is starting a little bit later than
usual be bo hours right yeah and and
there's a good reason for that but you
probably know about already cuz it's
literally in the Stream title
today I am inviting guests with me to
sing with off collab off collab karaoke
party so uh starting in about like 15
minutes the first guest will appear
um and then everyone will have about
like 10 minute intervals to like hang
out and sing with me and do a little
karaoke party yeah I invited a bunch of
people I'm actually pretty nervous about
it
I I'm I'm actually kind of nervous cuz
it's like off collabing with with so
many people of uh and they're all coming
here uh for me uh so so if if people
little
nervous people sounds a little little
shaky that's why but it's okay we're
going to have a lot of fun I'm doomed
I'm
doomed it's fine if I sing silly
whatever
Senpai me now please carry me today yeah
but yeah so people are going to show up
um fairly soon doing but I wanted to say
hi to everybody thank you for coming
we're having a party together I can't
believe it's been one year did you eat I
did I went to a bakery and bought like a
bunch of bread and like yummy little
like snacks for
everybody so that way they wouldn't get
like bored waiting around hopefully the
food will keep them occupied I until
it's their turn I was like hey please
eat my bread yeah so there's like a
bunch of bread uh in the other room for
them so much yeah I'm a good host you
see I'm a I'm a good I'm a good host um
let's get this bread yeah so hopefully
they enjoyed the little snacks while I'm
over here but ha thank you for coming
hell it's it's bble B is here wow what
what what what did we do this year I
don't know
um what did we do this year hey what's
your favorite beo moments this year let
me ask you guys since you guys a lot of
you guys have been like around with me
for a while right oh yeah we did some
elen ring we played lots of games we
played armored Core I found out what DMC
was and that changed my life forever
uh and then Hollow night oh Hollow night
was fun lots of fun um Hol live events
that we went to like the sports festival
and the Mario Kart tournament oh that
was good so many games
yeah oh yeah Gat for n
rler oh what if I make every single
person here saying Gat for nler with
that would you die would you die if if
if every single person here s g i I did
not come up with that I just saw a chat
and that's a good
idea
maybe no v no no you secretly love it
don't lie don't
lie maybe it would be it would be a fun
ice breaker though you know maybe help
me get less nervous you want me to be
not as nervous right if I if I see G and
a Whistler with my guest and maybe I
won't feel so shy around them you know
yeah you know it's helping me you want
you want me to feel comfortable on
stream
right by the way do I sound okay just
everything again I do not know this
setup I feel I'm afraid like to press a
button there's so many buttons that if I
press one this the the PCS and
everything will go boom like all the
equipment here is just going to explode
if I press one button I'm afraid
so yeah press all of them I don't know
that's that's not a good
idea I don't think that's a good
idea um but
yeah
okay the first guest is going to arrive
in about like 9 minutes but I thought I
would warm up with one song first um M M
M did you
know that that
event
released a new second
original have you seen it or have you
heard it yet have you heard it
Sirens yeah it's a siren it's a siren I
think I'm going to warm up with that one
yeah introduce you to the new original
so I told some of you this um
but I was like I made I tried to make my
voice a little bit different did you
notice did you notice people's slight
change in in in tone to siren I sound so
cool I don't know how I did that can I
do that for like this karaoke let's find
out I hope you're proud of me I've been
doing a lot of practicing uh for like
singing and stuff obviously doing a lot
of singing and all that Idol stuff so
hopefully you will enjoy today and see a
little bit of people
Improvement yeah your voice was cool
thank you I had a lot of fun with it hit
me I'll hit back a stronger
Maniac Edie oh yeah I'm so
cool but yeah a watch siren the music
vide is out it's pretty cool the this
you can stream it can you stream it I
don't no I'm not very good at
propon speaking I'm not very good at
speaking either apparently but you guys
are still here for some reason
so whatever okay let's sing our first
song let's let's practice
Reverb wait which one's the button oh
this is the thing where like I'm going
to press the button and it might explode
everything ah ah oh I pressed the right
button yay
yay a siren the first guess is appearing
in about 5 minutes but B need to warm up
B needs to warm up her voice before
before everything starts so I'm going to
start with one song and okay warm up
sticking out your
[Music]
girl your be attacks in Reverb I just
want to be aori
Sirens
okay okay we're going to sing one
song Get me
adrenaline okay people
start there's so many things there's so
many screens but I will navigate okay
hopefully wait does this sound
[Music]
okay can you hear
me
over
the
instrumental
okay okay I'm
ready a warmup song this is siren
evans's new second original song please
listen to it uh bble will do all the
[Music]
parts y let's play thought you like my
Wild Side all bark but you don't got
nobody good things comeing to don't
think they got a clue can't take a hint
come and roll the dice and
people my Foolish Games I can't behave
having to notice what you keep down cuz
back around your little secret open the
cage I'll Fly Away my New Horizon only
need one
chance I've been running so long don't
rush it just me until you you can't
breathe nowh living on the edge of far
ahead from where you do the line I love
it the sound of ecstasy drop siren to
siren to siren you know how I like it
like it I'm quicker than
Ling R don't a re I don't care what's
wrong once I siren siren siren floud
chasing spin me round and round play all
night I love the sty
up and down and under ground silence
flashing all around oh baby you make
[Music]
me okay
ready hit me I'll hit back a stronger
Maniac come break me but careful don't
touch I got long l no just about you you
try to make a move predict that you go
look around for help it ain't no use ah
ah ain't no use my Foolish Games I can't
be hit haven't you noticed what you keep
down comes back around at me you like it
open the cage I'll Fly Away my New
Horizon only need one
chance sir sir sir you know how I like
it like it I'm quicker than Ling diving
just
diving run don't need a I don't care
what's wrong and what's right turn it up
a not make make it dangerous drifting
through the night we're
outrageous coing through our vein to
can't turn it up a not make it day hey
Sirens give me
adrenaline my perfect Chase heart race
let's stay this way oh hear your call
come on give me a sign siren to siren to
siren you you know how I like it like it
I'm quicker than L to siren to
siren R don't I don't care what I hear
the siren sir loud Jason spin me round
and round play all night I love the
sound up and down and underground siren
flashing all around oh baby it makes me
feel
so oh nice nice duet with bib there BBU
did you know bib does the low part for
that wow that was a double bebble bbo
wow wow it's a siren it's a siren
now
siren yeah be was in this song did you
know all
Reverb double people yeah people does
Nissa does the oh baby and makes me feel
so and then big people goes oh baby it
makes me feel so I like I like unlocking
lower people
voice
so y b was wait you didn't know be was
in this song featuring Kaki oh is it
because it says Kaki bizu and it's not
Co biu oh that's why oh you I I'm I'm
also K bizu by the way
right hit me a hipac a stronger maniac
come make me but careful don't touch
don't touch me I'm hard okay it's a oh
oh hi oh oh you just come in okay I so
here here's a SE for you hello are you
surprised
me
what keep talking just ignore me oh oh
why you can sit down
hi our first guest is
here
guys sorry I I didn't know when to come
in I was just told maybe go in it's okay
you're perfectly on time yeah right on
time what's
up Happy one year thank you
oh my God oh my God how do you feel um
the same as I did yesterday oh that's
good which is um stumbling through life
uh drifting in the wind I mean when are
we not you
know um did you introduce yourself
already you should introduce yourself
what's up I am chaos the end of ends a
still roast trapped in a cage of ice
your best friend Belle's haos from Hol
live English
promise Echo please
oh witness me yay she knows how to work
this more than I
do how B thank you for so say wao I
can't talk my brain um thank you for
inviting me to celebrate your first year
I am so happy to be here yeah I'm happy
you are my first guest Y and I thought
bring you in um I don't know why you're
first you're just here I just made it
that way but you're important so that's
why first yay thanks majer so thank you
for joining my
party we're going to sing a song
together um but going into my second
year you know since you're my son I want
to ask this do you have any I advice for
bble going into my second year here here
going into your second year you don't
have to think too hard about it just
whatever I'm was trying to think what my
second year was like I don't remember my
second year everything kind of is a
blur but I feel like you know in your
second year you get you kind of more
accustomed to how things work um you
gain a little bit more confidence
confidence confidence confidence okay so
my advice would be to you know be
ambitious I think I think after your
first I think during your first year
you're kind of getting used to it um
getting used to everything and you know
you're still kind of like the dear and
headlight situation where you're not
really sure what you can do and what you
know you can go for and stuff so I
really want you to spread your wings be
ambitious spread you have things that
you want to do just do it because you're
amazing Kiki be and don't ever forget
that thank you she pointed at me you
didn't see it but she was like she she
was like you're amazing point I really I
really felt it there oh yeah did I
mention this is an off Cloud so they hi
I'm here they're in the room with me the
way we enter the room as well is like
behind her yeah they enter behind me so
I can't see them enter they just like
come in and I just see her and I was
like wow okay so I'm just going to get
jump scared every time there's person
yeah I was trying not I I was thinking
of jump scaring you but I'm like no I
shouldn't do
that well it would have been content but
I'm kind of glad you didn't yeah well it
is your special day well I you know
scaring me would probably scare the
nerves out so that that might help it my
nerves I thought there's a lot of people
here different setup
my yeah but anyway you want to sing a
song with me I do I love to sing a song
with I chose this song for us because we
kind of bonded over it kind of a little
bit one of the things we bonded over one
of the things many things we bonded over
yes yes and I remember like someone was
singing it and we were at the karaoke
and we like we all to sing this together
and I remember that I was like okay
let's sing it together when was that I
don't know I think it was iris's karaoke
I
she we were singing it in in chat Sing
the lyrics in her chat in her chat it
was Iris remember H was B yes I remember
yes do we know the song oh yes you you
guess the song have we guessed the song
okay hold on H okay why is it okay nice
I have this for you thank you so much
and I'm going to attempt to go through
the bajillion tabs and find the
instrumental okay take your time it's
organized though thank you staff for
organizing everything for me
wowe
okay I'm putting the Reverb back on
extra Reverb cuz we need to be in the
fields are you in the fields yet oh yes
you're not in the fields uh uh uh uh
you're in the fields I'm in the fields
now we're in the fields Fields okay oh
my God we're going to be hearing
extremely bad Nas vocals I'm so sorry
are you
sleepy I'm running on my first all
nighter oh are you proud of me I'm so
proud of you yeah how do people do
this but I feel like that's going to add
to the song you know oh yes you know use
that use that feel mhm wow did you have
fun yeah I did wow I'm so proud of you
thank you one of last she's turning into
one of us now now you just got to do
like a 12 hour stream by yourself yeah
it's going to be 12 hours and I have to
do 24 hours and then I'll be fully gamer
yeah and then a
week and then we'll do the thing where
you do 12 hours and then I'll do 12
hours and then you do 12 hours and then
yeah I do 12 hours and we'll just back
and for let's just start let's just
start with the one night let me get
through today and then we'll talk okay
okay we're going to start singing is hak
the volume okay
I
T slightly
louder oh the instrumental is very soft
is this quiet Pump It Up
more yeah I think I'm slightly louder
than you hold on it's all right cuz I'm
closer to the
[Music]
like
May
me I love you more fore
[Music]
you got
M we're so sad we so sad oh sadness
how's the instrumental check everything
good for you everything good
[Music]
fore
foree for
[Applause]
[Music]
I've been such a fo I'm so happy for you
oh thank you happy one
[Music]
year
me me
you got m
[Music]
thank you happy one
anniversary let's be together for a long
time yeah together
[Applause]
forever okay get out okay
bye
I bye
bye okay please send in the next person
I will send in the next I just want to
say you've done great for one year and
as technically your s by I couldn't be
prouder of course
sayu and you know what it's a special
occasion so I'm going to say
it happy oneyear
anniversary yeah B
boo bye thanks B oh that sounds
weird back to oh thanks for the hug she
huged me okay byebye s in the next
person thank
you
well that was hot B off all right we
await our next victim guest but wow
already starting off strong oh hello
hi
wow KY
K I ran this room is Big yeah it is big
they gave me this whole big space just
for me and I don't like it I like
everything like compact this is way too
big of a space I didn't even find you
when I when I came here was I went to
the usual rooms yeah usual rooms and I
was like where is P She should be
setting up but there's no one here and I
literally couldn't find you guys yeah
this is this is like the room they use
for like giant Co outs I guess this is
technically a giant Co out I've never
even been in this room before I didn't
know it existed there's more rooms that
I don't know about apparently in the
back room usual do you know about the
usual room I kind of I I'm aware there's
a meme for would you like to explain it
it's not a room you want to be in let me
just say that it's it's a dangerous room
Pun It's a punishment room yeah I know
it's a punishment room but the bad kfp
that you get taken out to the bath yes
yes you get it you have a room like that
for your Pebbles no but I should you
should should yeah it will be the room
where you crush them yeah crush them
yeah wants to be crushed by people wait
I think they like that yeah they also
like the usual room yeah I don't know
why they like it so much
masochistic Mochis I I always said
Mochis cuz that's what I thought it was
pronounced Mochis but Mass kissed I
guess yeah spell it B ma m a s o c h i s
t right oh yeah
yeah she can spell I can spell I didn't
I totally did make a typo on my
anniversary tweet no oh M I think I well
you made also a lot of typos in your
sleepy tweet yeah well those those were
on purpose those were on purpose yeah
it's a meme the the missile is I thought
you were really tired no it's a meme I
yeah it's a copy pasta oh yeah it is
I'll send you it a copy pasta did that
would I make it
no I get
it okay would you like to introduce
yourself ah oh yeah uh hello I'm frog uh
no I'm Tak from whole live English myth
your biggest Senai in
Ian yeah uh I came here to sing with you
thanks for inviting me thank you for me
again it is her in the flesh we are in
the same room if everyone here they're
all just going to sneak up behind me and
scare me or something people yes should
I should I should I say something now
about your Ann or after the song What
you let's sing the song first okay what
song did you choose bi boo uhuh
oh you know this song It's your song Oh
you chose my song I chose your song
because I really like your song I Really
I I go and press four all the time oh
press four press four did you did you
try pressing four on on my did you see
my fite night outfit my in
frd
oh I saw yeah the booty did you see the
booty I did see the booty and I saw I
saw the booby I saw the booty and the
booby it
wow I would like to see you in an outfit
like that someday oh me in an outfit
like that yeah I think those kind of
aerobics outfits are really cute yeah
they are really cute cute aerobics yeah
I say aerobics but apparently I'm saying
it wrong what's it what's it called I
don't know it's hard like I aerobics and
aerobics I guess a aob i aerobics
no no close but yeah oh well so on the
butt topic let's sing the butt song
Let's sing the butt song yeah it's the
butt song I guess let's go do you need
an echo a Reverb oh it's
on wow okay where did my files go over
there okay I
see I have everything so organized nice
okay yeah uh you're going to mute the
bgm too oh yes yes yes yes oh this
that's loud okay hold on bgm check mhmh
oh that's pretty loud
H okay okay I think that's good okay is
that good yeah I think so chat what do
you say it was l in the beginning but I
think it's good now right okay okay
ah
Nice N na n
na k i r oh no fell into the office
unknown left me bleeding heartless all
alone no
control don't you dare
apologize turn my back and f a cold
knife listen up cuz here some
advice you're out of time we out of line
it's taking over
like a renegade I for and I I'll make
you
cry tearing it down do just what I keep
calling me a sinner think
so Tak the CR now you're calling me King
you going to hear them all s Now sing
it l like that
don't back it up don't back it up keep
that aim I got thoughts that will drive
you insane come over if you like we'll
have a lot of fun but I got a lot of
Vine I do what I want make sure you
don't forget it an arm on my back say
I'm sick I'm just a distic not living in
a light for right in the night I want to
see the way you bleed nice it's taking
over like a renegade I for my I'll make
you
cry it down I do just what I
want no you think
so got me
Twisted such a missfit taking the crown
now you calling the king you going to
hear him I'll sing
sing like
that I want it all give me some more PL
but me up down into my core oh you wish
I stay down but then I just
ride you're not my
enemy baby you're dead to me hear my
voice screaming out loud no doubt
yeah break it down car down do just what
I keep calling
me taking the crown now you're calling
me King you're going to hear him all
sing
[Music]
in
the yeah it's so cool yay y yay nice one
B boo thank you I love that song your
songs are so cool it makes me want to
dance I'm going to get a cool song like
Kim Kim from you one day I hope so one
day badass be boo yeah bad beeping be
boo okay you can turn the r off oh yeah
re off okay would you like to say anyone
before you go did you see my tweet uh
about your guys's anniversary if you not
didn't see it I'll I'll basically say
the same I haven't because I've been
panicking for the stream so I have not
been on Twitter okay I was a few days
ago but two days ago or so but yeah I
was saying basically to all of you in
Advent you guys it's been one year time
passes by so fast it's crazy I feel like
you guys are still babies but at the
same time I think you all like really
quickly found your place here especially
you I think a thank you yeah and I think
you you found your role your place and
and you know like you're in your flow
and you're like doing so well and I love
having uh this generation of K eyes
that's full of hard workers yeah you all
I was from my POV really really
hardworking and you're really
interesting content creators and every
single one of you brings something
really fun and unique to the table that
is whole life English and so I'm really
really happy to have such great new
colleagues with me and one year is over
but I hope that many many more years
together can be spent and that I can see
you grow more yeah watch me I will grow
I will you will you actually grow in
like size though uh probably not but
I'll grow in other ways yeah I'm sure
you will as a person you're mental and
you gamers
and skillfully not physically but every
other thing yes yeah the best gamer of
Ian is is that maybe something you're
you're looking forward to becoming oh uh
I don't know that that's a pretty
daunting title you can do it people you
can do it oh oh yeah thank you for your
support um but yeah thank you for being
such
a you know yeah you guys have been
around for a while and and we've all
I've definitely looked up to you and and
everything so yeah thank
you come back people thank you yay have
fun everybody and and be be nice to
people otherwise you're going to go into
the the crushing room yeah the crushing
room PEB is that we're going to build a
new room uhoh all right I'll send the
next one right okay send the next person
good luck thank
you
bye yeah we're going to we're going to
set up a room in in rock car
construction it's going to be the pebble
CR pressure room don't be too excited
about that
[Laughter]
right
hello hi you have run
[Music]
run okay
okay happy
anniversary oh thank you it's oh
oh I
am yes first
time together
hi I a very very fun very very fun yeah
yeah just a
moment I want to hear the
word hi
oh
cooking I like
to oh okay can you say can you say
something for
me can you say
g g
G yeah okay sticking sticking out out
your your G G for
forler
y okay keep going your soul you are b b
b b okay okay okay okay your soul your
are b b okay okay okay I I just I just
wna wna be
[Music]
you're cool yeah thank you thank you I
Bano
yeah we are we are cool
together
yeah it's cute cute oh well then you are
cute too no no no
no no thank you
temp baby baby you're baby you're baby
no baby you baby okay do you want to see
who's cooler you want know which color
yeah you want to sing together to see
who's
cooler cool
what tongue do we think
together this one this one this one w w
wo W yeah are you ready okay
[Music]
okay I I chose this song for us because
both Haim and I have a cover of this
song I was like oh perfect so we are
going to say
together together I'm testing
audio okay okay
okay ready okay go okay let's see
together let's go let's
go oh echo echo
[Music]
[Applause]
your is and
[Music]
I
for
[Music]
foree for
sorry I don't want you more
thank you thank you thank
you we were cool right
[Music]
we I'll reg you soon to anniversary when
yeah yeah very soon so
congratulations thank you
happy very very happy thank you thank
you thank you for singing with me thank
you byebye thank
[Music]
you
byebye that
was H yeah we both have a cover of that
song so I was like oh we should sing it
and be cool together cuz everybody calls
is a baby but in reality we can sing
cool right yeah we were very we were
very we weren't cute we were cool right
right right right yes x y b baby
why oh
hey who's
here hey oh you smells so good really
yeah oh thank you she smells good oh I
understand the thing now where where
where they said you smell fancy you you
smell
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
fancy thank you for coming yeah so
happy is here we're
together yeah yeah thank you for coming
me I'm glad I was able to NAB capture
you a Justice member even though you're
supposed to be capturing me I captured
you for this like this is my plan your
plan I'm catching oh oh she's catching
me oh oh you're so warm I'm so cold no
no no it's because like I just came from
outside it's so oh yeah it's hot outside
I've been in this room it's air
conditioned so it's like my hands are
cool cool thank you yeah I'm so happy
how you doing is here I'm doing good I'm
I'm doing better now that you're here
okay long time no see it was we had a
lot of fun yesterday yeah it was so fun
we should play again yeah I want to play
my dead by daylight it was it was I got
a taste I got a taste for killing and
now I want
more addicted to killing addicted yeah
get to the prison again I'm going to C
no don't cat
it I'm coming I'm coming you never catch
me I mean or yeah be lot we can hang out
more if yeah
o did did did you see I was taking a
bath the same time you were taking a
bath last night I was like I had a buff
I feel like I felt you through my phone
taking a bath together yeah ni I did not
drop my phone are you have you ever
dropped your phone in the bathtub I have
never done it but I feel like it's
coming up soon no actually do you don't
you have like a bag where you can put
your phone in it during the buff toop oh
people put it in bags no I just I just
hold it no you should have like a bag
it's actually made so you can have a
buff with your phone I have to show you
oh yes show me the link yes yeah yeah
yeah I'll show you I'll show you ra
would you like to sing with me today I'm
so I came here for that yes we're all
we're going to sing together yeah okay
I'm so excited we're going to sing this
song yeah this song what song is this
it's a song It's a song you know it
right
I sure hope you do I think so I think so
I think so okay hold on let me get the
instrumental yeah I'm so
ready okay I really I really like this
song it's actually pretty good it's
actually very yeah it's so catchy I had
so much fun learning
it okay hold on let me I got to do a bgm
test as always cuz everything has
different
volume oh that's loud that's loud
[Music]
okay that's good let's go okay are you
ready I am so ready are you ready B yes
have you ever seen this in karaoke
before no yay first time together can I
can I tell you one thing this is my very
first off collab yes
y yay first
all yay it's mine I took it yes people
say p thank you thank you thank you for
being here thank
you call me St by oh mama okay okay
ready let's go
ready
unpredictable taking you all below
taking you
all me
irresistible taking you all below below
we go they think they want it they want
to get get down we take them down down
down them in the borderline run it no
surprise you ain't going to win but you
can try told you you got no up in my
line up listen listen
R already like your's games you always
play call me cor won't hear anything a
upside down right on your heart throwing
the forgiv no just
forget got them the higher I Rise down
further you
die standing on the edge don't know we
unpredictable typical you got nowhere to
go show something my you'll never know
as love you
so yeah
yeah
yeah we got it in the light oh my what's
wrong what's right rushing in
a never make
it
I do it do it L on it now enemies gr let
count see your
guilty
heart we're not going to stop it's just
our
star get down get down down like like
that run it like that get down get down
down the take it up up up let's go go up
go below you already know
run in the light oh my de what's wrong
what's right with you run in the night
oh my come take a
bite the for you're never
forgiven
we standing on the edge so now we are
predict typical you got nowhere to go
show you something real My Level no
you'll never know
and Below you should
know little unpredictable beautiful just
let's get let get him baby go next level
almost crial as a It Go
Bel woo
Let's go people yeah let's
go it was so much fun yeah I love your
song You're So
hype yeah I like I like how the both of
us you couldn't see it but we were both
like dancing and Bing I wish you could
see I I wish you could move right now
because we were we were all just like
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it was so H it helps the yeah it was so
high thank you for
coming you have one minute do you have
any words to say I want to say that I'm
so happy that I got to me you and you're
such a nice and and you're so nice to me
and I'm so excited to have more
adventures together and more games
together and and and we're hanging out
together hang out yeah I'm so excited I
love you and happy B aniv yay thank you
and I am I am proud to have you as my
cooh high even though I don't really
feel like a kohai but I will do my best
as a senpai to give you any guidance or
any questions you may have or just play
games together I don't really care as
long as we get to hang out more exactly
that's all it matters I just want to
hang out thank you so much
and hug me hug me yay have a nice time
you go ahead and stand in the next
byebye I love how they all just run
away that was RA we saying above below
which is their Justice is original song
go listen to it if you haven't yet yeah
by justce I guess you're okay hello
hello oh she's not running she's just
walking in a cool slow motion slow
motion let
go head on hi hi oh Dad hey every
everyone know they could hear me from
far away hey Dad spotted father spotted
hi I'm Dad yeah you you really you
really acted like my dad during the trip
huh oh yeah I guess I did huh yeah I was
just like following you around like a
little lost duck the entire time yeah
and you like trip over like a a random
like rock on the ground or something
like that and and then you're like B
you're going to die I'm so scared I'm
like oh it's just normal this is just
normal B it's just normal B oh my gosh
wow I'm glad you invited me though to
continue shepher owning you as your
father I here oh she's big oh well she
can stay big I have a huge head she's my
father put my brains in such a huge head
hello uh would you like to introduce
yourself okay here I go me and a song
it's me more k Hol live english's
hardworking shinig gumy from myth first
generation of Holo e and let's party
let's party yeah thank you for coming to
my anniversary stream yeah I'm honored
to be here can I have some of these
chips chips yeah there's some chips
right right in front of us oh oh yeah
yeah you can have some cool all right
real later but they're decoration right
now you know you can't ruin the the
stream decoration chips yeah decoration
but I mean you can eat them later though
yeah okay I'm going to steal them let's
go but if you didn't know I and and
Callie went on a little mini vacation
together for a couple days it was so
much fun yeah we did it was a secret myy
crashed the party crash well not you
didn't really crash the party we were
like hey come with us hey and I was like
okay if I'm allowed yeah cuz yeah it was
really fun we went on and the and the
cold water thing I will always remember
that that's so funny yeah that was
pretty hilarious I wonder if those
obachan are still remembering I remember
distinctly her
noise yeah I was like did she really
make a sound but now I'm like you heard
it so I heard it no she she definitely
made a sound we all heard it she
like oh foreigners repulsed by us all us
foreigners squeezed together in the cold
Waters hey I I didn't know anything and
you guys were in there first and I
followed you in so that's not my fault
my fault for not read hey you know what
I can speak I can speak a decent amount
of Japanese but I can't read kanji okay
so when the kanji says hey this is for
this is something that you need to not
like this is something you need to pour
on yourself with a bucket and not like
get inside of I couldn't read that okay
but actually listen though it didn't say
you can't go inside it said this is this
is for the bucket and you use your hands
to put it on you it didn't say say hi to
the side okay well now they're going to
put a sign there now because of us yes
they 100% are going to do that yeah
that's fine so see it was it wasn't for
nothing there you go bright side
everything what you like to sing a song
with me I would like to sing a song
remember remember that rap part that I
said I was practicing oh can we sing it
together because I'm not exactly that
confident in it by myself so I changed
the colors to the lyrics from purple to
Black so it together sing it just
letting you know that the colors Chang
because like uh there's a lot of songs
of pricing but we we can sing it
together oh you bet yeah I'll have more
confidence if we sing that part together
yeah don't worry but let's let's wrap it
together and uh and everybody in chat do
you do you have like a a b with
sunglasses emote or is it oh oh yes I do
have a b with sunglasses em I need to
see some biu with sunglasses in the chat
hold on let's go I volume check
okay that should be good I think should
be good and then we break it down here
no not this part
this yeah you ready I'm ready I know
this song you know this song I know it I
sort of know this song I hope I do
you'll do great I he let's do
it let's go yeah that's Karma yeah get
down
sorry j I'm a superar St but you rock
with it yeah like 247 I'm a hot miss you
love me get less boring oh my God home
run but swing my
shot yeah like a villainous villain
bring home a jackpot
[Applause]
[Music]
but yeah yeah yeah life just a TI Why
not stop to fool around chaotic good is
Peak right now I can show you how yeah
yeah yeah get confused we are not the
same I'm ruthless D no way no way I way
good versus evil so done let's kick back
and just leave it
to lose my lips lose my little lips yeah
that's Karma to die
haa ah loosen my lips I'm about to say
some is get it yeah that's
Karma I'm
just go
get trick while running but you think
you're
clever
whatever about
a hey y'all checking this out
yeah [\h__\h] with it Pebbles come
on we got
this it bu it
the is evil but I'm which one just stuck
here in the middle that's
fun listen my lips listen myps yeah
that's
Karma
whoops my lips I'm say so yeah yeah
that's karma
[Music]
while you're running you think you're
clever whatever
game
by we're so cool we're cool you're lot
cooler than me but I'll get there wrong
wrong we complimented each other your
your cute Vibes complimented my own Kaki
Vibes you know did you hear I I
pronounced it perfectly you did
yeah what a tongue twister perfect why
did you put that there I didn't I didn't
write the Japanese lyrics somebody else
wrote that right but I asked them to
make it hard so oh you asked them to
make it hard I see yeah cuz it's more
fun that way it it it is fun I could do
it perfectly a little bit but like when
they last saw I was
like it's okay we we totally did a
perfect the moment you did it perfectly
don't even worry about that was fun that
was so fun thank you for singing with me
I've had that song stuck in my head so
much that's how I know you know you make
a banger because when like the brain
worms right before you go to sleep don't
get confused we are not the
same no way no
way I'm so glad happy anniversary bab Bo
have any words for me let's see H let me
think you are a rock of sheer will and
determination thank you and and if you
want something nothing will stop you
yeah and I think that's amazing also
quick question uh after yesterday's
collaboration um I just wanted to let
you know we are hiring um we are hiring
down in the Underworld for Shinigami if
you want to take the job oh yeah I'll do
it a really good killer yeah I'm really
good at killing right such a g yeah if
you want me to take you on as an
apprentice I totally will swag I'll
think about it I'll think death Sensei
may say no but I just I think it's
really cool that whenever you like set
your mind to something you can do it and
I think that's amazing so so keep it up
it's called being stubborn I'm just
stubborn Like a Rock like a rock the
reason stubborn as a rock is like an
actual phrase yes all right well thank
you so for coming uh please feel free to
bring the next person in also hi GJ
thank you for the let's go so much for
being being a very good Senpai you you
you are a good Senpai I was teasing you
yesterday but you're an amazing Senpai
and I appreciate how much like we you
hang out with me of course let's keep
hanging out and play games have fun
having fun together I'll go get the next
person but happy
anniversary see you later G with the
rest of the karaoke thank you man I like
this collab I can just make everybody
praise me and well because it's my
anniversary don't get confused we are
not the
same we waiting for the next
person hello hello
H oh she's running
hi oh wait wait wait let me get your
thing
y for St Jor
yay yay yay this is first off collab
together yeah this is the worst
[Music]
timey you're here I always love playing
games with you and everything so I
really wanted you here and and we GL his
anniversary soon too right yeah in two
months I guess oh two oh two months oh
please put r Glass to they they are they
debut shortly after us so I'm still
technically a sampai and that's why she
calls me senpai yes you Senai Bai I'm
being Senpai by two months
yes but anyway yes yay happy V of first
anniversary
congratulations Kawai positive
jius very
I'm very happy that you're here I'm
happy
[Music]
too sticky y oh my God so
happy we just by Galaxy beautiful
cute have you remember to use the word
words I taught you have you been saying
gut yes yes don't get it twisted don't
get it twisted don't get it twisted G
yes o o oh yes
o yeah g g cat do you want to sing a
song with me yes I want to okay I'm so
scared I'm so scared
too hold on let me find it oh okay we
can do it we can do it I I had to learn
this one I didn't know this one but I
like I like this song but I've never
learned seeing it before so I gave you
the hard part okay it's fine I gave you
I gave you the hard part but that's okay
it's fine if we want you can sing
together okay we'll sing together yeah
okay uh let me let me test this one is
different yes this one is correct this
one is correct okay
wait I have to put my head head
here is the volume okay yes okay okay
yay
yay I'm sorry you can't move but I'll
dance for you thank you I'm moving so
much
[Music]
okay
go yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
y
[Music]
for oh you so
cute cute cute
cute I don't know how this next part can
you help me help me help me
[Music]
no no way it's not here
I know
[Music]
hey
hey oh my God oh my
God oh wait wait is it not yet not yet
it's over no here la la la
perfect
perfect yeah when I when I hear the song
I saw oh my God I want to I want to hear
v p Mor so thank you yeah I love I love
we and she's my favorite Floyd yeah I
like this song A lot but obviously I did
not know how it
goes yeah it's pretty timing but anyway
we are great yeah we were cute that's
all that matters
yay andai please please hang out with me
many times and I want to cow wither
again okay let's collab together let's
do all collab together while I'm here
and let's eat food we haven't eaten food
together yet and you said you would take
me out to eat food so we got to go eat
food I will differently yay
y thank you for coming to my
anniversary congratulations again you
please enjoy after this yay byebye
byee
[Applause]
you she ran
away oh oh
hi hello hey there's a party in in the
back room
huh oh this one this this one this one
okay
this is the first time we
miss nice to meet you nice to meet you
too we are actually meeting for the very
first time you you are here to witness
it happy happy first anniversary
congratulations thank you thank you for
coming today thank you too
thank you are we so excited to sing with
you yeah I'm so excited yeah I love your
new outfit it's so cute yeah thank you
yeah it's too bad that that she can't
move right now because her new outfit
it's so cute look at the Burger H you
can't eat it I can eat
it it's
oh thank you so much
I'm so excited yeah again I this is the
first time we met or we meeting so I'm a
little n k
nous nous nous
nervous we sing we're singing together
today y yeah yay we singing together and
we're singing
hatai song hat
we're singing her song today I was going
to sing it together and let me let me
set it up
okay
okay nice
nice I I like how your songs are in
English yay
English why why song do you have a
reason why you pick your songs in
English oh because I want study more
English oh very good very good reason
[Music]
yes
okay
okay uh sound test
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
ready okay okay
even if means you happy all day last
time I leave you alone for a while even
more you ask me to slap how can you be
like disgusting life yeah I
conratulations thank
you have a nice day
[Music]
even if I sneeze you happy all day last
time I leave you alone for a while and
even more you ask me to slap in face how
can it would be like disgusting
like
to my water hi are you really falling
thisy fing
sweeping open your mouth drink back
water step on you and kick you harder
give me your neck cut off your head all
time with me I'm to
you don't you hear me I will let go away
so told you a cross that it's not
actually thing you are swe please for
give
me oh people so cute thank
you K hit you baby slap and slap my
cuest Toby beg and please we hug and you
give me crying more more louder I'm but
your voice will make me know
my me I'm here
always where is your place by Wonderland
it will be looked like
underground they always fall them hard
away come here from the
when you are hide and cry alone we will
be the time wonderful say and do what
you want to be come alive follow heart
sing SM and will be happy happy when I
cry uny
will when I'm and and oh my goodness
when I start open up my Wonder
from my
wonder
[Music]
wonderland
hi
hi hi don't you the remember water yes
are you really falling this fing swey
yeah open your mouth Dr back water step
on you and kick you harder give me your
neck cut off your head all time with me
open your mou Dr B body step on you and
K
[Music]
[Applause]
C I'm so
happy thank you thank you come on thank
you for coming you are original e Senai
so I am honored to have you here today
thank you so much
thank you okay byebye
byebye have F yeah yeah yeah have fun
okay okay
okay you can't see me wave but I'm
waving e and there's like a party bag
there they're all having a party with oh
hello oh
it's a group this
[Music]
time a
group byebye
bye hi we came all together as sisters
sisters she
s than here
super
cool just like every day oh thank you my
baby baby
[Music]
hi
hi oh wow oh there's something Co here
is there is there a party going on back
here
I I keep hearing like every time we open
the door they're
like they have a party it's my
party oh I'm so excited everybody's here
all right well today we're going to sing
together unfortunately we couldn't learn
uh s's new song
but I picked this song because you know
M you and me everybody says you know
we're not sexy so I I bought money in
here yoube she could help us with that
boy sexy yeah sexy push sexy feelings I
will push my sexy
feelings
[Music]
set
you promote your stream
yeah yeah let's
tomorrow we have our first year
anniversary it's going to be a big
celebration cration big announcements
big announcements very very big special
announcements please join us okay don't
miss it
okay check
volume quiet
quiet what song this be what song this
be I don't know this
song Good you
[Music]
think
okay m
okay ready oh I'm nervous on don't be
nervous okay we're singing
together
[Music]
okay dangerous
Reverb for so
[Music]
[Applause]
you're going to get that Tre maybe
[Music]
me nice
in my
[Music]
KNE we will s the
1 son smiling
GRE
shining
my now please my newest
dream open up
thisx open it right now or I will
k a
what
[Music]
sex
say oh baby
you're you're sexy now right you don't
if you're baby people you don't need any
uh it's okay happy birthday happy
birthday
I Yay take me now
together I wanted to ask you know since
this is our anniversary and SEL has any
you know FES and life
get even more sexy okay sexy practice up
your sexy skills sexy
if you practice anymore it's going to be
[Music]
called my baby
thank you thank you for
coming
conrat for you guys tomorrow sure to
check out their stream tomorrow they
also having an anniversary stream they
yest or tomorrow not yesterday tomorrow
tomorrow so please be sure to give them
lots of love and congratulations
Evan go back to the party that I'm not
invited to yet by by byebye
byebye byebye byee byebye bye
baby NY Ned me
say not not me m not me okay we Cal we
calm
now give me a h I'm so happy I I reble
is winning today this is the best
decision I've ever made I'm so happy
right
now I think the next person
[Music]
Hi congratulations
happy first year
anniversary I love you oh I love you
you pretty girl
please marry
me yeah
yeah I win oh I'm excited to sing
together oh yes let's sing together uh
this song you sing a
lot
right hi hi bring you
sing a lot this song right are you Pro
you good at this song so I you practice
oh I I
practice membership Oh Oh Me Oh hi what
you know oh
wow ah ah okay I'm excited to sing
together how good
thank you for being here
today happy
happy okay let's be
together oh also uh
hi last guest of of today
yes congratulations you're very special
the final guest
today
okay oh
hi hi hi
[Music]
it's not me it's not me yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
best the best oh yeah
way
[Music]
watch
who the best I'm the best oh
[Music]
yeah the
I
[Music]
let's do more and have fun yes let's
play more and have fun
[Music]
nice kind kind kind very very kind very
very
cute alun is uh uh uh very
beautiful yes uh
for love love
love I love
you I love
you
anniversary how do you say soon
[Music]
hi I love you I love you hi
hi bye
happy I love you I love you
too thank
you and
[Music]
it
was just people and
you just people and
you just people and us today they're
having a party without me now oh
man but that's okay we can have our own
party over here how did you like it did
you enjoy my guest yes I'm very happy I
got praised by so many
people Encore oh you want an encore from
me did I prepare anything I did maybe
just a little bit oncore for just people
okay I will sing a song I will sing one
more song but I don't think it's a song
that you'll think it is but I wanted to
you know
re
rewind and sing this last song for
you uh because it was an important part
of my debut and people singing Journey
so we are going to sing it today oh now
that my guests are here I guess I can
get bigger
uh okay hi B's big now hello did you
have
fun I was really nervous because there's
a lot of really cool people people here
today um but yeah you know I
didn't you know we did we did the the
karaoke for my birthday and it was
really fun and then I was like oh yeah
I'm here in Japan now there's a lot of
people in Japan let's just meet all of
them and I asked everybody who was in
Japan like hey you want you want to sing
a song with me and and then a lot of
them said yeah so I'm really happy thank
you to everybody who um joined for me
today thank you for making the time with
me like they came all the way here for
bble just like to have like 10 minutes
of of collab time with bble so I'm very
very grateful that I can spend uh my
anniversary with now and I hope you
enjoyed us having fun together um but
yeah it's been it's been quite a journey
here first year now we are entering the
second year I have a lot more yeah I
guess and now I'm getting settled in now
I'm settled in now so I I think one of
the big things that I want to do now is
like do some idle stuff you know I got a
taste of it now you know preparing for
my 3D and everything so I'm I'm really
enjoying singing I'm really enjoying
dancing I'm really enjoying like doing
the things like you know you know going
up on stage one day and stuff like that
that that's really exciting to me so
that that I feel like that that's going
to be one of my goals for the second
year I know it's a lot of people's goals
but I feel like that's a big goal for
bble to continue on bab's Idol Journey
and grow into an even bigger be not
physically uh because that's not
possible but uh we can grow in other
ways yes one day and I hope I'll make
you proud of me yeah but with that being
said let's sing our last song
together
[Music]
um this was the song that I covered on
deut it has a special place in my heart
um and yeah I hope you will listen to
it okay I will get this right I've been
getting it wrong all day cuz I've been
getting so excited BTM off Reverb
on okay I'm checking volume cuz every
single file has a different volume I
guess uh
[Music]
is this delici you
[Applause]
loud too
[Music]
loud okay cool that's
good here we go the song that started
B's Journey uh
[Music]
okay I forgot I didn't have the lyrics
all so I have to look look up the lyrics
online just just in case I don't
remember them but then there's
ads then there's ads can we can we pick
one that doesn't have
ads
uh I I had everything prepared except
for these
[Music]
one well I know I know I know it but I
just want just in
[Music]
case please don't play any sound please
stop
okay okay ready now this one I feel like
starts right away uh okay B Bo is
ready
actually I don't know how to work
Japanese keyboards where is the button
where is the oh oh okay okay okay okay
okay good
ha
[Music]
okaye
e you
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
fore foree
[Music]
[Applause]
ahee
[Music]
for you will
die
[Music]
for ah
a
[Applause]
[Music]
everyone
yeah
yay thank you for spending one year with
B
Bo I will work hard to make you proud
this year two of our time together thank
you pebles thank you
everyone uh before B girl I have a few
things to show you uh it's not
merch not the people doesn't have Merch
this time H it's not it's not merch I'm
saving it okay but I do have a few gifts
I few I have a few gifts for you before
before I go
[Music]
firstly
boom for members you remember that
summer
wallpaper that that uh oh I have Reb
still on
boom that summer wallpaper I promise you
it's
done yay it's a it's a nice
one yeah look look at that it's boring
but I will be posting it on
um member in the members post soon it
will there be a download link so if you
have membership to biu you'll be able to
get this uh bio summer wallpaper it will
be available for two months two months I
guess yeah I guess that's like around
the end of the summer until the end of
the summer I guess so you can have that
um I got that for you happy birth Happ
happy
anniversary special wallpaper for you
and then
boom oh oh that's not it oh I got this a
many time tell me this thank you for
this thank you pal for this cute um
board that you made for me I'm I you
guys overwhelm me with your love and um
I am so grateful to have such an amazing
audience as you guys you guys make me so
sentimental and I always feel so
supported and and grateful for each and
every one of you pal so thank you so
much for this uh cute cute
board look at all the cute people are
thank you I recognize some of these
thank you so much for the board and then
B has one more thing uh that I will give
you without any context it's just an
image that's it that's the
image coming
soon something is
is
oh I don't know what does this
mean who
know I I don't know what it says coming
soon and there's like a water can and a
plant in the question mark I don't know
you get zero context as to what this is
this is just a thing that is coming soon
yay isn't it great this thing that's
coming soon be be forward look forward
to
it make your guesses because I'm not
going to tell you what it is I'm just
telling you that there's a thing coming
soon yes that's all I can say I'm just
going to repeat coming soon coming soon
cuz something is coming soon there is a
thing
ha a tea party I we could have a tea
party if you want to
okay that is it for the B
announcements and that's how soon soon
TM yeah soon TM thank you everybody for
coming to my anniversary
[Music]
stream yes thank you for supporting me
and aent all this whole time oh where's
my B there it is um I hope had fun with
my guest I'm so happy I was really
nervous to do this because like it's a
lot of people and in person and I was
like oh is anybody going to want to come
see me in person but then they did and
they did come see me and I'm very happy
and very glad that they could celebrate
my anniversary with and you thank you
you you yes you looking at me I'm
staring straight at your face thank you
for supporting people and aent this
whole time yes you
peble
yes I'm not I'm not that great with with
mushy words but I hope you can
feel my emotions me being the gem of
emotions and how grateful I am for all
you and yeah I'm just really happy to be
here I'll always be happy to be here I
I'll always be grateful um for
everything literally everything yes
grateful ha
H
okay bab's got to go I wonder if they're
still partying without me I wonder are
they are they still partying without me
I guess I'll go find out thank you
everybody for coming to my anniversary
soon thank you for all the supers and uh
memberships and listening to my party
today also uh memberships will be read
these memberships will be read alongside
the uh any memb for the 3D debut um so I
will read those together so if you're
wondering when those will be read I will
be reading those together and don't
forget that b uh 3D showcase is
soon soon oh jeez soon is on the third
of vust that's really close that's
really close it starts at uh 8:00 p.m.
PST
3rd of August don't forget I've been
working really hard for it um and I hope
you'll check it out but yeah four more
days four more days I look forward to
the rest of Adent though cuz we've all
been working hard and yeah all right bab
was going now thank you for the fun
karaoke party stream thank you everybody
I had so much
fun people love all I love you too happy
anniversary I love you okay I love you
guys
I love everything oh bio's happy right
now happy thanks everyone
bio
later byebye is this the ending screen I
think it'll just fade um
[Music]
oh