[Music]
take
want
[Music]
let's
go
[Music]
hi
k
[Music]
let's go let's
go
kids
[Music]
say
[Applause]
[Music]
are you ready 3 2 1
go
[Music]
me
for n n n
hey
wait oh my God
[Music]
k
oh I love this song oh my God I love it
wow
K uh do you see something
[Music]
interesting new mug no
not not
new the pineapple is there but what's
the other
video what's that other
video what's this
one
h no it's not do you you've never seen
it
before what is this no it's not fire Ni
no
doesn't exist it doesn't
exist this one this
one it's not even a teaser either no uh
it was just
a a crazy frog of no it's
actually um like the the
H not real MV but like the test footage
yeah MV like something we sent to
Eurovision for the new
song If you read my lips maybe you can
figure out the lyrics to the new
song I turned off the audio though so I
hope you're not hearing
it
yeah yeah yeah
yeah it didn't go orange well no well
yeah oh I mean you can maybe like low
key see at least the vibe at least you
can see it's not like a cutesy song but
this was just um yeah something thrown
together very very quickly in like one
day by Kaa uu or like two days
maybe yeah
woohoo it doesn't even have like dancing
it's just you know mimicking it a little
bit
oh wait did I not uh loop that one okay
but you're not hearing it right just to
make extra
sure you're not supposed to hear
it I I muted it pretty pretty certainly
okay okay yeah so H wasn't really going
to stream today but uh I went to the
doctor after not getting too much sleep
and then I wanted to nap after the
doctor but I came home and I realized a
yeah the Pokémon present is like so soon
and I was probably going to watch it
anyway before I nap probably
so here I
am to watch it with
you it's going to start in like 6
minutes but it's not very
long um you guys have to watch it on
your side on your own I'll just be you
know on the second test tab or whatever
is this the sea time friendly stream I
guess it
is um it so turns out to be this but the
stream is not going to be long um I
guess if there's super chats we'll read
the super chats afterwards and then I'll
dip although can anybody confirm I heard
something
about uh did the chat
die heard something about um oh hi guys
uh uh something being also released like
an hour from now like in on the full
hour or am I did I hear that
wrong did I hear that wrong or did I
hear that
wrong is it just is it just the 12
minutes nothing
else then it's then it's going to be
short very short lived oh froggy and
frog Bird Club
you're welcome froggy wa will forever be
single just like me cuz now frog bird is
dead I
guess hopefully one day she'll find
someone someone else someone you another
frog out there willing to take her and
show her a beautiful
life are we did I not do H did I no I
did ultra low wait and see why why are
you what are you doing guys I say ah you
say b a b
ah it's like the chat is uh kind
of oh oh it's very what's up the
delay I think it's oh there we go there
we go there we go
what yeah something's wrong with YouTube
it took me like so many tries to open
the YouTube Studio too it gave me a lot
of error
messages uh but it's okay it's
okay do you guys see the chat the same
way I see it like does it move the same
way for you guys on your
[Music]
side it's hick
hicking YouTube Broke itself
yeah
oh do I have hyper chat
on no let me turn it on I don't know if
that really improves
it oh my God it's starting in 3 minutes
are you guys ready the link is pinned um
for VA Watchers if there's any who like
want to watch with me in a vaud
afterwards uh I will say
when it starts or so I guess I'll give a
sign it stopped completely chat is
[\h__\h] dead YouTube come on I need to
do a watch
along yeah maybe maybe you the Pokemon
presents is lagging YouTube causing it
to
lag stream's been dying for me this one
the stream should be
fine the stream should be
fine on my side it's fine what what do
you mean you don't want to watch Pokemon
I know what you mean you want to play
Pokemon
understandable yeah come on just watch
it with me just do it just do
it na a YouTube
dying you say it's kind of fixed don't
jinx it it's okay we're going to watch
it whatever whatever happens we're going
to watch it and then I'll take a
nap uh I've heard of rumors of remakes
of the second Pokemon game or what the
second gen or so I don't really uh
remember that I'm not I'm not
like that knowledgeable about old
Pokemon games I think I played
like those green and red or whatever I I
think I played those but oh the Gen five
I see I see I see the black and white
that's the one that's probably going to
be announced I guess maybe people say so
I feel like I've played a lot but I
don't really know I don't remember
anything I don't
remember anything so maybe this will
bring it back into my mind I got to mute
my desktop
audio okay it's starting in the moment
it's
59 and it will begin
shortly what the
[\h__\h] my cats just did something weird I
don't know what it is I didn't see it I
only heard
it uh 40 seconds until the full
hour and then will there be a countdown
I don't remember if they do
countdowns you heard it
too weird
cats
Unova what what's what what's Unova is
that what is
that well 15 seconds
it's already live on Twitch what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] no you guys got to
watch with me on
YouTube you can't go too far ahead oh
that's the region what oh my god did I
play black and white did
I uh maybe not Hello YouTube Let me
refresh
that oh that's now there's a countdown
why do I have to refresh the tab why
don't you just have
happen Okay one minute countdown Pokemon
Black and White let me let me look
that um what does it look like was that
on DS
uh-huh
no yeah that might be one of the few
ones I didn't play
maybe so maybe not the best person to do
a watchong but I saw no one in the Ian
girl sphere is doing a watch along and
it's generally it's a good time for me
good time in the day so I thought okay
I'll do
it but if they do a remake of this is
great it will be a completely new game
to
me it's early as [\h__\h] na I know I
know that's why nobody's doing it so I'm
here okay three two
one zero
St B
Watchers is that the music from
five
wait that's a music from all Pokemon
isn't
it
[Music]
[Laughter]
incognito
hi
Hello whoa Pokemon
day
I think I played
[Music]
those oh what what's first the cards or
the game stupid question from
Wawa the game okay nice interesting
nowadays it's a lot of the time it's um
card game first and then game I feel
like
[Laughter]
Pokemon guys don't don't don't be so far
ahead chill
other
games okay what's first what's
first Pokémon
[Music]
go oh Horizons the serious ah is that
the
anime ah it's the the one with the new
protagonist right is
it
kill
Pikachu
[Music]
Pik good was that
good was that was Pikachu
using strong strong uh uh
uh
Thunder oh Pokemon sleep Jemma uses that
and I don't I don't understand it but
that's
cute that's such a high quality
trailer for
sleeping
hey
yo smoothie what happened to
you did it just
purr likeu
purse
cute
is a dog or a cat Master's
x what what was this game
again a saber-tooth tiger yeah so it's a
cat
right mhm mhm mhm I'll kute
uhhuh mhm okay that's is that a gcha
game a it's a got game
okay Cafe
remix cute chill
[Music]
game I want that
cake give me those
sweets
oh
[Music]
yeah
wooo okay okay they're they're just
quickly zooming for everything Pokemon
unite I played that we played that that
was
fun
it's like they're really stressed out
like they have a long trailer to show us
after this or
[Music]
so what I read Pizza Machine event
instead of prize machine
pizza
next next please oh Pokémon presents
here we
[Music]
[Applause]
go
cute
cool instead of Pokemon sleep now we get
Pokemon eat eat your favorite Pokémon oh
no it's something else genetic Apex what
whoow that's cool that you can open them
like that that's
fun TCG
TCG Pokemon
milk so
Innovative ah that actually reminds me
that literally gave me a throwback
feeling the ja Vu of when
I the of the very few times in my life
when I did open Pokémon packs when I was
very
young that felt
good Pokemon packs are
special the packet is just
m is this completely new this whole
whatever TCG on on the phone or
what they look nice oh
what
he that's
cool probably only for special
[Music]
cards so you can get these cards and
then also fight right
online oh two packs per day at no cost
coming 2024 I mean that looks
nice
well
h that's actually surprising that they
didn't do this until
now took them long
enough they did do
it
give me that folder give
me oh
shiny give me your Pok carts give them
to me or
else that's insane that's really
cool those will probably be the the
best
cards s s
sssr
Gemma will be playing this for sure for
sure she's such a Pokemon
nerd she's such a Pokemon
nerd
okay
end yeah okay this is the important
one last
thing yeah I mean it was always supposed
to be a short one Pokemon day lasts 12
minutes what's it going up
why is this one staying
behind what is that a question
[Music]
mik game
freak This Confidential oh my God I'm
breaking
NDA Urban Redevelopment plan blah blah
blah City a vision of beautiful
coexistence between people and Pokémon
what is
this is this
zova
yova is this not what people
wanted what is
this
Pokemon
Vision Pokemon
VR my
guess judging by
this oh welcome to
Paris
Matrix
caros Lum
City so X
Y did they skip one then is that the
sixth one Pokemon Legends
Z
minus uh
a
releas hey
what what is this my Legends was with
archaos right I really lik archaos so
many people disliked Archos I loved
Archos wait Legends so it's a new game
or what I don't understand explain to me
XY that those were existing games is
this a remake
or what is it the megas are back
[Laughter]
oh new megas okay
okay uh I'm so confused I'm so
confused it's not
Mainline a year away yeah probably like
January or so January 20125 is what I I
would
assume but it's is uh actually
surprising they're
skipping uh December like the the
Christmas
Market for gifting to your kids it's
like Aros you
mean as in
what I'm so confused it's modern day
Legends with s Gard yeah cuz like our
our chaos was old so this is the future
I
guess oh I wonder if the whole game will
be in that style Matrix
style I'm
confused m
yeah I guess they're spending more time
with it this
time mhm unless they suddenly reveal
next week that something else is coming
for
Christmas that would be a bum Boozle so
M they probably couldn't do gen five
remake a justice so they're settled for
this one
instead h no that was not enough
information when do you think that
release more information what how how
fast is it usually when's the next
trailer what what's the usual
Pace a month later
or maybe
summer oh what a
bamboozle ah wa XY suuk looking at z
a I'm on sub's Channel right
now oh is she doing like her Morning
News no wait it's not
morning
Channel
ah this one I
can
just talking about my
message what double watch along First
Watch along Pokemon now watch along sub
no just
kidding okay now she's not talking about
me specifically just about generally the
welcome
messages but
yeah okay well what do you guys
[Music]
think should be good should be good
might be
good what did that say though was it Z
minus a Z 2 a what what happened to the
rest of the ABC hm
Z to
A no FS head empty
same I'll take it well um there's a
there's a certain YouTuber whose uh
opinion I would like to
hear so I'll check it out after
this Z but V makes it a what
why that's Z and a is such a weird
they're they're looping it yeah so they
can start again
but when then why do they need to Loop
it when they missed already so many
letters what about they should do like q
and
W and MN how about MN o MN
o what's with all those letters
eh they're they're are cool they're so
cool those letters are so cool yeah L
and W would be
funny L and W Pokemon
LW and M and M and
N why don't they do that what the hell
now they just reusing letters as if
there weren't
more
um L
plus happy birthday w w
w you need to ship them that all right
I'll send him a
letter yeah just just use more use more
letters because this game is launching
in 2025 this could be the game to launch
a new
Switch
yeah
oh oh it probably is oh it might
be maybe that's why they're missing out
on the Christmas
Market oh maybe n nintend kind of forced
them to like yo sorry sorry gang we kind
of have to move the switch to you know
away cuz like damn we're not I don't
think we're going to get done I know you
you guys wanted to release it for
Christmas
but yeah so this is how it
is they're like oh man God damn it all
right guess it's aan sh thing
[Music]
the trailer also didn't have that little
switch screen with the finger snap that
they always
[Music]
do put on the tin foil
hats we know it all Nintendo we know it
all game freak we have to shout you in
German we say to shout we see right for
you
interesting okay
okay yeah I don't know what else to talk
about we watch the presents good okay my
job here is done let's read super
chats going to chill a little bit and
then I I'll go take a nap and you guys
you guys what are you going to do what
are you going to to do with the rest of
your day huh use it well use it
wisely use it like it's your last day on
Earth sleep reink
oh think about the
wow think about oh my God why is there
two people saying
that touch
grass doesn't work work on my
car
make Ki clip
oh thank you I like your
Clips shout out to SM ktj was it smk TJ
no wait I got it
wrong
smk what was
it
smk who knows
smk tkj smk
tkj what does that
mean but yeah I think I think you're
you're doing good work I think as far as
I remember yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
thank you so much I appreciate
it keep it up keep it up keep it
up all right do guys want some
[Music]
bgm preparing a ttrpg session oh fun why
am I not
invited hey
yo what's your PGM what's your bgm
what's your
bgm what's your bgm what's your
bgm what's your
[Music]
your
new jeans come back
when do Co come back I'm
waiting oh [\h__\h] I can't hear it
again wait let's do something on YouTube
then what ah H H life
y
oh what I never saw this one holoscape
ambient whole life
ambient what
what but there's actually absolutely no
no even like likeing plinging sounds to
reference song this is is this literally
just
[Applause]
water it
is they could have made those birds sing
one of our
songs whole life what the hell you're
just now an Ambient sound channel
what there's another one relax to the
sounds of an open
campfire
why they just want to show like some
moving
pictures this is
interesting such an interesting
choice I I'm
confused all
right
whoa when in doubt it's
this
haven't used this one in a while I think
cie uses these a
lot
yeah hey
he what a
Vibe I'm going to read Super
Chat and thank you so
much for all the love for all the sweet
words that you s to me
okay Holo
eoi we
we we caught up with super chats
yesterday
so Cruz D Jac 47 D James MC D mafin
eight thanks for the
pinky T to because I mentioned the poker
presents in my tweet yesterday I
apologize in advance if this turns out
to be nothing and to fill the the rest
of this Grand's 10th anniversary event
is about a certain Primal Beast of
Phoenix oh they're really baiting
me tails off collab and other stuff and
freaking Phoenix
event they want me if you want me then
sponsor
me trying to send me signals just make
it clear and direct
yo
man trust me don't do
but we can't lose you not again don't
worry don't worry I'm not falling for
CCH
game I don't know why mafin is also
mafin must be working with
them you're advertising them so much but
don't worry I don't know it wasn't
nothing but
um yeah well that's what it
is the the game will probably eventually
turn out to be very interesting
once we see a more detailed trailer
looking forward to that Legend said a is
huge lorewise I think the a is an alpha
is an
alpha if you think it's not an a it's
Alpha I'm a clean house and work and
think of waa hope you nap well and have
a good day thank you why would you think
it's
Alpha oh you think it's not a z but also
Omega what was Omega
om God doesn't look like that
right yeah no no it doesn't look like
that
what that was not an
Omega a for S not z a maybe maybe it's
playing in
Arizona Omega is the end minus Z is the
end of the
alphabet there's a character in XY
called
AZ
oh Pokemon Arizona Let's Go America is
Big you can make a lot of that whatever
it
is we won't know for
sure check monkey
d h k
D
ohuh yeah you learned something nice
[Music]
Els Pokemon XY was the Gen that really
leaned into French style fashion and
outfits so here's hoping they make more
clothes in Z for you
tal I I I think one of the biggest
things I was disappointed with with the
most recent Pokémon game was that every
everybody was just constantly wearing
those school uniforms and you got
variations of the school uniforms like
colors and all that but that's it I need
me some cute
fashion yo you can't take that away from
me when you gave it to me once like
really cute outfits and now that that's
that was a big disappointment for
me so please bring me the
fashionistas bring me Paris bring me New
York bring bring me
Tokyo bring me
Rome DLC had some better outfits but to
lock that behind the pay wall socks they
had non school school uniforms in the
DLC well well well h
w and you're welcome thank you for
tuning in so spontaneously and my push
HD thank you now I have to refresh cuz I
know you guys sent a few more in that
short
time
a Rowan thank
you thank you thank
you and the gamer cre than you're
welcome thank you for showing H your
face here you beautiful face you
beautiful chicken Sky D Slavic fellow D
thank you
oh
H you're welcome you're welcome yeah I
guess you're going to make use of
it Japan life hack Japan travel hack
space waterfall D and Cru
d a a a thank you that's
a good timing to tell me
that thank you so much guys I'm done
with the super chats wow
uh tomorrow I might play H maybe pal
world or something else I don't know but
I'll stream uh
something for
sure
tomorrow oh and I think I'll call into B
uh tosu
Mai no I'm still waiting on Dave the
diver rly with time you
know 5 p.m. one time maybe start all
maybe okay what did one more come in Oh
Yeah scratch cut me off thank you I'm
looking forward to Legends dead a
because X and Y felt unfinished to
me okay I can't really judge that I
don't remember anything are you going to
play a DLC for scarlet and violet uh or
you already played it I watched uh I
watched a playthrough of it from someone
else I don't think we had perms at all
for that
so yeah couldn't play it it's so sad we
don't get perms for the DLC I would have
loved to play it if we had
perms yeah but uh Pokemon perms are a
little bit complicated
always I wonder
[Music]
who same person who I'm going to go
watch
now yeah game well even that was limited
time so
yeah don't Island you want to go back to
Dondo Island it's calling for us our own
Island okay I'm going to go and German
we in oh my God 47 minutes
what this is like a YouTube short
basically
damn damn what the hell not not even an
hour
what I feel sick I feel disgusted I want
to throw
up see you
tomorrow yeah bye I'll be the
[Music]
same
oh and make sure to check out ity NY h
on the honey Works album kobu and kada
song it's so
[Music]
cute I got a message that I don't want
to
read
[Music]
e