[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
how are you
ah what time is it it's
hi
how are you guys doing are you alive
sick
well first of all one thing I uh you
know promised you guys was to covered on
as soon as I got the 3D showcase so
foreign
[Laughter]
we waited so so long for this finally
happened and um it's finally here it's
here I can't I can't contain like
something and I'm sorry
but you know I'm going first you know we
usually for relays we ended up with you
know the debut order but this time for
special
event I'm the first one to go so I'll do
my best but make sure you check out the
others uh three showcases coming up in
the upcoming weeks too yay but yeah yeah
well first of all I guess I can show you
guys around the place maybe maybe yeah
okay comment yourself follow me follow
me yeah so you guys have maybe a little
bit familiar with this place you know
there's some art supplies no my little
drawing Works face oh I guess I haven't
really shown you guys how I did
traditional art but
someone familiar
could it be
oh
I'll try
it's our time
in the flesh
being out and sleeping right now but I
guess you heard of Eden's back how about
I'll chun's back
I guess you don't really see uh elton's
back that often hey but apparently if
the TV drama has been decided on but
it's you know I I think it's still in
the works
but yeah this is our time
and I guess you can look around the rest
of the room well here's my little
bookshelf area it's not full of books
yet but there's a couch over there I
usually like to sleep on you know I
sleep everywhere and yeah some
miscellaneous things and of course can't
forget
my streaming desk that's right I stream
from here you know I go
hi guys
and you guys see see the you know the
view behind me yeah yeah yeah and then
if we walk over a little more this way
you get to see more butts I love books
but there's like a beautiful garden out
there you guys don't really get to see
this often right yeah and of course
can't forget this angle of the room
which you guys are very familiar with
yay this is my little Studio what do you
guys think isn't it great yeah
oh yeah you know I I really want to show
you guys you know this full space and
finally after what two two and a half I
mean two and a half two years ish yeah
um yeah I'm so so happy
I'm I'm losing my vocabulary here
because I'm so so nervous and happy and
just flooded with emotions I
but I guess uh
there's one thing you guys have been
looking forward to when it comes to 3D
streams huh something I have a children
you guys yet I mean I've appeared in
live a bit appeared in different shows
and programs in my 3D there's one thing
one thing I've asked to be kept secret
until today what do you think it is
what could it be
that's right my tentacles he knows bling
points
but you know it's it's a little it's a
little embarrassing dude look at maybe
let me look away a little bit just look
clear a little bit okay
are you guys ready wait
[Music]
um
that's right I told you guys it's not
it's not attached to my back there's
like a void gate in there somewhere that
there's someone from but
aren't they so
don't you just want to squeeze them you
can't but they're playing
[Applause]
ah okay calm down calm down
what
to get
it
oh tentacles you're kind of in the way
okay look away for a second look away
for a second wait
I'm done okay we good
we got
a message from me oh my goodness a
challenge hmm look at they have cooked
up for me well they sent in some
messages for me so let's see let's see
uh what they have okay let's start with
Kiara
foreign
[Music]
credit card number please
keep on doing that all right bye
yeah you look Cara flew over to uh you
know somewhere else right now
but yeah thank you I will post I don't
pull this is always difficult you know
but I'll try okay what do we have next
um
[Music]
I know it takes a lot of courage to get
up and do this stuff in front of a lot
of people
I love watching you move and wave around
the thing you do with your arms
you know I already know you look so cute
doing it too
videos request is first you got a plank
that's right you gotta get down on the
ground and do that Trend that people did
a long time ago this is just the first
step okay okay I'll wait
are you there yet
okay okay then okay if staff doesn't
yell at you you gotta do the work
oh no stop son is yelling at me it seems
I cannot do the worm
okay I can do this let me guess is it
more of like a full body wave yeah yeah
well that wasn't too difficult of a pose
thank you Inna
I love you okay
I love you
as well
okay who do you have next oh from Cali
[Music]
hello there
your your boy you're a Reaper could I be
Mori of the Miss Generations
wow oh man I have a lot to say but I
feel like
um it might end up being redundant or
unnecessary so I'm just going to say
thanks for being a shoulder for me to
lean on quite literally sometimes um
we've had so much fun together between
Guilty Gear strive and and playing
recorders together and hopefully soon we
can do the ukulele thing but until then
I just want to let you know that you're
a great friend that I can always depend
upon and I never feel weird talking to
you ever like um it's always really
chill and laid back and I think it's
because you remind me of
um my my art friends from the past so
you're very important person to me
um and so uh since I feel so comfortable
around you I'm gonna ask you to do some
poses that make you feel uncomfortable
but not in like a weird way like in a in
like a way where like it's hard for you
to do them because everybody here is
going to be asking you to do like cute
things I'm sure right well I'm here to
dig out the real challenges because life
is full of challenges
um so I'm gonna ask you to do the worm
can you do it more
I get to know her I can only do this I
can only do this I'm guessing the worm
yeah the worm might be a little
difficult for you but I I want to see
you put your back into it you know give
it your Raw but in the event that you
can't do the worm that's okay I've
prepared a second choice you may choose
between the worm or the splits
she's she's gonna get me back for this
one isn't she oh God
I should I should be nice yes you like
these because she's the first one
debuting 3D oh man I know in big trouble
okay look Nina
splits are good for you are they they
can be good for you for your health okay
make you flexible right that's not in my
dictionary you'll thank me later okay
I'll try not to stretch your muscles too
bad whichever one you choose okay okay
if that happens I'll give you a massage
to make up for it okay
that's not very good though not quite as
good as girl oh but still you can count
on me okay just like I can count on you
good luck
okay oh he disappeared all right
well I can't do the worm so I'll try the
splits I'll try this late
okay this is this is
you see I'm not that flexible see I
can't oh yeah I can't touch my toes
okay that is
I'm sorry I tried I tried I tried I
practiced but I just can't touch my toes
ah but okay we have I think we have one
last one last message
[Music]
huh
you know
I wanna watch you do the oh sure okay
okay
good luck with the rest of yours
3D showcase yeah
oh
how do I do this how does it go again
Chad I don't know how
um
[Music]
okay I'll I'll I'll I'll practice this
later thank you sorry sorry
oh but yeah that was that was the call
from from it oh they're honestly
without them I I really
I mean we couldn't be here without each
other so I'm really really happy they're
my gym mates and we can finally show you
guys our 3D showcases oh thank you and
and you guys too without you guys you
know this would not have been possible
so thank you very much thank you
uh yeah well
you know we're kind of warmed up now I
think we can probably move on to
something special like prepare for you
guys so you guys are curious how I you
know craft things from the void it's
time to make it easier for you to
understand I prepared a magical canvas
where I can draw something I can use it
as a catalyst that's right Catalyst to
summon whatever I draw oh surprise it's
okay let's uh let's let's go over there
and bring the canvas over
here is my Cafe
it's pretty heavy but I've been
practicing
[Music]
Orange
blank canvas isn't that so scary
number one you know things are this fear
but let me just grab this magical brush
here wait
hey isn't this brush really thick I
don't know how well I can draw with this
but uh how about we test out the canvas
for a bit okay
um I actually haven't tested if it works
so
uh just draw something really quick
I'm gonna smile
[Music]
speed paint who's that who's that who's
that cutie on the canvas
okay okay let me just put down my prize
so I prepared a special summoning room
just for this occasion so I'll just uh
bring you guys right on over
let's go
all right I'll put you guys on
okay are you guys ready there's a saying
amongst artists if you draw what you
want from the gotcha you shall
you shall get it so it's also called so
that'll be our magical spell today are
you guys ready
foreign
[Music]
hi
face all right
say hi
look at you wait
oh
seems uh seems a little empty
odd
[Music]
you're enjoying this aren't you
see that okay so the canvas works the
magical Canvas Works so I'll just
actually I'm keeping
I'll let you guys go and
since that worked you know special
occasion maybe just maybe if we draw a
whole live number do you think they'll
be summoned as well
oh we'll give it a try
okay okay okay get my special brush all
right uh who should I draw first
oh I know
there's no mistaking
this number I'm sure you guys will guess
right away
um just to make sure I like this okay
got my prize
huh
yeah
who could it be Chad who could it be can
you guess
any yes
uh we have a cup here and some wings
and the word ban hmm
take you to the summoning room
I should have built the summoning room a
little closer to the uh to the studio
bus okay here we go
[Music]
is it working
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
very soft
[Music]
yeah
thank you so much for joining me today
let's collab again let's play I'm still
here
thank you
oh yeah
[Music]
I can't handle it my heart is melting
all right all right since we know that
uh we can successfully summon some other
members there is another member I do
want to try and uh summon you know maybe
you guys will know who she is right away
grab my brush
all right I'm ready speeding time
there's no way like I can get this wrong
right so it's so so easy to draw oh
okay done
oh
can you guys guess who it is
who could it be who could it be
we'll see all right all right to the
summoning room
oh yeah
[Music]
okay all right
all right
[Music]
Mommy
what Mommy oh okay oh okay
mommy mommy no no no no no no no no no
no no no no okay okay I'll check it I'll
turn it I think I messed up I think I
messed up I messed up here okay okay go
back down go back down okay okay seems
like um I have to be a little more
specific
all right let me try again let me try
again all right let me grab my brush
I'll actually be more specific when I
draw this stuff all right all right wait
I draw that means a cute face here her
hair her flowers smile
and done okay
oh
duh how's I see pain I think I think I
stepped up my speed thinking
all right let me just put this down
all right I gotta save Lamy from being
stuck
in another four oh yeah all right let's
go
I'll see if you love me
okay
all right
surely surely it'll work I dropped I do
her more detail this time so
[Music]
and
then
[Music]
[Applause]
you know Mommy
tonight
[Music]
[Laughter]
Generations
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
let me know
come on home oh come home
love me
oh she's so cute oh I can't handle it
she's adorable adorable I can't wait I
really want to try her sake you know but
you know you can't really buy it
anywhere because it's so popular but
since you know I think I can just hear
me over to lami's place
all right all right or how about one
more one more one more member summoning
I realized I needed to draw a lot more
details you know in order to summon them
so maybe you know I can do a special
summon this time
I can do this okay grab my brush for
sure all right
oh
okay
can I already imagine her
oh yeah I can't forget a little
accessory here
um
like that and that
yeah I'm done all right this one took a
little longer but
definitely detailed enough
who could it be
[Music]
hmm it's not yeah
let me put my brush for sure what could
it be there's a watermelon
and some horns flower in her hair are
fluffy fluffy Senpai okay let's go let's
go call her and on the special the
summoning room
sure all right it's a little far I gotta
run you
[Music]
okay okay a little closer they've got
too much running huh
all right
yeah okay okay we got this
foreign
[Music]
videos
[Applause]
awesome on the face no no no no keep the
face
[Applause]
[Music]
it is
bye please show me 25
[Music]
[Laughter]
.
thank you forever
thank you
she's so fluffy and cute I can't handle
it
with my heart
my heart's beating not from the running
but from how cute they are honestly I
can't believe I finally got to meet them
and it's such a special day too
but yeah you know I think the summoning
canvas special magical canvas work
really well but you know what if we also
Drew something different like maybe a
new stage new place you think it'll work
oh we'll never know until we try so
let's give it a try Kelly
all right please get my brush this might
take a little longer because I'm not
very good at drawing backgrounds yet I
think but
okay
all right oh I hope the brush was a
little smaller but
I think I got this yeah okay we have to
use detail this is possible and done
done
um can you guys guess
the stage
it's pretty good I mean it's the best I
can do with this brush
[Laughter]
that's right that's right okay let me
just put down this brush
ah okay well we'll see where this uh
takes us I don't know if it's gonna work
but
let's see all right shall we ah welcome
over to the 70 room
I I should have never okay oh
running up the stairs is to work okay
one last time
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
to each other
thank you
foreign
[Music]
tomorrow
thank you
foreign
[Music]
he thought he did
all Beauty
[Music]
if you could lose
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't
believe
[Music]
foreign
how was the song is it to stay so so
pretty
ah yeah oh my goodness I was very
nervous but I pulled it off I did it yay
well I uh another song for you here but
we're gonna have to change things a
little bit uh so the next song Hold on
let's do this
cool
[Music]
it worked okay
um this place might be really familiar
for you guys
I hope you like the next song
yeah okay
[Music]
foreign
down down
[Music]
look at me
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
in the night
[Music]
foreign
oh my God
[Music]
foreign
you know
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
you're not happy
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
what do you guys think I prepared three
songs for you guys
thank you thank you
[Music]
finally almost over huh we waited over
two issues we planned it out at the Nemo
we had to wait so long but I worked so
so so hard to make this happen
to actually dance it and sing it like
like click live ah
it was all worth it it was all worth it
what do you guys think did you guys like
it do you guys like the stage oh is this
so cool we're in space we're in space
yes special stage for special occasions
so I hope you guys like it thank you
thank you everyone thanks for coming to
watch today ah
yeah oh I can't believe
you know it's I'm still processing it in
my head how
it's it's finally today
I'm gonna cry don't cry in it don't cry
no no leaking ceilings it's okay
but yeah you know um without everyone
you know
of you guys myths all the staff all the
studio staff thank you so so much for uh
making this happen
ah well yeah thank you thank you so so
so much
well you know um no no leaking ceilings
we got we got business here
for the special occasion you know I
believe it's time to maybe announce some
you know good since stuff maybe maybe
you guys ready ready
foreign
[Music]
taco be happy wait what
you you want to become the merch
are you sure about that
I'm sure oh okay I mean if you're fine
with it
well with this Noble Taco sacrifice we
shall free new merch for this special
occasion are you guys ready all right
Taco are you ready
okay okay
I think yeah I think I did it
all right hey you guys ready
[Music]
all right yeah
that's right
squished what happened
okay stop suck on my hand
get off get off
okay maybe not okay
stuff on my hand but
goods for this special occasion will be
oh stopper
Okay taco you can go back now
foreign
[Music]
that's right for all your cup noodle
enjoyers you can now have a personal
takorate to help you hold the lid down
in place or it can be a cute little
figure too that's also a possibility
is this so cute yeah I actually you know
played around with them you can kind of
like push it push the taco down and it
like sticks onto your hand it's very
nice
but yeah this will go on sale not today
not today remember that this will go on
sale starting
March 5th and what's on March 5th it's
Hollow mid
3D collab so after that after everyone's
is over it's gonna go on sale so please
look forward to it I hope you guys like
it oh it's so cute
but yeah uh one more thing one more
thing one more thing is actually tonight
tonight
around what five five hours or so from
now it's gonna be my real holography
[Music]
yeah apparently there's gonna be a lot
of tentacles so I hope you guys look
forward to it yeah
ah it's thin it's been an amazing time
everyone
thank you so much again and make sure
you check out everyone in this 30
showcases too next up is Kira Kara the
team it's you yeah but yes uh and then
it's probably Kelly and then the club
it's right it's gonna be such a fun
month
anyways thank you so much again everyone
for being patient and waiting it's
finally here and I'll continue to do my
best
[Music]
thank you
bye
[Music]
foreign