[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
n
[Music]
a
okay that was so weird
Okay
K oh my God you hear me let's
go I'm a bit bit bit out of breath
already why why hello Kitt oh my God I
hear myself so
loudly did your mic stop working um the
not the mic the the the the mixer was
being weird not properly
starting so I had to restart it and then
didn't uh restart automatically and I
didn't I didn't
realize mhm
did I get the right Final
Fantasy there's so many I think this is
16 we're going to play
16 my library is of blast from the past
yeah I rarely use my PS5 huh but you
know this time I thought cuz you can
play it on the PC too right I thought
I'm going to play it on on the PS5
because what do I have it
for last played game over a year
ago
really well oh there is no PC for okay
well then I had no
choice ah this game was expensive the
really
expensive I feel like normal normal
earning people Man games are a
luxury
yeah I guess it's a normal price for PS5
games but I rarely buy PS5 games so it's
like
whoa yeah it was uh 70 bucks I think
mhm kind of crazy but hopefully will be
worth it final fantasy 16 the legacy of
the crystals has shaped our history
history for long
enough what does it mean what does it
mean sure okay we are going to get this
started it has been a long time coming
but I forgot to tweet so I shall
tweet crystals are bad in the game what
I have crystals on my head yeah let's
just say it's not crystals it's
something
else
beginning my first
FF Adventure
now okay
somehow my my breathing system is not
working so
well
it's probably cuz I was like uh doing
trying to do some stuff before the
stream like vacuuming and doing my
cleaning my kitchen but even then that
was like an hour
ago should have calmed down by now I
don't know it's not like I was
like it's just uh I don't know I don't
know I'm so I'm so short of
breath okay tweet
is going to the
Twitter all
right okay to the left to the left to my
left screen wait you guys
chat to the right
side like this intense cleaning yeah I
felt
like definitely
need definitely we needed to do some
cleaning especially on my kitchen
yeah yeah it's not a labor intensive
task I know I know and it didn't exhaust
me that much anyway like at all but
[Music]
yeah ah okay did you hear my
cat uh how dusty was your PS5 not Dusty
at all no no no no it can't even be that
Dusty oh it caused to what for real is
that like for real for real that member
message uh cuz my PS5 stands like
upwards so it can't even have that much
dust on
it oh Dusty Dusty no you're the you're I
like you I'm not going to vacuum you
don't
worry I heard that this game is very
different from other FF games but to me
it still looks like every other FF game
just by by looking at this screen so we
will see how it goes oh wait I don't I
don't know if you guys have audio cuz I
don't oh no
wait you'll find out really
quick yeah well I would say it has the
typical FF
[Music]
Aesthetics uh Elgato sound capture
is here no here okay hope that
works
it well you know what we'll just do it
like
this
uh
oh ah what did I do ah I did it
wrong I did it wrong there we go I hear
it you hear it oh but wait do I hear it
because of
this yeah okay good good good we
already okay oh
might want to
adjust this a bit louder probably I made
it a bit louder um but you won't really
hear much until later I suppose screen
brightness what how does this
work
ah how does this
work how do I adjust
it I don't get it I I don't know how to
touch it Dad okay confusing mechanics
already it's the future okay I don't
know subtitles yes wireless controller
vibration sure unless it gets annoying
text language English engl oh should we
do English or something
else English English Okay game
performance
yeah should I should I really have to
choose with a PS5 why do I have to
choose I guess frame
rate okay uh
next a I would say frame rate cuz of
particles and
stuff not that strong anymore well if
the if you going to say PS5 not that
strong anymore what's Nintendo going to
say visual alerts en provides visual
representation of in-game sounds and
music oh like like in Minecraft when it
says like something rumbling for example
no we don't need that oh I heard that I
should go for this oh yeah okay wow
scary
okay it was Moss the chronicler
said that the land of
Alesia is blessed in the light of the
mother crystals mother crystals and that
it was this light which finally LED our
four Bears out of the
darkness yet what they saw in the light
nice voice gave rise to
Temptation Temptation Temptation that
ever lures us back into the crystal
Shadow and th did our journey begin
crystals oh my homie hate crystals W
Phoenix it's me it's me a let's
go
already yeah yeah yeah I remember
filming
this yeah that's exactly how it went mhm
I mean they cut a few
parts yeah they do
that
waa yeah that was pretty badass of me
but just a little just a little slight
finger snap does the
trick
o oh I look so cool I'm so beautiful
they did some nice makeup on me that day
yeah
Fireball oh I see I am the
Phoenix cool can we do this more often
yeah this is the live part we had to do
this one live so I'm doing it
now hey I red too early I see okay at
least thank God I have no
I
Fireball I have some more fancy cooler
attacks but they don't want me to use
them ah oh did I do it right this time
they want me to keep thean or attacks
for like another time oh fck
he see I told them we should pre-record
it I don't know why we're doing it
live so many things can go
[Applause]
wrong this part is
pre-recorded
oh
burn burn with
me
[Music]
why have I been reduced to a
fireplace the
year of the realm
873 the NAA defile the dalan Republic
what o
handsome
oh
Yu logo design be light soon both camps
have begun to
stir is that a Brit that I hear you all
know the target shiva's dominant Shiva
I've heard of Shiva and only the
dominant no one
else where's the funny
that he he looks like someone the girl
will be among them do not question
orders we follow them try to keep that
in
mind mhm oh he showed me the middle
finger really
slightly oh he's got like water
magic
what a name that just was Michael
something something coif
Fox so the
tattoo I need to
understand ooh nice
view
[Music]
ooh Focus wyvern Wu you are key to this
mission's success I'm a wyvern for them
what isn't that something you can ride
and the
Flies maybe it's my it's my code
name I said Focus W yeah I'm trying to
walk okay I already to move the camera
mhm okay so double
joystick oh the main menu
press probably that one at any time
outside the cut scene to open the main
menu mhm gameplay configuration settings
including camera inversion can be
adjusted on the system camera Inver is
it
inverted we don't have to
testing
oh uh main menu system options on the
system tab include wireless control
configurations redeemable items
additional content can be redeemed from
the system tab in the main manual upon
completing a chance encounter in the
main scenario okay already too much
information and we have just begun okay
not or maybe I
should make the sensitivity higher I
have a feeling that will be
helpful Target
[Music]
follow
oh I already know I already know what I
want for this all hell is about to break
loose hell is about to break loose
W what if I fall down can I fall down no
oh okay actually that maybe was too
sensitive it is too sensitive time to
move gently to walk fully to run wait
let
me let me undo the
sensitivity a little bit
okay it came over right at the
start just in time gosh it looks so
realistic it looks so realistic
especially when you don't see their
faces the face is Give It
Away the Republican Army front line
oh I see some magic going around who's
magic oh they does everybody is
everybody able to use
[Music]
magic Cho
ball I know
those
oh T anyone
was that a
sub magical a catapult okay okay okay
okay
inferior these I'm blood are more Beast
than
man way this is going they won't need
this new dominant of
those
what
let me in let me do it let me wipe
everybody on whose side are we on left
or
right
NRA stronghold Gates quickly move none
oh what do you mean you
refuse did you not Pledge Your swords to
our cause uhoh
oh come
now Marshall the king of wud is our
guest oh no she's H I was just thinking
she doesn't look like somebody who it's
just
a NPC who will never see again oh it's a
guy but yeah he looks important somewhat
somewhat
important
the other one is
Lady
what and I thought I had seen weird
water containers before Oh I they like
intr introducing me to what you can use
magic for in this
world I wonder that you summoned us at
all have you so little faith in your own
men
she's evil right it was the dalmax who
drove back the Crusaders in the battle
of the twin Realms was it
not or am I mistaken she's very
wobbly
besides your dominant has yet to take
the
field and when he does wait our nights
would only get in the way so what's that
dominant perhaps you have not heard but
the iron blood now have their own
dominant n we would be fools to
underestimate them buger their Knights
something that supports them I
guess should this Citadel be allow to
fall
chunk the how can you be so big exposed
he's like triple the size of everybody
else and I doubt the Crusaders will wait
for the good King's porns to line up
before for taking to the board did he
fall into the magic potion when he was a
baby what's supp the smoking going on
smoking propaganda just leaves
me is he a
dominant the iron blood will rule the
day they set foot on
storm I blood this game is
over I paid seven any bugs for
this you what he's more than just
that he has a name
too
Benedict oh
oh okay
attention take
care does the lion take care when he
chases the hair or do you think me one
of the latter no my love you are a
lion you're my lion doesn't have much of
a man I'm not afraid of a little Frost
benedictor but I will need someone to
warm me when I come
home
I have no idea what's going
on
huh the front lines are
gone this is our chance the chaos will
conceal
us what what's at the middle
button
[Music]
what I can pause for lore huh I didn't
see a middle
button where would that be in the middle
I didn't see
anything or do I have to or my
eh
the
touchpad where did it say touch the
touchpad for more lore or is that just
something you know if you know the lore
then you will find out more lore the
lore is touch to touch
pad it will tell me later a bit late
when you can already do it
now can I get lore now
no and quick and deadly as
always ah
take the
van they have
cards
wait something's not
right
huh what this is this a d
dominant must
be oh
a Titan oh okay D finally grew tired of
being
slaughtered oh oh is it going to
smash the
Crystal and look who's here to GRE is
that Shiva is that
Shiva must be Shiva right I don't know
it gives him Shiva Vibes I don't even
know who Shiva
is or is
Shiva I I connected the
dog
oh
oo small the small the
Titan small
TI
[Applause]
oo oh let's
go didn't uh those those those pool
people say oh not afraid of a little
cold
they must have been talking about
[Music]
Shiva
wow she's so
pretty
yes no
weak
seems spining
no
ah
you don't get to Die Here W
move why they a come
mey don't mind me what what
um yeah okay let's
[Music]
go
he I couldn't do anything about
that she's on she's on well you said
something
oh oh who that
sha I love how they
swear mostly games that I play are
always like so
game oh okay so climbing like this is
automatic I appreciate that
[Music]
who's going to stand
there who's going to
[Music]
stand what the
man where's my 10
snowboarding feels just like
[Music]
it
ou w w need
glasses who is what is
be
I told you before you do not get to die
here man he probably really wants
to
oh huh
brother brother which
one which one was
it huh get up
live I'm C right is this the past this
the
past 13 Summers earlier year of the
realm
860 the
grand well if you're not C out to be a
shield there's always work for you in
the Stables unless of course you think
you can defend your master while sat on
your ass in a puddle of pig sell
I'm sure he'd find a way my brother
always looks after me right go
on don't give up now oh my God the
little
puppy brother always looks a for
me in that right C what it wouldn't do
to disappoint the gallery
what it
bow
bow oh fight practice let's start again
from the beginning come very nice place
to
start attack the Lord
Commander me attacks press uh that
button to perform a melee attack up to
four attacks can be chained
together
okay is there a lock on oh yeah
L1 success
that was easy very
good such swordsmanship will serve you
well in the field oh wow can the same be
said of your
spellcraft the Flames of the Phoenix
burn within you yes they do now let them
burn
without Let It All Out Come CLI rain
fire down upon me
gladly land a fire spell five times
oh
easy oh we have to land it them
coming
easy now well done smaller smaller
Fireball you wield the Firebirds Flames
just as a first shield should you
flatter me my
Lord would you rather I flattened you
can't be arranged ask for that no let's
see if you can elude my blade after all
your attacking prowess will count for
not if you don't live long enough to use
it so true but I'm Phoenix I will live
forever on your toes Lord rossfield
there's something up there stay quick on
your
feet I want to
evade evading an attack at the precise
moment is delt will temporarily slow the
enemy making it more susceptible to
counter using this or that
okay oh to be so young and Fleet of
foot oh
okay try to evade my
attacks
oh easy
easy
good remember Clyde your blade is not
your only weapon mhm quickness of
thought and fleetness of foot are
indispensable arms in any Shield's
arsenals tongue twister but you are not
just any Shield are
you show me what set you apart from the
rest you have been blessed by the
Phoenix granted the use of its power H
Bliss call upon that power now to close
on
you okay well I'm waiting well I'm
waiting for the game to explain to
me close the gap
iconic Feats the blessing of the Phoenix
gr C the ability to perform Feats of
inhuman strength and dexterity Phoenix
shift is one such iconic feat oh it's
like a dash press Circle to swiftly
close in on a distant
Target
both
while
exec with it all our Shields could move
so swiftly
are you not blessed by the Phoenix then
prove it E I like
it but are we going to ever replace
these skills cuz we're using even the
most agile Shields can to escape every
blow and death may come by a handful of
cuts as easily as it comes by a
thousand there is only one way to ensure
that you do not
fall keep your wounds mended and your
energy enies
replenished uhhuh speaking of which my
Lord you seem a little worse for wear
what does that mean now that won't do at
all W what are you trying to
say men your wounds at
healing oh consumables consumable items
such as potions and tonics can be used
to restore Clive's HP or temporarily
boost attributes consumables can be
assigned to upright and down via the
items tab in the main menu for quick and
convenient use these items can will be
used directly from the menu I don't want
to use my potion now I want to hoard
them
forever what just smaller High potion or
or potion probably potion right do you
think those wounds become
you I I save them for f of
17 okay all right then all right
then a
foing okay I just wanted a little bit I
don't have to be fully healed battle is
a succession of pivotal moments wherein
life and death can be decided at a
single I don't want to use potions you
must be ready to utilize every tool at
your disposal if you are to navigate a
path to Victory or at the very least to
ensure that you live to fight another
day enough
practice it's time for the test you
recovered from your soaking I trust you
wouldn't want to kick a man while he's
drowned
is it like in like elen ring come then
Lord rosfield spar with me if you
believe yourself worthy to be called
Shield of the flame then prove it Clive
rosfield as you wish my Lord H cheeky
brat okay how that me boy make proof of
your
strength all right let's go let
go ah you don't have to teach me
anything the will gge indicates an
opponent's will to fight back oh break
their Spirit by Landing attacks and
strike them when they are
vulnerable o vulnerable AKA when the
will go is empty go on you're sure to
beat him this time you can do it C just
stay
come show me what you
got
ah oh Precision
Dodge nice
try you're taking this seriously keep
going
Clive yeah shift strike hey let's go
he's vulnerable take down he staggered
oh staggering your enemies oh he's got
no no Poise Lord Murdoch's will has been
broken leaving him Stager try dealing as
much damage as you can before he regains
his senses use
R2 and square to execute Rising Flames a
powerful iconic ability granted CLI by
the blessing of the Phoenix you're
welcome okay
R2
wow can how often can I do it
that it's time I took my own advice and
used all the tools at my
[Music]
disposal how long pressing just a little
more we believe in
you yay I don't like the lame bonking
sounds of My Sword I want the proper
sword and red go is cool down I didn't
see it I need to look at it
closer thank you thank you thank you
thank youy M I told you he could do
it who's the cute gray-haired girl
H where can I see her in the future
rested at last she's cute it's taken me
long
enough that was a display worthy of your
father you are a true Shield of the
flame and let no one tell you otherwise
okay no spoilers including
me what are you lping at back to your
drills so my father's probably dead I'm
assuming like every main character's
father and mother is
[Music]
dead why my hands so red oh it's a
glove it's not
oh maybe he's also a phoenix can't die
oh am I being
healed oh my broke
sure I was just tired the Phoenix's
Flames are a gift you mustn't waste them
it isn't a waste my Shields look after
me why shouldn't
I that's why cute you were coughing this
morning too coughing you shouldn't be
outdoors we'll be fine oh he's
don't push yourself
installed I started installing It 2
hours ago I thought it was already
done oh you're Grace please this is no
place for one such as you I would gladly
Brave hell itself to see my darling
boy gentlemen Rosaria thanks you for
your your indefatigable loyalty thank
you we live to
serve
Joshua you should not be out of doors we
have discussed this why does she talk
like this I'm sorry behind her
hand good day to you
mother h
josa stinky your father will be
expecting
us that was a that was a mean
look Lord
Murdoch Your
Grace bombastic side
eye oh
cute what a way to treat your own flesh
and blood I know it's not his fault not
everyone can be born the
Phoenix we should join
them pretty
pretty
[Laughter]
cute what I'm just saying she's pretty
I'm just thinking about the future with
[Music]
her CH
B
oh sir nice to meet
you I am under your
protection please protect
me
[Music]
CH rise my friends Rise Like a Phoenix
is that Daddy Home Father oh oh thank
you
Joshua you are well I trust yes Father
much better hot daddy jul and I went to
the Bailey to watch Clive's
Spa is that so
n girl chill too
young stop it boy not
now you'll make a fine Hound one
day
father lift up your head
girl thank you your
[Music]
grace the capital rejoices at your safe
return
Your
Grace war is coming my boy we must make
ready is the situation truly so grave
come to the throne room we will talk
there yes f f you're
[Music]
great that's not Shields dismissed
that's not
where a brist should go
butterfly it's a dead fist true oh no
where did they
go Clive here is off to see the arch
duuke
right
a What exploration
time sunrise sunset
mhm finding your way should you find
yourself lost do not fret hold down
elfrey mhm and Trust in your animal
instinct to point you in the right
direction my animal Instinct your
current destination will be displayed
with
uhhm is trouble Brewing
I'm not sure I need to speak with
father is that it I'm pressing it I
think it gives me a little
Rumble I guess the Phoenix Instinct I
don't know it's kind of weird to call
Phoenix an animal I mean I guess it is
but so what is this finding items ahuh I
have to hold it longer okay useful items
can be found Across The Realm by those
who know where to look items discovered
can be viewed in the item tab before the
potion I got it
back so this shows me where I need to go
when I'm lost well I'm obviously not
going
there obviously I mean
please I saw something shiny there I
want to get
it what why
can't my jump was
before give me the shiny
[Music]
thing up there too this one maybe I can
get wait that's not is that even an item
[Music]
oh
Apple if you have another Apple we can
make
a another fruit out of
it good is
near forgive me Lord marest pray to not
this bungling C bow to him you fo don't
I say to speak oh chill chill it's
[Music]
fine it was no trouble
really to not indulge him to be allowed
to stand in your lordship's presence is
more than his kind deserves why neither
the Empire nor the Republic treat their
bearers half so well you was lucky to be
born in your father's Dominion very
lucky as I remind him every
day can I move on stand
please
stun I trust his Good Fortune will
continue of course if that is your
lordship's wish oh oh
oh yeah don't be mean to hard remember
it is for the good of the duy that you
serve
[Music]
d as do we all my
Lord as do we
all come along now back to your
duties
yeah he's already got a pretty mature
[Music]
voice I guess that's
fine he looks oh what well how old is he
cute of course only the dog I only mean
the
dog
both M 15 mhm yeah that's what he looks
like actually nice good
well done in the character Design This
Is It lad time to put an end all right
they probably want me to go there but
now I'm not going
there I will go where I want to I really
don't like the camera I I shall change
it again d s provides a comprehensive
overview of C's current level status
abilities and
gear uh are we going to stay in this
timeline for a long
time you're late oh no
worries for sometime
okay y okay I guess I'll go where they
want me to go is there a sprinting
button or maybe I just can't Sprint at
the
moment wee
this is a long game I was told actually
well actually look like they're getting
ready for supper that other I think
someone's hungry FF games are much
longer and this is like on the shest
side oh we're getting to the
item
Y what I'm pressing the low
button
oh active time l
mhm thanks for telling me when I found
out already should have told me before I
find
out okay oh so there's like L about
these people specifically oh let's read
this one the mark appli to the cheek of
bearers oh across valy St identifying
them as something other than human
newborn babes are checked at Birth those
who are found to be bearers being
branded and taken into the custody of
the state rarely bearers evade this test
either because because their parents
hide them the testers are LAX in their
duties or their powers do not awaken
until later yet most do not remain
unbranded for
long he does indeed not have it right
now eh but don't they already treat me
special wheat harvests down I'm already
special though this war ends up dragging
on will starve best fill our bellies
while we can then eh do
you
just because I'm a
royal no but they were treating me
special you making out some peir we'll
be having a feast for the two of you
soon enough oh uh by the way I'm only
going to be doing uh main quests cuz I
was told that the side quests in this
game are not that worth it at least not
like if I'm streaming it and and and I
want to go through the cont content like
Saku Saku in a in a
good you know you know yeah
ooh nice and quiet in here isn't it
that's
beautiful there's more butterflies for
the
Dole oh no I can I can run through the
flowers wait what are you doing
W that I haven't seen that kind of magic
before only the red and the blue
one hi
Tim W it's so pretty oh my
God
[Music]
no that child is the future of our
nation he must be protect it she's not
talking about me H concerns are
insignificant she doesn't know I'm right
behind her listening to her excuse
me oh she just ignores my existence I
don't matter to
her
Joshua
Clive I are you worried about the
war the soldiers will expect the Phoenix
to help them but I don't know if I can
huh don't worry Joshua father will guide
you wait he's blessed also by the same
Phoenix will protect you
always I know thank you
Clive he is the Phoenix I thought I am
the
Phoenix
huh
huh he is the dominant oh I'm just
blessed by him should I notice
already
h
Huh so what was that in the intro okay
maybe don't tell me maybe all of this is
spoilers it's
implied just been well I mean I don't
know it's kind of confusing I thought I
was the
Phoenix some large Gates and stff I
maybe when he
dies the power goes to me I don't know
still
use extra access then I have to push
them
okay wow so
detailed when he well didn't he die in
the good
luck didn't my wasn't that my brother oh
no wasn't that my brother that like we
left behind under the stone in the first
intro scene thingy I don't
know that wasn't
him
ah I thought that was my brother didn't
you guys say that's my
brother I'm so
confused you commanded my presence Your
Grace how may I serve
you all right you can stop licking my
boots mother isn't here
H do the territories Fair any better a
brother in
arms most lie under a pole of
black in just these few moons the blight
has taken eye on all of the northern
reaches it is only a matter of time
before it crosses the
Border by the
Flames nearly every available bed in the
capital is already occupied by those
fleeing the
deadlands even if we were to send them
South to Port iselda more would only
follow in their
weake every day we delay brings us
closer to
disaster we must move
now against the iron
Kingdom feel like I'm playing
AE I must move now before the other get
stronger for too
long it is time to end
it at the very least we must secure
Drake's
breath without the blessing of the
mother Crystal we cannot defend our
realm from the spread of the blight
blessing thought the crystals were B the
iron blood will not relinquish it easily
this will be a bitter
fight we ride for Phoenix gate tomorrow
Phoenix gate not B words of our
ancestors as tradition
dictates I I to go with you with Joshua
Shield there is something anything else
I would have you do
first
Rodney you will have heard the reports
I'm sure of beastmen from the north
being cited within our borders goblins
in the still wind marshes I know of the
rumors yes then you know what must be
done I'll will give you two good
men while we ride North tomorrow you
will journey to stillwind search it and
clear he it then you will join us at
Phoenix
gate I love how phoenixes are so
important here I wonder how many
phoenixes they have in this world it is
time to prove in my world it's only one
and shut your mother up for good he get
me just the
one I will do my duty your
grace
that will be all rest well we ride at
dawn yes your
grace now hold wait I have a huge huge
sword now by the way not the wooden
sword
anymore oh fire
we should look
around I don't know where it's telling
me to oh it's telling me to go to my
Chambers I'll think about it let's see
can I enter any door
no items
doal where are my
items
also let's check this
[Music]
again let's read about about the mother
crystals the mother crystals enormous
glassy
mountains five of which
to is that one of the things that
dropped no is it Tower over the lands of
alista they are the source of all the
crystals that the people of the twins
rely on in their everyday lives not only
that but the lands surrounding them are
rich with uh ather making the Magics
with K the crystals cast even more
potent for these reasons great Nations
have sprung up around mother Crystal and
have long war with each other for
possession of Their
Blessings
so M crystal is not
bad oh also known in the local tongue as
heran the iron kingdom is an AR is an
archipelago Nation situated off the west
coast of storm uh with its capital at
Craig
Lo the monocrystal Drake's breath it has
a name called Drake's breath aha he just
mentioned that rises from a volcanic
island situated just within or without
its B borders depending on whom you ask
aha political issue and has been the
subject of long-standing conflict
between the iron blood and the
neighboring duy of
raria the iron Kingdom's inhabitants
shun any contact with Outsiders which
has given rise to Unique if largely
inward looking culture
not can I see those crystals from
here those just look like normal
mountains
[Music]
so they're all called Drake something
what why what's with
Drake
okay not from here
okay all right then we shall retire to
our
[Music]
chamber
H Drake is in a dragon oh
how long will you be away this
time not
long 4 days maybe
five and you will be taking Joshua I was
thinking I can't exactly leave him
behind artist can
I the blood of the Ros Fields runs in
his veins before going to war we perform
the right at Phoenix gate in it's our
way you know that and only the dominant
can enter the otry so yes I'm taking
Joshua oh to hell with your way the boy
is
ill you think I don't know
that but the boy is also the
Phoenix the heir to the
throne you can't keep him in swaddling
clothes all of his
life elwin don't worry Clive will watch
over
him though he is a youth of about 15
years he's already a fine Soldier he
will make a splendid
Shield you see more in him than the
Phoenix did he was rejected
elwin our household has no place for
such a failure he is worthless a man
like any other
wow okay I mean did I not come out of
her in between legs are the arch Duke of
Ros why do she treat me like this this
again why am I adopted you know as well
as I do that I only sit upon the throne
because my father was taken before his
time I am
merely warming the seat till Joshua
comes of
age you are your father's firstborn son
and you sit upon the
throne all is in its right
place unlike some you have not disgraced
our Noble
blood without men like Clive to keep us
safe your precious Noble blood would
long since have graced the
gutter we have an early start I'm going
to
sleep are you guys okay this is nothing
have you watched Game of
Thrones don't get excited about
this oh
pretty there's a red star this is it
then time to prove
yourself Wishing on a
Star red
star I'm a little old for
that I should get some
sleep
right is is it a phoenix
star or is it pimple a pimple of the
sky we got to pop it you're going with
them tomorrow aren't
you I am Joshua's
Shield I'm sworn to protect
him he takes too many risks the Moon is
recording I only wish I could save him
from himself you mean it's like a red
recording
do you're so funny I have another
mission
too father has given me my first
command well if you're not going to pray
to mea for your safe return I shall just
have to do it for
[Music]
you P
cry
he's
confused there's going to be another War
isn't
there since coming here I've begun to
take peace for
granted I assumed the war between our
nations would be the
[Music]
last but it never really ends does
it n never no
[Music]
the next war will be bigger than
before but you'll be all right won't you
Clive you're a shield of Rosaria after
all and blessed by the
Phoenix
H how do you bless
someone If He blesses me can he bless
everybody why not just bless
everybody it's getting
cold we should go
in bye
[Music]
lady good night
Clive
[Music]
kute you sneeze on
them is she promised to me or what what
what
so we're not going to talk about the Red
Dot
huh no just
friends what do you mean guys it's
normal in medieval times to have a s
osia cute girl promised to you and there
they don't even have a big age Gap he's
15 don't worry I'm sure you'll do
brilliantly I'll try it's crazy as
back
then good
luck it really isn't that crazy huh
to yeah many Nobles marry and very early
age anyway and often their ladies are
that areed to them we ride for Phoenix
gates are much younger than them may the
blessing of the crystals go with us and
shield
the
forever an old
story as Grace departs open the
gates open the gate t t t ch
ch how the chocob
balance doesn't really look like well
balanced body allow me too much weight
in the front hanging downwards thank you
legs too far
[Music]
behind that smile from the left guy
we're ready to depart my
Lord may I say what an honor it is to
serve alongside you
[Music]
is that cute R
investigation if there are goblins in
stillwind they won't leave
willingly the beastmen are a fierce foe
we underestimate them at our
Peril not today we
won't sir Wade sir Tyler let us do our
duty with pleasure my Lord as you
command to the marshes
then why is his head so small the
blessing of the crystals go with
us oh
cool that looks so cool world map
displays all the locations indicated by
glowing pins currently available to cly
for your fast travel
Co still
wind translates to still
wind in
German
wow it's just a coincidence that it's
the same in English I'm sure they wanted
it to be
German keep your eyes open for those
Goblins the reports place them in this
area wait yeah wait it still isn't
so yeah it might be more like mute else
quiet
[Music]
wind
yeah lost in a fog
lost in a frog frog feeling overwhelmed
try equipping one or more of the five
timely accessories for example why does
this feel like a a TV commercial like
the those those not a normal commercial
the ones where they try to sell you
something I guess wait they try to sell
you something in every commercial
basically I mean the the
the the ones with the phone
numbers uh for example the Ring of
timely strikes allows its wearer to
chain complex attack combos only using
Square the Ring of timely Focus slows
time before an incoming attack allowing
for an extended evasion window what all
the
time with all items
[Music]
time fine I'm fine not exactly the most
well-maintained path looks like Bal but
who do you imagine would maintain it
this is this is where the witch was with
the the people that we
killed testing the waters
literally
wow
water not wobbly
enough yeah water should be more
reactive to me moving around in it okay
well well fine I guess well it's hard to
believe that anyone used to live here
the old village of still wind is
ahead not that there's a lot left of
it
yeah I'm an expert with wobbly water you
know it what is this
item two
Gill and these butterflies can
I I want to get up there oh no no no I
want to go up maybe the butterflies were
telling me where where to
go
what
[Applause]
merlocks oh a
Golem
look
something kill us
enough you little
e let's kill him
e
disgusting they would look cute with
like if they were growing hair fur magic
vers us strike an opponent con magic
explosion okay like a
combo did that do
it wow okay
oh oh now now I
didn't easy I want to find more give me
more give me
more so the reports were true can I you
should press on there may be more
ahead
[Music]
no how do I get out of this like
fighting
window going back because of these
butterflies now they're gone but wasn't
there a path here too
no okay JN ni
checking that was on
[Music]
purpose oh there's another hole
there another hole in
there
[Music]
not can we fight some
more
it strength
tonic o another thing to hoard and never
use until the end of the
game welcome to or is that like
something that you use once and you get
your stats higher I don't
know or is this like a temporary thing
like during the battle you got to
use oh N Loot
okay what what there's so
[Music]
many
hey down with
you nice
okay I did want more yeah I'm getting
exactly what I asked
for Co this really reminds me of the
bers gate place with the
[Laughter]
[Music]
witch
potion potion
menion my R2 ability yeah thank you for
reminding me I was just thinking about
it actually that I will forget it in the
future I didn't forget it just
yet so you're welcome to remind me when
I really haven't used it for a long time
is this where I came
[Music]
from or is this where I just fought but
now I'm
lost this
way n Nar Nar interesting
oh oh oh we kick
it so every once in a while like before
it was a door opening motion now it's a
it's a kicking motion depending on what
I'm facing it will be different this
[Music]
there I really want to break them t
barel
t sorry that's an aier thing when we
played artier there were so many barrels
and the the character would always be
like T when they see a barrel hey
butterfly so are you actually telling me
where to go seems like
[Music]
it
oh I just jump down
huh no fall damage some of their number
of spell how I use again we'll all have
hands full
here but
okay hey you can use
magic new enemies approach oh from do oh
that one's almost dead
stop him somebody stop
him yeah wa nice angle too oh nice
[Music]
J I'm just think you epic
Wing okay so far I like the
[Music]
fighting beon
wait huh
[Music]
what a
x I'm used to Nintendo
[Music]
controllers oh use my potion automatic
well okay in this case I accept it cuz
it didn't make me do it
myself and I needed healing anyway I
think we should be nearing the Old
Village
Square it might not be a nest of
goblins I see it is very true I cannot
hold the potions very very
sad that is going to be a problem cuz if
the maximum is four
I honestly don't think that's very
much can we make the maximum bigger
[Music]
sometime we're trapped oh okay I can
increase the capacity I'm working on
it he's the
leader he has a a cute
hat but we'll have to take care of his
followers
first to show how important he is care
to thin the herd as if you have to ask
what did you see that
DOD
nice here let me help you
oh can we make it in time how far does
the death go well now I know are they
done and then there was one
oh yeah come down here oh more more
uh he's invited a
friend does he have relationship with
big thing here it comes oh the legs are
like so
froggy formid theable fo large enemies
must be fa with caution they have far
more HP sure use the blessing of the
Phoenix to not
only
okay founder that's a swing and a half
be ready to move when it winds up for
another can't have to tell me twice
hey
yeah oh hey I was I was
[Music]
dodging these
idiots I forgot I can spam these n oh we
partially staggered him enemies will
become partially staggered when their
will glasses reduced to 50% creating
short
opening
okay here let me drink a
PO so
op
there we go dagger okay halfway
down hitting them while they're down
yeah I'm sure that does more damage okay
150 okay cool hav we already kind of
learned that thank you
[Music]
though dagger damage 1,000
oh did I just
Parry she
was okay
oh I stopped
him I just ran into that I thought he
was
done
okay Oh you's almost dead
oh he's doing that thing
again going toward me nice try yeah I
didn't Parry this time okay but I did
something in between
[Music]
stagger and finish him with can I do it
yes
nicely timed gigos
slain
Yahoo level up is that my oh not my
first I'm level six now but did I start
off of level
five o oh there's a stagger
stat Vitality
Willow ahuh battle rewards following
important batt of
[Music]
okay hard lever armlets can I wa
oh good job guys
Yay good job good fight very very fun
wait he's still alive come back and
fight you
coward after him before he summons the
rest no well first I have to pick up the
the item gear can significantly improve
player attributes but only when equipped
with the via the gear tab in the main
menu learned Master abilities tab in the
main menu mastering existing abilities
as well as learning new ones requires
ability points okay so should I do that
now uh
attributes right so can I use wait I can
I can here do something right how do I
how do I choose
it do I have to go to
items
sh whereit
what a gear
okay using
this uh okay and then nothing here right
oh I do have some things
[Music]
here should we wear one of these
ah I don't know maybe this oh it's easy
mode okay
wait yeah I don't really need
it abilities my eyes are so tired maybe
I should drink my energy
drink this whole time I've been feeling
tired smoothie by the way let me sleep
more or less I didn't have to get up too
early for her she did try to wake me up
a few times but she gave up quickly so
that's pretty
good but I still woke up earlier than I
wanted to so I didn't get full
sleep ability points can be spent in the
abilities tab to acquire new abilities
as well as upgrade existing ones if
you're unsatisfied with Clive's current
build reset all abilities and try again
as there is no penalty for doing
so details of each ability and feet can
be viewed by selecting its
icon
uhuh damage breaking
Target okay what how does this
work are these the ones I
have looks like it this these ones I can
learn and these these ones are still
locked H this is like a yeah the Phoenix
shift and the rising
Flames get launch okay let me look at
what else we have
stump while in the you have to use this
while in the air use R1 to recover
immediately after being knocked back
o
taunting burning blade
oh mhm
why the air to slice down well I guess
I'll go with this but uh x x and
square I don't know if I'll really
remember all these things I'll just like
try button matching and hope something
nice comes out of
it oh no how do I there we
go oh it can Master things
too oh but it's kind of expensive
H oh wait they're
cheap you remember the more you play
okay then let's not use it all up right
away cuz that let's try to learn it one
by one maybe that would be
smart Okay so X and square to swiftly
close in and attack a distant enemy okay
okay X
square like this but not really right
now but in battle you're lovely in your
armor fight well thank
you D should oh another
[Music]
potion there he is oh
oh let's fight I need to test out my new
skill a he's he's baiting me damn it is
he moderately
smart cuz I'm getting that impression
are my friends behind
me why did you bring me here
H you have another
trump
card sleep end
now this ends
now of course he does I see it
see he does not have SLE maybe it's his
hat
oh wait this is like that
Pokemon small small
Pokmon squishy
[Music]
one keep clear of its more my Lord that
thing's breath is worse than its
fight
[Music]
wait I tried to use that for the what
One X and then
[Music]
Square oh wait I guessing I can't step
on
[Music]
that that reeks I said stay away from it
now disappear now the the the stuff nice
[Music]
try come
on I wish my Dodge was a little bit
[Music]
bigger
oh y stinky breath again oh
no so
stinky oh
dagger guys are you doing something or
am I the only one there we go I was
waiting for you
hey in other FF games that's no joke
really where's it going oh yeah good
question guess is as good as
mine
oh ah it's sucking me no hey
hello I don't want to be inside you
thank you w he no
cinematic strike when the screen flashes
blue like this during a pyal moment in
battle press square Before Time Runs Out
only once or like a million times to
deliver the de devastating blow
okay okay just
one go go go go can I stay up on him
no M now before it
recovers
[Music]
yeah hey D these dudes are barely doing
anything she has a lot of HP holy
I'm surprised that right in the
beginning of the game we're already
facing with like they're not difficult
but like longl
lasting enemies oh
stinky
I don't quite I don't know if I'm doing
it completely wrong but the combos don't
feel so good because there's not much
[Music]
combo that's just more ball
okay yeah just damage SP oh hey I did it
I did the thing oh I did
something ouch this should help
I used both I think by
accident yeah I don't have a lot of
[Music]
ability
hey
I par that little
bastard and I staggered
[Music]
him hey that was bigger than
expected man my my fump is getting kind
of
tired
stop don't you think it coming by now
even I like in many other games like I'm
really bad at like
remembering or like
guessing um you know like the
patterns cinematic thing coming again I
cannot fall
here yeah I know a cinematic evasion but
this one's so easy this one's so like
obvious and simple and gives me so much
time to move away before he does
something wow when the screen flashes
red like this during a press R1 okay so
normal normal evading Buton then okay
now for the final push my
[Music]
Lord
field don't
beol oh yeah I'm sure it can get more
difficult
not as easy as it looks oh it's raing
made it Angry I made made it
Angry you're trying to save
us so
many and now it's just
[Music]
spamming oh is it going down again no
I right then wow okay
chill
[Music]
H sometimes I don't understand why it's
not
working but it works okay he staggered
to go go
go kill him
please not the rage again oh no
[Music]
Go Go
Power ah maybe first part to
then
[Music]
oh
ah sorry I'm a bit stupid right now
because the battle is just to
out there we
go more ball
slain two things slain
already level
up wow then we just level up in the
previous fight it's going
fast
no
spils I guess I don't know what he he
would have given me maybe a
tooth and I can give it to the Tooth
Fairy I don't
know my Lord something thanks thanks
mate I never thought I'd see it kind to
learn to dodge I've been dodging all the
time area but more balls too I'll
petition his grace to send a detachment
if we don't stop them here they'll be at
our gates before long Elden ring
PTSD we should get moving we don't want
to be caught out here after dark if we
set off now we can still
me it's coming back to
me
a oh my God
please save me please please just don't
do this to
me oh we're moving on to the same the
next
[Music]
uh
location that's
position no Dodge only attack
oh sometime later it's suddenly very
vague Phoenix
G suddenly thousands of red
eyes no wait till you hear this wait
till you hear this his lordship draws
his
sword the goblin Chief runs off
screaming straight down a Mor's
[Applause]
[Music]
gun Mor more tail drink and be merry
boys good work on the tomorrow
gratifying to see your student making
such a name for
[Applause]
[Music]
himself young Lord has a
f wait what no was it just the the
shininess from being it looked like he
had a foam mustach to me wait does he
get one or is it just shiny from being
wet he
did oh
carrots
nin I love
[Applause]
[Music]
carrots w
[Applause]
are you that's me that's me being
surrounded by drunkards just a little
tired well it has been a long
day they all like Clive don't they oh
they like you
too but he's mingling so they're
tingling we're all very proud of
him
father why is it that the dominance is
always born into our family good
question doesn't seem
fair you want to help your enemy
instead we cannot live without the
blessing of the crystals and the
crystals work their magic through US
H you have been blessed Joshua blessed
to be a dominant to wield the power of
an icon icon our family has been chosen
to share that power with the
people what so that is what we must
[Music]
do from the
Shadows
[Music]
[Applause]
Ro my wings my
wings how many times has Calli made a
reference to me when she played this
game louder my friends louder there must
have been so many moments that were
calling for
it so
much a few a lot a lot
constantly can you make me a compilation
please cow car
[Music]
please I want to see a
compilation oh
Ki kiaha Oh yeah and kiaha oh Phoenix ah
yeah
kiaha oh that's
wa poor Jill she'll be wondering where
you've got
to
so much for you being a fine
Hound so this is where you've been I'm
going to go to the fridge and get my
energy drink cuz I'm weirdly tired today
because I did not get my daily
nap
BRB so the drink is finally being used
okay don't worry I'll only take like
small small
Sipes it's just like I've been noticing
since we started it's been really tough
for me m
to like take it in and and not be tired
just really tired okay this has been in
my fridge for h a month maybe just
waiting to be drunken in an emergency
how am I more tired now than I was after
4 hours of sleep playing AOE tournament
uh huh
how it's a Red Bull apricot Edition
it's apricot
strawberry Red Bull sponsor me I'm
literally in in the country of your
headquarters actually that's so true let
me WR to
JMA you know
how Red Bull sponsored aquan and Bon
right and put on sampai
before can we get them to sponsor me
because I am
literally in their
country and I drink Red Bulls sometimes
too you don't play any games compe oh do
you have to do that I mean I feel like
Red Bull sponsors anything in Austria
really anything they're like if anything
needs to be sponsored red bull is on the
list to be
[Music]
honest yeah red bull fight FL they give
wings I don't need Wings cuz I already
have wings wait what's this active time
Laura let let me see uh just the same
thing but I can like look at it in
between not hold okay so back to the
story I guess
you well maybe I shall drink it more
often I drink drink it
responsibly if I play 10ed snowboarding
snore
snor
hiding maybe what are you doing out here
I didn't see you at the
feast feasts are the only time Shields
are allowed to take their ease
and I've never really been one for cakes
nail it's the vegetables I don't
like
the baby dog go so
[Music]
cute I hear you slew a mble no I didn't
all the men were singing your Praises
you so cute didn't be used
to when I joined the ranks everyone
thought I was a spoiled little
lordling if I didn't know how to handle
a sword I'd be a laughing stock the
archduke's firstborn
failure you're the one they really
believe
in I'm
jealous that's not true they don't
believe in me they believe in the power
of the
dominant my brother the
Phoenix ruler over life and death
smaller smaller isn't fair it should
have been you
a I don't have what it takes to lead our
people I don't have the
strength but you
do
cute every man has his
duty ours was decided long ago when our
ancestors chose to instate the dominant
as the arch Duke of rer
all to ensure that whenever our nation
stood on a precipice the Phoenix would
rise from the Flames to drag us back
from the
brink it's the same story that the fate
of dominant shoulders when I was a small
small Phoenix it is your duty to bear
that
burden what about
you I was born to be your
Shield that is why I was given in the
Phoenix's blessing to keep our future
ruler safe No Matter
What H however hard it
gets I'll never let you
down thank you Clive I know you'll
always take care of
[Music]
me how are you before I can do that you
need to take care of
yourself all right
[Music]
I should go inside it's past my
bedtime good night
too so many flags
yeah
tense
is a river in
Germany
almost supplies from the
capital don't let them
in n there's no way that this is good
stuff not with this
bgm don't you hear this you took your
time sampling the wearers were you don't
I hear
it that also gave it
away they don't hear the BTM it's a good
job the north is full of enterprising
Traders Keen to keep us in wine SP bar
the did he keep on talking while his fro
was slipp
that was the other one
oh sounded so
close Gateway secured Captain we proceed
as
planned
[Music]
n oh
are you going to abduct
him or kill him right
[Music]
away little
bro Phoenix
child
is
that same way as his
mommy friend or fall forgive me my
prince it's me Wade you probably don't
remember me I remember what is it we're
under attack I don't know who they are
but they've set light to half the castle
I must get you to safety your highness
very well well if it's just light as
long as it's not
fire Follow Me Your
Highness oh I'm playing him Flight of
the
fledgling oh
cool I got my own Lantern above my
head let's go it's kind of hard to see
are the enemy already inside the castle
I'm afraid so your highness we must
hurry
cool can he go faster than this probably
only when he's further
away
yeah slows me down when I'm too
close what was that it was a pain scream
I have to help
them everything's on fire well fall back
your highness he's not one of us okay uh
way of fighting I guess oh got a bit
closer
wa who's next
strong I saw them at the
feast they were
laughing
this is SRA
quab but why would the
Empire we must find my
father
no but I have a bad
feeling we fight you guys too
yeah wa
oh oh he needs so much time to recover
though damn it the bastards are
everywhere why would the Empire do this
there are
[Music]
allies
maybe maybe they were never our allies
maybe it was
all
fake oh
I have the Domin how dare
you while you can what's
kaga need to try that one out maybe or
maybe it cures
people curing myself maybe oopsy
sorry ahuh it is a healing spell who
would have
thought
Tyler super massive
damn it his wounds are deep no
ohaaa your
highness trust
me I'll save you don't worry you're
going to be all right
a quicker my God them
[Music]
off come
on do I play him now or what bro so many
Bros C Joshua come here it's
me Tyler you're hurt did I not finished
my kuraga
survive Thanks To His Highness
useless Your Grace Lord Murdoch works
better in battle I
guess you rescued the Young
Prince well done
Sade promotion I'm in your debt Soldier
mhm thank you you're gra so now that our
daddy is here certainly nothing will
go we cannot stay here we should make
straight for the rear
gate nothing will go wrong
right our daddy
yeah uhoh uhoh no music is also a bad
sign oh not Turtle uh
owl
I feel like the name Turtle lost Alan
could have been given to an
owl May the winds speed you to
rosali
uh-oh the north Gate's up ahead there
are chocobos in The Stables chocobos
father take Joshua and get to safety
choco I'm not going without you you're
supposed to be my shield
remember oh yeah it would probably be
good to stay with him which is why I'm
going to hold the TW I did tweet yes I
scheduled it I will order our remaining
forces to rally at the gate now
go little merch reminder cuz it's uh two
more days before my limited uh before my
you must do your duty too three years
Anniversary merchandise is going to go
off
sale I I
know and those
pictures you have to keep father safe
are a couple of the few last counting on
you yo pictures before now I guess yeah
he's probably already done with
it yeah before he retires from taking
pictures being our
model yeah the bag you like it I tried
to keep it still like very hard to say
what was the word for something that's
not too Stand
Out subtle yeah
oh call
my back
to our not yet Phoenix
boy
K the hey my potions
are back up did I really collect so many
potions I don't think
so not fall to the likes of
you did somebody
shoot something
shooting good
stuff smooth battle everyone's dead it
resets
chapter
what where is the
door thank
you thank you damn it
all
ah oh
oh oh wow that is
[Music]
brutal blood
Captain yeah Red Bull already
working I wish they had like tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny uh Red Bulls they're like
just for like free sipp cuz that's
already enough for me man let none
Escape as you command
you take care of so effective on me I'll
keep the others occup wait I want to I
want to go
to
astrologer
oh nice
music oh sudden it ends so sudden that's
them done are you all right
it's my father and Joshua I'm worried
about we should head
back
oh
[Music]
oh H look
out somehow he doesn't give me an evil
Vibe he just gives me an epic hero Vibe
may I have this dance Knight of the
blinding ton and you are the shield who
was blessed by the Phoenix okay The
Voice is pretty save
youan one that's
s do you like my prision gods now huh
and now do you like it now there're
still Gods too much
[Music]
huh
okay see I can do it sometimes okay not
quite y b this dude is your B will
somebody come to help me this doesn't
seem like a normal fight oh my God
okay this not a normal fight right it's
just one of those fights oh
[Music]
boy wait wait wait wa wait
want come
[Music]
on stay still
damiel
y mus
[Music]
call my hands hurt it's so
tense
this
[Music]
one
oh oh
okay hey he's open can we do something
special yes
[Music]
now K how about
it you're going to regret that boy
please be nice to
me what the why why do it take so
long that's
s this Dan is
over quite precise Mrs
takiki not
[Music]
quite
yeah okay it was a double
[Music]
jump my my fingers my
arms
oh let's go let's go it looks so
difficult in the
[Music]
beginning you know some RPG games they
just have this thing where um they're
are certain fights against like really
important enemies that especially later
in the
game you'll have to take down but they
introduced them to you like really early
in the game to show you how strong they
are that not strong enough for them now
just to make an example of that they're
like not giving you a realistic chance
to win so that's what I thought that was
for a
[Music]
moment
to oh my underarms hurt so much my lower
arms
yeah doing great thank you level up
again oh fight gives me a level
up noodle arms getting stronger day by
day
[Music]
it's
okay so who is behind a mask I want to
take off the
helmet are you
hurt I'm
fine
so they sent in the drons Imperial
vipers do they really mean to invade
us not yet their numbers were too few
they were not here to take the
castle they were here to take heads
mhm our work is done we should return to
my father my Lord look
we issued these sashes but yesterday in
Ros if they were already Among Us what
if there were others I'm father and
joshu are in danger we must hurry take
your
Steed my Steed can we call CH steeds
what is
that that's a woman did she just say
you
it's just a
wind
hu don't oh
goodness
did that sound good your grace is
everyone
safe we ride for roosth to Rally our
forces I will need your help to see
Joshua safely back to the
capital on you Joshua I I hold I held
the
microphone you know the way I do it when
I whisper to you guys and sneezed right
onto it father giving it a more intimate
sneeze of sorry your grace but that
won't be possible oh
oh no the turtle you honor the
snakes stay back I'm warning you run J
run no I'm warning
you
oh oh
no
your
highness
run oh you must do your duty
too use Phoenix
magic become as Phoenix I have
to I had
to do
it it's already too late but
unless you use your super super healing
spell but you I'm counting on you
weren't good on that
before W
pretty
puy oh let's
go
yes yes yeah mhm
m
Phoenix is that I wonder if that's the
first time he is unleashing that wow
Spanky
spank oh there he
goes fully
transformed the Phoenix
yeah
Joshua maybe now he's stuck in that form
Joshua stop
this why is the sound
so muted he's lost
control I have to do something I have to
save him no my Lord fall
back benen Mark do you really think
that's a CO
dun it's just typical Phoenix colors I
mean depends on some cultures some
people depict them differently but
mostly it's just typical Phoenix
thank you girl you saved my life and I
am truly indeed a
phoenix get her on a f and
run
please yeah now you see what happens if
I were to take off my belt PUK Papa has
always been trying to protect us from
this not
now maybe he was right to do so his
shield do your duty he's also
like becoming
weird shave him shave him oh those
feathers are beautiful don't shave
them who the is that in the name of
it's like a like a Marvel movie
[Music]
now
wait am I becoming this right now cly
wait were we fighting
fire that's impossible no h how
[Music]
what that's what we were like in the
beginning but I
thought
what I was fighting my
but no I I was the Phoenix in that
scene who I'm you bro who are
you he me
Lord You're
Ready leave me
alone
[Music]
the bars stay away from me yeah that
kill you am I am I him now oh embodying
the Phoenix the following commands are
available when playing as the Phoenix
fire aim
evade
and we did this
before L1 K you
[Music]
ion no wait I
actually oh a l not not L uh one
actually L I'll kill you this seems
easier I think it had a
auto ah
it certainly had auto aim last time
oh this kind a
be oh yeah I've seen this
before I barely did any
[Music]
damage there is only one icon of
fire didn't you say it would be fair you
know kind to we that the icon of ion is
always the dominance is always in our
family maybe it's good to have two I in
fire you
understand take
it he's destroying it's not clim yeah I
think I understood that by now holy
can I
die
he's
coming probably doing soon oh no
no epic
music you break the castle down and then
with
it oh my God where did he
go I forgot what the aponer was we have
to stop
him
I have to save
them
oh now our HP is pretty much the
same and he can't fly he's got to jump
from Tower to Tower what if we get rid
of all the towers yeah what you going to
do what you going to do R1 R1 i1
i1 didn't really have to do that
I'm over
reacting but I'm in the group I'm in the
gr yeah my producing
Dodge oh he's fast he's a fast
[Music]
bullet you dodging through that I don't
know if I have to but I'm doing this
no no no no do I have to
I okay that was close I made a promise
to my
brother
no and I mean to PE it hell
yeah
uh okay I will do my
duty in a very British way thanks for
the membership welcome Awakening it's
[Music]
Awakening what do you mean that's
literally
me joshu is just voicing it but since
he's not a real Phoenix they had me do
all the Phoenix
Parts but
yeah I can't really take credit for it
because they won't there's an NBA
world where where is
he just did we
going I'm just a stunt double
basically damnation
who can
I did I do it that was so close for a
moment I I tried to shoot the the top
thing
what I
lost you guys are saying I did it but it
doesn't doesn't really look like I did
it my Str May Slicker but they shall
never die I just
rebirth it actually didn't well I even
for a moment aimed at the damnation
thing instead of him cuz I wanted to see
if I should shoot
that but I did penix never time
baby can't get me
down
overpowered so his damnation worked but
I still hey could I have died like for
real for
real Phoenix doing Phoenix things just
just the usual I could have that that
was really close though I swear it was
like one shot
less out of those 50 shots I did in 3
seconds that's really how it
felt both call and Ena failed I didn't
even give it my all cuz as I said I was
like not aiming at him
for one and a half seconds
maybe do you have to do the whole thing
again when you lose like the
whole following him through the
pharmacy
wa that That's What I Call Eternal
damnation there is a checkpoint
okay okay
but who was that Marvel
guy Iron
Man
hey no no you already down you have to
resign um E I thought I won
thanks for the
[Music]
gift no fu stop
it take your hands off my
brother so
stupid I was
winning Joshua stop it he wants fried
chicken
I swear you go to
KFC
please
please stop
it
oh oh oh
oh but you would think that I can't
really
die oh my
God
murderer I'll kill you
I'll kill
you so but that was basically still the
same scene right the fight that we just
did in the
beginning
okay please
we have come full circle
[Music]
yeah quite a mess that monster made what
about reir damn shame about the Phoenix
but can't be
helped oh my condolences Your Grace is
there ought we can
do haven't you done enough
Captain Joshua was my
world and now he is
gone I can only pray there will be a
place for me in the world his Radiance
seeks to
create I
see your grace over
here the rubble must have protected him
from the worst of the Flames shall we
take him prisoner no need for that kill
him
oh you can't cuz I'm now the Phoenix as
my husband never tired of telling me he
is a fine Soldier
I'm sure he would make an excellent
addition to the Imperial front line H
front line all right all in its right
place
hey chin up
lad you're going to be a soldier
yeah
Joshua oh that's what that is in the
logo I didn't look at it so
closely now it makes sense oh and now
we're in the current present time 14
years
later but they didn't explain the
mark welcome
back sorry what's our
situation let's just say shiver and
titans's little spat hasn't made things
any easier he's aged well
no but he's too
handsome it's
intimidating and it's as you thought the
Crusaders have sounded The
Retreat this guy needs to get rid of his
mustache we're down a man
sergeant if we return without shiva's
head Our Fate will be no different from
Beasts I'll take my chances with the
iron blood at least then I might die
fighting Shadow
bringer why because he looks like one of
the characters there or after you do
that
is I'll get a handsomer companion not
today then it's settled no dying now if
you don't mind we have an army to to
chase they all look fine but they
look so
plastic a new iconic abilities the
iconic ability Scarlet cyclone and
Heatwave for the Phoenix are now
available for acquisition and upgrade on
the ability stab in the main menu do not
forget that once acquired the new new
abilities must be equipped on gear and
icon okay do I need to do that how do
they expect us to kill something that
can do this they don't don't only the
girl holding its
leash do I have to do
it that looks I don't
know I don't understand this menu
yet oh wait so first when I press R2 and
then this uh Square I got Rising Flames
but if I do R2 and triangle I get
Scarlet
Cyclone cool
okay buy the other
move
Heatwave a projectile dispelling wall of
liquid flame before launching several
deadly shock
waves so what it's a it's a a block and
then I shoot some back
okay and then how does
it how does it go how can
I how
what how
how how can I only have two at
once
oh
okay I don't know if I would prefer that
over Rising Flames but I'll try to get
get good at
it so wait Scarlet Cyclone is just um I
have to be close for this but this is
more like distance and blocking
something when something comes at
[Music]
me sounds difficult to master
yeah was Square for
the for the blocking one square looks
like a wall so I think I can remember
that
H the game is like telling me right that
I'm the Phoenix now but you'll be hell
finding a way out do you think Army and
their dominant will fa any better the
moment in the story where he finds
out I'm not well of course I am I am
def I'm still just blessed by it am I
really I feel like I
[Music]
am by the
Flames but this is the the the mother
crystals right oh or is it did I
understand that
correctly these sparkly nice
crystals wait this
way is that just
ice oh she must
pee
uh
okay well they look nice
[Music]
did you hear that down
there can we free them so Titan has
knocked the fight out of our iron blood
friends where are the rest of them the
way he scooches in I can't be the main
host
wait is
that same hair color as my w fortunes
have turned sergeant it's her dominant
are you certain dominant the crystalline
Orthodox is a backwards faith for a
backwards people in the iron Kingdom
they teach that dominants are unclean
aberration born of blackest sin only
their priests are allowed to perform the
rights of priming and I see
many we end this
quickly
wait she
she
in s I'm so confused we'll find
out you can show her face now I know who
she is
yeah
please she does look like she could turn
into Shiva wait what did he just say
before priming the
girl
Shea for real for real what
elvation sha what why who is
Shiva has she always
been to Prim
end hey this care to kill some iron
blood
gladly we're not fighting you focus on
the target her are
we a it a it it
it does he not recognize her if even I
recognize her I mean okay I guess for
him it's been maybe 1 years and for me
it's been a few
minutes oh wait I want to try to attack
do that
again oh that wasn't the same attack oh
wait ah no do it again do it
again oh now I can't do
it whatever uhoh oh I shouldn't be
around she's
strong a wait girl recognize me come on
come on what my wife for
life
did that counter at the right
time you can spam
those in with a
DI a goodby I need to get used to
my new
[Music]
attack
tired W
man much
appreciated she's so cool I love her is
she going to be in my
[Music]
te
help too
thank you for the
red
oh let's go here we
go I don't want to hurt her she's too
cute
and she was being like kep prisoner by
them why does she not why does she
attack
[Music]
me oh I
very
[Music]
luing
I pared
again I
again no more orders
sergeant stoping and
move calm down white
icons icon she's not even fully
primed
true to
oh thanks for coming closer to me I see
you have a craving for me that just
comes naturally don't you think there's
something interesting about
that you think maybe we have some
special
history think about it for a second
while you're being
staggered by my sword
I will not have their blood on my
hands
oh you don't have
to leave
me I would love to
honestly but I also want you in my
team do they have different
yeah
uh oh did I do it at the right timing
again it felt kind of early but I just
realized I have different um what's the
word re re re
re re re
[Music]
re you know what I
mean
nah that was too early for
sure at lost y see defeated no but not
slain just defeated yeah different
like if I I activate one doesn't mean
that I have to wait for the other one to
refill as
well we got a frozen
tier yeah the last half was good right
once I got into the groove of using the
new attacks
too
now realize it maybe
now don't you she dead notice something
well come on what are you waiting
for
[Music]
a no no
that's not you not
here I'll bloody do it then no no no no
no
no oh oh
holy
whoa
y we've got company
wyv what the hell are you doing
Lord get your ass over here and help me
with these bastards
domination
abdomen I'm sorry
Jill you think she's dead don't worry
she's
not would have been more
dramatic we need her for the
story what is wrong with you
Wy the
dominant I know
her know
her look around you a nice AOE
actually good to when surrounded by many
people well but even my normal hits are
quite big AOE with that big range of my
sword what how did I do that
D now the D's
done I won't ask you again
wyv take her head so we can be done with
this no I'd rather take
[Music]
yours I can't I finishing move automatic
if they're knocked down who you would
betray the holy Empire I love anything
that's all Tre I don't recall ever
pledging allegiance to your Emperor my
service have been bought with this brand
but not my loyalty oh am I like still in
the same fight to survive of the one
that I was I don't at the end of my
years ago if we return
into so if you won't take us to
take I told you Sergeant
surprised and neither is she done with
himself let's find
out
[Music]
St do it again do it
again
oh
I don't know the timing is really
[Music]
difficult but somehow it
works still staggered yeah oh oh
Wy W have you forgotten who plucked you
from the front lines who drained you who
gave you a name when you had
enough you speak as if we don't bear the
same brand son
I've always had a name and I've not
forgotten it rushing at the same like
torn blanket then you will die what
precis counter shot years
ago that was a long long attack that
there
[Music]
I love spamming this no this
time for nothing no one oh and I will
not fall all by your
hand oh no no no three times he kind of
like moves three times when he does
that but it's not even worth remembering
his moves cuz I would probably behead
him after
[Music]
this go
ahead one two and three there we
go s
[Music]
kind I have nothing nothing to
you she dodged
[Music]
it traitor's bra in the end it's just a
SM SM
missile a bastard all these different
words to describe to kill
someone we just bested him level 11
level 11 level 11 level 11 level level
11 level 11 level level 11 level level
11 level 11 level 11 lelel level 11 say
level 11 11 times level 11 11 times
level
sorry I got
stuck level 11 level 11 11 * level 11 11
times 11 times 11 11 times 11
hey
oh I've got the
power has nothing to do with the Red
Bull no no wait this this is a thunder
Power it's different from what we have
must be someone else
right cuz I have fire she has ice this
is
funder or can we do
this
oh nice music it's um deserty M no okay
you I would have liked the Thunder Doo
this way
okay he's hot
oh bloody
wind well come on
[Music]
then
oh she looks like Bayonetta Hugo dear my
proud desert
life with I had taken care when chasing
the
hair I expected more from the mighty
Titan you put the ice queen on her back
No
Doubt but you'll have to work harder if
you're to claim this
PR my lady the
Thunder we'll be hearing more soon
enough
huh always were snakes
sit gather the men we have work to do I
mean cuz there's just so many special
characters and the coolest ones that are
super super strong and cool they come to
me but the others are also very special
like I don't know the way they have so
many special special things about them
you know I'll just shut I'll I'll I'll
shut up
chill is it really
you
Jill hello wake
up D have I not seen him for a long time
either and who's this fine Hound I see
before a fine Hound who saved your life
he must be really old now 13
years
to hi his name is
toal
acquainted well then you won't mind
taking him off my hands his voice sounds
familiar funny I'd always pictured you
as more the choco ball type it's
actually Clive rosfield maybe a little
bit
uh come now Fleet as flame Fierce as a
wildfire that there was the blessing of
the Phoenix I'm not sure if it fits him
I'd heard rumors that you'd survived ah
he voiced the I never played the much
and Game of
Thrones who was he in Game of
Thrones calm down I didn't come all this
way for your handsome mug now her on the
other hand she seemed worth muddying my
boots
for he's everywhere
okay yeah he sounds older and I don't
know bigger than the character looks
like none the worst for where still
might be best to get a second opinion
wait that sounds so weird I can't help
it back her
up great voice great design but not
match not step I mean
it it freaks me out well I'm not about
to leave her here not one with a warm
bed
waiting it's all right
oh wait he's like
holdor you're welcome to join us you do
want to help with are
you Sid if we aren't back soon n will
love our Reds that is such a holdor
character oh my
God I'll explain everything once for
back of the Hideway come on just a big
dude to carry someone a big nice
dorky dudes to carry
someone well we have a crew now I'm so
confused I need to relisten to that
dialogue cuz I was so confused about the
voice uh all right
let's go to the
Hideway you think it'll grow on
me will
it even this map looks like go yeah did
they did they take some inspiration from
Game of Thrones to make this this
game
oh wait are is this a mother
Crystal and
this and this now I get it and
this and this they did did they say they
did the producer had everyone watch Game
of Thrones while they made it no
way they
what okay like I was like getting Game
of Thrones Vibes this whole time not
hold on maybe that's why people say it's
so different from I like this
hole from other game of thrones
games final f
games there's we of time references too
for real for real for real for
real for real for
[Music]
real
Minecraft fantas game
of I am excited about this
similarity and that was obviously
inspired by holdor how much further now
cannot deny it in the middle of the
deadlands Keen ey you the BL suck this
place dry meaning no trees no birds and
no magic but it also means no
neighbors the last place anyone would
think to look they had to watch the the
ring you guys are saying this as if it's
like such a
chore they better have enjoyed
it for Meo excuse
me how dare you say
that but did they have to read any books
or did they only watch these things
because
because I always get
criticized for not reading the books and
it doesn't sound like they
did it's just faster to just watch the
the video versions did they also get
inspired by bers gate because this may
have come out uh oh what that
thing before bers gate but this looks
like another place I saw in bers gate we
didn't think they'd mind and it keeps
the black from our lungs but how do you
survive without
magic how as anyone hard work she had a
mark too you must be starving they all
have Mark we grow them here believe it
or
not show
yourself you're
back ah you no you're back and this is
the dominant how cold since we found her
I was hoping you might give her a look
over all right gos get her upstairs I
was just joking about B I know it
couldn't I've taken care of her fee all
of it she's the best healer this side of
the belt you've nothing to worry
about go have a look around I'll be in
my
Sol I see okay maybe that was a
chance hide hide
away pressing that opens a detailed map
of your current area
[Music]
okay new place to check out o
oh oh what a what a cool place still
hungry are you you're still hungry are
you might have might have somewhat wrong
to ear
what Surly
Smith there washing stuff here I
guess
no the washroom floor is all mened then
it will hold for now get a shirt I
suppose I'll be needing a new sword then
you'll need to speak with Black
Thorn I want to talk to him cuz his
voice sounded familiar to me
[Music]
chicken what came first the Phoenix
ordered
chicken can I get into the water no let
me into the water it looks so nice looks
so seethrough I want to go dive oh
trees what do you call these things I've
seen them before Oh my God is that an
orange on your head
Sid once told me the blight doesn't kill
the land it only makes her forget who
she once was she'll eventually remember
her purpose all she needs is a little
reminding I didn't mean that's a flying
thing that's a mle okay okay okay those
are trees
W no it's a
mle leave me be it's like a hospital or
what until you've had your medicine uh
uh a retired men home these apples are
all
[Music]
foul okay let's follow the real goal I
think it's up
[Music]
here a sick Bay
yeah early stages of a
hospital
Su
jashim
Turtle just working on a pet project of
my dragon Lance nope though she's not
above biting the hand that feeds
her recommend it to me again sometime
all right I was hoping we might try and
solve the mystery of poor Clive rosfield
mhm please do a bearer of the srea
Imperial Army sent behind Enemy Lines
with orders to wait until it turned into
a brawl then slip the dominant throat in
the
chaos I didn't know it was
her how could it
be and so to save her neck you slit your
sergeants then set your sights on the
Hills conveniently forgetting how The
Empire deals with
deserters cuz with that on your chop my
friend we both know you won't be getting
far
you've Fallen a long way Lord
rosfield it's like I'm watching a
movie I love
it I'll not have it said that I'm a poor
host what do you mean to do with
her do with her why nothing her life is
her own now if I wanted to use her do
you think I'd be talking to you all I
want to do his
help dominance like her branded like
you of course the realm doesn't approve
which is why we live in a
cave and it's also why we need help from
brandid do know one end of a sword from
the
other what say you
Clive will you join
us
yeah sounds better than the deal I have
now Sid was
it I trust that you'll do right by Jill
but until my brother is
Avenged I must walk my own path is it
really your own
path feel like you're being forced onto
my someone else brother was
murdered by a second dominant of fire
yeah what the was that the
Phoenix's evil twin well buger me
another rumor proven true I only stand
here today because of Joshua 13 years
I've waited for this chance I've slept
in filth junk from a gutter killed more
men than I can count o you're right the
Empire will not suffer a
deserter this will be my best
opportunity my last his eyes are so
pretty which is why you should join
us I told you I'm not interested I
know
one of my Scouts sent word there's a
group of branded fugitives north of here
in the Imperial Village of
loswing among them is one he believes to
be a dominance of
fire is he
certain what say we go and ask
him this doesn't mean I'm joining
you
H I think that's what it
means that's might ready
then
Turtle you'll find everything you need
down in the main hall as well as a few
things you don't have fun thank
you sorry I had something in my throat
must have been a
frog oh can I read this
no m can I talk to the
turtle where's the turtle I see
it I just committed to calling a turtle
now it's kind of cute careful you I feel
like the old morning on these steps the
old
morning think he'd have time for a with
old a before scampering back to his Sol
B lonely are we August what it's a joke
box
I can't activate it no and how did you
like this
[Music]
stew lumpfish
e land L if you can read don't let Otto
know we'll put you to work on The Ledges
too don't worry I'm destined for more
greater
things e who did most concerning that
sounds like you're like going like
through your throat up to your
nose or the other way around I hate that
so much the snorting the really deep
snorting oh no hold on go was it perhaps
you can help Sid asked me to make ready
for our mission how does one go about
that here um
well this old Nan's
place
uh on second thoughts you maybe want to
see Black Thorn first
okay why a blacksmith to the for is then
okay maybe a new weapon
please oh wait no hold up you'll be
needing this black Thor won't take no
notice of you
otherwise H might not
anyway
thanks continent of
R am I paying with alcohol are you Black
Thorn what if I am I no time for Idol
chatter I'm not here to talk I'll be
accompanying s loswing and I need you to
see to my equipment you could be
accompany the goddess griger to a holy
bed chamber for all I care I'm not
lifting a finger for you excuse me is
that
so yeah give give him the the alcohol
support his alcoholism let's go do you
want that or
not I can take it
back damn you
gos all right all right no need to be
Hasty Clive the enabler let's have a
look at
[Music]
you I doubt that lck could stay a mle's
fart bloody Imperial
they' rather see their bear as dead than
kid it out properly M well don't give me
I can there a favor To Go's
mind forging the crafting of New Gear as
well as uh the upgrading of existing
gear can be done at uh blacksmith as
long as you have the recipe and the
proper materials select the highlighted
item from the list and hold extra craft
or upgrade cool okay I guess we're going
to try to make this
wait what does it need and the belt CES
a square you want anything else you
bring your own materials I'll bear that
in mind oh was that free thank
you a word of advice don't let Sid
decide what's best for
you
[Music]
okay when someone has changed in the
hard something has changed in the
hardware a notice will appear in the
upper right hand corner of the screen
uh-huh in addition to stock updates for
Sharon's toll and new forging recipes
for the black hammer there are also
notices for new quests new misses misses
and many other
things okay I suppose I should think
Goods oh let me check do we have
anything else
quick what do you want no oh wait Broad
Sword plus
one but I'm missing something
anyway I bra CL one wait is this
some I would be crafting something new
right can I reinforce what I
have no wait I don't have iron uh iron
bracers
apparently and no
whatever can't make it crafted stuff is
always at plus one
aha okay wait uh I have
to what did I just make a belt right
yeah oh 15 to 23
nice okay I have Imperial infantry
bracers now want to come back when I can
make um the the the
braces arm
protection the gift worked you have my
thanks I
yeah come on nearly
there spit it
out heavily
breathing you blanket quick as you
like
all right we make him comfortable while
a bed's made
up well you're just going to stand there
someone face some water I'll get the
bucket you go and see if on needs out eh
needs out wait
me
Auto the hell where is this here's the
auto
auton who are
they
huh they're freed Imperial bearers who
the hell are
you this right you won't make it
through the night think you can find
your way up them stairs to the infirmary
we need TI not nothing go on shift your
ass so it's an actual like English word
it wasn't like a dialect or or like
accent kind of
thing but it's an old word is
it your friend needs her rest there'll
be time for tearful reunions when she's
recovered I'm not here for jail you're
wanted downstairs there are injured
bearers in need of attention well why
didn't you say
so North English I did say so North
[Music]
English have you guys watched C play
this game by the way or is is mine the
first one you guys
watch the first
playr yes yes no I wait you no first but
I'll need to examine them both in the
infirmary oh seems like half
half my work's just
begun first wouldn't want to watch Tes
yeah I feel like
um might be might feel a little bit like
a chore to watch such a long jrpg also
even so close back to back
twice did Ena finish another fine day at
the Hideway never I don't really
remember remember seeing arrive in this
state playing it's no easy thing casting
off your
chains by the time most pluck up the
courage already too far
gone these two here are the lucky ones
the name's Otto yeah I know call just
finished it you ask me well Otto I feel
like she had a lot
of do you now like breaks in between
lady Karen over there will be more than
happy to help you I'm going to try to
have mine be weekly
oh and get done within a a smaller time
frame I won't be staying is that
right well for as long as you are here
consider yourself welcome you helped us
today and we won't forget
it if I feel like it I might even do
like some side quests off screen like I
did with uh uh ter of the
Kingdom cuz so far I'm really enjoying
it
it's a bit slow paced right now but
there was already a lot of exciting
stuff and I like the I like the battle
system but a lot of the fights seem
unnecessarily
long although I guess those were all
like bigger fights we just had a lot of
the bigger important fights just so
happened to be the normal fights aren't
that
[Music]
long it's probably not worth to side
stuff from what people said yeah I was
told the rewards and the the content of
the side stories are side quests are not
really
good okay yeah more abilities go go
go mhm oh yeah I wonder how battle will
be when I have the icons in my team keep
an eye out for oh we were just talking
about quests so the green icons are side
quests
so to-do list after accepting
toist
oh Highway facilities an ever grown
compendium of all things Vala a personal
jukebox Al so now you can use it if you
collect something
okay the fat CH who are these
people ah you at least want to do side
quest with the plus symbol uhhuh oh okay
okay maybe maybe
maybe I need supplies for my journey to
loswing Otto said you could provide them
what's that does the newcomer think it
proper to make demands of a poor old
matron before even introducing himself
introducing it's Clive well Clive I he
that dog is yours yeah since he followed
sidom one night I've seen to it that his
Chin's rubbed and his belly bad though
suppose that's your job now unless you
lose him again I won't hopefully not not
again so did he for real not see the dog
for 13
years so what a coincidence then now
after 13 years finding everything and I
lost you didn't think i' shower your
lordship with my hard w we my with a
pocket full of Gill what the co life
doesn't work that way lad what a good
timing now let's say some coin
H and
shops brat
sword oh it's like Five Points stronger
no that's fine should we buy it 500 how
much money do I have wait that's like
taking all my money I don't know if the
five points is worth that I'm going to
go why you barely a guil yeah yeah I'm
going to going to go
stingy
again you taking this side
now in some RPGs it's worth buying from
the shops in some RPGs it's just worth
crafting all right I can some RPGs you
end up finding the stuff you can buy in
the shops anyway all the time so not
buying my stores are getting cluttered
and I need to make room for next
shipment I see in this one it's more
about
crafting thank me oh and boss weapons
thank you dog
crafting it might be more worth it you
find stuff in the main quest okay so not
really necessary to spend all my money
on shops
okay at least not all the
[Music]
time retri
sex bang warning uhoh uhoh oh what am I
doing just me getting closer to that is
activating that oh the
ar
ar stone is now accessible this
customizable virtual battlescape
provides c a safe location to test on
your
[Music]
ah
aha maybe not
now uh but interesting wait do I have to
can I get out of
here I can't get out of
here do I have
to maybe I have
to
oo I was pressing Circle but it didn't
work it wants to teach me this probably
training the Hall of CH is a fully
customizable B script that Prov yeah
mhh oh there's a training menu to adjust
parameter you going to fight at me or
no maybe there's a
wait
invincibility enemy aggro enemies will
attack
yes are you going to attack
now
[Music]
are
you
no
je how many are there going to
be oh I see my combos down there on the
left
side that's story you might actually
want to do those on stream okay if
there's like a Jill side quest or so
yeah I wouldn't mind doing that but you
guys got to tell me like point it out
like hey this one you might want to do
this
one that's enough ah I like
it okay they're infinite how do I how do
I
quit and training
okay this will be a good way of testing
new skills for sure see now I can exit
Okay I leave a long comment later okay
you're all
done does that work for other people too
that are not me can they use this
leaving already are
you it's you all miss the most lady
Karen it always is
don't stop you going does it only me
this should be fun
right how did they why did they why is
that
there I'm questioning the
logic a DMC game honestly who knows
maybe I'll play one in the
future I am the storm that is
approaching world map to instantly
travel to previously
unlocked like
now wait there's
a this was
exclamation
H I have to go to the next map
the inen don't joke about that she would
love it if K did try
DMC it's a button mashing game so it
could actually work for you excuse me
what are you trying to say with that
huh yeah green ones Cy Quest but didn't
somebody say specific ones with an extra
or something sign I should
[Music]
do
bastard blood flies
everywhere oh only I told you we should
have taken the crystal
roading and I told you we're Outlaws
Okay Plus instead of exclamation you
want every bounty hunter in storm
harrying us from
here to the holy
Capital besides what's wrong with the
shortcut through nature Splendor you the
deadlands claim more of the realm each
day but a place like this still exists
as a miracle in
itself blood flies and all we'll be back
in Imperial land
soon you all right never
better sounds like it you guys know I
was in Square Enix building
before think I told you before maybe out
there is a fine Hound soon took Fearless
as you like it's good to have you back
tole
now we don't want to be caught in the
forest after
Nightfall they were looking at my
face they wanted to use my face yeah
yeah
mhm they wanted to study my
face for future
games I forgot why it didn't happen
though I think it's just like it just
like just just disappeared
mhm he I'm
serious I was like approached by some
really important Square Enix person irow
and when I was in Japan and and I was
asked to come to the office and have
some talk and then they looked at my
face I mean okay they looked at my face
the moment they approached me they were
like can we like study face like you
know skin skin textures and stuff like
[Music]
that cuz they do stuff like that they
they try they study real people
especially like you're like uh not not
Asian faces I
[Music]
guess sure kiar
huh I'm serious
yes I'm
serious but I didn't feel so confident
about my skin honestly so that was
concerning to
me
what yeah k k says I look like FF
character well now I certainly do
especially in these
clothes
a hero's best friend togle has joined
the party and we'll fight alongside CLI
let's go pet
commands use the left thingy to toggle
between item shortcuts and pet commands
oh okay I have the
control he will surely also attack
automatically
right right removes the need
for can I please put this on did I
mention to be deadly beasts I am not
going to control
him which one is
it timely assistance
right thank
[Music]
you okay why do you mean what do you
mean it's game breaking the game keeps
on telling me to use the Rings too
nothing to tr
forg how
reassuring use them for that anty
shortcuts good good good
good okay they don't seem that op to me
as long as you don't wear them all at
once nice so detailed all the different
FAS
and and
floras maybe they're friendly like tole
oh maybe they're not
wan to
go ow we're hurting doggle friends those
are some weird
doggles stay down stay down bad do who's
a bad dog and who's a good Dogo that's
right my doggo is a good
doggo stay down stay down no tratos for
you no tackles for you no walkies for
you
m feel bad they don't seem that
different from my
go we still have a way to
go oh my God is that Moss
almost is it
Moss looks so
fluffy this way you Lord sorry I was
going to bring it to
[Laughter]
am am would like
that yeah I had a good talk with am
yesterday
made me really happy oh the dear Lord
are we going to fight that
too it's
cute stor stor
stom I'm glad glad Amy is back again
miss what in good Greer's name is he
doing this far
south looking for food no more wolves
where he's from the north was one of the
first parts of storm to fall to the
blight
poor s I'd invite him over for a cup of
tea if I didn't think he'd eat the dog
cup of tea cup of
[Music]
te so pretty Wow Let's try and stay out
of its
path oh remember when I said the Beast
oh well the shs in these parts are much
better and you only thing to mention is
now is there like
element I would assume yes with all the
icons with different elements is there
like elements that are more effective
for example like this seems gry so I'm
like guessing fire would be good
[Music]
generally no
boy
my
that's so weird but is the whole icon
thing a common thing in SF games are
there always icons cuz I feel like I've
heard of Shiva before too and
[Music]
EIT so those are those are common mhm
mhm level up well that's the underg
those are those are common so in other
FF games is there
uh element thingies
[Music]
reactions
yeah interesting that's one of those
things that are
different thank you kindly in this one
huh yeah
weaknesses m
mostly on the turn based
ruins they're everywhere aren't they
Austria looks like
Austria somewhat not a little bit some
say there was a time they blocked out
the
Stars down was the only way left for
them to
go there's probably a lesson to be
learned from that it can wait come
on he's a cool dude
mind
your will do thank you I mean I don't
know how I would think I could go
through there without mining my
head thank you sharp
[Music]
fangs I sense another
battle oh
sensed it
correctly Dragon it is is straight out
of Game of Thrones doesn't have to be a
friend of yours now honestly all my oh
did you that Game of Thrones mentions
are very much direct get up boy you know
what to doy legit
because uh it's l
like
Ridley def don't remind me of Ridley or
rley or whatever the that name
was I'm uh purposefully
fighting
good a fine Housey
earn really yeah from uh we're talking
about um Metroid
right hey wait this actually is a
stronger enemy uhoh okay I'll try harder
now sick of
tole get him get him get him get him
don't no no
no like ah ah
ah taste that pom taste that pom that
pom of course I remember him you know
what to do he traumatized me
after all
sick of tle One does not simply
forget there what's the
word you know what to do
boy know
what K the distance
boy get him boy get him get him get him
sick of
tole over here
there boy get him boy you know what to
do
boy ow okay
oh why do I have the doggle
commands sick of
tole give them all You' got boy
nice I think you beat really very easily
Metro Prime what do you mean what do you
mean I think it's the other way
around sick I'm too you don't know what
it means is he really saying that maybe
he's saying something else must be a
nest nearby keep your eyes
open got to use my potions I guess who
what
s he just like he even kind of pushed
himself from the wall how
how I'll admit I hadn't counted on never
ever have I seen somebody
cross a a section like that
before just like instead of like slowly
scooching scooching scooching he just
ran through it parkour
parkour uh why trust in your own animal
instinct when you now have an actual
animal at your side if you L hold down M
okay
cool oh he's so
cute oh my God at least one of us knows
these Woods thank you
tole you can Pat the dog well then it's
already an A+
game well they look not too happy and
for once he not my
fult keep your distance Bo
you know what to do
boy
vampire does my doo automatically attack
what I'm
attacking you don't what to do wow
tornado
tole sick
tole sick sound don't let them get away
stay down
thickening
I think they care
s give them all you've got more
foral get him boy chcken means a cat
there boy I'm learning a lot of new
English right get him boy get him get
him get
[Music]
him
nice dou
sounds
making you know what to do boy stay
down we did it doesn't only say that to
dogs huh doesn't mean I have to like it
no thought that was a specifically doggy
thing show me the way to
go this looks this looks
like such a pretty path like oh oh my
God what a nice
Forest that I would like to get lost
in E this like everything's so pretty
and details oh my God oh my
God yeah I'm appreciating the beauty of
this game for
sure sasuga Final Fantasy and there's
Moss somebody take a picture for ailia
MOS B fight oh yeah okay yeah it's
literally an arena made for a boss fight
okay
okay it would be lovely to go camping
here yeah only if we take care of the
boss
first okay focus time this shouldn't
take too long so much for your
shortcut
still short just not quite as quick but
it'll be a downside quicker if you help
me my thought name I've sick of
tole don't let them get
away
R
uh by the way do I have to and do my my
teammates do they heal themselves and if
yes do they use their own potions or do
we use do they have like endless
potions d boy get him
boy how do you if you on that side of
him how do you even oh was that a
you how do you dodge them d
boy
keep your distance
[Music]
boy they don't get hurt what right now
they're Immortal
oh there
boy get
him Dodge
backwards try
that oh o
o that's the second time I'm like kind
of missing there's a good boy ah
back you
B oh stag okay let's go sick
tole get
up get him
boy sick
tole there
tole what you going to do
you I've seen that somewhere before how
long are you going to do
that i k the way he land so cute not if
we kill him
first
you know what to do boy oh my god get
him
boy not this time get
him back okay okay okay three times kind
of I think there
boy
ah
right
got
point oh okay I went a little bit too
much uh was too much confidence into
that no this time get him
boy get him
[Music]
boy okay okay okay I'll Focus I'll Focus
I'll Focus get
up stab it
[Music]
wo sick of
tole there
boy give them all you've got
boy get him
boy
sick
tole sick
tole
oh he's spinning
again you spin my five new round right
round like Cor baby go around go
around get him I'm going to die sick of
to just kidding I'm not going to die
there boy yeah nice
damage there
boy don't let them get
away over
here
get him
boy give them all you've got boy yeah
nice
ending nice ending nice ending I went
back and forth and back and forth good
stuff you handled this guy better than I
did I was like messing around too much
for most of it but
yeah the way it was going in the end was
the ideal way of how it should have gone
the whole
time yay yay y yay I used up so many
portions turle can regen you too does he
do it without me telling him sorry I'm a
bit late don't worry
[Music]
welcome as a interesting fight also I
didn't feel like um too dragged out so
that was fine
and he was pretty darn cute wasn't
[Music]
he are still alive come
on
Al here comes the
Thunder
oh oh
wait the snip that's like
literally isn't that what the Thunder
Girl does
in t of the Kingdom doesn't she also
snap you're dominant oh you didn't
realize I am hi yeah Osa doesn't she
also not by choice mate oh bloody Roman
of strapping young Lads she does and it
was this sorry sacka Bon ramu saw fits
to home H
ramu oh he can also use the fire but I
guess it goes for electricity
Sid you say you want to help dominance
and
beers but what's in it for
you tell us your story what's in it for
me the same as for all of us what we
want
deserve save for our Knack dominants and
bearers are no different from everyone
else the ability to use magic or summon
great beasts should command respect but
instead as left as outcasts Our Kind are
used and discarded like tools yet we are
men so why must we die is less I see
what you're saying is you want to start
a war T ldr thanks
C you flatter me lad but my days is a
the Firebrand along behind me no I only
wish to offer our kind of choice a place
where we can die on our own
turns his
voice what's that like thing is it it
reminds me of like an object that if you
talk through it it has the same like
weird rumbling effect in your voice
like what what what is
it uh I guess like a fan I don't think
that's what I was thinking of but I
guess like that's that that that can
literally create the same effect
yeah how do you have that in your voice
naturally that's
crazy
C he does sound like a radio find this
dominant what do you think or something
like that I'll show him the Mery he
showed my brother and cut out the tongue
of any man who tries to talk me out of
it all right Forest dark enough was it
is cute
lizard yes let's cut some tongues oh
yeah give me those
potions and another one oh no that was
not the potion I need more potions
please give me those potions
[Music]
Hornets sick of and they have a lot of
HP sick of
tole those are some big job tole sick of
tole King your distance boy set the
ornates on fire and it's next as
well sick of
tole over
here yeah where's the a
nest it's certainly a smart idea to to
set a hornet's nest on fire
right get him boy get him get him
boy you flying enemies sick
of give them all you've got
for over here not if it's connected to a
wood sick of
tole get him it's over get
him you know what to do boy oh guys
yesterday you know what I did out of
Randomness I to a
emotional uh what eut test emotional
intelligence but I while I was doing it
see that
River we follow her up stream and we'll
be in Lost wi in no time it seems more
like a testing whether or not you're
depressed or not test uh uh are you
mentally okay kind of test how sad are
you cuz I feel like a lot of the
questions I would answer differently if
I was in a different state of
mind I don't know if it's supposed to be
like that
the eq's
[Music]
questions at the results
um it wasn't that detailed because if
you want to get a detailed result you
have to pay um
but it said something about there's room
for improvement but I know uh how to get
him
boy
function get him something like
that but it took me like 50 minutes or
so to do the test was a pretty long one
finished I don't know if it was a a good
result honestly because yeah I think I I
answered a lot of the questions
like you know
[Music]
like it was it was a lot of questions
that
really you might answer completely
different you know what to do
boy it's over when when you're not in a
depressor expressor
mood oh there's another one of these
[Music]
rly keep your distance
boy
you know what to do
boy get him
[Music]
boy you want to take this chest too
honestly it's not worth the time the
result I got it was basically just like
threee
sentences not worth spending 50 minutes
on him get
them give them all you've got forys no
let them get away
would not
recommend get I mean what are you going
to do anyway with that knowledge of your
[Music]
EQ what does that you knowing your
EQ get
him k your distance
boy
I would also like to know my IQ but what
kind of questions do you get in an IQ
like do you get legit map IQ IQ test do
you get legit math questions
or is it more like so there's a bus of
five people next station one person gets
out of the bus or something like
that two people get in how many people
are left in the
bus
[Music]
there Boy Logic
puzzle wouldn't it be nice to have a IQ
test stream boy that was kind of funny
to me
honestly testing my IQ on
stream you did an IQ test as a kid in
the was not map okay then I feel like I
can do
it
you good Dogg you won't be able to focus
yeah that's the thing like if I do it on
stream like I will be kind of like under
pressure and maybe not doing as well as
I would when I would do it in
privacy but still for the content hey
which way do I
go you say oh did I am I going back
right
now recorded m
[Music]
oh there's a
chest how is that the first chest that
I'm
finding
meteor are you SM than the
vtuber chances are yes
oh one only one soldier SC someone's far
from
home let's follow him Collective IQ are
your tests for Collective IQ or do you
just do an IQ test together and then
whatever the result is is your
Collective
IQ
oh
and hey they're just down that way all
of them Greg's my witness the average of
a group
ah
excellent okay lady move she likes to be
dominant but she will never be a
dominant H have I not proven Loy
I squeezed myself some orange juice
freshly today my le values loyalty above
all else that's kind of bitter today but
were you not quick to betray your
countrymen for the promise of
coin got
brutal no I didn't tweet myself there's
like a machine in the
supermarkets but the today the oranges
weren't so sweet
I oh like like a forghetti spaghetti V
beu
woman or is it more like a Benedict her
shut up and do what I say commander of
W's Elite
intell if we can capture
her air refresh you weapons on the
ground
Imperials oh no
thank
you wait does the lady leave
already let's get this over with
then at least they're not giant lizards
the lower button I shall press it again
soon sick
tole get him boy midnight
[Music]
R don't let them get
away sick of tole is he strong he seems
strong he's dual wielding the
BL you know what to do boy oh oh my
god
oh ni a togle there boy get the dot
damage get
him don't miss out on the dot damage
give all you got
[Music]
for what are you doing o showing me all
those six
jumps CU you're barely getting hits Okay
I
lied get him
boy sick of tole oh my thunder friend
also has
[Music]
a
know Thunder
attack don't let them get
away fund of friends of course written
with
[Music]
f so the might Clash when the screen
flashes orange like this tap repeatedly
okay
okay F the friend
60 no more Final
Fantasy hey hey hey hey
[Music]
hey yeah this guy's
aggressive what motivates
you get him boy oh what's
that he hardly leaves me
[Music]
opening the got
boy
oh get him boy he's got a all he's a
he's a fire breathing machine
oh o assassinate N I will not let
you did he just pull a finishing move on
me what I thought that was another one
of those cinematic
scenes
sh oh there's a checkpoint mid fight
there boy get him boy interesting there
boy
okay I guess I lost track of my
a SI
to it's
over King a distance boy where is he
sick of
tole there boy get him boy get
him
sick
tole I can barely get
[Music]
close your eyes
open there
boy we used our fires at the same
time moreal
coincidence don't let them get
away sick of tole get
him you're not matched is he like a
[Music]
ninja oh who wait he was trying to do
the assassinate thing again that thing
that just killed
me I thought it was a finishing move
you're sick of tole
[Music]
nice keep your distance
for he is a ninja there boy fantasy
ninja there
boy that is a finisher so was he about
to finish me
again can he only use that when I'm like
get
him there boy that amount of HP that
would take him
[Music]
oh futon wait that attack is called
futon oh now no
you holy okay uh w w wo w w this
time it didn't kill
me but it got really
close don't let them get
away
y
[Music]
all you got
for are you guys like with your eyes are
you following
along you know what to do
[Music]
boy it's assassinating me again will I
survive will I survive yeah my god get
him she I can't even really dodged
[Music]
that don't let them get
away you can do really much
[Music]
all get him
boy over here it's okay now what with
this
camera you know what to do boy
hey uh are we doing the thing no are we
surely we are this
time I'm already pressing it I'm already
mashing the
square
yay early Mash another one right
yeah mashed potatoes another one another
one and another one and another
one another one
[Music]
that was that was me finishing him all
right sheh okay this one has been slain
hopefully he will not come
back
damn damn
son first time I went game
over we thought we were
Imperials well
the was a exciting fight though you
fight like a true Shield of Rosaria
thank you and one blessed by the Phoenix
at
that sequel
movie Very
[Music]
fastpaced speaking of which I wonder
does the other icon of fire give
blessings do you think oh good question
you don't believe
me and lo the Creator did make of the
elements eight icons to serve as keepers
of the one law oh
eight not that I've ever set too much
store by holy Doctrine but on that point
it's
clear fire has always had just the one
Warden as of all the rest a new one
can't be born until the previous dies
and even that can take years
H
weird
well maybe exceptions to the rule you
don't strike me as a
li which leaves but one person who might
be able to shed some light on the
matter they in Lost
swing I'm trying to use the L button
frankness I would IM we should hurry
before it gets
dark but what if someone discovers the
bodies well and they'll be solely
disappointed I hold it I yeah
right H okay a fire expected
icon wait so sorry maybe stupid question
but
are are um dominance and icons are kind
of the same but not really right so the
dominant are the
people like the boy for example but when
they turn into whatever they represent
then that that's the
icon okay good okay
okay6 when Imperial forces attacked the
rosarian stronghold of Phoenix gate clad
in infernal flame a fish creature flung
itself against the Phoenix overpowering
the icon with a strength and ferocity
never seen before or since
uhhuh the warden of fire last seen on
the night of the Imperial invasion of
Phoenix
gate
that sounds like Watergate in the year
860 when the young joser was F lost
control of his powers you know what I
mean like that thing that happened it's
called Phoenix
gate it's a scandal
yeah the young Jos R the Phoenix First
awakened among the mores of fire an
ancient tribe who dwelt in the western
reaches of storm and the careful pre
preservation of bloodlands among the
rosarian nobility ensured that its
dominant would always be born in the
Dual line does that
mean does careful preservation of
Bloodlines
mean I don't want to say it
but
incest yeah oh
wow okay
hey so Clive is also a child
of
incest oh my
God mysterious figure who was first seen
amid the chaos of the Imperial invasion
of Phoenix gate immediately before the
appearance of the second icon of fire
the very icon that slew the air to the
Dual
Throne the very icon that slw the air
Clive believes this man to be the
dominant who murdered his brother and
has sworn sworn to take his
revenge got to remember that
mouth Royal intelligences what a name an
elite unit of the royal Knights of wud
led by benedicta Harmon that's her
name who
lead LED clandestine incursions deep
into the territory of enemy Nation for
Myriad purposes Espionage and
assassination Chief among them
what those within whom sleeps the power
of an icon though they look uh and think
no differently to any other man or woman
they can not only cast Elemental Magics
without a crystal but also transform
themselves into beasts of world
shattering strength at any moment the
quality for which they are honored
worshiped and
feared
okay
wud
wud stage Replay in arcade
mode oh
okay orabell D Downs the idic ples
of populated unless no unless this one
knows where to
look let's
go go next go next go next go next go
next sometime
later holy Empire of s brick brick so
much for arriving Before
Sunset I didn't realize we were this
close any idea what that is they built
the village around the Fallen Ru I've
heard some call it an
Airship though his flying days seem to
be behind it h it's a shame that can we
make it Fly again you truly think a
dominant waiting for us in that Village
my Scout has never given me any reason
to doubt him which is why I think we
should hurry come on I don't really
unless it's someone who joins our team
but they said it's a fire dominant and
maybe there was a misunderstanding a
tuning of an obelisk allows Clive to
travel quickly to the location on okay
uhhuh
uhhuh what wait this guy is also in ff7
huh in all FF games they there's a
s what can't they think of any other
names what they're different people but
same
name what the other characters too or
just
him sit in F5 is a hot
woman it's tradition it's
necessary this is like like HD Pokemon
here they have a area like this in the
new
Pokemon them out
there need to look for more
[Music]
items there
boy you know what's
boy there boy get him boy stay
down you know what to do
boy over
here sick of
tole so it's only
Sid that's in every
game damn you must be getting paid a lot
of
money oh why did I get
faster why am I getting faster how am I
doing
this F up ahead but are they friends or
how can I run for
this oh you
[Music]
oh that's
enough
sick
you know what to do stay
down oh my God okay calm
down get him
boy there
boy you know what to
doers but why you
I know I have to go the other way but
I'm going this way for the item let me
know how it goes
abilities okay just one
moment oh another
fight get him oh there's a nice little
pool of
water
get all them
exp keep it to me I'm almost level
up let's go
speed yeah they did in another fight not
lying they said it's not very populated
here don't let them get
away like all the houses and Vineyards
seem so empty can I enter though
no they're so
empty so
[Music]
sad uh abilities okay what do we want
there's like flames of rebirth
someon 1,6 okay
no never
mind
I did I even ever use this like I don't
know how to use
it and this has the same
combo charged Magic
ah instead of just going PE PE PE PE PE
I can
[Music]
go I'll learn
it depends if you're in the A on the
ground press them at the same
time ah I thought it was a combo like a
followup
mag
okay this is whole okay I I leave it at
that I have to uh remember uh holding I
have to test so holding the magic
and uh yeah Square holding
square and pressing these two uh at the
same time but one in the air and one not
in the
air was that
it and that just will look fancier in
battle
hopefully
oh I can do it
here all right
okay I'm try to actively use
it can I
remember last Wing So are there people
hidden here
mushy
MH oh pretty that's kind of pretty wow
so
calm that reminds me of a place in no
sign of theists first season or anyone
else for that matter it's too bloody
quiet even for this hour MH what do we
do now first we look for my Scouts you
start here I'll circle around the
back
[Music]
know good
question
subtle one just improves your Dodge oh
does it make it bigger or
faster is it this one you mean this one
or yeah this this
one after being knocked down that's not
really
dodging or do I improve
no ah this one I can improve
it at the moment of an enemy attack not
only allow increases evasion efficiency
effici e
efficacy but also allows for counter
attacks
yeah that's what I'm doing
right so mastering it makes it what like
just
easier extends trigger
window
h
extends trigger
window
H yeah just upgrade
whatever we have another 270 but for now
for now let's wait I'm already
forgetting what I just learned I
think intense music The Village can't be
completely abandoned oh can it rats yeah
it hasn't been AB abandoned by the rats
it
seems
oh
zombie no not quite just drunk maybe I
don't
know wait that's a Sid you miss me I'm
flattered but let's stick to the plan
eh I called him a
zombie that sounds like a child
sus sus that's going to turn into a
monster the moment I go
there child what is wrong with you
it's all right I'm not one of them my
friend and I we're with the Imperial
Army and we've come to help do you know
where your parents
are in in the
church I'm going to find them and make
sure they're
safe can you stay hidden here until
then to the church then my everything
hurts
what's going
on do I have to go up
I'm going to use my massage thingy
after the stream my shoulder massage
machine CU my my shoulder seems so crazy
stiff right now
it's
insane going to watch the V later thank
you tomorrow also final
F what's
going
baby no no this man's going to die if we
don't get into a Healer enough of your
Barking
Dog about
time stand
back who the hell are
you CL
who the hell are
you you w coming you still alive G
barely
oh been doing what I can for the
villagers but but I thought you were
joking it's all right he's with
me is this everyone his hairstyle where
this a pair of royist came for the
bearers just before you arrived was a
dominant among
them
maybe it's not like you as old in a
sign
okay what is this
weirdness I'll give you one guess where
he's going Clive after him I'm not your
dog just use the
bullets some Magic
Bullets too late now he seems like so
far
gone if only I could rush in this
[Music]
game can you really not run faster than
this any word from the
scouts not yet my lady but we have the
dominant companion it's only a matter of
time before we seize our
Quarry very good and what of the
others the bearers have been taken to K
novent some may still be worth keeping
should the dominant elude us all is in
hand my lady they will not be spoiled I
give you my word run speed is annoying
in this game so you're saying it doesn't
get better gentlemen a toast will you
join
me myx
hey to Our Lady Of The Wind and The
[Applause]
King Imperials drink this piss well it
would go some way to explain their
breath lady benedicta
Imperials she's got some hips
wow
oh and instead of killing them you lead
the rat straight to us Mercy oh poor
guy look what we have here boys an
imperial
Bearer good I was getting
bored
let's go here we go where's my funo
friends happy
Halloween
oo
W I've seen her before wait
it wait
I what is that oh T po If this means
what I think it does Sid has some wait I
only have two
Potions there boy N I have to be real
careful oh my god get
sick tole you know what to do boy
die not this
[Music]
time I was trying to activate
them this
time get
him Jing the checkpoint y
be you know what to do
boy too
[Music]
slow get him
boy mommy you know what to do boy there
boy so
bad there boy sick of tole you know what
to do boy sick of
tole oh
Oops I
[Music]
Did you what my brain sorry brain brain
hoard I
can't I can't perform so well right
now don't let them get
[Music]
away
sick her
tole help
me get
him the
lunch over
here you know what to do
boy I wanted to dash to
her get
him get him boy
why do I keep on missing that
one over
here oh my
God sick of
tole get him
no I'm certainly going to
die you're sick of tole get him
boy sick of tole tole was that you I
love you so
much my good Dole you better be on your
way the best
Dole get
him over
here
this quickly
no too can heal a bit well why does he
not do it
then sick of
tole Heal Me tole heal me get him boy I
don't really you know what to do I can't
I can't do it
myself sick
tole no not
again keep your distance
boy you know what to do
boy get
him you know what to do
boy don't let them get
away too slow that'll
help
get him sick of
[Music]
tole over
here
you know what's to boy there
boy sick of okay I tried really hard
there but yeah the close one
close I can do
it what is that
thing this means from Fall oh but I got
more potions I got my potions reloaded
okay that's that's that's
fair
here sick of
tole get
him this
time sick
tole get him
boy okay going
better there boy a I like to use the
moment when she charges that weird
wall charge my this thing this
shot use
[Music]
them don't let them get
away give them all you
for good damage there good
damage get him boy go this
time
get
him over
here nice nice nice we didn't get her
staggered at all last time get
him he's trying to do the charging
square
[Music]
but
Ah that's also that's what I was trying
to
do sick
tole one potion only so far a
[Applause]
ah get
him
d boy too
slow you know what to do
boy don't let them get
away get him boy over
here keep your distance
boy there's a good boy sick him tole get
him get him
boy
nice get them all you've got
boys
nice get over here not this
time
nice super
good
y I was barely
talking yeah I only used one
potion yum y good work yeah full Focus
cleric's Medallion oh can I wear
that
yay so where the hell is my funer friend
you've got some fighting you even for a
branded you impressed
huh I'm more than just a
branded
C look is here to save the day MW is
this how you recruit all of your charges
don't recall you complaining makes po
stronger
o
cool cracking my Knuckles
so sidus I that's the full name huh
remind me why was it that you betrayed
your
kingdom I asked you a
question Lord
Commander
why because i' had enough of you and
your kings
Antics and yet here you are stealing my
brandid what are you
plotting I would like to say tell you I
stole him
he's lady benedicta we have secured the
dominant always something isn't
there
give it to
us that was
nothing and she's
gone
so what she called was that an icon or
just some
strong wind
thing she's not a dominant right so
no if she was a dominant she would have
become the icon one of the villagers may
have heard something just Aon can't just
which is why I sent
gav uh there's nothing about the thing
she summoned but let's read hers command
did I no didn't I already read
[Music]
it well there's nothing really about
what she just summoned I read this thing
before
but
the man has a nose for these things
trust
me no lore on it
yet okay I'll
wait until more lore
drops by the way I got a friend to like
help me with the stream idea that I
talked about for the member stream that
is coming on
Tuesday so
it wasn't about bears at all they were
looking for a dominant that's right I
thought we were ridding the bastard like
any of us keep a monster like that under
our roof no offense when no one talked
they started rounding up everyone with a
brained and then everyone we out one and
all and locked you in the cellar hoping
sooner or later someone would
break you know
good might been different if you'd
accepted my invitation oh don't remind
us we were all saying the same thing
this is our own any it don't mean we
won't I hope I'll get everything ready
that I want I'll drink too well even if
I don't get the whole list of
things should still
be
lord it's literally
[Music]
vol 100 full Legions the young Dron LED
and watched as a
[Music]
million I like this kind of B
music
listen yeah Revenge won't bring him
[Music]
back 13 years ago
I watched a dominant kill my brother
right in front of
me and I did
nothing but now I
can I can kill the son of a
and bring peace to my brother's
soul but surely there will be after that
interesting
twist when we find out who that eph
dominant is
and be conflicting slave then maybe we
are them and what we were oh God what if
I'm right what I was seeing was not me
watching it happening but I am ifred oh
oh my oh god oh oh God I'm scared of my
power holy oh God oh God what oh I'm
probably right stop my brain I'm not
looking the Imperial host I also thought
I was really with um I
had of a handful of cowards and
Cutthroats
bam may need 100 full Legions could
it be that the Young Prince defends a
house of cards ready to topple at the
slightest
Breeze oh
God tell me something I'm too
knowledgeable why do you not resist I
need to be brainwashed Within Me lies
the power to slay Gods the Phoenix
pery a game theory not fight okay you do
not
flee you refuse your gift if good guy
huh wouldn't my theory have been so cool
though perhaps you are
distracted
wait oh
girl she girl my offer still stands what
you're saying she's e join us and you
will be treated with the respect one of
our kind
deservs no the other one is e
h Lord M Grace
[Music]
don't
I'll give you a moment to consider your
options oh good night thank you for
watching so
far do be gentle with
[Music]
them oh I was so scared of my theory
being
true when my brain just being too
powerful for my own
good Clive
wake up gav's
back toal is the real
Mastermind canand one of the Empire's
outlin strongholds though apparently not
strong enough to keep out the royalists
the captured bearers are inside I'm sure
of it if Benedict's orders are to stay
in the shadows she won't be traveling
with many men meaning she'll be keeping
her prisoners together and close by
including the dominant so we find a way
into the Fortress and conjure a bit of
chaos uh what about me excellent
question gav you will wait outside the
care and guide those I free to safety
and miss all the fun why can't he do
that Clive doesn't have your knows he'd
stumble off a cliff before he even found
the men come on Cav you're the best man
for the
job
well when you put it that
way suppose I better Scout ahead for any
surprises don't you let him
down he's funny I
won't all right shall we somehow the
looks suits the character
we wait until tomorrow but he's right
there and if we leave now we'll arrive
just as the sun comes up maybe join the
guards in breaking their fast come on
Clyde they only just took the place
they'll be there a while yet we've got
one chance at this you don't want to
waste it do
you
no
H
oh the dead of
night New Stock as the story progresses
new weapons and items will become
available ah yeah okay settled there's
someone I want you to meet at this
hour he's the owner of the talent and
I'll bet best hope of getting a decent
nice
kit Kim wait that's a merchant what can
I interest you in today what do you
got oh oh that's quite a bit stronger
but 700 oh wait now I have way more
money I think this one I might
[Music]
get
20 20 times 20 points stronger yeah that
looks fine hold another
it'sing my money is looking way better
than before
25 ooh 10 up is there a crafter dude
here
too is it for is this for the Juke
B potions potions are fine I guess keep
fighting the good
fight no I can teleport anytime though M
okay wait I'll just equip what I just
got and then when I get to that place
again I'll uh craft
something oh did it automatically equip
it
oh
oh okay then actually I'm going to look
at the abilities again I feel like I
used them all um uh the the this one
confuses me
cuz it's like not giving me a sign
that it's happening and it feels like
nothing's happening sometimes but then
suddenly it happens it's like kind of
weird confuses me what does the master
do reduces time well that I would like
the Mastery of
that cuz then I'm quicker sure that it's
[Music]
working I can't use it now okay yeah
charging that one up I I I did it
sometimes
in that
fight but I was like always like what
happening and also like it's kind of
dangerous the amount of time it took to
charge it was always kind of
[Music]
dangerous during an attack and it will
be charged ready when
oh but then all my attacks so far like
pretty uh
quick m not long enough but could I like
go PE PE PE with my magic while charging
that at the same
time like like can I do it several
times yeah
oh yeah okay that's that's pretty my
good man it seems we'll be spending the
night I thought as
much where do you find that one and
oh him you won't believe me if I told
you wow okay Quon here is an old friend
one who is sympathetic course
sympathetic Quint Quint Quint he knows
about your little sanctu
quintuplets I would never have guessed
so many people were bent on setting us
free when last I checked the mere
thought would only you a trip to the
Gallows I am well aware of the risks as
I am of the
rewards ah can you change rewarding in
your very own dominant of fire a
dominant
here now that I would like to see the
the the the controls like can I change
my magic Missile to but nothing passes
unnoticed in Lost twing take your brand
for example there something else is on
L1 m dodging so I guess you have dodging
on
triangle people will see that at
once and I need hardly tell you how they
will greet the inquiries of a
bearer you are afraid your words will
fall on deaf ears ah lock on yeah as
they have ever since the moment you were
marked whatever I'm fine for
now
happily I can provide a solution to your
dilemma as a favor to Sid that is I
think I want to
switch x with triangle so I jump with
triangle take
this I don't think I can it has The
Uncanny power to loosen tongues Square
continuously like
uh stay on that button while also
several times pressing triangle I don't
think I can do that but I think I I can
do it if this might be Imperial even
hearing swing not with the same word
that's law but
how you don't need to worry about that
just yet trust me everyone in loswing
knows what that seal means and what it
means if they don't take
note it's now we can sit here one you
want to go PE PE and the other one you
going to you want to go
[Music]
PE
let's see if this thing really
works let's make him talk and that's all
you can
remember tell me wood cutter what does a
wood cutter cut if a wood cut cut
ah quinson took a l into you I see and
there I was thinking you were in bed
with Sid wonder what gav will have to
say about this
this gay speaking of him if you see
him tell him thanks for looking after
us now what can I help you with I'm
searching for a dominant of fire gav
seems to think he might have taken
Refuge here we see a lot bearers around
these
parts but I do seem to recall one who
commanded the flame now whether or not
that makes him a dominant I can't say
but the Wuda certainly took a keen
interest poor sod did you go look at
him didn't have a chance one of the
other bearers might have thank
you
n didn't learn much from
that next one
please where is next
person
[Music]
camera still kind of annoys
me it's okay though could be better H
man I see Master quenty must think
you're important it was a good thing
You' done today getting rid of those
bastards yeah you come when you did I'd
be on my way to Ash by now along with
the others poor buckers these others was
there a dominant among them a dominant
of fire might have been yeah royalists
seem to think I was any won't help me a
fin bloke all swallowed up in his robes
like one of great Greer's churchmen okay
do you recall anything else about him
that gets close
though only that you weren't alone was a
young maid who went wherever he did
including the church and wherever the
royalist dragged them both off to before
you got here oh I see thank
you so close and yet so far s found
anything s bloody
cowards bloody
cowards wait up or
down up and then
[Music]
down okay a little bit
confusing
[Music]
my it's so
dark that's Sor right doggo down but how
do I get
down
do
uh
Jesus
wee wee
okay I have reached my
goal tell me that scowl means you've got
good
news I don't know if I would call it
[Music]
news
so a shady lad with a hood and his
equally Shady lass not much to go on but
but but I've been thinking if our friend
is a dominant why not just burn the
royalist to a crisp there's a reason
he's holding back that's actually what I
was thinking a moment ago partner why
does he not turn into that one of the
villagers I talked to said the two were
separated if the wud is have her our
dominants like to think twice before
starting any fires whoever he is he's
shown himself to have a level head I
guess he's careful cunning and he
doesn't want to be
found this could spell trouble foros and
the royalist
both still it'll be a whole lot worse if
we set off after them with blur eyes and
empty bellies there should be a pair of
pallets waiting for us back at the Inn
shall we
pallet all like sleeping
thingies now about those beds do we have
to share one beds I seem to recall your
request being to spend the night and for
that floor will suffice
suffice in a wet Rock I suppose
huh my thanks quincon next time you're
at the Hideway our
floor no need for thanks Sid this isn't
an act of Charity I mean I would
pay in exchange for my floor I shall be
requiring your services what the
royalist saw fit to erect a barricade
AC Village and failed to remove it when
they left I expect it to be gone before
you leave wow As You
Wish
[Music]
what the following
evening Well that took longer than
expected first time dismantling the
barricade it gets easier don't worry I
won't if we leave now we'll arrive at
the care when the Shadows are at the
deepest well I should rather wait no
more
waiting Ena would fail to see any
problem with this situation unless well
I know another shortcut that no that was
really weirdly Rude why so
mean like why would I sleep on the floor
to fulfill a request for him when I
could sleep outside in the grass which
would probably be more
comfortable
[Music]
wellow I missed the good old days when I
was a child and I was just like rolling
around and chilling lying in the grass
in the
[Music]
park I don't do that nowadays
H I tried it when I was hiking earlier
this
year grass was comfy but the whole time
I was worried about bugs wait am I going
the wrong
way am
I sometimes you have to walk around you
know uh-huh
okay yeah
bugs bugs everywhere
I would prefer bug's
[Music]
bunny can't feel same and why have we
all became such
it's just
grass where did I come
from
oh my wine I don't
[Music]
care do I go up
here oh no this is the
church okay okay I I I I I I
I I
I
[Music]
I I'm
stuck wait wait wait wait wait instead
of going there we go for the door
okay and then wait how am I
already how do I get there wait ah I I
walked like
underneath cuz there was no way to get
over here from where I was in the cellar
page okay now
left now
left and then kind of left
again no maybe not
there this way I think yeah okay now we
got
it oh it's a dog I thought it was a a
platypus oh o let's go I am taking what
you
own
[Music]
oh well it was because of the chest I
came here for the
[Music]
chest dog and
shambles I'm sorry
do you understand right he
understands do I have to go
[Music]
up
okay here
maybe I can't there we go I can't
possibly be the only one who got lost
here come back to me my
darling I can't bear another night
without you
is it about the girl that I saw in the
beginning this is where I need to go
right were looking to take the care that
have posted centuries to prevent any
unwelcome surprises at least I would
have well yeah would be nice to have a
mini map on the screen maybe even if you
don't want it to be there all the time
you could make it like talkable for
people people who want it and for people
who don't want
it but okay what where does this wind
come from how do I make that happen all
the time Royal
musti wait mff dog that's a thing
right get
him those are really I saw like this get
him really really cute
like a dog that looks like a moop a big
one go get
him H and so I was like staring at it
and the owner was some lady she noticed
probably that I was staring at it but
she the moment I was staring and and
admiring her
dogle she yelled over to me cuz we were
like 10 15 M apart she was like oh
you're wearing such a nice dress and I'm
like what what are the r is thinking she
said nice dress and I'm like oh
of holding when they no intention of
holding it she was complimenting me for
my
dress well you don't think they're
acting on a whim do you with all my eyes
were one of his Majesty's cunning stunts
and he sent his best to execute
it do dog owners not mind when all I
have eyes for is their dog they are just
as a lady say sometimes I wonder if they
get annoyed by that ever wow
what that sent him flying you know what
is that
normal get him
boy is that fist attack sick of
tole
teamwork oh that is uh suddenly charged
way
faster
Je toal always joins
[Music]
me boy I prefer if you don't notice me
and focus on my
dog really are you
shy is the dog The
Shield actually smart tactic if you
don't want people to look at you in
public ever if that makes you like
really uncomfortable get a dog I'll tell
your a really cute dog but the problem
is that might make people talk to you
like oh my God what a cute dog like oh
what how old is he B
blue sometimes I do that too especially
when I'm like stuck in an elevator with
a dog and a dog owner then I feel like I
have to make
conversation but I was thinking when the
lady was complimenting my dress I was
like yeah I bought that dress in Japan
and in Japan when I bought that at the
time so many shops were wearing like a
really H were selling like really
similar
ones so in Japan it's like really normal
dress but I was thinking about here in
Austria this dress is such a
special Stand Out
design the cloes are D in ja even when
it is special here I don't care who else
is in
there I love bringing my Japanese
clothes here I used to wear like really
over the top Le Lisa all the time I
stopped doing that a long time ago and
go for stuff that a a bit
more normal looking get him I I I like
to find like a good balance between like
elegant and to cloes like mature and to
cloes not over the
top oh no batter's
low that
boy yeah it's is really
unique in Austria the cloes that I wear
out I mean often nowadays also I'm just
too lazy and I just wear like really
basic too just to go to the
supermarket
yeah besides that how long does it take
for the battery to really deplete once
it tells you that it's
depleting too much cute would stand down
in Europe sadly yeah
it does as I enjoy battering down the
for some reason Nega this endeavor will
require people will make fun of you for
wearing cute clothes there's an old that
empties under the bridge it should see
us through to the lower levels of the
Care FR cute
stuff
s we both know why I'm here but what is
it that you
want how you risk your life for a
handful of oura
if anyone ever learned what you've been
doing with their property they have my
head in a box but this isn't just about
dominance and bearers it's about all of
us e it's not even only about high
school it's to build a place where it
doesn't matter what you are but who you
are oh nice SM but our world isn't ready
for a place like
that so oh until it is I use the power
I've been given to show people there is
hope
so tell me about this benedictor yes
tell
me the best and worst decision I ever
made don't underestimate a Clive a fight
with her icon is not one you're likely
to walk away from
guda Warden of the
Wind
hey
M the star explain the
star member of H Council well H Council
does doesn't exist now anymore
anyway
[Music]
H it does in our memories a
oh nice nail polish I like the color you
chose
I wonder what you call that shade of
green the land has
fallen the Eastern territories all but
belong to the
Orcs oh I'll have my men ready to depart
by noon no
bother but what of the mines without
adaman light would have engulfed the
mines air
long besides you already have your
orders
yes my
leash the dark swallows more of the
realm with each passing day the land
starved of The Ether that gives it life
and as the fringes fade the people flock
to the mother Crystal's desperate for
their
blessing yeah the war we wage for
possession of that blessing it breaks us
from within hastening us to our own
destruction and so you do what must be
done I unite the
dominance that we may bring an end to
the strife and found a new order to see
us unto tomorrow mhm mhm the world must
be restored MH mhm and I will see it so
you might have already had sidul has not
betrayed
us World restoring again asper L you
still for his
Embrace
but of course
not my
[Music]
leash I serve you and you
alone I remember well the day you first
entered these
holes your pale hand pressed into his as
if you would never let go that that was
a long time
ago maybe there's still feelings hidden
in D the only hand I need that we can
use to our
advantage now and
[Music]
always soon my dear soon all will
know whose hand it is that keeps them
from falling into the
darkness hold me my leash Never Let Me
Go
o one of our sentries has failed to
report my lady your orders pull the men
back inside the care Geral he is here
then have them lead Sid and his little
pet to the chapel I shall entertain them
there they used to come for me after all
yeah I can imagine it wasn't always like
this but I mean it's cool to to have at
least
one H RPG game series that goes there I
mean I'm sure there's more but one of
the bigger ones
clear this one is mature
rated
wowers
well then I hope everybody here is over
18 in my
chat you all are over 18 right trick oh
you'll have to teach me
sometime you can do that
to
yeah forever
16 yes
adults who call me
we should start with the dungeons they
may be holding the beers
there as long as we keep ourselves on
this side of the
BS only had here 3 years
ago
oh they're all
empty you going to give
up
Sid this
gate need some help
yeah do you think wrong man oh one more
the ARs to the lifting no no no no I
am don't underestimate
me c
the r two thing well to make you feel
like you still matter your interaction
still
matters did you hear
that unfortunately yes not everything
already is that easy good news
lad
over
wo
wait I'm I'm I know all the comos
now I just figured out the magic burst
that's
enough um
okay oh what I'm seeing nothing stay
[Music]
down now it's looking way more
interesting to
next let me look around
okay let's
go that was like so
natural Devil May crying this leads to
more royalists we better find another
one yeah yeah I was noticing the magic
burst like kept on going kept on going
what take your
pig take a
pig
oh what what
what just not that one obviously
eh oh what about this one how about a
window bloody show
off well I have to show off my combos
now now that I understand how to use
them unleash the full potential well we
found the Imperial
Garrison right were the royalists left
them
oh he hi nice to see you guys let me
show you my
combos this is just another
showcase you know what to do boy of my
six
skills hey what was
that
you're going to see that magic burst a
lot get used to it don't let them get
away sick of
to you know what to do boy get a
point sick of
tole
w
all right let's go woohoo
Yahoo
okay moving
on oh can I make one confession to you
guys I couldn't do it yesterday I
couldn't do it I didn't cook and I I I
don't know I was I was really not proud
of
myself
instead what I ate or tried to eat is a
thing that's really
famous in Japan like an instant food
that I received from um eoha and Fuki
Senai when I actually I didn't tell you
right
I met them in the
studio and Fuki Senai had like a
million yeah okay that's what I thought
a million uh
like poofs of that collab the the
sponsorship that they
had did you see
it every what's been going
on they have that Dawn other one what's
it called
again there's the the green one and the
red
one and they were like oh do you want
one we have so many I'm like oh okay
actually never a this
before because it always freaked me out
when I was younger thinking that you
know it says like Kon is
likeon noodles directly translated and I
thought that there's like actual fox
meat in there and for the other one yeah
I thought it was Tanuki actual raccoon
meat in there not I I don't know how
seriously I thought it was in there but
I was like what
if maybe maybe that's in there I don't
want to try it's actually just tofu um
but that's why I always like stayed away
from it and this was going to be the
first time I was going to eat it I took
it and I brought it to Austria and I
thought this will be my emergency food
yesterday last
night oh welcome back oh strong
boy why
no why no HP on the top
right
[Music]
ninja you know what to do boy is that a
bug
[Music]
sick of
tole give them all you've got
for you know what to do eat
this over
here
oh sick tole keep your distance
boy yeah but uh I made it and I didn't
really like it going to be
honest you know what to going over here
so then I was like well boy what I
do now I just threw in some Frozen um
fries into the oven and ate them and
just kept on being ashamed with how
pathetic I
am I could have
just I could have just took oh all
you've got
boy
woo get him
boy there
boy you know what to do boy my my thumb
is like kind
of like numb this
point you know what to do for
me sick of
tole but that was actually uh my first
time meeting
needa H you talked a little bit get she
so
sweet she was using the streaming
Bove oh oopsie and I was going to I was
going to use it after her for a little
bit she was so sweet like she was
opening up the programs that I was going
to do for me and setting things up she
was like oh yeah and you have to do this
and this and I'm like oh my God blame
you don't have to do all this thank you
so
[Music]
sweet over
here made me think I need to hit her up
for collabo cuz she was so so
sweet which way should I
go there's a door over there I think I
came for the thick door but there's one
here it's like a
oh like a a dead end thing there boy
don't let them get
away it's over
get
him okay dog says go outside
but but there's some stuff
here like a chest ooh and it still goes
up
though did I come from here and I just
didn't like see
the how fast do enemies respawn in this
game do they respawn at
all no I didn't put the chicken in the
freezer now I want to ask you guys um if
yesterday was the day uh it said it
should be used
by can I still use half measures were
you Benedict they they don't respawn
didn't know what hit
them it's been in the
fridge one day you should be fine smell
it okay do you think I can smell that
the alarm sound the alarm all is bloody
running should be fine right
Monday I'm so
pathetic but at least like today before
the stream I I I cleaned the kitchen so
I don't have to do that like before
cooking
now so that's one big step take already
and can go straight into K into uh
cooking it was um used buy I think not
Best
[Music]
Buy cuz hellofresh I think always uses
used
by if it feels slimy still after rinsing
it off and trying
it
yeah it will definitely be properly
cooked
for no it wasn't
Frozen just
cold used by means it should be thrown
out
H yeah don't people say don't wash
it isn't that what people say to not
wash it
actually wouldn't risk
it damn now now I'm not sure
attacking an opponent from the front
while it is guarding will deal no damage
circle to the rear ah yeah no problem
certain basic abilities such as burning
blade and charged magic as well as
iconic ability such as can easily break
okay have them seems they were
expeced
say sick
tole
give them all you've
got it's over okay there's so much more
action now compared to the
beginning stay
down I like it new enemies
approach
[Music]
okay get him
boy
get him sick them
tole don't let them get
away a razor to trim The Moldy hair off
what oh oh I don't think it has gotten
that
far you know what to
[Music]
do here
get him
boy stay
[Music]
down you H it's over how many
more you know what to do boy come here
let me do AOE for you give them all
you've got
[Music]
boy we just go fly in the sky
yay keep your distance boy get
[Music]
him get him
boy if it greets you with
Mommy you guys are so
weird what was stay
down get him
sick of tole over
here oh oh I didn't know you can level
up in the middle of the battle oh no it
wasn't the middle of the battle I
thought I just saw like half of its HP
was still
there okay let me massage my right thumb
because my hands
hurt
okay
it wasn't
Frozen I know I should always like
freeze
it I think of it too
[Music]
late the only way is through the chapel
then greater must have plans for us I'm
good thank
you a controller with a turbo
button
well I think
maybe I don't know the the grip is just
not that comfortable I guess speaking of
grip speaking of a controller I should
connect it to charge
it what the hell happened here
if I fully cook it it'll probably be
fine
right yeah thegg are bit isn't it
painful after a while do I seem so
desperate as to grovel at the feet of a
false
god I was waiting for
you not for too long I
hope okay okay T all this for a midnight
chat well let's CH then where are the
men and women you took from loswing you
mean where's the dominant well L shall
be requiring his Services
indefinitely come back to me sedus I
need you think of all the things we can
create
together the world that we can build you
need me dog is so angry needs me I'm all
for building a new world just not his
that bastard's dreams are as Twisted as
his promises are false and I want no
part of them King Barnabas saved you and
this is how you speak of him have you no
shred of
loyalty what to a leader who'd use
me like he uses you you know nothing of
me sfus you're right I don't know who
you are
anymore or what you
want I only know know what you used to
say that you were tired of
running that you just wanted to be free
free of it
all you weren't lying to me then so what
changed what made you think you had to
sacrifice who you were to get what you
wanted sacrifice I use my talents to my
advantage and you would tell me there is
shame in that if there's no shame why do
you feel so sorry for yourself arousing
speech Lord Commander I Was a Fool to
believe you might have
changed the only person I feel sorry for
is
you I can't do this
anymore
uh-uh uhoh she's going to
morb stand back she's going to morb
stand between our leash and his
dream then you leave me no choice oh I
love those clothes of goodbye sadus
oh
oh she's
moring yeah she's I mean definitely
moring
oh stand
back explain that to
me how do she do
that she's not a
[Music]
dominant
move she
is I thought the thing that the Garuda
was just her summoning something CU she
herself wasn't
a oh my god let's
go I want to see her in full full
Glory why don't they go full out maybe
it's hard to
control wind and thunder is
C beautiful match isn't
it yeah B oh oh oh oh
oh um really
nobody I didn't go there to stop it
great
why finish
them oh I still don't get to fight
her all
right two two of them at least it's not
three against
one give them all you've got
boy get him boy
quick get
him W you know what get him boy get
him oh she send me flying
please get
him over here
no I want to I think I want to fight the
other
one
oh wait wait wait how do I re refocus on
this one there we
go sick of to I think I would be would
be nice to focus on one first you know
what to do oh
why is it why is she so passive
actually maybe because there's two they
made them less dangerous for
[Music]
me they're dancing for
me oh uh
oh that's some cool
[Music]
don't let them get
away get him boy you know what to do
[Music]
boy
oh
get him
boy
oh sick
oh keep your distance
boy over
here oh yeah bet I can't
see
a
ah it's getting
serious oh
[Music]
okay yeah
by you know what to do boy sick of tole
you know what to do
boy there
[Music]
boy not this time don't let them get
away there's a good boy get him boy
[Music]
no
yeah sick of tole how did I do that big
magic burst
again over here there boy over
here not this
time give them all you st
for I think I might die once oh God
on that'll help oh was that a
heal it's not like a big
[Music]
heal get
him get
[Applause]
him
I'm out of
[Music]
potion sick of
tole don't let them get away a it
doesn't reach
[Music]
them oh I have
nothing sick of
tole get him
I'm going to
die sick of
[Music]
tole get him
boy well done
to
my my fingers are so weak at this
[Music]
point get them boy give them all you've
got for
me sick of
tole I can't I can't survive like this
she doesn't look happy to
come on what are we going to do
tole 6
hp
too
too oh it's like a continuous
heal K distance for there's no
way
10 HP and the dream I wonder if there is
there a checkpoint that's with
oh I would appreciate not having to do
the whole fight cuz it's kind of
long okay uh is there only one no
there's I think two
time or no there is only one okay okay
well then then it's
easy
hey don't let them get
away she can do the same
[Applause]
attack keep your distance
boy sick
to
[Music]
get
him well I don't have to be so careful
now with so many potions and only one
opponent
thankfully give them all youve got for
[Music]
don't let them get
away you know what to do
boy get
him I'm dodging that one surprisingly
well though
generally keep me distant
not this time sick of
tole don't let them get
away get
him there
[Music]
boy what
the sick too there boy you know what to
do
boy
I think I got to take a break soon from
this game
[Music]
today just let just end it ladies you
got don't let them get
away there you
go sua and Chira slain slay girl
yes burb ladies a clouded
eye used in crafting all right cool
stuff I probably should yeah I would
love to play more but this game actually
the time pass is kind of slowly while
playing it
surprisingly and my
fingers
H I'm coming up to a good stopping point
ooh
okay Sid are you all right cut scene cut
scene cut scene do I look all
right he you're not telling me he will
die
here
nah no no no no no he looks will be on
her way to collect the dominant if she
hasn't
already
you can't afford to let them leave
remember she has wings you don't what
about
you before or after I catch my
breath
sorry come on
tole
what
what are we leaving him to
die I'll walk it off it's fine you grow
wi
sh stop climbing those
stairs sit here sit guard okay it
doesn't sound like he's dying
okay all
right
he's got the plot armor right we're just
taking nap am I going the right way yeah
okay she must be here somewhere thanks
tole
potion oh that way but what about here
too see too you need an asense for
Treasure too but I guess I have the
sense for treasure you have the sense
for is there a chest
yes for direction o wait wait a second I
wanted to um oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I should put on the the the the
freaking
um necklace what was that no that's a
belt
oopsie no that's a
belt but what is this
though Heat Wave damage sheesh but I
wanted to put this on and that would
have helped me in the previous fight a
lot
actually uh wait should I put on the
thing the heat wave
damage what's Heat Wave again I use it a
lot probably right right right which one
was that what a suck he got a
SK why did I not wear it
before questions and over
questions to waiting for me the
withdrawal has been
signal cure some Opps will cast cure
spells to heal their allies defeat the
spell casters first thanks for showing
me who the spellcaster is ahead of
time get him boy wait that's not
him where I change ah no how do I change
Target you little
there
boy keep your distance more of keep your
distance that'll help I cannot
see no that's still not him
wait where is he I keep on losing
track get him boy did I kill
him you know what to do boy get
him I think he's dead you know what to
do
boy okay okay at some point
I killed him I don't know when it was
chaotic where were you when Hilo was
killed I have no
idea no
idea
oh no wait I want to get
there is there a different way I'm
running out of
tower oh
here
what where is the sparkly thing lady
wants us gone before Sunrise I guess I
passed this all I Call ar
rest give them all you've
got it's
over brutal I think that went into his
crot over
here but you know when things are going
so fast you don't really have the the
YuYu to check where your sword is
piercing through sorry dude
didn't mean to be that brutal oh oh
that's the item that I
saw nice my
potions any final
words there boy my final words I usually
and say in you should know
that have you not been
listening over
here you don't
[Music]
want there is over
loose and German we
say where what is this a door it is but
not one I can pass
through oh such a good
boy oh so many people supposed to
bead oh I see a Healer wait I'm I'm I'm
doing it
wrong don't let them get away I think to
wait there's another one hey that's so
stupidly
rude get
him King a distance for there's like a
rainbow collateral clone damage
indicator on the right side when I get a
lot of people I
think give them all you've got boy looks
pretty well done
to get him boy I love that
attack you know what to it takes so a
little bit to activate it but it's all
right K get distance stay
down get him
boy she better not have flown
away you say that as if we are
close he can't heal me now
huh oh who are you you
special H not another one of those
ah don't let them get
[Music]
away you know what to do
for
to
ah holy
[Music]
not this
time uh Ya by I hope I get some more
potions after
this oh my God what my WS
[Music]
B
oh thank
God over
here keep your distance boy get him
boy he still has so much HP
though hey don't do that you know what
to do boy
[Music]
thanks
boy there
boy you know what to do
boy over
here get
him over here get him
boy don't let them get away
get him 10 T sick of
tole get him
boy sick of
tole get him boy you know what to do boy
sick him tole get
him what is he going to do what is he
going to do what is he going to do yeah
okay
oh my God all my
potions oh we walked outside there boy
we're on the balcony now
to sick him
tole you know what to do
boy keep your distance boy I got
you I got you it's over
bastard these guys are so
tough catch me outside how about
that H all my
potions
man oh please be be
potion a high potion good good good more
please more
yes they're so tank yeah and
[Music]
fast that's
enough that
boy are we when am I ending this when is
this good place to end that you guys
mentioned maybe after the upcoming fight
that might may or may not be
actual icon Garuda oh oh I feel like
we're almost there finally oh we are
there but I only have free in one
potions I might I should just offer
myself to be killed right away
way
M but okay I'll
try y y
y I confess I expected more from the old
man I'll try to get as far as I can but
chances are I'll die and less from you
this is the second time you've bested my
sisters men of your talents are rare
indeed why cost your lot with such
undesirable if it is the Hearth you long
for you will find more than enough worms
under my
wings you know exactly what I
want hand over the dominant and I'll
leave you in peace you would dare to
make demands of
me know your place little
lamb fo is a Shepherd who heeds every
bleed of the
flock and I will suffer yours no
longer must I spell it out for you
brandid no one is listening no one at
all we are
listening come little lamb to the
slaughter with you shake hands shake
shake shake shake shake
shake all right uh
what uh okay she's a already a fast
boy get him there will be a lot of Miss
spamming sick of
to get up sick of tole over here already
reading her like a
[Music]
book you know what to do
boy
get him
boy you know what to
do get
him get him
really oh hey hey
hey
that there
boy get him
keep your distance
boy sick him tole get
him get him
boy there
boy get them all we've got
boy sh
to Final Fantasy battles the one time
where takanashi kiar will shut the
up
over
here sick of
tole wait for HP there's no way she'll
get like a uh she'll probably turn into
like
her sick of
tole there's no way she'll have like a
second
stage
or she'll just fly away and be like I
see you next
time you're not worth my
[Music]
time
oh what am I supposed to press
uh where is he our word task again why
is this happy
[Music]
music
why is music so
happy you for
that there we go there we go priming
face two is there face
three it's so
positive
hey okay but phase two rent really
really
well
Dodge this dodge this oh nice
Doo
du
hey hey hey hey do I have to fight
without
do trry all you
like there's no one she looks so cool
when she's
[Music]
primed
oh yeah I'm finding about
do oh she's so much
faster out of my
sight
[Music]
that three
levels oh okay I another one have to
wait
[Applause]
for get
[Music]
her
um how
long
[Music]
back
sprink I can't help but the PGM is just
like like it's like a reconciling type
of music it's
weird
oh yeah fre
time ah
no this
time a I
shouldn't I'm going to die and only have
one potion
left
oh I'm so searingly going
down this
time I'm not even I'm not even going to
think about
when time to join your pet oh
oh
she yeah yeah yeah strike me down let me
redo oh my God I'm F I'll buring it
together
okay I didn't even see what I had to
press I just like out of stay down out
of automatic
[Music]
uh yeah I I thanks for all the
cinematics but I'm not I'm not going to
make
[Music]
it you're giving me a great opening here
though don't touch me okay okay you
disgust me
sorry I Tred to be a not so disgusting
person but I guess I can't help it CU
you like explain to me a little bit
furer like give me some feedback what
exactly makes me like so disgusting to
you I would like to work on
[Music]
it improve myself to be more of your
liking
oh really you're going to pull this one
now yeah right after that oh you
you
[Music]
for
nothing
yeah just kill me thank you where's my
checkpoint I got really
far you dodged a perfect amount not too
much not too little it's disgusting are
you sure some people might disagree with
that
[Music]
oh for me oh wow it is that
after that this is phase two so even
wow very generous too
slow you disgust
[Music]
me in Japanese she's probably
saying
is she going to do the six time Combo
yeah her
you can't reach too
far
oh you I'm so
[Music]
tired G
what Gathering
clouds she's sucking me
in you're
mine
[Music]
okay
thank God okay I was hoping for
[Music]
that
thanks for the pink Sid
J oh my
God too
slow
W
[Music]
combo
oh right there was something off of
[Music]
that deadly embrace
what will I
push don't kill
[Music]
me bad
luck St going back here recover I'm so
croud oh
man Man's Best Friend
a oh man makes me love dog
girl um
let go slit her bro SL
her
slice you
good how long until she say don't touch
me don't tou me don't dare tou me
I'm going to call your
manager get him
boy yeah there you go I'll kill you I'll
kill you
both you know what to take oh who who
who
[Applause]
what she's
insane she's moring
again keep your distance
boy
okay Cal your
T oh she girl get him there boy sick to
openings
here that was
to
[Music]
can
I oh what happened to the deadly
[Music]
Embrace I not get him
boy
ah
tornado how about
tornado her aim is kind of off
there
how did I stagger
her I didn't do
anything Ah that's ground man
give them all you've got
[Music]
boy wait I thought I was like in her
grab grip still I was
confused don't let them get
away don't don't grab me this
time no I
can't give them all you've got
[Music]
boy I don't want to die now please no no
no no no
no
no I'm so
close is it the same checkpoint as
[Music]
before no thank God okay cuz
boy is this fight actually challenging
or am I just stupid I mean you have I I
will admit that after 6
hours it's really since like a few hours
ago the pain in my fingers too
[Music]
too
SL this one is so difficult to
die you know what to
do don't let them get
[Music]
away for me H every single
[Applause]
[Music]
time not this
time not the kind of Twister game I
wanted to play with you lady I did not
yet
to there
boy don't have to get
away sick of
tole sick of
to oh
come get him
boy oh
ah it hit me for
[Music]
once let me get to you
please no it went straight into
that it's
okay oh what that must have been my dog
like absolute genius dog keep your
distance
boy there boy
[Music]
sick of tole
ow get him boy you know what to do
boy get him boy sick of
tole
go I literally like waiting for
it oh I used both oh get him boy
I'm waiting for it and I still don't get
it disgus
me get him just Spam just Spam
tole oh for God I'm so
done
I could do that so much
better but hand
H let's watch a cool cut
scene you or but a
branded I I she bleeding from her
eyes how did you do it oh how did you
even survive how oh the knuckles the
answer is simple Benedict oh hi Sid GL
you're alive fighting for something he
believed in shut up why aren't you dead
because of Love we've played your
games now tell me where he is who
what are
you do I scare you
uh- what am I taking the icon out of her
it's quite long how can you do that why
does he why does he know how to do it
why
how did she just steal her
powers wow
so confused like what the
oh do be I come wi now what's
happening
sh
she's still so confused oh
eat no don't let her
go don't let her go enough of
this
what it's gone it's not yours
anymore
mm-
she she's
gone what what's H
happening oh she's going to be give her
back nope give her back nope give her
back my
lady her world's going to follow
apart where is she and she'll be useless
to the
[Music]
king she what have you done to
me what have you done I mean look at me
my lady we need you here must
have even a strong emotional connection
to her too what the hell is going on you
get like she must have been born with it
too right
so suddenly after all this
time losing the one thing
that you for your whole life you took it
from
her how' you do that how' you how the
did you
what what the did you do me I
hope the barar is found a way
out it's like the thing that probably
for her to find her this place is ready
to laughs it i' rather not be here think
like she's nothing if your dominant
started this fire and I'm betting he did
he'll be long
gone damn it all going to have
a
breakdown
meltdown just like stealing a little
chef hat no I don't need that stupid
chef hat hello
e what was
that I created a diversion as commanded
Your Grace The Villages escaped excuse
me there is lore to see a man named
margar a mysterious man that many
believe to be a dominant of
fire he is rarely seen without his heavy
robe nor his loyal attendant the two
journey together far and wide across the
realm to an unknown
end
servant of a man who goes by the name
Lord my res
okay Imperial stronghold located along
the South and fringes of
SE in
confusion as should we
yes
if someone stole my YouTube channel
started streaming in my place
yeah I wouldn't get it back and I would
have nothing left but not quite because
I can still build it back up again she
cannot build her Garuda back
up no
G nice
morning and here come the Cavalry
itching to butcher the bastards who made
him miss their morning GRL
H come on if they catch us leaving a
burning care people might jump to
conclusions
right okay wings of
change n the power of wind oh
Clive has claimed a portion of the
icon gita's Essence the tuning with
gitaa not only changes the element
aspect of C's magic spells but also
allows the access to several new iconic
abilities such as go gouge a deadly
flurry of talents that can tear Talons
that can tear uh into an opponent for
multiple hits ability details can be
found BL blah
blue let me watch that
again ooh
uh-huh uh deadly Embrace oh can be used
to draw smaller lighter enemies toward
CLI oh the action can also topple large
enemies that become partially staggered
when their will goge reaches 50%
toppling an enemy in this man can deal
sign
okay brain hord L2 to cycle between
currently a tuned icons in real
time allowing for more VAR
assault okay
L2 cool
down
uhuh benedicta said You' taken her
power still okay
I think I
do brain empty brain h no more no no no
we'll look at this in tomorrow no don't
show me now sh don't explain to me now
tell me tomorrow tell me tomorrow h ah
no don't show me
let me go to system I don't want to have
any more input in my
brain we didn't save a single time
dangerous this I saved now right yes
okay
tomorrow
[Music]
more am my first
save
I I don't know I thought maybe there's
like some Auto saves or I don't know I
felt fine without
saving I live on the edge thank you
narissa I am
exhausted I thought I could read
super chats but I'm
exhausted and I wanted to go to a good
point to end
it so fast what do you think awesome
love it playing it until the end no
matter what I will do it
I love it um but it's very tiring on my
hands I don't know if it's the
controller but I have a normal
PlayStation what's it called D dual
something dual sense or something like
that
controller I think the controls are not
ideal I feel like something that's more
like you know for example pressing with
directions like having variety in the
text through pushing one button and then
just a direction or so would have been
maybe easier I don't know maybe I'm the
only one e I've heard some people having
issues with PS5 controller really but
that's the only
way that's DMC controls yeah a lot of
games have such a
system you
relate this more
the Pro
Controller I don't
know is it so much better you can remap
the buttons I but I'm already getting
used to these ones I don't know I'll
think about
it generally generally it's
fine I'll probably
be able to have faster battles when I
fight more
efficiently with better
combos they make smaller PS5
controllers are you saying maybe my
hands are too small and these are not
made this controll let me compare to my
switch
controller do they
touch oh the switch controller is
definitely smaller
but or at least
like from the length it's like
similar but something about them is
different it doesn't look as
bulky and this is a Pro Controller I
think right is it yeah my Pro Controller
is just not as bulky looking I think I
don't
know SM SM by my
hands SM SM not those hands from the
King it's Joy CL
no yeah I think you're supposed to weave
single triangle after Mele
attacks for all yeah yeah
yeah eh
yeah try to take off the Precision do
yeah I don't know I'm kind of like
missing some Basics somehow I
think
um it's a lot to
process but still good you know I'm
still good you know I I do think Tales
of arise a battle
system uh helped indeed somebody said
that in the chat it it feels like from
how fast it is pretty
similar and the the movement and
everything partially the controls too
yeah
very
similar so tomorrow we're playing it
again tomorrow Sunday same time I'm
going to set up the stream right
afterwards and I will cook
something after the stream no matter
what I will cook
something I have
to ah members re broadcast oh good
question m m s this
[Music]
there I wanted it to be a good time
for both Na and S
EA oh wait I can just uh I don't have to
be awake for it right if I do it as a
Premiere Premier
premere then I can just play it
automatically and I can tell JMA to turn
it on private when it's
done I think I'll do that cuz otherwise
I'll have to be awake for pushing the
button sometime in like 700 a.m. go back
to sleep make sure I wake up again when
it's
ending that's stupid can do Premier
member streams H me like a video I think
so yeah I think so pretty
sure could also Loop it a couple of
times ah until I wake
up kind of funny
idea okay guys uh thank you for watching
my brain is fried but I really like it
so far so tomorrow next um I'll try to
maybe not do too much tomorrow maybe
just 5 hours because apparently this
game is frying my brain and my hands we
just do a bit little bit shorter session
and then read super chats I must read
super
chats sounds like a plan okay but it's
just like difficult in RPGs I just want
to get as far as possible I want to do
it make it into a long stream to be
efficient and yeah get as much progress
in one stream as
possible it's tough m
oh well who knows how it will go
tomorrow I went longer than others in my
first session
endurance that's just the Curiosity
curiosity killed the Wawa and her
hands thank you
guys yeah yeah
yeah it was fun it was fun thank you for
joining me and in Germany
see you tomorrow same time same channel
same place same W same game and same you
you hopefully I'll see you there uh also
oh I think that does 3D showcase is
tomorrow so guys oh I'm not trying to
like hint on anything but just support
her because we love ID girls in this
neighborhood yeah it is
right so if you're awake go and watch
[Music]
it you know
nothing we love
[Music]
idea I
forgot I learned I love you now I
forgot
ID
papaa
papaa not that one
okay en hope you
[Music]
byebye
oh my God smooy immediately entered the
room
hi she
no hi hi oh flop
[Music]
a
she will not be hugged By
[Music]
Me
O
[Music]