[Music]
no
that sounds like a god the god of gods
uh
yeah my god is ancient as [\h__\h] man
yeah
spooky spooky for halloween baby god of
god
[Music]
to me on this holy god night my ancient
wisdoms um let's see here's my ancient
wisdom i don't know how to play
minecraft but we're going to try today
that's a lie
i mean you've become a lot better from
what i've heard and seen
er
maybe
thanks though doing i'm doing my best
but you know it's
this is a game that oh man everyone's
really g
[Music]
oh they're saying hello to you everyone
in their own way ohio
oh it's not ohio though uh
pumbaa
we
no i said i said the regular one i i
decided not to be cringy for two seconds
anyway would have been cute though
because
all of them would try to read it on
their stream and be like kong bun ritu
oh good idea
i have so many i have so many melons
oh that's good all right well kelly um
today what are we doing
we're gonna get you some wings girl
[Laughter]
yeah i'm excited you want wings do you
want those
i like
wings
elytra yeah i keep seeing you know like
fly down from the sky like a wizard from
the future and i'm like yeah i want that
where are you right now um i'm hanging
out in the main central area um of like
the the portal i guess okay near one
second stay there you betcha yeah that's
good take as many melons as you can get
right now here we go
we go to the end we we're gonna do a
little bit preparation you betcha i'm
ready
yes and uh when i'm coming to you also
with my wings
[Music]
you're not done yet go in here to go to
the crafting table and then type in
smell
melon yeah
melon and then the big one uh-huh
do shift shift left click on it make as
many as possible oh the big ones
okay
what will they repeat that a couple
times what will they do
uh it will make you instead of
watermelon slices you will have a lot of
big watermelons and those we need for
trading in phoenix then oh
i have 44.
should i get four four okay make some
more make some more okay i mean yeah
i'll just i'll tell iris um i mean
they're actually being made a lot right
now so maybe it'll be fun yeah yeah
don't worry about it i've taken millions
of melons out of here
and melon
see what you did there
i i see that little that little trick
that you did there with the words
and uh all of those chickens in my
inventory are vegan guys don't worry
about it don't worry about it i wanted
to give something back to summer
uh brb you do the melons and i do the
giving back to sana
gotcha
[Music]
all right guys check it check out all my
melons leave all valuables in the cave
of course yeah check out cali's melons
check out her melons hey
huh you said it hey
i didn't say nothing madam
i i was talking about the fruit chad
what do you say did you say it first you
did oh don't you know what chat's gonna
say though
this area this is looking sick onsen's
so good i can't wait to completely
finish it we will finish it at some
point there's a phenomena
the carnival nah the carnival and the
onsen i'm planning on doing another
endurance
but even though it's not finished like
everyone was already super impressed by
it
i'm happy they liked it i got all the
cool like stone rooms down in the down
in the little cave are you by the onsen
now i'm taking a rest i'm taking a
little sleepy sleep oh oh i will do too
oh [\h__\h] yeah okay sleep slips okay good
night nighty noodles
good night
[Music]
melons as possible right yes ma'am let
me count how many i got um 64 64 44. i
don't know how to do math but that's
over 100. and all of those are big melon
stacks right yeah over 150 yeah i've got
a lot of them we're gonna
one second i gotta give back the beds to
bales because i accidentally stole her
bed
and i got lots of cooked rabbit by the
way um from paducah senpai and she gave
me 60 diamonds
yeah six feet yeah there's a lot of
diamonds yeah i don't know what to do
with them i remember didn't she say
something about being your sugar mama
yeah yeah she learned that nah with the
berries
okay we're fine look at that berries
right you get stuck in them oh yeah i
kind of where i see that coming i'm i'm
by the main fountain um okay yeah stay
there she gave me a lot of like you're
like an excited
mouse running around yeah i can't wait
i wanna okay
the place that we're going to today is
pretty uh
dangerous okay
in many ways
oh okay so what should i do you gotta be
super focused and careful and just do
what i do focus is my middle name i'm
always super focused guys haha isn't
that right chad i'm the queen of focus
let's go
all right i mean we're gonna go to
phoenix then first and trade your melons
in for uh emeralds and the emeralds are
going to trade in for
uh
some armor for you cool
okay
let me see where is that
know that we have the
and the barrels around here we got the
minecart yeah maybe in the back the
front back barrels got it
okay
um okay
let's go
oh rolling rolling rolling rolling what
so
angry
it's slow no you gotta go over the
the red tracks in order to become yeah
faster zuma
move there we go
by the way i didn't even say kitkat
yeah we kind of didn't we kind of just
jumped right in how i guess we should
introduce ourselves whoo
who is
who are you
kiara
um what do i do uh
i stream
and i make
something akin to music sometimes
i've already seen everything i need to
see yeah it's like
i guess i do that my brain's pretty dead
we've been i've been doing a lot of
streams lately
um but feeling good feeling good i'm on
a i'm on a grind
[Music]
that was powerful and
how much uh did that do i was only about
a heart and a half was you know a lot ah
yeah i wasn't even aiming for you maybe
if i would aim for you it would do my ah
let's go i gotta i gotta store away
these diamonds like a dragon sit on them
like oh should we go to yeah that's
important let's go to your house first
uh to store them away yup because i will
lose these
i will lose these diamonds
a whole stack of diamonds that's just
pretty
pretty nice vampire very kindly gave
them to me
beautiful very nice
i know
you're so kind
i
i arrived at your house before you
oh quick is it because you could fly
no i just ran
oh
wow that makes sense like
he hates throw my diamonds away
i don't need this [\h__\h] yeah that's just
the only chest you have no i've got a
bunch of chests it's just they're very
cluttered um
oh yeah what should i uh should i store
everything valuable away i wonder
yes like my diamond sword
basically what we need to bring is good
armor and
good food which i've tried to take care
of before stream a little bit like okay
we might be able to get some more okay
and
i will also bring another chest
and um i will also bring
us some shulker chests but we'll find
even more there what you could actually
bring with you is
um those two stacks of cobblestone in
your chest in that chest over there okay
there's no stability still um actually
yeah
two stacks of that
and
uh
wait what was i gonna say do you have
any ah
no never mind okay that's fine
now
follow me
oh yeah
lead the way should i get a pickaxe do i
need like tools and [\h__\h] or ah yeah yeah
yeah bring your tools like a pickaxe
yeah and
um
and the sword okay let's see oh yeah uh
i will
give you oh do you have a bow but
probably you don't really have a good
one probably i just assume i don't
really use bows very often but i can use
them so
i can use them i just don't use them
often ah
and a shield do you have a shield
no but i can make one i need iron dang
it let me go run to the iron farm real
quick
i can make all this stuff i just for
some reason i didn't have it uh already
which is odd to me because i usually
have a gazillion pickaxes i have more
than i need usually so
oh i could i could give you uh
i could give you
um um uh pick axes and stuff too or we
could get we could get decent ones in
phoenix down as well
thank you no worries i think oh my
goodness am i making all these new
advancements because um
it's a new server yeah because the
server connected yeah that means like
all
all of our advancements got reset but
the japanese ones didn't get reset hey
it's pretty wild here let me go and make
it real quick huh i could have sworn my
crafting table where'd it go did i move
my crew what are you making right now
um i'm gonna make a pickaxe and a shield
ah i can oh pickaxe you don't need to
make because we're gonna get a better
one than what you're probably making
okay add phoenix then
but the shield yes yes needs the shield
okay let me find a crafting table that i
know we must have somewhere
i have no clue where my crafting table
went what the [\h__\h]
oh yeah yeah that's so weird
you'd think there'd be just one
all right maybe i can make a crafting
table should i
do i have
should i give this one to cali
another infinity block it would be nice
no it's okay don't give me your your
nice expensive things i will probably
lose
we definitely need a good ball
i'm going to eat his house oh there it
is
do i have the levels i maybe do
oh
[Music]
maybe shouldn't put infinity on this one
power two punches one i'm breaking two
that's that sounds i don't really need
it
lame
okay i made the shield
okay
i'm gonna make you a
infinite bowl well really
the cool thing about that is that you
only need one arrow in your inventory
and you can shoot forever
with that one whoa
that sounds cool
what do you want to name it callie
um okay let me think let me think of
something super clever
um
[Music]
space
okay what does that mean it means no it
means uh it's an ancient language
okay i will name it that yeah it's the
language of the gods
eth
arigato gozaimasu
but you can dream right
that i blessed my senpai with the
ancient language well i just saw you out
there yeah one second stay where y'all
stand where you are okay i will give you
ath
yeah
thank you and
there it is
and uh
you only need one but i'll give you a
couple arrows thank you how is something
like this allowed to exist what the [\h__\h]
yeah it's super cool you just have to
have the arrow somewhere in your
apartment it doesn't need to be in the
main task bar at all just somewhere
apartment in your inventory uh-huh wow
and uh the ball you know how to use a
ball minecraft like this right okay
yeah yeah yes oh wow that is strong
yeah
whoo
nice thank you for the strong bow
i'll give you this stack of
fried chicken
thank you for our journey so now let's
go to phoenixton okay i'm ready let's
pick the water the ice express to
phoenix then yeah all right
that thing is super useful i've been
using it a lot it goes so fast just
maybe try try to not lose it okie dokie
i won't i won't lose it at all whenever
whenever you're like building something
i guess you could just store it
somewhere else yeah you betcha all right
please understood about understood
be sure there you go all right ride with
me okay oh i can get inside right
yes right click yeah
oh your wings are really pretty well
what happened here that huge white thing
down there
is that who built that
super close to i could
wait is your dog following you oh hey
dog is that your dog why is it hurting
what what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what
oh yeah
what are you little [\h__\h] let me grab
everything what's your problem it's not
my dog wait it's not a dick attack you
did it what the [\h__\h]
all right let me get rid of it attacking
you too no
what is it
literally i'm so confused
oh because you hit me
wow
now it's now the dog's unprotective
no get out of the
oh my god how
you can stick them up
i picked up all your stuff by the way um
okay
oh my doggy can you please go away can i
get my dog to like not um yeah you gotta
go back to your apartment and then make
him sit where your apartment is inside
otherwise people will follow when he's
not sitting
all right come here poochie
oh goodness sorry that my i accidentally
sicked my dog honey
oh no problem what the [\h__\h]
it came out of like a second dimension
to like come after you yeah yeah they
they actually teleport when you're too
far away
yeah if you don't make them sit down
they'll teleport
so i can have a whole group of dogs just
like attack uh my enemies
yeah incredible exactly
wow well i learned something new
so are you at your house right now i'm
going back
okay
wait is this phoenix done oh [\h__\h] this
is phoenix then hold on
oh you went the wrong way yeah can i
just make the dog sit like the dog isn't
following me anymore by the way
oh
okay well you can just make him sit
there for now i guess okay are you on
the highway no i i went down to
phoenixton
oh okay wait i'm coming okeydokey i'm
gonna chill with your villagers hello
there's a big squidward noses
i'm on my way
i'll wait for you all to talk is
that was odd that was odd that he just
like sat down in the boat like all right
i own this [\h__\h] now that was very weird
he's lucky that i only have an arrow and
and a bow and no error right now
i don't even remember
hating that dog
okay i have arrived in phoenix then and
hey welcome
welcome back to your place let me tell
you everything maybe i okay
let's see you know what's my stuff yes a
lot uh hot wheels yes
yeah
paper
uh your crafting table pumpkin
um
here this is your bow
stream sparks bow
um regularly i actually had yeah i had
two bows in it yeah fireworks then your
armor your diamond armor your shovel
your eggs and then uh you had a diamond
sword uh uh usaken keybind sword
um and then a pickaxe from pecora senpai
and then
um
and then another bow yeah yeah and then
yeah yeah pumpkin pie food and then yeah
uh more chicken chicken for you
um but i think you had more hang on i
need to split it up no i gave you the
almost full stack and uh i had a little
bit left as well okay gotcha
that's fine that's fun here here um and
then there's spider eye something and
then oh yeah uh some boots and i think
uh that's okay
yeah thank you
no problem i'm here to help i'm helpful
in minecraft
oh i feel good i think
why you're expensive what's the matter
with you i want to get you also um
feather falling boots if i can find the
right guy
holy [\h__\h] they're expensive is it
because they're tired
we should try to sleep let's go into
this house and
goodnight
can you kick one of these out
oh we oh wow we gotta kind of share it
yeah get off of here you weird not not
you the the villagers are creeping oh
yeah arrows arrows you got to give me
like one arrow oh yeah yeah yeah that's
right it's totally stacked from here
it's fine too here you go
thank you no problem okay
all right
[Music]
but pickaxe we can't look for a good
pickaxe okay as well efficiency do you
know like all of them by name and stuff
uh some of them i give some of them
names so the really good ones useful
ones nice
guys
[Music]
what's pants guy who's probably gone oh
no
there's a chance that my feather falling
boots guy
is
dead oh that's no fun it was like he was
selling boots that um make you take less
damage when you fall on the ground yeah
yeah
and that is pretty good oh that sounds
like it would be useful we can keep up
the search yeah
there are so many villagers here i mean
they could be anywhere
hmm what are you oh this one's just
making up i'm still sorting out stuff
but wait you have watermelons right so
follow me okay
let's go trade those watermelons
basically where we just where that's the
district that has like armor and tools
and all that and that district that you
see on that side the bright one
has like like books like enchanting
books like this dude has for example
loyalty and silk touch and all that yeah
and you see how they can't get out
they're not gonna be able to go to the
other districts because they place this
this trap door here nice so you can
still fruit but they can't yeah it's
really smart
wow so yeah here are the smart boys with
all the books and also uh this dude
sells like lapis lazuli and
blowstone and you can even here you know
how from zombies you get rotten flesh
and you never know what to do with it
yeah you can trade them with him
emeralds
yeah that's very cool cool right wow you
really set up this place super well
yeah okay follow me the third district
is where you can uh trade your
watermelons okay
it's down this road let's go to the
right
do you remember this place actually
kelly huh uh this is not that village
where we for example jump from the
window and into into the water
oh a long time ago right
yeah the the one that we kind of killed
by visiting them yeah we ransacked
everything and ruined their lives yeah i
remember that was fun yeah exactly and i
i uh revived and renovated it wow you
really you came to the map yeah
that's pretty cool yes
what a twist of events i gave someone
a villager the title so look in here uh
ask any of these actually you know what
i
didn't i get a
discount oh yeah oh my god you i i
actually i personally have a disc
discount with one of these guys can you
give me all your stacks of watermelons
i'll give you all the emeralds i get
from it here you go
one
two
three those dough
nice
because normally you get one emerald for
four
what watermelons uh-huh but i currently
have a discount where it's
one ammo for one watermelon so it's way
cheaper
but i gotta wait a little bit because
they got a restack but i already got
wings
emeralds they go
thanks one second thank you respect
please pasta well i'll go with him too
this is a
listener use 12 more one for one i guess
that's pretty a buy i didn't realize
that is because one for one is you know
you want to know how i did that at
discount
am i allowed
i don't like the way that you no no no
it's a good thing actually so um zombies
came into phoenixton village
and attacked my villagers during the
time when there was a lot of japanese
tourists on the server
for some reason they made it in and uh
they attacked some villagers and they
became into they they turned into
zombies uh-huh and then
uh
when the good thing is about that if you
cure them you can't cure them with like
a potion and like a golden apple and all
that yeah and then they will give you
super special discounts but only to the
person who cured them yeah
this game is way deeper than i thought
uh that it was it is
what it is they're all like indebted to
you they like owe their souls to you
wait there's twelve more oh i i threw
them over there thank yous uh he already
restocked twice today now i think they
only restock twice per day so we gotta
wait until
night time actually but hey let's see
it's pretty realistic i suppose
yeah but i wanna see if there's wasn't
there
how many emeralds do we need
ah good question wait what was i going
to get for you i wanted to get those
boots and
and
pants and boots and pants and boots
yeah i guess all kinds of armor do you
don't have any armor at all right now
any diamond armor no ma'am only a
diamond sword that's all good all right
a diamond sword diamond sword is that
does that have any enchantments
let's see
sharpness oh that's a lot of emeralds
sharpness too oh that's at unleash
something yeah
or are these the blacksmiths um
these are the blacksmiths
and [\h__\h]
and you know what how many do we have
right now emeralds 36
okay use this this one where i'm
standing here this dude
if you scroll down he's got a helmet
with protection free and breaking free
okay cool
get that one for now
protection three hang on i'm trying to
access him please let me there we go oh
sorry oh because i was accessing
something no problem um
what am i looking for what's the pits
the protection free uh something
something free from like the the helmet
we'll protect
uh protection
uh hold on
section three helmet helmet yeah yeah
cool ah this one should be good right
should we get this got it diamond just
played for kelly what do you think jet
i'm breaking that's pretty cool
wait who was that
last protection two i'm breaking two not
yes no do you have anything better blast
protection
probably gonna need more emeralds huh
yeah we're gonna get them we still have
a lot of watermelon snails
this one instead
yes wow
projection one on breaking two
you have a special shield
yes i do
actually you know there's like only one
type of shield that you can craft uh-huh
um which is the one that you're carrying
but you can
no but you can decorate them uh
like you can you can you can make like a
million different patterns you can
combine all those patterns and then they
look fancy and my mom she taught me how
to make this phoenix looking shield
that's so cool
wait how many do you have left
nine
nine nine yep
okay for now
ah wait oh that would have been good too
projector protection because they're
gonna get shot but all right we're just
gonna get one of these um
oh wait there's more i feel like a lost
little baby child following around like
my hero like the the 10 year old little
boy who's like falling around
the master that's what i feel like oh ah
i want it to be night i'll i'll check
with the i'll check with the watermelon
guy again yeah see if he can there's
some more melons
we have enough we have enough and
actually i have a [\h__\h] ton of emeralds
at home i'm thinking of getting those
so that way a bit faster okey-dokey
squire yes precisely
okay
yeah i'm your squire
i'm just here to be helpful yeah even
though you already have yeah
they're not restocking yet yeah i'm
impatient i'll give you these you can
rough them up a little bit
maybe maybe it becomes night before i
come back but i'm gonna bring some mmos
you just have a talk with them tell them
to restock or we're gonna kill them okay
we gotta be nice to the villagers tell
them tell them
tell them try to bribe them
yeah i'm trying to get um what am i
trying to get from them
uh i'm wrong you wanna get those
emeralds yeah okay gotcha yeah it looks
like it's out of stock right now um tell
them to restock restock or i'll punch
you with the sword
i'll do it and i won't do that i don't
want to ruin phoenixton but
you're making me angry
oh my panties only we had we huh oh wait
those panties are better aren't they
oh you know what uh wait what about this
one
oh wait i'll just give this one to
callie
this chest plate because that's better i
think than what we have there but i'm
going to repair it
um
anyway can i repair this
uh
panties
you have 60 diamonds don't y'all i do
i'm i'm gonna give you a better chess
play than than what their those dudes
have right now
okay
can you like later give me one diamond
or two in exchange
i mean i have 60 of them so i can give
you a lot of them
nice because i don't have many and i'm
repairing the armor right you're giving
me a lot of free stuff so i mean yeah of
course i'd be happy too
equivalent exchange is what it's all
about
[Music]
i'm down okay stunks
good so that's that's gonna be
it's gonna be mine a little napping it
is it is it getting dark yeah the sun's
starting to set a little bit
oh nice oh my level
yeah they're sleeping right now but i'm
jumping all over the beds and having a
good time it's a slumber party
yeah yeah yeah pillow fight lads come on
wake up
oh they're sleeping with their diamonds
that's kind of weird
all right you know they really don't
trust me
[Music]
i love playing that as a child yeah
that's a fun game
especially when you've got like couches
and chairs and like beds and stuff like
that yeah yeah and then the room gets
super messed up afterwards
sleepy time
okay
i'm going to sleep
on it oh [\h__\h]
no did it go into my elite row it no it
can't be if it's full full exp if it's
full health then it will go into me
right
one second i'm gonna go to sleep in the
moment
yeah okay okay okay okay you'll be able
to see it talk to you
wait i'm not getting exp
huh
give me exp i don't know if you're here
i mean you can kind of see but that's
fine
it's not giving me
my ass
i'm in control
uh
[Music]
you good
yeah i'm uh i'm um
i need some exp right now because i need
to repair um some diamond pants now i
ran out of iron oh well you know
i'm iron
yeah i have a ton of iron they're still
out of stock though for emeralds
oh yeah they take some time in the
morning uh when you do you want to come
over to the blacksmith district yes i'll
give you wait now i have
you're right chat you're right
this is where it is right i'm figuring
out the layout of phoenixton
mm-hmm this place i think
yeah oh no this is where they live just
kidding is this the one that i wanted
here's the iron for you throw to your
face there you go
thank you
[Music]
okay well i have indeed received and
also i will give you now this diamond
chest plate thank you
i'll give you the diamond after the
mission
yeah i can give you stuff no problem and
now you're missing uh boots right boots
okay
let's see what we can get we need some
more
oh wait no i have emeralds what the hell
uh boots boots so we have protection two
boots or
[Music]
uh
death straddle one unbreaking two what
do you think chat which one is
better
oh yeah maybe you can try buying them
don't kelly okay protection protection
okay
you you gotta look at the guy uh-huh uh
wait uh you you probably don't have
i only have nine emeralds yeah i wonder
what i should do okay i'll give you i'll
give you some how much did he need
how much did you need where is he here
uh inside inside there in the corner
there is a dude called
he wants 20 20 emeralds
for
uh
the boots the boots i throw you over
some more thanks i'm getting them okay
okay and then ask that's all you got the
boots yeah
nice you can put them on
you got some new shoes
new shoes
okay and now we're talking yay and i
still have 10 emeralds left what should
i do should we store them
ah wait we can maybe buy
something else ah wait let's let's try
to go get some
decent food we might need some more what
do you think do we need more food i got
29 cooked rabbits and 45 cooked chickens
that's actually quite a lot yeah
hello oh quite a bit where did where did
you go you rascal
uh uh
uh now that's oh we could get golden
carrots
i'm gonna
i'm gonna go get some golden carrots so
fast
more won't hurt
golden carrots i'm gonna go get some
more
what mentioned oh okay okay
you can um wait uh i gave you the melons
right indeed
a 64.
it doesn't look like it oh nope they did
he did oh the the one with the discount
did wait can you give me those back yeah
only one stack is enough for now
thank you you're welcome
did i did i pick it up
no wait i didn't i didn't pick it up oh
i re-picked it up let me throw them
right at your head
oh and the pickaxe oh yeah right we need
a good pickaxe for you
right cause you don't have a good one
right now yeah i was just gonna make one
out of iron but i guess if we're going
to the end i really should have a good
one huh oh cheap
[Music]
yo you're a cheap man i like it
oh man that's a lot of carrots i'm gonna
go grab some more
what a deal okay what a deal
i
will give you hmm
i already have twenty
wait how much food do you have like
which i have
and uh let me list it out for you 45
cooked chickens 29 cooked rabbits
approximately one raw cod and 20
20 golden carrots and five melon slices
20 golden carrots okay let me add on to
that with 26 more golden carrots thank
you i always welcome more tasty
vegetables
i think you're good with food now yeah
sure okay
and uh i give you the rest of the melons
because he's done for the day cool can i
eat these
now the big blocks you can't eat oh you
gotta like if you place the big block
the melon block and then destroy it
again it will like scatter in many uh
slices oh cool
i'm gonna try that
harvested melons
like a summer festival
yeah
let's go okay okay okay and now and now
and now we're gonna get you the pickaxe
and then we go to the end okay okay i'm
ready this has taken more time than
anybody else
that's okay
what's the best pickaxe you guys can
offer yeah
you got no pickaxe you got i'm just
gonna be here smashing melons
yummy
uh the
melons were probably not gonna bring
with us though because oh we're not
gonna eat them they are food but we need
food that fills up a lot uh asap
that's why we're bringing the better
food only so i see you can you can keep
it at home should i give
efficiency too we can add on more things
later this is like for the end
for the end for now that's enough i
would say
we can add some stuff to it
yeah okay
okay pickaxe callie
here there you go
thank you
i will treasure it
and while we're at it
while we're at it
you don't have a diamond axe do you i
don't
okay
so with the watermelon emeralds you also
receive this
diamond pick a diamond axe thank you
wow i'm i'm getting very lucky today
actually this one is good too
now i ran out of emeralds oh no wait i
didn't
i'll give you a diamond shovel too
how can i pay you back for all these
things
no you don't need to basically you paid
for it yourself oh [\h__\h] this would have
would this have been better technically
iris paid for him i guess if you think
about it
with all our
melons i'm getting confused wait i'll
get this one okay so and a shovel
there you go
however we don't need the shovel and uh
i think we don't even need the axe in
the end let's go back to our
headquarters okay
oh let me take dad
oh okay it sounded like i feel like i
said i don't like my uh mickey mouse
yeah for a minute you did it was a
little confusing you gave me a shock
there
[Laughter]
that's a great impression you know what
i got better boots uh
but uh we gotta repair them
[Music]
let me repair them
the other boots you can keep in case you
lose the boots that you currently have
which i wouldn't recommend because
they're really nice like better
following
one of the best traits to have on boots
i would say oh yeah wait so you take
less fall damage
yeah yeah yeah so here they are
here they are new boots make sure to
swap them out okay
thanks okay wait you can come back [\h__\h]
i should have combined it oh wait so
sorry give me both back here
you can combine both of those
trays and then you will have
super super nice boots what do you want
to call them you want to call them
something oh man okay let me think
um
[Music]
that's a good question chet what do you
guys have any ideas
what should we call these these shiny
new boots
death boots oh that sounds nice b
these dead boots
death strikes
mega drift oh yeezys that's right
that's kind of cool
um
air maurice i like that call them air
morning okay please
and more was he one of the capsular
yeah all caps real nice and aggressive
thanks chad for the suggestions
oh i can't wait to equip these air
mauries thank you so much
thank you i can't believe you've been
falling i can't believe that kiara got
me those brand new air moris i feel so
lucky thank you french very expensive i
shall make it up to you
i think now we are armor-wise we are
ready to go food-wise we are ready to go
material-wise i'm gonna take pick ups a
few more um building blocks and then i
would say we're good wait ship ship boat
oh we might chew it on a mountain uh
your dog on the way oh
can i i mean has is it calmed down or is
it going to still try and attack yeah
but it's in a boat right now hello dogo
um
you have permission to not be friendly
to this dog by the way
um i just want to get him out of the
boat one second because i'm actually
without hurting him yeah i'd prefer that
you not but
all right i want to break the boat
okay okay okay thank you uh
you need to right click him again right
right okay and then he will portal
himself into your home okay if if we
just leave him so get back into the boat
he doesn't seem aggro so i think it's
fine yeah yeah because i died once ah
you feel god's who i am uh shout out to
kill and i'm gonna make you remember who
i am if you don't move away
i can't believe that the dogs know where
the house is that's kind of cool
i mean they know wherever you are oh i
see i see we're just going to go to your
house and then make him sit down i'll
leave him there oh yeah
gotcha okay it really is nighttime
oopsies
we're going to your place and then you
can give me
uh maybe maybe maybe because i ended up
repairing more stuff can you give me
like six diamonds yeah i can i can give
you as many as you need
i'm cool with that but yeah it's just
yeah i mean i guess you can go throw
them in your chest before we go on the
journey
yeah yeah i really will
cool all right oh i'm just going to take
it take them out of your chair yeah just
take them
i'm going to take i'll get in the hood
let me put some other stuff back
can you find other cool stuff in the end
you really can find a lot of cool stuff
really trust me
uh we can find shulker chests and like a
lot of we can find dragon heads
cool
that sounds neat i want to drag a
wait um i threw out the cobblestone in
order to save your items last time
should i get like other rocks or
ah if you don't have it anymore let me
see i i think i have more materials
over on my place because um it would be
i don't know can you make andesite into
stacks uh chat i don't remember stack
them up on top of each other into slap
slaps sorry i mean
ooh slubs
[Music]
you use it for getting around the end
yeah
uh so take that one stack that you have
of and the side okay
got it
[Music]
oh wait i haven't this one up
it blends in so nicely because it's gray
wish
all right all right all right okay i'll
take i take a couple of blocks of
cobblestone we probably have to go
pretty far
and because the nearest end cities
have already been pretty explored i
guess by
me and ina and gura and ame and i
already went back there once flying back
with my elijah i went pretty far
so
this time we're just gonna do the
original strategy again by not flying
but actually placing a lot of blocks
over the void
trying to not fall down you will see
what i mean when we get there let's
sleep for a moment sure you said i don't
need the shovel right
uh yes you can put the shovel away and
is it not like oh wait why did i think
it's nighttime uh yes uh
the axe hmm actually you know what keep
keep the axe cause
if you fight one-on-one against someone
then
uh the axe does more damage like than
the sword actually wait what
yeah
only one i wonder like because the sword
does aoe damage while the axe does a
single target damage yeah
wow you're very like um
kwashi
with with minecraft
like you know you're cool
yeah
i uh i got all my knowledge from the
chat
you have something cool you're looking
out you guys you're
in your inventory in that chest i saw
maybe fill that up with water and bring
that along with you yes ma'am
and
i'll take i guess no i'll keep that in
here
and
let me see we don't need this we don't
need that all right i got it i got the
water okay
um
i'm doing some last
second last minute should we turn off
yeah i'm getting the suggestion to turn
off shaders yeah
okay we'll turn them off
i will i'll let you use that pumpkin
should i take a bed but
uh
no no you can't sleep in the end right
you'll blow up um
exactly we don't need a bed we're just
gonna set our spawn before we go into
the into the end okay um
[Music]
yes
oh yeah we used that last time to fight
the dragon
yeah that was one of our strategies we
used a million strategies if you even
can call them strategies
we we won in the end so
yeah yeah i'm gonna bring
those
two shulker boxes and we can make more
once we're there yeah yeah kiara said
she's gonna bring an ender chest as well
yeah well i guess i'll leave that here i
don't need that i'm trying to clean out
my ender chest and my struggle boxes
anything else that
leave electric yeah i'm leaving my
i'm leaving my lightroom
or maybe i'll just put them to the end
okay and then wait no diamonds uh the
apples
this and that and this sorry one moment
you're almost i wonder what the cities
are like done
the cities they they look
interesting it's like high towers and
and really slim towers and so the the
thing is that um they're filled with
these enemies called uh
what are they called the shulker enemies
oh so not endermen they fall again uh
enemies are everywhere too but inside of
the towers we're gonna have issues with
the shulkers yeah like a searcher's code
no clothes shulkers um they look like
the shulker boxes and we got they they
dropped the shulker shells to make
shulker boxes i see oh i want those
but they're they are really really
annoying to deal with oh wow um we gotta
be careful there because if they hit you
you're sent flying like you literally
start floating
oh um
wait so should should i hit him with
arrows
yeah that's why we need that bow okay
and
yes okay i think
i think
i think i think we're
we're pretty much i'm going to turn off
shaders right before we go in guys i'm
keeping them on yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
because kiara's name is
fancy and i'm jumping on beds okay
okay um
do i need uh do i need even more blocks
so cali has a couple blocks
i guess
a diorite can be made into two slabs too
and and this time so i'll take that
if i have any other i mean worst case we
can just get the end the end material
yeah
we'll probably use that can you hit that
with pickaxes or shovel
probably not shovel pickaxe gotcha cause
we're not bringing the shovel that's
right i remember now
yeah i don't think we needed that for
anything there
push
point point
i mean come on that must be enough for
us
okay
everybody wanna come over to my house
yeah
and there uh i have a stone cutter that
will be most efficient to cutting the
stuff okie dokie i'm not gonna bring it
with me naruto okay are you okay
[Music]
okay should i make the regular slabs
yeah okay shift click on them to get uh
as many as possible all right 64 44.
okay that's about 100 or so
is that is that all the the stone blocks
or whatever that yeah
okay i think i think we'll be fine i'll
take this with me whoa what's this
beautiful
what sparkles
that that's the material that we'll also
get in there and
in the cities really because that's an
end rod and they light up the room too
and they're really cool you can place
them also
like look look over here you can place
them straight you can make them look
like lamps
the end rod
yeah they look like
lightsabers wow
my mama uh put them all over this
apartment because she thought it looks
fancy ready i want them for my onsen i'm
gonna do my best oh we're gonna get a
lot of those don't worry okay cool um
awesome sorry sorry that i took so much
time i'm kind of nervous that we're
forgetting something um
now
we're fine let me give you this pumpkin
head
thank you
i i think it's like i personally don't
like using it but if you wear that then
the um enderman will not target you oh
what but oh my endless yeah but i don't
really like it because it like put it on
and you will see that you will see less
much less
oh i see i see
yeah but you look funny now
yeah i do i look like a little
jack-o'-lantern dude
cool but it's less protection as well
huh
exactly but it's more about like we
gotta be very careful with where we
where we are walking today
so
i feel like
um you can press that i want to get a
better view is that true
yeah f1 no f5
oh it's fine
f1 is something else f5 is like there's
three different like angles that you can
play yeah but i pressed f1 and now
everything's clear
yeah yeah that's for like taking a good
picture i guess oh i can still walk
around no you mean ah ah you mean you
don't see the ah
i think that's only with the shaders if
you turn the shaders off
then it um
will not work i think that was a thing
right right chad
only with the shaders on it removes the
hp which i guess you can keep the
shaders in the end we will see how it
looks like for you maybe it's too dark
for you not sure no
no it'll still work that's kind of
interesting but it turns off everything
so like i can't see what items i'm
holding etcetera and that kind of stuff
yeah but this is nice but i am worried i
feel like i want to wear the helmet just
to be safe i want my head yeah yeah just
if you feel nice let's see if they
target you the enderman because you look
at them too often
then we will use the
the pumpkin helmet if
does that make them stop targeting you
yeah yeah they will like you can look at
them and they ignore you but
we will see how you can control your
eyes
i'm really good at controlling my eyes
trust me they definitely don't dart all
over the place and go all over
yeah one thing though
can you put your bucket of water into
your hot bar
oh yeah it's in there
okay good because if they happen to
target you and start attacking you
just put the water on the ground because
they don't go into water okay so they
don't like the water okay why am i going
up here wait don't go down go down oh
okay i was just following your lead
captain it's it's this direction that we
shouldn't really go up here again okay
for sure for sure yeah i'm i'm gonna get
one and don't worry guys it's just well
around it
i'm gonna walk around it
yeah
okay it took us one hour to prepare i'm
so sorry i hope we can find a city asap
no props i'm i'm here just just ahead
it's directly as long as it takes kiara
as long as it takes
okay okay i'm here for the for the ride
i mean i guess your sleep rhythm is
[\h__\h] anyway yeah it's pretty pretty
boned yeah
got them at these these mountains
i should i guess i should have gone up
yeah
because it it ends somewhere and you can
just drop down into water i guess oh
oh oh well
we're gonna go with the safe rooms we
like some mountain climbing
ah do you like mountain climbing
yeah wait
my legs are getting strong now where did
you go into the abyss oh i see you went
down there spooky are you good i didn't
want to
yo
uh oh [\h__\h]
yo okay okay i'm back oh rabbis let's go
it's starting to get a bit dark i hope
we can get there in time
oh yeah [\h__\h] i didn't bring uh a bed at
all
what should we do oh well we have to
arrive
before it turns into nightstand okay
let's go quick
go go go go go go
how do i swim like you
um you gotta try to get under the water
otherwise you can't swim that fast okay
like
point downwards to the ground while
oh i see yeah going forward and then
while while you're in the water if you
press ctrl
yeah then you're dumbing through the
water
i'll fight anything yeah beat him up
following the path jumping on some
watermelons in the nighttime
uh-oh
oh oh oh boy
ct oh wait are you guys making fun of
because i said see the rl and not coming
oh that was a creepy thing i heard a
creeper did it blow you up or i don't
want to hey i definitely felt like i
felt i felt it hit me but like it didn't
hurt me so
okay good
i can't see [\h__\h]
oh wait why
it's very dark
oh you still got the shaders on maybe
they make it like pretty dark huh yeah i
turned mine off for today it felt a
little bit laggy okey-dokey
i'll turn them off shortly then
ctrl
control
no
yeah control
ah let's see is there anything else i
should warn you about oh you know is she
playing minecraft today nina
at this time
why is she
yeah she's usually around
a similar time whoa whoa whoa whoa
don't fall down do i hold shift i'm okay
should i hold shift it's just i'm going
so slow uh shift no no
try to walk straight
keep your
that that little cross in the middle
that you have just keep it on the middle
of the path and you should be okay is
that a wolf
is that my wolf a wolf
no did you make it sit down oh i didn't
that's my wolf
okay then we'll just have it follow us
until like the room uh where we jump
into the end and just have him sit there
yeah sounds good to me
wait a second
i didn't bring oh no this is silk touch
okay fine fine do i have my other
pickaxe in the enter
because i never have enough coal
i never have enough coal oh there's no
one skirlington
i see a deadbeat over there
oh oh be careful you'll see a couple of
beads
oh and that's the creeper i think
that's the enderman oh okay uh-oh
run run run run run run
oh don't let them all the
the spooky spooky uh skirlingtons and
endermen are coming out to play
uh-uh all the spooky thugs
oh the moonlight is reflecting on the
left spider
is this the right direction
wasn't there one point on this path
where it splits into two paths yeah i've
never
took me around oh that's a creeper
falling behind you
uh wait i'm gonna go into the water for
a moment and eat some food
can they follow us into the water no
wait oh wait they can't go into the
water
there's a lot of [\h__\h] going on
around here oh man
creepers everywhere literally all over
the place
now what the hell did you just come to
support
[Laughter]
[Music]
we were in a pickle there we were in a
pickle thank you
thank you you know
wow
stream sniper
yeah the best kind of stream sniper
away you demons
well yeah i think we're getting pretty
close
[Music]
oh no
on y'all
are you using the infinity bow now right
yeah
i'm gonna get real good because it feels
strong it does
i like it a lot thanks for making it for
me i hope i don't
want to hold on to it you've got the
power oh my god
there it is i think i see it and yeah in
the distance i see the tower the last
time i went to the end actually was
literally the time that we fought the
ender dragon
oh i played a lot of minecraft yeah
but i'm excited to fly
yeah and
yeah that's gonna be really really nice
for you i think yeah but you gotta get
used to flying i brought some fireworks
because the the wings only work if you
have fireworks with you yeah are there
limitations to flying
limitations
what do you mean
like you can't just like jump in the air
and fly wherever you want right
well
you can as long as you have fireworks oh
i see
and i guess you can kind of fly
like if you jump down the high tower
with the with the wings on
then you'll also kind of fly but it's
not that effective without the fireworks
okay
are you by the really tall tower yes i
am
you're so quick i see you i don't see
you anymore slain by kada again yeah
she was slain by fried chicken
poison
is that if he is dangerous
i think they probably
oh hey i spy i think they probably put
the
like put the name kadaga on a weapon i
guess that's all there is to it i see
i get it so my spawn point okay so we
have a rafter yeah set your spawn point
got it i guess we can put the beds back
into this chest here sure and
all right
what are you
what do you have in your inventory right
now all right i'll tell you i have a
diamond pickaxe 45 cooked chickens i
have a pumpkin head i have um i don't
need this raw cod i'll put that away 46
um golden carrots i have 64 stone slabs
and plus 44 actually so it's over 100.
then i've got arrows i have a bow i have
18 watermelons i have 27 cooked rabbits
and a diamond sword the watermelons yeah
wanna know let's put those away in the
chest we need space we need as long as
much okay as possible can i have a water
bucket
okay and i'll put those here as well
okay okay okay we're ready to go all
right uh fill your health up one last
time if you don't have full health yes
ma'am
and uh it's gonna be dangerous callie oh
dangerous okay i'll do my best just
just be very careful if you're if you're
on a narrow path just um
no i'm trying to press shift okay how do
i hold up the shield
when i'm when i have a bow uh with right
right uh uh with the ball it doesn't
work only if you have like a sword one
hand weapon i see i understand okay
sounds good oh i didn't i can switch
them really quickly so
okay okay okay
all right i'm ready
i'm also very nervous whenever i go to
the end but let's do this let's do this
it's really nice did i notice oh i
didn't turn off my shaders whoopsie
doodle
did i not set my spawn
did
did you not oh well it will just be it
will just be in the in the i will just
be respawned in the
can i leave the game and come back
oh for the shader yeah
no you can do it um if you press escape
oh okay options one set guys and then
video settings okay
and then shaders shooters okay it's like
on the left side and the middle off and
then you click off exactly and then it
will take a moment to load but then you
can just get out of the
options okay
nice oh apparently i did okay chat made
me nervous i did set the stream thingy
um
all right let's go
okay
careful careful how do i make sure that
the endermen don't like i'm not looking
at them
no just just try to look as much as you
can on the ground like lower your head
but not too much like just just keep it
somewhat low
okay
just mind your own business okay
i always felt like i had to kind of keep
the cross hair away from them but they
seem to like it's like i'm looking at
them anyway yeah like they
you can look at their body you just
can't have your your little cross in the
middle on their eyes that will anger
them i see let me hold on i'm going to
put the pumpkin in my bar
just to have it ready wait no i don't
just kidding that wouldn't work i need
to actually equip it um oh well
we'll be fine yeah we'll figure it out i
think like it's not the scariest thing
here um
at the end of
this like island yeah there's like
nothing right nothingness um that's like
we're gonna build a lot of paths over
the nothingness oh
want to be very careful when going up
here okay very careful
gotcha oh god
no problem you guys made a little
stairway wow
yeah this is
by going into this portal we're gonna
port ourselves onto a different island
oh
okay so uh how does it work again uh
this is cool looking you guys just found
here
uh yeah this was here like already i
need to change my thing this portal yeah
okay look at what i'm doing so i put
this this this trapdoor up right right
and i jump here up here be very careful
again and then crouch
all right then push uh can you
wait how how does she do it when she's
one second i'm again i'm getting some
different oh there we go
excuse me when you're when you're
crouching
uh-huh i guess you wait you don't need
to crouch no no crouching
uh you stand under the trapdoor and then
close it and then you you i'm flying
right now right so now i i went into the
other dimension
what you're gonna do is stand under the
trap door like first you have to open it
i guess gotcha
and then uh when you stand directly
under it you right-click the trapdoor to
close it
okay
and now i think you're flying right
you're like kind of in the flying
position
am i i'm trying to crouch probably i
press shift to crouch right
no no no no crouching no crouching just
standing underneath it uh normally i did
it i did i did it okay and now i go to
it
yeah just go through that little portal
whoa there you are okay careful careful
turn around oh wow there's a few steps
towards me okay
there's a lot and a little bit more a
little more
all right try pressing try pressing
shift okay
oh no you're not standing up yet oh
there you are okay okay okay okay all
right we got this let's uh go uh go down
these stairs oh boy this is really quite
terrifying yeah it is i'm really scared
i'm good we'll be fine i'll be fine
now we can go here into this little safe
house oh you guys need a little safe
house
it's cool yeah together ourselves okay
um
now the question is which direction
should we go
um
uh is this the path that i created the
last time i was here is this my path
guys or is this inna's path
bring it back i don't know where are you
uh
i'm i'm i'm i'm here
here i'm behind
there's a lot of pretty stones around
here
so if we go
if we use my path again we will we will
uh at least
pass one ender city or two actually that
i have already been through but at least
the
at least the paths are already made and
then
from there on mm-hmm we will continue
building maybe okey-dokey yeah sounds
good to me all right captain let's go
let's go
onward to not getting
in trouble with the enderman
wait what iris
what about iron race
i don't know is this really my path it
doesn't matter i guess well we'll find
we'll find it in the city eventually
okay careful here even i will shift here
because i'm scared all right nice and
slow i can do it yeah okay well i'll
hold shift because i know how i am so
i'll just yeah okay please no sticky
keys computer no sticky keys
do you have shift on
toggle or
i don't know i think in minecraft it
turns it off to be honest because i
don't i never have issues with sticky
keys
okay i think
with what
if you when you press shift do you like
have to keep on pressing or you only
toggle it once and then you're shifted
until you press it again yeah
you keep on pressing it yeah
oh you should change that maybe oh
um where was it again controls
in minecraft
uh
yeah okay
wait a second where was that options
controls
accessibility ah accessibility settings
okay on the bottom right okay and then
sneak toggle i guess sneak toggle okay
it's not
someone wrote to me something about
iris's stuff did you die in the end and
like left your stuff there because
you died
if we get too close then it will i guess
disappear i hope that won't happen yeah
okay now when you're you're [\h__\h] okay
you only have to press it one second
yeah i don't have to hold it anymore
i'm glad i had no idea how to do that
before
okay okay well you can scout out the
area while i'm slowly but surely making
my way over
yeah i'm gonna drink some of my
some of my uh
my gamer drink
i have a gamer drink
i
um
i guess a friend of mine like had some
kind of
gamer drink sponsor and like they had
too much of it at their office and
they're like just take it callie just
take it
cause i've been drinking it
the gamer drink
it uh
it's given me a little bit of energy is
it bang it's been no it's not bang
um i'd be acting a lot more suspicious
if it was bang i still have two
if it's red bull i feel like you could
talk about it because there was a whole
live red bull collaboration before yeah
that's
right yeah well i mean i still have two
bang in my fridge but i just won't drink
them yeah i know i'm really afraid
because they're i see the enderman
looking at me too and i'm like oh boy
oh i see you there you go there you are
ah
where is the next path that i built
so you know in the
basically it's like a [\h__\h] ton of
islands in the end and they are uh
mostly not connected so we will have to
build the paths this is a path that i i
guess i built before
uh oh while we're at it um
yep
is that how you do it
uh
um we're getting some coarse fruit you
see those little
purple trees yes ma'am they're pretty i
like them
with your ex oh i can break them rory a
couple of them yeah okay cool cause they
drop chorus fruit pretty
what that is is it fills up on your
health yes but we don't really use it as
food we use it as a way to stop floating
because
look look at it look at me look at me oh
where'd you go look at me behind you oh
yeah
oh zoom you zoomed
you will always be teleported to like a
nearby uh
ground
oh really
so if you fall if you eat it you're fine
yes nah i i don't and what would happen
well
if callie falls into the void and tries
her best to eat it in the
as possible
i wonder if that could save her yeah i
guess it depends on how deep everything
is huh
only if you do it rapidly it will stay
you won't be fine yeah you probably
won't be fine uh yes no it's not work
okay what a [\h__\h] okay stop try to not
fall into the void but um when we go to
those towers the end cities
there will be a lot of mobs that send us
flying so if you fly too much if you fly
like up too high then you should always
eat a chorus fruit
um oh you could get back to the ground
and you wait so you float like
in the sky after they hit you yeah yeah
yeah yeah so it's like you can't really
control where you're flying to like it
will send you higher and
higher yeah
and it will wear off like you see like a
timer uh-huh and it will wear off
eventually but oh
okay yeah
wow
lots of things to discover here
ah yeah well so far it's mostly
nothingness but yeah but it's just kind
of like interesting i don't know in the
main game i just like didn't
expect to find this
very interesting by the way it's uh
infinite this this place is infinite
wait really
so like new villages will just keep
spawning forever and ever and ever
yeah but they will be further and
further and further and it will be more
and more difficult to find them wow so
it's like the universe
you go really fast
ah that's the fastest way to run it's
like if you have if you have full health
double use of front running then ctrl
plus jumping oh i didn't know that five
buttons
but don't jump into the void you gotta
okay i'll be careful
yeah leave it to me i didn't know
jumping was a factor
yeah it
makes you even faster oh enough left oh
there she goes guys probably like we we
taught them
enough things they're fine yeah yeah
nina's so pro
i can't wait to fly like i haven't seen
a path of mine in a while
real
i guess i kind of cool you remember the
paths that you made
no i don't remember that's the thing
just kidding
um in the first place i guess i
have like
half over there
um how do you get out
you're gonna shift behind me okay
very carefully all right i've got my
fruits ready to start to work but still
so
scared i didn't do this for a while
one second take your time
okay
[Music]
captain
just don't press shift again
[Music]
oh yeah that's right you're talking to
yourself i was pressing shift i was
holding down shift and i was
jumping up and down doing a little dance
a second ago
yeah
gotta get used to it
this place is super high risk
wow
it is
wowie
this is the end after any second yeah
infinite okay the path is done oh nice
you're gonna make a lot more
all right i can help with the path if
you want
um
i'm thinking i mean i understand the
skepticism but i'll be the builder
i would like to be helpful
it i can fight
definitely
i i think the building maybe you should
leave to me okey-dokey
i got your backpack i will build over
there
i think we're already definitely off
path i don't see anyone's anyone else's
path maybe we can go in a new direction
it's for us
there's a myth though that um
let's say
you come to the end for the first time
uh-huh
and you
uh start building a path into let's say
south uh-huh the like the end since it's
infinite
it will
create
um
it will create it will like load in
and while like it will create everything
while it's loading in like it's not
pre-created what
so
um every every area that you have not
like gone to yet has
not been created like the game didn't
decide yet what it would look like so um
that is not a myth that is a fact but
uh let's say you go south
and the inner cities there's a myth that
the inner cities start spawning
only in that one direction
like from north to south or
that explains that but cool i don't know
there's a lot of stuff
about this game
i hear a scary sound
scary things
but i mean if it can be proven then
then they should prove it
i'd like to see them in the video or
else it is just there's a lot of people
who oh god
you got this you're fine
uh you got this a lot of people who who
say that is it's true because they have
they have seen it and
[Music]
you're you're doing great
no
i mean you haven't talked a lot
[Music]
just keep your pinky really far away
from the shift and you should be fine
it's just
it's just it's just like you stand on on
top of a nothing tower that's made out
of glass you see everything yeah
around you yeah i've been a place like
that tokyo tower you can you can stand
on some glass and you see all the stuff
down below yeah right okay are you
afraid of heights
currently yes um
generally
no probably just because the stakes are
super high we are holding a lot of
really important things
and if we fall we lose them forever
exactly like that i get it careful
there's uh there's another
uh void here oh
campbell
uh
are my steps gonna be enough for that
little gap
oh my god
i'm like standing in the nothingness
are you scared of heights i guess not
um depends on the situation i guess
oh we could have ender pearled oh no
if you throw ender pearls um you can
like teleport yourself as well whoa to
the place where you throw the ender
pearl too
that's pretty neat
yeah well it's fine we're doing a
hardcore mode you know super extreme
mode for experts yes yeah yes no problem
getting those ender pearls will have
been quite some work as well yeah i do
have four of them though just for next
time
let's go a little bit left here oh i
found the portal oh oh
but that will just bring us back to the
main island i guess oh okay well just
good to know that it's there kind of
like a checkpoint
um
well i'm going to take a screenshot of
that
i guess we can go over there
um
the end is the same as the
updates change how chunks load the first
time but that's still seed based old
chunks don't change interesting
i guess it's kind of like the same thing
for the overworld huh
oh
a lot boy jumpy boys around here and
cities only spawn on chunkers that are
dividable by 20 like 20 40 60 800 is
that true
not true
we
oh right
oh [\h__\h] uh what oh [\h__\h] oh oh i looked
at it oh did i
at least they died
i gave it some damage but it's not dead
yet come on over here
come on okay shoot him
the good thing is like the others won't
attack you so oh cool oh nice shot
is it dead now uh oh this one wants to
know oh hi
oh it hurts itself by going into the
water that's good this is an interesting
position we found ourselves in
there we go okay uh i want to take back
my water
sponge
oh [\h__\h] there we go okay yay i guess
i'll i look dead then at the end of man
huh see that's so weird sometimes i
don't even feel like i looked at them
but i guess i did so
it's weird like that
[Music]
i haven't ended the chest with me chat
look
of course this is not perfect very well
in the yeah i know what i'm doing you
prepared very well mostly yeah
definitely more than me i have no clue
what the f word's going on but i'm very
grateful for the journey
we want to go to like a big island you
know cause mostly the end cities are on
those big islands i'm gonna path
of wait i see a pep
oh did i make that puff before who are
we like circling around to
stuff you've done maybe
have i used that material arrow or
projectile can't hit enderman okay
gotcha so i'll use my sword next time
that's iris path
best avoid it should i not go there
okay let's go
oh
i mean i'm trying to go mostly straight
so
i just see a lot of legs
a lot of legs spiders legs everywhere
they're supermodels they're super mottos
looking very stylish today please don't
kill me
it's very stylish
love the way you work it girl yeah yeah
it's just another sign that black is a
very flattering color
it it is though it goes with everything
that's why my whole closet is the color
black
yeah i heard you say that why did i hear
you say that just recently yeah i talk
about it something oh uh in a thing we
can't really talk much about
oh ah
yeah
the secret
i think i know you'll probably learn
about
next month
next month overall yep all right told me
next month so look forward to the thing
next time i gotta go over to that island
i think i don't really have
a choice
which
because
over there it doesn't it doesn't look
good to me we'll see okay
whatever you want to do
i'll follow you into hell i'm gonna go
further than iris
yes ma'am
oh yeah outfits should maybe come
sometime soon too hopefully yeah yeah
we we were totally not much longer
i love kelly's new outfit so much thanks
i'm glad you like it
it's uh something i've wanted for a
while that kind of style thing and stuff
oh good it looks so good yours is dope
too though it's perfectly fitting for
you
our two new outfits for some reason even
though we didn't really um do it on
purpose
i think our outfits are kind of color
matching oh yeah i think so as well they
do have like a similar thing going on i
think yeah
yeah oh some people i saw someone in the
chat being surprised about what new
outfit uh
it's been so long since we announced it
and nothing has been happening people
forget about it
i mean i don't blame them
you know things of course kind of you
know
get a little messy sometimes and but
it's fine it's fine no worries guys
everything's all good in the
neighborhood and you'll be seeing them
shortly
shortly yes on our one i mean i've been
ready for a while now
dad
yeah we've been ready like at the time
at that time i was ready
me too but we were i see another path we
were
just
you know waiting for the right moment
yeah exactly and everyone's got to be
ready so
whose path is that
whose path is
my legs oh you lost me i'm too fast yeah
you're very quick and these long-legged
boys i'm afraid of them
here here here
don't look at them
actually that's not even
that's that's
that's uh i thought it was
i'm lost in a little never
never stuffed but it's not oh iris i
don't think i it's not never iraq
actually it looked like it was uh the
what's it called i wonder who's that is
well it's a path for us let's walk over
it where
are you
oh
oh god
uh
i lost you you run black okay
[Music]
oh where did you go
i saw you before here uh here mojimo
straight straight straight oh i see you
hot hot hot they're so scary okay you
gotta go to where it feels the hottest
that's where the phoenix is okay i
gotcha i'll i'll turn on my my
temperature receptors i prefer the cold
you know this but i'm in good on you
scram it
that's ahmed good as perf how the hell
did i get there oh that's a smart idea
to like code them by different like
types of blocks that's a really good
idea yes so
i like that us be careful callie oh yeah
be careful
oh yeah yeah
they they took quite some
time to
because i don't want to go into a
direction that has absolutely no
understandings
you got good gear to deal with them okay
i'll try not to be so spooked by them
but yeah yeah they don't do much damage
though than and the enderman okay don't
don't panic no need to panic all right
sure i'll just be a little cautious then
um
definitely be cautious
i don't see you anymore i went too fast
are you too excited for yomokon yeah
oh yeah i really like doing panels where
i can see everyone it's like exciting
for me so like see the fans they're my
fave
i thought
a while ago
i thought that the panel that i did a
while i guess the one with you yeah
that's my last one
and i was a little bit sad about it that
um uh that was the last one but now we
got a new one extra i didn't know it
would be that fun
it is fun because i feel so like it
feels like we're connecting with the
fans in a whole new way like seeing
their faces yeah it's totally different
when you can actually see them you know
and hearing their voices and seeing
their emotions when they talk to us they
all look very nervous always though
so cute i mean we're kind of nervous too
but in a different way i think
you know yeah so don't worry guys we are
also a bit nervous you know but yeah but
it's it's all good we're overall it's
the it's like the excitement is number
one number one feeling
yeah
it's always fun to see everyone's
cosplays too yeah people get so creative
i love that yeah i love seeing all like
the cali sights
careful i'm gonna preach do a tiny
breach
okie dokie
little bridge
ah good i met the feet completely so
funny i saw that
oh that was that was pretty hilarious
it's like a faded meeting you know
there's like thousands and thousands of
viewers that we have right and then like
making a connection to people that we
know from chat or from super chat and
then they show up like those panels and
they're like hey i'm this and this
person
it's so funny it is really neat to
put a face to the name yeah yeah
oh i gotta eat
but yeah eating is important
okay i see no more paths maybe we're on
our own path again i think so now this
must be like our our own way do we have
to find our way all the way back by the
way
um no so what i was thinking is like
we're just gonna i have it in the chest
with me mm-hmm so we're just gonna put
everything in our ender chest and die
and then yeah fall into the void nice
idea
yeah okay keep going out like here
oh my god i'm already like
running out of
do you still have slabs don't you don't
need to keep them yeah i have a bunch of
them
over hundred four oh no i have over 100
okay
no worries we can also use this probably
i'll probably have to use the the spongy
material that they have here eventually
because we we need to we need to go far
i guess pretty far
yeah
sorry it's it's really like oh where's
the luck thing wherever or not the city
spawn or not if you run into one they
can't be very far apart and that's all
right there's one problem
kelly i'm gonna tell you the sad sad
story of nino my inaudible oh no did ian
get in trouble
well i mean no but
so
you know after we killed the ender
dragon
um
both me and ina made a stream
reservation to
um go into the end and get those lighter
wings asap
and
i
my stream was scheduled uh on the same
day as hers but like about
[Music]
eight
eight hours or so after her stream
schedule starts
so that would be a lot of time for
someone like ina to get her elijah right
right
yeah eight hours more than enough uh-huh
so she starts her stream
and
goes into the end really motivated she
prepares so well she prepared so well
she prepared like night vision potions
wow so that she can see in the dark cool
which we aren't even using
um
but yeah so she was super prepared she
had like motivation as well she was
super motivated mm-hmm then she goes
until the end and she she first of all
first of all it takes her
a million years to find an inner city oh
like hours of bridging and
you know
she went over so many islands that
didn't have anything
and then and then she
finally finds one
and
it's it's bugged
no in a way that
it's broken and it doesn't it has
everything except the wings
absolutely ridiculous that sounds
horrible
what a shame i want to go watch that now
actually i i know that sounds like
sadistic and whatever but i'm i want to
go watch
it this
pretty sad
no
nina
and they do i think yeah that's pretty
much the story so that took her hours
and and
she kind of gave up and then i came
online i started preparing and from the
start of
from the start of going into the end to
until the i got the elytra
it only took me like
one to two hours
uh-huh i was so lucky i immediately
found an inner city immediately found
the the wings because i wanted to a
different direction than inna did
i found
it so quickly and i felt so sorry
because ina was like yeah must really
just be locked then
yeah i'm always like
for some reason i'm always so lucky when
it comes to minecraft
well let's let's let's hope we get a
good roll with you today then yeah
now i hope so too so far it's not
looking that good but it's because we
got to go further it's cause you got me
i'm super unlucky
i put all my luck into getting into holo
that's about it
no complaints no complaints yeah it's
just because it's already been explored
a little bit in the closest areas
i need to drink water
grab some grab grab your your gamer
you're getting
after my bridge
first bridge and drink
okay
now
so now she's good
yay but i think she only has
one pair and then ah didn't she go to
the end and then got ro roboco senpai a
second pair of wings because the roboco
senpai lost her wings
so ina was so nice to look for another
one that's so cool what the heck what
what a chad she's such a hero i'm
telling you yeah
even though they're so precious she
got new ones for local senpai
what a savior
that's really cool
hina is never right now well
she only has a little bit no
i have i got the first never right in
the server though oh wait really
is that wait maybe it's not loading in
is that already explored how do you know
it's the city
[Music]
uh
uh wait it's maybe not downloading it
just don't don't how do you know it's a
city though
uh wait do you see that what spawned
over there maybe your thingy is
oh is that
no
we will see we gotta get a little bit
closer i guess your your chunk didn't
load in over there yeah i see a city
we will see it in a moment okey-dokey
lead the way captain
i'll do what i can
it might be broken though i'm not sure
what we'll see
no dragon hat so far
render distance too low oh yeah it has
either been looted before
or it's broken
i did fly around the
end kind of aimlessly before and looted
two cities in a really random place so
it might have even been myself
oh
i feel like i went like further than
this all right well we can we can check
it out well it looks so looks looted
that looks very looted
how can you tell yeah yeah
um because like you see um if you look
up
there there's a ship right it looks like
a ship
yeah now
uh
on the edge of that ship there's
normally a dragon head
oh which
oh cool but but there isn't which means
it has already been loaded because oh
the courtesy is you take the dragon
heads um if you included it gotcha well
that's fine we'll find another one
yeah question is should we go
you need new strengths go over there and
then go straight from there
um uh yes please okie dokie
should we check it out anyway sure i'm
fine with that
i don't know i don't want to waste too
much time on an already looted place but
i guess we want to at least go over to
that to the island
is that all you had
yeah
okay well i i do need to
should we try and get more blocks from
here
yeah
okay i gotcha i can i can do that
oh it's easier to do than i thought
yeah just mine everything that's in
front of you gotcha
a few more blocks yeah i don't see a
bridge either but yeah that that's why
it could be myself cause i just flew
onto those islands rather than bridging
oh yeah you can fly now so i guess
yeah it's it's a bit dangerous so people
don't recommend it so i did it off
stream
oh
we'll always go like
no kiana is dangerous don't fly in the
end
no
i see i can see how it might be risky
yeah
it is because like it loads in so slowly
while you're flying so quickly and you
might bump into something and die
yeah and fireworks i mean i wonder how
the flying thing works with like control
and stuff like that is it hard to
control where you're flying
it's pretty easy to control but the
thing is like most of the time when you
fly everything loads in slower than you
fly so
you might end up flying into a huge
mountain and it kills you oh
which uh
might have happened before
i take that as it has happened before
i'm not sure did it
did it chat
did i die i definitely bumped into some
mountains before did i die
[Music]
getting lots of blocks for you
almost died there you go a phoenix never
dies at least not completely well
maybe just the the past the past a
little bit
oh
oh boy
that's me
i'll help you oh good job kelly good job
thanks
let's kill him here where'd he go i
can't see where he's eyes he keeps on
coming back
come on clausa come on oh we anchored
this one
oh boy okay that's fine we'll get them
uh you hurt yourself get those free end
up girls yeah
okay
here we go
it would actually be really nice if that
one drops a pearl for you because yeah
uh all right i think you picked up the
other picked up one but i can give it to
you
oh okay nice yeah and cause with the
ender pearl that's another way to kind
of save yourself when you're floating
yeah say you're like really up high
floating and you're like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm
gonna die i'm gonna fall yeah and you
just throw the ender pearl onto like the
ground and then it will teleport you
there and you you're safe oh wow that's
extremely useful
heck yeah yeah it is i'm usually like
always too
too panicked to do that kind of stuff so
i usually try to
just go with the flow
and
just
land
wherever or try to
float against a wall and save me that
way
smart
yeah it's dangerous
man this place is super dangerous i
didn't realize like how yeah kind of
clutch this whole place okay
out of out of those little out of that
tiny mining session i got one two three
four five six seven eight eight stacks
okay that's pretty good for now we can
always get some more later yeah yeah
there's more than enough so it worries
me though if this place has been looted
i feel like maybe a lot of places nearby
have been looted too so i'll probably
have to keep going for a while
um
the thing is normally when people loot
uh
uh one of those cities they're usually
done they're like okay i'm going home
now oh i see i got my wings i'm going
home so
the hope that i have is that
if we continue walking the next city we
see it will not be looted oh i see i see
looted
looted chat yeah yeah
[Laughter]
apparently i say it in a lewd way i mean
i kind of felt like the way i was saying
it was not too far off either it's just
one of those words where it's
unavoidable you know yeah
right
there's no way to loot and ender city
come on yeah i mean well now you're
challenging the internet here i i don't
know about all that
um someone will find a way bikini or
like a nice
lingerie on the industry
we're going to get those [\h__\h] posts come
on
give me those chickpeas
away
you know the rules and so do i
oh
nice uh all right here we are
excellent the one step that's triggered
i feel like i put like a sign of like
this this place has been wait that's
it's kind of small
it doesn't look
very it's oh okay oh well uh be careful
callie um see this is uh your first uh
whoa what's this um
you can always block them with your
shield okay because there we go look at
me i'm flying uh oh
and then i eat the course fruit because
i'm up very high
and i go back to the ground but until it
stops hitting me
uh i will not stop floating
as those are the the shulker boxes there
are enemies like they will keep on
opening itself up
until we kill them oh okay you have to
shoot him with the arrow
see now we got some some uh
um i just wasted that ender pearl excuse
me
oh [\h__\h] oh no that's that's okay there's
more than enough that we could get here
if we wanted why does it look so
unluted
is it maybe not
the city at the end of the game
maybe it's just really broken or
someone um i love the thing i did when i
uh off stream looted the the cities uh
one of them i looted completely and the
other one i just went in there to get
the wings so
uh i like the eyes i'm taking them
they're nice right yeah i love the
purple
it could have been me just taking the
wings and then leaving
is this familiar to you
been too long but you know what else you
can get here to end rods because there
are more than enough of those end rods
the fancy ones that you wanted
oh yeah oh i hear them
okay well oh did you climb if there's no
dragon head there's no way that there
will be uh
the electrons right oh god okay
okay it's been a while it's been a while
oh god
what should i use to fight them
uh i always use my arrow like even while
i'm flying i'm i fight them i'm just
that badass that's sick that sounds
awesome
i got sick hey meow yeah
oh i see it's over
i found the rod
look give me that
oh yeah be careful so that they like
don't fall down be careful to loot them
properly
um
well that's cool that over there is
pretty neat
like another ship over there
oh there is the ship
yeah yeah there's usually only one ship
like that
i guess if it's there i'm gonna go no
are you flying no i'm trying no i'm okay
i'm going up the spire oh if you're
flying always try to like bring yourself
to and like an area that has a roof
gotcha
like like uh i'm gonna fly here see how
it stops me there yeah now it sends me
flying again but i'm just gonna go here
okay
and i'll fall a little bit but that's
gotcha
really okay okay i want to
where is that where's that chocolate i
was attacking us i want to kill it whoa
look at this big dragon fortress thing
that's cool
yeah yeah over there i want to help
nice shot
he's already dead there's another one up
there
yeah i see it oops
oh is that too far
let me go
[Music]
ah got it
there we go wow you're really good at
eating
now we're gonna make another path over
there because those those uh ships are
never connected so we kind of yeah i saw
that i was really wanted to go over
there
but i'm guessing there's
usually that's where the wing would be
but i'm guessing there's no no wings
there yeah it's okay oh well we'll find
another one
yeah
legolas
and legoland yeah
[Music]
here
oh
behind you just stare i'm gonna try to
just
mine into it there you go okay
there's
what huh
there are wings to cali really wings
their wings
mostly just
go wings
yay i can fly look at all this cool
stuff in here golden horse
whoa i want all this stuff
i'm taking it
wait you should take that pickaxe is
that okay that's a really good pickaxe
thanks you can ignore this shovel we
don't need to shovel okay and now
you
left click
the wing okay
ah and that's i picked it up but that's
yours i give don't don't smile with that
one yet because we have to enchant it to
be actually like cool good okey dokey
and here take that take that end rod
yeah did you pick that up i think i got
it
oh my god we got the wings yay what wow
what the heck
thank you kiara
no problem i guess it really just didn't
have the dragon no wait it does have the
dragon head it was on the other side
oh my gosh no way you want the dragon
head i'll i'll get you one
i'll get you the dragon head i don't
know if you see it i do i barely see
it's little ears
oh bill's kind of hardcore carefully
around it
wow i i thought we're just gonna have to
look for even more
ender cities here wow
wait be careful actually stay stay over
there i want you to stay in the safe
space because losing their lights right
now would be uh yeah that would suck
that would really suck a lot
uh we will put it in the inner chest uh
and then we'll be fine
so wow wait how do i can we take that
again
what's in the really big places
where ah
wait what do you mean do the other
houses they're over there yeah that's
got all those like things coming up
they're basically
filled up with treasures and uh those
those mobs so we're gonna even though we
already have the wings we're gonna go
for all of those two
we gotta put them in then i get used to
um in her chest though right
yeah
okay
we're gonna get you some nice material
thank you i can't wait come back here
come back here
and take this dragon head and see your
[Applause]
[Music]
phoenix look strikes again thank you for
the help i i love it i'm a cool dragon
now thank you for the help
wow
wait one second we're gonna place the
energized here for a moment and uh
i'm gonna take the shulker boxes out and
you're gonna put um if you right-click
this it will be empty because ever every
ender chest
has its own player's inventory yeah
that's right yeah
exactly so you put your
uh wings and maybe the pickaxe put that
in there as well okay and the other the
other uh super cool stuff that you
picked up and actually actually wait a
second sorry uh-huh take this shulker
box that i'm throwing at you okay
did you pick it up yeah i got it
and place the shulker box uh somewhere
open it up
and put those important materials in the
shoulder chest
uh-huh
and then the shoulder chest we will
place into the energy so we have more
space cool nice idea
you put it
yeah put the wings in as well yes and
the diamonds oh damn it yeah yeah good
stuff yeah
stuff good stuff all right let's see
what else i have two pickaxes so
let's see the new one the one with the
soaked up
yeah this is a touch i would put that
one in here okay
and then another one
you can have some of this stuff too by
the way wait wait the the chest plate
was that in the chest yeah it was in the
chat the one it's not the one i have you
can take some of that stuff too and
maybe the dragon head yeah
i said yeah
all right you should put the dragon head
back in
oh i put my helmet in with the doodle
give me my helmet and then i'll put the
head in the box okay
okay
and then mine the chest again okay
see
and then put that into your energies
well infinite inventory
the thing is with energized
um
you can only really mine them with a
slick touch pickaxe which i do have so
don't worry i will mind this
okay take it with us gotcha
because if you don't mind it with a sick
touch pickaxe it will fall apart into
like and the pearls and all that that
sucks that does not sound fun
yeah
oh she will go back cool
thank you and we'll finish loading yes i
want to get all their treasure i want
all their treasure yes you're not safe
from takamoto it will destroy you yeah
let's get them i'm feeling confident i'm
not gonna hold shift oh i'm gonna hold
shift okay okay
just
i immediately started veering off the
path and i'm like never mind i'm gonna
press shift
what's that noise
ah that might be an enderman
it sounds like an enderman usually
they're not uh
i think you heard something else usually
they're the end the men shouldn't be in
here only sometimes they're in here
no don't fall down
good job good job kelly don't panic no
you did it you might come back though
yeah definitely
my man's not giving up that easy
oh you died julie you were dying
i i'm gonna take care of the stupid ass
jokers whoa you can try while you're
floating i think in here you're safe
even if you fall down
you can try to shoot them while you're
floating
yeah got him
the chest uh has boring contents but
okay we get a free ender chest here
okay heck yeah where'd you go oh i'm
trying to find you these are really
complicated
it's a little area
i'm already uh
done here already cleared it i hope you
do
but i'm taking out uh some some end rods
for you thanks
the fancy lightsabers i think we're
done i think we're done here
uh wait it doesn't doesn't it go even
higher it goes way higher yeah
we just got to do some mining i think uh
there should be like stairs yeah i'm
sorry i mean
sorry i don't know oh that was you i
thought it was an enemy no i don't know
what's going on
don't worry don't worry oh oh boy oh boy
i'm gonna make the breeze i use the
fruit and now i'm in trouble hang on
where are you
outside hold on
oh give me a minute are you like i don't
know where apparently like outside of
the city i have no idea but i'm gonna
survive
come here oh no
that's why i never actually use the
chorus fruit once i am in the city
because i don't want to be teleported
completely far away yeah that's
yeah
well i'm gonna build the the bridge
while you're uh
[Music]
god
oh my god
let me down
let me oh i'm just outside of the place
i can come back
oh yeah you should try to
um
come back inside oh boy i'm being hunted
by whom
um i just heard a zooming noise
so oh that's an enderman
did you look at him again no
however in the thick of the battle
you never know thank god it was elena
falling from a highest place right you
yeah you would think it might it might
be a boy but here we are
i survived
congratulations yes that's not something
that normally happens so
good news
where did you go hey rachel i'm on my
way back
okay
i've already oh boy um
i'm already climbing up the next tower
thingy all right
me too in that case oh i stopped
floating okay
oh you're oh that's where that is fine
i want to go back to you find you wait
i'm going to try to find you
i messed up well i'm on my way back need
to protect nelly
it's
okay i'll be all right are you are you
down here
now i'm on the stone bridge
stone bridge i'm the one from the
elytra the ship yep that one down there
is looking for me okay okay okay
[Music]
your monster yeah but let's just try to
go over here all right
just gotta keep it on moving oh it's
coming for you it's coming for you take
me instead yeah oh no
no problem no problem just takes a
moment how that works
and okay
okay so now
i already started building some kind of
a bridge there uh
see actually
uh this area it attacked me um so i
floated up so let's go here okay
and here
yeah and uh
so this is where this is where the the
end of chest was i already minded some
of the treasure but it wasn't really
anything good there
except some iron and the sharpness five
sword whoa okay okay so here we go
right hmm
okay fine and close this here i already
built the
stairs so we can go up
all right okay and i already killed a
bunch of smokers but there's another one
all right
you will die soon enough friend okay
yeah i'll go that way oh
oopsies sorry i don't mean to you can
take those you can take those end rods
uh when you come over here okay i'll get
them all right be careful to not drop
them to the ground like stand right on
top of them when leaving them
gotcha
oh okay got it
i've still got it in me chat yeah you're
killing it
yeah
yesterday was great yay i hope you had a
good time
yeah but we basically cleared another
mission so i wonder what's going to come
next right
do you already have like a plan on where
to send us next um guess you'll have to
wait and see huh
[Music]
are you ready to come inside because i'm
building the stairs i just killed uh one
of the shulker
dudes
they should be dropping shells uh with
the shells you can build more of the
shulker chests cool really really cool
all right
oh there's an ender chest here
oh
you found the treasure
yeah uh-oh there's a lot of them in here
i oh i can imagine yeah i'm really
getting beat up
i'm gonna come to save you when i stop
floating
oh good
just just try to shoot them while you're
flying yeah it's when the boxes are open
right
they're not here
i'm coming
i think some of them dropped some shells
so maybe you can pick those up as well
okay
i'm on my way now
i'll be okay getting ready to fight on
site got my best friends by my side
it's really cool sakura they're
beautiful they're beautiful
i mean the lyrics are pretty simple i
guess yeah
pretty simple yeah perfectly simple
isn't it
[Music]
that's something nice
did you have a shoulder shell
and a chest here and then you can never
have enough of them cured
that looked good that was a good
treasure yeah the i'll save half for you
okay it looks so nice i fell down
three that's three
three gold for each of us and two
diamonds for each of us
and there's uh there's a cool diamond
sword if you want it you can have it
because that's with a pickaxe oh
i want to take a look at it yeah it's a
nice looking sword
well i can help you
are there any more i'm fine this place
is crawling
main of arthropods five is like a pretty
shitty enchantment i mean oh it's only
helpful if you're gonna go out to hunt
specifically spiders oh what the [\h__\h]
why would you ever hunt specifically for
spiders i guess so
spiders uh ah wait uh you don't have the
soft touch so i have to mine it with my
silk touch gotcha
oh i guess so wait i'll put my chocolate
chips down put some stuff in
yeah
they're making funny sounds
you wanna take down sure
um
on the bottom trying so hard to attack
us let's see
through the windows under rods i don't
see us
and the upper above your head
nice
sugar chest should i mine it no end rods
okay no no no take that end run okay
thank you
you said you like those i do i can't
wait to decorate my home with the onsen
as well
your
okay i will mind his chest yeah i guess
we can keep ascending the tower yeah
what we can keep going up the tower yeah
yes yes yes cool
and keep on mining everything that looks
nice to you i could also get you that
purple glass actually if you would
that'd be really cool i really do like
it
i i do feel like i hear that sometimes
in rap songs oh all the time yeah they
do sound like uh some news some new age
like uh did you sneeze again i didn't
hear it
john says bless you callie no i don't
think so
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
yeah we gotta build that where did you
come from oh boy a new friend buddy a
new friend
oh well uh i can't reach him though
oh yeah oh he's under the he's under the
stairs
i built a little slab uh at the at the
uh thingy that was
nice we got
there must be more work yeah teamwork
oh there's another one
all right
it's the chicken
all right oh god i gotta eat too it's
pretty high up in the tower but did i
forget a diamond
what do you mean i never got a diamond
over there i'll look on my way back then
we're pretty high up but i wonder how
much higher we get from here
oh from here on there shouldn't be
anything i think oh really
there's it there's a shulker there
though that's kind of scary oh
let me get those interrupts
over there i wonder
so many branches
so many branches around here yeah but
this is
actually still like a smaller
yeah really i've seen much bigger ones
where'd you go
i'm here i'm here i'm here i'm in bed
i'm back inside i went all the way
around to get the end rods whoa
okay so that's all on this branch let's
go down again okay
do it
careful careful
oh we chat
i've got the situation on the perfect
control yeah you're doing pretty good
where where where
sometimes they teleport
yeah all right also did you forget your
water you can pick your water back up
here i think you should did i leave it
oh yeah this is a big bottle of water
oh nice
i mean you can totally tint glass
yourself and i suppose it's pretty easy
but
why not take what we can get here yeah
of course see if we can get it yeah why
not
oh boy definitely a branch that we
haven't seen yet i'm gonna go left now
okay there's an end man here
let's see
that was close
i'm alive
ha ha ha ha stay alive staying alive
[Music]
it's fine slowly but surely i'll just oh
boy
that was an enderman just walking by
oh my goodness he's just chilling he's
just but mine is busy hey your house my
dude i already built up here but did i
elude it
there you are
is this where we work in the same place
no it shouldn't be
it shouldn't be
you guess it all your enemies
yeah yeah they do they do look
similar
[Music]
i've been sent flying oh boy
are you able to come up okay yep i'm
here
oh oh wait we've been
here yeah have we i was gonna say this
really reminds me of where we were
before but
um
hello i'm gonna fight you right here
this is kind of
weird i'm so proud of you callie you're
gaming you're trying you're gaming
yeah i get them i'm getting them
yeah nice okay
we're going down kelly close arrows
all right
we're gaming
yeah yeah yeah you you
i missed i missed a diamond somewhere
apparently um i think
that branch
oh there's two enemies be careful where
you're looking at okay
i'm super tired diamonds i guess here
because i said i i'm going left
did i really forget them
how
how is that possible
it's hard to remember like what branches
we've been to today what not
i did forget them okay oh yeah yeah the
stuff that i left there for you sorry i
probably should have taken all the
invited later but no no it's empty now
we can go okay uh so we went left now i
think right we haven't really been to
yeah yeah there's there's got to be one
placement probably no treasure but i
want to kill all of these monsters do
you want all of your soccer chests yes
[Applause]
dime monster
um
yeah they sound a very certain way
yeah you got something
you went up there got the shell good
jazz yeah yeah i got stuff for it to
make it yeah okay wait i'll take the
glass
okay oh look they're still attacking
themselves where did they come from i'm
not sure they're still able to get in
here somehow i don't know how
i of weird
it must be placed outside somewhere
okay
cali is
soundcloud rapper
you got me i've actually i never used
soundcloud but
i guess there's a lot of good music on
there too i mean yeah for sure like like
any place really but i guess it's got a
reputation of having a certain sound
that's uh more common on it i guess
but nothing beats uh
audio stuff
yeah audio stock i love audio stuff
my favorite place to be
they do have some bangers
yeah have we been on this one yes we
have sorry i'm getting confused hey have
we been i think there's this one one
that we haven't been into
it's this one right to the left no
no i see the windows are already
shattered oh yeah
we've been in all of
them we haven't taken all of the rods
yet oh
well i mean i have plenty i think but
oh 18 i guess i could always have more
but
have we seen everything
oh wait is there something connected uh
more on the
ground level yeah maybe
oh i'm done we're done it seems like
we're done looks like we're done
with this one it's a rather small city
but i think it's perfect for like
introducing you to yeah
and you didn't die and you had your your
body under control and there you fell i
can't believe it
you killed the shulker chest you killed
enderman you didn't panic when they when
they attacked you yay
i feel good about that so great hang out
i did my best
i did my best thank you you learned how
to conquer an ender city he taught me
how to do it though i bet that guy
dropped something
you taught me how to do it i appreciate
it
hey
welcome
we got a lot of loot out of it too how
many shulker
uh shells that you end up getting i have
four
four could you put some in the in your
ender chest oh it might have yeah yeah
yeah
how many do you need to make a shorter
chest
two
oh so basically you put um you put a
wait actually i will teach you now how
to create one there are
once you start using them you never want
to use normal chests ever again cool
wait
as well as different colors
yeah you can you can uh if you have like
paint a dye uh-huh which you can get out
of flowers you can paint them in any
color that's really cool so i brought
some
i brought some wood actually just for
this purpose
so
uh i will give you
some planks here okay now out of those
planks you first of all make a normal
chest
gotcha
a stinky normal chest i got it okay i
made it
and then uh
after you make the chest you put the
chest in the middle of the crafting
table
got it and put one shoulder shell above
and one shoulder
below that i made one
[Music]
which is purple by default but you can
always make it any color you can even
make them black cali really fancy wow i
can do that later
as well so if i have a purple one i can
make it black later
because it needs to be when i'm making
it oh okay
no no you can do it later lately cool
that's perfect um
yeah wait how many hmm
wait i didn't loot as many shulker
shells as i thought i did
only maybe i don't know maybe i'd pick
some up do you want this chest i just
made no i mean i have i have a lot so
i'm fine but i feel like i just
dropped oj they
they they don't always drop them they
sometimes just die without dropping them
i guess we had a lot of those oh i see i
yeah i left it in the shoulder
oh
wait that's my other shocker
oh wait i got a lot never mind hey
wow
okay wait so um
what we're gonna do next is we put um
all our important belongings into the
shulker and the stroker into the
energies and then we jump into the void
aye i can
so you just made a shulker chest i did
place it down put everything in your
armor
i can't put the shulker box into a
shulker box which means yeah that's that
would be uh yeah yeah
20 i get that that makes
sense i don't even need these anymore
but okay
this and
this and this
and this and this
yeah have you put everything inside yep
okay then put both of them into the
ender chest i just break them by hitting
them with my hand
uh oh yeah i guess wait i can
um yeah move your hand i guess if you
have nothing left okay as long as it
doesn't like hurt my box or anything
then yeah no no no
cool
all right and into the end of jessico's
very efficient this is
yeah so futuristic i feel like i've
upgraded from angabonga caveman
um to now i can see the future with you
and ina
future travelers the matrix wow oh we're
gonna try out flying in a moment okay
then we can end it but i want you to try
out flying all right i'm down um
actually you know what we're gonna
give it mending at least
okay because
the thing is with the elytra uh it
doesn't wait does it even have al
enchantment it doesn't break i think it
doesn't break even if you use it all up
i think or does is it only with
unbreaking
chat help me
there's so much to know
it it won't break okay so it won't break
even if you use up all the
um health on it okay
but but the thing is it's like you need
to put manning on it in order to repair
it
and
um you need to put like unbreaking free
on it otherwise it will be used up so
quickly oh okay wait a second i put my
oh
wait
you really gotta enchant it quite a bit
ah i guess i can't
mine it but all the other ones are in
here so i'm good to go okay the ender
yes right yeah
yeah there's one energetic all right
okay
we can we can go
we can jump into the void we're sorry
you're still using the same elytra that
you found in the beginning right
yeah i didn't lose it yet cool
but people like mikko senpai they have
already lost a couple of no that sounds
wrong because one thing that doesn't
save them i guess is
falling into lava
or falling in or like dying no i guess
dying somewhere in the middle of nowhere
and then not being able to pick it up
anymore yeah a couple five she lost
seven eight
she lost seven elytras that's so much
that's so many
oh my god oh wait should we like sign um
i guess it's pretty obvious that we
looted it i don't yeah i think we need
to put this on okay
okay and are you ready to jump let's do
it together
this time we're allowed to jump yes
because it's what we want
i watched you die before my eye oh if
only
i watched you die before my eyes anyway
what's up yay we did it
yeah yeah
and now if we're looking to
[Music]
are you kidding me
wait what's the matter with you like why
why would that well at least the ender
chest is safe
here wipe it
yeah let's put it down yeah uh and set
spawn again because i think your spawn
was that bad
um
we are going to
[Music]
just
go back um just take some food and your
weapons and everything out again okay so
that we can defend ourselves outside
take your armor
and
food
[Music]
you yeah need to do all that you big
dummy are you a big dummy you're not a
big dumb man it's okay
i bully myself every once in a while
you don't need to do that i know not
good i know
i forget oh so let me give you don't you
don't use it yet but let me already give
you some fireworks here thank you
cool oh i should get the elytra too
right
yeah uh no keep in mind first because
we're gonna go back and then and we're
gonna enchant it
okay
we're gonna put the fireworks from the
here i'll put the fireworks in the box
too
we put our the beds that inna gave us
into this chest wait i guess we can take
them again and you can take your melon
slices if you want to sure oh it's like
this
i got always your melon
give me that
all right
and we go outside
it's a normal sky
beautiful i put everything that you ever
find wow
okay i'm gonna double click fresh air i
can't afford to have made a mistake one
second
no problem take your time
[Music]
i'm so amazed we both didn't die i'm so
proud i know i really definitely thought
some death was going to be in the cards
for us especially because i'm involved
death and i have interesting reasons i
am deaf so i really can't avoid it but
that uh that went way better than i
thought it would
but i gotta say a lot of it was your
very careful planning and also being
able to make bridges very well
yeah bridgemaster yeah you're a bridge
master
but you're the balance master your
gallon stone that is one block paths
perfectly i did by by pressing shift
yeah yeah and now and now you also know
how to run superb properly you like
stannis yeah yeah i'm real quick now
real quick
around
have a little race now i think
wait so
now everyone in myth has a electro i
think i was the only one
yeah but i mean you don't it's not like
you really needed it until now yeah i
mean i play minecraft sometimes but just
not a lot this will help me though i
think
probably good for travel huh i just uh
yeah exactly i just really wanted it for
for like going on adventures to far far
away
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
they know how to get one if they want to
know sure absolutely how long can you
fly with one firework by the way
um so there's uh three different
strengths of fireworks the one that i
gave you is the one that i always use
it's the weakest one but
i think and most people would agree with
me that that one is good enough
um so with that one
you get like a small boost and then you
can just glide until you
completely lose the
power you will see in a moment when we
enchanted i think i got a mending book
um that we can put on it and i'm
breaking i don't think i have an
unbreaking book right now but
it will be fine as long as you have
mending on it for now good you you
should make it your goal to put
unbreaking free
on it mm-hmm
as soon as possible i'm breaking now i'm
over here there you are and [\h__\h] i'm
breaking through okay wanna do i have do
i have one breaking
ah kimmy schmidt oh you're right kimmy
schmittas
i'm breaking
i'm breaking two uh how did i get on
breaking free
real
you need ah we need exp to
uh
enchant
yeah i remember that you know thing
exp
huh well you know what maybe i'll just
give you mine for now and then you can
test it out oh yes to give that give the
stream a feeling of uh
we have done it successfully sure
okie dokie and then i will help you
enchant your elytra uh another time make
sure yeah or we go to the experience
yeah sure thing
let's just go home once and then see
yeah we're gonna do gotta eat food
yeah food it's important
well i guess you can combine
unbreaking two with unbreaking two to
get unbreaking three
which
sounds like my map is off but that's how
it works i guess
yeah
two times unbreaking too in the game
only makes unbreaking free oh wow not
well that's strange that's not how math
usually works
your shulker box what color do you want
it to be oh i want black and i want okay
uh teal
teal
yeah like a blue green
i think i have a lot of dye at home
actually actually red let's do red red
easy easy black and red edgy colors
you know what i can teach you how to
make red dye here take this red flower
oh okay i think that's the red flower oh
but that came to me
yeah get a bunch of those
red ones we're gonna make dye out sure
yeah there it is if you put like you
don't even need the crafting table if
you put the red flower
into the crafting box in your inventory
uh-huh one is enough actually kelly oh
yeah
so put it in there
let's see and then it should give you
red dye
okay yeah i got it
got a lot of it
thank you
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait go back go back oh
oh better okay
got it
nice
that felt good don't get too into a way
no no no no no oh there was another
creeper there i guess
come on mr bone yeah that's right you
don't like that mr bones do you yeah you
only missed your bones
there you go yeah
sorry pepe sorry that's cool
my my deadbeats are extra well-behaved
these are rambunctious ones that need
punishing
right
oh that rose bushes give two red
diamonds that's pretty neat
nice
all right we're pretty much uh there
just gotta go through the water okay
ignore them
ignore that
skeleton yeah maybe skellington
do you feel like you
learned some
new minecraft skills today yeah
definitely there was a ton of stuff that
i didn't know you you taught me thank
you teachers
i feel like
it's funny because like
normally i like have stuff under control
but whenever i play minecraft with with
people i always feel like a little baby
and like baby student who's like
learning
learning with my teacher i mean it's fun
but
so sorry
[Music]
yeah oh i'm level one time
yeah me too
i have one experience for it
for enchanting with mending chat how
much exp do how much levels do i need
one one mending on an elytra how much
does that take two
let's see
with fireworks you make that with
gunpowder right more than one mending
needs two and fireworks yeah i can teach
you how to do that too actually so
that's why you need gun powder but you
also need uh paper oh okay
so paper i actually have a farm for
paper i will show you so for the future
if you need it take as many as you want
thank you
next okay
nice i'm gonna remember
okay
oh wait i show you
i'm gonna show you i hear you are you
still here yeah yep i'm following
i'm using your jumping technique but you
are still so speedy hey you're so quick
uh if you're if you're like if you
didn't eat enough food then you will not
be able to run so far oh i see
i'm still probably so this is where the
paper farm is basically i have two
you look inside and you see sugar cane
but out of sugar cane you can make paper
so this is basically a paper farm cool
but you can also make sugar out of it so
it's also a sugar firm wow bakery nice i
like it yeah i'm sorry so
whenever you need those but i already
gave you some fireworks for so for now
just for trying out you're good sure
and
okay i will just give you my elijah now
thank you
i want you to try out flying yeah i
believe i can fly
let's sleep first yeah and we gotta get
to an ender chest
well you can uh i'm placing i'm gonna
place a bed here for you thank you
sleepover
that's what are you bed used to be
back in the day exact same spot
all right
they're still uh
they're still the little
[Music]
yeah with these bars like you've uh made
a shiny prison for these chickens
yeah i like it why you want to make a
shiny prison it sounds like fun
i'm going down
i'm going you can go back up again i'm
going up you've got a secret little
basement in there oh my god
shiny smiley prison
shiny smiley frisbee
all right kelly okay the wings
uh-huh um
just uh
you're here for testing out i think you
gotta put them where your chest plate is
so you can't wear a chest plate while
you're wearing electron i see oh wow
that looks really like uh there's
something like seductive about that oh
yeah yeah it makes sense with the with
the shader
or optifine or something cape that you
have oh really so should i turn on
shaders yeah
no no i don't know i don't know you
already have a special cape oh normally
if you play normal basic ass minecraft
you don't have a special cape but you
have a very special
yeah and it mixes with the elytra wow so
you're gonna put the fireworks in your
taskbar i don't have them yet because i
put them in the ender chest i didn't
want to lose them well then let me let
me give you here more oh thanks
all right where did i put them basically
you uh on the task bar somewhere
and then you jump twice
first of all try jumping twice you will
you will feel some kind of difference
whoa
yeah and then when you're on the second
jump you gotta
uh
make the rocket go boom okay give that a
try and maybe
yeah
you gotta aim kind of upwards oh i see i
see okay gotcha okay i can do this i can
do this all right you can do it
wow
my god
[Music]
one or like when you're flying you can
keep on wait really i think the
fireworks go off again so you can cool
over okay i'm gonna do that again
whoa
i'm flying
ah toward the sky i believe i can fly
yeah oh watch sands tennis racquets
whoa i'm flying around i'm flying to
ollie i'm going to the passing express
yes ladies amelia show me
show me what's good
there she is this is
amazing this is so cool
going through your hair
yeah that was that was beautiful this is
so wonderful i'm having so much fun
i'm on amelia's chest
not like um fly into a mountain okay
okay
gotcha
as i said sometimes they
load in slowly and you can't quite
prepare so always fly very high
uh-huh on a high level
um and you can always if you're if you
land you got to try to have a soft
landing by going uh
getting closer to the ground like slowly
oh i see not like
not like a like straight dive into the
ground you just gotta try to land like
an airplane basically imagine
you are an airplane
yes i'm an airplane and i need fuel
and if there's water around it's always
safe to just dive into the water if you
need to land cool
wow this is awesome
accomplishment listen
whoa that looks amazing someone's house
i think didn't i did i give you a
mending book before i think i saw some
enchantment books in your
in your chest
[Music]
you see you slam dunk into the water
yeah
you got mending in your chest oh heck
yeah wonderful so i can apply what
you're gonna do in the future
to make your own elytra work properly is
you're gonna take that mending book and
your elytra the unenchanted one yeah you
put it put both of them into an anvil
uh-huh okay uh
and then you while you do that you can
also name the
like one i gotta i gotta think of a good
name i'll think of a good one
because mine are called hotlines so you
gotta top that off with one more yeah
well yeah that's right one that's
perfect for me i'm gonna do that
thank you so much yara it's wonderful i
love it i believe
[Applause]
i took some screenshots of you flying
i'm having a good time
let me go up to kiara and gura
oh cool
oh i feel like i'm definitely going to
run into something watson tennis rackets
let me see if i can find it
oh it's much closer now than i than i
felt it was before
yeah you can go so quickly between
phoenixton and the spawn point and your
carnival and everything uh-oh
uh-uh go in the water did you hurt
yourself
i ran out of fireworks ah yeah yeah
that's see see that's why you need a lot
of fireworks like one stack is not gonna
last you very much understandable uh oh
i wanna do here
uh that was pretty close but you know
what we're safe we're good
i couldn't yeah i do not have i'm
breaking but i can probably get one from
phoenix then later on
hold on heck yeah i'm gonna go back to
you now
okay
kfb what is this animal yeah uh that's a
goat they're goat are they now animals
they're new yeah
wow
nice grass that's cute yeah goat it's
too perfect
they're they're so adorable like they
can actually jump up um like several
blocks rather than other animals who can
only jump up one block young goats can
jump up many blocks
can you ride them
let me ride yeah
no can you
go
oh
do you want to give me back my electro
no yes of course
there you go i'm playing with you
thank you thank you for teaching me the
ways of glorious elijah it was nice
taking hot wings for a spin as well that
was fun
hey
wait a second i want to turn on my
shaders for a screenshot oh me too me
too
all right one sec
i'm going to turn them on as well
let's see
[Music]
wait where's your electron now in the in
the chest yep i can go grab it yeah
let's take it together with the elijah's
on nice idea
sounds good to me where should we do it
i like how my my wings i don't know have
you noticed it kind of looks like my
cape looks like a phoenix too oh
you see
yeah it does have like that kind of glow
to it
right like the pattern on it you see the
pattern yeah it's yeah it's like it's
like wings i love it like a firebird
yeah yeah cool i don't know how but
okay uh you need uh you need an energy
right right
there's one at the
portal okay
yeah i see so how do the designs get
chosen for the elytra
is it random ah but normally it has no
design it's just like kind of black oh
but you can add one on
not really like if you have a why is it
so buggy what the hell it's very laggy
it's usually not that laggy what the
hell very odd did they change something
could have been
there has been a new update recently i
think it definitely changed something
um but yeah so uh depending on what's
like if you use optifine or if you use
um some kind of shader they sometimes
give you some fancy patterns on your
cape i see
interesting okay okay let me read these
real quick
all right
i have what i need for now now it's
better i think our render distance was
too high
oh yeah
okay okay oh yeah good stuff yeah
yeah yeah you put that on that suits you
very well thank you i think so too i
love my head now let's while the sun is
going down so nicely let's take a
screenshot here yeah nice idea the
sunset
perfect with the we should take it off
our backs maybe ooh yeah maybe get a
couple of couple screenshots yeah
all right how do we take a screenshot
again listen
uh f2 and maybe turn off the interface
with f1 first okay
nice idea
all right and now and then wait on the
front front
yeah peace
peace
weight position
there you go okay yeah yeah yeah okay
like this that's a little too close hold
on all right perfect perfect all right
ready cheese wait f f2 okay gotcha let's
take a couple
geez
yay
you got that huge snoot now i do have a
big old snoot huh
maybe you can smell better now yeah
extra extra sniffing senses
this has been amazing congratulations
thank you
kiara thank you for the fantastic
adventure that was so fun
i'm glad it went well
you know so much about minecraft i feel
like if i wasn't with someone who knew
so much about minecraft i'd be in big
trouble um oh thank you don't worry
about that i can teach you more we can
go on another trip sometimes please
with the wings we can fly together
let's go on a trip yeah yeah yeah we can
go anywhere i'm down
i'm down i'll show you red cows if you
want oh that sounds cool is that is that
the new place that you found
yeah
we found that me and ina found a special
island that has red cows that give
endless milk and there's like mushrooms
um growing on top of the cows what the
[\h__\h]
that sounds amazing minecraft is cool
it's just full of new surprises i have
never heard of
it is it do be like dan damn so thank
you kelly for the collab today thank you
um to the audience for watching and uh
sweating sweating yeah
together such moments
there are some clutch moments for sure
but you know what uh it ended up being a
great adventure and i'm glad we went on
it together and i'm looking forward to
the next adventure that we have
um
yeah and thank you audience as well for
cheering us on and uh and entertaining
us with your quips and also helping us
uh every once in a while we appreciate
the heck out of you thank you you guys
thank you
thank you i hope you had fun i had fun
all right i hope this dad had fun yeah
we all had fun yeah
do you have any announcements you want
to make
yeah i'm not really stuff people coming
up no like i think uh yeah i think my
audience knows that song is coming up
and all that
sounds good
all all righty i mean i guess that's it
yes we're done then huh
[Music]
i'm excited
yeah me too that was a blast even though
my frame rate is like 10 10 fps eating
[\h__\h] right now turn down the render
distance go go escape and then uh video
settings and then on the top right
render distance maybe put it down to
like 10 chunks or something like video
settings render distance
yeah 10 chunks
sure yeah something like that should
make it much better let me see
maybe that will be fine oh yeah i think
it's much better yeah
it's a little better it's a little bit
yeah
okay all right and just make sure that
the elytra you enchanted before you use
it i will you could use it already but
it's not really good enchanted first
okay okay sounds good i'll be extra
careful i will not miss this fantastic
gift i have been given
i will i will be fun with
hope you remember me this is kiara she
is a phoenix
minecraft
my craft expert
so thank you for coming on our journey
you guys and i guess we'll catch you on
the flip side what should we end on yeah
yeah sounds good to me
all right i'm gonna turn on all the
effects here we go ready
three
two
bye guys
[Music]
you