DET
[Music]
A
that
[Music]
H
T
[Music]
Ta
This turn is brought to you by Mr. Misao
[Music]
Masu Dub
O
[Music]
every
alsoThereisSpecial
EXTRAattheendofv
makestay
for
every
backdayisthe20epeI
thoughtknowforthe
20THepeIneedSpecial
forguysand
areSpecialTalk
EPbringtotheoneand
onlythatLet
metalkasI think I gave the usual explanation at first,
so please listen.TalkisLIFEtalkwith
thep
andlyJapaneseHLIFE
tal
TALENTBR
asesVI
asbyHost
Takahoto is an interview talk for English speakers.The
purpose is to mainly focus on Japanese talent while still being active.  The
purpose
is to let people overseas know more about it.This information is
provided by the host, Takasekihara.
So, today is the 20th time. It's already the 20th time, so I've
prepared a special guest. The 10th time was
probably A-chan, and the 20th time was Yago,
so the 30th time will be the same. I
'm already worried here, but it looks like I'm going to get angry.  Today's
EholoTalkIhope
everyonewillenjoy
todayHTalkforgetby
thewaysinceAVery
SpecialEpisode
PleaseUseTheHASHthe
hasagHTalkevenin
EnglishorinJapanese
toTweetaboutWhatyou
seetodayWhatyouhear
todayMaybeevenwith
somescreenshotsI'd
love to have a hashtag holotalk on Twitter and share my impressions and screenshots.Thank you very much to all of you.  I'm
not really excited. Well, it's not my first time,
but it's hard to talk properly like this.  It's your
first time, right?
[Music]
LIFE Today, I would like to find out more about Hol Live and Ya-san,
but are you ready? This is my husband.
Thank you. Yes, but first, I
would like you to introduce yourself.  Introducing myself,
either in English or Japanese,
please.Yes, HMyName
Tani CEOofcorporation
our
prodthankforinv
meI'm sorry, I
made a mistake.Ah, did I make a mistake?I
should say thank you for invitmetotalk.
No, no, no, that
's perfect. You're wonderful, Mr. Yag. You can speak English quite well
. I thought of this myself. I also asked him to
teach me a little bit about it. That's
okay. Well, everyone
knows Mr. Yago, so I do
n't think he really needs to introduce himself.
But, okay, I'd like to get into the questions right away.
Well, the first question is, what kind of activities have you been doing lately?
Well, I guess so.  I
often work at a company, like
conducting job interviews, deciding on company policies,
thinking about how to improve the company's organization, etc.
Yes, I see.
[Music]  ]
says
aswsComp
ORC
orimpr
[Music]
That
's a perfect answer, so I'll move on to the next one. Yago
's name is Yag. I
would like to know the origin of it.
Well, Yago is just a big plate.
It all started when Mr. Sule couldn't read the name of my name and mispronounced it as Yago.
Well, I actually knew it, but I just
asked. Yes, Subaru-senpai.  It was quite a while
ago. How long ago
was it? It was quite a long time ago, about two years ago, two years ago.
Before that, I used to call Mi-chan by her book name.
Until then, I probably didn't use her name much on stream.
I don't think I was ever invited, but that has changed quite a bit.Recently, Yago-san has
been appearing in a variety of ways, such as introducing merchandise, and appearing in videos of some strange super bits.  I've been working at
Momosha, but I don't feel like it's a little tough right now.I've said
that before, but what kind of work do you do?  I'm
doing photo shoots and recordings in the middle of the day, so I'm doing a lot of photo shoots, so I'm
a model. I'm a
super model.
Thank you very much. I see. I
don't have any hard feelings. I'm
glad you guys.  That would be great. That would
be a great help. To Holoto, to
be honest, at first I was joking that I would invite Yago-san for a day,
but I
didn't think he would really come.
Thank you, Yako-san.  You can call me here.
Thank you
aboutyears
agylongtimeAGtried
toreadHISnameonam
butShereadthekanj
wrongThereislike
severalwaystoread
kanjAsYouMightknow
andmademistake
instead
ofandfromthereonIGU
EverybodypickedUpon
itandIasked
untilcallhiminstead
ofand
rightnowhesooften
SocialMedialike
showing likeyou
showingothermers
streamslikefor
feelingshesaysNohe
isveryhappytohelp
outWhereverHeCan
WheneverHeCanYeahso
helikestohelpout
likethatandiisaid
thatIoriginallyjust
saidthatweshould
invitejagasajoketo
mytomySTREAMWHOLE
Talk
butYeahIthinkit
wouldreallyhappenI
thinkhewouldsayyes
butHEREWEAREHeis
Partoftalknow20TH
Episodesoreally
happyaboutthatand
thenIsaid
Sorryforbutsaidthat
Thereare
typicallySome
peopleWhoknoweven
InsideoftheCompand
have
Specialprep
foralsowantESP
person
Watchfor
Well, let's take a look at it together. The
first one
[Music]
have
Yes, this is an amazing design. Oh
wow, this has me written on the shoulder. I
think it's very nice.
[Music] It
stinks, it
stinks, it looks stinky. Looks like Yamume-chan doesn't know about Yago-san. I've seen
this and that. Oh, that's right. I've seen that.
Oh, I'm sorry, it's my house.  I do
n't think Mu-chan actually knows what he's saying, but he's
such a forgetful kid, so I'm sorry.
Yeah, were you shocked when you saw this? Well, I guess you're right
, he's moving so much. I do
n't know.  He was probably wearing a mask as well.
[Music]
Now, let's move on to the next question.
Please tell me about it. Well, after I graduated from that university, I
first joined a game company and
worked as a game producer.
After that, I went to work at an Internet company.
Well, before that, I
started and ran my own Internet company, so I guess that's
true.
Companies like Local Information and
Internet service companies
are the ones who don't become covers.
OkSothatnotsame, how
many years did it take from graduating from that university
to being able to cover?
Well, I feel like if I say that, my age will be revealed,
but I
don't want it to be revealed, right? It's been quite a while since I
went to university.  That's
fine, but let's find out a little more
. What's
your average work day?
What is your schedule like?
Please tell me in detail. Yes, this
seems like something you do after you wake up, right? In the morning.
Well, I wake up around 7 o'clock and go for a run,
and then I
go for a run every day on weekdays.
After that, I study conversation three times a week, and then I
go to work around 10 o'clock.
Before I go to work, I have A conversations several times a week.
Yes, I study about three times. That's
amazing.
After that, after going to a meeting, I
have about 23 interviews a day, and then I go home several times.  I
often go out to work and do my own work.My
job involves thinking about the company's strategy, and so on.Yes, I
see, and I
go home around 9 o'clock.  That's right, that's right
OKHehasverybusyDay
everysousuallywakes
upat7amandheGoes
runningeveryweek
rightafterwakingupI
reallyRespectThat
Thatwasasurprisehe
staysFithestaysbuff
runseveryweekday
beforeWorkand
actuallysaidtimesa
weekbeforeWORKhe
alsoparticipatesin
likeEnglish
lessonnotaproper
Lessonmorelikea
conversationThing
whereyou just talk to
someonewhospeaks
EnglishandThrough
conversationyou
learnthelanguage
Theydothatlikethree
timesaweekandthenhe
goestoworkataround
10amuntil9PMand
withinthose11hours
Whathedoesis
andenheattend
[Music]
and
Thank you for the details.Running
every day is probably good for your body,
but I'm
surprised you even find the time to do it.
Yes, it's very difficult
[Music]
Yes, let's move on to the next question.
Ejajin,
tell me about the life and death that started Eka.  I would like you to
tell me what the environment was like before Hollive and Hol Live started.I heard that
life and death started, but I
had experience at a game company and an Internet company, so I was able to use that experience to my advantage.  I was
wondering if I could start a content company like that,
and in the future, I'd like to
start a business in VR and develop games and things like that.I see.
[Music]
togowithsomeVR
relatedstuffinthat
fieldbecausehethat
inthefuturethereisa
ofuninthat
Businessand
He
went to
[Music]
I see, I see. Well then, what about the cover?
Before Hol Live started, were you doing some kind of game
development? Well, you
were making things like that VR table tennis game.
What game is it? It's a table tennis game. I see.
[Music]
I see. This leads to the next question.
Hmm,
how did Eno-gyo go from being a technology company to an idol management company
? Well, my company is still a technology
company that
also manages talent.  That's how I
feel about it.I first
experienced managing So-san, and then Roboko-san, and then I
started Hololive.I
see.StillConsiderthe
compybeTECHCompany
asDo
Management and
laterJOINaswelland
startedmaningthose
talentsandafter
experiencefromthat
They
GENERATIONI'd
like to ask you a little more about what happened after that,
but I wonder
how that happened, and you
suddenly decided to include that idol.I see.That's
right, that VR.  When I was making the game, I
thought, ``Isn't it possible to use this VR
device and say
something like Nemic?''  As I was
thinking about it, I
realized that I was actually starting to test the idea of running a virtual talent company.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
Moving on to my next question,
what kind of image did you have before launching Jajin Holive
? And I'm
sure your vision has changed a lot since your initial vision.
Well,
when I first launched Hololive, I had the impression that it was a
group of streamers from the real world or another world.Yes, well,
while I was running it for a while,
Hololive...  After performing for the first time during the summer,
they performed a non-stop
story show in uniform costumes, and I
think that their idol side has become more noticeable than their average appearance.
fromuniversoreven
THEREALWORLDlike
anyandthenCome
TogetherasaGroupso
forexampleWHOLE
Summertheyputout
theirfirstORIGINAL
SongFromlikeall
talentstogetherand
thenTherewasNONSTOP
whereforthefirst
timehadaconcert
wherelikeeveryone
wasingthesamekindof
[Music]
I'm sure that's a famous comment, but they
wanted to create an idol group like AKB.  You
said it kind of, right? Well, I
guess I'm pretty
good at it myself. I like Cross Frontier and things like that. Well, I
know what you mean, but I
have a dream of becoming that virtual idol talent.  That's what I was thinking.Yes, I see.
Say
4islikethebiggest
IdolGroupthepopular
IDGroupJapanandhe
sayslikelikesFRfor
EXhe
alsoto  She
's a Cheryl fan, I see. Yeah, that's
great.
saidmoreFcertain
IDsaidAF
ofOther than that Hololive, my
favorite is Sheryl.
Well, she might be one of my favorites.
Well, yes, she's pretty, she's
good at singing, and she's very good.  I think he's an idol-like figure,
yes, but many people have said that his image has changed from that first
image to the point where he's
probably
crying.
However, I think the current image of Hol Live is quite different from what I had in mind. I
think it's a more interesting group than I imagined.
[Music]
people, so you won't be disappointed.
Yes, that's right.
Neko de here.
But I'd like you to see Kinoki. I've
prepared another one, so I'm
going to theST. Let's
take a look. Yes, don't worry, I'll go to Yago today.
One day, I
met Yago, and he was smiling a lot,
as if he were saying hello to you.Why is
Yago always smiling so much?I wonder if the
captain who was grinning so much had a big smile on his face.  I'll do
my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best I'll do my best.
Yago, I thought, ``Wow, the captain is real.''
When Yago is surprised, he yells. No, he doesn't do that at all. He's so kind. He's so kind. When something sad happens,
Yago cries.  That's what it's like to be on this trip.I
cry, but I'm full of charm, and
even if something bad happens, I
don't get angry.I don't know, but what do you think?I wonder if they're
yelling at the employees, no, no, but.  The
employees also
praised Yago a lot.He
seemed like a really nice person.He seemed really nice.He
seemed kind.He
was crying.He was crying.He was crying.He was crying.He was crying.He was crying.He was crying.He was crying.He was
crying.He was crying.He was crying.  Maybe, maybe,
maybe,
but I'm sure everyone has seen it before. I
wonder if they're going to broadcast a crying image of Yago, so sweet. It's
not okay to sleep. It's as popular as Ego.  It would be
nice to have that April Fool's Day.
Yago is still 2D. It's still 2D.
Hey, Yago had a new costume today. Yago
had a new costume today.
[Music]
Yeah, that's right, he had a new costume today.  Fu-chan also
looked like that today. Fu-
chan was wearing a new outfit today. It looks
like she was taking some photos, or maybe it was a photo shoot.  It's
okay, but today
when I was sitting on Corone-senpai's lap, Sago came to say hello, and
Ko-senpai started pumping his knees, and the
captain
greeted him by saying "eighting", which was really
awkward.It
was weird.  I'm in the mood.Oh, I
see.I see.LetMOVback
so
ofhave3DNow is the time to make my 3D debut.Maybe
this is my 3D debut.Maybe
not.Maybe that's it.
Oh, and even this, this
is a new book.It's some clothes.It's some new books.Oh,
where is it?The shirt is
new from 2000.Yes, it's new.Oh, it's
unveiling.Awesome 3D unveiling.New
costumes.  The shirt is already so exciting
Hey
havethinkcouldand
alsoaboutifThisisa
newoutfitthathas
beforeButhesaysTHE
tshirtTHEshirt
underneathisSowe
haveSpecialreveals
todayhisnewoutfit
And
HisIthinkVery
SpecialtodaybythewayBy
the way,
all the celebrities said
they had seen Yago cry,
but I have never seen it.Can you
please show me that?It makes
me cry.  I think
Yago puts a lot of emotion into his work, so I think he can
show everyone crying. Nene said that thoughts that everyone has seen HIS Crying FACE.  beforebutI personallyhavenever
seenItmaybeIneedto makehimCryOneDayand Isaidthat perhapsis emotionally invested
intoLIFEandknowHIS
CompanyHISBabyso
Maybefeelslike
I
feel like Hololive is my baby.  I'd
like to ask about that member,
but Yago-san, I'd like to ask about that member.  I
have an image of entertainers as being incredibly kind,
but I don't think I've ever seen them
be that kind, but are they really strict with their employees? Well,
maybe they're strict when they need to be strict.  No, I see.
[Music]
AllasSweetandperson
Who
neverHIS
says
mustIf you ask Mr. Branchsha, he'll probably
say that he's the best boss and the kindest person.I
think that's true.It was a clipping of Marin-senpai,
but let's move on to the next question.
Let's go THENEXTquestion:
Well, what's the most important thing when hiring new talent
? I
guess it's the motivation. Well,
you've done Holotalk 20 times today, so you're going to
continue your streaming activities.
Personally, I think that motivation is the most important thing, because I think it's quite a difficult task, and I think that if the person himself is not motivated, he won't be able to continue.Yes
I agree
strongly
that would
beknow
Essays
knowbeingable
toly
knowneedhave
quite
AndLife
I wonder if it's okay to ask this.Do you
even participate in interviews for that new talent?I have
n't participated in any interviews lately, though.
BecauseWetalkedabouthimdoingalotofinterviewseverydaybutthoseareforlike
newemployeesForThe
companynotlike
talentsandIaskedhim
ifheStilltakespart
inAUDITIONinthe
auditioning process
ifhechecksOUTifhe
doeslikethe interviewsforNew
talentsaswellandhe
saysthatthesedaysNo
notanymoreButhe
makessuretoalways
likeBeforetheDEBUT
kindofintroduce
himselftotheTALENT
At first
Yes, I was interviewing, etc.
Yes, what kind of things were you looking at
? What kind of personality did you see? That's a
difficult question. No,
it's difficult, but I wonder
if it's a person who is meant for broadcasting.  Yes,
that's right.I think I was
watching whether this person could continue streaming for a long time.Yes,
Oksoas
[Music]
was
Focus
person.I see,
for the next question [Music], he often plays original songs by live members.  Is there a
song that you sing along with or that you like? I
don't have a song that I sing along with.
Kanema: I'm behind the scenes so I don't
want people to know about it. Yeah, yeah,
Shiny Smiley Story.  Yeah, I
guess I don't understand the lyrics,
but I only listen to the songs once in a while,
so I guess I get it, but
in my private life, I
listen to anime songs and idol songs like Hololive.  I do
n't care if it's true or not, it's quite like that.Well, there may be times when I listen to the soundtrack of a work I like.
Well, the music that I listen to in my spare time in my spare time
is anime soundtracks, yeah,
and rock and metal,
anime soundtracks, etc. I'm
biased when I listen to EDM.
EDM is good, I like it too.
[Music]
there
wantP
[Music]
Maybe
LittlePUSHmoreWhat
kindofSONGShe
listenstoInhisfree
timeprivatelyandhe
sayshelikestolisten
toSoundsfromanimor
alsoHelikesEDMso
thereyou
guineat
edmcI'm not going to an EDM concert.
In that Japan, I
went to that Japanese Leelim concert.
But on the other hand, I thought Chiara was floating. Is
n't it so easy to see?
No, on the other hand, is it easy to tell when she's wearing a mask
? It's really hard to be a famous person.
What do you respect most about being a Hololive talent, Mr. Jin-e-ya
? Well, I think it's the fact that they are working hard towards their own goals, and they have been
given a lot of lessons, and that's the result.
When the performance was amazing, I was
really impressed and realized that they really worked hard.
[Applause]
comeandtheir
goalsgoingtodance
lonsandimprovingtheirSkillseveryand
performComeOutthat
asimpressivehimMOV
After all, do you
often watch concerts by that member?
Well, concerts are basically  You've been watching all of them,
haven't you? That commemorative broadcast,
Moruto, and the important broadcast.  Well,
everyone is working really hard on that
concert.The technology is getting better and better, especially in the recent Holo
Live concerts.I
think they're really working hard.
[Music]
Speaking of the concert, it's scheduled to be held in March.
What are the highlights of Hololive Surface?It's
exciting and exciting.That's right.Look,
there really is a lot of it.I
feel like there are many things I can't say.I see.  We
hope to provide live performances that even people who can't make it to the venue can enjoy, so please look forward to
it.
However, by the time this hole talk
was broadcast, it had already
been announced, so I'll just say it. I'm
glad I said it.
Well, it was announced on Friday, and this
is now
in the future.
Noe is
Future
RECONfridwasjust
announcedwill
beare
highlightsandPOINTS
worthyToeButhe
reallysaymuchatall
andalotofSecretif youcometotheactualconcertyoucanstillenjoyyouknowwhile
towatchITOnlineso
arepreparingtomake
itenjoyableFor
EveryonePleaseforto
andwanttock
[Music]
This
is the first time that Ano Shikataka and ID's Ea have appeared, but this is the first time for a concert
like this in which the Japanese members of Hololive are participating.
But why did we decide to include us this time
?Well, right now Hololive
has fans from all over the world,
so we
want to make it enjoyable for people from all over the world.
I'm really
looking forward to it, so I'm very happy to be able to participate this time.I'm really looking forward to it.I'm
looking forward to it.Yes, there are many things I can't say.
But everyone, please wait for the third festival.Everyonewaitfor
theNowaboutStill
Little
whileareexitfor I
think Wawa will be able to answer the next question in more detail.I
think there are still people who don't know about Hololive, or Hololive, and Hololive, so I'll explain them here.
What kind of project is this?
Could you give me a rough explanation? Yes, there is a project related to
Live Alternative and Followers.  It
's a Metaverse project, similar to the kind of virtual world that appears in Hololive Alternative, and I
want to create a place where talents and fans and fans can interact with each other.  Yeah,
yeah, yeah, Hololive Error. It's a horror content project that aims to show you the
other side of Hololive celebrities, other than their broadcasts.
Well, there's also a game coming out now, so definitely check it out.  I
hope you give it a try,
but I feel like Hololive
Alternative hasn't been explained to me yet.Hololive
Alternative is
like Tama-
Other, which depicts a world where that Hololive talent might be.  Is that what it
feels like? Yes, I see.
Maybeguys
[Music]
virworldend
Earthout
[Music]
oftalentsthatare
madeoutoftheVirtual
WORLDthatyouseein
WHOLE
Alternativesothe
GOALHereis  toofferaplacewhere
theFans and talents together allCanCome thererecentlycame
OUTagamewhereHorror
GAMEactuallyand
theshow
[Music]
theirSID I see, they're
working on a lot of projects, yes,
yes, they're busy. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, they're busy. Have
you
tried Full Live Error yourself? I
haven't tried it directly yet.  So, I want to try that.What do you think
of that live streaming?
No, I don't like it.  I wonder
if I'm not good at that kind of horror.I'm a little bit scared of that, so I'm like, ``I
tried
saidasked
fortrying
OUTlittle
[Music]''
and
just like that, when it comes to horror, I become like that.
Now that you have entered the number one spot in en and ID, do you have any plans to expand to other countries
? Well, first of all, let's talk about en and ID.  I
'd like to do my best to expand the business.I've
just started selling mags, so I'd like to focus on this.Also, I'm
sure male
talent Hollow Stars is also overseas.  I
think it would be good if people in other countries knew more about it,
and if possible, I would also like to
be able to translate it for people in other countries as well.
Well, I guess it's for various countries.
Well, for example, content like holograms, I
think it would be great if it were possible to translate videos.
Now, Korean  It
's very popular, so I'm
looking forward to the possibility of it someday. Chiara
just wants to give you a
hint.
I guess it's because of Aki who liked it so much.
OnceAgainofsecrets
knowwhatwillhappen
inthefutureLIFEAll
Tryimpr
curLIFEasNext.  Next question
NEXTquestionSo that you
don't lag behind in terms of technology,
companies or indies in the same industry.  I've
been watching closely to see what kind of technological developments vtubers have made.
Yes, I'm checking the technological developments on a daily basis.
Yes, there are quite a few people from overseas who
use VR chat to stream videos.  I
wonder if there are a lot of them.That's
right, I
can't collect them in real life, so I'm using VR chat and
having fun.I
think that's really amazing.Thank
you very much.  Thanks to Amelia Wasso  That
's right, Amelia, I
think it's really amazing.
I'm looking forward to the day when Melia will be behind the scenes.
In particular, I've
been watching Kira, and overseas vtubers are evolving into live 2D and other amazing things.  I
think it's amazing. It's the
same with everyone in the indies. I'm already
working hard on my own 3D models. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
it's great.
[Music] I
see.
Mamonue development. Don't give up. Hey, cover. Try your best.
Let's do our best. Let's go to the final question. Let's
go to the final question. Let's go to the final question.  I
want to eat Aki that goes well with Meto, I
want to eat, I want to collaborate,
yeah, yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm really
happy and Nejipet Nejipet
Yes, I understand, I think so at the festival too. Yeah, Yago and I
are friends of the soul. We're friends of the heart. But it's true.
Minecraft's thumbnail Yago is here, Polka-chan.
Yes, I know that they send each other things and replies, so
that's the kind of image that can be created.So the
correct answer was Lupolka.Yes,
and then there was
Yago.It's true that Yago is such a friend.  That's
about Polka-chan's
face, and I'm sure that's Yago-san's.I want her to
have a really smiling face instead of her usual smiling face.What
's wrong with this?  We're
very determined, and we
think about each other on a general level.I think that this is my
heart, and I think that I am also my heart.
[Music] That
guy and Polka-senpai are really
close friends.  I
have an image that I was asked questions in English almost every day, and I was asked to answer them.Epolka
Polka Senpai on Twitter.
I think he was like, ``I'm pawning my English to Mr. Yago.''
Why? Ok
[Music]
likes
ENG
May. I think Polka-senpai is really good
at it. I think of Kara-san as a friend.  I do
n't know,
but I have the impression that I get invited to projects
quite often.Yes,
yes, Poka-senpai, there are quite a few projects like that where people behind the
scenes are invited to broadcast.
Yeah, that's right, I have an image of Borde appearing a few times.
Yes, I'm rooting for you.
Anysayes
[Music]
Thank you very much
What do you think hall live production will look like in five years' time
?
What is the vision for Hippo for Yako? Well, what will it be
like for people around the world in five years?  I feel like vtubers have become something of a
commonplace in the world,
and I want to make them an indispensable part of everyone's lives.
One person I've heard of  A
member said the same thing. I
think someone will probably answer it now, but
actually someone
answered some M answered the same Way as did ALI think was
ORIGINdiffquestion someone answer the way Maybe guys know who the answer from him Was
thathewantsto
makeinto
thatthepeopleall
over the
worldliveany
[Music]
I'll probably watch it later in the chat. I
see.
[Music]
Perfect  I'm
going to Anne QUESTION,
oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, the
next question, I
don't think everyone knows the difficulties behind people and companies.  However, we often only look at successes,
so
what kind of failures and hardships have you faced as individuals and as a company, and
how have you overcome them?
Yes, that's right.I'm quite an
old man, so I think I have a harder time compared to the average person.Yes, yes, that's
right.I don't care what other people
think of me, I don't care what I've accomplished in my life.
Personally, I think it's important to focus on what you want to do and then try not to make the same mistakes again.
Can you give it to me? Yes.
Well, this
is the second company that I started, and it
wasn't like my first company went really well,
so after running a company once and learning a lot of things, I decided to start my first company.  I've
tried this company several times, so
I guess that's quite true.
Managing a company is difficult in its own way, so even if I
tried that one time
and it didn't go that well.
OK
[music]
sayhas
peopleisalways
focusingonwhathe
wantstoaccomplishIn
hisownLIFEandhe
triesToNeverrepeat themistakesagainand
everyimpr
and
heto
andisSECONDComp
himselfsoItwasHIS
firstTrynotlikeit
surprisinglywent
wellonthefirstTry
andHereitisMiracle
CompanyNohedidlearn
althefirsttimehe
createdACompanyand
hedidsaythatleading
ACompanyisIndeed
pretty
TOUGHJ
[Music]
Well, I'm
sure every company has something like that Unkuro or Kamoe, but did Mr. Yago
originally think that Hol Live would become this big
?This is quite a difficult question.  Well,
why did we
start these vtubers,
but we wanted to reach out to people all over the world, um, because
of Japan's strong points?  I
wanted to provide a service that people can enjoy, so I guess I should say, in
a way, it's
just as I imagined, but I'm
really happy that so many people got to know us at such an amazing pace.asassay
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I see, but I've had
some trouble growing up, and I've
had some hard work, too.I guess it's really,
well,
becoming popular or being seen by people.
I think there are more and more things that we have to be aware of as we become more and more. I
see. That's what
EXpeople said. So that's the
next question.
What has been your biggest accomplishment since creating Hololive?  Or what kind of things do you want to achieve in the future?It's
really hard to choose the number one thing.
Together with talent and other creators outside of our company, we hope to provide content
of this kind that you can enjoy.
Sorryalreadytime
havetosaygoodbysoon
toButTheLast
questionistheone
thatwealwaysaskin I
'm sad about the next question,
but this is my last question. It's a question you know very well, but I always
ask it at the end, but for Yago-san, what is
Hololive?
This is a difficult question, but after all, it's the
power of words that motivates you to do your best at work.  That's
what I think.That's the power of speech.The fact that
everyone in the live production team
is working so hard makes me want to do my best
as well.  Yeah,
I want to make that happen.
Yeah yeah says
[music]
fortheworldtoenjoy
Yeahmakeforallof
YeahSoweareHISis
thatWonderful I
see, Yago-san, I
heard a lot of stories from you today.Answers
Thank you very much for all your answers. Thank
you very much.
Finally, there is something I would like to tell you all.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you for reading today.
Thank you to everyone who is watching today. I will
continue to work with the talent to deliver something that everyone can enjoy,
so please give me your support.
Who
withandask
[Music]
AGAllUS
andHforme
have today someone I respect so much, I
was really nervous, but thank you very much.  I
hope you continue to be a wonderful person. Please continue to support us and the talent.
[Music] I
was asking this question for this program, but I've
already received about 34,000 questions.  It's
really amazing.It's amazing.It seems like everyone is interested.How
is it that Ungo is so popular?Thank you very much.Thank you very much
for your popularity.
abouthisSecretplans
and
aboutIdeasandAll
ThatandconceptsSowe
talkto
toinDetailabout
theseThingsbutYeah sureItwas interestingtoyou
guysandforgettouse
theHASHtalktoTweet
outyourimpressions fromTodayIwillgo
Throughthemandthem andIwouldbevery
happytoseethoseso
Yeah.
So, that's all for now, but at the end,
Chiara always greets me in that German language,
but I wonder if you can say it with me.  What
does it mean?Yes, yes, I have heard of it.I was
studying German No. 1 in the negative case.Yes, are you
serious?Are you telling me now?
That's super interesting, but
yes, I feel like I remember it a little.  The language is quite difficult, isn't
it?  I'm
going to go there.
[Music]
I can't touch it, but I managed to do it with my body, bye bye,
thank you Cuba.
Rice Nusslice Rice Nudonununu
Rice Rice Rice Rice Rice
Saizeria Saizeria
Love Saizelia
Saizelia Zeria Boze
[Music]
AsaizeliaSaizeriaSaizeria SaizeriaSaizeriaUsaizeria It's
decided to be Gashitter Ivy
Twittera
TwitterOly Twitter
TwitterTwitterIhave instTTTwitter Twitterrutter
TwitterTwitterTwittera
Coca Cola Coca Cola Ah Coca Cola Coca
Cola Mel Mel Cookin Arab Ko Ah Orange
App Ah Orange Ah Jua
Apple Juice Ah  Apu orange
juice apple juice apple apu
Apur Apur Mountain Climbing Mountain Climbing
Ah Ya Yaa Mountain Ah Ba Mountain
That's right So Ah
Masson Ah
Ah
Cry Ah Climbing Maten No No No No No
Double No Climb
Mountain Climb
Maten Primer Mountain Massou
Mountain Nun Mountain
from the Mountain Computer Ah
Concert Ah PC PC PC PC PC
Computer  PC ah console
uh pc ah pc pc pc pc
pc
Pinea
abut soo
sweet mo
suu suu suu sweet sweet spicy
spicy
swift
like ah
spicy spicy su su sweet
soo su spicy su o te
te I love milk tea both are bad te te te te te chama te te ti ti
tea eh dreamy trip to the beach in old age
Paradigm U  Beach Beach Beach Ah
Big Town Wow
Vacation Pibi Ah Famous Master Ah
Vashonia Beach Ah I want to sleep on the beach
Spin-o-beach, nice beach, big city Tokyo,
ah, beach paradise, big city,
hum city,
city city, Uko Daito city,
metropolitan stay, I'm going to hang up
my clothes, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa is the naked kid's clothes come to me ahaaaaaaaaaaaa, I
'm going to go naked with Kusuuku
Uzuaa I'm cutting off my clothes  PK Oh,
Close with Close,
Ukua, don't take off your bra, giggle, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Sunday Christmas
Christmas Well but it looks like a cat after all
Everyday Holiday Happy Halloween Ah, Christmas Christmas Ah,
Hadecrismas,
Hadecrismas, New CrysMas Halloween
Up Christmas Oden Halloween Christmas Family Bart
Eleven Kana
Seven Rouson
Rosenthal
Lawson Family Mort Ah All My
Life No, I used to go to a convenience store All of them
Please choose one We are currently collaborating with each other
Family Mart
Family Masen Seven
[Applause]
Losebu Family Mart Oh, I guess it's a phone call
Fu
temaki Wow Wow
Hmm, ah, I guess it's a phone call
Tech tech Anh,
yeah, yeah Hmph Hmoshihoshi, text, text message, text message, I want a text message, sing present [Music] I guess giving is also receiving.
Ah, I love it when we receive things, even when we're together.
Giving Presents Giving Presents I'll
Walk Uwa Station
Train Train
Train Ah U Train on the Train Ah
Train Train Ah Train Walk Walk Ah
Walk A One Station Ah Taxi Ah Train Ah Train
Train Go Go Ah
Train Tare Train Pink
Ah
Secret U  White
Pang Black, I'll leave it to the black bread
orene
chin.  I
don't wear black pants anymore, so
no, bye
Bye
[Music]
MN
YX
[Music]