oh nothing's
playing
why
it just have this
random
music
[Music]
meow meow
meow
[Music]
K uh uh
uh how you guys
doing uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh
yeah I'm back I'm back I have descent oh
ah
ah decent internet
again screen oh it's not there on
purpose I kind of lost
my wait I'm so small I kind of lost my
my f
my background I think no never mind
there it is but I don't know should we
play with it or without
it and I want to commission a new one
too I want to commission a new loading
screen a new ending screen and a new
gaming
screen everything I want to renovate it
all yeah without what without for big
screen yeah I think so
too I think so
too new W screens keep
the I might just you know whip out
whenever you guys are being being little
[Laughter]
shits and you never know when it's
coming so you'll always be like anxious
about it like oh my God I hope today is
not a CH day is today the CH day I don't
know I have kind of a weird feeling
about it I feel like I feel like I will
be asked to wait a little moment and I I
can't bear it it's so scary to me I
don't want to wait a moment I don't want
to wait at
all I'll just mute you hey no no no that
is not an option anyway chat why are you
not visible huh why are you hiding why
are you hiding are you scared to being
seen in HD again me too me too
uh wait I want to make you bigger how's
it work again bigger
without I mean I guess I can
this why was a
streamer why would the P what am I doing
though like I'm not going to use this
anyway okay never mind
oh
wait let's do like this oh did that
change I okay then no none of this
nonsense we're going to play a new game
how
exciting and it's going to be a game
that Ena and and
um Ina and well Zetta and Buu in case
you haven't seen my thumbnail are
playing and they
have they have um told me they would
like to play the online multiplayer and
they need a team of four I mean they
could probably do it without four they
could just do it with free people but I
was asked and it's a game that generally
I would totally play the problem was
just that I was currently in the middle
of you know being busy with other games
like Yakuza yeah I'm making myself a bit
louder after Yak Yakuza and there's
other games Tales of AR rise just uh
revealed that their content ban content
streaming ban of the DLC is
lifted uh and you know in this house of
takanasi Kiara we must play all of this
kind of content because we are
ambassador of the English
region to that game but yeah uh honestly
for that I'm not like oh I have to play
the immediately I'm not worried about
that but still still I feel like there's
so much i' have liked to play right now
and Grand blue fantasy reeling while it
is
exactly up to my taste
buts I it did not come at the right time
so I am not fond but everybody says I
will love it so it will probably um be
tund first and then I will love it
forever
so
yeah y let's
[Music]
go and yeah uh my internet problems
should be solved
so oh I do see we we dropped 0.3% frames
when was that did it uh buffer for a
moment somewhere in the loading
screen but it should be fine generally I
don't know if you saw my screenshot but
should be good my mic sounds a little
odd right
now now first first I was like oh I
sound odd because I was sounding like
this because chunky wonky stepped on my
broadcaster and activated this oh that's
loud and then I was like wait this is
not how I should be
sounding and please tell me I sound fine
because I have I don't have the brain
capacity right now to do some trouble
shooting with my microphone everything
sounds fine I sound fine I sound uh
crunchy I would say uh although I don't
know was
microphone was I on a different
microphone what was
that could it be I was on a different
microphone
okay I know
oh which one was better this one or the
other
one yeah there's some noise in this
one uh but I can probably get rid of
that
uh there you
go this one's better
okay
um remind me to watch The V of this part
so I can hear the difference as well cuz
it's the same in my
ears new mic is so crisp it's not a new
mic but it's just uh
differently set up I guess in OBS I'm so
confused anyway let's go play this game
I just know I know nothing except that
this game is
um a gacha game a gacha phone game
originally and I've always had my eyes
I'm getting cut off oh it's the it's the
the thing okay then we'll we'll get rid
of the we'll get rid of the noise
cancelling because you won't hear the
noise anyway once there's bgm from the
game okay this is better so yeah I was
saying I always had my eyes on the on
the character designs for years and
years I was always aware of the game
always thought it was really cute but
you know I also don't want to start a
million gcha games so this game kind out
came out of nowhere for me but it's a in
FY a welcome one but you
know you know oh it wants me to get a
controller uh sure wait which one uh
should I wait didn't I uh I have a I
have
a where did it
go I I I used to
have I used to have a pink controller
but I can use can I use the can I can I
use the PlayStation one okay but I have
to connect it with a cable to the PC
right needs to
be connected like that oh what is
this PS is
good is that what I usually go for I
don't
remember okay sorry I just brought over
a
cable
y y what's
I bought a while ago maybe I told you I
bought a bunch of pink USBC cables and
pink USB like adapters that have like
several USB slots and this and that
everything pink pink is not my favorite
color though but but you know when you
want girly things it's usually always
being
so always being sold in uh Pink even if
you don't want it whatever you like or
not if you want to be girly it will
often be
pink what is your favorite color
honestly I'm so unsure I would like to
have more yellow and orange things cuz
my my current matte that's under my
keyboard is the baguette
quas one if you remember I think I
showed you before with the cats and it's
like yellow and orange and
brownish mhm but I do I love purple but
I feel like orange and yellow suits me
better
[Music]
okay okay I hope this controller Works
uh grab a controller and kick
back and any kind of controller looking
device that can connect to your PC I
like that would a switch controller work
too uh steam input games this game has
native support for steam input uh-huh
okay
I don't care I'm I'm not going to read
that controller please
work do you you have supper yet you mean
if I had l a dinner yet no I had right
before the stream I had a little lunches
kind of um grilled ham and cheese
sandwich I've been making a lot of
grilled ham and cheese sandwiches and
it's
bomb is Bomb I brought out my
griller my grill my grills
um oh sorry breathing is today not
possible I may have better internet but
breathing is [\h__\h]
uh T will join you later uh and Ena yeah
I don't know what you mean with later
I'm playing I'm going to play the main
story as far as I have to probably going
to finish it cuz you guys said it's a
short game anyway um like you you guys
said 12
hours are you for real
uh if that's the case I'm I'm planning
to play it tomorrow too so we could
finish it um it's about 15 hours okay
let's see let's see I'm I'm motivated I
have snacks I have water I have a tea to
get
going
uh
yeah 6 hours per day 6 seven hours per
day you know we we're rolling we're
rolling we had a long Yakuza stream
we're rolling here it is here's the game
does it have audio wait it's not it's
not reacting though to my
controller
help help this is why I I think I don't
use this controller normally
um why why not help me why my PS5
controller not working might have to
restart the the game
okay have you tried turning it off and
on
again yo it's crazy they had to change
my fiber
cable uh and I was like lowkey watching
the process very interesting yo dual
sense controller isn't supported by this
game Steam input will translate the
device okay but that seems like they at
least found my
controller PS5 was buggy for you vs team
input
buggy
buggy yeah a kink yeah it was a very
kinky fiber cable
I'm so glad it was done because I was
really doubting that anything was going
to happen and yeah that it was ever
going to
work I don't know I thought I was stuck
with this [\h__\h] for half a year or so uh
is there sound supposed to be here now
cuz I don't hear any English
English I think I heard Ena play it in
Japanese Voice language I don't mind
whatever is fine to me in this case what
do you think what do you want guys is
there a lot of story is there a lot of
voicing Japanese okay do they have wait
uh X or
o oh X nongo where is the where is
the H barely visible
here okay wait there should be surely
there should be sound here right now
sorry guys
oh
oh yeah Windows Windows is using my dual
sense controller I need some kind of
like
application in to install on my PC
surely people will love it where you can
say you can tell your PC to never use
the Dual sense controller for audio ever
so like automatically block it
forever send it to Oblivion send it to
the void where did that go there we go
dual
s oh headset microphone no no
no now this is probably
uh
oh I can't I can't
hear you know the Japanese so you do the
English please I mean yeah we could do
that but I I don't really have strong
feelings about this
really I don't never know I never know
these
days ah I found the
sound wait you don't hear it yet that's
okay well where if I find my mouse again
then I'll fix it
oh
uh uh how's it work
again
[\h__\h]
yes
[Music]
finally Y is this we're going to see if
it's loud too loud audio I'll putut home
theater uh what where am I why am I here
oh uh hi can we get higher no
okay oh this could be higher but no need
cuz I have it windowed
anyway what the what the [\h__\h]
does this matter for you guys if I
change it for me how would how will it
be an
OBS give
me wait now I already said it on English
didn't I or did I no I said it to
Japanese can we get much higher so high
that cones initial game set
up this game uses auto save okay let's
go auto save woo we love auto save
Grand blue
fantasy a new jrpg game on Wawa's game
list that she will
finish ASAP relink
mhm I hope that as a non or as a as
someone who never played these games
before I hope I hope that it will be
easy to understand but I'm going into
this with no knowledge except that there
will be cute
girls
uh
okay
okay should could I have said no to any
of
these this seems kind of loud already
maybe Story Action
hard
action oh it do be loud it do be
loud
[Music]
okay heart no I would like to finish
this in 12 to 15 hours please let's not
make it harder for
us wait did it say it can be changed or
it can't be changed
later action is fine yeah you guys is so
glad that I don't go easy all the time
on all
games wait I'm too big it's it's
okay the Stars we're going to go to
space
o probably not for seven days your crew
weathered the storms before finally
breaking through the
clouds
oh they couldn't have made it this far
without you without
me what did I do what began as a chance
Encounter of a girl named L I became a
journey to reach the ends of the Skies
okay cool and now a new chapter in that
story is about to begin is this like a
story sequel of something
what do you say shall we start writing
the first page okay as long as I don't
have to read it writing is
okay a Side Story
oh any people here who play the
game okay it's too
loud any people who played the phone
game
yeah
I know it's still a bit
loud not me sorry recently for seven
years oh wow okay of course I'm choosing
the
girl no
question a did a yeah I know that's her
name I know a couple of the names and
Designs yeah uh no I can I change it
huh H how do I change
it
how I don't know what to press to change
it I can maybe I can type in right right
here oh yeah
okay
and
W simple but
beautiful eh are you ready to fly I am
always ready to fly
[Applause]
woohoo it's still too loud what the look
at her girl look at her she's so
[Music]
happy
wao
big
a oh that's yeah was that M I
[Music]
know
yeah what's your problem
huh
[Music]
sweet crack the
Kraken unleash the
kraken Grand blue fantasy
reing wee
camera and movement controls move your
character with w and
okay
lsrs yeah it'll probably come
naturally yeah let's check everybody out
is that what you're saying
talk let's do the
[Music]
Talk t
I left stick right stick easy
calina what is
it h oh they're not going to say the
whole sentence are they what do you
think it's out there no they they
are they do say it
all a
wall maybe an invisible
wall fully voice to go
the typical invisible wall in all games
there
[Music]
are this lady has Kisa
Vibes anatawa
[Music]
anatawa no idea but I'm dying to find
out we'll find out when we get
[Music]
there uh I am it as a phoenix I'm always
dying to do anything because it doesn't
matter she didn't say the same thing in
Japanese he did
[Music]
either similar things but not really the
same thing yeah she didn't say she's
dying to do
[Music]
it
H I don't know there's at least two
things where
who
Lu no her dad is is on that island or
[Music]
separately let's
go we're so in SN
we're the same yo I love this I love
her she's
cute hey you weren't supposed to be in
the
conversation I didn't invite you it
didn't warn me that you was going to be
part of it I was looking forward to TT
girls conversation and then talk to
[Music]
you
I did you guys know I watched the other
day I watched like a deep dive about uh
domains how domains are kind of what
word did they use I don't know Capital
online digital cap not capitalism
digital something it was a fancy word
like that and that all these like um I
didn't realize that
like net. iio do m
whatever all those they all come from
countries and some of them are kind of
like exploited
to you know other
people small skip again ah yeah tuvalu
tuvalu
is.tv and tuvalu got really exploited uh
many many years ago so that other people
could use and and make money from that
domain and back then back then talu you
know what tuvalu got the country for
giving others their domain for giving
others their rights to control their
domain more or
less free
internet which sounds of course great
especially many years ago to an island
that H doesn't have much but now years
later after the TV domain has made so
much money and then I saw a picture of
the the the internet building on that
island and it's ridiculous it's like a
little tiny shed so it's not even like
the internet that they did get for life
is like any
good a [\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah and now yeah they kind of lost
on on like a big billion
dollar deal more or less because they
could have made much more money from it
like okay a lot of countries don't need
that kind of business to get their
economy going but for countries or like
islands like that that don't have much
else it would have been a useful way of
making some extra money and I found that
interesting so I'm sharing it with you I
didn't know that do iio
also wasn't something that was for hom
pages that you know are like development
style I felt legit that there were some
some domains that just like don't belong
to countries but like legit are for
these kind of purposes like TV or iio or
net what's net for what's net
[Music]
for or is net a different
story an net is worldly Network okay
okay okay so the the triple the triples
are for like yeah not country things
[Music]
interesting
discussion oh you Secrets why you
hiding net
[Music]
gol
she reminded me of someone I
think cute probably a
famous famous voice actress
[Music]
right but she just reminded me of a
person in whole life I feel like
scanning those
[Music]
vibes
ah okay it is yeah very
[Laughter]
famous I
maybe oh
cute
man her magic I I was
told
uh that I should play a mage but right
now how do I even how do I even do that
I'm playing this like
basic character can I change her class I
thought I thought I'm choosing one of
the cute
[Music]
girls do I have to make that choice now
anyway you can't choose eventually you
can change later aha
[Music]
okay okay I don't like
ver
W stop stop stop don't don't talk so
much
[Laughter]
[Music]
same I'm glad I'm not the only
one we're we're glad to have your Eagle
Eye
Lou
[Music]
ninin he did not say anything about
carrots in Japanese but I love carrots
too yeah I already did
though I already talked to everybody
what do you want is there someone
else I'm
slow why am I
[Music]
slow because I'm done
talking
okay fight
fight loud to
me Power Attack jump
okay it's so loud in my
ears but for you probably it's
[Music]
not
ah
H why is it not is it even changing at
all in my
[Music]
ears feel like it's not
changing
I should I need to change it in the game
press X to attack nearby Foos when
playing as the captain makx
y comos why
okay it's so loud let me take my head
off press y to unleash a character's
unique attack some unique attacks can be
charged up by holding down the button
like the Captain's y
[Music]
attacks it's
sign is this too quiet guys please say
no
okay okay better so much
better
[Music]
am I doing well I'm already
understanding that if you are in the air
you can use different
attacks oh incoming danger when a fo
glows red watch out be prepared to guard
or Dodge the powerful attack that's
about to come okay ah yeah uh lb to
block which I'm probably never going to
do taking too many hits while guarding
will result in a guard break okay they
probably want me to guard
those is is this what I'm pressing lb
what which one is lb L2 or
L1 I L1
okay people told me that the the way to
battle is kind of similar to T Horizon
yeah I already I already agree I like
that battle system
though
I like it and dodging
okay ah wait RT so uh what R
R1 no R2 [\h__\h] did I
[Music]
dodge I combo finisher there's a combo
finisher
I did just want to script it okay okay
okay take my hand let's
fly are we going to fly are we going to
jump
what feeling
Shivers [\h__\h]
yeah
Freedom
Dragon [\h__\h]
Overkill
Mama nice nice
nice
nice who does that who
does who does that
I know that voice actors has many voices
but like this voice specifically reminds
me of
someone no I don't watch Fairy
Tale I mean someone from Hol
live oh
you cannot imprison
me foolish
humans I shall teach you a
[Music]
lesson shut up child you can't control
me I am a Celestial huge ass [\h__\h]
Legend
oh
he's going bonkers like
junkers I got attack he's so
far
I
is he going to do it he's going to do
it it's so
[Music]
shaky he so quickly
gone
ow give me more than three hit come
on nice
oh oh she needs a lot of time to recover
from a
Dodge ow wait I'm dying what's the
healing item this
one yeah
okay oh yo yo yo y
recover you can turn up the shaky it's a
little bit too much a little
[Music]
bit if you dodge three times in a row
you have to recover
uhhuh I think I want to get rid of the
shakiness is that here uh or
[Music]
here vibr screen
Shake
nice gave me no
time what is she doing is that a healing
Circle Healing
Circle yeah I think it
is healing
Circle
oh holy
maoni nice Instinct SP wait it's still
[\h__\h] loud sorry I see it on OBS too
isn't it too loud
[Music]
guys
silly CH yeah block that's right he's
already gone cuz I'm staying too far in
the
B music is okay yeah all my settings are
messed up cuz I'm playing around too
much with
them not not I'm not playing
but
[Music]
is she revive no she's healing
cute yeah I want to I don't know I was
just something wrong and then I made it
even
wronger Music Co music will be louder
effect
slower
no no it's perfect like
this you can't tell me that you're not
hearing anything right cuz I that's
impossible looking at
obs
yeah the music is
low
true overall
[Music]
it's maybe like
this
ship isn't going to fly yeah but but ah
Sky oh SK fall it's a purple
thing let me attack
[Music]
it we're not going to be flying anymore
but our mission will be to fly again one
day with a new ship right
don't worry we'll do that we'll we'll do
it I
believe for the blue-haired girl L
right we'll make an even bigger
ship we'll make a Airbus A380 or
so set a new big
one a gold
break nice thank
you yeah metal ship let's if we can they
can already make armor out of metal look
at
them let's make the Airship out of metal
it's
[Music]
time
hello can someone catch me catch me
[Music]
catat yeah just drop me and you stay up
there I don't care drop me drop
[Music]
me
bye-bye nice ship just realized it looks
like a [\h__\h] bird from above with the
legs in the back looks like a chicken a
blue
chicken the captain tucked away on the
secluded island of sinken still that is
so
German oh that sounds so German nothing
excited ever seemed to happen to this
young woman or her pal ver but that all
changed when a girl named lra arrived
out of the blue and she has blue
hair Sega Grande skyum waas that's me oh
my God I'm in the game waas newest
Adventure unfolds across this Western
stretch of Sky home to Islands such
as Len at the
eino
aripo Lego Lego
Lego this game is made for me literally
have a character called after my name
it's made for me
[Music]
oh then we land in the
ocean from such a height we should be
dead water feels like the
ground at that
[Music]
point just adding my name in
there is she even
human
[Music]
I
live
debatable
half
for
[Music]
foree
I don't like it I don't like it I don't
like this thing I don't like
it maybe it's uh more bearable in
English can I hear oh oh kute wow Su I
like
it nice screen it feels W it feels so
refreshing and clean and new oh mod
[Music]
let me hear I want to hear uh can I
change it to
English I can't it's only the T SC
okay Ian is
worse
okay
uh where ver have you seen that golden
sign over there I think she might just
be over there and yet I want to go this
way because items is there a map yo
that's an
item W
[Music]
run my instinct it was even dark over
there so it really looked like maybe
maybe I shouldn't but you
know over here there's nothing though
right
okay it's just the the feeling I can't
hold it back I need to pick up
everything that I can
sense damn those
jumps Cobblestone I found
Cobblestone ah to
I have to dash when I do that jump
probably y it's going to be a lot of hot
hidden things yeah wait there there
there there okay
nothing oh there's nothing
here
M oh
oh oh there was nothing there
well getting all all the mats and money
early just a nice
Flex you're peeking quite a bit I
thought so
mhm I don't know guys I have to figure
things out all over again I turned it
down a little bit shouldn't be
peeking that much yeah
okay don't sry there's literally a
golden Quest marker over
there you know what that means don't you
don't don't act so
stupid we all know what that
[Music]
means there's something in my way to
block me from going further it's so
sug but you can't can't stop
me I am on a mission I'm doing this for
them oh you want to know who is
them I'm doing it I'm doing it for Ena
and S and
bi they want to play online they want to
play multiplayer I will be their
multiplied
player it'll be
me do it for them
[Music]
lulia is is she alone like powerless or
why is she so
scared oh maybe because she's a Healer
and healer is
loner LT have the camera automatically
follow a Target LT H okay that's
probably L2 while locked into a Target
move RS to switch targets press LT again
[Music]
okay
nice
the
rude I want to dash like that
too no
no oh another
[Music]
one why didn't you dodge oh I don't know
man
I'm still getting used to this
okay we'll get
there we'll hopefully become a useful
asset to our multiplayer
Team no I'm playing on action which I
guess is
[Music]
normal hold RB what the [\h__\h] is
RB
I
think that one and press X Y A or B to
activate a skill okay iron one okay
skills go un cool down after activation
represented by their icons going dark
some skills however allow for multiple
activations okay oh
o that sounds
[Music]
Scandinavian nice slow
motion
[Music]
nice cry about me don't worry I have a
quest marker I'll always find
[Music]
you does ver know that it's just third
Wheeling
[Music]
us every character has their own support
skills one of the captain's support
skills is called Adept Arts which
enhances the ability of activated
skills
okay hold the cross to use yeah I
already did that
thanks okay let's
go it was what I was about to do without
you telling me so
H how did she just say
it sounded really different in
Japanese I feel like you could put it
into Katakana like Tink and
shu
so it's not so so difficult I went up
there it looks like I could and then I
go up
there I need bigger
jumps what's going
on the
archives why are they wearing such
casual clothes why is she wearing
jeans hold down the jump button
hold can I charge a jump check out the
archives and ly journal to read notes
and other documents you picked up along
your
travels don't think about
it oh wait now it kind of worked a
okay temp Stone
oh healing item right oh I see a chest
door
more money rupes o shiny
shiny this looks really
nice I wish this was an
mmpg multiplayer modes just don't
satisfy me Elemental properties fire
water Earth Wind light dark and plain M
plain grind blue fantasy
every character's attacks and skills
have an El Elemental
property is represented by a colored
icon next to the character or skill the
captain's element is wind fos take more
damage from damage from elements they're
weak to which is represented by the icon
next to their health gge oh so that's
not the the element they have that's the
element they are weak
to
okay yep
[Music]
go away Bird Go away You're not welcome
they don't take much
[Music]
damage but I don't have
fire o nice
[Music]
recover
uh how does it
wait okay wait that was he was almost
dead anyway but you told me to use
[Music]
it Captain is one of your least favorite
characters in the
game it is like
a a pretty basic like
player character you know what I mean
those are often kind of
basic but it's good if they give you
choices for other characters to
play then I don't see any issue with
that yeah yeah you're supposed to self
insert I guess you got to get good at
self
inserting skill is
Sho night one rupees and a glitter
[Music]
Stone don't question it just do
it what does it say with
Arts is the Arts too free is that like a
information about the
[Music]
combo
I found a secret
[Music]
path did you find this
path did bi boo find this
path surely they don't go forward and
then look behind like me the jpg
Pro
[Music]
oh I I sense a boss
fight where is paranoid
me oh what are
[Music]
you
crocodile love name
I to win how
[Music]
convenient it does sound like a p name
not going to say the word I'm
paranoid
oh how often can I use that
skill so frequently oh hey what's
up we group
[Music]
now was interrupted
when I was trying to say
um that I was told I should be playing a
mage because the others are playing like
Fighters like the close
combat I'll see what I can do but uh
doesn't matter what I
play in my solo play through uh does
that matter to
my uh to my multiplayer play pro I I I I
I I have someone in terms of mes I have
someone in my
eye it doesn't
matter uh what about levels
though what about
levels play whoever you
like characters gain XP at the same rate
n is really pure uhhuh okay okay
[Music]
okay A F stun goge fills up as it takes
hits once a stun goge is full a link
chance will trigger press speed doing a
link chance to perform a link attack oh
cool a
be performing certain actions such as
link attacks raises the party's link
level if all parties party members
perform a link attack at 100% link level
you'll gain temporary
Buffs okay thank you for putting that uh
in that moment
there
n nice music a boss mold bar boss's mold
I can't read today fills up as it takes
damage once full the boss goes into
overdrive and becomes even more
dangerous conversely a boss's mode bar
depletes as it takes damage while in
overdrive uhuh once the bar is depleted
it enters a break that's your chance to
lay on the
HT okay I got to lay on the HT all the
time
though stop running away from me you're
so
[Music]
f
it DEET
[Music]
slowly what is this circle is that from
him
no
[Music]
for uh Sky bound Arts Press LS and rs
when you Sky B oh right my is that the
orange go go thing is full
unleash okay it is that one
unleash crocodile you
must
die your
days yapping
over at the same
time oh every
[Music]
now what the [\h__\h] wa what was that Full
Burst when multiple Sky Bon Arts are
activated in succession oh they're like
literally waiting for it it triggers a
powerful final attack called a chain
burst try chaining everyone's s together
for full I have control over it I don't
think so they did it
automatically uh aha okay ah okay I can
control that in in some
way hey I missed the last hit someone
stole it from
me they Incorporated many mechanics from
the main game that's
nice
oh
oh what was that it revived and then
someone stopped
it yeah very or she
to how dare you how dare
you
[Music]
not I don't think
so how's the game so far you like it I
like it so far game play is
nice
[Music]
cute you have a feeling have you also
played a lot of jrpgs and just have this
kind of
feeling
too
uh but what about the grand Cipher I
don't I don't even
know let's ask good
[Music]
question our
ship
teaches yellow B terms
oh wait that's not
it wow like in the Final Fantasy game
that we played so
go wait did we come from
here because then I would like check out
this um invisible
wall
okay well usually in these kind of boss
fight areas there's actually nothing
hidden to find it's just that
area I wish I wish they would put some
stuff to explore there more often than
RPG
games yeah usually it's just it's just
that very
disappointing
cute it did be
pretty by the way daa not only answered
me on Twitter she also answered me on uh
Discord and was like yeah let's play
together the graphics are so nice yeah I
love this kind of graphic you know it
you know it yeah and people saw as well
I think Ena is the only one she probably
won't even see it unless I like force
her to see it I feel like she's she's
not much on
Twitter or at least like she doesn't
really maybe she tweets her own things
but I don't think does she really look
at at other members tweets I feel like
it doesn't appear in her
feed it's okay you know it's
okay but you should see it en know my
hit tweet and my hit thumbnail they the
playing Z yeah I already heard I already
heard that there's a character called
Zetta check your Google calendar what
why what do you mean did she do
something did she put a secret message
for me
there
[Laughter]
cute ooh nice architecture on that
church wake up my thumbnail you have to
look at it for real for
[Music]
real talking about that time yeah but
that's ages ago you're confusing
[Music]
me Port
Breeze
why are they babying
her is she that
valuable and faints every now and then
perhaps there's some experience
there she kind of baby she's 12 so what
12 years old can be strong enjoy some
time maybe we could grab grab a bite
yeah
please let's eat burger
[Music]
P what me I'm I'm a foodie yeah a little
bit all bit
Kimbo I am
Kimbo apples that's so boring let's have
a
burger I cooked uh fish yesterday I
didn't post a picture
cuz it was
late but I did
cook I had um basically it was a fish
filet SE SE
SE I think
um filet with like a uh like baked in
the oven with a like a
topping thingy and V mantel which was
almonds and must mustard and fresh herbs
and
some what was
it something like that but yeah I was
covering it with that just a little bit
of mustard it really wasn't much I could
barely taste any of
it yeah and I put it in the oven and I
was also making like a uh kind of like
mashed potatoes there was supposed to be
one carrot in a two but when I when I
opened the ingredients from Hello beep
the carrot was so old it was like it
wasn't molding yet but it looked like it
was close to it it was really soft and
old and cranky so I threw it away and I
just made it with the potatoes and the
leak so it was a mash mashed potatoes
and stuff with leak and then it had like
a balsamico sauce on top of it and I was
so confused when when I was cooking the
balsamico sauce because I thought it it
was balsamic sauce and like sugar and
water and I thought it was supposed to
thicken at some point but indeed the
recipe said nothing about the
thickening and I was kind of like
waiting and waiting and I'm like hm why
is this not getting thick and I added
more salt and I added more
balsamico nothing was happening it was
so watery and like okay maybe it's uh I
guess it's supposed to be like this
everything else was finished so I just
accepted it and then at the end when
you're done cooking the the sauce you
you add like a herb bow butter that made
it pretty yummy I was I was going to
drink that sauce straight from the
frying pan was so good the sauce was
good the fish was
H the filet and and the topping was
great but somehow
uh overall it looked much better than it
tasted it was a bit uh
underwhelming but it's good that I eat
fish every once once in a while
so yeah yeah I love balsamico sauce
though but I like it more when it's
thick thick as
[\h__\h]
[Music]
anyway my cooking news I still have one
more serving so I'll eat that today
after the stream yooo I don't have to
cook Let's
Go Fish yeah I don't know if it's always
hit and miss I think it you know it's
it's a recipe
thing h
d
d I'm hanging to try the local
bruise drunkard yeah get out of here I
deserve a refreshing cocktail after the
long
hike a mocktail is what you're
getting mhm
not PA
paa what's this archives
right I go here first oh I can't it's an
invisible wall made up by children that
I could just jump
over oh small
child
show me your face small
child I has a it has a
par cute those ears are
huge cute
bird
can the bird please attack verm I would
love to see
that let's have a fight and I'll be on
the side of the
parot
siero what kind of name is that is a
renowned Merchant who offers a pleora of
goods H or a peora of goods and services
to travels and residents alike and FL
inflect let's trade with her right
now uh looks like you have enough Rafal
coin to trade for fortitude
shards a crystal Shard reped with the
memories of Warriors these Recollections
of training coax a minute amount of
power uh out of AR armor for
[Music]
crafting uh trade for uh
one
[Music]
oo nice I like that
little cave you got there your man
cave this is what I call a man cave guys
not what you guys
have this is a real man cave get
yourself some iron and some metal and
some fire and make some [\h__\h] soul or
else it's not a [\h__\h] man
cave back to the roots back to oaba
guys real men live in caves with a few
scraps and [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
yeah black SMI takes care of all things
weapons weapon related you can also sell
your items there okay okay see what
should do doing you want me to craft
okay what with this what level up ah aha
to level up the
weapon so I'll just use all of them I
guess and hats
H and and hands
why F what the [\h__\h] Prismatic slime
what's what's why
you coming out of nowhere with a
$400 Super
Chat is Prismatic slime is that a a
thing from The
Game
[Laughter]
Jesus
sheesh thank you m MW MW m
m is it is it a game thing an enemy a
rare spawn wait what somebody said it's
like a money spawn thingy that gives a
lot of money oh so it's like a jork an
Insider a gaming
Insider much more than just money yo who
is this person what who are you why can
I not well now I can confirm what what
did I
do icons displayed at the top of the
screen indicate where useful facilities
are located m it's Jor nice
Jor it also gives Mastery points ahuh
wow I'm learning thanks to the Super
Chat I'm learning things too
early soy thank you so much that is so
generous holy [\h__\h] so out of nowhere who
are you mysterious
slime uh I you can save your game at any
time for the main menu well in town
okay can't go deeper into your man cave
huh women not allowed huh H well I'll
make myself a women cave then [\h__\h] you
you won't be allowed in my women
cave I'll show I'll show you the inside
but you won't be able to step inside so
I'll freaking tease the [\h__\h] out of
you do you have what like a side quest
or
what yeah it is it is a side quest
I have a whole women ship yeah but
there's also men on there I'll kick him
off I'll kick him off if that's how it
is if I if I'm not allowed in your
spaces then you're not allowed in my
space you're only allowed on my
Facebook Town people M with an icon are
in need of help a good deed never goes
unrewarded are these worth it though
Blaster
goblins goblies they they've always P do
sure but L they've become more and more
vicious teach them a lesson will you you
know what I'll do one of
these one side quest in the whole game
is what I'll
do you have like a a bird icon from
your from your bird
cute crewmate card use crewmate cards to
unlock new party to join you on your
journey the morning Mar
[Music]
damn buff holy macaroni so I have my
eyes on fairy actually cuz I always
liked her design so much and I would be
excited to get to know
her although Naya is a [\h__\h] Queen but
that's close combat so we don't want
that we need more and I love her too
though but but yeah I think I think this
is me by the way I think uh but it's
also
Zetta and it's Zetta
andto H I'll probably go for this one
then mhm she has fun can I get her
already no how do I get a crewmate card
no add-ons okay
F
[Music]
someday chap
okay what what do you want Golem but my
[Music]
is
what Golem he wants me to kill a
Golem chapter one and two super short
okay no worries no worries really
[\h__\h] drunk It's the middle of the
[\h__\h] day it's probably like
12 sun is shining he's [\h__\h]
drunk Prime eval
Prime
[Music]
Prim M um
don't call me when you
[Music]
fainted
for what it her fault I mean the Bahamut
I
guess this is Sanji from One Piece you
mean the same
[Music]
voice
I'm not surprised they got big actor big
actors I do think this
game no it's been around for many years
I don't think it has a big name in Japan
M it's well known characters are well
known and this is a big project for them
[Music]
ah it's
be
lizard I thought she was calling Laria
lizard
I thought they hate each other I thought
e hates Li and calls her [\h__\h] lizard
cuz she's
[Music]
blue I would have loved
that she doesn't know about makeup she
should doing girls
talk I'll teach
you
yo you can also join Girl
Talk yeah I can't wait to see cuz the
old Lia sucks just
kidding she voiced M Maxwell and Tas
ofilia oh my
God didn't
[Music]
realize m
can I open that no
silver
[Music]
okay well for girls talk I I want to say
to my
defense that I was on a little break and
FAA from what I've seen also was kind of
like on a
[Music]
break um although it was never really
like set in stone that it has to be
those
members cuz like from the beginning it
was already like oh this week I can't so
feel free to get someone else uh
but oh I don't know I guess I'll bring
all my all my shows back again hopefully
soon it's kind of a you and M show you
think
so yeah I don't know um there's
obviously still lots of
I'll see what I can
[Music]
do I'm not in Japan
no I'm in
Austria I've been living in Austria for
a long time
now I lived in Japan only in the
beginning of my whole life
Journey
and since then I like kind
of I end up in Japan like maybe I think
last time last year was maybe like six
times a year which somehow doesn't even
sound like that much but some of those
times were like pretty long
trips and you know in between those
trips I also had other
trips yeah so this year is probably
going to
be a lot of Japan pant Trips Again
too I do have a couple of them lined up
already and some are uh again kind of
like inconvenient as to like I'm going
and then I'll go back and I'll go again
within like a short amount of time
like why but it's going to be worth it
it has very specific
reasons yeah but the next one
is next next month h very soon for the
[Music]
fast what do you mean three months long
that was that was the longest Japan Day
last year was two months
approximately and that was
for in a lifetime important project Frey
debut had a good
reason I was actively
streaming during
that
probably more active than everybody else
even H maybe except for cie
so I don't accept complaints during that
yeah in between I was back home a little
bit but I was also streaming during that
so I was very active during that mhm had
Fire Emblem lots of Fire Emblem muchos
muchos fireemblem and then I got sick
but you guys know you guys know how much
I was suffering and then I streamed
anyway okay
so no it sucked so bad to get sick back
then it sucked so bad cuz I I had my
fredd debut man my fro [\h__\h] died in
the worst time oh my God I was so so
[Music]
devastated the sick Ark U many sick arcs
to be had back then
no FR de I still have the picture by the
way I still have the the
picture characters gain Mastery points
upon leveling up oh Mastery points are
spent to raise stats learn skills and
more now would be a perfect time to see
that in action let's have Captain
acquire new skill oh masteries I love
the screen I don't know it's so
satisfyingly
clean I love
it it's so
[Music]
blue thank you yeah yeah my immune
system no no Jinx please but it's been
fine each Mastery node is unlocked with
Mastery Point select the armor break
node uh okay uhhuh
this I got a new skill okay but wait
what was it a fast launch attack that
inflicts death on a f how do I use
it bad way guess we'll find out effect
strength and duration are based on Arts
level uhuh wait should I do another one
this one are my MSP for
everybody oh yeah seems like it's all 10
so I don't know if I if I want to waste
all of it on
me they're
shared well let's save we're probably
going to keep I maybe so will give her
one I don't know what kind of team I
want who I will keep in the future I
don't
[Music]
know wait the lyria girl isn't even in
here is she like forcefully always in my
team probably all girls team yeah you
get
it I'm not contractually limited to any
language um although I think I I you
know I'm I'm not supposed to like do
only Japanese streams all the time
because yeah that's just
the I should be mainly speaking uh
English but um I am the M speaker of Ian
after all so that is no problem she's an
NPC she's not really figh so she she's
just there to
heal okay got to talk to Rosetta it is
known it is known everybody knows I'm
the my speaker
ofan but yeah I made a German sub
Channel
and I might stream on there
soon
again with mixed feelings however
because I always feel like M streaming
in
German I feel bad for the people who
don't understand but you guys always
tell me to do it anyway so
no oh my God oh my
God but I think what I'll do for that I
might even do
[Music]
um uh what's it called
again a dual
stream on
Twitch in the hopes that there's more
German speakers on on Twitch to find
me
a no not
AOE there's something else that I got
perms for that I
requested but don't worry I'll mix
English in as as well a little
bit
okay how do I leave this city I want to
I say wait for Alice but can I do my sop
Quest first
how do I leave this
place did I come from
here yeah I think
so man I want to do my sub Quest
okay oh it happens as I play normally
really you say so well it better be true
what about crabs what is it with
crabs I'll take the
quest this boy rescues a rare creatures
called wee pincers if you find one he'd
be happy to take it in I'll see what I
can
do we pinc is a
small
crab a
crab okay I'll I'll try my
best wee
wee is there something
here yo it's really nice these paths
these houses the
plants everything really
nice there's a cat two
cats they are walking
slowly oh my God there's no Collision
they're not real man cave oh it's a
retired man cave I can enter this
one I'm just exploring right now cuz
really nice can I jump on here and that
on here I can
yo 42
Char oh TR St but I need a q right gold
key where do I get the gold key oh I
can't get higher
I can't get much higher but can I go
onto another roof or is it just this
[Music]
one so
hi can I get much
higher
oh hey I heard you use to to live in the
capital is that true me or that person
you're talking
to oh was
I a can't go
there I have absolutely no directional
sense of like where I am though on this
in this
city but that's
okay whatever that was I'll do it you
guys say it happens like automatically
pretty much so it better be
[Music]
true why is this not an mm RPG guys they
could totally make it into an
[Music]
mmpg why is why why why no MPGs guys but
you know what's happening guys blue
protocol is coming closer of each day to
the en
Market they said summer I think
2024 and summer is
approaching let me tell you
that
[Music]
they announced is it is in summer I feel
like they said so before not recently
even just before before before or I just
wishfully think that and trying
to make it Reality by just believing in
it
okay let's
go yeah one year after the Japanese
server and then came up in summer last
year summer is
coming
manifesting I've seen it
[Music]
all oh em just can't really sustain
players they're so lucky
then they're so lucky to have me because
I'll be bringing all of you guys into it
too you guys are Sur going to download
the game and join me on the
server I'll actually be a [\h__\h]
blessing to it then me playing that game
I'll bring the audience I'll bring the
players holy [\h__\h] actually oh my God
they should pay me for
that I'm still waiting I'm still open
for a sponsor ship for the um release of
the game I'm really open to working
together bco my beloved I love you so
[Music]
much what did I
do yeah I did that
I am so coak for doing
that did someone just ask if I if I
think I'll get a smt 5 sponsorship I
already did did I not
you mean another new
one I don't know if I'll get a new
[Music]
one oh that was a DLC that they
announced
[Music]
okay I feel like DLC sponsorship are
rare although I did get a Tales of arise
DLC
sponsorship cuz I am the
Ambassador sorry I thought it was
s new guy
[Music]
he looks like a
vtu looks like he could be part of Hol
Stars he does yeah
it
does but like specifically H Stars cuz I
feel like they have so many RPG fitting
designs he means no harm but I mean harm
I
do
sorry
[Laughter]
roll he he be
rolling
tornado Primal Beast time
baby wait if they had bah do they also
[Music]
have the other
one it's Final Fantasy all over
again let's go technically
yes I didn't mean the Phoenix I meant um
what was the one for wind
again where we
going
here
yes you know I'm honestly like really
surprised that so many members are
playing this
game just
because I felt like in the recent 2
years or so besides like Yakuza
maybe or like not even considering
Yakuza when it comes to like fantasy
jrpgs like this feel like I was almost
the only one picking them
up so I was surprised to see so many
people so many I mean it's only free in
the end but uh still
yeah it's it's nice to see
though yeah FF 16 got a lot yeah true CI
was playing it Ena was playing it who
else was playing it besides
me was someone
from uh promus playing
it I don't
remember that's it oh it's not even that
much yeah but generally it's just nice
to see more people um dipping their toes
into jrpgs even if it's maybe not the
greatest streaming game but at least
this one's apparently relatively short
so easier to pick it up I
guess
promise don't play it else yeah I just
realized that I was like the
[Music]
M don't tell me it's actually
gudo
fishy sorry that's the what I cooked
last night sorry about that
y just finished PS fre wow that's a long
game right really
long yeah Persona I know that I would
probably really enjoy it but I you know
I'm busy with my other CH PES I I don't
think we really need to get into
that a primal Beast
baby a
PE my schedule is full I have so much to
do h
[Music]
stop asking about the go collab give us
time stop
asking for days now there's like one or
two people who keep on
asking
patience I want it to happen she wants
it to happen um but I got to set up some
things
[Music]
and it's going
to there there's got to be some
[Music]
technical troubleshooting and all that
H oh I have to choose up to four
characters can be in your party at one
time it's your choice who you want to
Adventure with
with I I want to ADV adventure with
with uh
party the character in the left most
slot is the one you control the captain
must be in the party for the main story
but you can play as any character you
like surprised no no one's surprised
about
this nice
cute I think the balance is great though
like she's our tank she does some magic
I don't know what she does but we'll
see
I like girls girls girls I like girls
girls girls girl girl girl I like girls
girls girl girls girl
girls clear quests to raise your level
and get resources for upgrading weapons
and sigils you'll also earn Mastery
points used for unlocking new skills and
stats learn more about the character by
viewing their fate episode it's also
good way a good way to gain extra status
oh really by watching it it's
like I don't know if that's still a
thing but it's like how you
can
uh I feel like this was also a thing for
the mmor pgs I played like if you watch
a lot of ads you were able to get like
free cash shop money points or whatever
yeah uh so this is like that
gotta watch the
ads all right so in
here is
it is it this the
journal what cute L takes many notes as
the journey continues check out her
journal for useful tips I think that's
something else but it's cute
a
oh
[Music]
cute field notes
F
[Music]
archives
glery oh my God too much information I
read it all thank
you try going to the quest counter ah oh
I have to do it there okay it's not in
the menu okay okay uh wait Quest cter
here I always
jump oh I like their
uniform oh more
Quest
okay if you really need it okay take on
various quests from the quest count and
earn valuable rewards for clearing them
oopsie ah [\h__\h]
sorry undertake Quest crew Alliance
Rafel is always stocked with Quests for
the Intrepid Sky far quests are
organized by location difficulty and
[Music]
tight should I take them
all defeat all goblins defeat the
crocodile already did that oh I get the
reward
right H wait what select
call
what what depart for
Quest so
rematch would I be going there
immediately so is it like an
[Music]
instance test you can also
change but open or close
random okay this is like
online Clos are we going to go right
away okay after
accepting ready
okay probably
ready wrong button I
guess this
one and yeah we'll probably be fine or
is it going to be like much stronger I
hope not oh my
God please be
[Music]
kind no I'm okay with this character for
now until I get the one I really
desire I just cracked my hip
bones uh oh wait I thought I was uh
waiting for this to load I thought this
was a loading screen skill
icons are visual indicators of a skills
AV yeah okay yeah I know that oh wait I
okay this is stuff that I know
okay no hips I'm not addicted to hip
cracking it just happens
[Music]
sometimes it's by far not as bad as
before this young woman is on a journey
to reach a solution she's a solid choice
for any situation learns all types of
okay thanks for telling me something
that sounds like it should have been
told in the
beginning
okay my adapt level that was the only
thing that sounded
[Music]
new
fore did you get
[Music]
me looking pretty good though I
think
[Music]
why was I not able to do the armor bre
was it not ready yet it looks so
ready blood first some bosses gain the
blood first effect it makes sky bound
arts in effective Sky bound okay it
greatly reduces the damage taken
thankfully the effect is only temporary
what what's skybound
Arts the the special skills that are on
on like
[Music]
here okay stop
rolling you can stop rolling
[Music]
now okay I think he's done with being
thirsty nice nice nice nice
that was loud in my
[Music]
ear nice nice to
you been good with
[Music]
dodging wait uh what okay I'm not ready
though she was ready though I'm ready
I'm ready I'm ready I'm
[Music]
ready do we
get do we get different ones depending
on who my party members
[Music]
are he's rolling so much
again can she
teleport yo Harless
H7 thank you
CH Chang it on depending who starts it
oh
nice oh link time is triggered when link
level is at 100% and each party member
performs a link attack uh okay I mean I
don't know this seems to happen
automatically
so during link time enemy movement is
slowed and you granted various effects
such as increased attack power Health
regeneration and shorter skill cool
[Music]
down
he was so
[Music]
slow I broke to get up get
up he's going to die with my sword in
his
heart the time is
now or or [\h__\h] kill Steeler
again
sassy
B can't
[Music]
believe a land Beast claw and one
MSP some Cobblestone Earth Shard and
fortitude
[Music]
Shard okay
oh yeah that's my girls that's my
girls oh well no healing needed long
distance Run debilitator Ninja
backstabber yeah [\h__\h] backstabber you
probably stole it didn't you no no
Rosena did it she got the last hit I got
backstabbed twice then by the
backstabber and by her she smells
weakness though what did IO do
uh okay and now
oh oh I didn't clear all the side
goals sad
okay
mhm uh
[Music]
yeah so when we're talking about
multiplayer is it basically just this
going into these like monster killing uh
instances together or is there actual
like story
[Music]
too it's just that
okay okay I mean I fun you know fun game
and all that but it's really worth to
drag me into this for just a few of
these
[Laughter]
fights I mean I'll do it but I thought
there was like more to it like you know
cuz everybody was like let's make a
group let's make a group
okay
[Music]
okay they get
harder yeah but it's just a fight and
then that's
it do it for them do it for them now
that you've obtained the sigil you have
to equip it in order to take advantage
of its effect
oh yeah okay do in the main thing or
here oh here's the okay let's watch a
fate
[Music]
episode her name is
Laria
[Music]
I'll watch these offscreen they're kind
of not
so good for watching it
here it's just repeating
we I thought it would be like side stuff
that I wouldn't know otherwise or just
some conversations between
them can I do this still
[Music]
count yeah we're sharing 50/50
oh go to the Fest let's
go oh by the way who are the four the
fourk of pce from those pictures from
was it
Kon you know you know I love
KATU who are those four in the uniforms
that Us Saw pictures of any names
names I just want to know who they were
cute my sweet
[Music]
chickens you'll be on my good side
trust
me not
trap was what was I supposed to
check
[Music]
hold what was I supposed to
check
gear ah the
sigil
uhhuh uh uh-huh stun power
uh-huh
okay we're not sharing are
we ah okay can only give to one person
okay are you guys not telling
me you don't know
it are they not
here we loyal employees are they busy
working at
kfp are they on a shift right
now witness
protection my Chens I need to know their
identity and their social security
number and their bank account and
everything the address and their car
number plate and um yeah all of that
please the phone number of
course H I think we're good to
go I mean just the social security
number will do too just
kidding
[Music]
don't trust autopilot too much you
you'll
crash
nice
winde
[Music]
fore I Like the
Wind
it's all blowing into One
Direction no yeah it is so nice so
coordinated marriage
counseling marriage counseling with a
sword h
she I love I love
[Music]
you that's why you guys was saying that
it's like ret Ralph and fix it dude
Oh chapter one
finish chapter one
Swedish chapter
one finish chapter one British chapter
one
[Music]
Austrian everyone could use a little
dragon pal like ver why was lucky to
have such a good
[Music]
friend
yeah I'm so lucky am I
not I'm so
lucky I should be so lucky lucky lucky
lucky oh my
[Music]
God this makes me
angry h
oan is haunted by his past what happen
he has much wisdom to impart if you
ignore his frequent complaints about
getting older and if I ignore him when
he's drunk
you better worse than
fiser I don't know cuz
I I kind of it's been so long I don't
remember how strong my feelings
were
but I think this might be
worse cuz I think fee wasn't there this
much like around to annoy me
24/7 like fee was holding back a little
bit
[Music]
more
okay what what speak
[Music]
okay one of the C oh
really but there were so many
comments how am I going to find it but
yeah um speaking of uh
yesterday I I told you I told the
members but I went to my doctor's
appointment and I guess I'll tell you a
little bit um
why why it was shitty it was fine like
okay so I went to a private doctor cuz
in Austria we have free healthare right
so with free health care yeah generally
um unless you are like a mystery patient
like me normally you should have no
issues with it you know you it's not the
worst okay but I've noticed over the
years that I just can't find a solution
for my pains and I keep on running
around being sent around and doing
physiotherapy a million times even
though it's not helping and then the
doctors there's like basically a main
doctor that you go to and then they
refer you to other doctors or if you
just dare to get like um an excuse to
stay off of school or so cuz you have a
headache or whatever you go
there um yeah so the last ones that I
had I didn't like them especially the
very last one so uh yeah a general
practitioner yeah I I found a new one
that's um private which I feel like is
rare to like all the other doctors you
can find private ones but a private
general practitioner practitioner I
didn't find much like
that um and it's generally so
unnecessary I would say cuz they're
going to refer you anyway but I just
wanted to be listened
to yeah yeah generally they take better
care of you cuz they they get paid
[Music]
better and so I went and I was so
stressed out because I was like I wasn't
late I but I was late to being early cuz
you know they say please on your first
appointment be there early blah blah
blah and I kind of I kind of was late to
being early and then I even got lost and
ran in the wrong direction and then I
was even more late to being early but
it's okay that was no problem I I was on
time and I quickly filled out the form
and yeah I I filled it out within a
minute so all
good um and then I went into my
appointment and I started off by saying
sorry I'm going to be an annoying
patient that yeah I'll I'll have to tell
you a long story and he's like okay no
problem and so I started telling my
whole story and I did feel like I was
being listened
to and doctor was taking notes and
everything yeah
so I feel like I I got my point across I
also made like a clear distinction
between my fibromyalgia and my chronic
shoulder
pain
um I do feel like I I I was able to tell
it all
[Music]
mostly and then at the end of me telling
everything I I said like one thing I
would like to do like I told them also
don't send me to physiotherapy again cuz
I've been there 100 times and I've tried
this and I've tried that and then I said
one thing I didn't do yet that I maybe
it's like you know crazy from your point
of view but I would really like to see
uh what an MRT would say about my
shoulder cuz I want to see more than
just those bones and I did also bring my
previous scans and we both agreed that
the little part that was scanned there
of my neck is not enough like we got to
check the shoulder too you know but yeah
anyway the reaction I got was like yeah
that would make sense to like get
that but then somehow
um we we ended up going in a different
direction and uh he said I should go to
uh what was
it
[Music]
um what the word again I should go to
those doctors again that look like at
your feet
and and like generally uh your way of
standing yeah or for petas I wasn't one
like many many years ago but it was more
about something else I think back then
I'm not sure but it was a long time ago
so generally yeah okay what whatever I
guess um I
guess and then I also was recommended to
go to like
um um like
a I made a joke like aren't all doctors
specialized on pain but like he
recommended me some pain specialized
institutions apparently that's a thing
um so I'll be checking those places out
but he said I can't like I said in order
to save time can I please just do like
like the doctor visit and the MRI at the
same time and he's like no no no cannot
do and so I was like
okay all right I
guess uh that's that's too much saving
time no that's too much you got to come
more often to give me more
money I give you one task you run off
you come back you pay another 150 bucks
for the appointment I send you somewhere
else again you come back with the result
and then I make you pay another 150
bucks you know it it's an endless cycle
that I want you to go
through yeah no it's okay I guess yeah
one more step and then maybe then but
the reason I was getting upset at the
end is
like I was like asking some other things
that are like more or less unreal Rel
like I asked if just generally if cuz
with other General Practitioners I also
was able to get like um
prescriptions uh
that originally I would get with other
doctors but like this doctor could give
it to me too but he said no he said oh
oh I don't I don't really know anything
about this so no I'm like yeah but I
know which one I need and all that and
you know he's like no no sorry I don't I
don't do this I I I don't know uh you
should go there to the other specialized
doctor and I'm like um okay even in the
past no it's not about if you he's a
general practitioner the thing that I
want he can easily give it to me my
friend also gets it from her general
practitioner all the
time no no that's just ridiculous cuz I
don't it's I've had experience myself
also with a different general
practitioner that the same exact uh
prescription you can get from a general
practitioner but whatever and then I was
like okay then another
thing and I don't know if I ever told
you about this I don't think I did but
um generally when I'm being flown to
Japan I get premium economy and
generally premium economy is fine but
I've done long distance flights till
like 12 to 17 hours 100 times in my life
in economy and premium economy and with
my chronic pain I'm going insane there
okay my shoulder especially in
situations where I have to sit still for
a longer amount of time it's it's
killing me okay and I've been suffering
through it for ages and then you know
recently I experienced business class
once because I paid for it out of
curiosity once and it was so different
it was so much more bearable it was
amazing I could lie down and I could
actually sleep through the pain which
makes a huge difference in not going
insane
um
so uh then I will not say who I guess
cuz I probably I don't know maybe I
shouldn't I don't know I don't think
it's like a big issue but a certain
colleague told me that uh she got uh
from her doctor like a writing that uh
she needs to do like exercises and stuff
and it would be recommended to get
business class for her
flights in the future and that worked
and she's been getting business class
since so I asked this general
practitioner if he can just write me a
note like
this and he was like no I wouldn't know
what to write in it and then I I told
him exactly what my colleague told me
what was in her note and it it wasn't
like too serious it was like it just
like
scribbled yeah but even then even when I
quoted it like he wouldn't even think
about writing
it uh I don't know
why and then he said well just go to the
doctor that wrote that for her then and
I'm
like well that doctor is not in Europe
so uh I don't think I
can uh thanks and that really made me
frustrated after the other things he
also rejected and me just being referred
again which I mean the referrals were to
be expected but generally I just felt
like um not really helped not like like
it just felt like always the same [\h__\h]
and and then this wasn't even the few
the few
little yeah um only guys that I had he
couldn't help me with that
either that's not reasonable no like you
can easily write a note like
that my colleague
agreed that that's like you you must
have gotten a weird doctor you and then
my friend also agreed about the
prescriptions that that's it's easy easy
to write such a note
yeah
whatever
[Music]
whatever business
class okay guys just
shush now you're making me frustrated
cuz you're not even trying to
understand anyway after that I went to
pay my 150 bucks for that uh
conversation and at the end actually
like I also got
like anxious because he was trying to
get rid of me cuz it was a long
conversation already and I was like okay
I thought I thought we had time because
I'm paying a lot of money I thought I
could have a not Tim restricted message
uh conversation here but no um so it's
like basically basically asked to leave
and then I paid and then while I was
paying I was like feeling
it coming to me and then I walked out
and in I walked the stairs down and I
couldn't hold back and I broke out in
tears because it's just always the same
[\h__\h]
um
yeah and then I went to get cake uh to
cheer myself up and I sat down and I I
looked at my cake and I I was crying so
much I couldn't I it's ridiculous You'
think the cake would make me happy but
the cake just made me cry and cry and
cry there were so many people around me
and I was trying so hard to cry in a way
that wasn't noticeable and I was looking
down only and
like
quietly go uh blowing my nose in in the
in the tissues that they gave me and um
I don't know I just I just couldn't stop
crying and just couldn't
stop
um I it was more like I guess again like
a general of frustration cuz it felt
like like as always like I've been doing
this for years you know and it just
feels
like it's probably never never going to
get better
ever and
okay if I have to live with this pain my
whole life I would have expected at
least a little bit of uh support like
such a simple thing as like a doctor's
note that says can you please Let Her
Fly business no even that's too much to
ask from a [\h__\h] private doctor I went
out of my way to go to a private doctor
like that's also a thing like I feel
like I'm having a hard time finding a
doctor that works for
me yeah anyway that was my doctor story
yesterday um I told him also about the
headache by the way but he just gave me
painkillers and was like oh yeah it's
because you're you work on your PC right
um I'm like okay I mean I I've been
working on my PC for years and a
headache like this was a first timer but
okay
whatever you still have it I mean ever
since the massage I think it's been
gradually getting better
yeah
[Music]
yeah maybe you need to re-evaluate your
daily routine oh my god do you think
after 13 years of living with pain I've
never had a different
routine I'm sorry but this topic is so
frustrating to me I've tried so many
things in my life I've lived in
different countries I've slept in
different on different beds and
mattresses different pillows I've uh had
times where I was more actively doing
sports and less actively doing sports
I've had different styles of food intake
and Lifestyles and more stressful Ms and
less stressful mths if you're going to
say that's something in my head only or
so etc etc so yeah
anyway it's okay I um I'll I'll do the
things that he told me to do
and maybe I'll go back once to get my
m i or MRT or whatever after that yeah
yeah yeah I just need you to listen yeah
that's
[Music]
it end of
tangent end of
tangent the cake was good though it was
just hard to eat because I could only
breathe from my
mouth
[Music]
cuz of my nose dripping
dripping temp
temp
maybe I need a surgery I wish I could
just get a surgery where I rip off my
arm that and the where it connects to my
shoulder feel like that would solve my
issues I just want to rip off my arms
and my neck maybe
too I feel like that a lot I just want
to rip off all those parts where the
connections are cuz that's that's where
it
hurts I wish I could do that I wish I
could regrow my
limbs G is this
[Music]
you
become cyborg lizard CH I'm not the
lizard Lia is the
lizard taste your two pieces of cake and
love thank
[Music]
you
oh what
happened
explain froggy wow froggy wow is a
separate person from
me I
know I know especially as a general
practitioner like he can't just solve
all my problems at the spot I know that
but I don't know I somehow expected more
now that I finally like made the step to
start
you know going for doctors
again cuz that last time I was actively
doing that it was a really frustrating
experience
so you know
anyway where's the
button
fro
candy the Goblins wa this is the side
[Music]
quest
do I just get
rewards literally like you guys said for
what I'll be doing
anyway healing
potions
[Music]
okay side quest gets completed on the
side okay so generally I should just
accept all my side question I
[Music]
got
don't give up with the doctor Goa thank
[Music]
you the problem is with private doctors
here I don't
know I want to give them the benefit of
the doubt but sometimes it feel it feels
like also with vets I felt the same
thing I feel like they just make you
come back a million
times cuz you keep on giving them
money no I had the same feeling with
vets with my
cats no the Vets it might be even worse
honestly the times they made me come
back for checkups to give me more
medicine when they could have just given
me all the medicine from the
[Music]
get-go and the of money they charge for
all those times oh my God
[Music]
crazy yeah so but then you know if we go
if I go to free healthcare with like big
serious issues like this where it's like
hard to find out what it is then it's
like an endless
charade that never ends and uh
especially as uh a young
looking py py woman it's hard to be
taken seriously by these older male
doctors I'm sorry but that's really how
it feels
like Hallowed Ground fully heals all
party members and replenishes your
recovery items
ooh it also replenishes my healing items
where have I had this before the [\h__\h] is
that ne ne gate
what
huh
oh
safe but why would I go to an American
doctor why that's so far I don't I don't
go to America that
frequently I'll find a good one
eventually
eventually why is this the first time
I'm destroying
boxes how come I've never tried that
until
now all the boxes I could have destroyed
Japanese doctor well been to a Japanese
doctor even before whole
alive the fences too
oh my
God but not I don't think it was about
any of these issues
no I wouldn't even want to start that
now like trying to go to Japanese
doctors about this when I live in
Austria like if I only am in Japan for
like a week or
two I go to Japan a lot but still it's
like not really efficient I think
oh cute oh it's pretty that's one of the
crabs we PES are rare creatures that
hide throughout ziga Grand there may be
someone out there I know I have a quest
for
that
cute the
hills the Hills are
alive The Sound of
Music a world room well I like how they
write that
cute
[Music]
World crappy
tuer
OMG the
[Music]
gos Goble
Goble
[Music]
turkey
fore
oh damn there was a link I think there
wa why do I never get the last hit so
[Music]
unsatisfying yeah there's a lot of
voices I wouldn't I don't really want
to I I don't feel like I need to lower
the voices uh I uh volume I want to
lower the amount of voices in the battle
there should be a ruler for
that the amount of voices please
L and
more yeah
greed this N I don't I've never seen a
game that does
that
[Music]
never
I might end up hating dragon's dma
too you think
so just like Tales of games yeah and
tales of also has a lot of voices in
battle but it didn't bother me that much
yet wait are something
else
leave it to
me
[Music]
mm
o oh this is the healing Point nice
hello ground
no need to save I would
say oh over
[Music]
there I feel like this game could work
on the
[Music]
switch
no I can't get new creates yet but I
have my
eyes on one specific
one I mean basically I have my eyes on
every female
[Music]
character just take that as a general
rule for
Wawa jrpg streams
should we jump down do we get fall
damage I found crab yes yes yes I have a
six cents for
crabs did
immediately
[Music]
no stop with the laser beams make me
nervous okay that
Archer has got to go [\h__\h]
annoying the lasers make me
nervous
[Music]
you
prer K isn't even a
nickname but I've gotten very fond I've
grown very fond
of
wa from kiawa to
W please call me
[Music]
Wawa always check behind the waterfall
yeah K is just
so it feels so um
distanced if you call me Kiana that
means you hate
[Music]
me
muscle
conister you're a muscle conister I'm a
massage
coniss but I like getting massage not
giving them although I've been told
before that I give decent massages but I
would say that only really applies to
shoulder like really upper shoulder
massage that's the only place I get a
grip cuz I my hands aren't so big and
strong I need
I I I don't know I I can only do the
shoulders cuz those are easy to grab but
those I would say I I I'm pretty good
at cuz I also I know what
I like in a shoulder massage
so I can guess people
usually like strong massages
anyway
yeah
this place is so big I don't want to
miss any
[Music]
items should I have saved that if I save
it do I get it in another
fight probably should have saved it miss
an invisible
chest kind of Overkill what the goblin
was
[Music]
actually invisible
chest how can I see it if it's
invisible I right this one what the
[\h__\h] how did I not see
it oh cuz uh if you get closer you see
the
Sparkles chess will be soon shrouded
again oh wait I have to
oh oh it's like a
challenge
no we're
Roofing can I
restart was it here do I get a
[Music]
chance I want to try again
parkour run the timeout yeah where where
was it other
there
parkour
oops be faster
girl okay that one jump was was tough
cuz you kind of have to jump around
that middle a
pole
what what oh okay I can jump
over oh what the [\h__\h] I thought I have
to restart again but thank God it it
brought
me it brought me to where I fell hey I I
need to go there there's a chest there
too
nice okay I'll go there again 1,400
rupees first try
easy easy a world room a world I feel
like I can't say it
properly
okay
[Music]
what wait
what the
super where is it oh it's already dead a
that was easy hey that wasn't that much
money I'm sure there's better of
slimes it came out of one of the jugs
that I was just trying to normally
destroy it's like one of those treasure
chests where an enemy comes out but
instead it's a
jug check out these
jugs I mean they're gone now but they
were here right
here B yeah it's a mimic
jug I bet I was the only one to find
that what what okay they want me to go
there but what about here will I go
there later or did I basically already
do everything here cuz the Goblins came
over to
me maybe I'll go here
afterwards earliest slime you've ever
seen let's
go yeah let me have that
[Music]
one ooh Witch
Doctor oh my God honestly can I I wish I
could turn off voices during the battle
at
least
I need the oh my
[Music]
God almost I almost got the armor
Bri
[Music]
no I don't know if it actually broke any
armor now his shield is not to be
broken
see that voice is much louder why is
that voice suddenly so much
louder
yeah that is my head isn't
that or did she steal it again fake
[Music]
Kar strong Goble
Goble why is he running away
[Music]
Eble he's not even that
strong effects lower yeah at least
effects we could lower
more so it doesn't sound as
messy say no oh wait that was
[Music]
music nice finish thank
you before I save the lady let me look
if there's items around she's been there
a while she can wait a while long
longer
sorry that feels
funny yeah she's not going
anywhere oh there's something
[Music]
there
yeah
okay money these were real JS oh you can
destroy that too
ah nice what what about
[Music]
this
for
for Sky
[Music]
fan okay okay that's the that's the
place where I wanted to
go let's
go let's save
[Music]
everybody
is it a bit better now
guys don't forget to
loot which
[Music]
one they're not using their thing why I
mean yeah it's still kind of Overkill
but okay yeah now it's good to use I
guess ah [\h__\h] did that even
work it's called skills I got an
achievement that says it's cold
skill wow what a
[Music]
flex
oh what am I
doing what what what he's
charging he's strong they're strong
aren't
[Music]
they they got a lot of HP
man
do
it
for easy I got them all figured out
they're like look at the HP of the
others what are they
doing why using their skills now their
[Music]
special is it because of whatever
setting I have on but before they
actually used
[Music]
it they're waiting for you I I can't do
it I already did it and they didn't do
[Music]
it
H I guess maybe now I can
it changing the setting wait wa what
what's that again uh what's that
again what was that what was that was
that special glow
[Music]
everywhere link
time link time was when
it's slow motion right
okay what's
this what the
[\h__\h] an alond
[Music]
Stone got to go to work oh goodbye I
thought you were already working right
now what the hell om Stones can be found
for Grand travels be aware Mighty FES
are sealed within defeat all of the
released foes within the time limit and
you'll be handsomely rewarded if the
enemy is too much you hand to retreat to
fight another
day uh am I do not those hard
okay okay maybe another
day oh you father I came here to save
you no no no I'm here only for the
treasure
okay I guess that's
it sorry I always do it
wrong
I miss TR in the
middle yeah of
course well I hope the treasure wasn't
so important
then cuz it seems like we're going
straight to the next
place what there's another invisible
chest another
one [\h__\h] another are you sure there's
another one not the one I already
got God damn it oh well it do be like
that
[Music]
sometimes
it's okay right sometimes oh
crap hey hey hey I got the second
[Music]
crap hi
cutie Cutie with the
bird
services oh okay at these healing points
we can
also buy and sell stuff now mhm
[Music]
M uhuh uhuh uhhuh uhhuh my rafhael coins
should
I save
them I don't
[Music]
know
oopsie lat
save them okay if you say
so what was that Shen
voice [\h__\h] I'm so stupid that
said one
[Music]
MSP it's a big
arena we ain't going to
run only cowards
run I am a parttime
warrior once full time now part
time CH one of them was you
yay thank you for telling
me see guys it's not a big
deal they love me so they tell
me he got that big
ass
got to stay on his
side he barely
attacks yeah here we
go let's
go second from the left but did you guys
stay in the same stand in the same order
on every picture cuz I saw
several
pictures but I guess the most recent one
in the tag is what you mean, total
damage it almost sounds like it's
[Music]
C okay I should probably stay back I
mean she did say
so
it is Cap huh lame why cap it why limit
my power also Shield is
gone who the [\h__\h] did I just attack the
wall damn
it nice nice nice
nice
[Music]
broken he's
broken I'm the guy just left really oh
my God already identified two people
let's
go thank you for representing K like I
think you know it's so sweet cuz like I
wasn't even a guest or anything there I
think any from life was
there so and still you choose to wear
your uniforms out in the open like that
I love you I love you for
that you're doing that out of your own
will cuz you want to do it
amazing do it for them do it for
me
I just realized his name is mad
beat said a dead beat after another
count 20 hour stream
[Music]
Marathon like streaming marathons were
used to kind of like or like not even
official marathons but streaming for
long hours used to be my thing and then
cie some at some point she just decided
to
especially cuz she wants to end games
with those Marathon usually she just
decided it's
[Music]
now oh my
God I'm but I'm too
early [\h__\h]
[Music]
hell
oh someone's dead when you hit Z you'll
enter critical condition won't be able
to fight rapidly tap any button to
recover faster or hold down to use a
Revival potion okay she going to do that
on her own Rosetta is dead I think hold
be on a party member ah okay I have to
do it okay hold be okay okay okay okay
where where is she this
one uh OB come on come on y
okay you little piece of [\h__\h] why would
you do that to
[Music]
her y there's some crazy [\h__\h] going on
right
[Music]
now attacks from other that you can't
react to I mean you know that's
just that's action
[Music]
baby
cute but that wasn't sure was
it
o where the
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay okay we can do it just a
little bit more okay okay okay
[Music]
okay oh no not again when he enters that
mod he's really strong oh it's already
gone the Golden Glow is what I
[Music]
meant this time I'll get the last H stop
stealing my
kills what if I killed this one first is
the fight immedately going to end even
though the smaller mobs are still
[Music]
there oh they're so loud again is there
like a sound
bug feels like a sound
[Music]
[\h__\h] it's my hit it's my
hit they're going to show me right like
the who did the last hit are they or was
that only in that one instance thingy I
think it was
mine photo
finish
where the hell was
[Music]
garuna my
controller not in this game damn
[Music]
for yeah I'm
okay
M okay so that was not the Primal yeah
so we still have a chance
[Music]
for it trust
us
for skills for my team you mean I should
give them all those
points
Oh you mean the
Roland
oh
Roland oh no that you say it yeah I can
hear
[Music]
it
so
uh
this oh her next skill is like down here
though but I guess I have enough points
Which Way further boost attack
power uh boost Stone power I don't know
let's do this
one cast a water element spell and
inflicts attack down while jumping
backward gain a Mystic Vortex orb on the
[Laughter]
cast I
[Music]
love a m hit Vine attack the targets
foes near Rosetta also causes all
planted roses to attack mm yeah I was
wondering about those Roses I was seeing
in the ground I I knew they were from
her but I was wondering what they were
doing okay can I also get a new
one enables the use of
launch H it's not a skill but
okay press X right after jumping jumping
to launch foes into the air leaving them
open to aial attacks
[Music]
uh what we'll see we'll
see this one was that it I think that
was
[Music]
it
style oh what why why would you tell me
I don't am I supposed to
know
what you this lady you tell me this lady
who can't even go around the fence is a
primal
Beast this
lady she's a primal
idiot I
[Laughter]
think
H should I do something you guys said to
wait
right I don't really understand this
anyway says I need a Griffin Griffin
feather thank you very
squishy I just had two cakes yesterday
you think it's okay for me to get
another one another one
really you you will let
me have a cake let them have
cake well now it's kind of difficult
can't get a cake
now I knew it had this feeling that I
got to look into the sides as
well
no I think today and my stream's going
to end about midnight so no time to get
a
cake I have ice cream
though I have offbrand almond
Magnum it's good
though it's pretty
good I don't have to hoard the Mastery
points
[Music]
you
really you think
so home
[Music]
Tony she doesn't even get any
skills I do have a lot of points so oh
what greatly increases power raises
charge speed when charged immediately
after combo finisher
okay go wild
okay oh there's a defense
tab
invincibility
yo roses compel foes with en range to
attack
them that was a close
one uh perfect guard no perfect dot yeah
baby that's that's where s
cast a circle that restores allies HP
hold while casting to aim the
circle can I skip that I don't want to
be the
healer I'll I'll keep I'll keep it this
way for
now poor
Rock we are literally an episode of
girls talk what did you expect
I see
you R ra ra
ra what who is this I only see girls in
my
party
where's what are you doing
oh this maybe this one's may be a bit
stronger oh oh no he's dead how much did
he give me not even that much I I
thought those would be giving me crazy
amounts of money cuz of the Super
Chat damn Super Chat slime is kind of
superior nice slime
down
I love how you can destroy all of
this
[Music]
sick that's end
game one day one day our f
meeting shall
occur
aha oh what's this up here oh secret
path oh
chest wait there's surely again like
secret invisible chests here too right I
hope I'm not missing out on them this
time
[Music]
want to Pi the next little bit okay
thank you for letting me
know
uh what which way this
way did I I heard a
sparkle was that my imagination or was
that telling me
something huh I heard the sparkle
again why is it
sparkling Sparks somebody streaming
Sparks is that a
sign back you missed it what was the
spark the
chest that was a pretty cute comment
oh
[Music]
CRA come
down come down
yeah
what I missed the the chest
right the invisible
one is that what you're
saying
where why would it be there's not much
where I could have missed
it oh what the
[\h__\h] did I really is that what you meant
okay
no a this is what you mean a don't make
me go back for something like
that okay was there anything else here
no
okay no
stone Left
Behind sounds
like sounds like a beu thing to say kind
of sus are you beu side
account be
honest oh my God
it's
yeah I think everything's going to break
down where the [\h__\h] are we going oh my
God oh my God oh my
God what what about what about stuff
items there wouldn't be any items
right I don't think people would
discriminate cob Stones yeah I know
she's more about Pebbles but Cobble
sounds like Pebble both have bees lots
of
bees and it's both a
stone I feel like she
wouldn't she would love
to take in the Cobblestone every once in
a
while chest coming up okay
I kind of knew it I kind of saw that one
coming you slimy
boy no don't wait don't use it no no I
wanted I don't know I shouldn't have
done
that I'm so
sorry it was a reflex cuz if it shows me
down there I feel I feel like I have to
break
oh
hi you're protecting that Cobblestone
huh better be a good
one
[Music]
oopsie it is a
cobblestone I see
it Pebble and Cobble have the fine sizes
wow
but yeah as I said I don't think she
would
discriminate and then
ooh okay yay and again it drags me back
even though I just saw something down
there that's so
mean yo I'm the savior of the crabs
they'll be so thankful to me the whole
the
whole uh all all of the
crabs of the
world will be at my
disposal oh nice that was worth going
back
for H but how do you go back
up
parkour hold my hand why she not hold my
hand kisawa would do
that K would do
it if I could replace you guys with
crabs I don't know maybe I
would both you chickens and crabs don't
have hands and thums but whatever crap
got it seems kind of
useful more
damage just
kidding just kidding just kidding
it's oh hi I can't fight you right now I
think I don't know if they would let
me but there's a
blue
finding a new
o
no I'm
sorry I'm sorry I didn't mean it like
that you know it's
j it's
j believe believe
wa believe your love for
wa you know I'm a jokester you know
[Music]
it kind of windy here not going to
lie um my bang I'm not enjoying this I
need
Hairspray
money congrats on your vtuber
debut let's go oh my God I can't go
faster chickens riding crabs yeah that
sounds like an amazing
combination all right big fight coming
up Moy you're a vtuber now how does it
feel to be in the virtual
world
Garuda a it's not
Garuda why the [\h__\h] is it a horse
thing that doesn't really look like a
windy
thing h a
centaur why is that wind
element
FY why is that so
funny I don't think hurricane can hear
me is something blocking your connection
it's just like what happened with
B she lost it she's useless we can we
can replace her with other cute girls
[Music]
now
he's so
[Music]
jump I want more attack
I should stay
away what is you
doing how much longer is he going to do
that
okay oh
[\h__\h] okay it's
time our
[Music]
time how's the bit rate
guys
is it looking
good can you see what's going
on fine stable pretty good
nice that's what I like to
hear [\h__\h] I missed the link
attack are they doing it she's doing it
why so early change hands
wait I don't have girls too early why
are you Sly so
impatient there you go I got it
quickly it looked like it was still
relatively far
away dirty
[Music]
Rose hey this time it wasn't capped
3,717 nice oh
for there was a very SC song that's
called I know dang dangan is like
a to you but you're in the middle
girl wow
so
[\h__\h] what's going on yeah bullet
yes
again once he transformed into something
else he's doing a salon
[Music]
thing
can you [\h__\h]
stop oh my godett stop talking who has
time to listen to you chitchat
now really not the
time they're talking so calmly
[Music]
too
foree
[Music]
foreign
I'm
[Music]
dead sorry
sorry oh my
[Music]
God come on more
power get
[Music]
out oh thank you I'm I thank
you everybody full
power
[Music]
for thank you na for the
pink oh thank you no need for
[Music]
compensation epic
music oh no no let me get
[Music]
oh no no no not this
time
[Music]
W of the Goddess y it's F me
no Roa missed that [\h__\h] she's going to
be replaced for that it's
[Music]
over can I go back again
here
uhoh is it okay to go no maybe
not go go
that's oh what the [\h__\h] is that I know
sometimes I don't know what's from me
and
what's whenever I'm going
in not over
no no no
[Music]
no it was never really over and now we
are doing the
[Music]
thing
oh my God we look like an idol
unit where'd he
go just don't going to overdrive right
away please where where
hello blood first h no no
[Music]
no come on girls be
careful FL
[Music]
sword
I will not give
up you cannot for me
[Music]
away
yeah and yeah two
times
[Music]
invisible I think that was my head
okay I was invincible but it was so
useless cuz it was a at the end when I
literally killed him what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] here look at how cute I am and calm
the [\h__\h]
down it's all good if you look at a cute
anim
[Music]
girl dainty Rose not dirty
Rose
who knows officially English she says
Solen
Rose
what
what n we're not fighting no more he
already had so many
phases do something Lia do
something oh
oh don't kill us
though oh
[Music]
L wait if I don't bring these ladies to
my team will these lines be spoken by
someone
else that's
amazing cuz I only see I no the guys are
here
too the girls just get more time to
talk
nice whoa what is this alien ship the
[\h__\h]
is this the Generation
ship can I
[Music]
join oh what the the red he looks
interesting I like this voice
[Music]
before don't know if it
suits
got to see her
[Music]
face he thinks he's
hot
oh no he probably
will oh I've dealt with mysterious
swordsman before dud you're
resisting not even worth
[Applause]
trying
W you have fing PL
armor oh wait I'm doing damage now wait
is this real uh a real fight now but
we're not winning it wait is he
recharging
invincibility what's he
[Music]
doing it's
scrip should I just let him kill me or
should I hold
out okay that scri for
sure
[\h__\h] could I revive
her
oh no not you no I'm going to cry and
I'll kill
you she important to
[Music]
me I'm Invincible too now [\h__\h] how you
like that now your own
[Music]
medicine I'm going to play the best
Dodge game of my
life that's no that didn't do any damage
hey I'm not
dead I was going to hold out for 30
minutes I
[Music]
swear no not my lizard
girl what
[Music]
the
n
H who's who's pretty
girl who is
Lady oh
yeah oh yeah she a
lady if evil white
heart white hair white hair don't care I
love mine mine mine mine oh
goddess
pretty
[Music]
lovee
love
[Music]
shut up I'm having a moment she's not
even that big
bbba I like medium
Bubba
okay if she's the leader of the
Generation ship I'm definitely
in I love
her
[Music]
for she's so
nice
her smile is so
[Music]
kind I would go with
her shut
up how can you not respect her she's
beautiful yeah mhm thank you for doing
the thing we all wanted to
do a look at her grace her
beauty her El against her
charm
or I love her so
much she did not just bring Bahamut
back that's what they wanted
maybe her power cannot be measured with
this world's
[Music]
measurements
what did you just say to
me I'm worthy of marrying her that's
what you were saying right that I was
unworthy I'm
not whatever it will take I'll make
myself
Worthy
oh yeah the
void good old
void we all know it too
well take a
oh it's a
trap it's a
trap please save me w says
[Music]
wa the [\h__\h] are they doing to
her
n fake
yeah we all know when anime characters
don't have the lights in their
[Music]
eyes then there's also no light in their
heart freaking
baby give me a freaking moment to get up
dude
spee
fore foreign
okay sorry
was having
fun they're not even bouny but I'm
bouncy
[Music]
hi it's okay we all were weak too weak
oh my
God I'm going to assume that you guys
are just saying it because they said
rafian in the dial
didn't even like really register
that but you can't fool me
anymore Rosetta looks like she could be
an idol
Master she looks like she in but like
older and in an RPG
[Music]
game
doesn't
she
n what what say it say it oh no don't do
the Chio
thing what is he
charging
power he really pulled a t on us wait
that's what I of
[Music]
him
my if I close my
eyes oh my
God
he just came here in this fantasy world
to expand his
harm I
mean look at
e it's like his fantasy haikui
replacement
literally
you'll understand
[Music]
eventually ah oh should I check my
gear
just so that I guess it's so that I
don't leave this room immediately
H maybe there's
some
treasure
wo my
woman
oh oh it's me
oh new
trip I like this
drip good
drip good drip do we get new drips per
like every couple chapters we're in
chapter 4 now by the way let's
go I received a sword of alos your
broken weapon was sold for scra hey why
was I not involved in that discussion
you received fre 42 charts and 150 did
you just do that on the own huh I like
drip this good drip yes good drip yeah
oh yes good drip yes good
drip so was there something for me to
find can I destroy
no can't use my weapon in
here I guess I get to talk with
[Music]
them so cute
I like it I like character designs from
Grand
[Music]
blue it's a church no weapons
understandable we sa for no matter
[Music]
what
S I got a
DM let me check
my where's my
mouse sorry oopsies sorry I haven't seen
my mouse in a while there it
is oh sorry if I Tab out oh okay but
nevera sent me a picture of her cats
cuddling with my
wanket
[Music]
nice are you
okay need some alcohol to get through
[Music]
it oh yeah I want to ask
you
okay give me another idea for a merch
item that you guys want one more
please just throw them at
me I have like two already like pretty
much
set
for over here again for birthday merch
[Music]
keyboard caps
interesting oh oh my God so much phone
case I would love to do that but it's
like the only one that really would be
okay is the one that you can like open
like a book because that works with a
lot of different phone
sizes so yeah that could work in theory
uh I don't really have like a set theme
this
time it's like all over the place but
that's okay
knife set I don't think I can do that
that would be nice though animal or
metal
pins
socks yeah but that's also a thing like
generally I never look at sock sizes but
I feel like at least men and women socks
are
usually different
sizes a Rob that's probably considering
the other item that I already have in
mind I feel like I need to choose
something that's a bit cheaper in
production oh ble
[Music]
box I was thinking about Bendle box
before too a kfb Bendle
box that might be a bit of a expensive
item though depending on how good the
ble box will
be I like it too though y' cuz we
already have like the uh stainless Ste
no not stain the
fos
tumbler and we have a cup before so for
drinking we have like a lot of
[Music]
stuff MH M coasters I don't know what
coasters I feel like they're
not I personally never use
coasters so I don't
[Music]
know cookie cutters oh that's kind of
adorable like chicken shaped and I don't
know if you could really make it w
shaped though cuz it it's got to be
simple that's so cute though
[Music]
oopsie can I give back like some quests
here cut Cutler yeah yeah the box I mean
the bental box would have Cutlery
ideally probably like plastic or so
[Music]
though
okay my take table no my table's fine I
don't smash my glasses on there they're
fine
oh you got one but I have four you want
more next you need threee there you go
oh I give it back though here I get
rapel coins
nice I
accept need one more
crab can't be sunglasses
H sunglasses I
guess I guess kind of same with socks I
have this feeling that maybe
between male and female
anatomy there might be an issue
there and yeah also with sunglasses H
the shape really changes if it looks
good on
someone a shield badge yeah that might
be cute
to maybe in in the future maybe if I do
animal animl pins or something like that
yeah then a shield one would be nice
really
[Music]
cute something practical for cl I would
say a Bendle box is practical for
conventions I think I like to even the
phone case not really a case but that or
the B
box
[Music]
or I think
um yeah the pins
like some pins sound good
too but pins
[Music]
are you don't need to go to a convention
to use a band
box you can take the bandal box to work
get some lunch do some meal
prep n l is
[Music]
fine
hi
hi okay thanks guys I'll think about
those thank
[Music]
you oh oh let's
go can I
[Music]
choose oh wa she got a
whip just
like what was his name Indiana
Jones
wow my pretty girl oh my God there's
okay I really appreciate did in Grand
blue fantasy there's a lot of medium
Boba
ladies thank you Grand blue fantasy
for giving some some exposure to medium
Bobba
ladies
[Music]
mediums do you want to practice a fairy
against sir
baral uh who is Sir
baral oh my God I'm so cute ah Fair a
young a Ru from an island hi te yes I
chose I choose fairy to play with you
guys because I was told um I should do
maybe some something of magic or or
something something from further
away
[Music]
mhm passed away a long time ago uh what
what what a young every from an island
shoted and Miss pass what she's
dead what what do you mean she's
dead I I just got to know
her what are they all
dead or is just she
dead only her she in particular what the
[\h__\h] why is my chosen woman
dead oh my
[Music]
God she's kind of a lingering spitting
what means I can't die ha damn take
advantage of her Whip's Long Reach and
hold X to deliver a Barr of blows one of
her pets will be summoned on the last
hit oh sounds fun wait my chat
died hold wide to unleash a storm of
blows wait wait hold X to which one is X
again I don't know we'll find out um
hold wide to unleash a storm of blows of
a wide area if any pets are present on
the battlefield they'll hop in on the
beat down let's go okay
so this is the dog go one where
eventually the pets will show up no what
where are the pets and then this one
where the pets will join in but now I
have no
pets it's do blow means blue
Ghost it's
St oh there we go
oh no this gets rid of them no no okay I
thought perge Spirits means gets rid of
them a so my skills are basically like
summoning them what the [\h__\h] is
benediction is
that oh a healing
spell oh there they are I thought you
guys were
gone
got to hold just read and hold which one
benediction hold light attack to Rapid
Strike
[Music]
cool he likes to be
whipped wait is that just like me
re
if I use that skill when the blow isens
is already
there I I'm holding y but nothing's
really different oh wait now it's now
it's going on longer okay is it is
it
[Music]
okay
nice
[Music]
fair not
F just so you
know oh oh let me
see pleas upop nice she's
cute new wife new wife many wife's Grand
blue wife to see okay I'm
done I'm
done very
good I'm I'm excited I'm happy I want I
want all of the
ladies but I'm quite happy with her so
now I put her my team or
what I oh restricted okay okay no
problem did I do your quest are you
happy no I didn't do the Golem where
would have where would the Golem have
been she wants
Cobblestone I can give you
Cobblestone
[Music]
nice it those rewards is that like a a
stat Improvement just by finishing the
quest right
[Music]
mhm okay good good
good yeah they look they seem very nice
to her but who knows what's going on
behind the
curtains but I think I think they're
treating her nicely
ch ch ch chart
chart why would I get
that hello man caveman refin is a
resarch that increases a weapons level
limit this is called uncapping uncapped
weapons can be leveled up
for
should I do this by the way she's level
10 already nice guys stop it's also
German ghost
whip oh should I do it should I do
it she's leading a cult so
what so
what me
too oh now it's level 30 is cap
okay uhhuh press
x uh what is X this
one
enhance okay wa now it's level 30 holy
[Music]
[\h__\h] should I do it for any others two
maybe
Isle oh wait she's still on level one
anyway okay
uh
oh
here
easy um should we uncap it we only have
one more of these for now I think we're
good we can think about it and then for
you also enhance it a little
bit good to upgrade everyone's weapons
okay seems like Bina and na Wawa all
found characters that were meant for
them honestly every character is meant
for me
though every every single one of
them I I could have chosen anyone and I
would have been like I love her oh my
God she's the
best every single one of
[Music]
them so what about
this I wait I don't have enough anyway
okay good then I don't have to think
about
it
okay was there any more like quests that
I took that I want to give
[Music]
back don't level Sig sigils just equip
them
okay don't no need for them for a
while
okay
good I mean I feel like if the game is
that short like maximum 15 hours and
like we already 4 hours in
yo makes me
worry when I need to like take all these
functions more
[Music]
seriously until end
game damn okay the dudes yeah I think
the the dudes also have good designs and
and surely they're also great but uh I
got to prioritize my
gires I'm hungry a little bit yeah for
real for
real actually no I've been snacking so
much I shouldn't be really
[Music]
hungry
got spoke with them
all hi oh new quests are available on
the in the city
or on the quest board
thingy wasn't there something else here
I feel like I took more quests when I
left do I have a key for this now
no
lame
hi that's what I'll
do
yeah the Calo girl I like her
too can't have it
all s this
n oh I can go to oh this one I can give
back wait what w w w w w wrong button
this one trial to CL wow
convenient hey nice the others were not
completed I guess oh like I gave them
back already this one wanted that this
is new one he wants all always some
crabs and he wants the Golem finger I
don't know why we didn't meet to
Golem it is super Nifty yeah
convenient
Nifty when I see that word today the
second time already I think
of uh that that
show not giving you much am
I uh sorry brain H H the show yeah Mor
thank
you see if you can get it just by me
saying show and
Nifty then maybe it wasn't uh too little
information to go by after
[Music]
all oh let me see what you
got what do I get for this
again was not telling me
beforehand I want to do another
one I'll do
[Music]
this you watched Rick and Morty no U I
think the newest season I didn't watch
yet oh
[\h__\h] wrong buttons always oh I bet
no oh
[Music]
I have to choose my party
solo if I go solo are the
um
enemies going to
be uh adjusted also how uh swap I if I
if I if
I
swap
will
I play
her I guess
so but okay yeah wa has to be in the
party okay that's
[Music]
okay oh my God I'm blue haired now
cute hey I'm ready how do I go
again how do I go
[Music]
again Bo
X which one's the
X this
one
[Music]
okay sorry the buttons they don't they
don't look the same I have an X but it's
a different
X my the the ex that they mean is square
for
me loal right
there
[Music]
now I can just stay back and do this all
the
time
no
[Music]
please can just do
this can just do nothing
just endlessly press the whip Watch Me
Whip watch me neigh neigh watch me whip
whip watch me neigh
neigh okay maybe that right now it's not
so
effective
for
[Music]
wow maybe
maybe the game
play it's not as interesting all like I
I can I can do this all the
time maybe I should do someone
else also this
one I don't know if I'm doing it right
though
spin whip to
win no I like her but um for the sake of
making my battles interesting for you
guys maybe I just need
to not stand around and rely on my
[Music]
whip o last hit foretta
again
should have I should have removed her
the moment I had the
chance
[Music]
yeah
okay Z is fun I'm not going to play
Zetta because Zeta plays
Zetta it's this easy as that that makes
sense
right even though some people
recommended me Zeta but zaa play Zeta
so I guess I'm
[Music]
ready
these loading screens are
non-existent you can immediately move
on what's up with
[Music]
that is it just my
SSD is it m being
good
[Music]
thanks for the membership
gift uh I don't know seems
okay
yeah
maybe maybe it's like that
[Music]
hopefully I mean I could read the tips
cuz I don't have to immediately cancel
the loading
screen but the the fact that I can
is
amazing
but the SSD is my SSD
right learn his
name
it's learn
it or we'll eat you up roasted flying
dragon
tail you want to watch the anime after
this yeah I wonder what the anime story
is
[Music]
about too bad I don't really watch anime
anymore nice everything repaired
now looking good
can I go there
no time to go
oops that will change soon
mhm moving on to the next destination
with this cute looking girl it looks
like a shoe the bottom part looks like a
shoe
[Music]
it's literally a
shoe furry
cane first have like a epic name like
baham and then follow it up with
furry
I guess wait maybe it's supposed to be
Fury cane I don't know but it's
just funny to me
f ooh she's a pretty
[Music]
lady she reminds me of
Nisa similar
vibes
the Elegance people said the same
[Music]
thing
oh B think about n s too
much what is that pink ship what the
[\h__\h] the
pink pillow
chip what's that
[Music]
for oh thanks you thanks you for aving
the
rest oh there here again
those D from the Generation ship just
decided it's a Generation ship
now oh why no why no subs for
[Music]
that and once I summoned these pets does
it even make sense to why am I so
far does it even make sense to like
press those skills again when they're
loaded back
up oh now they're gone are
they but I have two
now these two that are actually
I'm supposed to summon them in my
[Music]
combo oh I'm supposed to
shoot
oh
oh am I not going to get hit when I
stand
here help oh there's another one oh
protagonist doing her
job go can I do more okay ah
[\h__\h] wa and they don't have HP right now
oh okay
welcome I don't know what I'm doing with
this character I don't I I feel like my
range I don't know where my range
is now I'm
[Music]
hting guess I'm so far I'm
overestimating her
reach uh the red ship is this should I
go in guess I'm going
in
P release free what you mean my pets
[Music]
what
I don't
know I have to get rid of those cannons
right let me do that
then
the pink hit will summon your pets yeah
yeah I understood that that they join in
you don't mean summoning you
mean that they join
right
invincibility
hey
also
[Music]
summons oh finally someone's giving me
company over
here saber where's your saber face take
off your
helmet
okay I saw it like happen in this very
moment
yeah I can ignore oh God okay okay then
I'll focus on this oh it's okay it's
okay
we're
fine I probably needed to kill
everything I never run out of
time I it now the now the time is going
the other
way but is there like
items
sorry I'm L the
party see doy do me to me
too wow I'm sure they have really
valuable items there I have to
check o
o I like this strip
design it looks like the head of a
dragon that's surely on purpose
h
okay one down dragon versus
Sho kind of lame our
design
special
attack hey
why would you do
[Music]
that clear what
now H uh chase the red chip uh
what me what do you mean
[Music]
Chase what can I
do can I help
you Chase there we go I was just
waiting La was not in
control another
one
ship we just prepared
it y more
ships what why do they that's not fair
why do they have so many
ships aort Mission AO
Mission excuse me
oh welcome on
board I'm the damage dealer
okay can't rely completely on
me okay
okay this little
bit I can't reach
[Music]
him
I hate these laser
arches so
much
finally anything else no okay we're
infiltrating okay maybe not look at the
boxes then I'll focus on the Cannons
[Music]
again
I can go straight to the
core really ma that's boring though what
the [\h__\h] is that
though mother
mother I want to kill it is it the time
waste no she's
dead mother is not giving
anymore oh oh there's
more
oh my God so much purple stuff on the
ground
nice well I I held strong as long as
I that's
it
oh the whip is popping popping off
Indiana Jones would be so proud of
me he taught me everything that I needed
to
know and I still felt kind of lost
so jump
jum you like the movie was all
right the Rings is
better no problem bring on the next ship
then this
one that is arguable excuse me arguable
oh can't believe
you what's wrong with
you I hate the
lasers wrong
target
how how bad am I guys I mean I'm at
least hitting them
[Music]
now they want to use their
special
is it special
time wait I should go I should stop
fighting these
bugs okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
okay try using your cool down
okay I just bought
Mash that
[Music]
right you who are we attacking the core
okay good good
good the little but maybe the Cory got
some AOE damage
[Music]
too you can keep resummoning your minut
for a deep
fryer all I didn't even look anymore how
much time we had left was
clutch
good I want to fight I'm not done
here
Oh I thought this was a gacha game it is
the base is a gacha game but it's a
popular g game so it gets an anime and
other spin-off games isn't that
nice isn't that so
nice there was a chest engine [\h__\h]
D
oh the big one is the big one oh he
looks different though I is not the
[Music]
same silver wolf curs
okay cute
ears looking like Dumbo over there you
dump
oh he didn't like
that okay give me a nice fight last man
standing that's not going to work we're
a full woman
[Music]
party well you are already by default
The Last Man
[Music]
Standing
link time how do I activate link
time I don't see a
problem
ah [\h__\h] I used too
much okay just when it pops up
right have to cancel my attack so many
times after the bar fills the blue
on
okay
for that what was that
sound there we
go it's that time of the
day I'm not
[Music]
ready I'm so cute I'm so cute I'm so
cute
[Music]
woo we all look so
dope oh now we have a different burst
right oh no he's
first go what the [\h__\h]
where you
going
ah ow hey why is it hitting me I'm not
in the
circle nice
heal
o what is he doing he's going super
saan he's going back
to
his blood first kind of weak I got aible
frame a [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h]
vble
for actually used my healing skill can
you believe it
indeed
[Music]
[\h__\h] thank you for doing that thank
you oh [\h__\h] that was almost the full
party
life oh my
god oh
dear
[Music]
for get oh
d
foree
triple
jum
I need to remember how long the
invincibility time
is
for that's pretty
cool slow motion
[Music]
time didn't really make good use of it I
guess
but uh
Chu
chain it in let's
goo the second time in this
boss
it oh so far away oh no
bloody
[Music]
we got to do it twice then he gets to do
it twice
[Applause]
H I just
said you're so
outdated nice moves
though you
done
no no don't Target
me
again blood first
again I want to do
invincibility please okay okay okay
okay
oh there you
go I got it in my blood from playing T
of you
know
what did I do why did I jump into it
it's almost dead though oh never mind
yeah t uh maybe but more Final Fantasy
huh did we have more inability frames
[Music]
thereal ah they're taking care of it
right what I was not in the
circle uhoh get up get up I'm so
busy my
hit my
hit no it wasn't my
hit it was our
protagonist
[Music]
[Laughter]
this me she's wearing my
[Music]
name getting roasted by small
colleague will we ever see this person's
face evil
potato yeah
okay I really hope the voice is going to
fit the face cuz I kind of doubt
it
[Music]
Goose where' that go he s
it let's
go
[Music]
wow
take your
meds I forgot his
name there was never such a person
here
never that was pretty messed up
now yeah for real man I love his hair by
the
way he's been blessed with Godlike
hair
I got it from my mommy I got it from my
mommy he looks really different in the
artwork galanta one of obious free
generals Halbert at the ready he gives
off an intimidating
Aura let me read these actually the this
Elite military corpse is led by galanta
one of the free
EV a generals
fvf hopefuls are recruited from the main
body of the church of AIA then put for
Harsh almost Soul crushing training yay
this huge island is Fred throughout uh
with mountain ranges with the highest
peak Mount n Loop Pier piercing the
underbelly of the clouds I don't see an
island I see a ship
oh okay transceivers mhhm calina
okay
lazaga yeah level up
nice Al some a couple good fights uh I
like the I I liked the ship infiltration
too all
right I wouldn't have minded doing some
more shooting at the ships though I only
did that for
like a moment and then it was over then
then it was only
infiltrating but
okay I'm kind of trying my best to get
used to
fairy I don't know if I'm
doing if I'm ever going to do a good job
at
her never mind I wanted to
do I want to look at her
masteries
oh huh she already has so
many oh I didn't have to spend them on
my
own okay I thought she wouldn't have
anything that's
nice
collection what how is this diff What
what what is this
part I get this
200 hp is quite a
bit thanks for the membership gifts 10
of them
T Buffs from weapons aha so if she got
so many I should give them a bit more
too here now that I'm not even playing
you anymore you can have the healing
skill and
stuff I attacked the entire party oh
let's go
oh what
oh oh wait ah that's what's going on
oopsy oopsy ah
uh I mean both is
fine
no
not I got so many
points stun
power critical
raid
here have
[Music]
these and
then I know that I know that for
[Music]
everybody AR packed
strike yeah yeah yeah
yeah and her defense
also
give me give
[Music]
me and a little bit more for
Rett I'll give her this one
too more
gifts what's going on thank
you so
generous
not even looking at them they're all
fine okay maybe not that much although
her offense have to boost her offense
offense uh oh yeah that's
fine
attack critical hit rate plus one up to
free rowes now can be
planted link level gain roses can return
four
skill damage attack I feel like oretta
is a strong fighter so we can give her
those points okay okay I think I
upgraded
everybody some whatat did I give up on
EI though am I going to bring her back
sometime maybe I will maybe I will self
reassurance what else was I supposed to
do this is
fine uh
do I have something oh wait those
are oh oh
ooh what the [\h__\h] is this Ry
Tycoon crabby res resonance I'll take I
don't know the crit
R
uh
[Music]
huh
huh ah here we go go
[Music]
eh it's pretty cracked until the end
game for
real
[Music]
wait boost space health no raises trade
level based on WE pin is rescued oh you
then gain the associated effect okay I
don't really
know how to
think about
that I'll give e one to oh wait why not
give the heal level
two okay we can
go uh the
part
snowy are we going to
fight like a snow
enemy equip new skills what I gave her
new
skills chunky
won chunky wony walked
in and flopped and
rolled and Str
now she's just showing me her belly you
know when cats show you their belly that
means they trust
you cute
baby cat cat flop give her RS she's too
far and she will run
anyway
yeah I guess she just woke up want to
know what she's doing
here I want belly
wus Yes Yes chuny
W anything
interesting spoiler I don't
spoiler the [\h__\h] who the [\h__\h] are those
people you guys want belly rubs
too chicken belly
W oh are there characters that I could
have gotten with one of my
cards yes
please
Senai what are you doing in my
stream why are we trying to to escape
fubuki friend is here yeah fubuki means
snowstorm
foree you heard
it
well we'll
walk been For
Worse
you
alone are going to repair that broken
ass
ship
okay good luck uh I guess
guess he's going to use some magic to
fix
[Music]
it they don't call him Mr Fix It For
Nothing fix it dude
yeah let's
go nice I like the
gloess wow oh this one's
[Music]
green oh I guess we could
save H do you have something that I
should
buy what about the water shards I I
don't have any 42 shards I have a lot of
those you guys said to keep them
right ice SP wait I can break them huh
oh no
[Music]
money
very practice time well I've been
practicing in the boss fight too though
every fight is
practi so after I get the the this sound
effect and turn purple I I've been
always uh trying to
summon with the w attack
and then you guys said for the combos in
between I should use these two but I've
been trying but I don't know if that's
the way you're supposed to do
it oh wait what the
[\h__\h] no I'm experimenting I mean the
boss fight was all right
so I think we good
o it's so pretty
[Music]
here
monster o
[Music]
dead what happened to
you
[Music]
got the de be some
sweater well why did they not buy the H
live English
uh ugly Christmas sweater from 2022 huh
or
2023 I love that one get out of here
girls from Amazon you could even get it
from
Amazon snow pillow
mm
yeah I mean we have a lot of Hoodie
merch but I feel like the dead beat
should be wearing the Christmas
sweater it's
cute an ugly Christmas sweater on
skeletons what else could you ever wish
for
yeah the Amazon Basics I love that
they're available forever and they
arrive immediately and they don't charge
you crazy shipping so it's like one of
the best merch options for a whole life
or the best merch
option can I hurt them with
this
[Music]
for you want more t-shirt designs
there I should design one just kidding I
don't want to I don't want to too much
pressure yes you say yeah oh secret
chest
I want to make like t-shirts with really
simple like two minute uh scribbles like
U for the idols that I supported back in
the day their birthday
merchandise was always like a shirt in
their image color and then um it was
like a little small scribble from from
them but somehow it always looks so cute
and when I say scribble is really just a
one
color little
[Music]
scrible what down
up okay up again uh
okay
[\h__\h] H oh oh
dear that's going to be
close but there it is and they're
sending me back again why do they do
this
yeah they kept it really simple but also
because I mean they're just Idols like
no one expects from them to be like
bringing out the most amazing designs
but because they scribbl those things it
makes it
personal yeah I think so too it's really
Charming I feel like I showed you guys
those kind of designs
before
they should spawn the the secret chest
here so that I can get both and don't
have to run back each time it's kind of
stupid yeah I think for the Amazon
t-shirt
stuff that would be
acceptable to have like less effort so
to say less effort uh t-shirts but
but they're so cute they could be so
cute more
[Music]
personal I don't know maybe there's a
reason why um I mean well obviously we
don't want to spam you guys with
merchandise we're a big company now many
members and I also already
feel bad about like my my
birthday being so close to the
anniversary and having to sell my
merch when the dates are so close to one
another yeah I don't want
to make you guys feel like you have to
get so much
merchandise it's expensive special
shipping I know for Amazon that wouldn't
be the case but
still that just adds another layer of
things that hardcore fans might feel I
knew it might feel like they have to
get
[Music]
slime
okay that one cuz the the um storm so
strong was hard to
see but I thought that looked kind of
sus a good eye I have
runs yeah runs a really old things yeah
I wouldn't mind doing it
but I can't just say I want to do a
rerun and they let me do it it's not
that
simple I got to
be a strong merch seller and there has
to be
hi like
a safety a feeling of safety that if
they do a rerun that I'm actually going
to be able to sell them
well yeah they needs to be in proof of
demand I'm not sure if I can really give
that like enough enough that they would
do it surely there's some people who
want
it but I don't know if it's enough for a
reun
but the thing
is that shirt that everybody wants me to
rerun the myth first ever merchandise
shirt that
one uh it's not only my merch it's
everybody's
merch so all myth fans should buy
it beh feel
horse hey I worked so hard to get up
here right now I feel like I'm playing a
Final Fantasy game of the these small
characters in the
ropes
they look like the small
ones in Final
Fantasy yeah the
L I don't know let's ask her
[Music]
fa
everybody's saying they're
potatoes wow
fruit she's so
cute
okay feel like I've seen you elsewhere
before
[Music]
yeah these kind of monsters are
everywhere
interesting
name oh it's time
[Music]
again wait I'm not ready what are you
doing I can't make it wait wait too far
to do damage oh my
God
for stressful stressful when they start
before
[Music]
me
is that even worth destroying
that can I take that down oh my god oh
it's it's too
hid wow the NPCs are also so
smart
[Music]
I was going to take it down and it
wasn't going to protect us anymore oh my
God I'm not a team player it
[Music]
seems that attack is a bit difficult cuz
he shows all the lasers at the same
time but he shoots them in different
timings so you don't really know went to
dodge oh my God
[Music]
stop
for
foree I did it this
[Music]
time someone help her she going
die wait what the [\h__\h]
okay she's
[Music]
back okay can we attack him normally now
nice o really Godly epic music right now
very
nice
see this one I don't like this
one
yeah what is that cigre than
you come down
I'm
[Music]
small it's an
amulet me watch
me watch me whip
whip I'm sorry but I can I not sing this
when I'm
playing my wife
oh I think that was
me oh I would like it to
be I felt
[Applause]
it oh was all right interesting fight I
like how they
implemented the ice
[Music]
spikes
for okay thank you
guys so
pretty if only there was a place like
this in real
life
the Deads are
[Music]
back it's nice to see some
life
here cuz it's so
lonely there's
not h
oh that's the secret path right to a
treasure slime silver slime that's
upgraded we didn't have a silver slime
before I
[Music]
think he's also there's a little small
normal chest there
too
[Music]
MSP
itak slime level two
yeah I'm hungry should I snack more or
should I hold
back for
dinner I'll go dinner m
I probably won't eat dinner until a
while
[Music]
later is this also a secret
path that feels like a path from
yeah I don't know maybe it's not but
feels like it belongs to this chest now
I'm not missing them anymore that's
good yeah okay it is
ha then it's good that I got that out of
the way first uh
here this gives me like jump and run
vibes okay like it's a jump and run game
cuz I got to
speedily did I miss one the
[\h__\h] speedily got to go
and collect all
these objects which one did I
miss what the
[\h__\h] what the what how how do you get
that
one oh my God oh my
God what
sh this is making me
salty
how okay with style is
how oh oh and oh God
ah oh that is the last one okay thank
God I thought there was more oh the most
challenging one so far I might
say w but I got to run up there again
anyway cuz there were like five chests
over
there the
audacity
one
two
three all the types of the
chest
oh yeah know I could have grab them
first but I quickly wanted to try
if they would make like quality spin-off
games like this out of every got game
that would be amazing cuz like a lot of
spin-off
games
I don't know yet about enfields I
haven't tried it
yet I want to
try this one wasn't in development for8
years
wow eight
that's good that they put a lot of time
and love into it without rushing too
much so that you get a nice result like
this do you guys watch the Elden ring
DLC Trail about way cuz I
didn't I'm sure a lot of you guys were
really excited about
it how's it
look 40 40
bucks I mean depending on the amount of
content I think that's
okay looks so
good nice
nice oh CI reacted to it you mean not in
the Stream but like on
Twitter I guess we're going to see some
more L ring stream not from
me I'm busy with other the games anyway
is that DLC coming out
anyway soon
TM June 21st uh-huh oh hi there you
can't hide from me oh this is a normal
slime though
interesting
cute July will be full of
streams I want to see BOS on
return BOS on in Elden
ring [\h__\h] yeah I want to see am
anything give me B and give me armor
give me any armor
content h M but yeah her collecting Moss
was nice it's nice to see I'm a
happy isn't it nice to see I'm
[Music]
happy
sure gosh I'm getting more and more
hungry the snackles are in front of me
they're talking to
me
[Music]
okay now that you guys reminded me of
the link attacks I'm doing a lot more of
them are you
proud
I feel like I totally couldn't register
them anymore in
my I didn't see the prompt at
all
wow
[Music]
show I'm an ice
figurine
let me go oh that's that's so
long what the [\h__\h] why are there like
just
invation what's this enemy
[Music]
spam
he was
scripted this person seems to be a good
person
[Music]
interestingly Egyptian Vibes even though
we're surrounded by CH
know I'm still eating the peanut
flips no it's like the golden details
and
the the um weapons or whatever they have
and the
ears yeah Anubis exactly
[Music]
mhm
please open it for
[Music]
me yeah just bring out the O and the PN
and the Cutie
PTI
what
fire
her kind of
dead doesn't even
blink
thank
you wow what's going
on very inter
[Music]
can't stand on the
ball you
good woo let's go
[Music]
bye
so cute that you always here wherever
the [\h__\h] I am I don't know how you do it
maybe it's a
illusion I knew it oh my God there's
another
slime it it's not a
slime for once it's not a
slime
H I guess it was kind of untypical for
it to be like literally in front of your
face
ooh the Primal primeval God is in
there okay nice boss fight AA
[Music]
okay you're going to do another
fancy fancy
ritual I have to look at it
okay everybody please
behold the door will be
opened
but not
until we got some more skeleton
Intruders ah where the
protector I am your
armor I am your turtle
[Music]
sh
small
they're
so I am the
[Music]
storm someone got I think no okay okay
they're doing a good job stopping
them
they are the storm that is approaching
yeah oh let me fight that what the [\h__\h]
what are you doing there stay
behind oh this one's a bit
stronger
am I hitting now I'm
[Music]
hting you guys want to
know my newest deep dive Obsession since
like
uh two days
ago don't judge
me
don't judge me you have to promise me
promise
me you promise me
right before you judge me you must think
about yourself if maybe in the past you
may also
have shown interest in such media okay
but you were
younger
already touching already disappointed
okay I'm not saying anything
then then it shall be my my tangent I'll
keep my
[Music]
tangent okay so when I was younger like
really younger much
younger I I I may have consumed a little
bit of German big
brother and um oh
nice and don't tell me you guys never
maybe watched a little bit of Big
Brother back then reality
TV was only big brother
basically okay okay yeah judge me all
you want I know I know I wouldn't watch
it now
but okay back then small
Wawa was wondering what if Wawa joined
the the Big Brother house someday would
I would I do
well probably
not
and but I think maybe small W was
dreaming of one day oh no don't do it
actually don't do
don't maybe one
day go to the Big Brother house and win
all the money h no no it's kind of crazy
I feel like it's crazy because on TV
they showed like I think it was always
like maybe an
hour of like cut content like Clips
basically
ha but then there was a service right
where you in other Big Brother countries
as well a service where you can watch
like all of the footage which is so
crazy cuz you can see them all the time
and that's [\h__\h]
freaky right that's freaky it's such a
freaky
concept
insane so I don't think I would ever
want to
be in that
position um although I will say whole
life big brother sounds amazing don't
you guys agree I mean come
on big
sister when like a spinoff with h life
yeah yeah yeah that's when you suddenly
give big brother a
chance
Chan give Onan a
chance but so what's my deep dive though
let me tell you I suddenly I don't know
why I suddenly got a
recommendation on my
YouTube for a like
American Big Brother deep Di of like why
in certain Seasons a certain person won
and I've been watching certain
people's
uh Journeys in becoming the winner of
their season and it's
interesting and I've been wondering if
if German big brother ever was this
strategically played cuz I don't
remember it like that maybe it's just
the Americans are smarter or I was just
too young to understand the strategics
behind that but it's actually insane cuz
it it felt like it was
legit reality TV chess played with
humans because the let me tell you the
amount of like backstabbing and lying
and then also not necessarily lying some
players play it with like more honor but
still like so much F into it into every
Alliance they make like a million
alliances and stuff holy
moly same with Survivor okay Survivor I
don't know but they did sometimes
mention that one there oh she's
running now I just I don't I wouldn't
watch Big Brother but I just thought it
was uh interesting to watch completely
random deep Dives of things I've never
seen
before it's a
nice a nice reminder too of the times
when small wa was
small
and then speaking of
living while being
observed I I remembered when I was small
smaller
child going
to what's it
called before uh elementary school I
guess W would always take a bus to go to
elementary school each day
and it was always a pretty crowded bus
and on the route to school H Get
Wrecked on the route to
school we always drove
past a building a a really small little
building basically one floor one floor
building and and it had a glass front
and inside was like like basically I
think living room furniture but like
facing the outside so it's basically
just like showing off furniture I guess
like a showroom or so but it was really
small and it was just one room basically
or it looked like that to
me you know what small W was thinking
that people live in there and I was
always wondering why would you live like
this isn't that so
embarrassing I can't imagine living like
this who would live
here and why do I never see people there
where are they maybe they moved out
maybe they need new
tenants God you live like
that really naive really naive of me
small
W it was probably really just
some yeah Furniture sh
[Music]
room big skeleton a
big you would also watch those shows
get okay I have to stop this
thing give me the small
ones
where the other ones
hello where's everybody else where's my
tank literally oh are they just do they
want to stay
here I don't why would we why would we
go so far behind you idiots when we have
The High
Ground
when we have the
advantage okay I think the most most of
the small boys are
[Music]
gone tequila oh my God yeah I also used
to watch like a little bit of
those I mean I was genely just watching
a lot of MTV back then you
know I think I was like Elementary
schooler or like maybe my last year for
elementary school and then first one two
years of Junior High School were
probably my MTV
[Music]
years but I told you before that like
they have legit interesting shows like
the show where uh like fans who are
obsessed with a certain star like ever
LaVine for example it's like a dating
show where free candidates they dress up
as much as they can like ever LaVine and
they get like a room designed after ever
Laine and then they showcase a
performance you know and then he chooses
depending on who's the most like his
beloved ever LaVine chooses which one to
go
for Quality TV
y'all that was I think my favorite
dating show that MTV
did and then I I hated it but I kept on
watching it
the the one with the old
dude the one with the old
dude now his name is escaping me can you
guys not oh my God there's so many over
there
is she going to
be
[Music]
okay I hated him and I hated a lot of
the ladies in the show
too but yeah you hate things and you
still watch them don't
you it do be like that
I'm just so happy where is the Big Boss
by the way he's almost
there I hope she's done
soon no but count go on him no
whatever
[\h__\h]
[Music]
what was I
saying I kind of can't remember and is a
bad bad situation right
now what was I going to say
though
[\h__\h] why am I doing that one
no
about Flavor Flavor I don't know I feel
like I was changing topics
again I was saying I was proud that oh
my
God interesting
attack I was
never taken by the plag that is the
Kardashians Keeping Up with the
Kardashians I never even tried to watch
that
and I never
[Music]
will where where is
he what where the where'd he
[Music]
go I was safe from the worst yeah oh my
God
oh like I was I was having a really
philosophical smart fa the other
day reality
TV is barely reality TV at all like when
it comes to shows like the
Kardashians because that's not reality
that's not realistic Rich
[\h__\h] living their best lives
being and having successful companies
and all that clothing lines and makeup
lines just because they're born into
this
successful dramatic
family that's what's realistic about
that what's realistic I want I want you
to show me a
family that has to collect food
stamps that's way more realistic give me
that give me
that
finally Mama
[Music]
Mia oh what happens with the guy I
didn't have to kill
him
what surely I could have killed him
before the time ran out and then I would
have gotten more treasure and exp right
but he had a [\h__\h] T HP and you're like
busy with all these little mobs and
protecting her
[Music]
man damn that's just called a
documentary no no that is exactly also
reality TV if you if somebody would make
it but
no I mean I guess people watch it that
kind of unrealistic [\h__\h] that makes you
feel bad about your own life because you
can't afford five
Lamborghinis people just eat that [\h__\h]
up really surprising on YouTube too not
even reality TV but like YouTubers you
know all those House
tours all those House tours although uh
I have to say though I think there's a a
big demand uh of like apartment tours of
like tiny places like especially if you
make them look really nice I've seen a
lot of successful videos that are like
about smaller Apartments especially in
Japan like oh my God the tiniest
apartment in Tokyo
ever and then I see others like just
living a more minim minimalistic or like
Chill Lifestyle too at least that is not
as cursed and
as
monopolized as reality
TV yeah compact Liv then
yeah oh oh crap oh my God what are you
doing here let me save
you yeah normal day-to-day life is just
not interesting you would think I think
it's pry
interesting I mean what's not
interesting about having a mental
breakdown about not being able to pay a
rent
what's not interesting about that come
on no for real though I think um we
shouldn't like spam TV with all those
like unrealistic laps because that like
it [\h__\h] up our society we live in a
society it [\h__\h] up our our expectations
not our expectations but like not that
anyone one would think that that's
achievable but it [\h__\h] up our
expectations of what we should what kind
of life we should be
living and just it's
depressing she's
gone she got new trip too
oh good
[Music]
trip yes guys I agree
everybody I
agree I like
evila
oh on
chan oh yeah Oreo Chan
and by watching those TV
shows we're just giving more Fame and
more money to the people who already
have enough of
it [\h__\h]
[Music]
society
exactly
for I'm glad this game isn't forcing me
to be either a Dodge master or a B
Master because I generally always prefer
dodging as you can
[Applause]
tell
is that is that
normal is that scrip
that okay everybody's
back tell your hom to dodge too man they
don't
[Music]
listen
what come can you guys tell me what
they're talking about later cuz I I
don't have to I can't read what's up
right
now oh they're just talking
about oh my God
lar I she's going to
[Music]
be
okay I wait I heard a
sound is that a link attack oh
oh oh man it's an impossible fight
again oh
no
I like her
booties you got
go small cute powerful anime girl being
used for her powers and turning evil
anime Trope let's
go
for let's
go this is a battle I can
[Music]
win he's got his eye on
me
[Music]
I don't like the skill the Pendle cuz it
like pushes me
back am I getting
any
I
[Music]
excuse
me
for so
nice
oh why why would you look at that why
where' it
[Music]
go oh did he just transform I blinked in
that exact moment did you always look
like
this
stomp stomp stomp anle stomp stomp
stomp
nice he's
upgraded stom stom I like his angry
stomp it's so
[Music]
cute
for ah I was too
[Music]
close come
on that takes so
long
[Music]
do I have to give it some
Kibbles
he kill all is that what she says or is
it
wait
[Music]
momy please
help
okay my
turn oh heal all is what that skill is
okay I mean that also support her if she
said kill all I like that
motivation sad sad
sad what was that Bo Flip
Flip wasn't that also uh
scrubs
Flip
yeah I
love
[Music]
fore
nice
nice good
damage
oh should I be concerned oh my I'm
concerned I'm I'm concerned I'm concern
oh what is this I'm panicking I'm
panicking
get me out of
here no oh
[Music]
no
I'm such a good teammate oh my God okay
[\h__\h] stop it now that sucks you kind of
went crazy there not
cool that on my
head I need damage damage
damage
okay everyone's HP is like stabilized
very very
good we're doing okay he's not doing the
crazy
things let's be calm just be
calm
[Music]
why you got to go so far final
swim I went fully into that I was like
[\h__\h] it I'm going for it I
believe under
is it that time again I'm ready I'm
ready I sound like Mario what was that
noise
[Music]
one nothing weird
here Happ CH title title chos let's go
why you sound like you're
[Music]
dying I couldn't get it
what
[Music]
a
spee
[Music]
we got to be careful this is danger
time I hope
it end up like ah okay R
de I can't revive her now please
wait okay oh
yeah wasn't so
bad oh no I hate
that he through oh wa I have just I just
have to stand behind a one of those
oh well at that point I couldn't move
anymore
so that's
that
[Music]
for oh oh [\h__\h]
oh
please
chilling chilling I get it I'm just
chilling
for
[Music]
foree hey
baby
damn how is he
still okay sweep time okay I I'll go
where everybody else goes
here is that good maybe
here that one I could just dodg
though anyway I felt like he was already
dead but I guess he's
not still a bit more I feel like we can
do
another
another fancy attack
[Music]
move here we
go he's overdriving
me
yeah blue eyes blue
ghosts is just so
[Music]
perfect go run run run r r r r r r
run
oh
[Music]
oh this is where it
gets [\h__\h]
hell targeting
me okay I have it under
control
[Music]
uhoh what can I
even everybody just don't
die
uhoh okay
oh
[Music]
for I bought it hits me still what why
is this HP not going
down
it was like this 5 minutes
ago yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
yes
for I think was the
[Music]
correct it's the final
sweep
[Music]
no he's dying he's
dying tomato
tomato this
one I hide behind the
pillar this boss is a bit of a damag
sponge a little bit unnecessarily long
but okay it's it's a Prime
Evil Prime
Evil yeah I got the last hit cuz
everybody was hiding like little little
chickens I'm a bit on the level really I
I don't really run away from fights and
I did the little quests and all
that missing E I mean it's not miss
there's someone else
there five level
no how many chapters are there guys do
you
know
10 wait how's I started so late today
tomorrow I'm going to start an hour
early by the
way
that
mhm 4 p.m. wow
[Music]
time
that call our do be
king
[Music]
peanut flavor so
Goode
I just did a side twist on my
spine good
cracks
[Music]
yeah I think that's a good point to stop
but let's see what they're going to talk
about okay
[Music]
okay can I save in
here yeah okay then I'll just uh end it
here over in chapter six I think maybe
at the end of chapter
um no I want to finish it in two
streams I don't want to because the
third stream might be really short
then start of chapter 6 oh okay
okay you can do two no problem yeah
right I mean especially tomorrow we
we're starting
earlyish earlier than
today
yeah and then if we're close to the end
then I don't mind going a little bit
past midnight at all 6 and8 are pretty L
streams but I think you can finish in
one more stream yay yay yay holy [\h__\h]
this game is so short so short it feels
like it could be could be a longer game
but short huh compact smaller smaller
RPG game I'll save it one more time how
do you like it I I like it a lot I like
the the beautiful character designs now
I get to play them
too uh I wish we could get more
summons uh yeah that fight just now felt
like a little bit of
a uh damage sponge but I guess I should
have grinded a little bit was a bit weak
this and there m
but yeah fun I like how the fights are
all kind of different they got some
variation the stories the tutorial the
post game is much bigger
huh huh what do you mean what's in the
post
game what do you mean the post game is
much bigger is there more story in the
post
game
eh what's what's with my
microphone
what what what what do you mean mic
issues I mean it's kind of weird but
isn't I sound fine in my
ears a lot of Co-op Co-Op part okay so
you're just saying that's where the
co-op
starts post game has a ton of missions
that you'll play co-op
H okay but that won't be that I'm saying
I'll I'll complete the main
game um I'm almost caught up to the
other girls oh my God Ena did like so
many streams but I guess she did shorter
streams
um uh sounds fine thank
you you sound great thank
youa hasn't finished the epilog at least
on stream what's the what's the epilog
what part is the
epilogue aab is a fairy player yes I'm a
furry
what I just noticed a moment ago that
she has this oh now you can see now you
can't see my mouse I here ah
[Music]
no you know I mean I mean this uh the
ghost that gives her flowers so
cute
cute but yeah uh I ideally I want to
finish it tomorrow I'll do my best uh we
won't stop for 30 minutes Dr tangent
don't
worry
mhm H I don't know we'll we'll read some
super chats though I'm I'm fine to do
that
let's
[Music]
for let's read some no I
promise
um oh we can go to the RPG
office this one's
cleaned no mess because I resized things
to be smaller or
whatever uh come on come come
on
hello there you
go oh I did change the uh CSS for that
for the Valentine stream so you guys are
looking kind of cute and
pink
yeah
whatever and now I would like some
[Music]
B
RPG
PGM
we
[Music]
H how do you know we're not constantly
cute or pink you're definitely
constantly cute but pink no did you have
fun yeah fun fun game
game yeah it's
good the art style is like perfect
perfect
perfect the story hasn't I mean I know
it may seem like I'm not I haven't been
listening
much I just feel like the story is very
simple so
far pap besides that music is dope
characters are um
cute battle system is
noise yeah yeah simple
[Music]
right M
yummy stay got there also some really
good voice actors but um verm
can go somewhere
[Music]
else agreed right
guys no the actress is epic
legendary but those kind of
mascots they can be so
obnoxious and they have made it kind of
[Music]
obnoxious
yeah
anyway I wonder what I should do for
thumbnail tomorrow cuz this one's epic
too I wonder if I can make another meme
thumbnail that would make
sense to keep the theme
going would that be
nice now I'm going to go to the Super
chatos did I I didn't finish reading the
ones from the W back stream did
I did I give you guys a
[Music]
number I didn't why did I
stop
62 63 62 okay yeah that's that might be
cuz I do have uh those selected around
that
area
[Music]
okay
okay H chat that what happened to you
guys you guys just got to ride more it
disappears
faster uh okay here we go doing
Moonlight thank you for the red super
chat welcome back you my beloved yours
beautiful as the day I lost you maybe
even more we H the restaurants clean and
functioning we love you oh yeah did I
read this I don't know but anyway thank
you # # be love forever yay thank you so
much for waiting for me why did you lose
me why did you put me on a leash or
something HH why' you lose
me why why are you so clutzy eh your
fault be more careful don't lose me I am
valuable I must be kept safe h
thank you
Lou unknown for the pinky welcome back
boss hope you had a wonderful break I
really missed you thank you I missed you
guys too it was weird not to stream but
my break was nice bit stressful but also
nice just happy that now
the technical problems are finally
officially resolved since today
[Music]
I actually I have to go to the post
office and pick up a gift they sent me a
gift I wonder what it will be probably
just some merchandise
from the
provider like you know how Discord sends
out these plushies of their
mascot no I didn't get the cloud of the
working yet it's not in use right now
they sent me a gift yeah but also of
course I'm also getting compensation
otherwise I would um be very
unhappy
yeah from your IP yeah some gift like as
extra compensation I need to pick it up
cuz they sent it a while ago and I
didn't pick it up yet y also cuz I I
couldn't care less about whatever that
is a t-shirt or a plusy or whatever if
it's something nice okay I'll take it
back
but maybe it's a coffee cup coffee mug a
new
4090 it could be a coffee mug I was
thinking so
too ice P
do it's just so
annoying I won't go into too much detail
but it's just so annoying that you can't
reach the right people in the first
place because there's just this def wall
of
defense that you have to go through but
they're so stubborn and they won't even
take you seriously just like with
doctors but yeah cuz first
I I I I I couldn't get the staff that I
actually wanted and then I got them but
then they also couldn't help me then
they sent the same oh my God it's a long
long
story I'm that it's
over now I never want to talk with them
again yeah can't get straight to the
point because it seems like it seemed
like they really can't like there's a
list they have to work through and they
said they do a diagnosis on my
situation and then they have to do
certain steps before others and they
their hands were so to say tied but
I just wonder when I talked to one of
the employees IRL at the store then they
were able to help me cuz they're like
you know
different different branches so they can
help me differently but I knew all along
I want to call them I want to call every
single person I talk to and be like I
told you so it wasn't the [\h__\h] modem
it wasn't me connecting it wrong
whatsoever it was none of that it the
cable the fiber
inside was somehow broken not by my
fault but you
[Music]
know but you wasted my time for
weeks could have been so much faster if
you could have sent me a technician
early on than the technician could have
made that assessment
[Music]
earlier do it be Petty no because the
chance that I'll actually reach the same
one of the same people that I talk to
solo and
um I I I kind of you know get it you
know when when your hands are tied when
you're in a call center like that and
like yeah it's [\h__\h] annoying that the
process is so tiresome and actually
super frustrating and almost feels like
impossible to reach where you need to go
but still it's not not exactly their
fault I mean partially but not
[Music]
exactly so I wouldn't call them I'll
just think it to myself I'll told you so
I told you so I told you so
tile thank you for
[Music]
the
thank you for the pinky congrats on your
return T I missed you so much for three
weeks the three weeks without you were
so painful for me huh I'm so glad and
happy that you're back always cheering
you on and loving you P.S I woke up at
4:00 a.m. Korean time to watch you
before
work oh I hope you were able to get some
sleep oh
man you say it was so painful for you it
makes me feel
bad but also also happy of course cuz uh
it's good it's good I've trained you
well guys that you're suffering without
me
no but I also feel bad like man I don't
want you to be sad cuz also that um
makes me sad but also I want you to be
sad oh man it's like I'm torn
apart but now everything's fine right
you're feeling better and I hope you get
enough sleep for
work come Sita thank you so
much Roa dear say and thank you oh here
we go guys it's been a
while thanks for the pinky yeah let's
say that P is a test subject for instant
teleportation that's so funny just the
other day I watched a podcast an old
podcast from Jenna
marles and it was an episode where they
talked about uh the fact that
the certain is actually working on
teleportation and they actually already
managed
[Music]
to so to say
teleport
uh smaller smaller smaller thing I don't
know what the word was not like a human
but uh what do you call like a particle
or
so and the problem was only at that time
that's years ago I guess at that time
the only problem was uh had at home at
at home only problem was like when you
perceive it that's when it falls apart
interesting but in theory the
teleportation worked but it when you
once you see it when you perceive it I
don't know
how but then it falls apart but since
then
probably they've made more
advances but that's so scary I don't
want such advances to be made just like
with AI man it all goes too far at some
point and only hurts the world who knows
maybe our demise will not
be Earth becoming too
hot maybe our demise will be [\h__\h] like
that could
[Music]
be teleportation could [\h__\h] up
everything but yeah uh so pek has ATT
test subject for instant teleportation
is being sent to your house however
something goes wrong and she's instead
sent to the middle of Vienna
Woods is that a specific place because
you capitalize it what will we do to
save peka in this
situation um she'll be
fine she'll be fine she has a good
survival Instinct she can
probably chop some trees and build a
house and all that just like in
Minecraft yeah she'll be fine that just
doesn't seem like a big problem and I'm
okay I'm not sure what kind of place
that is if it's just a forest in in
Vienna then she just has to walk a
little bit and then she's back in the
city can't be so bad
it's not like if you say like in the
jungle or so somewhere where there's big
jungles I would be more concerned but
this is not so concerning Roa you had
better ones
before you had better ones what is
this seven female thanks for the
pinky wome back wa thank you I can't
can't believe how much stuff I got done
when you were on your break welome back
to
procrastination ah
no damn I hold you back or you holding
yourself back and I'm your excuse huh
but for real I probably do hold a lot of
you guys back from being productive I
also hold myself back from being
productive often very often like now no
no not now
but that's a real problem although the
past couple days I was productive so I
hope you guys you two SV people I hope
you could be productive while I was
being productive I was really actually
having fun being productive for once
relatively
fun no you
wonder about what you can do it you can
do it maybe just one task per week I'm
not even staying one task per day well
it depends on how many tasks you have
and how difficult they are but even the
simplest ones I know like even maybe a
phone call to
booking.com wink wonk to myself can be
really difficult to just do or think of
like cuz like okay I my one of my
problems is I like I I I I I wake up I
have breakfast I work on my thumbnail
and stream prep and all that and then
somehow I just don't remember these
things I have to do even if they're
shorter
ones small
things I I do have a good General
overview over my
work from whole
life but when it comes to real life
things like anything related to my
taxes I especially CL cuz my tax lady
keeps on telling me the deadline is not
the issue cuz I already
paid just makes me procrastinate
endlessly I'm
honestly glad that it doesn't all have
to be sent in
[Music]
immediately but
yeah don't remind me about
taxes I paid my taxes for the first
three months of the year um like a week
ago or
so I sent them a big chunk of money
goodbye goodbye money was nice having
you momentarily
[Music]
temporarily it's only been a month
though yeah I don't know in in February
I have to pay for January February
March and then
in May I guess I have to pay for the
next three months or
so four I have four installments the
good thing is like last year my problem
was I I paid for two years in one year
and that caught me off guard cuz I in
2023 I was paying for 2023 ahead of
time or like at the right time and then
for 2022 I was paying in 2023
like after payments I guess not not that
I ever paid them like in that case we
did we just I guess chose to do after
payments and then for 2023 we did like
prepayments and that was in the same
year
[Music]
so it was [\h__\h] and she she didn't make
me fully aware of it so
yeah I wasn't careful enough did you not
pay last year of course I did
that's why wasn't what I'm saying that's
why I had so many problemos cuz I
paid like two years in one
year what is an after payment I don't
know there's just two ways of paying
your taxes here I think that's probably
not
uncommon so right now I'm paying like
it's kind of like a
prepayment like at least it's not an
after payment I paid in advance whatever
they think I need to pay and then uh
eventually once I'm done they maybe pay
me something back if I pay too much but
if I choose to do an after payment then
I I'm free the whole year I guess from
payments but then at the end I have to
lay down a big chunk of money I guess I
don't know yeah it's normal
yeah but you know honestly I can't blame
you because when I had a normal job in a
hotel I had no idea about any of these
things taxes just happened
automatically deducted from my paycheck
same with Healthcare I wish that was
still a thing like automatic deductions
then I don't realize it and I I I don't
feel stressed out about
it auto tax is
hype
yeah
yeah yeah freelancing
man Ichiban also must deal with this
[Music]
[\h__\h] they don't teach you this in school
unfortunately for real like that's so
important those kind of things like what
happens after you're done of school when
you live alone and all that kind of
stuff like teach me about that teach me
how to live life don't teach me how to
math I mean math okay can be helpful if
you're doing your taxes yourself maybe
but
but I feel like Freelancers mostly get
themselves a t tax
personel
ideally anyway anyway
[Music]
anyway it's not just that but just like
general knowledge about things that you
will come
across after school M yeah oh
well time to calculate the circumference
of a circle centered on a triangle where
you only get the length one that still
sounds like pretty simple low-level
math you couldn't think up something
more difficult
[Music]
huh no thank God they allow the usage of
calculators I would have died
otherwise and anyway thank you seven
evil good luck with your tasks you can
do it we can do it come
on let's do it just do it watch my Just
Do It video just another kfp than
rainbow thank you for the red of chat
welcome back I hope you got some good
rest I'm writing a fanf of your power
world stream it'll be based on real
things you did but also adding my own
story elements such as your battle with
the wandering Merchant and adding a
romance of n
Isa that's that's what you're
adding thank you that sounds cute but I
do still want to start you know a
new but I don't know man no time right
now um but that's exactly also why we
got to finish ground blue
ASAP and then I'm going on this like
short little trip and then after I'm
back maybe we can balance Yakuza and pal
World a little bit is anyone playing
anymore well I know that GAA will jump
back into it for
me and generally I
heard uh I think maybe from Cali or so
that they want to do a myth pal World
collab I
think uh
so if they want to do that and they
legit waited for me
then I guess we might do
[Music]
it now it's just difficult cuz I was so
hyped uh I really liked it when I played
it once um on stream but now after my
break I personally don't have the hype
anymore I don't have the desire anymore
I'm sure I can build it back up within
myself but it's just generally sad that
I missed the most hypest
days um but if all of myth plays I feel
like we can bring back some
[Music]
hype
yeah it would be a waste if I don't play
at least once or twice more
[Music]
maybe wait for the next MJ
patch I think like with Minecraft it
will like spice it back up who knows
about
that she can help you out on level up I
don't really want to be carried like
that though that's the issue that's why
I was like also
feeling me about being left behind
like got to catch up but I also don't
want to be carried
by uh high level players if that even is
possible cuz in some games obviously
like there's ways to um prevent that
with like
[Music]
exp splits but yeah you know am only
play once that's good that's good I
should do I should team up with am a
little bit and then
see where we
get perhaps maybe I don't
know yeah I don't want to be given
anything everything and also can't give
me
EXP H oh well thank you though rainbow
thank you so much for your support and
your interest I'm excited that you're
excited about my PBO stream so you might
have
to start another story though when I
start
again
chicken thank
you I'm not new
what Richard G thank you oh I'm happy to
hear that fo thank you for the red chat
welcome back T hope you had a good break
thank you I hope you also had a good
break
huh did you cheat on me huh Paras social
waa sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry thank you EO I hope your passion
has
respark not them
back as if it ever left but you
know
distance makes the heart grow
[Music]
ther she said she will play off screen I
wonder if she really
[Music]
did so
eah a d thank you for waiting for me
cold hand Eric thank you for the pinky
welcome back yeah it's been a stressful
time and I'm so happy you're back
stressful for
you
oh why are you okay I hope I hope now
it's
better was stressful for me too though
yeah like
[Music]
partially you know there's such phases
it sucks really sucks but we get over
those phases and then we can chill so
always look forward to the end of the
rainbow over on the other side of the
[Music]
Hill maybe you'll even be greeted by a
pot filled with gold
and a little man in the green
suit I don't know
maybe think of think think of the
[Music]
possibilities not t go not yo no uh the
those those little guys that have money
at the end of
rainbow leprechauns yes
leprechauns that's what I
mean thank
you yeah wouldn't the leprechaun am be
so
[Music]
cute oh I'm sure she would love to be a
leprechaun I just have to put it in in
her head I just have to insert the
thought in her
head she'd be so
[Music]
cute I'll I'll tell
her new
am verse amerse idea
amerse character idea Le prorn I'm
surprised you guys can all write that
spell it leprechaun
Amy would be so
[Music]
cute she be like what what she
want all right Moss she likes Moss I
feel like leprechauns and Moss there's
some kind of connection
there Bruce
[Music]
Cho Tang milk Jack than thank
you o I don't know that song sorry and I
don't I never watched fairy tale before
sorry I'm sorry I don't know it at
all big bad Wolfie d chimo thank you for
the red super chat welcome Kiana I
certainly missed but I hope you had a
relaxing break and now you could read
some of the books you mentioned well
well with your return also came your
summer merch that I ordered so that's a
nice combo I also picked up drawing to
finally drop out oo
exciting oo I'm curious to see
your advancements but yeah the books you
guys should give me respect cuz none of
you even expected for me to read
anything at all during my
break but I did and I read quite a bit
but I just didn't like it I'm not going
to force myself to read a book that I
don't like but I read like a little bit
more than half of it like
60% oh you guys were so shook at when I
told you I read a
book yes I want a
sticker how many
pages oh
I can probably find that out roughly um
actually I already threw away the
book I was like yeah I could put it on
my bookshelf to you know look more
sophisticated because the more books you
have on your bookshelf the more
sophisticated you look but I was like I
don't like this I don't like it I want
this out of my house yeah if I don't
like it what am I going to do keeping it
anyway uh what is it called again I will
not tell you cuz I don't want
to I don't want you know you know um
what was it what was it um ah that's
[Music]
it okay
so surely it will tell me the
pages
[Music]
um
that doesn't sound like a
lot I uh
[Music]
I
um so I um
[Music]
triple digits yeah triple digits yeah
per I read like around I must have read
around 10 to 130
pages H it doesn't sound like a lot but
um she was yapping you
know
[Music]
how big is the font I don't know it
doesn't say here I
[Music]
think stop questioning me and my
sophisticated m
it was not big big children's
letters no there were no
pictures so mean so
[Music]
mean anyway good luck
Tassimo also I'm glad I'm glad my merch
arrived please make good use of it or or
treat it well well don't overuse it
treat treat it
well thank you Matias thank you for the
pinky what a terrifying profile picture
is that hatam is AA or
ha welcome back thank you though thank
you so much glad that you're here to see
me Dr
H I thank you for the red chat wa
welcome back
I am a dedicated VA Watcher since the
start finally I have been to catch up to
enjoy your life oh my God finally it
took you fre and a half years to catch
up here's to show my appreciation over
the years and missing your
accomplishments in real time uh thank
you Mom for making me a proud fan of our
community thank you too you know you you
don't have to catch up in order to watch
the stream live right you can like maybe
just go watch your stream live and then
return to like uh C catching
up you don't have to catch up in order
to watch it live it's not a it's not a
um um uh what do you call it it's not a
thing that you need to
do you're always welcome here it's not
like a homework that you have to
complete first the timeline must be
preserved requirement
this which season of Ki I have to
understand to the current understand the
current season I'm not an
[Music]
anime although there do be some you know
tangents that are good to know
beforehand to build up on later on but
yeah anyway it's nice to hear from a VA
Watcher every once in a while thank you
for trying your best keeping up with the
takian I appreciate it so much thank
you good luck hope to see you again
sometime in a
stream keeping up with the
takian a d GD D for the pinky welcome
Beck and I missed you glad you enjoyed
your vacation and I liked the artwork I
commissioned of you and like it yes yes
you have the honor you you made
something you commissioned something
that I'm I have since been using JMA
together happy report I'll be cheering
you on in person at fast Stage One X day
two let's go looking forward in meeting
other KS oh my God that's so
exciting isn't that your first time like
coming to something like that seeing
Wawa kind of kind of imp person
right oh my
God oh my
God
finally I'm so happy that you get to do
that thank you for you know I'm sure you
spending a lot of money to go to Japan
to do that thank you for your
commitment that would be so great
yo and please take some time to enjoy
Japan as well I don't know how long
you're staying
but I hope you can see a lot of things
that maybe you've been wishing to see
and eat for a long
time
yeah have lots of
fun good luck
mate That's so exciting it's coming
closer and closer every day oh my God
about a week oo that's pretty short but
I'm sure you'll make the most of
[Music]
it go
shopping Jo hereo thanks for the pinky I
left almost immediately after I get sick
of a cold today is the first day since I
feel completely better coincidence why
would you say that it's because you were
so sad that I was
leaving that you got sick seriously
though I'm glad you could take a much
new vacation thank you I'm glad too it
was about
time that's so sad chicken's getting
sick cuz mommy's not around
man I wish I could be there for you guys
when you were sick you guys are here for
me when I'm sick more or less like I
mean virtually you know sadly you can't
bring me soup IRL
and you know help me out with stuff but
at least I know I know you always got my
back if I want to
watch 10 hours of Lord of the
Rings while being relatively
quiet I know you got my back that's what
the voice pack is for yeah my first I
think yeah H my first voice pack
was you guys being sick and me helping
you
[Music]
true that's that's an old one you got to
have it you got to have
it I
haven't been doing many voice packs I
think my last anniversary and birthday
both did not have a voice pack but I
might do one next time I don't really
know what you guys a stances towards
voice packs if you actually like really
think they are interesting at
all um but I might do one you love them
really
really I I have to think of a theme and
I might write my own script because
after the Advent video the sock puppet
one I
feel somewhat comfortable and confident
writing another script maybe maybe I
don't know what what to write about
[Music]
though yeah we have I I participate in
some of the company voice
packs cuz they're like they're always
like a couple months in advance they're
like hey we're going to do this kind of
voice pack who wants to participate and
then if you want to participate you
participate but I don't want to spam you
guys with voice packs I want it to be
like still special so I don't sign up
for every single one but also I don't
like the theme of every single one I
want to only participate in the ones
that I feel like oh These are nice so I
like the the sports voice pack I think
that one was
cute I even got to be part of the lineup
of the
[Music]
cover sorry that was my fingers so
anyway I hope you will stay healthy with
Wawa let's stay healthy together let's
take those vitamins yo let's eat those
apples let's get that vitamin
[Music]
D was that loud it was like I think kind
of
reverbing
here's your reaction to me reading
wow rine thanks for the pinky welcome
back T glad to hear that our boss had a
great break thank you so much it already
feels like it's been over for a while
now thank you for supporting the waa
throughout my break I'm glad I have a
place to come back
to thank you I appreciate it my sweet
chicken
H Dan Omega gaming Chan thanks for the
pinking I've been wanting to do this for
a long time I kept my promise and said I
love you every day while you were on
your break and even wrote you a thank
you letter thank you for everything you
do how I love you and kfp thank you are
you wor the letter did you also send it
out or are you just writing it just you
know for
yourself did you send it cuz then I
don't know when I'll get
it h H maybe on my next Japan trip who
knows you said I love Wawa I love Wawa I
love waa every
day perfect I felt it I knew it I heard
something I just wasn't sure where it's
coming from now I know thank you for
your sweet words I did it but I'm
revising it we'll have the new one done
by tomorrow oh okay okay send it ASAP p
so that maybe there's a chance I can
pick it up on my next tripan
trip yes yes yes
yes thank you for thinking of me and not
forgetting about me h no no no thank you
for the pinky it's an honor to meet you
again like this sir I'm sorry it's been
a while since you've been back sir but
let's negotiate this your
salary
o o
[Music]
sir
Hulu you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] you can't just put your messages
through the automatic translator paple
and then think this will
[Music]
do no no Ando under
you
nope this year's
salary negotiate this year salary there
will be no
negotiation there will be only delivery
of this year
salary and next time be careful what you
say to
me I am a lady
okay
this chicken is in danger I'll will turn
you into Korean Fried Chicken next time
you address me
wrongly thank you so
much K STS Lulu thank you for the right
super welcome back you also happy Lunar
New Year here's my Red Envelope o thank
you s
it's red envelope time again thank you
very very sweet what a culture I wish we
had that culture in
Austria well we
don't so
sad Asian countries have some good some
really good cultures
[Music]
man thank you very much and don't give
too much to me give some to yourself too
okay treat yourself
nicely Fafa also with a red envelope I
see thank you so much than
sha and the rest
I cannot read just like that but I see
oh I think I can actually recognize the
Kani and kind of put it together I think
it says something
about red envelope and
then my beloved I think I got
it red envelope for my beloved Teno I
think that's what it's
saying oh my
God Japanese kanji coming in clutch very
helpful wow wow wow wow w w w w
wow happy Luna New Year hope everything
going well it's here welcome back wow I
missed you thank you I missed you
too thank you so much for being so
generous sh sh
[Music]
all the red envelopes go to
Wawa I will collect them all thank
you senior MC dad also thank you for the
red jet welcome back thank you
o thank you oh there's an emote for it
nice so many
emotes m Phoenix emote coming sometime
this year too though I think
right but we're not going to change my
Oshi Mark don't
[Music]
worry yeah you can already look up the
design for it too I don't know why they
don't implement it immediately anyway
thank you senior MC Tad as always I'm
glad that you're around thank you so
much for being here my sweet loyal
chicken looking for the top thank soon
Rene thank you for the bre of chat the
last few weeks I felt like I was like
something was missing oh one day one of
your shorts pops up and partially fills
up the void as I was drinking from my
hotel Co cup [\h__\h] with the huge Cy
plushy on my side I realized I miss K
more than I thought welcome back thank
you every [\h__\h] time someone tells me
about their holot talk merch it hurts me
something inside me breaks cuz I still
don't have it and it was here it was
literally here it arrived and they
wouldn't [\h__\h] give it to me and then
they sent it back and I'm going to pick
it up going to bring two empty
suitcases or one full and one empty on
my next Japan trip I'm going to bring
back merchandise and
[Music]
stuff I could put anyone on this date
yeah it's so nice right it's such a
genius F you can have your own whole
talk
[Music]
episode anyway I'm glad that you missed
me I hope you watched all of my shorts
because I did a lot of work to prep all
of
them and film stuff for you guys off
screen screen and then edit them so I
hope you all enjoyed all the all the
shorts I I think they turned out really
really nicely too
mhm nano block Phoenix oh nice
sick re thank you for the red super chat
m d d gold d wdp d
[Music]
event SLT thank you for the pinky hi k I
love watching and listening to your
streams you're such a passionate fun and
sweet person oh thank you I appreciate
how truly you devote yourself to bring
entertainment for us you're amazing I
will stay as your fan and support you
thank you all right I'll take that as a
promise
[Music]
H you will stay in my fan and pro and
support me and looking forward to our
future together to our endeavors
together thank you so much I try my best
and it's nice to have it
acknowledged thank you so much thank you
soon please continue enjoying my
streams yeah oh you're here yeah keeping
your promise I see keeping your promise
very nice
good
employee yeah getting on my good
side Unity chat thank you for the pinky
during your break I mostly focused on
IRL stuff so I barely watched other
streams during that time nice okay very
good it just wasn't the same oh that's
what I like to hear for me personally
Holo is Bleak without you you're simply
Irreplaceable you being back now puts a
big smile on my face Unity Chad what
Chad you know what to say to me oh hi
smovie smovie likes you too
[Music]
hi oh she
dropped she
rolls oh she already got up
again
[Music]
hey M
baby no she doesn't
care oh you rob your body on the door
why not on
[Music]
me she came back towards me and then she
turned around again and Dred on the door
again I think she's telling me to end my
stream soon smothie soon I'm
like almost done
with the super chats from that
stream
[Music]
almost Come on Mommy I slept all day
waiting for you to finish
streaming she standing in the
hallway she's coming back she's coming
back hi oh she's rubbing the door
again come here rub my
leg
[Music]
I have to pick her
up oh
oh
not yeah wet
[Music]
yeah
only a little bit I should have I should
have been suspicious it's always like
that I should have
[Music]
known
I washed it
already you also always forget
it no it's okay she's honestly both of
them stay generally very clean I feel
like they had they I'm not sure both but
they had more accidents when they were
younger where I guess they had I don't
know more diarrhea or
so and
they I had to like you know clean their
the
[Music]
butt and sometimes I I I don't know it
was like really sticky and you just
can't get it off that easy so I have to
cut it and then they run away and it's
difficult to stop them and show me their
butt clearly cuz then they put their
tail down in a way that I can't get
there
properly it was always a struggle
yeah with a
scissor yeah that would happen sometimes
but honestly I haven't to had to clean
their butt in a long time they've been
very clean very elegant about
it he don't say ew I mean it happens
accidents happened and it's not really
their fault in the end it's like my
fault for giving them food that makes
their tummies
upset if they don't have a really
good bowel
movement it to be like that and with uh
honestly with long fur cats it is very
common a very common
issue they my babies yeah they were
younger they were definitely much
younger when that was a
problem yeah you get it you get
it
it's gross but you do it for your
babies gross yeah sometimes it got
really gross yeah I see I see smoothie
like loafing in the hallway in the dark
cuz I have the lights off I see her
though she's looking at me she has her
eyes on me okay I'll I'll do my best
smoothie
uh so Jason Henry D you got mik than S
swc Ronin thank you for the pinky K is
honestly so good to have you back I got
a new job during a break so I may be
stuck as a VA gang until the weekends
now oh okay but I guarantee I'll be
keeping up to the best of my
ability
really [\h__\h] let me drink some
[Music]
water
okay really glad your break went well
you lovely
bird thank you oh my God I'm happy that
you're so excited for me being back and
congratulations on your new job I hope
it's going well so far it's been a
couple days for you now
then thank you for the members message
almost done almost done yeah I hope you
enjoying your job I hope it's treating
you well and I see you're still very
motivated and committed to staying
caught up with me so I don't feel too
worried don't feel too worried but
G juggling two jobs kfp and another job
you know which one to prioritize
right thank you and see you hopefully on
the weekend Life In Action
uh if I
stream
if V faction ultim MK to a free d Jack
47 D thank you oh yeah there's a Tom
raid Tomb
Raider remasters releas I don't know if
I'll play
yet I think I was told if I want to play
Tomb Raa I to play one of the later
entries I mean triangle Bobba might
belov it
but if if I'm being told
so to for once play something old uh
newer than older then there must be a
good reason for
[Music]
it we'll see right now I don't have the
time for any of that
anyway ion thank you for reminding me
thanks to the pinky too welcome back
T we missed you but I finally managed to
solve some personal issues while you
were away nice me too me too thanks for
cheering me up all these years it really
helped me get through it all is this too
par social
no no no it's okay I feel
like it's fine you know it depends on
the streamer I feel like maybe
um maybe certain streamers might not
like it when it gets super social um but
I think the how how we do it is still
fine I like to hear from you
guys I I want to
know these kind of things I don't mind
knowing them I mean there's sometimes
there's maybe things where I'm like okay
why did you tell me
that but most of the time no I I'm
curious
and um I enjoy reading
about these things and you're not even
going into much detail
anyway you're keeping it really vague
anyway I'm probably the more parasocial
one but I'm also the streamer I tell you
things because I stream all day
I what else am I going to talk about you
know I'm just sharing my life with you
because I got nothing else to talk about
you
know so it's fine thank you for being so
sweet and thank you for supporting me
for years I'm glad I can be a positive
vibe for
you as you do the same to me thank you
so much tahan too thank you for the
pinky welcome back boss I have to miss a
stream today because of work V gang hope
you saw that nissa's parents wanted to
meet you and uh and your mom yeah I
think I mentioned it anyway also I'm
going to try Deep Rock Galactic so I
hope you can play it too hope you had a
good break I didn't expect those two to
pick it up uh especially like now so
soon after I got presents for other
members where by the way I
have uh
a a uh suspicious
that probably a lot of them didn't
activate their game code because the
other day I messaged one of them and I
was like hey by the way did you see this
did it work did the code work and I did
this like
recently like two months two three
months how much how long has it been
after and they like oh sorry I didn't
you know get to or
whatever I'm like like okay no
problem um but I
wonder who
actually activated their code cuz I
haven't heard
back from
many most of them I didn't hear back
about this particular topic like
anything like oh thank you I installed
it uh thank you or something like
that so I've been
wondering m is there like cuz like when
I for example I bought
Nintendo or gift cards no I bought I
bought an activation code I think yeah
it was an activation code for a game and
that
expired I think that I think it was an
activation card for a game I I [\h__\h]
expired so I wonder do these steam gift
codes also
[Music]
expire yeah it full on expired but it
was indeed like a year
later
I hope they don't
expire um but I might need to remind
everybody or like like poke them hey did
you install this because otherwise it
will like disappear in our logs and it
will be forever
forgotten I'll poke them I'll poke him
real
[Music]
good yeah cuz I know going to play Deep
Rock Galactic and I gifted that to bibo
didn't I
so I also have the game I got it for
myself too so I'm up for
collab with anyone really but that
wasn't the the group that I expected to
form at this
[Music]
moment yeah cuz I got pretty much
everybody humble keys in the
end I could probably Google it
though do humble bun oh there it is Keys
expired uh
there is an expiration
date oh
no it says the specific expiration date
will be located on the download page
which is typically 2 weeks after the
promotion
ends they probably all
expired um wait can I um
you can probably check like one of
[Music]
them that's those must be for actual
bundles okay let me check let me
[Music]
check okay let's
see for
example
this
one so it still says redeem so it's
probably not been redeemed
[Music]
right it doesn't I I can't see a
expiration date either
though
[Music]
humble emails me about it
really yeah I'm going to poke them all
anyway thank you thank you thank you
thank
you it's a good reminder sometimes I
think about it and then I'm like H I
wonder if they redeemed
it cuz I would probably forget about it
too if I'm not like urgently having an
itch to play that game that I was gifted
but
yeah anyway
anyway I don't know uh about the rest of
parents I talked about it before I
actually did I did we did any of us
mention this when we were in the Mal
Dives narissa had a call with her uh one
of her sisters a video call and she was
like purposefully for I guess my privacy
and all that she wasn't like trying to
show me or anything and she wasn't even
trying to involve me in the conversation
but I involved myself anyway cuz like
they were saying goodbye at some point I
was like like poking a peeking peeking
my head in and I'm like hi cuz I thought
I should great I'm in the same room I
should say hi so I talked a little bit
with one of her
sisters and I saw her
room I'm not going to comment on
that state of the room but um they she
was really sweet she was really nice and
uh I did feel like they um had lots of
similarities facial
structure so yeah it's nice talking to
her family but that's the only family
member I talked to and then her father
indirectly told me to go to to to come
visit them anytime I'm always welcome
and you know shooting range is always
open oh
yeah I mentioned that one last time
anyway so yeah that's the
extent that's the extent
of our
interactions but I think it's so funny
how cuz I I involved my my mom before
yeah cie involved her mom too before but
narissa is involving her huge
family oh my God she has so many family
members appear on her
stream and I like the designs people
made for them
too now today I saw somebody even
animated like life to
deed uh her mother's design really
quickly it's crazy Nissa was a package
dealer what a deal it's crazy
it's
[Music]
crazy her whole family is
involved and I haven't seen much cuz
like a lot of it is like unarchived
kokas and all that but from what I've
seen and heard her family members are
interesting and quite the characters as
well nice interaction
[Music]
a fun
family you and P were the first to have
your moms on I don't know if it were the
first but uh it was definitely not too
common yet at the
time H it's definitely still
very like a unique thing to
do yeah and I was so nervous about
it I was so nervous about it
yeah anyway uh s this where was I uh
Jimmy fried penguin jimy oh my God d
zombie d rainbow oh you're sending
another red Super Chat thank you it's
okay there's never a good time to take a
break yeah I mean for us yeah it's like
always work work work work work you're
the most important I would never forget
about you I always enjoy whatever decide
to stream because it's you who's doing
it why are you so nice thank
you that is very reassuring I appreciate
it thank
you than for your sweet
[Music]
words I'll try my
best from now on too so please support
me
rainbow thank you for being so
generous C j i
AEP May thanks for the pinky remember
kfp K serious business our T takes it
very seriously you should do
to DOA what's wrong mayap Lea I mean I
don't know I wouldn't quite say so not
necessarily I I put some pressure on
myself and I get nervous but generally I
also just feel like you know just vibing
and having
fun I wouldn't say I'm like that
crazy about it being serious
business
H I hope it's
not uh uh too
[Music]
too that's not really how I thought it
was coming across is that how it was
coming
across you guys are just sending emotes
not talking to
me you're just nodding
nodding casual Vibe
[Music]
yeah new profile Pi thank you for the
members
message no nod
[Music]
nod it's late yeah true true true yeah
anyway thank you M for being excited for
the K I'm sure you were excited at
least and um
I don't know I
mean it's good if it's serious business
for you I guess because I imagine you in
front of your computer listening to my K
with the pen lights out right maybe uh
like a small not a towel what do you
call it like a like a fabric around your
wrapped around your head around your
forehead tied in the back you know what
I mean serious business yeah headband
mhm
that says
kfp serious
business ma thanks you thanks you wow
Engish thanks you for the
picky welcome back D so glad you were
able to take a long break GRL is
definitely your kind of game oh how
fitting and it's a bit short so you can
play between Yakuza oh and want uh wants
to watch you play more power she wants
to watch me play more power nah n n n
she can watch me catch up and then we'll
play together maybe maybe maybe but yeah
Ram blue is now forcefully being put
between my Yakuza playr I hope I can
play Yakuza again next week I think it
should be no
issue so thank you very much for your
recommendations I was definitely
influenced by
them Andre than soon thank
you
a I'm back and I've been providing hours
and hours and hours of vaud content for
you so please enjoy Blake than thank
you okay I'm done with those and it has
been almost 8 hours again and it's 1
a.m. so I shall take my
leave have a DM
ah what is this
go eat yeah my mouth my jaw is
exhausted thank you for watching I'll
see you tomorrow uh the plan is to start
the stream tomorrow an hour
[Music]
early maybe I'll just use the same
thumbnail I don't know for now I might
for through the night cuz I want to put
up this reservation now maybe I'll do
that
then so in when we say
a byebye bye bye byebye bye bye
bye-bye
goodbye good night see you tomorrow
we'll maybe finish it tomorrow so be
there and then you can say I survived a
2hour marathon a two today marathon of
Wawa's Grand blue fantasy
streams you've seen it all you've seen
it
all bye-bye
[Music]
why is
this I told
you I told
you
[Music]
n