[Music]
somehow yes
hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm very used to speaking English
yes well
hello first
of all so this stream will now be
live on this  transmission of this this
now
real-time transmission if we
want to do it properly in German it will now be in
German
let's see who else
can speak German to me
now that I'm in there I
probably even have German but
earlier at the beginning the reason for
automatic
kiki first of all I've already said that
I should probably speak slowly
so that the translators can keep up
because we
're voting
so less than 50 percent
actually speak German
thank you for
your right
to speak slowly
so
please behave yourself
[laughter].
us a nice
[laughter]
man that
so I'm not really nervous now
but it
somehow brings up the fluttering
feeling from
my first ones
so yes here is teaching completely new things and so
on everything is well prepared
you feel very very fresh  on her
as if this is almost my first stream
but it's not for everyone who for
some reason is now seeing me for the first
time maybe
some archiv.de
in five months will watch this stream
because they've only just
gotten to know me over hello, I'm her
taxi xiao tian thank you
so thank you for the memory
don't analyze and I feel for the
first time
let's put it like this
here new music also new music
for the first time
as that's been the case for two years
but not on these can
but I'm happy for you all here  on
Watching this channel
and now it doesn't even fill up
so much that I thought about
speaking German because I always
refused to speak German on my main channel.
Furthermore, there was a reason for the almost always
feeling of being forced and suddenly so
sudden
yes yes yes
well I
'll introduce myself to you again today
but I'll leave out a few unnecessary things
as I need them because
actually I assume we
all already know me apart from the way inventory says
which people from the future
are there now  view archive
So I think that's going to
happen,
no, you can also
write in English from me Energy
Award and to
[Music]
your Google translate is
yes
my enemy says Koran
and to our files and is
now at the time it says at  us
well
good evening yes yes yes
I don't have
that many to prepare now to be honest
I didn't have that much time
so wait so much it will be a
perfectly normal pace no big miracles
will happen here no big
surprises
so just killed once
and then  Let's get this
over with these stars of this canton
that has actually existed for a while
[Music]
although this is 19 an German speaking Pippo
monster with screen software
maybe a little bit too
early until I spoke in Japanese in between, I
might be doing my English streams now  Mixing a bit of
English in between might be
a good idea
[music]
and then there are
people who don't speak German,
even research said they
can speak German, some of them can speak German
like me
[music]
well
As before, the only thing finished, but
at least we have a few translators,
yes,
that's my normal entertainment
layout for guests, whether there's anything down there now.
I think it's about titles
or
soy
[music],
I know
when I started planning like that
I thought about the whole thing here, yes,
it definitely has to fit the man in
a car because the plan is
the hand in the dialogue systems,
well, I want to be on the channel
other than the child because it
just fits so well
and  then you want it  that fits and
I thought
[music]
[laughter]
from Kenya
carlos martins I didn't want a role, I
didn't want these colors that I
always had, I wanted something
refreshing
and airy, we're here on the new
knowledge not on a mountain
of a mountain
very nice, I still have it like that, it does
n't move
and even without mountains and so on, so
yes, it doesn't move like that, we
also have that because it doesn't so I can already find it
in the Oscar fans when it moves,
I have it on  reported in Japanese
yes, yes, it's nice when you
put in so much work who
did it and then I'll tell you
[music]
four times over
that's pretty flat it's read here you
want to get rid of the vote for
many  Thanks for
doing it for me
and this is the version without mountains and
in Munich
nice or
nice but not so nice
now
tell you things that are important to all of you
[music]
whoever convinces themselves you have to
come from here or
where I have to be up to now  so
[Music]
was my name is
that is yes yes yes
[Music]
Japanese for
well so there are several
translations
so once there was no simple
reason here there are no bars here
because the other version was
[Music]
little birds are playing yes
yes yes
[Music]
you are also welcome to
follow me so far
[music]
ice hockey
but you
know something like that, there are lots of people
why you discuss
[music]
times of rule
everything with peace and quiet
wasn't built in a day either  asks
after st
on the cheap seats
ok so birthday sixth of july
yes
I think I prepared myself
as in a normal debuts stand
that's why I'm trying to drag this out
[music]
everything is good for that afterwards a thank you
is important now you
dialect of the Rhinelanders is coming
[music]
now we want to get
according to man from after there
is already a reason so first of all it
was already for the translators to repeat so quickly
[music]
holy [ __ ]
politics holy [ __ ] keep going  and
holy [ __ ] is holy [ __ ]
I'll teach you German
rowohlt or not,
well exactly but the language is no
longer any longer that's fine
[music]
well I'm unknown
Mainz is unknown yes
well I know
but let's pretend  As this
is also unknown,
we don't know anything
about it,
nothing is important,
one point,
but
we are talking about the
size of my font, he
obviously doesn't have umlauts,
combinations,
discrimination, I just
pronounced the English word German, yes,
that's how it is, yes, that can happen
animago
[music]
cinema co
yes so Mr.
165 centimeters
it's been right for years that's how they say
numbers in German
nothing is written I think so in
German eyes so with a
yes maybe not so much I'm and
special glass where I ask him
if he's bored enough of it
[Music]
easily this team only 40 minutes times
already when I'm of course the horn in
English
[Music]
the people who don't know easily
about this from the future
soho body is a diamond
rogans b
oh
yes just
as strange moving anime girls
and how deep down to streaming
and making videos
it actually always fits every day and
how much we already have no
idea 50 cents
there are always other generations is
the Polat Japan  and body Indonesia these
are the three
boys also have me
male specimens
I already speak with so much more
vocabulary than in English so something
was noticed I'm already
there so English was probably my darling
died
[music]
my start is good why is it gone
[music] is
running wait a minute that's not how it
works that's not how it works
let me here and on
yes
[music]
yes so I come from
something like the hate generation, the absolutely
free  Production was first generation
in English
September 22nd 20th wishes yes
and the noise it doesn't
yes the reason why I now but
said I'm doing it with all Germans
I would like a few more so
mostly
milestones no no
really
let's say it
so directly  I
would like to see her still
rolling around, yes, yes, I would
like to get the title, but
we'll talk about that later,
but in any case, I'm from below.
If you want to see more of her, then
you have to watch my English channel
because that's always the case  still the
secondary school and here I won't record like that
[music]
my dad
is he okay he was the computer and
stone skate aid and a lot of other
things
in this world and
basically my designer
he came up with my look and
then in shape  brought
yes yes
yes
[music]
yes it
's not my important partner I do
n't want to cancel either because in German
I don't think the word hartzen is sick,
I think it was more like the
Germans
but what do I know,
I don't have anyone else and I
still think so  ten times she understands here
can
[music]
[laughter]
you want to use that to my advantage
[music]
that from cathy, although nowadays it
's often just the base of me from cathy and then it
often comes from other people  because of the
value  I think it's too much work,
but
today the work is divided
up a bit because the
outfits
[Music]
screen everything
contacted me very nicely or
was only recommended
on Twitter and asked if
anyone  want to do a few things to me
of course I have to pay yes
yes yes
[music]
yes
yes you did very well
[music]
yes thank you very much
no I am the only whole life
German but we  He really has to let the whole thing
out  trumpets because
actually hole live German
unofficial doesn't exist at all then it
only consists of me
we probably shouldn't make too much of
it that it's something
official because otherwise I'll
probably get a dot on my
head
[laughter]
if it bursts when I  I'm just a
subscriber to wars then maybe you'll be
aware of it and tell me that it
would be cool if I were to look for something like that and
make it official.
That would be because of which two
generations and I think I would be
the only person there
[Music]
is okay
but it's still the same
industry probably live year driving
I would then be two industries not two
generations but also two industries
pisano two generations
good
[Music]
now next
I'm sorry that it's with if not  so fans
here is here you
prepare yourself sorry
languages German English Japanese but
here in the first place clearly I have
written information
that is
otherwise not always there
because
I have already told it all in my
first ones, we don't have to repeat it
[Music] do
n't want to know
so I speak German, my
mother tongue has
a bit of a dialect but I can
speak standard German without any problems
actually if you look at it
depending on who I'm with
so as long as I don't have a partner in the
stream
I probably
don't speak dialect directly either  so can't not
particularly much
yes
because I'm so strong sounds yes
my dear word it was in the dialect
wish
is young he is
[music]
an old one
say in German that your son in
Austria and also if I
speak in standard German  and with every now and then
on or out
[music]
an important word in my vocabulary
so
can there is there but you can about
his English
English
favorite chocolate very important because
I'm a student come
very German word I like sweet things
[  Music]
and I can see that sport but
especially the one with the biscuit so that it's
so good abroad that I wanted to
come back
can of course be a
classic and
everything is also great,
it's probably great  Another kind
word,
I think the Austrians and also the
Bavarians probably
use the word awesome
much more than others,
so also in others
with for other purposes like
a wedge under
America in front of me is very tempting,
Ricardo is basically German hockey
tastes much better to me too  because they have
chocolate under tics much better
and children's chocolate so everything the
conga do nothing wrong
probably because they roll it so much
sugar that you can't
stand there anymore
[music]
yes yes yes yes yes yes my
[Music]
favorite sport
doesn't ask me why I
asked that because actually no
sport is my favorite sport,
I don't like doing sport but I
still have to put it in and I didn't want to talk about
what
things went into it that wouldn't normally
be discussed in a stream,
at least I did  now ice skating,
swimming and a crooked track, I'm not
particularly good at any of them,
it's still fun
as a sports boat, you could get involved in it
[music]
such a real new offer was a guest at the time, it
's a good man, it's good
to do nothing at all
[music]
Here with this can and how thinks must
spread in the German area
become better known to
large German speakers like at the beginning
because the word no longer
fits in
I maybe now
maybe we still have to work towards it
we can do it it's already an o
maybe maybe
we can do it  That
's always the title that I would like to have
that I can write to myself with my achievements
in the largest
German-speaking one as heard
[Music]
[Music] I
already have a few
things that you get
100,000
[Music]  I
'm already loud, I need more
stickers
because I think that Merz without a sticker,
a sticker requirement is usually pretty
thin
[Music]
really in Hermann
really firmly in Hermann let's go
go go go
go that
means says jam feels the same
probably times these people from
Twitter  flew here
[Music]
100 las palmas I would say it's
quite acceptable for this channel at first,
maybe even create more but there
will probably be - Kramer then
white are the noobs attack because
they are fans and drivers  are even though they don't
know any German and even though they
probably won't even really
watch,
which is okay, thank you very much for the
support
[music]
I hope that the whole event will
also give
viewers here
who were actually still
spectators,
so that was the answer  We stumbled upon this German path,
which of course won't be very much,
but it would be quite fun.
Then I want to collaborate and
make other German speakers like Thuban
[music]
let's see who I haven't agreed anything with yet
certain standards so it's
not with everyone now
but I look at it sometimes
[music]
doesn't exist but the important thing is that
I notice that the people
have a talent for inter teeth that's
important to me and a talent for suite
[music]
still  I would like to go back and play from now on
again in another country.
I would like to deal with this topic. What I
mean by that is simply that
the social system has
been let down very high in there. To be
honest,
maybe I'll be able to box soon. Let's take a
look  this is now
almost
[music]
never had  Finally
everything is
ok, thank you and goodbye,
his plan place group German karaoke
and I have to say that I
still have to stick to the same rules
even if I wanted to protest against them
in the sense of something to take,
says Anna, I take it on myself
if I'm banned or something
shows we only have what I know
but the problem is with German
songs
yes that would otherwise have that means the
company
and
therefore doesn't even see this topic without archiving the
stream are okay
because we are  Let's look at such a page
diabolo live
features of ideas we already have a
headlong time because other Japanese
coupling websites have to type in every song
that you want to know then
see that there are no games for streaming
and then there are often so many
[music]
Reithofers
rights holder yes
and if four out of five say yes
then it's not okay because then
the gema is often the fifth person I
said I wasn't right
yes that's pretty [ __ ]
[Music]
if the hay and bakuba then like
it because otherwise I have no choice
bhp
[Music]
has what I wrote under it I
can write myself I thought
maybe I can at least go
to Japanese songs like Almunia and so on
and maybe too  overtake live songs
so write German versions of them
but I'm
not sure that it will be that good
[Music]
Let's see
who is where
and when German players are
and make no mistake who
would specifically want to play in German
but let's see
mario frick year is at least the
only thing that comes to mind how common is
the problem oh and
that's a rts like
[music]
another
village romance well that's
also available in english like
but that's what the german likes yes
yes, I still have to think about it
[music]
my best friend wrote to me and
suggests something to me,
what's the matter? I've
never heard of it before,
okay, landfill tells me something,
but I don't even look at it per year
[music]
a click  and  click adventure
yes click away that India's next
the most exciting the excitement sap
games caf cuba what you can do sweetly
maybe I'll make a poster
board
[music]
yes
and I want to bring a clip like this every two three weeks
where
there's
not just one  part of it is
then this channel is
still kept alive during the boom
and yes you all reacted whether it was the first
time so that there was no real
six, I have no idea whether I
really like him but I used to have
channels on my farm and
read fairytale fairytale and it was a
bit too much work for me to
translate it but heaven
from German English means sudden death
you can use it as the first time
I just need
something that makes sense and I do
n't like a first man but
as long as it  I don't have to listen to it myself
and so slowly important things should we tell
them how should
[music]
speed up that such a fan service is fit,
it's okay for guests but no first
time microphone
maybe we'll just read a few brave fairy tales
but that  It's actually not a first for me, it's
just reading fairy tales for bedtime
stories
[music]
with German Austrian dishes
also interesting jan o let's
see if there's any activity at some point
so if it's just because it's here for fun
I'll make it official
but I really think so  not but
I already have the following,
I'm surprised that vision
is 51 minutes
[music]
yes, that's all I
have here
[music]
what I still wanted to do is Anja
German courses, so to speak, German course
streams
will be available in others  We ca
n't
serve too many indications now, which
picture is simply not a teacher
but he will do a few more,
also teach German to other people
baby
children bio
[music]
after 120 years I wanted to
have a stream planned for
I think on Sunday or something like that  On this
planet
that would be different. I know who I'm with this week,
but don't get used to it and
a clip is actually supposed to be
pumped in this week. Come here,
I know it will
be uploaded
[Music]
but we don't want you  That's
probably why there will be more
content like once every two weeks
and then if we're lucky a clip
like that in between
nothing shows every week main 9 1 2
weeks
I automatically only have it sometimes
[music]
OK,
by the way, I'm having trouble breathing
again  I have very short breath
that's why it wasn't so easy now but
wait a minute here
I'll recycle it carefully
then you'll have to forgive me
I'll see
two songs
in German you've heard before
What can I
say to God about songs that I
can sing? Apparently I hope I've
already checked everything is good, everything is good,
yes,
to bring a little bit of mood into this
[music]
what
okay
and what was that
[music]
okay  let's go
it was whether I sing
[music]
euro
now we come with us the
whole world becomes a big
player for bacteria and drums best
friends now leave the homework
[music]
point
the
[music]
posters  milan ordered
and ballet
[music]
we are wide and there was something
welcome
[music]
the hammers came
the biggest fan
[music]
and I'm fine
if that never
[music]
everyone packs up
[  Music]
no
were then in our world
[Music]
or was again with a full version
for me is second
[Music]
and no
pop stars was unexpected
[Music]
again I have seen it before
but again  credits to the cell
[Music]
Flora Dora
Sentence
like I do it
[Music]
What's included in it
I want you alone not to be better than
the other fans I want to
take away your unique weaknesses of your fears
but think
that never happened and me as a
human being  this wall in absolute they get
from gaining until everything is dismantled again
and now we are still nothing but there
is only
[music]
yes
there
because it is not
[music]
I sat in there
when I fall in love still the post
riot dog  is not me says I  I like it,
it's a
natural emotion card, that's why
it doesn't even have the world in front of the other places
more
[music]
not with him
can
come in not only see e-mails
that critical
a
leaflet with no
I'm never sure rises
[music]
nothing more
no
[music]
[applause]
what  with in
[Music]
that was
vanilla salt what
[Music]
please and so we had a great
swim for longer than an hour
[Music]
it can just do this even if I do
n't have any content
[Music]
the ju
in the morning  on the channel again but
here's another clip up
then let's hope that now before
mx war with this panel
yes definitely I'm happy I'm happy
that I thank you very much
[Music]
no no no
goodbye, let's leave that alone  so
[music]
and now comes the beautiful one
beautiful
[music]
where is mom