[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
ah
[Music]
there's always a lag though right
seems like i'm too stupid to hum along
in rhythm with my own opening
[Music]
it's not me now i know how to
stay true to the verbum
[Applause]
all right all right right away
[Music]
um
didn't want to i'll make you guys wait
too long
oh wait but i forgot to i forgot to do
my starting to it i usually always do
this in my loading screen but
now i forgot because i didn't want to
let you guys wait too long
let's see if i can do two things at a
time
uh where's my tweet okay and then
quote tweet starting
[Music]
if you guys are following my twitter um
i also retweeted a giveaway
uh from the apprentice connect uh
account
on twitter retweet
okay okay i did they're doing a giveaway
celebrating uh because i am i am
streaming
uh but for the first time i'm streaming
a sneak peek for you guys
so even though the game is not out yet
you might want to participate in that
and get some nice stuff
yes all right all right all right let me
see here
turn on the music i'm on the i'm on the
starting screen
uh we are today
playing the not yet released
princess connect redive
english version from crunchyroll games
because up until now uh prince connect
rehab was uh
already existing in other places
but it is finally coming out in english
finally
and whole live english in cooperation
with
princess connect great life is very
happy
and by the way this is not a script i'm
making this up in my brain right now
we are very happy to present some sneak
peeks to you
i'll be the first one today er
yes it is a gotcha we all love our gatta
games
so i will start from the very very
beginning
very very beginning i
am the skirt my brain is the script
there is no script i am the script oh
we'll start from the very beginning and
let me show you in one second and
oh god
[Applause]
apparently the story is really good many
people told me
that the story is really good let's see
let's see what they got
okay so this is uh i already played a
test plane a little bit but we're
basically beginning the sisters i don't
even have to do anything here
you're just showing me the problem some
intense battles
but how can she still have so much
strength left who is this boy
princess
[Music]
dramatic
is that a cat or is that a lion or is
that the tiger
[Music]
i feel very very at home already
okay so here you kind of have a sneak
peek on
how the battle will be and how it will
work
she's drunk she's drunk
the attack animations are pretty nice
pretty fast
she destroyed me
[Music]
oh
what's your name anyway
[Music]
he's already
thank you mr knight
he saved me
was either just was it a dream was a
division
but she's extremely adorable
wine she's adorable okay this is my wife
can i make her my wife
actually i ain't i woke up pretty early
today
[Music]
um
yeah that happens when i revive i always
lose my memory for a little bit but it
comes back comes back sorry that i don't
remember you
[Music]
because you're cute
your wing is a little
[Music]
i like dreaming down
thank you hopefully yours will be a
happy one too
amelia no it's amethyst
okay sorry i have speed internet don't
worry
[Music]
what is this anime scene so i know
there's an anime for this that i didn't
watch
so they have fancy anime seems like
really high production
oh she's not good she's too good she's
naked
not anymore too bad orange hair i like
it
just like me orange hair perfect must be
me
me in another dimension
is that kelly's tiara though is that is
that
me wearing cali's tiara
[Music]
this is this must be me in a from in a
different dimension
and she's hungry
priorities oh that's where her name come
from comes from pecorino
because she says
[Music]
cutiepie
foreign
[Music]
now actually i i wanted i want to serve
you
can we do it the other way around your
store though i will do anything for you
[Music]
my name is
hey my japanese input is messing stuff
up okay
okay can you remember that
register that yes
[Music]
i have no reason to uh what
are you m i am do you have like a little
mustachistic side like a big mesocystis
excited in yourself oh my gosh
[Music]
okay i'm not really into whipping girls
but
you're also hungry everyone's so hungry
me too i didn't eat breakfast
[Music]
please give me some rice i'm hungry
wait wait do we even know you did you
just randomly come here because you're
hungry
oh no this is for me this is for me
[Music]
have some because you're me from another
dimension um
[Music]
i remember her name
no cute out of my girl getting chased by
monsters we gotta save her save her save
her
[Music]
who are these monsters where did they
come from
[Music]
okay
everyone
i have no idea how to fight even though
i'm a part-time warrior
[Music]
okay
okay so mostly it's automatic but i
gotta activate some skills
all right
[Music]
and he's dead
thankfully not too challenging because
i'm not very good at
[Music]
are we not ready to tell each other i am
am i the only one who who like was
reminded of piccolin's
voice that was reminded of a fubuki
senpai
by her voice
[Music]
pay attention next time
hi
[Music]
m
my
[Music]
but i'll stop i'll stop mentioning
names now
[Music]
that's the cute that's the cute cat girl
that i saw before many times everywhere
on the internet
[Music]
yes yes she is of course she is
i love how you can tell by the looks but
i like sunday girls as you know
[Music]
um
all right all right it's a cute name
[Music]
my heart is beating so fast when she
says that that's so cute
this is where our story starts together
oh okay speed
nice anime animation oh are you watching
the opening
[Music]
oh is that me doesn't exactly look like
me but okay
[Music]
i remember that that's the kaiser the
german one
carol where's your crime
why did you cry where's that
[Music]
is this straight from the anime or is it
for the game i wonder
i really want to watch the anime
the everyone has been up for a while too
right this is from the online
[Music]
nice opening
nice that really hypes up the whole game
i like it i'm hyped up let me play let
me play let me play
[Music]
my lord oh you don't have to call me my
lord you can just call me kiana
[Music]
they're telling me where to go on their
main quest
oh the cute crazy
out there the strongest barrier ever
what would i do without you you're my
guide okay
[Music]
i look like the fake casper that's not
the real password the real casper is
cuter
and we can speed it up by the way
[Music]
as evil casper i would never fight the
real castle
yeah let's keep this one for later
if there is a later oh there is no later
[Music]
and level okay nice okay whoa
well that's easy enough when we get some
items we get some fancy diamonds
is that the gotcha currency or what is
[Music]
foreign
six
[Music]
this is what we got from the battle okay
and then this one except this one too oh
so we have to equip all of these and
then she gets some like
upgrade or something
[Music]
um
is that is that in the english
dictionary yet it's the english word now
it's part of our lives drama okay
i wanna i wanna draw thousands though oh
we got a special animation for drawing
godzilla
what rainbows
is that you always get that in the first
draw i suppose
your big sisters
[Music]
going i want to get some more but the
game is telling me to fight
i want to counter more
okay let's get it over with
okay we're adding her to the battle
i i test played um the japanese version
as well
and i got a different girl in the in the
first round
i wonder if this is fixed
for your first role in the english
version
wow i guess you can do it i want to
does it just use all the skills
yes it does oh
it's nice to have an auto function i
know that from other kings it's very
nice to have another function
then you don't have to use your brain
all the time and you can do other things
on the side
[Music]
it's a random freestyle oh and we got a
stick in the hat
[Music]
we just received is that is that that's
a currency give it to me
[Music]
i want
you didn't leave me after all you're
gonna we're gonna talk every day when i
log in every day
i got you got skip tickets what's up
what are they skipping
money that looks like money to me but i
want those katakuri
[Music]
even though this is not officially
released yet
[Music]
did you guys see something that that
you're really excited about for that
that that you didn't know uh what ram
grumble fantasy crossover
woo okay this is a nice starting screen
let's see what we have here missions i
did some
[Music]
and of course we're gonna go straight
into the katja now
what what is it
[Music]
on i guess what's selecting normal
display down ah okay no whatever that's
i find the way it is okay so i can
i have five no i have only 120.
[Music]
wait do i buy jewel use premium juice to
draw the katja one time
[Music]
but i have it needs what it needs uh
50 so i can do it two times
what what what can i not
what what which one do i go for daily
jewel pack
oh no way this uses actual money i can't
do that on stream right now
you might see my my personal information
wait what do i do to get more i want
more
oh up to two three drops per day
what is this draw normal gotcha ten
times for free yes yes please yes
ah that's like the equipment oh
i wanna do some gacha though
[Music]
i wonder if i can get quickly more of
these because i don't have enough
maybe if we proceed we'll proceed a bit
more in the in the main quest
maybe we get more okay let's go we gotta
fight for the gotcha
let's do more quests
[Music]
hmm
we can roll we can roll but let's do one
more
let's do another one let's get as much
as possible
[Music]
so by the way guys you can pre-register
for this game right now
on crunchyrollgames.com or at the app
store if you look up
the game in the app store you can
pre-register right now
it's coming up soon very soon
i can't tell you when but i can tell you
it's gonna be soon
and while you're at it check out my
twitter um because i
retweeted a tweet a giveaway from the
game
so you might want to start uh out with
what is
for yourself you might be a winner a
lucky winner
and yeah the game will be available in
every country that doesn't have princess
connect
available yet in their country this is
the global release
another gems
against
[Music]
see snipers of daily life for the girls
what is this a table full of happiness
is this an anime
oh yes let's let's download it what is
this
ah a second it's so pretty
[Music]
um
who's your favorite girl guys see
there's a lot of you who played um
other versions of this game before or
watched the anime who's your favorite
[Music]
harold
this is the first time i talked to you
and you are already at simpson
oh my god more please
[Music]
she was so nice to you
she was so nice to you though
[Music]
oh oh she's angry again what what what
is it now what is it now
what you can do wrong
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
the pronunciation in japanese is kind of
different
[Music]
you and me
nice one guys
[Music]
but now
where do you want to go
that looks familiar
that looks um that looks familiar
[Music]
are you telling me that's not a hat it's
not how you use it
oh they're using it wrong
[Music]
someone
is
[Music]
i guess there's a lot of new people
today industry that don't understand yet
that i'm not a chicken because my
viewers definitely know that i'm not a
chicken
they should know they know right right
[Music]
whatever
maybe that's what kfp stands for
[Music]
you should say
i am
foreign
[Music]
me
there's nothing lewd about that it's
romantic it's pure pure
[Music]
we can give them presents can i marry
them too
wait they don't have my name okay let's
go gotcha let's go
let's go i can only draw
one right now the pain come on give me
something nice please
please please
[Music]
how do i do that deep in your bottom of
each character to unlock new stories
unlock one other eight oh you have to
watch stories with them ah
oh you get 20 20 of those
cryptocurrencies out of that
that we already saw twinkle wish is 50.
guys can we watch one more or
wait is there anything else i should
check out let's see um
nice oh we have a 7100 we could buy some
stuff but i don't know what's really
important right now
let's uh let's do a few more fights
actually
i know that's the story oh wait wait i
got confused
a question question
how much jewels do i get from those
usually i forgot 30
okay that's good too let's go guys
[Music]
later and for now we're still very
strong
me more give me more currency
oh
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
i will take some time after uh the the
streaming
part uh to read the scriptures we got 30
we got 40.
come on more more more
maybe we can complete the first chapter
oh wait i forgot to switch it off sorry
guys oh another wrench
thank you oh another one thank you
guys guys keep the money for when the
game comes out so you can spend it
[Music]
so the japanese game has been out since
like three years
and finally your dream will come true
is there a happy birthday
happy birthday for
daisy or wait i don't i will see it
later when i read my super chat
we got so many so much equipment oh we
should try to equip it on our characters
as well
oh you want me to watch it now okay i
guess so
okay okay coco okay coco girl i will
watch it okay okay
don't hurt me i will watch it and voice
on
[Music]
don't believe the rumors guys don't
don't don't believe them
[Music]
of course
foreign
[Music]
wow 40 girls i've met 40 girls
i think we can all learn something from
this main character
about how to how to learn how to get to
[Music]
[Laughter]
a
i will also be your friend i'm a serious
girl
chapter one
a clumsy man's request oh
around the mouth has passed since kiara
began her excuse me
new life in the city of land assault our
story begins on an ordinary day like any
others
[Music]
oh
let's give her some money wait we need
to give kokoro all our money
i don't want her to stop
[Music]
you didn't hear that she's 12.
she's 12 real oh there yeah that's what
i'm saying she's only
only in her brain
[Music]
uh
to make you happy
thanks for the allowance
[Music]
but you shouldn't have to worry
and we're almost uh at one hour mark but
i want to play more you so small and so
cute
but i'm also quite small
oh don't look guys don't don't close it
no no no
no no no no no no no no
close your eyes
[Music]
um
again
[Music]
do we know each other
foreign
[Music]
oh everyone here is in my service
is
[Music]
wait she's still sitting on me what what
she's still sitting on me
um i mean i could have said something
earlier i didn't wait so long
[Applause]
what the hell
you just made yourself comfortable on
top of my face
[Music]
and she fell down again oh my god
it's over guys it's over it's over
[Music]
all right
wow that one's quite intense
i can't draw one more time
who is this mate though sticky also
hair guy can play i wonder
what's her name oh
[Music]
let me try um first of
all can i cook more things
oh i can equip
oh i got everything i got everything i
can rank up
oh shrunk thanks
oh i see well that's how it works
you see oh we still we still have new
boots
nice so this is how you make the
characters stronger i suppose
um i wanted to do one one last thing if
it's okay i wanted to
uh change the characters
in the battle so instead of for example
[Music]
you can take a break for a moment
so um one more time the game
is um
right now but it's coming up soon just
uh keep on following the
social media of princess connect
and you will find out so you can
pre-register if you
uh look it up in the app store
you can go to the crunchyroll games uh
website
before i need to use my skills
multitasking is not my first time
[Music]
if you retweet and follow i think that
was the rules but you can read the rules
in the tweet
about the giveaway uh from princess
connect english twitter
or just find it on my uh twitter
timeline
okay
chapter one episode two as a rock but
unfortunately this is all i can show you
today
and but i think that was already a nice
little sneak peek
the game
[Music]
excited there is be more from whole life
english because
um i'm not the only one promoting in
this game
whole live english all together will be
promoting this
uh in the next few days or weeks or who
knows how long
so i hope you guys will follow us and
continue uh
joining us on this journey yay
and you better try it out soon it's
coming out soon i'm already
playing level nine well i got access so
i'm gonna continue playing after the
stream
but first we have to read some super
chat is there anything i forgot to say
i don't think so i think i said
everything
in my in my youtube description uh
there's a link to that tweet that i was
talking about forgot to say it's in my
youtube description if you are too lazy
to find it
on twitter on your own it's in my
youtube description
check the missions first missions
[Music]
hey sorry guys we can we can do it one
more time
last round last round
come on come on come on
welcome in the team unfortunately
unfortunately i cannot try again bad
oh well oh well
i think i'll have to make some
investments
once the game comes out i'm our fans
unfortunately yeah
but that was fun thank you so much
princess connect redive
crunchyroll games for sponsoring the
stream thank you
for uh doing this cooperation together
with hello live english we're very
excited
to do more soon now
let's switch over to the main
main screen
[Music]
sorry i have to fix this the chat and
then i will be reading the super jazz
thank you everyone for coming by today i
hope you enjoyed it
and you'll definitely see more that was
really fun those it's a super cute game
the characters are really cute the story
is cute
story is very uh like everyone keeps
talking about the story being
really really high quality let me put
the logo here anyway
but i'm definitely excited to uh hear
more about the story here more about the
characters and
and get deeper and deeper there's still
one feature that we weren't able to
unlock the guild house
feature i think it would have come soon
um
but i'm really excited to see what that
has to offer
well that was fun thank you guys so much
for joining and
or if you want to stay for the super
chat thanks you're welcome to stay
on
gosh i can't allow myself to
to fall back on the super chats because
oh only 150 that's not close oh there's
more features
more features than that according to you
guys i don't know much about the game
yet but i will find a lot more
yes let me read the super chats
gillard 67 thank you shane deal of 67
pakistan thank you for the red super
chat
oh no i can't send super jets and i
haven't slept that my usual incredible
self-control is failing me your usual
self-control i don't think you have much
of that
thank you thank you thank you for the
support you love 67.
thank you sean
looking for carol pacquiao should i see
you have
changed your name and i see you're a big
fan of carol she is indeed
very adorable she has her charms if i
will if i would have to
choose my favorite girl for now
it would be kokoro
yes because i like her personality
i like her i want to get to know her
more
i want to protect her what no
no no no no no fbi no
what the hell shout out guys it's all
innocent and pure
i want to protect her she's my little
sister
and she has a very pretty voice yeah
looking for carol thank you
i see what you did there
i don't understand
i don't know what you're talking about
jonathan cause love scooters there's
nothing to apologize for
thank you for the super chat though but
there's nothing to apologize for
jake it's monkey duncan i see four
princesses at the front there but
but one is a lot cuter than the others
you're doing a flirt oh i wonder how
much i'll have to wait on rolls to get
that phoenix princess
well unfortunately kiara is not included
in the game
but my my different dimension twin
piccolino pekkerine is in the game so
you get her from the beginning so i
think you'll be fine
looking for camel dan kitchen thank you
for the pinky almost forgot congrats on
your fourth month anniversary ah
it is four months now yeah yay
for moms we are close to half a year
soon
how's your poinsettia doing thank you
for asking it's actually still alive
uh it did dry a little dry out a little
bit recently but i added the of
water so hopefully hopefully it will
uh revive itself but it's still there
can you believe it
it's been alive for much longer than i
would have expected it
i'm impressed it's also been a month
since you bought it and the shop lady
said it would
last about a month oh if it died use
this money to buy another flower for
700k
thank you but now it's still alive it's
i mean it looks
it at least at least not all the all the
um
uh leaves have fallen yet
so but i i don't want to buy a new
flower as well
have a line thank you and have a light
dancer
punches for the previous super chat that
was blank but it was purposely done to
be
perfectly frank otherwise this message
wouldn't make much sense then
before i run out of space i'll end with
oh wait it continues i'll end with heart
rates will chicken now's the time to be
simping
our attention will be wailing no don't
call it addicting
expect much fan service all you guys in
attendance
here's to good catalog and overwhelming
resplendence
hey wait in the end the end of the first
one was confusing
but other than that you're dropping the
virus nicer
smooth as always is that your thing now
rapping for me
[Music]
thank you peter 10 dan kashan the love
67 dan kishan
do you love 67 i see you're doing a
rainbow
i saw that but i don't understand the
letters that come with this
with it it's o g
b y v
or i v i o g b y
iv i don't understand that i understand
is that some secret code or something
rainbow
first letter of the color ah
i see that's rainbow colors
oh i see a csc but the the the one
one i guess you can't input any letters
so it was without any letters
ah ah and that's what ah that's why
that's why i
is in a in in in in
in uh i forgot how to say that
i forgot how to say it anyway
[Music]
thank
other games dragalia lost for crossover
event oh
yeah i saw yeah that makes me remember
when i play shadowverse
all these games are connected that's
that's like so cool
they're all connected you see all the
characters in the other games
they keep showing up
yeah it's like it's like a big family
it's all connected
yeah they had a crossover with
shadowverse right
i saw the characters in shadowverse as
well
that's fun so maybe shadowverse
characters will come to princess connect
and the granblue fantasy characters will
come to princess connect
i saw there was like a banner oh
pokoro is also in grambled fantasy
that's so cool
that's like if you play a bunch of those
games that's so fun
because you you see so many familiar
faces
the yw dankeshin y-o-t
[Music]
if you link a crunchyroll account you
can get enough currency for 10 row and
some extra what for real
yeah i didn't know that okay everyone
remember that when the game launches
connect your crunchyroll account so you
get a 10 row whoa
optimus
i wonder what kind of girl she is i will
i will try to find her
and then judge her and then get back to
you
thank you thank you for your support
[Music]
mr
thank you what
hi kiara i'm responding to your mating
call from a clip
your life is very intoxicating i love it
and youtube channel plus i know you
phoenix
oh thank you and indeed i am indeed a
but i don't think the mating call was
towards you
thank you for coming anyway welcome to
my stream
vanguard baron man thank you
daisy thank you for all the red super
chats oh my god
[Music]
so my super chats are usually dumb posts
oh post but since today is my
birthday oh
i'm going to do one of those big gooey
emotional ones i'll be honest you
weren't my favorite at first
being blunt i thought you were pretty
annoying
but as i watched something changed
first in your premiere when you said i'm
not really good at singing well that's
not true
i thought her voice was pretty good then
in a collab with ahmed you said speaking
three languages doesn't make you smart
maybe but i can only speak one and not
very well slowly but surely i stopped
seeing that annoying chicken and finally
saw the majestic phoenix
and now you're my favorite youtuber not
just from ian but from whole life thank
you tanja for melting this old cynic's
heart
now back to your regular scheduled
pose
there's been rumors you're going to
reorient kfb back exclusively towards
fast food
oh god please don't disband this none of
us
are actual aerospace engineers and kfb
is the only place with low enough
standards to let us make spacecraft
wait when the hell did we turn into i
guess when i gave amelia though the
spacecraft
the the thingy her gift is that when we
turned into
i don't know whatever we are now we are
everything
daisy happy birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear daisy
a very special happy birthday since you
sent so many super chats thank you so so
much for the support
and i'm happy i'm happy you um changed
your
opinion on me and gave me a new chance
not not everyone
does that and i really appreciate you
being so open thank you so much
i'm glad to have you in kfp and don't
worry um
you you can keep your job you can keep
your job don't worry about it
i i don't want you to leave anyway thank
you love you too
let's continue liam no one also sent a
red super chat saying
did you say gata yes i i did
thank you no one for this red super chat
i see you're very excited for a
navigator game coming into your life
well soon tm it will be there for you to
play
are you ready are you ready do you have
your funds ready for it
thank you and thank you for your support
and look forward to more
content from how life english with
princess connect
[Music]
like that kiara i mean i always do when
i
when i hatch you guys i like to sit like
that on my members
to hatch them but once you're
there they're once they crack then
not sitting on you anymore i only sit on
you until you hatch out of your eggs
you know that you know that
there's nothing new to you i'm a chair
anyway
yeah we got some kfp chairs those are
the lucky ones
although maybe that's the only chair why
is there no more chairs we need more
chairs than that
we are a restaurant we need more than
one chair
[Music]
weird
i haven't played the gaza game in here
but i might try this one out the
characters look interesting
oh i'm happy to hear that yeah they look
very very cute
they're really adorable
[Music]
so you're welcome to check out more soon
tm
ace crown ah a 10 roll increases the
chances
damn it
all right refreshing and where did we
stop
here jenna tools
princess connect is honestly 200 iq for
advertising with whole life
two weeks and we let's spend too much on
2d waifus
what i mean
i have to say yeah they made the wise
choice i'm very happy that we are able
to promote for them
because it's a cute game and i think it
suits our our style it's just my style
i like gacha games i like cute anime
games if you look at the games that i
usually play
i prefer to play like anime style games
so for me it's um really right up my
alley it's
exactly my taste
so yeah i need to keep up
[Music]
what the though alvida what the
minnie mademoise thank you for the red
super chat
always enjoy your content keep working
hard oh thank you i will i definitely
will continue
thank you so much i'm glad that um
i'm glad that you like my content thank
you i hope that i can
produce more and more content like this
that you
will enjoy thank you thank you
[Music]
i appreciate it thank you for your
generosity thank you
sarah does gaming dance
thanks for the membership by the way and
let me do one last refresh
if you sit on the employees you'll crack
them like you did so what is trash can
and hr will be angry again and just kiss
me
shut up i didn't that was
hello thank you
[Music]
oh i think i know what you're talking
about yeah but everyone who wonders
about the mating call look it up on
youtube
well that's it guys thank you so much oh
no another another
red super chat sneaked itself in delphi
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
saying hey buzz reporting in to say a
crazy driver
did a hidden run you is it you
got to see the culprit she had blue eyes
and blonde hair
her license plate was your mom's 69.
kami said she was playing lenore
i think i know who you're talking about
she bump into you i will talk to her i
will have a talk with her
that sounds like something ami would do
also check it's monkey donkey how do we
petition to get kiana added to the game
that would be amazing are you listening
are you listening princess connect
re-dive stuff
are you listening
hello
[Music]
why don't you what shape-shift into
amelia so kelly will finally declare her
love for you
guys stop the super chats
[Music]
thank you for your support and i think i
missed the up hunter on the gaming thank
you
one more from you thank you so that's it
now now now we're at the end
okay well thank you guys i hope you
enjoyed today's stream tomorrow i will
be streaming uh a collab
with uh
[Music]
thank you
oh yellow oh my god yellow stop it
johnny lakum thank you very much
i'm saying goodbye already stop it
what the princess connect love is our
shadow versus leaders too yeah
i saw that it's so cool
yellow thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
daniel ryan now for real goodbye you you
can't i'm leaving i'm leaving now i'm
leaving i'm leaving
i'm leaving thank you
thank
[Music]
[Laughter]
what the is going on
[Music]
stop it okay i'm turning them off i'm
turning them off
you brought me this far you forced me to
do this
you forced me ah they turned off guys
i turned them up you forced me to do
this
did i really have to do this did i
really have to go that far
was that really necessary
okay i think now i got everything all
right
now i think i got everything
i think i got them all okay okay
[Laughter]
i think i finished i stopped you you
guys were way too fast what the hell
oh dear lord all right all right
[Music]
thank you guys thank you thank you thank
you for watching that was
princess connect pre-dive english
version sneak peek
pre-release thank you guys
thank you and in german we say auf
wiedersehen see you guys tomorrow
see you guys tomorrow
thank you for the support i'm going some
breakfast now
my stomach is pickle pickle very pickle
pickle
bye bye
thank you love you all
[Music]
you