[Music]
la
a
[Music]
la
I'm praying I'm praying it works I am
praying it works oh my God does it work
hold on hold
on does does it work does it work it's
working for
me yo yo yo yo yo I need to ask chat oh
my gosh this this mouse is so slippery I
can't deal K KY
K hello hello there we are here yes in
Minecraft to just us just the two of us
along with the stuff of course the two
of us
oh oh no your Riv is over there diamond
armor oh my what my rice your Rivals oh
my rival sorry I was thinking about food
it's okay we're not officially Rivals
yet are we we haven't begun
yet
ah my golden armor I need to where do I
put it is there like lockers
[Music]
here there lockers because the way they
set guys do you notice anything about my
Minecraft looking different today looks
different right I like
it I need to put my diamond armor
somewhere I'm scared I'll lose
it and the chest is full
Ollie yeah can I M is there like a
locker where I can put my diamond
armor oh uh you can put it here wait
wait I think that's one that one's full
sorry yeah let me uh okay this one's not
full okay but no I hope nobody takes it
don't worry I I'll hold on to it okay
sorry guys it's because of can you give
the sheler back I'm on a very different
setup that I'm not familiar with thank
you thank you
okay uh let me try to do a little intro
um K uh today we're playing Minecraft uh
H ID C practice and I'm a cat meow chat
free ah wait
H I see I see I
see no problem let me move this here
then it should always work yeah uh I'm
on the team with way and she stole my
thumbnail but that's okay
also before the stream I was on nissa's
3D showcase hope you enjoyed that uh we
can talk about it another time later
perhaps but that was
exciting um
yeah uh let's uh Ollie and we I think
are here to like explain stuff to us and
oh yeah the other team that is here U
there was like two more teams that
didn't practice yet just like us because
of scheduling um but Kobo and Canada are
doing it later in the evening seems
so uh we adjusted our time a little bit
to at least be with eoi and soda Senpai
uh the one and only die Senai so we're
going to be four I guess two teams and
and then uh some you know OE and wiu for
helping I
guess okay sorry I did a little intro
waya okay okay I'm going to do my little
intro alone to then I'll listen though
okay
life ID attention please I win from
whole life ID generation 2 what's up
guys it's been a while I'm going to do
practice with Wawa for holo ID Cup
tomorrow let's freaking go
guys lima
lima lima tonj she's so smart she know
she's like she's like honorary Indonesia
member
cuz and that's like what matters what
pretty much it though are you like in
your uniform
this yeah this is the uniform they told
us to wear you're not wearing it oh well
I'm going to wear it tomorrow because
it's um because the real event is
tomorrow I'm going to wear it tomorrow
it looks like I'm going to go to school
in this I'm like a
student
okay so anak uh it's high school uniform
in Indonesia oh wow yeah
wow pants I'm wearing pants pants I
guess pants were not banned
[Music]
yet all right oh God I think everything
is too loud welcome to the B Bo
[Laughter]
[Music]
now me and will guide you guys
inside pleas follow us
hi we're in a study tour you know stud
study tour
let's go I have a
question yeah did did you all build this
on your
own yes that's [\h__\h] insane that's crazy
I thought you guys were going to hire
people just hysterically answer
yes yes wow and tears
so our Blood Sweat and
Tears oh
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what is
that why is it doing that it's security
system
security I have been
approved
nice
ber climb down and then we climb down
the berries Berry's got to
okay climb down sud
climb
wow wait one question to my chat um I
feel like my mouse moves like you know
too fast you know what I mean how do I
change D in
atics okay hi hi
hi please come
here I was inside and I was like oh
shoot how do I exit again then I did it
one more time welcome to
the
welcome we have uh five games in
total yes okay five games wow uh Lima Ki
Lima
Li wow
yeah the first one is actually called
treasure
hunt Tre
hun um because we want to keep it as a
surprise for now we're not going to do
it but let me explain the
[Music]
rules for
so basically we'll be hiding emeralds in
a bunch of chest and then you guys will
have to um look for it there's going to
be a lot of gimmicks going to be a lot
of platforming so you guys have to work
together to actually get the emerald
that's the Treasure Hunt game that's the
Treasure Hunt game but we're not going
to do it today okay but is it
easy it's easy you you just need to open
chest
okay is it time like is it time do we
have to be fast with it
yeah do we all do it at the same time
all all
teams so you can also hit like other
team members oh oh we can hit them okay
okay wait can we I don't remember I I'll
have to check with the staff again okay
you have
popsicles okay po oh it's the flags you
want it
yes
Y
[Music]
indon in indones
AA what why are you bleeding from one of
your
eyes why am I bleeding from one of my
eyes oh that's the Indonesian flag on
her I didn't see the white part
oh I'm bleeding
[Music]
okay but for now follow me first s
w wow wow so God who how do you wait I
want to can you ol can you tell me the
like history not history but like when
you guys were building this like who
made the plans the layout and what what
you built it right but did someone else
make the layout or did you guys make it
because you guys are insane oh some
somebody else made the layout we just
built H but that's crazy how long did it
take 2 months was it oh my God two three
months's go I think I saw you guys
building the floor here on
[Music]
stream bro crazy you goats absolute
goats Minecraft
[Laughter]
goats damn
so if you guys built it in case any
accidents happen I can sue you guys in
particular for yeah sure why not causing
it like if the stones from the ceiling
fall down on me and I I
die our building is safe really
really is there someone
[Music]
I sue you I sue you but so far all is
good no problem all is good in
Japanese letuce you this is the Simon
says um stage Simon
Says Simon Says
stage so uh to put it simply we'll be
doing Simon says but everything will be
in Indonesian wait you mean there's
stuff down there Simon says no no no
just this platform this Simon
sayon I'll be explaining a little
bit so
[Music]
for
yeah Engish please thank you yeah we'll
be doing Simon say and it will also be
kind of a memory game because we'll be
giving you guys instructions in
Indonesian by the way yeah
um and uh it'll be like cons uh
consecutive
it'll be consecutive orders in
Indonesian and everybody has to do it so
like it's not only the guest team but
the ID Girls also have to do it so it's
a memory game for them okay and uh if
you succeed you'll get emeralds which is
very important because you need to
collect as many emeralds in whole ID
cup okay it'll lead to a very big this
game we will practice
right yeah
okay
soda I almost forgot don't remember
anything yet yeah so these are the words
that you guys need to
remember
K Kanan Kanan
which is
right which means forward you go
forward which is the opposite backwards
you got to go
backwards and then L which means jump
jump jump jum jump lump part jump and
then numbers from one to
five
[Music]
tiger lima lima
lima and then so St
p p p p you hit you punch what I thought
that's
t t is
different is like Rand hit but tonj is
like punch you know but in the in the in
the text you sent me it says pukul
equals hit SL Punch Yeah so it's like a
more the more broad term oh punch can I
say ton punch punch
sure okay I don't have to use these as
long as it's Indonesian I don't have to
use these particular words or do I have
to oh you just need to memorize them and
that's it but can I say ton instead
of yeah
sure it's just that you know uh when
we're doing the game uh the instructions
will be saying P instead of okay you
know what me talking about this right
now already made me remember it I think
just discussing if I can change it
that's good that's good p is don't j p
is don't joke hey Ollie I'm just uh can
you hear my voice clearly
actually yeah it's beautiful making
Beautiful cuz I just like tweaked it a
little
bit
Crouch Monday Tuesday wday
[Music]
how can we remember all these words
until
tomorrow I told you
yesterday I had no time
true you're
right okay come come come
here which one is difficult for you all
of them except
ton everything well just the it's not
the singular words it's like the amount
of words is
difficult yeah we can just say k why you
speaking Japanese to
me you're so
[Laughter]
cute
oh yeah
she right yeah yeah why are we speaking
in three languages now I don't know it's
just the japanish thing yeah
okay how many are there I see only
one but why why is it that's so
long technically a red
[Laughter]
color so you don't have to remember yeah
so you don't have to remember wna cuz
wna is uh technically is redundant so
just remember
Mera yeah yeah easy righta if if they
were make you remember meta is there any
other colors
no
no maybe is it because of that red
block maybe okay and then there's lamp
power fro L
run
sh maybe maybe a red if if red you go to
the red stone yeah probably okay well
for today for today I'll just look at
the reference
sheet and uh I will you know just learn
how the game works today and then
tomorrow I will know the words for sure
but today I just look at the words I
think um if you already played the game
you will eventually like you know put uh
you know like a priority in your brain
like which words are more important than
others which one you have to
[Music]
honestly no because you always only said
t t don't to me but today I learned Lima
Ki Lima Ki you never learn not really I
don't think I don't think I knew what
you were
saying Li five okay and will be giving
instructions are we playing this with
all teams at the same
time oh there you
go whle
[Music]
hello
Squall
cute Hello
Squall cute where's your
[Music]
tail
it is that what goes on in
Indonesia behind the curtains eh we eat
squirrel stale in Indonesia for
breakfast and then sh grow back every
day oh
[Music]
no okay how do we how do we test the
game I'm not sure I think you guys can
watch uh your s first and you guys can
go next okay okay okay okay where
[Music]
should please listen
to okay example I will I will have I
will give you three stages got I know
stages of grief
St okay three stage so let's start from
the first
stage
St and after I set the command I will
say three 2 1 and then you can move
[Music]
okay okay let's start from the first
command stand on
her I can't stand
her
okay okay let's okay
start stage
one blocking her view
[Music]
L three two one
r l ah
L yeah jump one time yeah that's that's
first
stage wa can you see can you see well I
can really can you can see well enough
yeah yeah yeah I can okay good good
making sure you got a good
[Music]
view one
woo to
difficult so just three
times I don't know I'll Teach
[Music]
You 3 two one
oh my God you damaging private property
that's
[Music]
funny okay okay
it's your
[Music]
turn you guys can do it it's easy
practice is easy
we well
yeah sorry uh you stand where do we
stand in the beginning ah it's it's up
to you okay uh you just stand in the
middle okay I'll stand on red like right
here
okay I might not stand under red oh we
should stay on we should stand on red or
what no no no uh don't stand on red okay
anywhere but red anywhere but
R I
understand okay so are you guys ready
yeah please speak slowly
slowly okay slowly okay okay let's start
stage one um had up Canan three two uh
one uh uh uh I I trust you I trust
you yeah but well I'm looking it up
still so this is not amazing I'm just
looking at my
notes
practice sorry sorry and then after this
we go back to our initial position or
what yes please go back to your initial
position
okay okay so stage two
3 2
[Music]
okay w w w wow
wow I'm amazed at you wait for knowing
your own
language of
course okay so and now we return to our
initial position again yes yes okay okay
okay stage
three two
one wait no how do you throw how do you
throw
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
yay forgot how to
hi it'll be like this wait is it like uh
you go on until there's a mistake and
then some people if they're too good it
goes on for like 30 rounds or is there a
cut there will be
um there will be set
stages and the more you guys write get
it got it right the more uh emeralds you
guys will get yeah okay is there like a
limit though yeah there's about 10
stages I think 10
okay okay but you but you always say uh
each previous round you you repeat it so
I don't have to remember it really cuz
you say it I
guess well be 10 of the commands yeah
okay I guess that's but it's kind of
like you have
[Music]
to I I get yeah at the point of 10
stages it will be more difficult because
you say so many things and we have to do
it in the right order one goes first
and not a
language leave it to
me leave it to
[Music]
me
okay guys
[Music]
are I'll try my best
wrong wool this next is going to be the
wrong wool stage let's go wrong wool
let's go I read I read about this this
sounds difficult well I would hope you
read about it
way no I would hope that you read about
your own events
challenges yo I'm here to accompany you
I'm not te okay you don't need to know
everything yes just roughly just
rly sorry we're
late where no it's okay you can climb
from
here careful first accident
chotot no no no no no no
[Music]
don't don't sue
us I'll be explaining in Japanese first
okay
[Music]
okay for
explain it in English basically the team
consists of a wool cutter and a foreman
Forman will be in the Upper Floor which
is here this is the Upper Floor and then
there's going to be a lower floor and in
the lower
floor there will be a wool
cutter so basically it's like playing
Splatoon kind of the foreman needs to
color all of these uh White wool got to
replace them with like colored wools
while the wool cutter uh on the lower
floor they have to like cut the floor so
that the other team's foremen fall and
lose or so that they could help their
teammates to color more of the wools oh
because you see the foreman replaces the
Wool by hand but the wool cutter on the
lower floor they have like the shears oh
and this is all teams at the same time
or there's going to be about four teams
four teams at the same time so or maybe
three I think it's three teams oh okay
so six people six people okay so per
round there's going to be three people
three p three
paars okay okay wait now which one do
you want to be below or
above um I can um wait uh I don't mind I
can I can be below it's fine oh you want
to
sabotage you guys can switch and then
you guys
can okay I think I
[Music]
understand
for okay uh do you want to the W cutter
or do you want to be the
foran I can
be I'm up I can be
the they're going
to uh show the example example
okay so on like how to play you want to
go down first guess
downstair
oh how they going to cut it from down
there I guess you can reach can you
reach we're going to give an example Ru
is going to be the foreman and I'll be
the wool cutter so you guys know how it
looks like mhm okay yeah you guys can
Che from above or you two colored w just
in
case okay I'm I'm going up okay F1 why
F1 okay I am right
now uh the foremans will be using F1
later oh so that they don't actually no
MM cuz you can see the name yeah yeah
yeah okay
okay okaya are you ready I am
ready okay we're starting in five
Forman was the one on top or
[Music]
[Laughter]
bottom Ollie opens it up for you okay
but can also punch her own wall ah so if
Ollie is like busy um making holes to uh
drop someone down she can make her own
holes during that time yeah but like so
the people on top they have to be
careful so they don't fall
let me see
below so I think like the foreman just
makes holes and there's no way the
foreman can know who's under or up
because they're using
F1 so the one above has to be
careful uh wait who who's who's supposed
to press f one the bottom one or the top
one the Bott the bottom one the bottom
okay at the top one if the top one falls
down game over for them yep and they
don't uh their wols do not get counted
and they're eliminated and the the
bottom one if the top one falls down
that means the whole team is like out
right yeah so yep I can't cut anymore
okay so
uh my tip is that it's best to not fall
just so that you can get your walls
counted try not falling
[Music]
so the person at the bottom can also
make holes and undo your points
yeah but like if you're the upper person
can only do
[Music]
now I get
it yeah and if you want to cut the walls
like if the foran want to cut the Ws you
can cut the white ones but you can't cut
like the other things okay yeah well the
wool cutter they can literally cut any
wo they want okay and we get only one
color right because now it was two
colors was just showing how it'll be if
there's going to be like two teams ah
okay okay I don't know crunchy audio I
don't know would you guys try
yes okay so let's go down to get the
shear and world you sound normal to
me should we all do at the same time
Minecraft so I guess like my Minecraft
is like showing is making the audio CLE
so I'm going to try
to try to
[Music]
dis there she goes oh she's back okay
what about this one you sound normal to
me test test it's
back what's what exactly is crackling I
don't know somebody says there's like a
crackling sound but I can't hear it
either are you getting one
guide I sound robotic on her PV
personally cannot hear
anything do I sound like a robot to
you no okay
way has audio problems right now
[Music]
uhoh are you okay
okay yeah because if you're going to be
the world cutter you have to jump to cut
[Music]
them I'll do
both I'll do both yeah I I think I think
upper is easier I think I yeah you don't
have to think so
much head empty
okay
[Music]
okay I'm waiting for w I guess
okay blocks
blocks block
[Music]
blocks
uh how many blocks should we takeen and
for me which color cuz they took I think
green this one you can get it from here
uh you can get one stack one stack any
any color but green oh okay you need
more than one
[Music]
stack
okay of course it's orange
[Music]
Ki is left left Kanan is Right Mau is
forward Mund is backward L is
Jump Lima
to remember this until
tomorrow
[Music]
no kitty kitty
kitty
kitty kitty
[Laughter]
kitty mau mau
[Music]
mau
m m
[Music]
Mund
Canon kitty kitty
[Music]
sorry H thank you for waiting I'm not
fixing it but yeah yeah you know what
it's fine it's
fine
[Laughter]
okay if you need to mute it's okay
I ah
okay if I keep on doing that with s
Senpai I might remember the words
oh nice
[Music]
oh oh okay do you want to be the foreman
or do you want to be the wool
cutter I'll be the I'll be the top for
now I can try to be I don't know I
already have the blocks what do you want
to do I I'll do top and then later
bottom okay I'll do bottom then okay
okay you see how it is
chat you see how it is I suggest you
guys to take about two uh what's it
called shears just in case one
breaks and if you guys hear uh I would
suggest you guys to like hold the shears
in uh both
hands just so that if it breaks if you
guys hear it breaking you can huh
on both
hands jungle jungle jle woman please
press F1 yeah a dam
okay okay we're going to
start
[Music]
y okay starting in five four three 2
one wa which one is you sent me a
[Music]
away
from can I just
like fill these
[Music]
up I already ran
out okay okay I'm close to you
my controls
are someone's getting rid of my no no no
no no no no no no no no she wants to
kill me
down where
[Music]
no well but I think it was pretty even
in terms of
colors pel the colors do not count so
the winner is
Pabi
yipp
wow sorry guys uh I forgot to press F1
but I will make sure should not do that
in Home bun sorry I'm in the middle of
troubleshooting as well so tough this
will be even more chaotic when there's
free teams at the same
time
[Music]
yeah oh also I don't know how to
translate this but basically if there's
a stacked wall uh there will be a staff
that will clearing them out so you guys
don't need to waste your time you mean
if they're accidentally placed like on
top like this yeah oh okay
[Music]
nice okay nice what a
service yeah so would you guys like to
switch now yeah
[Music]
switch I'll be bad at it okay I'll bring
back my
[Music]
orange get the greens off
because WWA was nearby anyways so it
wasn't like I was specifically targeting
anybody so give her the Ws please I
already put them
back R you can take the walls
here nice translation thank you
yeah
[Music]
just I'll take is there setting to just
turn off the names instead without doing
F1 I think there is
right cuz that's a point
[Music]
not
really okay so for the foreman follow me
upstairs am I for no no
okay foran is up happies happies for
[Music]
theform
byee you have two stacks
take two shars in case one breaks oh
okay got to listen to the sound cuz I
won't even notice I
think you have two
shears yeah yeah two
shears no one two ah please uh what
What's it called um just in case it
break for the up one up
people the upper people don't need one
so two Shear on guy please like put uh
two shears on both
hands two Shar catching you in 2K okay
okay like this the two shares yeah I
don'ts it has is work again like left
left left right just so
that how do I use the other one
breaks so uh when it breaks you'll hear
a sound right yeah hopefully so if it
breaks you can just switch it out with
s Okay so
okay
okay I feel like when everybody's like
screaming during the match maybe I won't
hear the sound of the shears
breaking oh well I think you'll notice
if you start gu if you you know if it's
slower mhm oh r f f yeah if want please
press F1 okay okay
are the foran ready
[Music]
for okay we'll start in five 4 three 2
1 wait what color are you I'm I'm like
blue my okay oh don't
worry this confusing
me be careful
careful wait I'll go sabotage a little
bit well the colors look so
similar
sorry the too similar in this
lightning they look too similar I don't
know if I'm really getting rid of green
or
[Music]
blue I wasn't even doing that
intentionally uh I have one uh
suggestion although I think it depends
on the monitor on on one of my monitors
the colors look pretty much the same on
the other monitor it looks Sim uh very
different but like maybe we can light up
the space somewhere I don't know or or
we should like I don't know worn
contestant you know like just just use
the
redock yeah maybe we add some more
contrasting blocks yeah like maybe we
can avoid having green and blue together
in one match I don't know but if I look
at my my other monitor they look very
different actually sometimes it's it do
be like that like it's much brighter on
my left monitor on my right monitor is
so
dark I don't know what's the real one
though what's closer to the
[Music]
reality prepare it okay thank you but so
far how is
it
fun do you guys want to do it again or
move on understand I understand too yeah
okay no didn't break
okay I got confused of like moving
forward and backwards
so do you want to be
bottom do we only do one round in the
home
bomb hey the is there only one round
wait let me
check yeah it's definitely monitor but I
don't know which one's more accurate out
of my two
monitors think the left one is brighter
and but less saturated you don't have to
worry about it and the right one is
darker and more
saturated uh yeah honestly even way is
fine for me though okay so there's going
to be about three rounds okay well
there's no problem so um but each pair
will play um at the maximum two
rounds against each other in the
finals yeah so like kind of tournament
style there's
preliminaries and then the last round is
like finals between the two winning
teams I wonder if the others are
practicing this game a lot or if they
also just did it one time and then call
it a
day at the same time I think there's
really not much point to practicing too
much just the same thing plus love M I
would I think during home buun although
this is already Strate strategy talk but
like I'll try to find your color and
then stay close to you but sometimes
maybe I'll go away and sabotage but I
can tell you that
right um yeah but then the other team
will find out as well yeah that's
fine okay well we find I can see your
name at the bottom anyways basically if
there's a hole near me I'll feel it all
right feel the hole Misty feel the hole
Misty if there's a hole there's a way
yes there's a hole there's a way missy
real oh oh okay
okay okay wait I'm sorry there has been
a misunderstanding at the end
misunderstanding
corner so it turns out there will be
three rounds and everybody there will be
six pairs against each other for those
three rounds six pairs at the same time
what the H yeah to be a lot more chaotic
than we thought six pairs at the same
time I feel like people will fall down
immediately I think it's just like kind
of
yeah it's pretty luck based there's
three rounds
[Music]
so only
only when come
here when when for example if somebody
falls down first uh versus somebody who
falls down third do the do the third
ones the the ones who fell down third
get more emeralds even know
um it's a
threeway like it would matter probably
right uh who who fell down first they
get less emeralds I wonder yeah you're
typing I hear you
typing yeah and then I guess so if
somebody Falls they have to immediately
announce like for example
pavoni yeah yeah it becomes easier for
the organizer yeah I think with so much
going on I wouldn't if I was at the top
I wouldn't even notice h no if I was at
the bottom I might not even notice when
you fall down immediately and I might
still be digging holes
ah only the last one standing gets the
emerald three rounds and then okay MH so
only three pairs out of six pairs can
even get points yeah so it's kind always
only the last man standing gets points
so if even if you finish second you
don't get
anything if we lose it's going to be
just can we try one more round where all
of you including Ollie and Riso are
participating to like recreate the chaos
a little bit more we can yeah we can
yeah um earlier sorry Ollie because um I
earlier I said uh just the colors that
are contrasting to each other but then
if there's going to be three going on at
at the same time right cuz it's like is
it six teams or two teams or yeah so we
need six colors that means there's no
way there's going to be it's okay
there's definitely going to be weird the
contrast colors next to each other it's
okay I just have to look at my other
monitor okay okay then okay I was I just
wanted to clear it up it's just cuz it's
darker down here when I was at the top
it wasn't although we use different
colors at the top but I think it's
darker down here uh so maybe lighting
will help more lighting down here a
little bit on honestly yeah I think uh
but it's hard because like because then
you guys won't be able to uh yeah you
guys won't be able to it's okay I I will
look at my other monitor but we should
tell the other members if they have the
same problem that they should brighten
their screens or something cuz yeah okay
okay understood thank you well uh that's
what practice is for yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
okay wa you want to be top of bottom
this time uh I can be top I'll try okay
I'll try with bottom of bad at putting
the boxes but we'll see okay yeah I need
to practice being at the bottom okay um
cuz like I feel like walking was so
confusing for
me okay take a picture if I just pick
dark blue and I'll put this it's okay
I'll put my game on the other
screen I'm going to be building
blocks chat also move other screen
switch
Oro doing a switch Oro
okay
okay uh do you want or the wo cutter I
want to be the for man what are these
digo sounds does somebody have a digo in
their
home a
dig what's
what's uh it's like an an instrument
that's really long and it makes a d d
oh the it's the the horn thing right
yeah kind it's not really it doesn't
look like a horn it's just a long tube
yeah wa what is that you I hear it yeah
who is it did you
do who's making no sounds no not
[Music]
me is it you ollie say something hello
say hello h
well well we'll we'll figure out later
for now let's try practicing again
vibrating I yeah it could be a vibrating
[Music]
sound everybody position Dido you
okay did you
[Music]
weo oh it's me versus Oli and eii down
here
[Music]
do you guys
have didn't go under their call for
Aid maybe I have one I think that's ju
yeah very very very very ju this is
insane going to guess this is a maze
maybe not start it wait let me get the
timer ready it's going to be 1 minute
um wa what's your color wa wa dark blue
dark blue dark blue dark blue okay so
starting in five four three two
one oh I found you I sorry I removed
yours what are you
doing sh
[Music]
I didn't even
noce I didn't even noce did
was I think I made I made the hole that
you fell
through I think it's very
honestly think too much about this
game I didn't no
[Music]
this what what's going on
no I I punched T Senpai to the ground no
that's no ton no t wait is that allowed
I'm not sure that it's I wasn't even
jumping what do you
mean I to do
I I I think that's my phone what a
vibrator my phone
I have I I never have my phone on
vibrate I always have it completely
muted and no
vibration I was afraid that I would lose
it I never notice when somebody messages
me
never but I'm always on my phone
[Music]
so you heard
it my phone your
phone
is the squirel it was the squirrel all
[Music]
along wa do you want
to you want to go up
or do you guys want to do it again yeah
one more time one more myars my shears
my shears okay you want more
shears oh there you go it's okay K's
handing me hers okay I'll take I'll take
orange only only you can go up orange wa
orange I might punch people
again okay is there more orange oh well
it probably be fast
anyway okay time
to create some
[Laughter]
[Music]
chos
yeah wa go go go further away
we're starting in five 4 three hard to
tell 2
[Music]
1 I don't know
where who is this who is
this sorry I'll get rid of it yes get it
get it get it get it get
you guys have 35
[Music]
seconds no no more orange paint the
world Orange
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
don't talk don't talk okay it's very
orange we like it we like the
[Music]
[Applause]
orange because you guys are still alive
we're going to count the Y
wow I think orange wins what happened
with
purple I at them
nice OHA was at work wait don't don't
don't break them yet
bl's oh you're counting the orange one
tail ah
okay
sabotage orang I think
way yeah you also prefer putting down
the blocks yeah cuz like I realized my
strategy now what's the
[Music]
best like I feel like in uh in previous
rounds I was trying to find wherever way
it was but this one just didn't try to
even find her I just tried to find any
hole and fill up any hole Yeah just
focusing on
that be
[Music]
fast okay so I'm
top I will stay
top just don't die
easy but if there's going to be six
people at the same time be crazy but I
feel like I was pretty good at dodging
the holes that came close to me so if
it's if it's like six people that means
like three three
right or is it
six6 six teams yeah I guess wait three
on top it's going to be six pairs so
it's six pairs I know six on top six on
top and six on bottom oh my God o 12
people care the double of what we just
had yeah so I mean we just just like um
improvise adapt overcome okay or you
know a tip would be you got one of the
wool Cutters they could just cut like
the edges and the other ones can just
fill it from the insid or
something manage yeah wool
manage so funny put this here okay uh
what's the next game we should go to the
next game I think waya doesn't have too
much time so
[Music]
yeah let's go since we don't have many
time we'll go to the um last game
first
okay game yeah wait before that I need
you guys to put your items in one of
these oh
no is it a death match ooh elytra
69 never right
pickaxes I see this this just
construction
stuff my
bread my bread
anything but Goan oh but will we all
have the same Gohan because some
different gohans are more strong than
others
[Music]
chicken I have bread what does she
want I have steak a
[Music]
potato love
potato butter and salt or sour cream
oven potato
[Music]
Queen oh this is going to be a little
bit tough
yeah we'll be using the group
VCC let me you
[Music]
I read the tutorial how to do
it but don't I somebody makes a group
and I just join it
[Music]
right
gr do you want to make it Winer
[Music]
itou group
typeal
isolated that
arear shitty
password uh
isolated wow let this let this be a
lesson to you for the for your future
passwords to not get hacked just
for1 1111 this is
[Laughter]
one okay W I'm going to make pavi group
and then you immediately join yeah but
the thing is after after we join the
group we can't hear the people outside
that's the problem okay no problem
please make the password
1111 okay okay okay okay
okay I'm super
hacker hacking into pavi
gate I'm
here all right
take
yes yes no no
[Music]
no
g g i don't know what that means but g
g i wonder how oh ah now please what do
you mean now please leave VC
okay this was just practice that we can
make it
okay
okay you guys already know how to use
the group V only only one question um
this place is really big uh toilet
Kim toilet you can you can you can do it
uh behind the bushes here have so many
bushes okay
and if you want to no no no before you
do your business you have to say permiss
permiss
don't you don't want to make the
Mad
end
[Music]
okay hi for
so yeah for the English viewers
basically in May's fight there's going
to be a fighter and a navigator the
Navigator will sit on the top and guide
the fighter throughout the the main
yeah so they have to help the fighter
defeat the opposing opponents as well
and the team whose fighter is standing
last advances to the final round okay so
it's just like
fighting it's fing and then there's a
navigator that will help but Navigator
you say they on top H where on top oh so
we have all of these
temples and if you go inside
you can go to the top the stairs I
missed
you here here here here this is the
stairs it's pretty Hardbody can follow
me maybe we can put up a sign here's the
stairs oh dear yeah okay but it's hard
to see what's like far away oh no don't
worry you can see the names uh-huh do I
only care for like this area that's in
front of me the red area
basically if I'm here
am I one more time please am I
navigating through the whole maze or
just this red area the whole meze you
can just say Oh Renee uh there's a
fighter if you go to the left so go
there or something like that and
Navigators they'll be handed bows and
arrows so that they can help the
fighters win oh we can shoot the enemies
too yeah oh you can even shoot the other
Navigators too oh oh oh what scary what
the other Navigators you B
so I guess over
there let me explain to the other team
okay yeah okay ooh wa what do you think
you'll be better at being down there or
up here I I'm not sure honestly because
even if I'm up there like what's what's
the
goal uh like helping the ones down there
and like killing the other like people
see like for the ones down there like
they have navigate I'm just like do they
need to go to the center or yeah that's
I want to know that too yeah no but she
did say that the last one standing wins
so maybe not necessarily going to the
center just
surviving but honestly we can't really
um go that far because then you wouldn't
be able to see anything yeah that's what
I was thinking like a you should like
sort of stay yeah well but then they
know that they'll maybe see oh they're
always in their own territory so they
just go to our territory to fight
us that's what I'm thinking you know
like if you there's there's only so much
but it's also hard for them to see yeah
for the others not just for us but I'm
just thinking like at some point the
Navigator wouldn't be able to do
anything
mhm no armor Weapon by what
Ma I also I only can tell there's
another place there
but this is like probably I see one
there but it's too far really and I
don't know where are the others like MAA
said no armor weapon bu so we buy the
weapons from the emeralds we have
gathered or something that's why it's
the last game o but if you didn't do so
well then you're not only going to get
shitty
weapons I know guys but the one good
thing is that the sniper like for bow
and arrow is always the same like
there's no better weapon it's just going
to be bow and arrow maybe if the if your
person down there doesn't have like such
a good weapon you can rely on the
Navigator a bit
more pay win it's pay
win oh my
God I'm just I'm just the messenger okay
and I guess this is also everybody at
the same
time do you think it's everybody the
same time I'm sure it's everybody at the
same time considering how big the maze
is yeah is there a platform there hello
I'm back what's
up
weap thank you I'll I'll stay up here
for now how about
that wa yeah sure okay oh also don't
forget to touch the bed in case one of
you guys die one of you guys die mhm
yeah okay oh oh
oh no you can just touch it here
rain there's a bed over here
too oh
here okay if only I can only take down
the basically the emeralds that you guys
collect throughout all of the mini game
so you guys will use it oops uh for this
one mini game
mhm yeah hia guys will use the emeralds
to buy weapons hey hey MAA hey
Ma
[Music]
hey please please give me hey hey
Ma are ready we I'm ready yeah I guess
what if in the off chance that you know
Navigator and person down there does at
the same time wouldn't the other person
get kicked out of the bed
huh they if we touch the same bed and we
die at the same time and they're like
very low chance should we have should we
prepare like two beds
instead it's okay like even if you guys
yeah and and one more question just
respawn one more question um the goal is
to just survive there's nothing like in
the middle that you have to touch or
something right yeah you just need to
fight
okay let's go
winner VCS ah oh
okay wec groups let's
make she's going to be my what do you
call it again in in the coliseums
hi wner hi so Gladiator yeah you're my
Gladiator
way okay can I is it am I allowed to
like stand here I wonder be
dangerous oh
wait oh you have to eat way I I I ate
before
I no I can't climb up I'm stuck or
whatever well it's too late way you
either die or you live down there okay I
will do my
best maybe first is that oh I to shoot
fighter stand by below okay I need
Minecraft fighting tips
guys um instead of like mashing mashing
mashing mashing mashing buttons I think
hold right for yeah just loaded back up
yeah what weapon did you get wooden
sword there's only wooden swords
okay 5 4 3 2 is that s s by oh
God go he where do I
go no I can't see I can't see I have to
change my
settings wait have to change the
settings H uh uh uh um
uh render
distance render distance yeah I can't
see so by when she steps
back yeah I know because
um computer with sticky keys what is
this what is that for how you doing down
there way have you seen anyone yet
no oh should should we go F1 or what
because I see Nam I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry she's not even fighting back oh no
she
is my die Senai die say bye I'm lost I
don't
know yo uh is that you I wonder are you
running towards a corn a you on the blue
okay
[Music]
more minutes I don't see anything go go
go go go go go go go go oh I'm at Sho
again shoot again shoot again she's
hiding oh oh wait that is that you
you're you're still on what color I'm at
dark blue right now
okay and not anymore I'm at the
center I almost got it a oh
almost who's that who's that oh oh no I
hear it's so hard to
hit I'm at purple right
now oh there there's some people
fighting in in pink that's you that's me
oh God I don't know which one is you
it's I literally can't tell which one's
you you died no no no no no don't
die I killed Yi yes I I got so many hits
on
her oh you did it wait Pap she win he yo
what oh [\h__\h] there's only two oh I guess
so I forgot to navigate I don't know
what to navigate like I'm busy like
taking down the
enemies I think that was fine though
like you just you know we got to we got
to be
independent oh I yeah I guess so you can
have yeah we we should be independent
both people fight yeah you just got to
look for some enemies to fight I mean I
can kind of tell you like oh there's
someone in pink but that like do you
even know where pink is you know yeah oh
we got to go to the group chat I can see
like name tags that's why I was asking
should we
be oh I see we can ask that yeah yeah
because um I saw like a name tag back
there but it's like I don't know but
like for real I can't even protect you I
wasn't sure like which one was Yi and
which one was you because you both have
like white hair in game what Miss
something yeah all right okay let's go
back honestly I think it's better to
focus I don't know how to go back Andy
you you press V and then leave group
like uh v v and then two it's like I
want to go up
oh ask
Ollie oh hello hello
[Music]
she couldn't see me
maybe if I up
my and that's how you play
[Music]
okay
okay I I have one more question
actually um is there
like okay
[Music]
oh so for the people down
do we die at some point cuz I I didn't
get hit so I don't
know
naor okay
[Music]
oh we can continue even if we die okay
oh
[Music]
ah fighter dies and lose okay uh okay
okay yes one more
question
uh so I saw s senpai's like Tower over
there but besides that I I can't really
tell like is the the thing on my right
side uh the big house is it also a
temple cuz cuz it's kind of in the way
and like merging with the other
area is that is that also like where a
team would be or how how's is that do
you know what I
mean
Ollie wait sorry uh I'm uh communicating
with the uh the staff oh what was the
question uh like where I stand if I look
to my right there's this like big house
that's like merging with another enemy
area but like is that where another team
would be cuz it looks different from the
tower where I am and it kind of like is
in the way oh it's it's uh it's on how
do I say it um there's four Towers just
like yours on each side of the maze four
uhhuh yeah so not everybody will be
competing at the same time
either if it's four Towers yeah there's
it's going to be like uh 3 three I think
mhm
I think I I'll have to ask again also it
turns out I I there's another
miscommunication on my part another Mis
understanding it turns out uh once the
Navigator dies then the game is also
over
okay
yeah if you die once
[Laughter]
[Music]
so and uh this will be this will
actually be like tournament sty so 3
three and then one one three three and
one
one yeah uh okay there's three rounds
one is three and then one is three and
then the last one are the finalist fin
by one um is there you say there's four
Towers I guess on each side in the
middle like my view you to the right
tower from my side is blocked by the is
it the wool game no it's yeah it's the
wool game the wool game is blocking my
view completely from that side yeah well
um every side is also having some of
their sides blocked so it's it's fine
okay okay it's okay we pray destroy the
building oh okay maybe can switch
[Music]
now wait wait wait I'm going to put my
items back in I thought yeah okay I'll
deal with
it I
thought more sides that can't shoot you
that's true they can't shoot me
either let's go back to group VC okay
[Music]
res
res sounds like a
pasta thank you for the raid by the way
yippe okay wait hi uh I should I uh try
the bottom you want to try top okay um I
I kind of suck at bow and arrow if I
gota be H okay I think I'm pretty decent
at it I got a lot of hits on S Senai
okay so let's um okay we got our then
you stay
bottom yeah sure okay just like how in
the wool game I'm also top and you
bottom yeah sure wow okay about but
actually I'm I know it's it's okay I
guess I have enough arrows
probably so now the other 3x3 is so
scary because like there's it's there's
a possible scenario that two two teams
are going to gang up on one yeah
unintentionally
yeah it's all right it is what it is I I
can only really reach with my bats the
the pink side from here realistically so
I can help trying to get the Navigator
down there and maybe also the whoever's
running in there I think it's still eoi
but the others Le I don't think I can
reach them from here okay so pink uh so
ideally where do you want me to be try
to go for pink first for sure I can try
to help you there okay M and then after
that maybe let them come to youi should
try to come to you in red because there
I can shoot them in red okay yeah we we
we bring them over we bait them I don't
know if that's smart but I think it's
this can support you it's so scary
though because what if like I fight and
then the other team third
parties yeah feel like I'm super tired
then you run away it's all right it's
all right but what if there's a
stalemate at the end and they like
there's only two teams left and they
stay on their side we stay on our
side nobody goes to the other side oh
end maybe they'll come up with
it end what the hell there's an end yeah
all right let's see if s Senai will try
to oh I can't see I can't see can't see
she's too far what the hell why can I
not render that
distance she's she's she's better
now she's better now are you in yellow
oh yeah
oh I can't see [\h__\h] I don't know where
the exited it is a what if I
accidentally look at the Enderman right
now oh no oh no that
sucks open what the hell
man Yi is still in pink Yi is getting
closer to you H wait waser is in red
waser
in
oh oh
oh damn it come on that squirrel that
squirrel
wiu is in the middle wiu is running in
the middle you're there too I think
right yeah take her down take her down
don't duck don't duck BR wearing armor
there's no way I
win oh
hi
ah they just me in the middle I think I
die don't die I don't know which that's
not you for wait someone's wearing
diamond armor though is that uh yeah
it's Ru like cheating
cheating wellit I guess we're out I was
like I immediately realized R was
wearing armor there's no way I win uh
but anyways that's what happens just I
think going to the middle is very
bad yeah yeah don't get baited there
straight up get third parted yeah maybe
better just stay away but anyways it's
just a simulation it's whatever
yeah well now it was so much harder to
get sort of
simple but anyway it's fine just just
testing I wish I could see
better the UI didn't make the names
bigger
either but renesent needs to be like an
accessibility like setting or something
no it doesn't make it bigger you can
make the UI bigger but it doesn't make
the names bigger I tested
it but I should yeah render a bit more
distance like this but um you see what
just happened if I go to middle I get
third parted
the yellow part is so open so yeah but
like they're not they could also you
could for like uh go with you know the
other team against someone else too like
it could go both ways yes but uh that's
only after I like I hear somebody
fighting mhm
basically well whatever like your
instincts tell you is I think
fun oh they're still
fighting they're fighting still
yeah wiu was in red area and I was
really trying to hit her that was the a
good opportunity I think she was
probably looking for
waya maybe oh my God there's an end oh
we wins yeah so that's like that the
squel the squ takes revenge for the her
stolen um tail St stolen tail even
though I was the one who sled
it good
job
oh did you just hit MAA no no what
happened she
fell
mysteriously I
see okay I guess we go back probably
yeah I'm just
oh Moy mhy hey hey
hey hello there
hey hey hey
hey n the
freck L give
me no I'm poor please give me money in
my she doesn't even feel like doing it
anymore no no no very much so
oh you don't you don't feel like talking
to me anymore CU I'm so poor and no uh K
is not with us anymore I am P
Senai please give me
[Music]
emeralds uh what would you say uh hi
what would you say
question
arises let's go
[Music]
I have
question I have
[Music]
question I don't know
[Laughter]
no that would destroy
everything I would
[Laughter]
cry foral
[Music]
that would have been good yeah
if I die in the game I die in real life
can you still use B to fight the other
na no no okay no you can only support
[Music]
mentally so um okay
all right you lose the
perms I think we can move on to the last
one does everybody still have
time I told you I told you that's what I
was saying it was 25 minutes ago earlier
no I'm looking at the time for you
because I know this will take
longer uh what else do we still have Oli
uh just uh the build and guess so
basically you build and then you guess
what the other is building oh it's
easy
no don't joke don't joke don't joke
don't joke
yeah if uh Ry needs to leave um no I
think um just just continue and then
I'll tag along for as long as I could
don't mind me okay then I'll I'll pick
you guys up and then we can do the build
and guess build and guess is that the
last game or is there two
more there's actually one game we have
in practice which is the treasure hunt
but it's not done yet okay okay no
problem um
your your gen mate MAA had a terrible
accident I don't know how she fell down
there but her leg is broken and and I I
think you need to help her she she she
can she can recover it was definitely
not me though she's a strong person
strong independent woman
[Music]
the the where we were oh wait I might
die I might die I might
die
ol see see so much for being a sec
securely built
building accident well you know I can't
sue myself
yeah well if the employees who built it
die I guess that's just yeah
where do I put the weapons lady eat your
vegetables eat your
[Music]
greens see there
is somebody peed in the bushes that's
why oh my God
can can proper safety precautions be
taken tomorrow that Endermen are not
running around can we can we uh GA in
where we're supposed to yeah let's go
let's go I don't know where it is W can
you guide us
I'll
okay how do you throw it again what
ah we could turn on peaceful mode but
this is on the
main I guess it would be
fine
okay okay okay let's go a little bit
over here to a bit more open space to
the open
[Music]
space yeah they do what they want it's
okay it's a natural
[Music]
obstacle oh so like if you you try to
build and it look if it looks like an
apple like you know try to make it look
like an apple
[Music]
okay so just take any W any is okay
uh wait is just it's just one of us
building
yeah and Li color Okay wa you're a
better artist than me you you you do
it okay okay
yes I'm going to try to make she'll do
it with flying colors AKA yellow and
[Music]
orange
okay wa where are you I'm here I'm next
to you are
we okay how about here Pavo she stands
here okay we have an intruder can stand
there
okay okay I'll be giving the theme now
and Indonesian since the the one
buildings are
[Music]
ID I hate
yes okay
okay
me I just try
to do I just shout it
out do I just
shout okay um
[Music]
tree
heart don't
know does this one mean anything this
[Music]
one
snail
uh GP
does this not look like it see the
letter
c the Le
SE really uh cheese I don't know how to
make it even more I
don't I think I think rain is doing a
good job good job right it's not my
fault doing a really good
job do a good job what is
[Music]
it's only because I read it from the
chat
[Music]
okay so something like
that I
take
uh please uh mute
andely I'm going to leave
[Music]
def is okay
though okay why they mute themselves how
do you know what they're saying I'm
going to give you
guys okay okay so so
so okay key okay
[Music]
okay that's the first
thing
[Music]
yeah I starting in
what excuse me she built nothing so
far you can spell okay okay we'll
[Laughter]
[Music]
if something like that
if you're lucky on the color it
will influence your brain to go to
certain
words but
that's you can't do it thead
so but like
literally I feel like the color was
influencing me when I was
guessing I was talking to ch
ch yellow one was okay
I was like I was just like I I know that
the the Raina was saying like yellow
does matter but at the point when I
didn't know yet that yellow mattered I
was like what could this be like the
color is making me think of cheese I can
only think of cheese and cheese and more
cheese but I have to think of other
things I need to ignore the color and
open my my Consciousness my Giga brain
to other things it's difficult but I
think that the green may have like
positively influenced
the the font of
trees yeah that's just really like you
got to get lucky on the word and the
color you chose beforehand I
guess but I just need to also stop
thinking about the color then if I'm the
one guessing you was difficult
[Music]
difficult
[Laughter]
for so
[Music]
soothing yeah nice
for
[Music]
[Laughter]
spee
for
firefighter
firefighter what are you discussing
about
kathyy tathy
[Laughter]
wait why are you Anya now I hatea you
know that oh sorry we shouldn't be
talking at all
even hello I am back I was so long
why maybe way secretly envies Ana and
that's how she expresses her Envy I know
this is like my you know it's kind of
like a PR math to
oh my
God they
[Music]
cute wait I didn't know your your was so
good
[Music]
okay but if you guys want to practice
again we can give you guys prompts
[Music]
[Laughter]
what are some what are some Anya words I
can say to make myself sound more like
Ana just Japanese anything Japanese just
Japanese any Japanese would be fine but
no no no but like her her Japanese like
everybody when they speak Japanese they
have like an accent like I have to I
have to study that I think you have to
sound very like like angry I think she's
like often yeah she goes
like
okay like angry I'm going okay I'm going
to Def hi hi
us
[Music]
hi oh okay
oh yeah sure totally easy so
easy by the way is it like uh decided if
we have to build like upwards or can we
also like build like you know on the
floor you know what I mean you can build
on the floor it's free
yeah come back way come back way
she lost okay ah
okay wait I'll build on the floor it's
allowed so I'll build on the
floor really
yeah build on
the build the
maze Ma question mark duck bird what the
[\h__\h] are you building
bro you that doesn't look like a
flower okay mine doesn't look like it
wait I maybe leave it to
you building building on the floor I
guess
so yeah yeah
okay okay I
mute I leave it to way I think I'm not
good at this like I also take too much
time building I think waya is like
faster at building um I'm not
necessarily good at guessing even
though we'll try we'll try iosa is just
they have too much of a uh you know
connection
hi sorry sorry I pressed wrong okay oh
orange
[Music]
chees no no no you're better than
me just take your time or don't take
your time
but
orange chicken
chicken
bird
no can look at what they're buing to a
[Music]
that's very good
good um a horse uh
um you're doing good too
[Music]
[Applause]
ah wait it but I see it now you're like
building it three dimensionally upwards
okay I thought you would do
yeah it's fine it's fine to build on the
floor or no it's just hard to
tell banana
didn't you already get it discuss
beforehand our
team I build on FL now even whatever you
think like fits the situation I think
you can adjust
[Music]
I thought it was a
trident good as ooshi
[Laughter]
[Music]
Mark I leave it to you
gu I don't have any tall space
maybe can can we bring our own scolding
and
build yeah here uh here's some scaff oh
oh you have your own
okay what are we
doing we'll be doing it again oh again
okay ID team building right you're
building again right Ry this yeah wait
it
build I mean I mean if you don't want to
do it then oh no no no no it's fine it's
fine but by the way they're not allowed
to pick colors after they know right
they know they pick the colors first
right the colors first okay okay pick a
versatile
color Okay
mute I think she told her in Indonesian
I don't know
okay okay don't spoil it Chad okay don't
spoil it I look too
much ready ready
this oh she's building on the floor
okay
M uh-huh very different building style
so
far
uh spoon
spoon no
[Music]
really I was thinking
my first
one s
[Laughter]
s ah magnifying glass yeah it could be
magnifying glass
I'm okay yeah me too good job good job
job oh but the heads up the rules may
change for the
head up okay maybe rule change but
probably only
slightly
[Music]
okay
nice thank you so much for you
know thank you for practicing thank you
thank you good you guys must have so
much on your plate but good luck guys I
support you see you
tomorrow
[Music]
tomorrow where's my stuff how do you get
out of here can we uh can somebody ENT
us to the outside and we s there
okay make a picture and
this practice sh practice sh and uh the
picture using neck neck
day okay
okay uh where is
outside wait I think I found the path
maybe here maybe
[Music]
it should be somewhere
here I think I'm almost there I'm she's
in the wall I'm in the first
game I'll get you I'll get
you I'm at the first game
first oh Simon says yeah Simon
says I see it I see it I see it hello
hello Okay
Okay
meet okay hello I don't know which exit
is
which let me out let me out let me out
let me out
wow you guys put
a lot of work into this damn you didn't
have
to do all this outside
stuff I made it to the
outside uh I am in the outside where
should I go oh you can climb climb up
again
[Music]
okay over
here looks
good okay
[Music]
okay
cheese what about what about Ollie and
wiu com com
[Music]
wow
cheese
C
[Music]
okay
scaffolding sorry let me let me take a
picture of you guys too oh no
okay nice you thank
you thank
you Pabi
[Music]
Pabi Pabi will win number
one I I doubt it but I have to say it
anyway sometimes you're going to be your
own hype man you know yeah
[Music]
thank you guys thank
you see you tomorrow see you
tomorrow but I'm staying a little bit
getting my stuff actually I guess ah I
guess it doesn't matter because ah wait
wait wait wait wait is Ollie already
gone
ah
maybe she can even keep it
or
h
ah okay thanks I have caps lock
forever okay okay okay yay so that was
the
practice for this oh my God what what's
what's what why do they put like this
extra crazy amount of work into this
this is
insane like especially cuz it's all
happening inside the outside doesn't
need to look this
crazy now one thing I was wondering like
they built it and I saw them building it
but I didn't it didn't look like they
were using creative mode so all these
blocks did
they did they also gather all these
blocks or did they get them from
creative mode and then
wait wait wait
zombie they might they actually [\h__\h]
mind
it holy
[\h__\h] H oh it's because it's based on the
LL Temple ah okay then that makes sense
that they would um try to recreate the
looks of
that ah
amazing yeah it was definitely a good
excuse for them to play Minecraft for a
long
time yeah it's a long running project
for sure is this like a little Temple
here like a Minecraft
Temple they have so many of these like
beams I'm trying to find the side of the
beds again I'm on the wrong side an
abandoned project from 2020 oh really
they started it before and then stopped
oh or maybe they started building the
Temple without in mind that they would
do something inside of it like this kind
of game maybe that wasn't even the plan
first who
knows okay I sleep in
here but I guess I'll log out happy
birthday reer wa you're like more rained
than wayed cuz you're
Rainier I guess I'll L out
okay I have um a massage
later and I
have um still things to record I'm
recording many many
things yeah uh but tomorrow uh same time
plus half an hour I think is the
starting time for
tomorrow already on today but before I
got
ah I let's talk about I was on Thea's 3D
showcase I hope you guys watch it if you
didn't then watch the VA
afterwards
right yeah Nissa
showcase her singing was so beautiful so
gorgeous yeah the niku Jaga was actually
so freaking good and I was legit hungry
so like I I wanted to really
eat everything but they were kind of
rushing us with a
timer timer on the screen and and like
yeah I mean you could tell there were
Cuts in between so um we had to like
stop eating and then go to do the next
thing and all that uh yeah but I yeah
you heard the you heard I said abdom
mination see I even said it wrong I I
was
domination the chicken was all right but
the nikua was really good I really love
the H me simple flavor of nikua like
it's a simple it's a really simple
common dish in
Japan but it's just so
[Music]
yummy Timmy was just all right yeah by
the way like Nissa came up with that
like it wasn't my idea to involve kfp or
Jimmy or anything like that I didn't
even know like that we were going to
cook and
stuff uh until until
then I didn't know
anything yeah Nar Isa she's so
cute but actually I I just want to say
like did you notice I look kind of funny
there was um cuz I noticed um already at
the time my something was wrong with my
head and neck
and I can't even describe it but
something was wrong with it and I was
like what the hell is this can you guys
fix it and they couldn't fix it on time
like they were trying a little bit to
fix it but they couldn't so the
dancing and the the cooking throughout
the whole thing maybe you notice like my
I don't know it feels like my head is
like sticking out more and like it's
just weird I don't know how to describe
it but something was wrong with it
something was wrong with it I don't know
I don't know you can also tell I think
from the last post uh the last post at
the at the at the song performance like
I was I was standing in a way where my
neck was like reaching out so
far that was
weird
unfortunate but you know I try to make
it work anyway with a broken neck once
again w i working with a broken
neck anything for
narissa man I want to eat that Nika
again it's so good I want to eat that
home-cooked food so good I was like
slurping really
loudly I think they lowered the volume
of it though but I actually was slurping
really
loudly
y but it was hard to eat cuz um you know
special gloves
don't want to break your immersion but
special
gloves I was in a Fredy W but with a
broken [\h__\h] neck
yeah rate the suspicious
steel
um I'm I won't comment on that
one I won't comment on
it but yeah had a lot of fun dancing
together and
practicing M there n a Nissa had like
dance lesson on the song uh like before
me like a few days before I came uh she
like learned it on her own with her
teacher uh like for like 4 hours or
something and then so she already she
she wanted to keep that a secret to
impress me she
said like to surprise and impress me
that she already like you know did did
so well but yeah so like at the day when
we were learning the dance I literally
had it it was it was on the day before
like literally on the day
before and she um she was like kind of
teaching uh because the the teacher kind
of has been very very busy coming up
with a million choreographies and this
choreography is like actually the
original choreography just adjusted for
free people but
um it's it's not like a completely new
choreography but you still have to learn
it right and the the the teacher she's
been like coming up with million
choreographies for million projects and
her mind is like filled with so many
different dances you know so she was
actually getting kind of confused a lot
of the times and and didn't remember a
lot of the moves so actually uh narissa
I was like often looking at her to rely
on her to teach me because she already
knew the dance and she was reminding the
teacher too
yeah therea became a dance teacher
y n said teaching me how to
turntables yeah she did so well she did
so
well especially for having a rod in her
back like what the hell I'm so proud of
her I'm looking forward to dancing more
with her in the future
she she's like we had so much fun
practicing like I became such a gremlin
sometimes I remember like I was like
messing around so
much cuz brain brain was just empty and
then it's just fun like the choreography
is a really fun one um and the song is a
really fun one we were just like
screaming and at some point and and I
was I was like sometimes I was over
dancing like really extremely to just
like fling my my whole body
around and then sometimes I was just
like dancing really stiffly like a robot
on purpose I don't know what what was
wrong with me on that day I was so hyper
on that day and I don't think I drank
Red Bull but I was so
hyper it looked like fun dancing it was
very exciting thank you yeah it was fun
I'm I'm I'm happy when we can use
existing coros from cuz this is actually
I don't know if you realize but it's
like from the idol um company the song
is from the idol company that has all
these Idol groups that I like Hello
project and it's their most famous group
morning mus with one of their most
famous legendary songs love machine so
Japanese people all know this song
everybody knows it and I've heard it a
million times too it's very very
familiar to me I was surprised when she
chose it I think she chose it because
both me and uhy like hello
project maybe she chose it because of
that and I think she was also not like
just generally um I remember her a long
time ago when she started planning this
I think she was asking me for uh like
recommendations and stuff
yeah I can influence her to do more
Hello project songs
but yeah the helic choreographies are
generally they have some dorkiness in
there um so there's there's some dorky
moves in there for
sure it it was fun always always lot of
[Music]
fun so I'm really happy that narissa
invited me for her 3ie
showcase I I I'm glad to be her friend
I'm glad she's I wrote it on Twitter but
I'm really glad glad she's part of whole
life English because the the time the
day she joined for me was a little bit
of a turning
point cuz like she came at a time where
I've been feeling some feelings
for a long time like you know you know
let's not get into it but she she
really helped me with that and recently
because of her being in Japan for a long
time and me not being there and now now
like I'm in Japan you know and like we
just don't have time we haven't had time
to see each other and talk to each other
like we normally did on on Discord like
in between our streams when I end my
stream and you know I hit her up and we
chitchat on Discord and you
know and we did so much of that and when
the Japan do started we kind of stopped
and it felt kind of lonely and I really
miss her so I hope when I get back to
Austria and everything's back to normal
then you know we can we
can you know talk a lot again cuz I miss
her she's she's been such a delight to
have
around and I'm glad she finally got to
show off her beauty in 3D and her
cuteness and her singing yeah her album
is really nice her EP so make sure to
listen to it on Spotify guys I'm sure
she worked hard on
it really cool
songs English guys in English her songs
are in English isn't that
awesome always I think you guys always
appreciate having more English songs in
whole life
English so I like singing I like hearing
her sing in English but also in Japanese
but you know I think it's it's like like
more relatable for you guys cuz you
understand the language
[Music]
better and maybe maybe maybe with
English being the language maybe maybe
it can reach more people outside of the
vtuber
realm
somehow hoping that too for my own
songs you don't need to understand the
lyrics yeah yeah but I I feel like
um for me at least
like that's not it's not just with
Japanese lyrics but also like Japanese
uh producers it's like a very different
kind of sound uh and for me person I
like all of those sounds but what I
personally want to go for for my own
music stuff is is not that at the moment
but I'm glad that because like K-pop
Style music is also very popular in
Japan so um I'm hoping I can reach
everybody with that music you
know I've had I've listened to like Jpop
for my whole
life and you know been trying to make
that kind of music too with heart
Challenger and H and so on but for me
for me I think I hit the spot and the
the Wawa
style can you hum your new song please
no no I'll keep it
undercover it's still going to be a
secret no spoilers good try though good
try
but I I'm I I have to say um for the
sake of like music video
creation um I'm I actually
um moved the streaming date of the frd
live uh to be another week later so now
it's actually going to be a little bit
later I'm not going to say the date yet
I want to like properly announce it at
some point um but you know just to make
sure that the music video comes out at
the same
[Music]
time yeah cuz we are going to use the
motion capture data from the actual
recording from the 3D Live uh to use it
in the music video you know I could
always take it with my accent suit but
the the thing is this time with accent
suit I can only really record myself and
it's not as high quality so you know I
want to use the opportunity to um use
higher quality motion capture and the
the chance to use backup dancers you
know cuz backup dancers I could in
theory dance several Rolls by myself
with my exent suit 2 and put them
together but with the optical motion
capture um we can record it all properly
like they're already in place in the
right position you know what I mean and
we can interact with each other I think
it's too difficult if I do that all on
my own and then we have to splice it all
together that's that's kind of crazy
sounding I'm going to make the most out
of my opportunity
here you know so that's coming anyway
tomorrow tomorrow is another freey uh
the last one another last 3D showcase
foko B and then they have a pretty
collab I think next week is it next
week tomorrow is another one
yeah and that will already complete it
huh h
[Music]
H yeah yeah so that's also why uh the
cup is a little bit later in the day cuz
we don't want to overlap with them
obviously so see you at 2:30 p.m.
jst
for
this yeah Home bun are you a guest no I
can tell you that I can't tell you when
I am a guest or something but I can tell
you when I am
not I am
not one their movement in sync in 3d2 oh
yeah we'll see we'll
[Music]
see take care of it doesn't bu oh you're
so fast you're so fast saying goodbye
yeah no it's okay I'll see you tomorrow
have to get going I
[Music]
think in German we say Al in thanks to
the ID girls for having me and and
thanks for building and preparing
something so big and amazing good work
girls they did so well tomorrow Pabon
Nashi will
prevail
maybe no I'm scared I'm scared of Ky
crony kind of scared of them and Ameda
right I'm scared of
them have confidence I don't know
scared the the freaking wool game is
going to be so
chaotic
God and I need I need to learn the I
need to learn the Indonesian words I
hope I can remember them otherwise I am
going to be effed H I'm going to be
effed you seem to have a good handle on
stuff well today was fine because I was
looking at the words and but the other
games yeah they were
okay the wool guessing game I got lucky
at the last one I I don't think I'll be
doing so well at that but it's okay we
don't have to do super well on every
game yeah aren't the emeralds just for
the final game yeah yeah you collect all
the emeralds and then the final
game oh I wonder so does it only matter
who stands at the very end of the last
game or do the scores the total emeralds
still
matter like you could win without having
the most emeralds after all you could
win the last game without having the
most emerals up until that
point yeah we'll find out tomorrow who
how who how who wins
yeah we'll find
out sh hopefully it's not just the last
game when that that's difficult oh I
don't know if I can if we can win that
last
game but yeah everybody has similar
chances I suppose I hope
so yeah okay enjoy we day I see you
tomorrow I'm going to get a massage
because my body hurts so [\h__\h] much
it's insane like if I
ow if I put my head forward like like my
head looked like in the Freddy showcase
you know if I do that it pains me so
much hope it gets better but I slept
better this night at least
H yeah yeah I get massage off off
massager SC
massage
massage massage massage bye-bye
[Music]