[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
can you guys remind me last time I
played this game was I playing it in
full screen because I can't find the
Window mode option anymore
and I'm like did I really play it like
this because it's obnoxious
to tap out I was playing in full screen
yeah there is no Window mode right it's
so [\h__\h] obnoxious because tabbing in
and out it's always like messing up
everything and as you can see it's
making it so that it won't really show
the game properly
but we'll make it work if I'm inside it
should show it
uh yeah there it is but where was I put
in the chat and also ah every time I
attendant moves my child away
[\h__\h] hellmate
I'm just gonna do full screen yeah
um
but I don't remember where did I chat
was top middle okay
where was I
um
[Music]
maybe I was here
add Windows to launch options
oh in properties
but if it's a steam game can I do that
are sure
I will hide them okay they're not even
be here it wasn't map on the right side
bottom right
oh well okay
oh
toshio
eh
I moved my chat away again even though
the
the game pops up in the middle of my in
my middle screen and I have my chat on
the right screen when I open up GTA it
moves my chat to the void so annoying I
and I have to Tab out to fix it but
when I Tab out
the game disappears of course and I'm
gonna go back in and then
[Music]
I want to try the windowed thing let me
close the game
because chat keeps on disappearing
I don't want you guys to be in the void
either you're all I have
don't go
oh
wait one second
what are
okay
so what in in Steam
close the [\h__\h] game
there it is okay it's closed
uh
steam steam my beloved
properties
please please tell me how to do it
uh where in the launch options what how
do I
um
[Music]
add miss my mine is just anywhere at the
end Maybe windowed
okay
window
[Music]
beginning or end okay
oh okay close and start please be
windowed please be windowed please be
winged out
thanks for membership renewal
oh please be windowed
Rockstar please be windowed
everybody pray for Window mode
oh it's winter
out
yes baby
okay I need to Tab out anyway for a
moment because of reasons
Rachel uh since it's so small
let me do this
this wonderful
um
I I did prepare music
uh well let's hope that that works too
it's been a while since I played it is
because I didn't play during my London
trip obviously I didn't play touring my
Japan trip and then in the one week in
between did we play it or did I
did I take a break during that two for
some reason
it's been it's been too long
um
did I have an energy drink no because
it's not good for my throat and I I
still have to be very careful of my
throat
foreign
it's only the third stream too yeah okay
who is she first time I see her
oh wait did she someone I met before
already
my mic is being weird
your mama is being weird
it's probably just uh another one of
those moments that's only doing loading
screens or whatever right
yo yo mama
wow
hey
well burnt whoa [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh no
Ah that's uh-huh okay I don't remember
her
I don't remember at all
I hear
I hear music from the radio
but uh
I don't know if I said it correctly and
I said it too sequential wait I wait
pick the
which one is my radio station
independent I don't know
quickly in the pen okay photo
[Music]
wow wow
hey I thought that it actually fits
quite well not only Coronado I got a
couple this and that oh God I don't
remember how to play this game
push punch what's right click oh no
nothing what's what where one weren't
there like some keys that I had to push
during
doing just doing punching
for like special moves I don't know yeah
I bought a fancy suit for stupid ass
dates it was so not worth it I right
click aim
uh okay
what have we been eating
a banana peel
and I don't know what the [\h__\h] is that
foreign
scared to [\h__\h] at me that was really
loud in my ear
oh there
[Music]
oh dude
open put the gun away
okay
how wait where's the door where's the
right door I guess that's a door I can't
open
uh it's the audio fine guys was that too
loud for you guys as well or just for me
this meal
what's up dog what's up dog orange cars
my car right yay audio fun
shut up what are we what are we doing
what have we been doing I guess we can
just you know go on and go to E and x
and all that Elisa beta is that the lady
that we were just talking about
shall we go to Elizabeth
uh was it like right click yeah okay
GTA weekend has begun I remembered how
to get into the car nice
wait that's not my radio
[\h__\h] where's my
ah there it is
n and B will skip forward and back for
your songs okay
[Music]
it's high fat yeah you got it
guess the song who gets it first this
will be a challenge
[Music]
are we already there
what
no I didn't
we didn't
I guess I have to walk okay
[Music]
unfortunately we can't continue to
listen to it because I gotta go
see these rides are always too short
also wait I might I scrolled my channel
[Music]
foreign
is
something you have to go to the hospital
for go
go if your blood is clutching see you
later
right
I don't understand
what happened go to the old hospital
okay
stand [\h__\h]
hospital this thing here
this is my destination yeah well it will
tell me anyway I don't know why I'm
marking it I think it will automatically
mark it
uh yeah yeah I'm just like whatever I
don't understand but I'm just gonna
follow my waypoints is my wife
[\h__\h] my car here did it
hey
but literally I don't live so far away
right where's my home
wasn't I like somewhere here I don't
know I didn't go that far where's my
home why does not show my home
what
where my car at
papaya
where's my car
yeah where's the house icon
I want my car
I was gonna take it for a ride
and the taxi looks pretty uh
much like my car
because it's orange
what do you mean it doesn't go back to
my home
wait what did that did it really get
stolen no [\h__\h] way
oh you guys you guys
you guys
why don't you not properly remind me to
not take my own car for anything
[Music]
where's Integrity and not Integrity
Independence
ah just be there by default
what is this
is it high tide again
no ah a well only kfb recognized this
one
[Laughter]
it's a remix
almost hit police
[Music]
this was the
astrophysics one right
[Music]
hi hi
that's right guys you get it
oh keep on fighting fighting till the
dark
oh
everybody in the house
[Music]
this mission is hard oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
yeah my first original song but it's a
remix that's on my channel on I think I
released free hinotori remixes
on my one year anniversary for hirotori
but they keep pushing and pulling me
if I go along
could you tell me please where I need to
go
I guess Hino Tony was written at a time
where GPS wasn't the thing yet
or Google Maps
let's go
tell me I can hear it Chloe tell me
[Music]
was that even the right Luke
oh even after
after all these years I Don't Know My
Own lyrics
so freaking embarrassing and bad
embarrassing
the intonation
[Music]
the best at
the best at remembering my lyrics better
than better than with other songs
of mine
her Coca-Cola is somewhere in the old
hospital uh-huh
straight from Bolivia
you're an American now the best
everything gets made here if the best of
them made in Mexico or Colombia or
wherever why do you all run across the
border tell me that to bring it to you
it's a service to you because you ain't
got [\h__\h] over there
in America
find the dress in the hospital and take
out anyone in your way
uh is this better to do without car
all right uh which gun
maybe this one there's so many oh wait I
already see them can I like snipe some
of them
uh uh let's see do I have a sniper still
this is sniper right oh yeah baby
oh
okay
oh [\h__\h]
get down and
where where are the rest
of them
I hear shots
they're not hitting me though are they
oh I still hear the music from my car
Nani
what what I'm looking for you I can't
see you
there's someone here no okay I think I
gotta continue
okay okay I just wanted to take care
of as many as possible while I was out
here oh oh I see
you
see that did you see that was he did he
die
stealth Wawa
right I barely saw him
it was really small
[Music]
now I'm surrounding you at this point
even though you're many more than I am
I think by this like logic of me being
outside of the building I'm surrounding
you because you're all inside the
building
how do I do the the thing again just
like this right
I can shoot
when will he shoots huh doesn't shoot
Q
this like he moves after I I I point the
gun
[\h__\h] so I have to go like here
no
I don't like Q that's the moving to the
door here this is much better
[Music]
excuse me
okay
yeah I still need to kind of get back
into it e to pick up
do I should I nah
I think I ah
I have what I need
okay
he's dead sorry I'm still taking it very
slowly take it
wait okay
I don't know what it replaced though
ah [\h__\h] I I keep on thinking that uh
sprinting what was that sprinting is on
[\h__\h] see again Ctrl because in most
games it's on Ctrl I feel like
oh oh okay
um
got him
on this one
got his hand yep no more hand-holding
it's illegal anyway
he did right and it's Mission easy if
you just gotta take it slow anyone here
no okay I I know I know they're like in
the Upper Floor
Matty kit can I take
oh I'm full full health oh
Nani
that [\h__\h] that's a good position
okay I thought that there's a prop
ceiling okay no ceiling gotta be careful
they could be anywhere
you're mine
I hear him but I don't see him
Mommy
huh
he should be
he should be straight ahead
nice
and he tumbles down
thank you
what
give me that give me that oh no I'm full
health again what how am I how do I
manage to be full health all the time
I'm invincible
[Music]
first fresh crash
fresh hot cash
uh two more or is you alive
foreign
helmet you found her stuff the Coca-Cola
is on the table and a nice
neither do I put that on automatically
I'm guessing no
where's the uh Coca-Cola there
easy
I take with me
oh
I do blue bar went up oh okay okay
convenient I've got this stuff Clippers
where the heat is coming from shout out
to the Clippers
oh oh that's what you guys meant oh [\h__\h]
they're rating it oh no oh no oh no
no not the sound you should know this
earlier
oh oh God no
thank God quicker thank God for that uh
okay uh oh yeah oh yeah
uh that changed the music too uh uh here
we are multitasking
this should be a remix uh that was on
the official Channel I think
where do I go
I am
[Applause]
keeping an opening for me thanks guys
okay okay okay okay
don't escape now just lose them thank
you I will do my best I think it was
good that we all gathered them and they
all kind of crashed a little bit
now now I'm on the right path
[Music]
uh how do I uh is it space
is it is uh stopping your car space
I don't remember
to get a new car
it's not F go [\h__\h] yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
I want to avoid curves at any cost
oh
um
[Music]
all right going this way I guess or
where I don't know
okay get wrecked please
good remix isn't it it's fitting the
situation I think the the vibe badass
[Music]
oh yeah I'm almost out of the circle but
they're right there uh
stay stay
did they did they see me
oh now the circle is here
[\h__\h] I was
article but they were waiting in front
of the circle
uh
uh thanks for the new car
[Music]
you know Ghost Rider in German
is what we call people who are on the
wrong side of the road
that's me right now
okay where Yahoo
[Applause]
where do I go oh thanks
maybe I should they keep on coming from
the front
[Music]
I'll go back into the city Maybe
joining me though oh no oh no
what did I do I'm I'm just delivering
some Coca-Cola what the [\h__\h] what's bad
about Coca-Cola
[Music]
it's so difficult to get rid of them
right now
well great
okay Roblox
I will
stretch
we can do this we can do this
um I'll go here
oh I see the end of the circle I could
[Music]
possibly Escape now what why did it get
bigger
bigger no
oh [\h__\h]
ah no
no
no let me turn thanks
okay okay my I see my new girl
just gotta go left here
[Music]
ocean
there we go and it's not it's not police
car wait how long do we have to wait
[Music]
finally that took ages
hi police so nice to see you one moment
I actually remembered I should um
probably
uh lock my door really quickly
or my cat does something stupid
[Music]
and you're just vibing to the music
wonderful
avoided the incident yeah
just in case because it's gonna be
a little bit longer stream so
it's too risky
I wouldn't notice if she opened the door
[Music]
yeah I Dreamed a couple days ago I
dreamed about
suicide Senpai I mean she wasn't I don't
think she was the main thing of my dream
but I just ended up
asking her if she wants to do a song
cover
and she was like thinking thinking and
then like really happily agreed to it
I didn't ask her no
I don't know I don't feel like I'm
worthy
um at least not maybe for one-on-one
that's it
because you know for one-on-one it's
like a direct
comparison and it seems so it feels so
intimate
the chat broke YouTube why it's like
every day now
how far did we like drive to escape
that like we went so far I see your
hearts guys thank you
[Music]
let me take a fruit candy that was too
much screaming
we just started
[Music]
welcome back
to go through
coaster was really good Ryan
I was that was really fun to sing too
I'm not gonna press F no no no no no
only when I really want to get out of a
car
oh I heard mummy's cover of Stella
stellar
when I woke up it was so beautiful
oh someone I was doing like a collab
karaoke right for her birthday did she
say did she say that there will be more
because I recorded something for it too
and she said sorry Wawa I'll show it
next time yeah part two
and she thanked me for actually
sending it like before the deadline
because I sent it quite early and I was
going through the folders to see if any
other girls like submitted theirs yet I
was I feel like I was like very close to
the deadline though if not on the
deadline but apparently
oh no there was no I I didn't even know
of an official deadline but I thought oh
she might probably want to get the audio
data soon
so yeah
I was kind of like stressing out about
my own stuff but I had to get it done
before flying to Japan or something like
that something around that time
yeah
he's doing a part two yeah hey Nico so I
will be in that hey
because she's sick right now she
couldn't do them all this this is no
place for you Michelle as it happens it
is
you see Nico I have been working for the
government I'm afraid it's my job to
watch you money and now I have to ask
you for the coke this is a joke right
please please don't make this harder for
me than it already is
look they're about to take down
elizabetha beta I don't [\h__\h] believe
this no way
I'm sorry it had to be this way Nico I'm
really sorry
are you really
you know you could have gone down too if
you weren't so useful
you [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
betrayal pure betrayal
voila you remember so you're going to
let us off just like that not naguan
that one well my employers need the help
of a guy like me please subtitle it in
like English that I can read the office
is in Algonquin
please no
um
why'd you give it to her it's just her
just shocking method tell Elizabeth what
can she do
what can she do
yes
man
that's so lame how do you refill reload
again I don't know
what how do you reload because I feel
like it's not Reloaded
was it was it f r i guess it's reloaded
the zero is confusing me
Elizabeth I'm so sorry like I worked so
hard to get your Coca-Cola
but I guess you gotta from now on drink
Pepsi instead I know I know I know
I know you prefer Coca-Cola for whatever
reason but Pepsi is nice too and if you
even you know want to risk it for the
biscuit how about a Dr Pepper
don't write it off immediately okay
oh [\h__\h] I shouldn't wear this
yeah what what's up with the fact
infiltrating my private life my family
and all that that's not cool
that's not cool at all I'm looking for a
cool car though right now but there are
no cool cars
is somebody watching me
don't make me kill Ed
airplane
why it always switch to other stations
the sun's like
[Music]
what's this
when am I beloved
the game spawns Cars similar to the one
that I was in automatically you think so
[Music]
Nike sorry it will be cut off
immediately
[Music]
oh yeah gotta get out of the other side
sorry about that bad parking bad parking
my fault
oh every car is default radio station oh
damn okay hey man this is getting out of
control the police are all over me I can
feel them yeah so so so
oh
send
life is over
nothing man
oh you
are being tough in a man's world
because I wasn't so tough huh
thanks for always cutting away from it
one's a rats not me whatever
whatever yeah indeed not me
the streets I'm the only one you can
trust
all right man this is what man is all
about man many many word up [\h__\h] you
better stop slinging that [\h__\h] on my oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I don't want it anymore
Collision of Worlds the streets have
spoken now leave my people alone
what are you doing here
I am not in the mood for this right now
see this is what Coca-Cola does for you
well don't do it he's going to bust the
dealer what the [\h__\h]
can you help me clean this mess up what
the [\h__\h]
come on let's put them in my mind she
canceled my side quests wasn't that a
different side quest
s
oh not anymore yeah no no I'm done with
that side quest
uh my car is gone too so sad
but I guess it wasn't really my car the
beginning was that's okay I get it
[Laughter]
I wasn't attempting anything no no no I
wasn't attempting anything
oh
stop my toe
stop my [\h__\h] toe
just might tell though everything else
totally fine of course please let me in
look at the map why is it close oh
Ah that's where I go
there you go no they want me to take a
specific vehicle
ah [\h__\h] you can have your car back
what that's luxury
I'm still in a mission
yeah so
forgive me oh
did they move my car up or is that
someone else's caught
that they prepared for me
I didn't come in this car right
you may want to close wait this is that
this is such a nice music to listen to
while I'm transporting dead bodies how
do I close it wait
I want clothes how do you close it yeah
wait what it said you might want to
close it how
yeah I can't I can't
swim
yeah
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ah man
we're not in Mario Kart man
[Music]
I want to listen to that calmly
yeah yeah I know that wasn't good either
but I'm already I'm already wanted
wanted wasted I am
ah this is gonna extend my circle again
ah come on how am I
about those bodies
bodies need to go because now I'm
getting so far away there's no way that
I'm not meeting in police again
on my way back
[Music]
how do I close it I tried it normally
you know the the side doors you can
close right by just walking against it
so I thought thanks for their help
I thought that's how I could do it
without opening my [\h__\h] trunk
don't shoot me I'll add you to my dead
bodies
I'm so unfair
um
which one
yeah
a top one not the top one
oh
[Music]
no oh it's way too early
man I looked up today it's true
[Music]
so
what's happening are we gonna maybe have
the conversation again that's fine for
me
that was such an unfortunate bunk do the
uh does it normally really always open
that easily I don't think so I think
they rigged it
for this mission
so it opens more easily oh my God
okay
I will have a car
you're getting carjacked nobody's
watching right
now
wait is that a talking radio I want to
listen to that one too eventually
the remixes that I got from the whole
life Channel
they're like all connected so I don't
know if we'll ever get past the first
songs I downloaded two
wow
oh
there we go I'm sorry we can always this
is why I didn't really think it would
make sense necessarily to make my own
radio because we'll always just
[Music]
listen
mm-hmm
I feel like in GTA 5 we had more
um more situations where we were in the
car longer for really long rides like we
had to you know drive over to that
desert place so often
there you go
okay okay no bonking because this car is
rigged
he looks
hi Todd where are we going
oh pretty far okay
[Music]
no problem leave it to me
dead body transportation is one of my
specialties
just don't Bonk against anything I don't
trust this game anymore
so uh
-huh
[Music]
how's this let's go
what that was on purpose that's one of
the policemen probably trying to [\h__\h] me
up
[Music]
can I go first
um
okay you can go
[Music]
nice Muna what's next song
I ended up not adding any Cali songs
because I thought maybe
um because she releases them in a like a
label that's not whole life
it might create issues for my my
don't want to get in trouble
take it amigo
the only took songs that
were released under the whole life label
as far as I know
[Music]
um
big brain
s
they want to open my trunk why are they
like
what the [\h__\h] yeah pre-umg I was
thinking about that too but then I
wasn't sure when when exactly you which
songs which is this which songs are are
pretty umg
and I kind of wanted to put in wanted
wasted but oh well
that is definitely umg times
[Music]
quack
and I also cannot stop singing when I
put in music into the radio
but I mean especially if it's my own
song you have to forgive me
all right if you're saying wanted wasted
hmm I should
next karaoke next archived karaoke we
should do a Whole Life karaoke again
it's been a while since I did order of
karaoke
I've heard you'll take care of them
and natural causes yeah of course seems
like a bullet in the head is as natural
as it gets at this time they weren't
sick were they no
had a few problems with sick bodies
no one wants a liver if it's riddled
with tumors huh ew that's not good no
no
looks like the bullet went right through
this one's eye the price of eyes is
through the roof at the moment
button
the cheese organs out on the street in
no time awesome they're gonna help a lot
of folks
onto the black market huh
it's so scary
it's already so bloody
[Laughter]
okay he takes a car all right three
thousand bucks for that
what was that music
okay okay I think Elizabeth
is quite happy for now
yeah we can now uh
help out the Playboy I guess well I
don't wanna
wait what is this by the way is this
should I go to the unknown contact
the complete admission music oh I didn't
hear it until now because I had it
turned off
um
the guy that called me I don't remember
that at all
what's going on but I hate playable I
think I didn't I hate the Playboy oh
the doctor has that stuff
[Music]
party yeah this lady she's she's too
much trouble
to just
ignore her leave her and read red
in my personal opinion
let me take this car
and then we'll go to the Playboy
yeah I I just can't I I don't I I don't
think I can you know
deal with a lady like that who can't
control herself and loses herself in the
drugs you know I am I I can't who the
[\h__\h] is Mallory
Michelle
are you okay she was lying to us all
along and
oh [\h__\h] music
Roman's girlfriend ah
I keep on
forgetting about the
music
[Music]
my lights well my lights are on what do
you mean another off I guess I destroyed
them wait how do you switch songs there
we go
13 or 22 often but there's two remixes
of you know Tony in there so
new song please
I thought B was
ah
wait I think I hear the beginning of
astrophysics okay
there we go this is something different
or is this high tide again
oh yeah it's high tide again
[Music]
donkey donkey
why does this genre just works so well
for her
[Music]
oh
I never saw something like this before
in GTA
[Music]
yeah monkey monkey I have that one too
in the radio
[Music]
ow
I'm not going out
[Music]
it's a dog eats dog world has somebody
told the twins that yet
be careful
was the the first dog in Hollow
and it's a dog eat dog world
wait is that what you say it it was a
dog eats dog what always what's this
wait that's such a weird saying
why would dogs eat dogs
wait I'm questioning it real bad right
now because like saying it out loud
makes him feel really
unlogical
[Music]
but only if they're like really
desperate and they're and they're
starving and there's nothing else
they're all right
no
[Music]
I mean in a normal environment they
wouldn't do it
wow yeah
[\h__\h] up I want to listen to the rest
of the song
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah finally we heard the song Until the
End
probably
this
nice balcony
oh them tiny ants down there man this
[\h__\h] is crazy tiny ants you're not that
high are you okay
yeah okay well I guess he is what about
you
what motivates you hmm well
I need money this pays I can do it I
don't care if I live or die
and I'm looking for someone
yeah you could say that
so why do you need me
I'm always looking for good guys
Holding On Me but it might work
change Money Changes people not me I'm
still a hustler from these truths
and I heard good things about you okay
But I'm warning you I'm not low budgie
do I look like I live low budget though
we've been around long enough to ask for
a high budget nice
no some [\h__\h] I don't know well
Dwayne
my dude
son what's going down
you didn't tell me you was getting out
man I would have laid on a party got
some freaks out we got out of jail
a couple of times what happened man hey
Dwayne
is that the cool thing
we just say it in German
money what's the
what's the what you mean what's the plan
but when we left off
I'm back we keep on rolling
you say we yeah we bless you too fine
what you silk sheet fancy dress wearing
life too big for me now oh hey I ain't
saying that you know what's mines is
yours
I help just holla hey this is my [\h__\h]
any good he can help
no
anything I can uh but right now we gotta
roll
give me one second he got the hot top
bubbling 24 7. that's not good for your
electricity bills
some folk
s where did you get out from
preschool
[Laughter]
we gotta roll
please make yourself at home
how kind
all right where are we rolling where are
we jetting
[\h__\h] must think I'm an idiot
an idiot I learned grammar
from an English grandma
weapons in a car in an alley in downtown
oh that's really downtown
okay we're going by car please join me
he's still in preschool all right okay
you heard of yourself on me big real
estate developer I don't know
this guy's a big difference at that
point are you and him having meetings
about how to run the city not yet but I
got an idea about how me and him would
be a friend some Italian dudes shut down
his building site on some union [\h__\h]
they all up in the place strapped to
their fronts with hard hats on and [\h__\h]
won't let nobody get here
[Music]
Mafia types off the site meantime I'm
gonna tell Yusuf how good we've been to
him that cat me is going to be Titus two
cell mates on lockdown after this what's
in it for me I'll give you what you
asked Cold Hard Cash that what you
chasing right amongst other things
I don't know how good your plan is
though Playboy if I get rid of the guys
on the site then won't there be more if
it's a union problem doesn't that make
it bigger than a few guys with guns [\h__\h]
Union is just another word for Mafia
These cancers yeah is that when you guys
have been always trying to build
is
City to make it big it's my duty to
watch this cat's back my ancestors came
from Africa now he's coming out a bit
later me and him could be cousin [\h__\h] I
think you might want to look at the map
Playboy Dubai is the nap
get all the same Africa America Dubai it
don't matter we're brothers spiritually
I mean and that's the important bit
[Music]
I thought I could do a cool trick that
was really lame
oh man
[Music]
it is
we gotta do something here
[Music]
foreign
everything
was that Time Square I drove past Times
Square really
[Music]
man
some jokes I just get so addicted to
um
[Music]
foreign
all that [\h__\h]
[Music]
ain't a star
okay unfortunately we have to switch
cars
so sorry
yo there's three Lookout cats making
sure no one makes move on the site you
best take them out with the rifle before
you hit up the rest of them but they're
up so high I'm gonna get in the position
where I can see all the [\h__\h] going down
if you can take out the main catch then
the rest of them shouldn't be a problem
I
come here
and start still running
and
take out the Lookouts from here
I guess I could
nice easy do the others notice yet that
I did that no oh he's confused nice
very convenient oh
[Applause]
well
maybe maybe shouldn't have placed the
car there I should have placed something
to catch you more gently I I don't know
where the
where is the last one
well that's hard to tell
here
[Music]
what maybe uh maybe like
not up so ah there should be there maybe
on this one
wonderful outside out of my mind
that all them Lookouts gone buddy get in
there and free up the site okay go to
concerts refine the first union leader
Mafia leader you mean
okay I need a police cars here nope
I just feel kind of concerned running in
like this
foreign
okay
all righty
where are they oh
are they all up on the top
oh yeah
cover gotta take cover
why the hell screaming like that
stupid I said the
the the normal people
panicking oh my God
how do we go up again
this is a union enemy enemy enemy enemy
okay everybody you can just come down
here oh
dad why would you do that
did they know I was down here that was
so stupid of them
[Music]
[Laughter]
another one really
I'm excellent
are they all gonna come here huh
how many of them are there
I hear I hear someone
no way I didn't do this on purpose
this was not my plan but it seems pretty
quiet now doesn't it
okay the problem was I didn't know how
to get up there
I have okay long and pressing f
big freaking Kusa
laughs
that
ah I need a zoom
a nice Hedgehog
what about him
is he
is he a normal person
I'll give you the benefit of the doubt
let me see if he has a weapon oh yeah he
does
okay I'm just guessing anybody here at
this point is uh an enemy right
anyone anyone
me not taking
me
okay so now only at the Upper Floor
don't even need the medkit again I am
too strong
really nobody left down here
[Music]
who's talking to me that sounded so
close
wait are they normal people
I'm so sorry if yes
that was Nico ah the talking one was
Nico
okay okay
I'm so sorry dude
wait are you a friend or full
I guess he was a friend
[Music]
okay let me try maybe up here
huh
foreign
thank you for putting me in position
oh [\h__\h]
can I do I I have more oh
I think uh
uh
okay
come on
that would be good
okay yo
nah that's not so good
bro
can I just why are they motivating me to
use the grenades I want to use guns
[Laughter]
grenades are fun and all but I need more
accuracy
you can barely see them
you guys can probably see even less
how's my half doing so pretty good
nice
beautiful shots here your tiny tiny ants
huh okay okay we're done in this area is
that what you're saying
don't forget to pick up the money if
they drop some money
we're in it for the money after all
I love how they put me in a position the
game puts me in a position where the
grenades just keep on bouncing off
oh hi
whoa
[Music]
ah he almost fell down there oh no there
you go ES
do I hear a helicopter
is that police or or enemy I mean police
is also the enemy of course
I need a bazooka
I'll do my best ah [\h__\h] hey
where's that coming from
too bad
get out get down get down
here why why okay I guess you can't
let's try it again
too far or
let's go
pretty good pretty good yeah
decent decent
a present for you little souvenir
from Liberty City hey
this lamp is my enemy
gonna use them all up where did that one
go
okay I'm gonna shoot
what
um
no that was me again
how's it going I thought there was one
more life ah
[Music]
I
love that there's so many people here to
see me
it's like a
it's like a meet and greet
why no picky up why does nobody have
money
where's the chopper good question where
did it go did they just drop him off and
then leave
seems like it
yeah
okay a union leader is down below but uh
oh
is that the union later
should I kill him was that the request
or do I need him alive
[Laughter]
I think I think I have to kill him right
I got rid of all the union problems
that's fine as you can see this killing
Dennis it's too late now man can't waste
time
this [\h__\h] they're gonna start listening
to Playboy
oh these are in a sense right I mean
let's be nice I don't want to traumatize
them anymore
nice
are they are they scared I'm so sorry I
don't want to be scary I want to be
loved by everybody
I want to be a hero
[Music]
put down the gun yeah I did okay I did I
did I did I am not dangerous dangerous
not dangerous
oh Playboy again
so true
like me I'm a fake cat when I have my
cat ears on
him
over in Northwood he holding up there
and needs help with some [\h__\h]
this broke ass I'll send some paper your
way how old
payback of [\h__\h] peace out money [\h__\h]
oh what where what what this uh d
well when I wait the fact the fact is
we're all the way down here so we might
as well check out the question mark
they sure
coconut
it's like at the at the pier Pierre and
a Pierre
at the end of a Pierre
I think
over there
Pierre
oh my stamina
no slacking off oh it's like getting
really great again
who is it
who could it be
is that the chopper from before
police Chopper on duty
oh
are we having a date with this lovely
gentleman
I wouldn't mind some nice dinner
no poop deck
hey strange seeing you here officer
McCreary I told you to come here [\h__\h]
Maggie
mag you did
why I know
and damn that is
you think this is a town that can keep a
secret I really don't know what you're
talking about yeah you do I really don't
know I know that a man's gotta do what a
man's Gotta Do
statue of happiness is that's what it's
called here
so
so there's a guy trying to Blackmail me
I don't know
thinks he's getting paid though the
guy's smart he arranged to do the
exchange by the Humboldt River off
silicon Street oh said to call him from
the Viewpoint there okay listen I did
what I did I made a mistake that don't
make me the devil
what did he do I don't remember
then he gets money and I'm admitting
guilt I ain't guilty enough
nothing I don't really care one way or
another well I'm a good man no doubt you
don't remember him either [\h__\h]
yeah
oh it never said what he did but right
after
Nico don't remember either these boing
boings why are they so boing boing
this is not realistic is it
well this is wobbly water it's like the
pool water in the wild Earth in London
it's really [\h__\h] wobbly
it's following me everywhere this
[\h__\h] wobbly pool water it won't let
me go
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
I don't want to see any more wobbly
water is this wobbly water too no this
one looks fine
it's not so wobbly
this is good water
that's evil water evil he wants me dead
no
it is
uh uh okay okay the yellow marker
just gotta find the car
I gotta visit New York someday ma'am
which car maybe this one
but
um police
oh I like this music I wanna keep it
too bad where's the talking one uh
uh what's the talking one called
[Music]
is it integrity
that sounds like talking the talking one
I mean you don't understand
is it too loud guys for me this is good
volume
she's on TV Liberty City
radio
oh there's several I was
this was one of them right totally
when women were considered property
women are defective and misbegotten but
I don't own her I would like to own a
human being someday I mean is this a
comedian I'd be uh young nubile Filipino
boy and who could sit in my Tropical Hut
and
play games and decide who does what by
playing hands-free catch the quarter
what
what's look what's happened to you why
you gotta hyphenate why are you gonna be
half a man she took away your manhood
she emasculated you good and proper well
that's some bitch's name on half your
[\h__\h] do you pee sitting down
what
[Music]
you're an [\h__\h] hey
go back to beating beating that wife
shut up come down and beat the [\h__\h] out
of you hey you know what I'm just gonna
get a couple blocks away from here
where are the street vendors in this
town since [\h__\h]
all right this is the last low show on
Integrity it's an association with zit
you know my sponsor yeah speaking of
foreigners if we're gonna get to the
underbelly of the city you know we
should take a cab ride do you think Taxi
yeah uh take me to Frankfurt and Jade
near star Junction please so riding in
the cab it's a serious Liberty City
experience you know because these people
uh drive for like 18 hours straight and
pee in soda bottles talk to their
friends on cell phones and Jack [\h__\h] a
Stan or wherever they're from and uh
toss off but the immigrants that they
they bring the city alive you know them
and the stock Brokers but you know
people say Laszlo are these people
you're kidding me I remember you you
used to be on the radio you were so
funny yeah I think yeah man I was on
Chatterbox and I'm coming back I'm on
the air now you were flooded for a while
but what happened you oh
you mean you don't
all you talk about is how many women you
sleep with you don't look like you've
had any women please okay this mustache
a lot of girls have ridden these
handlebars huh you know I mean since my
divorce nobody wants to hear about your
problems hey dude that's Show Business
okay it's about reality these days not
entertainment okay because I gotta tell
you once you've flown first class you
know it sucks to take the bus again
[Laughter]
don't don't tell me how to do my
I spit
[Music]
and stuff dude I'm doing a new show
seeing hell buddy see you later all
right the station is called Integrity uh
I should mention they were we're
sponsored by zit uh we're gonna take a
quick break
on Integrity your ringtone defines who
you are and how much money you have so
take bling to the next one okay
interesting
I don't remember that
tones like the sound the money be
counted
two million dollar bills being counted
be how about a ringtone of a private
[\h__\h] yeah he was in San Andreas as well
man he's famous
[Applause]
tones only 100 bucks be an individual
get a VIP luxury ringtone nobody gets
ringtones anymore
[Music]
that's an interesting theme for a radio
station maybe we should make a podcast
like that
and hold on
you discover a pair of balls well guess
what baby the [\h__\h] is back but I'm not
a [\h__\h] I'm a man so he's in the strip
club he's the dancer is that what he's
saying
surprise that's me is that what he's
okay enough of that that's too much
already
foreign
I'll never get that car back up uh what
where huh
did I miss it is it up here yes okay
can we go back to the whole radio
I just wanna let you know loosen a
little bit what it is and then never
listen to it again
all right this guy told me to bring the
money there and call him that means he's
somewhere close and he's got a phone I'm
gonna text you his number you've got to
call him and keep a lookout for someone
answering
you know you want a hot dog yeah yeah he
was talking straight to my heart my
heart does want the hot dog messages
wait how do I open messages again
uh help help help help
help
up
thanks
read blackmail his number is so and so
um
do I have to remember this number or can
I okay
[Music]
who's this a friend I'm calling about
your exchange with McCreery yeah
I'm sure he's got your money have you
got the stuffy ones
yeah and there's a lawyer called Tom
Goldberg who's real
he's hungry for my career did I shoot
him
good thing Francis is paying then call
me when this
is oh my God
[Music]
did I did I get what I needed uh
I want to hide somewhere
we did it I don't think I did did I
what did I
who are you
a police oh
okay
faster
[Music]
three stars
and here we go and here we go
[Music]
games
Independence here we go
[Music]
new original song
big recommends
I like it
why is this the car to wobbly
oh God I have no wheels
[Music]
they can't get me
nice pretty Empty Street love it
easy
foreign
[Music]
she's so cute
the girl that I will always only collab
with via uh calls
on session
it's the only way we will ever interact
it's like
ah
they have like something special going
on you know oh
[Music]
she just released this guys watch the MV
on YouTube do it do it
[Music]
it's very fresh
this is also one song I want to learn
for an inevitable for life
time
I feel like she got better at singing so
much too compared to the beginning
yeah
good job Anya
[Music]
hi hi
I gotta listen to it to the end we've
come so far I was taking my time
so we could hear it all right
we start what we finished at kfp
sorry it's quiet
because I turned down the sfx
read the subtitles
because
only a thousand bucks what what status
cheap as hell
I'm not such a cheap woman all right
what's next FM
what's FM Francis
Dwayne and Playboy well Dwayne is the
closest
so I'm gonna go to Dwayne lucky man it's
your lucky day
the solver of all problems oh oh I think
there's money and running on the radio
but I gotta switch cars uh
without getting caught by the police
that's over there uh I want this car
though
can I take it wait a police is left gone
police gone I think
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
please make a U-turn we're safe there it
is
[Music]
shut up woman
listen to The Other Woman
is 100. shut up why now she never talked
before
because this one I I made on my own
can't get rid of it
make her shut up
[Music]
and come over to my mind
see you there okay
[Music]
this is just like a Vibe with me stream
vibe to whole music with me
it's so cute I love her new song
foreign
[Music]
yeah especially when the president's
turned into an [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] nobody wants to roll with
me no more it's like I'm tainted
what do you mean Playboy don't want to
hang no more he pays for you to come
over instead
girlfriend the love of my [\h__\h] life
gone man I was pulling moves in the
joints so this [\h__\h] could pay rent
she won't answer the phone
man I gave her everything when I was
inside
cause
houses Apartments bank accounts
everything
I heard she hang up with
who
Punk who [\h__\h] talked
now [\h__\h] [\h__\h] my girl
real
[\h__\h] up man
but here I know it's really quiet let me
skip
[Music]
to help you guys
can I re-watch it
ah
we got the gist did we
sorry it's sorry
it's a nice car
kind of decent
[Music]
right I'm so sorry
it's hard to find a balance because I
wish I could I wish I could filter out
the voices from the NPCs
and all the other sfx but it's all the
same is 20. yeah
[Music]
how do I turn off the GPS
was it there
ah
ah thanks
[Music]
yes I want volume Sliders in my game of
course I do
for every single detail please let me
let me
micro manage my audio
[Music]
cook
ie
[Music]
I didn't get to see her merchandise yet
what does she have for merchandise
[Music]
an ashtray
what no way
and the French toast bags
no way
[Music]
you made a [\h__\h] ashtray
what
no way no way okay it's still an ashtray
it's a tray for okay that's a joke huh
it can double as an ashtray wait wait
wait I need to see wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
it's [\h__\h] ass try I can't believe it
let me go on her Twitter she must have
posted it or like reposted it
what's this live action cute uh wait
wait wait wait wait wait no she didn't
post it she retweet it at least
marketing
marketing advice from your mama
post your merchandise wait I'm just
scrolling endlessly through fan art did
she did she
oh I found it found it
found it is it
ah I see it I got trays like that if
they're not if they're relatively big
then I would say it doesn't look like a
ashtray
don't use it as an ashtray to all the
smokers out there don't use it as an
ashtray if you're getting the tray
Tumblr cute I like tumblers
the hootsie hangers what are the hootsie
hangers
and cute
detachable can be used on smooth
surfaces with no unevenness depending on
how does this work
oh wait it's like one hanger ah and it's
like ah I think I get it I think I get
it
and the bag the bag is so cute oh my God
oh God I want to see real life samples
can't wait for Yago pictures
yo her birthday merge completes that is
so much cheaper than mine how did she
manage to keep to keep it so sheep sheep
sheep
the Polaroid cute maybe I do Polaroid
instead of postcard next too because
this is cute
because we already had postcard can I do
Polaroid too
cute
no plus you're a special big item yeah
yeah true
all our debates over time you may be
real ones although I've had Polaroids
some really old ones
and they haven't faded I have some
sticking on my um PC case for example
and then I have others just like
um
in a little box really old Polaroids and
they didn't fade
mine don't paint maybe if you keep it at
a place where it's constantly being hit
by sunlight
I swear where oh that's five square
[Music]
This Time Square
it seems so empty shouldn't be so empty
right oh wait this is
which part exactly is the Time Square
[Applause]
or maybe
yeah I think I see it
and people do like uh all kinds of
videos here
[Music]
foreign
parts of New York that everybody knows
that I even should know
does this street is this accurate does
this street exist like this
I want to compare everything
this is very accurate to the
actual City escaping
sorry corner I have to cut you off right
away
doggy doggy doggy world
Street
it's close
but not enough traffic of course of
course
when he was in The Joint he wants his
money what Dwayne must have finished his
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] he gonna be mad angry
bad attempt execute chorizo let her live
I let her live
I mean
Dwayne don't need to worry about having
that girl's blood on his hands on top of
everything else yeah
would you guys have killed her
where is where's where's he right now
straight down
[Applause]
do
[Music]
um
I switched over I was gonna come to him
[Music]
of course you know
okay
[Music]
sorry
I have to continuously check where he's
going
[Music]
now
[\h__\h] how do I open it again
how do I do it
[Music]
okay thank you
[\h__\h]
yeah I wasn't
I was hurrying up I wasn't even
doing that bad I think
is this right after we skipped the the
cutscene they could have at least let me
listen to it again if they set me back
so far man
is that my card I wanted
[Music]
God that scream
I watched like a police body cam for
this video
fellas
so so ridiculous
[Music]
oh my God where is the station
there it is
with a certain Shakira flabbergasted
does anybody know which one I mean no no
no no it was not about an incompetent
cop it was a freaking insane woman
[Music]
that's what she called herself to the
cop when he asked what's your name
Shakira uh-huh really what what's your
last name
[\h__\h] insane woman
[Music]
like gravity I'm gonna sing this one too
pulling on my list guys
and I gotta sing all of the GTA
kiwawa radio songs
all of them
[Music]
dead
be careful look where you're going
[Music]
I think the gravity
still remember the time in
[Music]
was it third Fest right
where she performed it
damn girl
[Music]
foreign
well I regret keeping that woman alive
so we watch this
I'm keeping her alive again I just need
my car
I saw him
this time at least I'm not like
hesitating like last time and I will
keep on going straight I wonder if he
goes for the exact same route or if it
changes depending on
or should I have taken the bike does it
change depending on where I'm going
same route
yes yes for same route okay well then
we have the absolute advantage
[Music]
exactly where are you going
you could not go this way right
you have to
[Music]
do I shoot with him when I see him
oh
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
do I just push him off his stupid bike
not as planned
a nice day am I still see him
[Music]
tell me I'm taking the bike but with the
car at least I can Ram him oh God
[Music]
oh yeah
wait quit he's in trouble where is he
gonna go
[Music]
why is this guy on the road
why I wanted
what about the shooting yeah
[Music]
uh okay [\h__\h]
oh smooth recovery
[Music]
is smoking I need to move my ashtray
randomly shooting
[Music]
no more invincible
what armor I see
[Music]
okay nice
get the money how much was it oh God I'm
not going with this car also it seems
like nobody noticed what just happened
so I can give it to you
hello
okay and the bike seems kind of you know
um
[Music]
why am I wanted
about along the way
[Music]
huh stay there while I just stay there
come on come on come on
[Music]
this game by now
waffle but I don't listen to this
[Music]
ah there we go
some days
[Music]
passing through
me
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry I have to get out
um nanny
inside
what
where is he
how to meet
this man
how do I get inside wait this door
this is Future
nurse's future as a cave beans are
literally this could be nervous right
now hi there so how's it going
keep unlocking the floor outside yeah
Marissa
oh I love the little Tippy Taps on the
floor that's so cute
we should make that at kfp they pay it
up guess my name still means something
out there people are still scared of me
they are I got rid of Javon for you but
I let your ex go um she just couldn't
help herself she always told me she
burned me good guess I should have
listened happy she ain't dead though
really just an idiot okay good good
seems he's happy with it what what would
he have said if I killed him six pounds
yeah now we're talking
Young
oh yes I made the writers very good okay
would he have been pissed off otherwise
he wouldn't like it he gets paranoid
okay
then my intuition made me do the right
thing
okay guys we're going to the f
all they're doing they're doing
Cowboy coutures can I get one too
I want one too
um I can't get one it's so sad
I will walk by the way
because I feel like I always get lost in
the music
it's uh not good
um
and it's close enough to walk
Elizabeth
[Music]
[Applause]
really
good thing around with them too much
[\h__\h] is [\h__\h] up I'm sorry for getting
you involved don't worry about it you've
got enough on your plate looking after
Roman see you soon
why don't you come on over memory
Mallory
Shakespeare on drugs
interesting is that a musical
where am I where am I going
no I'm basically there just uh straight
ahead
there it is
slow down when you see
somebody walking over the street
what the [\h__\h]
Fitness what did I just get a workout
thing
have a nice day oh hey uh Jimmy how you
doing
have a nice day
hey chief hey Mitch looking good gastric
bypass worked out well for you I see
yeah thanks I'll tell my therapist about
you tell them my boss keeps sexually
harassing me yeah you wish I could use a
drink you no
oh the [\h__\h] thinks he could drag
me down what's wrong now
oh man
listen [\h__\h] his voice I don't know
let me put it like this
if a guy makes a mistake should that
ruin his life
it depends on the mistakes a bowl of
fruit slowly rotting in a hot kitchen I
don't give a [\h__\h] about the life lessons
friend what do you want I'm a good guy
he's got it all wrong he's
he's but one stain on my character and
I'm finished
I want to make a difference what ah
some lawyer
big white shoe firm thinks he's a
crusader some morality [\h__\h] who takes
photos of guys in the shower at the gym
and then jacks off on his wife's face
way enough did he take one of you sorry
the guy's name is Tom Goldberg thinks
he's got something on me gonna go to the
D.A with it use it to get into Congress
okay yeah
so
it's him or me and it might as well be
him right but he's hard to get to
guy's got a bodyguard limo everything
you're gonna need to get one-on-one with
him you want me to kill him a shower's a
job interview
then you can steal some files I need why
not in the shower an interview sure
it'll be easy you're an immigrant
they're almost legally bound to
interview you
but uh get yourself a suit I am in a
suit
okay hello
I'll email you the what's the problem
with my suit you're a good man
I'm over prepared coming from you that
means a lot it does
huh
well then I guess I don't have to do
anything only going to an internet cafe
[Music]
[\h__\h] internet cafes man
if they're not like those in Japan I
don't want to go to them
[Music]
oh it's really far okay
good then we can listen to the full song
Maybe
[Music]
[Applause]
I want to hear Cobble
[Music]
it was already so hard to learn the
lyrics from her
um
first song
Indonesian lyrics
now I have to learn these
a gumball
[Music]
because this one's longer too like the
other one is like short length but this
one's like full length right
full song Length
[Music]
yeah the cars are so loud that's why I
turned down the sfx but then the
dialogue is also freaking quiet
[\h__\h] loud car shut up
what's the quietest car I could get in
this game
[Music]
competition for covers uh I don't know I
missed it
a hybrid
I know how to find a hybrid
[Music]
oh
yeah okay now this is clown man
[Music]
I'm driving extra slow too
yeah
oh no not my fault not my fault not my
fault not my fault
I only indirectly uh uh uh damaged the
police car wasn't me
really wasn't me
or Pepsi actually isn't this a Pepsi
or bag what are we looking for click the
link of the Lawrence advertisement or
enter the web address oh this guy Tom
Goldberg
oh interesting it's got a mall it's got
a interesting beard is here wow it's
like he looks
like an important character not just a
random NPC
Goldberg ligner and scheister
was founded on the ideal that no man is
beyond judgment our firm has endeavored
to seek out corruption and advice in the
highest echelons of society coming from
founder Tom Goldberg's dream to level
the playing field GL and S has amassed
one of the most impressive records in
the legal industry our firm has
successfully litigated against CEOs
politicians priests Community leaders
and Charities glns believe that
corruption is always there you just have
to look for it
hmm sounds good I want to apply I feel
like I would fit right in however I want
you to add my letter to the name of the
firms that's my only request
reasonable no
I mean if I'm part of it
I want to be part of it for real for
real
to rise to the top of my professional
Liberty City
blue
sounds good
skills people management coping with
cultural differences
that's that's the skill you got nothing
else you gotta write that here
shooting boxing running swimming
shooting shooting that's kind of like
writing that as a first is kind of
dooming I feel the Doom upon this Law
Firm
thank you for submitting your resume
we'll call you ASAP all right thanks
[Music]
oh
alrighty been there done that
I got so much money wow
what should we do next I guess unless
they quickly update us we could do one
of these
center of the application
I've always wanted to be a lawyer has
anyone really like just a land of
opportunity
uh okay
I'm looking for a cheaper car I mean
whoa my kind
don't like the color so much but this
could be quiet no
no it makes boom
make lots of Boom
I needed this car
finally we're back at the remixes but
where am I going
um you know what we'll go here because I
want something that's far away
we'd like to arrange an interview for
you at the earliest come into our
offices at noon tomorrow is that all
right oh there okay
do I have to your interview
have a nice day do I actually have to be
like really on time like the date
[Music]
I have an interview with Goldberg
tomorrow
you guys gotta remind me when it's time
to go
[Music]
at the community
I don't have my hands on the wheel
tap your hands
clap your hands
[Applause]
oh my God that wasn't police
don't pass Don't touch don't touch
no talk to the police car
[Music]
okay oh I get to clap your hands
clap your hands
[Music]
come on
stop your hands
[Music]
only in this country they let blind
people drive
why was he stopping
down
keep me crazy amazing
clap your hands
.com
bye
your hands
clap your hands
[Music]
nice one
oh hello Grandma all I'm saying is that
we'll all be judged in the end all of
your brothers and you Patrick and you
Kate who's gonna judge Kate what would
she win if they did virgin of the year
I'm thinking maybe you can catch VD for
both [\h__\h] you Patrick language sorry ma
excuse me may I disturb Mr [\h__\h] crazy
man that's me we're here no good because
I ain't [\h__\h] got none very funny
maybe if being a drunker doesn't work
out you can be a [\h__\h] off out of here
well aren't you going to introduce us
sure hello this is Nico some drug
dealing to [\h__\h] generate from some
armpit in Eastern Europe that's my ma
it's nice to meet you did I not
disconnect my sister lovely life my OBS
disconnected okay foreign
nice to meet you at the stream stuff
around was just a second yeah it was
really short bye
quick request
I think she likes you
word to the wiso she don't put out which
is convenient because if she did I'd
have to kill you understood good lad one
just do you got any drugs on you boy
nope [\h__\h]
well probably a good thing we got some
business to take I got them taken away
unfortunately
hey what's the business
tell me about it
okay but we gotta finish it before noon
tomorrow this is uh uh where's my car
this is my car
this is my car now
all right get back into the car man mind
your own business
[Music]
okay there's a ship coming in and we're
the welcoming party who are we welcoming
and what have they got that makes this
drive would be if we're welcoming some
of our cousins from the East but we
don't know what it is that they're
bringing in exact all we know is that
it's worth a dollar or two my brother
Gerald had word about it through this
Italian ravaccino he gave us the heads
up in exchange for a cut of the hall
well the information is legit first off
I cannot focus right now
across this Guinea for a second we
wouldn't be working for him if our
family still had the same status it did
back in the day but that's another story
am I going to hear this story
around my family hears about the old
days just wait oh yeah Ray Pacino's a
slimy [\h__\h] the one thing you can
rely on him for is greed I'm too small
time to be worth setting up so the one
angle he can be playing is the Casual
makes sense yeah he'll probably try to
give us a fraction or whatever this
stuff's worth but it'll be a fun night
depends on what you think is fun a
stealing gunfire Car Chasers all the
usual stuff I still can't focus what is
he talking about general population I'm
not so sure general population that's a
prison tournament you ever been inside
in Europe they do things different there
not so much of the fun in the shower
that you guys have here in America must
have been a real disappointment but a
guy like you thought he was going to be
real popular with the lifers did no one
pay you any attention as I said the
whole prison [\h__\h] thing is an American
phenomenon it don't happen on the other
side of the ocean well you got to do
something over here see what you've been
missing out on and you chased European
jails on that send me a postcard
dangerous sometime will do might even
put you on the visitors list I'd be
[\h__\h] touched you'd be touched if you
did some time that's for sure if they'd
be able to touch me I got some moves
you're a good man Nico I like you not
enough fun in the showers kind of way
you know yeah yeah
go back to that topic
was he okay was he trying to uh do a
cool skating move on the on this bridge
ceiling thingy railing thingy
like he's on the skateboard
oh
absolutely
snaking my way through you
okay
so wow what is that Poseidon or what
it's got a trident
[Music]
do they really have this in New York
pretty impressive
[Music]
I would think that that really exists
but do we have any people who've seen it
who can confirm
Buddha's dad
[Music]
and Old City there's lots of stuff there
it's freaking fancy wait the Sun is
going down but we're still on the same
day right as when I got the request for
coming to the interview
[Music]
it's still the same
music can we can we not listen to music
for a little bit because it's like
always distracting me
all right here we are what's the plan
and we keep on the roof of that
warehouse
so we can scope that [\h__\h] out we're
going this way
oh okay
follow Packy
let's let's not mess up my suit though
because I got a job interview okay I
don't want any blood or stains or
wrinkles wrinkles on my suit
[Music]
because I probably don't have time
to bring it to the cleaners
wow so in sync
and now
what now dude
oh
a [\h__\h]
didn't work man
I'll try again
wait wait wait for me
I want to do that too
parkour
it's even worse than the the off the
office but core
how
I'm trying bastard
they don't like momentum
Shimmy Shimmy Shimmy Sammy Sammy Sammy
look but it's the same button same key
as jumping so of course it will make me
fall off
or more shimmy yang
if this time for real
no
well that was unfortunate
it's because the game is stupid it won't
let me just jump on it diagonally
not my fault
it's kind of being like super slow in
order for the game to recognize what you
want to do
uh
the input
okay and now
get up
sorry to keep you waiting ah
now what now
I'll get here on my own time
huh what
this is where the deal's meant to be
going down can I throw a grenade
and here's the boat right on time
okay
see those boxes on the back of the boat
they must be bringing clone meds
meds yeah they're cloning people
Housewives cutting their wrists and make
their husbands get wood meds Molly
sedatives antidepressants meant
okay how do we do it we'll wait until
the truck is loaded then we'll take it
simple as that um
I'll cover you from up here while you're
down on the ground cleaning up these
better be some good [\h__\h] pills the
housewives better be grateful
climb down the mini cabin to get to the
ground
okay
uh yeah
still the truck
should I kill some people before I do
that
yeah man have Adam
yes it's a yes
honestly wait maybe maybe the grenade is
a good idea because I can get all the
ones in the middle
but it's difficult to aim you know
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
that escalated quickly
[Music]
oh
oh my God
yeah it was a good choice to show some
people first but oh my God
[Music]
yeah
wait
ah
[\h__\h] me Bush me
how you still alive
it's so loud
oh [\h__\h]
we got him
no we got him now we got him I think we
can go down there might still be some
alive but
[Music]
y'all being my health is there any Med
packs like for for once I actually
really need them
and I'm doubting it
foreign
what did I run into
um
get it quickly come on come on
come here
come on
ain't got no time
all right all right Nico you drive I'll
take out anyone who tries to follow us
here and Drive West
all right please don't tell me I also
got a Dodge Police though
go to the lock up here we go
quicker it is a really [\h__\h] slow
truck I'm trying my best here also it's
kind of tilted
why is it so angled did they shoot my
hands [\h__\h] put you down are they
calling me
of course they are okay it makes a lot
of sense yeah yeah
coming
it's not like to be robbed again
what the hell oh my God
oh my God it's so loud
he's sabotaging himself
[Music]
okay nice turn
holy [\h__\h] stop shooting
peaceful
let's just be friends
grenades well he's the one shooting
right he's supposed to take care of it
yeah
[Music]
oh God
oh
[Music]
that was good I think
wait if I rate my quest marker then
we're safe right
ah [\h__\h]
um okay we're already safe
easy
I feel like I I had oh now I have two
uh lost tires so I feel like I had one
since the beginning they must have shot
it really early on
[Laughter]
only a professional driver can still
drive a car that's so [\h__\h] up
all safe and sound whole truckload of it
one of the wives and Mistresses are
gonna be happy when them men get a hold
of those whole City's gonna be hard in a
few days time
he's an absolute savior couldn't have
done it without him
Nico come over here
Nanny Smith bastards [\h__\h] Guinea I
work for whoever's paying yeah I might
give you a call sometime get in Packy
hey I'll catch you around man
it's night time now huh
hi Miss passing tick tock tick tock tick
tock
[Music]
all right 7 500.
the Moon is about to fall on us guys
It's The End
where is the
um job interview gonna be anyway
probably on This Island right so
I don't know what to do until then dawn
of the final day
yeah but you always mask reference
South part of the Middle Island oh okay
what's this
what do I do until then
I guess I'll listen to one of these
Playboy
heal up I would like to
wait and maybe we make
well ah
I don't know if any food stands in that
area there must be some
but otherwise I guess we can try going
to clucking battle for once
Justice once will go to the rivals
list
[Music]
it's famous
I'm more famous than you
and I don't even need to tell you
I don't feel the need to tell you
also was a burger joint really
man I don't know if they don't show it
on the minimap then I have no idea
whoa
this speed was kind of nice with the
bridge
wait but this is the Time Square right
so it
oh we can go to Burger shots here
wait this is really uh amazing though if
that's realistic like right before the
Times Square if you look over there in
the night and you see a glowing bridge
if that's really how it is
then that's freaking beautiful
no
it's miniature everything is closer
let's look at these Burgers let's give
them a shot shall we huh the bleeder
Heart Stopper
sexy one with no 6 lb Burger
meat-free meal torpedo meal money shot
meal what can I get sir
just a bleeder I have no choice okay
six pounds I don't know how much that is
it doesn't feel like much to me
am I getting my burger what can I do I'm
just standing here
don't say that to a customer
okay nice heel
yours
was yummy four messages
um
so I just lived a tree story about us
and I'm trying at the fish market when I
was looking for some hot amateur [\h__\h]
online totally killed my uh-huh okay
um who
who the [\h__\h] are you
oopsie
I want to read more messages
ah
and I have more messages how do I use
this venue again here
meet me at the station from when is this
Roman what's the point in owning a car
service if you can't all right I was
supposed to ah you can't read it I was
supposed to answer these messages right
um
okay
I should uh
what's the point now if you can't give a
family free rides come if you want me to
send ah
that's what that was about
oh is that is the Burger Joint ah it's
marked on my map now too okay so I have
to go to them once
before Mark said okay cool cool
now we still have 12 hours
[Music]
let's go to the x
thank you God because that collateral
damage
well that's a little damage oh a
policeman
with their donuts and their coffees
Donuts did you notice infoamuku's uh uh
uh W they talked about ponderlingo
I told you about ponderlingo just just a
little while ago remember
oh it's so yummy so much yeah
did you think of me when you heard that
Nico what's this I hear about you
running with Patrick McCreary now these
days he's got work and he's a good guy
you're not planning on taking him down
though lay off for me
God damn brother you idiot Becky
McCreery Francis McCreery it's all
starting to make sense
my new Irish families were big but they
didn't no it wasn't a hint I didn't know
they liked pondering the size of Liberty
City yeah just thank the Lord you ran
into packing and not my other brothers
package just a hood but Gerald is into
some serious [\h__\h] and Derek he's the
worst that that [\h__\h] ever comes back
from Ireland I can't be held responsible
for what I do my brother
trust me on that you know what me and
Packy get along maybe if doing what you
do is good then I want to be look at my
beautiful spatial awareness
wow
Flawless execution anyway
yeah donuts donuts or not Donuts
is best it's the one with the like round
balls
that are like stuck to each other
and they're really like
um texture
I want to eat them
I miss I missponding
never had one before well if you ever go
to Japan
put the uh was it from Dunkin Donuts I'm
not sure
or Mr no it was for Mr Donuts Mr miso
dog
put Mr Donuts on your have to go list
and I mean the other Donuts are fine too
but ponderingo is just um different kind
of level you know
foreign
how are you
chilling it's all good
well mostly good mostly
yeah the wings yeah getting on my nerves
Mr Donuts pushing me man
but whatever we spoke about that [\h__\h]
already
I give him time he's just out of prison
for real listen G Dwayne ain't the only
thing I got on my mind I'm gonna eat
some chalky no
some motherfucker's been calling me a
phony calling me a snitch calling me all
kinds of [\h__\h] big deal yeah big deal
damn right until I discover that same
[\h__\h] well he's got some real
loose lips
so bad at billyard so you'll need this
guy silenced yeah he hangs out oh wait
is it not called billiard in English was
it like pool okay what does he look like
well son ain't too diesel in that
he a regular looking dude Nami now he
don't flash as well but you can see it
in his eyes okay hey
Homie Ain't Too Brolly but he ain't
scrawny neither and he'd be staling on
him a little you dig what I mean he
ain't too bummy but he grind me too what
so he's the average one look
he's brown skin B
um
but sometimes abandoned look I need more
than that to go on Jesus
take this head down there take a photo
send it to me I'll point out which one
of them [\h__\h] it is right and
that's a little gift for you oh
he's giving me a phone with the function
of taking photos imagine
oh
let's go
we got some high-tech [\h__\h]
um
I appreciate it can I take a selfie too
technology
I mean with our amount of money we could
have afforded it ourselves as well
um
right now
I follow yellow line
no brain no thinking stop
[Music]
okay
and that's why the penetrators ain't
doing nothing this season they got no
one who can work the lanes man
[\h__\h] Lieutenant that's something I was
forced into from the necessity of my
financial situation my body is forced to
Rob and deal in order to sustain my own
well-being and that of my immediate
family
okay how
oh
Mouse to move the camera
there's a [\h__\h] down [\h__\h] cars
what the [\h__\h] is that
now
I can't turn it anymore I have to
maybe drive around
but I don't want to be noticed to do a
h
what
I can't get out okay
until oh like this
pretty bad quality though
does that work though
is that even can you make anything from
that
did she send me a message
what's that sign on the oh there we go
that ain't Marlin take another photo of
that cat and send it to me cat
what which one not the free ones in the
middle
what about what about them
but I feel like it should be the ones in
the middle
um
right that's that's not them
they're another group neighbor yeah but
I guess I need it to be closer
um
here
um does the face need to be visible from
the front
can I can I can I go in really
am I not gonna get in trouble
huh
here this should be good enough if it's
the yellow one then I would say this is
good enough but it's probably not the
yellow one
right
this they would surely already beat me
up by now for taking
huh they're looking at me and he's
calling me
mom is the one dressed like a damn
Canary
oh it was him get rid of him how did
they know it's like they knew it's like
he's about to get a message that
confirms it's them
take him down but I'm gonna take
everyone down I suppose
[\h__\h]
okay
okay okay
get in this fancy cup yeah exactly like
that through the door that's right
yeah yay police will never know I did it
right I did it
I did it
[Music]
I'm your man I've done your job
is dead
you're so the police wow
police didn't give a [\h__\h] they couldn't
care enough to uh chase me for more than
one second
week anyway oh [\h__\h] what time is it six
six A.M
[Music]
I don't know risk too much now right six
more hours do you think I have time to
talk to Dwayne
[Music]
yeah
no maybe
um
let's just talk let's let's just talk
and then perhaps we do
the rest of whatever he wants us to do
afterwards
we're gonna lose that car again am I not
Michelle who's Michelle okay Nico it's
me yeah who are you the [\h__\h] can you
remind me that doesn't
mean
nah nah I'm not gonna
no I'm not stupid Michelle who do you
think I am
Dwayne
what's up man
not much wait what what's wrong Twain
he seems so vulnerable
prison was easy compared to this [\h__\h]
really sure it was
[\h__\h] it man
[\h__\h] it all
I mean he used to have every
everything I used to run uptown Bohan
all that [\h__\h]
the music makes them feel even more
vulnerable
I wanna give him a hug
I ain't got the energy no more
stabbed in the back too many [\h__\h]
probably literally and figuratively
for you I mean nah
[\h__\h] that come on man stop being so
miserable what did you lose
a real gentleman's place no place for me
triangle
talking real class you know what I'm
saying okay when I went down some
[\h__\h] I want to see that
I'll clean out the squad
the problem that your favorite strip
club got taken over what
ah we'll talk about that later
truth
is that the one I went to
is it different one
time
that took like an hour okay
we good on time it's the same one oh
well I have very very much sentimental
feelings towards that club of course you
know
I want to help I didn't think I would go
back there but I I guess we will however
I don't know if there's enough time to
finish this so I'll just I guess chill
around this area
in a taxi to go there
um
ah sorry ah sorry no no I I no I
wait the stock goes when I take over
taxes right last time it didn't end well
I didn't want to I just wanted to get in
on the back
but it was occupied anyway
uh what about this one it's sorry
please wait
no no no
no that's not what I wanted to do
you hold it why does the game not really
tell me that that's a nice car
[\h__\h] okay
uh I'm gonna get another burger then
okay
pressing F longer where will I have to
go anyway for the job interview I can't
believe they're not like telling me
beforehand how am I supposed to be on
time
if they won't tell me where it is
I have a suit look at me
ah because I started
what do you want huh [\h__\h] you
you don't want trouble with me
believe me
I'm having mercy on you right now
I have to finish the mission
okay
why is that Pastor still following me
he won't hit me while I'm doing this
Get Wrecked okay
[Music]
why
okay
okay stay out of trouble
stay out of trouble
[Music]
okay so uh we gotta quickly very quickly
finish this I suppose this is swearing
me
or should I
should I quickly get into a cap because
that's faster to get there
oh can I cancel it
okay
then I think that's smarter to do
because I don't think there's enough
time to finish a whole mission like this
oh
cancel
press E when you see a taxi okay okay
I'll remember
[Music]
use the phone and call Dwayne
thank you
I doesn't want to talk to me though
um
maybe if I
[Music]
organizer
yeah I got the interview
you know that
reload oof
ah
Majid there that was like
uh
a while ago
hey what if I'm late to the interview
what do you mean I'm overthinking it I
was told I can't do the interview if I'm
in the mission
the thing will just reschedule over
um then I'll try
you have hours after the Pierce
after 12
it will be moved to 24 hours later hmm
but then again I'll be like
trying to manage the time and fail at it
again
waffle out
sorry that must have hurt
okay Wiggly wiggling wiggling away
through
unsuccessfully
[Music]
I'll eventually run out of missions what
you mean these like side missions but
aren't they all like main missions
isn't me running out of missions me
finishing the game
[Music]
that was close Brucey
baby
I'm sorry fancy actually on my way to
the place where there's the naked ladies
no why
no one join me
man Brucie
the other half of my personality turned
him down I would have taken him with me
foreign
what already
no it's 10 but they
let me know now oh
okay
oh no way out we can take one of those
nice little cars
all right so what exactly is going on
here do I just kill everybody again
except the ladies perhaps
take out the free strip club managers oh
locate the matches by listening in on
the conversations is it bad if I already
have the gun out
let's see oh the latest are it
the ladies are panicking so it's
probably one of them is probably there
[Music]
man
yeah on the back
here no not here there's a gun free gun
uh
oh they're here for me
but those are not the managers right
where's the back
what does the back mean
this club oh oh don't worry we've
already uh
collateral damage
if I were to show the whole strip dance
uh from this club so
no worries I'm gonna kill everybody now
I guess
[Music]
I'm sorry not you lady
oh God
ah okay okay I was too Reckless I
admitted yes
I'm sorry
but wait but this way no wait what
happens when you
when you end up in the hospital I still
got my things do I do I not huh
the interview go [\h__\h] something came up
I didn't make it but maybe they'll
schedule another one they [\h__\h]
wait no I still have my things but I
gotta reload anyway so
but my last reload is this
the photo shoot
um
I forgot to retry it over the phone
ah wait I can still do it I thought it
was loading
okay
try again oh and this time
why don't we change in our strategy
maybe hide behind something and go
calmly
Condola
six it's six a.m again maybe if we hurry
now
because I gotta go straight to the strip
club right
hmm
if we hurry now
we might Maybe
squeezing everything
uh just need a taxi here's a taxi excuse
me e
H but he's got someone E look at all
them taxes coming for me
this one
may I may I be your passenger
long pressing no no no no what what no e
no it's not
I was pressing F really loud but he went
to the other ah because he's busy too
what the [\h__\h] what about you why all
these taxes taken this one
this one this one hey hey hey hey
over here can I get in thank you thank
you finally so where to yeah that
Waypoint uh
can you take me to Bronco Street yeah
okay then took them long enough to
finally accept me I thought they had a
problem with me as a person
um
okay here we are then that's uh very
kind of you the right place
I need to go up there I think
Mamma Mia why would you
drop me up there
bike
this is so hard to bring me up here
really
okay
Maybe
walk in without
this way yeah thank you
oh God
well I know already where he is
at least one of them excuse me
so now it's time we're gonna get some
wood you're gonna have to wait okay
okay we're gonna rock it now
rock and roll baby
that may have been just a normal
customer I'm sorry about that
it's like confetti
I might be killing some ladies I'm not
sure
oh
okay
the lights are confusing me on me
is that hitting the wall
as you did
God
and God and God and got him oh
the mini map
I see something yeah but
from here I can't see
I just want to clear everything up
before I run through oh
can he escape
oh nice nice nice nice nice
[Music]
okay I'll take cover
I don't see him oh my God
this one
did I did I get him yet no I didn't I
still didn't get him
wait ah they're coming
what there's a big one here or is it
outside
this one
private stuff only okay whoo
okay
they're here
I know he's not here
you lied to me
I think I got him
and police is so no no no no
[Music]
no
let's go
were they just waiting in the car the
whole time
[Music]
sure thing we saved the Triangle Club
yay
the Illuminati script strip script
script club strip club
[Music]
what time is it
hey we can still make it to the
times
right because now the mission is over
right is it is it
it's over I think it's over
I have a message
You've Got Mail
why at this evening why I could have
made 12.
okay at least it's still the same day
hmm okay
I need formal shoes really
really
check your emails bro there's some work
for you it's paying heavy bro hello bro
[Music]
um
okay
okay if we got so much time clothing
store
or like this one actually and
is there uh there's this one
this one is there any more
armor places I want to buy armor
[Music]
per sales only what does that mean I
gotta head to purchase ah for the for
the shoes okay
the fancy shoe place hi kiwawa hey
hey so
I'll I'll turkey maybe she has some
armor for me
but she needs
oh and we can't share
I gotta get my own armor
Mallory
I'm getting worried
he likes to party romance
didn't get back last night
what happened with my man bro man
we gotta take him out bowling soon at
least once this episode I promise
serious about it this time
last time it was about swings and strip
clubs this time it's about bowling okay
we gotta we got a set priorities and
sometimes we gotta take care of your
homies
you know
this this is the season of bowling
yes
I'm serious
mascara
[Music]
nice car thank you
wanna want to ride
oh wait
Playboy
you got a problem with it hey that's
what I was doing don't help him out when
it [\h__\h] up my business
thank you
why he mad now I was just counting damn
he needs a friend too okay
I'm just everybody's [\h__\h] right now so
I'm just doing whatever everybody wants
okay okay
a robot
[Music]
I just function on whatever people want
from me
no music yeah I don't know the music
froze off my focus
we can listen to it again eventually
wait I drove past the store
are the shoes really necessary
[Music]
okay here we are
at Louis Vuitton I have a reservation
please somebody uh where's my Ops I'm so
sorry so I'm so sorry I'm so sorry is
there somebody who can help me find the
right size of shoes for me
[Music]
here they are oh
yes yes black oxford okay
200 bucks Brown Oxford
beige oh
light colors
oh sweet books
nah don't like those
black wingtips nah I like the oxfords
actually
yeah but I think I'm gonna go for the
light one the beige one
me liking
uh bye
excellent times if you don't mind me
saying
hmm
yes
this one's nice too
should I get a new suit
a new suit
two suits better than one suit
[Music]
why not yeah we got enough money right
will I ever need like a lot of money in
this game
but then with this one I don't know if
the shoes really work well but you know
I want
them why not
somebody said something about glasses do
they actually have glasses
I don't see any man look where the [\h__\h]
ing access
separate
fancy I was never in a store like this
before never
I don't see any like accessory stuff
that I could get
visit us again soon visit us again soon
uh-huh
okay we styling we're looking really
fresh
so next what was I saying I want some
armor right uh
it's kind of far
but we can make it
I don't know
[Music]
only in Russian store the first store in
the game oh okay
hmm
nahuna
[Music]
it's on the way to the interview oh I
guess so I kind of also want to get some
food but
what's going
on
what how did I do that
they enter some kind of different
dimension
what happened
oh spin give I a call if you need some
cash I and Batman usually got some jobs
easy okay thank you for letting me know
I will forget about that immediately
uh let me get some food really quickly
yeah was that a glitch or what was that
no
hey welcome to Burger chart how can I
help you
I would like the
what are you making it did you take my
order I like the bleeder please
[Laughter]
I thought it would never end
I would like an
um
that's is that was that San Andreas by
the way the I I like uh
um
[Music]
yeah
damn it
looking forward to experiencing that
sometime someday
ah
what the hell
Ah that's crazy Cleveland
show
okay we're gonna get that what time is
it the armor okay we still have plenty
of time we're gonna get the armor
and then we'll make our way back maybe
wait maybe I can tell your tangent until
the interview
starts because I'm not gonna miss it
again
not this time
is
[Music]
all right I wish I could stock up on our
murder
that would be convenient
I can just buy several
that's not it
where is it
this one no on the map that's literally
it is downstairs right
[Music]
it's my first time here oh damn wow I
like this uh atmosphere
[Music]
um
how much are the grenades because I
wasted so many of mine
maybe I buy some how do I buy them
I take I take this please
no
let's play mode checkbox
I don't get that yet I guess that's not
even grenades that's just the the
for the
thanks for this like grenade launcher
the
ammunition
yes you got it so dark I can actually
not see anything
but I don't need anything else right
just this is fine although wait this
this is a grenade
a per grenade
the [\h__\h]
foreign
no need then
I don't
need them so
Alex I got the armor
Nico
[Music]
how did the big real estate deal go
that kid wants to shut down the side and
[\h__\h] let me get a memorial to union
workers who've died in accidents and
[\h__\h] yourself on me I got bigger
problems come see me now yeah but uh
where
um
also is it urgent can I go to my
interview first this dude's asking for
me but I need to go here
can I go there early and started early
otherwise I'll just tangent like I said
interview first okay
what is the car
do not police it to the report
I just I just went there guys I just
went there I just let it happen
haha
I'll bring it back
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is rigged
there we go
oh big building
Goldberg lignor and scheister
like liner
what a weird ass name
I could go early but
final interview it's my first interview
oh
you know
uh it's Nico Bellic I'm here for an
interview
fancy looks damn
with all that money
does he really still need to be doing
more of these jobs
lignor it's not Wagner it's lickner
apparently I'll just see if Mr Goldberg
is available
Mr Goldberg Mr bellock has arrived for
his interview
okay great uh tell them to come through
to my office would you please follow me
Mr bellick yeah huh
oh
who are those such a
[Music]
hydration guys
sorry I wasn't listening lady boy are
you in trouble if you get in his way
I always get nervous before interviews
is this like
it's more hydration
don't be nervous he doesn't bite okay
well maybe I'll bite
oh he's looking at my resumes he's
prepared
I'm looking for a man who can get jobs
done right
Nikolai I like your resume you seem to
be the sort of man who would go the
extra distance yeah I mean I've came
from Europe get myself reacquainted with
your experience
when you're ready to stand up an email
[Music]
a guy who looks at the world sees
problems and tries to fix them yeah yeah
that's me my problem is that people
don't notice the Decay let's listen a
bit more they leave the Decay alone and
soon it's too late so you have to pull
the whole tooth um
I am the guy who goes around shaking
people for people read Society read City
Hall I shake them and I say floss are
you actually a dentist by any chance
prevent Decay you're talking too much
about teeth
it's not
you don't know why because the law is
clear
what's the name of that cop I may know
him actually
[Music]
what about me here
sure stand up if you want to what makes
you comfortable I mean
we tripped fast
retrieving retrieve
d
I was never here you understand
now it's just ah
well at least I got the armor
okay uh where whoa
why are we on this wait second floor but
uh the action was there right
run faster
and locked
what about the exit here
thank you for opening the door for me
three stars here we go
uh
the car of my choice will be what if I
take a a hot dog now would that
fix
the situation I'm in
truck
no the truck is hard to control
I want a donut and a hot dog [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] there's no cars
run run
uh why is there no cars
did they want me to take the truck
because this is a weird amount of no
cars
uh okay
total a problem this one
okay oh there's some normal cars
I take I take a car
wait wait wait wait
thank you thank you for leaving thank
you
I mean finally sorry for the little walk
around the block I I needed some fresh
air
okay Highway baby
this is my
chance
OH police cars
wow I think I chose the right car I have
like a lot of
power with this
and I think it's time for music again
not that one though
[Music]
find the right station excuse me
there we go
sure fine
let's listen to Kobo
[Music]
so fitting Cobble is so honestly she has
criminal potential in herself
Ah that's a problem
no no no thanks nice physics game
[Music]
where do I go
too bad there's police there
whoa
otherwise I would have been out of the
circle
foreign
[Music]
for you cannot trust love
just a distraction
[Music]
I was just chilling
if I go into clothing stores it's uh it
cancels it right
in the helicopter saw me no
it doesn't what the [\h__\h] okay
I am a 2012 time for a new car
done
I thought someone told me before
that
what the [\h__\h] lag
once you enter or was it like
like something else that you have to
enter was it in GTA 5
[\h__\h]
uh
assistant
not with this car
[Music]
um
well Fort said Brute Force
[Music]
me
no go away
wait ah you also went there huh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
put your hands up
[Music]
dangerous doggies
mentality I feel like I can do this
[Music]
oh
because the police is right in front of
your face put your hands up or you're
gonna be arrested
[\h__\h] I'm never getting up
one in the car
[Music]
s
I think
[Music]
I wanna swap cars but they're all on my
end
this this one that's just on my ass all
the time
thank you forever
[Music]
nice I handled that one better than him
[Applause]
[Music]
put your put your hands up what
about my car
which one
this one or
pain and pain and Sprout car wash car
wash works too or paint spray
thank God we just just so happened to be
there
okay okay I
uh
it's got a park properly into the garage
or whatever they have
yo it's already opening up for me
[Music]
[Applause]
but what now
wait what's happening
but what's happening why is it not
working
why is it not working we're all
celebrating I thought it was happening
[Applause]
oh
wait one more try one more try
it's gonna be faster
[Music]
no they still there
I can't control this car anymore
[Music]
I want I want the pink arm
no
no no
[Music]
so fast
[Applause]
[Music]
[\h__\h] seat belt what didn't he have
time to put on
no logic behind that no logic behind
that one
can I get a hot dog
give me give me no why not
why not
I'm dying
it's a hot dog person shouldn't you be
helping Humanity huh your job is the
same as the people in the hospital you
know feeding people is as important as
operating on people
[Music]
I am going to die
it doesn't run fast enough
no
it's hot dog I'm not even gonna try they
don't want to give me hot dogs when I'm
being chased is that what it is
I don't think that people are moving the
cars the police cars
yo yo
[Music]
all right guys we cooking we're cooking
we're cooking
[Music]
I am I have no crimes on me I am
innocent
[Music]
Eternal Chase
this this could be it this could be it
unless it's not it no please be it
please be it there's a helicopter
um
I thought that was it
[Music]
this is the longest Chase I've ever
experienced I must be on all TV channels
by now
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
can I drive through it last time I tried
that it wasn't really possible
[Music]
all right
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
they're all stuck I think they're all
stuck
stuck to all [\h__\h] stuck [\h__\h]
idiots all stuck
is that another police Roblox
[Music]
this way
can I go down
here oh it's so quiet
there's
um they're everywhere
[Music]
oh
yeah
there's some normal cars there I could
take them please wait for me
four stars is fast
I need to spray I need to spray I need
to spray
with this there's uh maybe at this point
here or here
[Music]
in your car first yeah yeah yeah yeah I
know
right one closer you think so
but I need to get past all of this
police
I got no choice
okay
they can't charge me for this crime
because I don't have a car walking
through is okay I think
um
I just don't want to take the police car
because like that in itself this doesn't
seem like a smart choice
what's down here
I will die if I jump down here
was that is that fault there's fall
damage right
hurry alone no
yes
cover me and make a move please don't
make a move please don't make a move
please don't make
a move well not there's someone like
right behind me are they on foot I can't
look back I can't afford to look back
oh
okay that's on the police part okay nice
nice I sensed the waters
no
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I tried so hard
and I failed
I got so far I I I got far in distance
but somehow it all just became worse and
worse and worse
what's happening are we about to have
our interview or
what's going on
idiot
it didn't [\h__\h] matter
I tried so hard and got so far
use the knife to kill
is that really like a
helpful
a good idea
[Music]
no okay
we're getting armor again
might as well
hopefully it will not be as difficult to
escape as it just was
how you doing
all right how you doing
you did recently do it with a knife
[Music]
yeah me just eating a hot dog in the
middle of all this was just
perfect
[Music]
okay I'll try with a knife
but that seems almost too easy if that
really works like the
uh
[Music]
yeah breaking the wind that was actually
like a little bit of a thought that I
had while it was going on I noticed the
window and I was thinking should I could
I like shoot the window and jump out
there but uh it's nickel Bellic
Nicole I know I know we went for a lot
of [\h__\h] just now but don't be so
aggressive
I'll just see if Mr Goldberg is
available
yeah some people a lot of people are
saying it won't work
[Music]
knife
I mean we can we might as well try it
if it has the same effect as the
gun then
I mean
whatever
goal swim you know can I go in just in
here okay hello Nico
okay
take another look
waited with your experience hmm
yeah what's with the horn
doesn't wait to get told what to do a
guy who looks at the world sees problems
the armor in full health I could
definitely make the jump out of the
window
they leave the Decay alone and soon it's
too late so you actually pull the whole
tooth
yeah standing up assertive move right I
I like do I still want to escape for the
window can I though I am the guy who
goes around shaking people for people
read Society read City Hall I can't do
it and I say floss
get rid of the Rotting Flesh stuck in
your teeth I can't Decay mouthwash you
hear me
there's this cop good cop but he thinks
he's where are the files for your case
against me
wait [\h__\h]
why did you have to show that at the end
[Music]
you didn't see anything okay
so come on
yeah
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
you can't I tried so hard and I didn't
come at all far
where am I
was right in front of it this is like
how I was like trying to climb the ledge
thingy
it just won't let me because it doesn't
understand what I'm trying to do
it's really dumb
getting armored again do you have to
kill him I think so
that's
what I've been asked to do
[Music]
okay
one more time
[Music]
a car
without police car attached to it please
how about this one
oh
[Music]
I can listen to this unfortunately even
though it's funny
[Music]
when I want to go to the remixes
no whatever we're not gonna be listening
for it till for long because we're
switching we're getting out of this in
the moment
[Music]
can't always
Corner I've got things to do how do I
how do I do it should I try again
through the window but
[Music]
um
I don't know
wait for him to walk to the window does
he do that Mr Bellic welcome I'll just
see if Mr Goldberg is available
push him out of the chair Mr bellock has
arrived for his interview but it seems
scripted so that the lady comes in the
moment I pick up the documents anyway
and then she tells everybody
because or is it when does it not happen
if I don't shoot does it really not
happen
I seems scripted to me
uh whatever whatever
Brute Force we're doing it the Brute
Force way
experience
[Music]
but I don't know about the window
world
yeah I'm the guy who goes around what
are you doing nothing people read
Society reads City Hall
and I say floss get rid of the Rotting
Flesh
oh
okay please do not I was never here you
understand
what I hate this
book
what is he doing oh thank God
okay uh why is the street always so
empty at moments like this
why
okay here's a car
here's the car
good night
okay
let's not angry the police anymore let's
stay on two stars okay let's just stay
on two stars
[Music]
and I don't know if it will work but I I
might give
this a try I'll try although I can't
um will they always block the big
highways or is it only at a certain
amount of stars maybe I should try this
one then
[Music]
okay here we go but I feel like they're
always so close on my butt I can't feel
the the spray thing
[Music]
going on
I'm really full of stress now I need to
get out of this mess okay looking good
we're out of the circle
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
thank God
Mamma Mia
[Music]
dios Mayo
oh
wow
wow wow wow wow
[Music]
the first one yeah it was it was funny
everything going wrong
wrong door
everything going wrong was quite funny
nah
finally the chase is over
the chase of a lifetime
here are the files great Peace at Last I
feel cleansed me too you silence
Goldberg too right I don't need to worry
about him he's done whoa music to my
ears a weight has been lifted here's
your payment thank you how much
this music
a thousand bucks for all that [\h__\h] I
just went through
really
ah
what emperor she found me down really
[Music]
there's a quest going on here might as
well start it
Francis page so bad
is it just him
yes I'll make commissioner
no I don't care about packing listen Ma
I've got to go
I love you too
good to see you I'm sure
uh you know it's funny but I see a lot
of me in you
why why
you know there's no good and no evil
just shades of [\h__\h] great in this
game yes
lots of gray one percent better that's
enough
if you say so oh I do say so I want to
make things a bit better by any means
necessary and you what do you want
I want to get paid more than a thousand
bucks please yeah sure you do
so listen
I got something I need you to do
what's this this is the last time of
course
drug dealer is holed up in a tower Block
in East Holland this scumbag's been
pushing drugs pimping women you name it
he's done it
I need him dealt with isn't that police
work
good
and the Moon
it isn't what
um excuse me the guy's guilty is sin he
is sin yeah why do you not take care of
him it'll take me a year to get the
evidence more maybe
and maybe good men will get taken down
by that evidence maybe people make
mistakes
but this guy is scum
how much how much
um
this time we ask upfront good money what
is good money two G's who 2 000
yeah yeah thank you you know let's get
our monies or our times with some fresh
off the boat killer with more balls and
brains I say it was about right
okay you got a deal head on off the
vauxite and call me nice
he knows what he's worth and what his
jobs are worth thank God Nicole
good Hagler
now even 5K is yeah if you think if you
think about it but let's not think about
it thinking is illegal
ah okay where where does it lead me
up there
what do I have marked other spray
uh-huh
[Music]
okay
let me tell you a tangent what tangent
do you want I can tell you Japan
tangents I mean there's not endless
amounts of Japan tendons because I
wasn't even there for so long
and I was busy
people in there
but let me turn off the music for that
time
okay
well do you know did Muma or bales tell
anything about the shopping
laughs
did they tell anything does anyone know
when we did a little bit
so there was this one day where
um I wanted to eat
this was after the horotoni
English-speaking hoteli collab I wanted
to eat like something special so I
looked up some special places and I
found this like pancake place
uh didn't I only have pancakes but it
had some really special pancakes so I
wanted to eat them so I I had janma join
me and I asked because Elena was busy
after the collapse I asked what do you
want to join
and then we may joined
so the thing is women kept on saying
that she kind of has like plans with
Bales later she doesn't know when they
start and Bales doesn't like Bale still
has to get back to her to tell her when
they meet and where they meet and be
blah blue so it was kind of like
uncertain
uh but eventually we took off uh oh and
movement's manager also joined
so it was like two managers and me and
mumei went to get some
yummy pancakes and optionally maybe some
normal food as well
and yeah so we took a taxi and after the
collab and finally we arrived it was
quite all right and then
it was so cute the whole like Cafe
outside it's really cute
really like unusual definitely not like
Japanese style
um it was really really interesting
so it was already Charming from the
outside it was really popular though so
we had to wait a little bit to get a
seat like maybe
10 minutes or so
and and we finally get in and we're
really excited start eating and we were
really hungry too I think and I think on
the ride until we got there me and mume
were also talking about like chronic
pain and this and that
feel like we have different kinds of
chronic pain but uh or like General pain
but we do relate about pain a little bit
I think yeah
so yeah we were bonding about pain don't
call us old people you don't have to be
old to be in pain
um
yeah and then we got into the cafe and
we ordered so okay it was mostly because
I chose the place
and we were four people and they were
like you know
we had the chance to have four different
beautiful pancakes so I ordered I asked
I asked everybody if it's okay but I
just wanted we got some normal food too
oh yeah I shared first I shared omurai
with mume and the managers had some
normal food too but then we had the
pancakes yeah four different fancy
pancakes like one was with I think like
oranges
orange themed one was I think kiwi kiwi
themed one was like strawberry themed
and one
maybe melon might have been melon like
uh not watermelon but the the greenish
melon Honey Melon
I think that was it so
they all were topped with like a [\h__\h]
ton of like what was it cream cheese
some fluffy cream cheese
and stuff yeah honeydew Maybe
um
uh they looked visually so appealing I
might show you guys a picture uh later
on but it looked so beautiful you know I
took a picture of all of them together
and then we started eating and
yeah we quickly regretted getting four
of them because they were quite filling
and
um
not even that good
at least the ones there was like one
that was
better in my opinion but then three of
them were like from the same kind of
like
um series of Pancakes and they just had
like so much of that cream cheese stuff
or whatever that was
and I don't know it was just kind of
weird
um
yeah but but but but
it doesn't matter if it doesn't taste
like as good as it looks because
I just wanted to eat interesting things
that you can't get in other places you
know yeah and then eventually
uh manages to get a hold of Bales and
she
um Bales joins us and we were like
really happy because we thought she
could help us finish the pancakes and
then Bales arrives and she's like what I
don't I don't I don't like sweet things
so she couldn't help us
ah
and we had to leave quite a bit of food
we tried though we tried our best Bales
was not helpful with the pancakes
were planning on going shopping and I
kind of wanted to go shopping on that
day too coincidentally after eating the
pancakes and I didn't really want to
like force myself
um into their group so I was like no no
you you two can go on your own I am fine
I'll go alone blah
but mommy
kind of insisted on that it would be
fine for me to join So eventually I was
like okay
okay
yeah uh I felt
I felt bad but I joined them so they
however wanted to originally go to
different kind of place they wanted to
go to like a department store like in
Japan
um like at stations on the ground
stations especially big stations they
often have like like in the underground
Department
stores
that are they don't sell like Harajuku
fashion usually they sell a little bit
more calm down mature clothes
and yeah it's like they all have like
their own nice
um
what's it called
I forgot but you know it's like little
little small stores one by one next to
each other on the ground
and and I normally don't go shopping
there
when I'm in Japan but I also don't like
going to ichimalukyu you know the 101
boutiques yeah it looks like boutiques
yeah
um but you know I told you about that
shopping place that's really stressful
because everybody screams at you like it
is
foreign
yeah
um I hate that and it's always so
crowded that that place is so crowded
but the good thing is that it's like one
shopping mall for a female clothes only
usually no maybe there's no it's really
just feel my clothes and they have shoes
they have bags and they have clothes
mostly and there's five five million
different brands there in there you know
so you can find so many different styles
just in this one building so I was
planning even though I hated it to go
there
and if I would go alone you know I could
just quickly Zoom through very quickly
just look for what I need buy it leave
it's it's not so bad when you go alone
but still I don't like it much
it is
but yeah so they wanted to go to the
department store but I said I kind of
wanted to go to ichimalukyu and so they
they were fine with that they agreed to
go there so we made our way to Shibuya
yeah it's in Shibuya it's the
10109 building
and
I immediately find something for myself
quite quickly and buy something really
fast and then that was on the first
floor and it has like I don't know
maybe eight nine floors of and per floor
there's like
maybe seven eight
shops Maybe
so it's a lot
so after I buy something
we go through and I I kind of
can't manage to find something that
interests me that much anymore but
bayels is looking for clothes too and
mama is looking for clothes but mume
warned us that she is really bad at
buying clothes and she wanted us to help
her but she also said it's like she she
is also bad at being shopped for so
yeah she was like very very insecure and
uh I I first I kind of I can't look for
clothes for myself and for her because
it's kind of like different things that
she's looking for
you know very different things
um yeah uh you know so it was difficult
for me eventually I just gave up after
like
getting to the the middle of the
building I kind of gave up
um
stop spamming when did this become story
time it's story time now deal with it so
let me tell this one story and then
we're all happy
and we finally reached like the middle
of the store and I kind of give up on
finding clubs for myself because mume
still hasn't found anything like
we just can't find anything
and then I focus me and Bale start
focusing on finding something for her
and we're really like
trying so hard we're looking at
everything but a lot of these like
fashion stores they just sell
clothes that are not not really what
we're looking for
um
and then we try out some things we send
mume into the dressing room and she
comes out and yeah a lot of the time
like the the fits of the dresses would
be kind of like awkward because it's
like bulky or whatever looks weird
so more and more I was getting tired and
it was getting exhausting because we
just couldn't find anything good it was
difficult because the problem is that
these stores they also usually only sell
one size and they call it one size
[Music]
so if you don't fit into this
standard one size
because you're too tall for example
then
[\h__\h] you're [\h__\h] and even if you
like maybe on the smaller side then
still you know you can have like
different shape of hips maybe your hips
are a little bit wider than Asian girls
or you know the Boba or whatever yeah
although the legs are just longer
proportions different for me often I can
make the Japanese one size work not
always but sometimes depends on the cut
of the clothes
but this was quite a hurdle to overcome
yeah
child bearing hips exactly
now finally we found like maybe one
outfit like yeah yeah one outfit that we
were like really happy about finally
finding something uh and that was like
we were already at the top of this
building we went through every shot we
went for every shop we would basically
go for every every shop
ah
it took so much time yeah but I I want
to I was like joking that me and Bales
we should both like go separate ways
get a like a budget and just buy
you know and then just bring it to mume
and then have her wear it and then she
should choose like you know like a
competition I thought that would have
been a fun idea but we didn't do it
maybe next time
and then I noticed like when I was like
choosing things for mermaid
every time I would choose something
where I was like oh this this could fit
her this could suit her this could look
good on her for some reason it always
almost always
was brown clothes
which color of her is influencing me but
Brown just looks good
man beige and brown it just looks good
on there yeah
typecasted
honestly it's just it just naturally
happens
agreed Brown just looks good yeah
Brown make it is her color yeah it's
it's so interesting
Brown looks so good on her hmm
it's not a problem Brown is nice I like
to wear brown clothes too
but literally all the clothes I would
pick out were Brown
almost all of them yeah
yeah but we got some clothes on women
luckily and a little bit of clothes for
me but yeah I wanted to buy shoes and I
uh kind of like
gave up right because I was focusing on
women and then the morning after my
shoes broke so I was like damn
I wish I would have bought shoes that
last night while we were already
shopping
if I had those now
I wouldn't be in trouble I did get them
that's one small thing
um I I was watching Japanese TV or was
it on YouTube maybe Japanese program on
YouTube I'm not sure but
um there was this program that just like
follows
people throughout the day I guess or
like just you know checks what they're
doing and there was this one guy who has
a little fixing shop for shoes and
suitcases and all that kind of stuff at
uh Narita Airport
yeah
a cobbler a cobbler that was the word
um
[Music]
that guy he was just like portrayed as a
magical cobbler uh in the in the in that
TV show
um because like he could fix anything
really fast and I found him I found him
at the Narita Airport I was looking
forward to finding him because I still
had my broken shoes and I brought it to
him I was like can you fix my shoes and
I felt like I was going to this like
famous place a famous person's shop and
was meeting a famous person and I had
this like I was like I was so like
excited I was smiling I was like you
know acting weird like as if I was
meeting a famous person and and I told
him I saw TV and he's like oh
like the whole time he was just like you
know acting so like normal and like he
doesn't really care you know but he was
nice and he he fixed it quickly and
everything was good his work was done
well and it was cheap yeah but I was
just like I felt like I just met a
famous person there
foreign
[Music]
but he can fix everything so fast I wish
he could fix my life no just kidding
yeah I didn't I didn't glue with myself
I had professional
do it um
I'm outside the project where is he
second floor keeps an eye on all his
boys from up there
see her in one way or another uh-huh
anyway these projects all got the same
layout a staircase leading up on either
side try to get off the ground floor
before getting violent violent me
does that mean trying to get off the
ground so does that mean get to the top
Francis McCreary is the community now
you're starting to see and then start
shooting
okay
what was the entrance
yeah sure man
can I
dude they're not very welcoming
but may I
I think upstairs for residents only I
know your white ass don't live in this
edition whatever they told me to not
shoot before
but it's like pass now well they should
let me
oh no
okay
you just crossed the line you punk ass
let's go
okay I need different guns
ah
Mamma Mia
so sorry I don't want to hurt y'all
this is just you know it's my job yeah
bae
I don't like the position I'm in either
you did
I think he I think he is
making extra sure
help me
[Music]
nice
I'm glad that works
what
that sounds like he's gonna throw down a
grenade or something what do you mean
man kid let's go
[Music]
appreciate it
okay my armor is gone
I saw you little rat
IO
oh John Wick I don't mind watching
another John Wick movie maybe sometime
also in the plane rides I've had so far
recently
they all had like a lot of John Wick
movies you know and I was like should I
watch it should I watch it but the whole
time I was thinking about what if I want
to watch another one was kfp hmm
I feel like I'm betraying you guys if I
watch too many movies on the plane rides
what I'm feeling like what if I would
where is he
I'm seeing
but I watched Mr Bean because I thought
I don't think I would watch this with
you guys but Mr Bean was so cute
honestly in hindsight maybe I should
have watched Mr Bean with you guys
because it was such a sweet cute movie
where's the guy by the way
I didn't expect anyone there
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I have a lot of uh fails today that was
him though right because it seemed like
no one was there
hmm
watch it with us again and I don't like
we were re-watching movies
but I never watched the other uh
Mr Bean movie there's another one right
I never watched that one
gonna try to get a cab this time
oh
taxi Maxi thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you hello are
you waiting for me or what
can I take you
oh the Waypoint please
take me to uranium Street good as gold
yeah
which one did you watch the one where he
goes to France that's great it was so
cute really liked it
oh yeah yesterday we and my members we
watched Belle the anime movie from 2021
it was really nice it was with a pretty
no regretty spaghetti glad we watched
that
wait didn't I come in here first with uh
armor and now I don't have armor
okay [\h__\h] you
unfortunately
oh yeah you might be right because last
time it did indeed not go well for me
let's prepare
Let's cross
are they gonna are they gonna come up
no
where's that person
oh Dad
never realized there were some people
down there
all right all right all right all right
all right
I need the medkit immediately
[\h__\h] oh there it is
coming in clutch yo
okay
um
where are weren't there like way more
people first time I was here
also like it's pointing down now
is it not
higher up
where are they
I started shooting a lot later huh ah
you mean that like they were able to
catch up with me more
there must be someone over there I
remember there were people here
oh
what a shoe
huh
oh
you think they're all on the floor below
hmm
we gotta be careful nonetheless because
otherwise something will happen the same
way like last time
okay there was someone here also
what about now
huh
you know what I know
okay
so
sassy quiet and then over there I got
shot
well what's confusing me now is that the
Red Dot is pointing at the goal being
down
I don't know if I should really be here
okay
but
it's like where where
oh
should I clear the lower floors um
that's the way I came
that's so quiet
oh okay
finish you off
[Applause]
the [\h__\h] away from me
what is it yay
okay what else
I didn't lose any HP on that I think
someone's here
someone's here oh he's running
no police
not again it'll be
suddenly like you feel safe
I feel safe you think you're safe
and he's up he went up
okay I cleaned this area I think
yeah I wasn't sure
[\h__\h]
okay you're going to die
is there no more Med kids
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
I'm gonna die I'm gonna die they all
spawn now switch to AK
uh which one is the AK
this one
hot dog hot dog
[Music]
yeah bye
that was him
yeah
because now
I'm a little bit in the kerfuffle I
don't even know how to get out of here
should I jump I don't have health
um colorful
this now
oh no
oh that's bad
can I go here please survive
they're right there
give up you're wasting your time
okay
okay here we go here we go here we go
here we go baby
all right we have music off anyway
[Music]
that's not a good sign lagging is not
good but he did he do his seat belt he
better
oh wait I'm already out of the danger
zone
oh easy
ah comfortable comfortable Escape
is the Sweet Escape
[Music]
away oh I need a hot dog now or some
food of any sort of any kind nothing
close by really
Piata meat factory can I eat here it
doesn't look like you could enter
worry about Clarence anymore you did a
good thing Nico that boy was
his way out of court willing to
compromise anyone to get out of trouble
thank God for real Justin
real Justice surfed by Yours Truly oh
actually hmm
there's a
hmm yeah but I need food that doesn't
heal me does it
any food here
I feel like I saw something
yeah 5K way better than last time but
still
a little bit meh
I'm just looking for food
Central Park
is this Central Park
hot dogs in Central Park
has been kidnapped I heard he also
rushed his money
a climb at that point he owed them money
he never told me anything I heard they
took him to a warehouse and both
I'll check it out
and I have to take care of so many
things
okay but we have to go to Roman like
Holland hospital hospital
could I go to the hospital
forced Mission it's okay I I wouldn't I
would do it even if it wasn't
forced
um
Nico I thought I would send you this
picture looks like your cousin is no
wait wait wait wait wait let me heal
myself first
uh excuse me there's the Central Park
I'm just like sightseeing you know
really beautiful wow it's going big Park
Tokyo has its own kind of Central Park
by the way did you know
it's uh right at halajuku where they
also have that huge huge shrine
it's really big and there's also like a
lot of people just like doing whatever
like maybe picnicking in in during the
Sakura season everybody is
doing a cherry blossom viewing there you
know
I went there A lot of times
it's really popular and it's like
connected to Harajuku and Shibuya you
know a lot of like big places
so if you work there and then you like
want to go on a break then maybe
you would go to the park and hang out a
little bit and then finally
[Music]
I don't want to call ambulance ah
and finally something
hey y'all please feed me I'm suffering
finally if you don't mind
um
oh thank you
okay should I buy another vest before
this one
before going to
oh it's pretty far is this the
is this the the the
Roman one where he is
okay but yeah I should buy something
they're both like the other way
opposite direction
let's go that way because then we can go
up from there
[Music]
I want to see you escape four star I
tried before I oh
I tried really hard
I couldn't
I died
and wasted so much of my time to
oh
you ever been to New York yeah no I've
only been to like two places or so in
America
barely seen
much of America so far
and
I would like to see more yeah
American people have been very nice
but the the sheer size of the country
intimidates me
and I don't know the whole atmosphere is
very different from European cities or
or you know Asian cities that I've also
experienced
very different atmosphere so and that
also intimidates me
well at least it didn't exhaust the [\h__\h]
out of me in like London did
what the [\h__\h]
some crazy [\h__\h] that happens here what
what why did why did the screen Shake
an earthquake
you should do it you should go on a road
trip
I don't know I like road trips but I
would prefer to do road trip in Europe
to be honest because then
I know where I'm going
I don't know I mean
I don't know I've done road trips in in
Europe
I don't know I don't know who would even
be up to do a road trip with me in
America
do any of the new girls know how to
drive do we have such information
I feel like I heard something from them
about it
I feel like they some one not all of
them but somebody told me something
where's this entrance
[Music]
yeah maybe erisa but I feel like she
told me she wouldn't want
truth Drive I don't know try anything
funny I can't remember
[Music]
let me uh
okay
[Music]
you too
have a nice day
a lot of Polo en members just can't
thrive
it's actually surprising to me because
like in my
um
acquaintances
and friends like a lot a lot of people
have a license if not almost all of them
actually my closest friends
which is like one two three four five my
five closest friends all of them have a
license
my mom doesn't my mom has refused
until this point in her life still to
get herself a license
and has always been
um
when need be relying on my brother
laughs
or even before my brother had a license
or a car you know just like significant
other
it's actually fascinating I told my mom
mommy when I'm getting my license you
have to get it too
you have to we're gonna get a license
both of us okay
I don't know if she's gonna do it
but she's come so far without a license
she's probably gonna continue to
refuse to get one
but yeah everybody has a license here so
I wonder if it's just like a coincidence
that so many girls in the end
came together who don't have a license
or because like especially from what
I've heard America is a place where you
kind of need a car
unless maybe if you live in a really
really like one of those cities that
really function best on
Subways and so on but mostly that's what
I hear right it's correct right
you kind of [\h__\h] close
you kind of want a car in America
it's like yeah the place is [\h__\h] huge
um
depends on the city yeah but still like
it's so weird
so many of us just don't have a license
and for me personally I
I just I I grew up and still live I
would say in places where you don't
really need a car and
um I just never really
um
really desperately need one and I was
also really just scared of the idea
of
driving in traffic because I'm even too
scared to drive a bicycle to ride a
bicycle in traffic
really that's like one of the reasons
why I just don't ride a bicycle
I'm too scared
because it like overwhelms me like I
don't nobody ever like properly taught
me how to ride the bicycle in like a
traffic situation like this
so I don't know where and how I don't
know how to act like what to do like
what's allowed what what can I do
um yeah it's just freaks me out it
scares me I don't know the rules so well
I can only ride the bicycle like maybe
in a park
I don't even have my own bicycle
so yeah I never really wanted to learn
it but I decided that maybe after
um
if I ever leave her life that's when I
would consider getting a license because
then I can focus on learning it because
I also just I don't think I can focus I
can I can learn
it I would be just
I don't know I want to take my time and
focus on it so if anything I would do it
after
so for now I stay licenseless and Carlos
yeah
never
walk too
public transport tool Uber tool
s
you're going to have to think about how
you will pay your debt a friend of mine
Dimitri raskolov he would pay a lot of
money for your cousin I'll get you the
money just not that way I think we
should make a big [\h__\h] off long tonight
I feel like this is not gonna go well
at least not first try
should I be sneaky or should I just
blast
first aid testing exams
Maybe
last sneak blast blast blast blast blast
blast
is this what I have right now the gun
that I want to use
beer hash and prostitutes that's my
perfect evening oh yes what if we line
them up nicely there's like free
I don't think I can get all free but
I want to get both if I smoked any more
I wouldn't have time to eat
I hear you
are they dead they're dead
okay okay
yeah
easy
well let me get closer to him
[Applause]
Ramen I'm coming for you oh you can
destroy this oh
okay he's dead
I think I can tell now when they're
really dead it's when they
died when they drop something red
that's when they dropped their items so
the light indicates they're really dead
ah [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Music]
I hate the camera thing sometimes
no he's not dead
let me get rid of this can I no
yeah I got it
tiny tiny tiny baby Target bubble bubble
head
I still have full health too but there's
a medkit here hmm maybe on the way out
is there someone no
okay I think I pretty much cleaned for
you
ah okay there's one here but hard to
reach oh and
this [\h__\h] but I can't reach him
I did
come on why not yeah
yeah
okay I'm coming I'm going up maybe
after I pick up some stuff
low thing I'm a Luke Goblin
foreign
thank you for showing your face so
clearly to me that was really helpful
swap for it
better right how can you see that how
can you tell so quickly
this one
okay oh yeah that looks better oh
yeah
you're coming up here
why it's really loud
yeah beautiful
I think these ones are all dead
okay
um
was there like an explosion thingy there
I get you on me that got him there was
literally like only like one strand of
his hair visible I swear
whoa yo I'm good
you see you see my bombastic shots
bombastic side only
have you spell disgusting
it's me Destiny hopefully not because
I'm close to them
[\h__\h] me
and my HP is still looking
oh no the only thing I'm really worried
about is escaping after we have to leave
again
because I'm always bad with like
escaping I'm good with infiltrating but
I'm really bad with escaping
have you noticed
[Music]
so
mad kid right there so whatever oh but
it's taking my armor first noon
okay
you noticed in Pizza Tower
yeah
he's with my family yeah
it's like I don't need the medkit
[Music]
I romance already
sorry woman I didn't go bowling with you
if I would have gone bowling with you
this would have never happened
that'll be okay I'm being a little bit
more Reckless oh [\h__\h] oh
so much more painful if you gave us
something I have no choice there who is
he shooting
is that Roman
shooting
are they shooting Romans
[Music]
where is Roman
you come to collect your fat cousin
right away
you want them
the blue dot okay okay so that's not him
okay good good good
people who wish they did
you're pathetic
thank you
time to eat your feet
you're the last one buddy
last one
okay Roman I don't want you guys
[Music]
and walk away or your cousin is dead I
am not afraid of death
did I do it yeah
easy I saved Romance
we should get out of here
yeah we should I follow Roman okay so
this time I follow you know that you
follow me that's maybe better that way
around
there's a car where is the car oh
I hear police
but that wasn't for us huh
they have yet to
look for us
what is this place sorry sorry so sorry
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I know we're
in this dress in a hurry
please move on
go on go on
Ah that's so Gray
[Music]
oh wait where what's up here
you have been gambling I give you money
how are you in debt there are Cycles
cousin you must lose a little to win a
lot that was successful baby that's my
new Dimitri he was trying to make me
give you up to him I don't know where to
go of course you would not Dmitry has
taken this too far he wants you dead
forehand is not the same I I'm going to
get this a place in Algonquin are you
okay I'm used to taking his beatings
Nico I almost expected man no there are
people who want to kill me men who will
kidnap me I'll never marry Mallory I
won't be able to sleep with another girl
no bro there is a knife hanging over me
a clock is ticking
yo that wasn't so bad I thought that the
Escape might be a problem but no not at
all
[Music]
[Applause]
Roman is on edge
[Music]
understandably so
very clean rescue thank you you let you
go to shooting thank you right some of
those shots I want you guys to like take
close-up clips of it
like how I literally gave someone in a
headshot even though I only saw
like
not even the full pixel
it wasn't even a full pixel
aqua
it's a miracle
mm-hmm
[Music]
I heard this before what was your name
is it car
afo
[Music]
oh it's a swear
first person shooter bro yeah it has
been proven again and again that I
am better at first person shooter than
first person shooter it's so weird
ah son of ah
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah man this is I know what are we
going to do I don't know we're going to
die I don't want to die man not like
this how would you like to die
this is my 100th birthday I don't
[\h__\h] know I'm scared you called the
bastard what are we going to do I'm not
cold you're cool oh you got it after
Revenge getting your own way even though
you care about this money and gambling
it away on the internet oh isn't America
great I can sit in front of a computer
and play Mr rich man and get into death
with Crooks okay I messed up I know I
did I thought things would be different
I I don't understand this place so good
stop sitting in front of the computer
gambling our money stop getting into
illegal card games stop spending all our
money it's so difficult thank you
and stop thinking about the Russians man
we just need to disappear as far as
they're concerned this appeal okay okay
but I want glory in the dark I need to
know what happened give me that fine
leave the Russians alone I was not the
one gambling in their private club I
didn't know
hey okay
everybody calm down now let's just go
bowling I had a bit of an accident back
there
you disgusting
um you're welcome anything for you
we saved him I'm a hero
oh that was our place I forgot
[Music]
oh yeah right we're on this island I
want to be on this island already also
we've never been to this one before
kildor
Nani
I am
is there really no weapon place up here
and I just haven't discovered it
or is it really just those two
left island is New Jersey
oh New Jersey is it uh in New York
I thought it was its own City
one per Island why are they all like on
the bottom
man
it is oh it is its own city state
it's a state
it's kind of small for a state
what's this music
let's go to X or to PM what do you want
me to do packing
or Playboy
in the end I guess we have to do
everything but
yeah
Packy
all right
ah Little Jacob
I don't care
Little Jacob can go [\h__\h] himself
I don't know I mean this game confuses
me I thought I had it with GTA 5. I
thought I had it
[Music]
and GTA 4 just confuses me it froze me
off
it's a low rider after all okay
God damn it
it's pretty white though you know what
judge muscle cars behind how wide they
are
um
but okay these like this weird shape
okay
a typical lowrider I will try to
remember that
why are you running on the highway
[Music]
ah
let me check something
[Music]
oh
I feel like I kind of mentioned this uh
at some point
already but
when I was uh out of Cali
I noticed like
so many people this is so crazy like
what the [\h__\h]
so many people would like
they see her phone and see that she has
a one piece cover what the [\h__\h]
and they're all like oh One Piece One
Piece of cutest girl do you like One
Piece
they all talk to her about one piece
what the [\h__\h]
and I'm just the whole time I'm just
sitting there like okay yeah cute having
they're having a conversation I have no
idea what's going on I feel like an
uncultured swine because I don't know
anything about one piece I cannot
contribute to the conversation I'm just
smiling and nodding
hahaha
I feel
I got the impression because like
literally everybody reacts to it that
one piece seems to be like the the
National Treasure and I don't treasure
it I feel so bad
cousin
you brought it already
[Music]
at least here I'm not the only one it
wasn't so long
so long and the mother will be better I
can't lose I was just talking about
switching Islands let's go foreign
quite convenient
noise
um also
well that's
did I tell you about horotoni
everybody
from the overseas verbs when we were
together all of horror stories and all
the overseas verbs
all the overseas Birds brought like
snacks
sorena brought Indonesian snacks Mumbai
brought her snacks
and I brought the Austrian snacks
and so we were having like a little
snack party yeah
Senpai were trying all of her snacks
International snacks and they loved my
soccer cake we're gonna hide the
diamonds in the Queen's ass I'm so happy
I felt so okay so what's the word get
your [\h__\h] hands off my [\h__\h] sister
boy we're talking proud but also thanks
Patrick I pray after the amount of
practice confirmed the difference sure I
know the difference one leaves you
feeling sad and empty and alone and the
other's casual sex validated yeah that's
what I wanted to say play date
coming Ma you boys play nice now for
sure
okay
oh we're gonna play real nice
the clean is a [\h__\h] whistle one
previous owner you safely driven those
look like [\h__\h]
those weapons I have better weapons
we got an opportunity my boy yep fortune
favors the brave gotta make hay while
the sun shines
so is you down boy
where's you out down for what down for
robbing a thief Robin Hood exactly Robin
[\h__\h] Hood who are you going to rob
[\h__\h] Mafia boy
is the money good what's the risk well
the risk is we all die a very slow and
painful death
and the money is good very good indeed
so you win big guy
do I have a choice
well
since you put it that way
I mean right all right let's do this
Nico seems to be quite
motivated about it
seems to be quite fond of this job can
you get us a car
[\h__\h] you pack ing yeah [\h__\h] yourself
uh find the four-door car okay so not
the car that I came with
also not the is
also not this one
are they following me
no I gotta bring the car there
are you a four-door car no what's up
for cars on this one's this one's fine
but I mean
police
yeah
okay
[Music]
get in everybody
Colony Island big man I totally got that
sorry can you put it into my GPS
thank you
drive to the waist the PO okay
Mafia controlled Waste Management plan
you [\h__\h] guessed it it's an ancelotti
operation Ray tipped us off about a big
payoff they just got a fad right let me
see
enchiladas I can't tell all those white
families apart enchiladas gambinos
pecorinos it's the [\h__\h] pegarinos man
we're working for them pecorino's a type
of cheese pegarinos is a bunch of cool
gangsters they're all Mafia though of
course they are kosa Nostra and all that
[\h__\h] our family used to be bigger
Northern mafia families put together
back in the day that is not this [\h__\h]
again I heard this speech a million
times the mccrearies ran the city people
were scared to say their name let alone
come there that play some Purgatory life
was great we were in charge it's [\h__\h]
true I'd like to hear you tell Gerald
that it's a boring story My Brother
wouldn't take too kindly to that now
would he you know the Purgatory is
called what it is because people were so
scared of the mccreeries did you know
that Nico let's call that because people
find McCreary stories so [\h__\h] boring
listening to them was like being in
purgatory [\h__\h] you Corey now [\h__\h]
come back there and kick your [\h__\h]
ass in a minute
Francis McCreery is your brother [\h__\h]
Frankie my brother he may have a badge
but I tell you for a fact he says
crooked as the rest of us McCreery's
more so
between [\h__\h] Hypocrites Kate's the
only decent one I can believe that you
know Frankie do you I got a story for
you if you do another [\h__\h] story shut
up Gordon so Nico when Francis in jail
was growing up Frankie becomes an altar
boy besides to this day that he wanted
to serve the Lord Oh you mean like God
knows the truth though he only put on
that plastic so he could pocket the
change in the collection plate fact
that's Francis down to a [\h__\h] tea I
don't even know if he realizes what a
cookie is that sounds like the Francis
mccarry I make I bet model Community
leader my ass I'm just worried he'll
start clamping down on you ain't your
package I'd like to see him try it not
gonna happen with the things Jerry knows
okay you done talking okay seems like it
oh my God
[Music]
they see this and they just ignore it
wow New York police
unbelievable so yeah everybody loved my
my soccer cake you know the little cubes
that I brought and then did I tell you I
feel like I told you but they were like
freaking shocked when I told them
I think it was uh specifically Louis
standpoint
they were really shocked when I told
them
comes from the Saka Hotel they didn't
know there's a hotel but when I
explained to them that it comes from
a hotel they were like what what did I
say Senpai again oh [\h__\h] sake
there's a German person driving in there
um
yeah
[Music]
Luis
about new jeans because
um in January February when I had that
off collab with her
we were talking about K-pop and all that
and she really likes Kpop but for some
reason she had yet to find out about new
jeans so I introduced her to new jeans
and she she really liked it
she was really into it that was like
when they still only had a couple songs
out there but recently they released so
many songs I was like did you did you
hear those yeah and she's like no
so I started playing
we were all in the room I started
playing the new Jean songs the other
members were also a bit curious
well it was mostly me and me and Louie
enjoying some K-pop songs I'm I'm
introducing everybody to new jeans I
don't understand why
these people who claim they like
they light up haven't heard of new jeans
like how can you not hear of new jeans I
honestly don't understand they're like
everywhere if you listen to K-pop you
you must have heard of them until now
because they also win all the award
shows on the K-pop music stations I
don't get it it's outrageous yet
and there should be a boat docked out
back for the getaway all right it's up
and over the fence
they're so popular they even just
performed in Lola palooza some American
big festival and they had like a huge
crowd I was watching it a little bit
because they were doing a live stream of
it
Larissa's here
what a freaking coincidence
it's like Coachella I guess
is that an enemy I think
don't remember a red-haired person here
oh well I don't see anyone
you're just they're not even taking
cover these [\h__\h] idiots
and then I won't take cover either
ah Chicago
where's Chicago again
is it in the middle of the country or on
the left side or on the right side
upper middle Oh I thought it was in the
middle
[Music]
I don't remember friendly fire was a
thing so I just shot someone else
instead
alola palooza happens in eight countries
really
look like fun the girls are like so cute
but they're empty
their MC reminded me of our empty
because it was very it felt very
funny script
they speak like the most adorable
English so these are K-pop Idols but let
me just like remind you guys they're
amazing because they all even though
they were raised in Korea mostly
um they all have like perfect English
and they have Aussie and New Zealand
accents and I speak like now remember
they speak it was like five times
stronger accent than Bales does I swear
what am I doing
by the way
it's literally so hard to understand
what they're saying no but it's cute
get the cash from the office okay
you're covering me right right
I don't feel covered
I don't feel covered I don't know I
don't know man
something
foreign
[Music]
I would like someone here in the time
zone
and I know I know once again we get a
gem that doesn't cover any European
countries or so
but it's okay guys
see it positively because look at look
at all the
all the in in the same time in any Prime
Time and you're like who the [\h__\h] do I
watch like everybody's streaming now at
the same time maybe they will spread out
later but I don't know
so I'm happy I got my my European Time
Imagine imagine I mean okay sharing is
with one more person maybe not so bad
but still you would have to make an
important decision who do I watch
so I am enjoying uh
I'm gonna continue to enjoy my
my uh Monopoly
even though everybody hates Monopoly
Monopoly is a good thing
you guys are bad at covering me
got it
okay kids I got the cash [\h__\h]
and even though they don't scream at
those times they seem like nerissa and
fulamoku at least
is that my friend they seem very open to
like streaming at whatever time I ask
them to
hahaha
like you know more European times
they seem fine with that
well I don't know
who is that I don't know where are we
going anyway
where was that mad kid I kind of need it
now
oh well
go down
foreign
[\h__\h] useless NPCs nobody actually
covers me
now he's trying to get up but he wasn't
getting up I just wanted to move fast or
he they wouldn't let me
all kind
um
let me redo what
what
is it broken
huh
what the [\h__\h]
I don't know
okay here is also
is arigato
yum
can you get us a car man yeah sorry
about messing that one up
looks like a oh that's a corridor
sea tall
oh wait what if I get the limousine
that's more than four seats
no no no no no
oh there's someone inside how many
though
get out get out
it's calling the police
get out
here my people go in and you go out
this is better than four seats so much
better
yeah
yeah it's an upgrade
okay but you turn some strange places
first you take me to a fish market and
now a waste plan it looks like you need
to please with the date you've been
taking them all Patrick you gotta learn
how to treat a man right shut it Gordo
Ray's giving us a tip off about a big
payment the answer can I skip this I
already heard all of this real well out
of this places are messed up I think
this red guy is [\h__\h] with you no
one's [\h__\h] with me Nico this is how
things Adventure Holly
I think they're [\h__\h] when you're
packing they're laughing at you they're
gonna they're having a laugh take over
my car
jackets would have the balls to do that
kidnap my car and bring it to you soon
you're gonna spill all their freaking
drinks
my beautiful limousine the only thing
they're doing for Gordon just keeping
The Bookies off his back for another
week how much you lose on that swingers
game last week that [\h__\h] was red I got
screwed in the night damn inning a guy
who bats 150 it's a three-run homer
[\h__\h] don't go dropping too much
green after this the ancelady's here
we've been spending it up anyway
I have time zones and all that
wow
he's like Gordon over here saving it up
so fine what are you doing with you cut
I feel I feel kind of like bad for the
people who want to watch streams at n a
prime time because it really seems like
difficult now but this is what you know
Michael here this is how it's like for
whole Japan for a long time already I
guess as well
you stream at prime time right
understandable
you want to make the most you want to
get
we want everybody to be able to watch
you don't want to force people to wake
up in the morning like me to watch you
it's inevitable
[Music]
but who knows it might not stay like
this forever
so
yeah
much Choice oh no how terrible yeah I
mean there's always a possibility to
vote and
I mean I mean do you really need to
watch everybody
you just gotta prioritize
gotta make priorities
only you can watch
[Music]
true meaning
in the truest possible sense Patrick
will Caster guilt so true
for real for real
but you guys are lucky anyway because I
don't I don't stream at DNA prime time
so you don't even have this kerfuffle
[Music]
I should have gotten armor
just realized I was like
kind of planning on getting armor but
yeah we are boys moment of [\h__\h] truth
did I have armor last time when I went
in here
I did
I mean this one's kind of close
shut down
now
one of the first things I asked the
girls when I first met them
like talk to them for the first time was
what language are you girls speaking any
new languages I was like any Spanish
nobody I just heard trips what
driving in Liberty [\h__\h] City eh
activated it yeah uh yeah I found out uh
no
what a great start
the [\h__\h] way yeah
oh I don't even have the weapon
half [\h__\h] hell no way
nowhere
[Music]
you [\h__\h] idiots why did you start
showing showing you idiots
I guess not
[\h__\h] whack this [\h__\h]
so annoying yeah Bijou
was like kind of the only one who
brought a new language to the table I
was like no Spanish
Espanol
or I don't know anything but okay we got
we got Tai now very interesting
cute
maybe she can teach me some
this really bothers me how this just
went down really bothers me but there is
a medkit there
wasn't there way more people out here
what
yeah there's a couple still there
hmm
where are my friends there
took you long enough
[Music]
when
I do know a Spanish-speaking video well
I mean I'm sure there's many many
Spanish-speaking YouTubers
just gotta make it
into homo
yeah I don't like entering from this
side man it makes it a bit difficult
okay I got him
I'm gonna run I'm gonna run for it
foreign
[Music]
okay
clean
just gotta be careful now
huh why are they shooting
let's go in boys
you said you're gonna cover me yeah I'm
relying on that
where do we start and
got him
I live for this [\h__\h]
he ran away too fast have they killed a
single person can they even are they
okay well you just try them in the belly
but I feel like he's still alive
are they even capable of doing that I
don't know
but we are
moving on
top what's this like bug I don't like it
it's like shivering
I know there were some people up there
that came out once I went up
is that
there's someone's what I hate this
I don't like it
it's so flashy
okay you guys take care of this one
please uh
[\h__\h]
is that only one
stop getting stuck everywhere all right
ah this one I shot early oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay kids I got the cat got a
flickering it doesn't stop what the hell
I mean let me try to do something here
hey
there were so many
yeah okay it's good to stay up here for
a little while maybe until
I was able to accomplish some things
friends
not friends
walk weapons oh oh oh oh my ammunition
okay I'm coming down and I'll take cover
friends
they should wear we should all wear like
the same color of like a pink T-shirt or
orange T-shirt so that I could really
immediately tell who's on my side
these ones are still
[Music]
there
okay I'm out of here
hmm
these are my friends right okay he's
busy with the ones in the back oh
I have it let me let me try to help it
but he's kind of in the way
should I go to the back door
[Music]
like the opposite of where it came from
both of where it came from has met kids
[Music]
[\h__\h] ow I'm sorry dude
you're in the way
sorry
I can't help him in this position he got
there Mom
today
I can't shoot it won't let me shoot
because like he's in the way
[Music]
hmm
Pro grenade oh
it's just gonna bounce off again
[Music]
dude
why are they not taking ah
cover
okay he killed him
oh my God
do they just not stop
coming
[\h__\h] I I I'm losing I'm losing my
patience
ah what
huh which way do I go when you
ah
am I even I can't proceed you
no
okay how are we looking here there's
still people there right last time I
checked
all right unbelievable
yeah I'm feeling it I'm feeling the same
thing you guys are feeling but let me
just push this so that I can
um
be sure that
this is where we'll continue that next
time tomorrow
it's annoying me
um I need a break
I can leave it here can I this is like
the last checkpoint right so
uh because I'm hungry too and I need to
go to an aisle meeting and I'm just
losing patience like why why why why the
[\h__\h] are they all so useless like oh my
God like is it even my fault
killed it
yeah
um I need yeah fresh brain and a filled
stomach so that will be tomorrow
tomorrow will clear it easily first try
now
no but I kind of need their help because
at that point they just keep on entering
the this like warehouse and they're on
both sides while we're in the middle is
really
[Music]
rough and then where I want to take
cover they're taking covers or they're
in the way and they won't move
what the hell man
um
snipe them from above maybe I'll try
that next time I don't know
yeah I could have just run out too but
like when I try to just run straight
through
it ended up in depth and it was uh on
the first time and then the second time
whenever I would get close to running
that way
just felt very very dangerous
I do need the armor armor would help
I don't want a bowl
[Laughter]
we basically we saved Roman in this
episode okay this was better than
bowling
[\h__\h] bowling
bowling bowling is just a metaphor for
hanging with Roman and bonding with
Roman and we did that
um
also the title doesn't say 100 we will
bow it's just like indicating an
interest in bowling
metaphorical bowling is what we did
today
so true thank you for understanding uh
but maybe we'll go bowling tomorrow if
you wanna you know go bowling with me oh
maybe I'll go tomorrow so better be
there tomorrow just make sure you don't
miss anything any possible possible
bowling
Adventures you know
I'm so hungry oh my God I think I'll
read some super chats but not many
because I'm I'm so hungry I have to cook
um
but I'll probably go phone idle meeting
really quickly if that's okay
nerissa sent to me
some ideas
I'll read those later
oh I smile down
down
[Music]
I'm so hungry
I only have like chocolates and stuff or
I do have cake I have a little bit of
chocolate cake maybe I cut myself like a
one one little slice off of the
marble chocolate cake and I come back
your glasses are cute thank you
no no no so put that reading yes yes yes
let me just
maybe here
see you in
uh
three minutes approximately please don't
go stay for super jet reading
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
amazing
on me
[Music]
[Applause]
I love you
foreign
[Music]
when I can go away
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
hello hello
[Music]
it's moving as
demanding
attention or food I'm not sure which one
nice movie
hi
why not both
they're on my lap right now
oh yeah right it works so well with my
casual outfit because it's summer themed
yeah
Chad why are you not showing up
what's your excuse
there we go
maybe a bit wider
[Music]
huh
oh well
looking beautiful tonight
you guys look so beautiful
[Music]
um
I'm eating you guys now
[Music]
fried chicken yummy
um
[Music]
you ready right you waited for this day
not if I eat myself first no
you can't do that
um
if it hurts just close your eyes and
imagine
um
imagine the days
when you were just a little
cute little chick
um
the good beautiful
comfortable days
ah yeah
there's a little Carefree careless chick
I have a big big future ahead of you
everything was just still so open
so so many possibilities
okay bgm what do we do
[Music]
um
wow
sorry that may have been a bit loud in
the beginning
never bite
just so that I survived the Super Chat
rating
[Music]
hmm
I have been
to like you know this kind of Japanese
style beach houses before you have yep
oh you know what we should check I don't
even know when the deadline is but one
thing we have never really talked much
about
is the bingo
um
I was kind of motivated in the beginning
but because I was so busy I couldn't
really think of like completing them
um
where is
where is the Bingo sheet
um
I hear
basically I don't need to complete all
of them anyway right I just need like
five in a row
let me see
okay
let's see how many we can actually fill
out so far and I'm gonna go easy on
myself okay I've seen some other people
other members fill these out and they
are just
eating so I will I will take it easy as
well let's see I showed off my yukada
yes
foreign
let's see what I did okay
get over a fear or do eat something you
don't like
I feel like I did
I feel like I did and then I was like oh
this was you know
I can clear that off in a Bingo but if
you ask me now what I did I don't
remember
but I feel like I did
ah okay we could say for example the
spicy food in London but that's not what
I'm thinking of but I feel like I did it
yeah
oh and I definitely didn't like the egg
whites yeah that was disgusting but well
in some way or another I surely
definitely did that
uh hang out with someone I did that
learn a new skill I feel like I did that
too wait what could I have learned
I learned
how to
uh what was my recent um video
oh and I have Korean I guess yeah but
what was my recent am video
seal see I learned how to become a seal
go on an adventure I definitely went on
an adventure in real life and in games
you know London was quite an adventure
so that's already bingo
well let's see what else we can get
uh have a scary experience in the summer
the wobbly pool was so scary
and London in general was so scary
hmm
okay
um
watch a movie yes
did I do experiments
did I
what would you call an experiment
hmm
is retro GTA voice retro now let's go
um I will have
not barbecue but kind of like a pool
party
uh with like a pizza party can we
it's a PPQ because pull pizza and Q
I feel like
I feel like if you say no then I will
just bring some sausages and Grill them
that's coming up soon uh sometime soon
I'll just clear it for now
yeah it's the the thing that my friends
asked me to stay in the country for
um you do the social serving a man lying
on the island social experiment
experiment
experiment I feel like if I wanted
something to be an experiment something
that I did
it could
oh you know what I kind of did an
experiment
um
I think you will understand later I
think I could categorize this as an
experiment
uh I did like I had an idea for YouTube
short
and it was recorded with several people
I directed it
and it worked out and everybody was
happy so it was even a successful
experiment it was kind of an experiment
you know what it was an experiment
because it's the first time we did
something like that too
um
for them especially hmm
okay
bingo
uh take part in an event or Festival
since this
am I not part of the whole life Summer
Event like the whole summer this is all
of this is an event
oh oh The Comedy Club sure okay
that was an event of some sort and Lord
of the Rings sure sure
and uh next weekend ID Sports Fest as
well
many many events plenty plenty enough be
number one let's keep that empty for now
unless was I a number one somewhere
um
in your heart
no I'm nervous now
honestly yes we can count that
Melissa just joined within this whole
life summer
event
and I am her number one
ah I won a race in GTA see many many
ways to say I want things
um
I I we said I did this uh I did the off
collab I showed off my swimsuit
hang out around the sea or a river
yeah in London I
the river in London for example mm-hmm
and a pool that was very wobbly
sample oh it's a little
bit which I don't know if it's
at the Lord of the Rings
um
little Musical
that was cute uh
I did not catch insects of fish I did
not watch [\h__\h]
I mean I was at Bilbo's birthday party
but there were no
fireworks were there
I don't think so I think I don't think
they recreate it
does oh
I did just kill a Lego insect I caught
it by slapping it
but it died
does that count us
catching it I just like a few minutes
ago
I did
I caught it with my hand
no I kind of did
it cuts
it died because I didn't want it to live
that's my choice
hmm
but don't worry I won't clear this row
anyway because I was planning on eating
shaved ice in Japan but I um didn't get
to it
um and I'm I don't know when I'll be
watching real fireworks we can say I'll
probably be watching fireworks in
Minecraft though
um there probably will be Minecraft
fireworks at the festival sports
festival but whatever stargazing I
haven't gone like purposefully
stargazing
but
I remember
I remember like looking at stars
uh and I'm really standing out to me
just like what was it during the movie
or what hap was it during my Netflix
watching session
looking at suicide Cuts I trapped up soy
said that stargazing true okay in some
way or another I did two stargaze
I don't know about right in the field
right now what is that even what what do
they mean with that
what does that even mean a field Journal
did I write in a field Journal probably
not
hmm
this is your comment from me for me a
comet is a star
also she's just like a star AKA like as
a artist she's a star
I take notes yeah but those are on my
phone
um
but a journal can be on your phone too
right but what what do they mean by
Fields Journal
where do I mean
accounts
um
I will not be clearing the 47 Japanese
prefectures I'm not gonna go out of my
way and learn them
huh
especially because they don't even allow
like a overseas equivalent
when I asked them
they said no
I will not go through that trouble
but I've eaten something I've never
tried before
the Indian food for example but also
before that I remember trying something
in Japan
um and I was like oh I can take that off
but I also don't remember what it was
this thing that I don't think I did it
but that's okay
because they even management even
notified us like hey today is the day
when you have to do this task if you
want to
but no I couldn't
you have to eat something that starts
with ooh on that special day usually it
would be like unagi or something else
um
I feel like
hmm
maybe I could have accomplished it but
you know too late now
maybe I subconsciously just eat
something that fits that but
I don't remember now
oh my
God okay
and then
your goals for this summer
what was one of my what would have been
one of my goals for the summer
um
I feel like it would be like welcome the
new gen
because I knew they were coming in the
summer
ah release an album which is still
happening
um go to London yeah for the musical
[Music]
um
I'm sure there's many that I could
yeah
new outfit reveal
that was a goal for the summer
and there's definitely many so we have
one two
three four five
bingos I see five bingos
I could probably somehow
Force this one I could make myself
shaved ice maybe I could just take the
ice cubes out of my my fridge shave them
on the cheese grater and make myself uh
shaved ice
diagonal one I didn't see that one
okay one two three four five six yeah
six
bingos but we only really need one I
think
I don't know if it matters how many we
got
um
what we are getting for this
it probably won't be anything
crazy because they'll have to give it to
pretty much all of us
mmm
I think like everyone is going for
blackout all squares so yeah but that
clear so people get like really eager to
clear everything
47 Professor memorizing is that
difficult yes it is good night thank you
for watching
[Music]
RTX models for all winners
yeah I don't know if I wanna
no I can't I'm too busy
I know a couple but out of out like the
top of my head off the top of my head
um
[Music]
cheap okay
here's let me try here let me try uh
Kanagawa uh saitama
oh
Tokyo one of them I would say so
um
uh
wait Hokkaido is not Hokkaido is a
Hokkaido is the whole thing so um
Kyoto
Kobe
or other cities
no
no I think those are also
prefectures
uh
Okinawa
[Music]
um
it's not a prefecture
uh okay okay
uh wait don't don't tell me things in
the chat
that's this was 10 already
um
um wait uh
um where was the place that I went to
um
so now I'm blacking out but I um what's
this place that I went to uh wait I
didn't even say
um
[Music]
gunma the one of the horses
still can't think of the one I'm trying
to think of
huh why can I not think of it
is the city [\h__\h] yeah I know ice cream I
know that place
okay we're not we're not clearing all
the 47 ones anyway now there's more that
I know but I'm just not thinking of them
uh
foreign
[Music]
47 prefectures
uh
three factors of Japan
aha
okay
I kind of had those yes Fukushima even
yeah
[Music]
um
one two three four five six seven eight
that's not awesome
wait wait wait wait wait wait okay here
from the top
wait let me let me show you
oh dear
Hokkaido almond
Yamagata Miyagi Fukushima
I mentioned Hokkaido I mentioned
the others I didn't tochigi was what I
meant of totori
ibaraki said she might say saitama said
come again I said so all of the green
ones I said I know those well
um
[Music]
a lot of them you know I've heard before
they are familiar to me
because I know someone from Hugo
Mia
[Music]
at that Island I feel like well it's
kind of people joke about that Island
because people forget about it
because I've been to tochugi to look at
alpacas
but totoki also exists no
foreign
um
okay
no I can't okay I don't want to learn
this
okay but now now that I got them back
into my brain
do you want to try
guessing them
maybe it would be also
eventually easier to do it when I have
the map in front of me but without the
names I feel like that would be allowed
and then I can point at them and be like
this is this this is this probably maybe
then my maybe some of them would be
inaccurate but
um
okay let me look again
I should go by alphabetically but maybe
I could remember
I could try to remember how many
are
at each letter for example there's so
and so many that start with A and then
when I'm missing one
I I would notice
that could be a strategy
[Music]
there's no way I'm gonna get it now but
kind of almost
foreign
no nothing entered my brain
okay let's start with the easy one
Hokkaido Okinawa
Osaka Kobe Kyoto No what's
no no no no wait restart uh restart
restart
Hokkaido Okinawa
Fukuoka
uh Tokyo
let me stop my region let me let me
first do all the green ones Tokyo
Kanagawa saitama
Chiba
Tokyo Canada
one of the green ones
uh
is that one of the green ones I don't
know
I don't remember the rest
was it
who knows
um okay let's continue
I'm just gonna go random
um
[Music]
this is a 12th noun
Yogo
did I say 15
uh
I don't know which ones I said Osaka
didn't say it I think in the free start
ah
[Music]
that's that's 22 already I
feel or 17 I don't know I don't know
17 probably
ah
Guma
uh
[\h__\h]
um
I didn't say Nara yet did I
I know I don't know
oh
I did get all of the all the green ones
even though that one is so easy to
remember
it's too many
20 mmm
yeah
I can write them down yeah if I try
again but I don't
I don't wanna
not bad for a crash course yeah I have
an advantage of already having been to
Japan and knowing quite a few places but
um
I don't wanna not work on this unless
they say there was something for
blacking it out
uh but if there isn't then it's not
worth it
um yes
yeah okay well well well this is the
current state okay more or less some are
gonna be filled up as I said very soon
100 sure
it's happening
yeah
learn each color learn one color your
time yeah yeah I mean there's surely
ways to do it but do I want to no
it would be impressive to know it though
like it's it's like kind of like
a challenge that people like Japanese
people will even give themselves like
can you say the 47 Japanese prefectures
and and they struggle themselves often
so it is impressive especially as a
foreigner to know all the Japanese
prefectures
hmm
it's shaved ice yummy I personally
prefer like normal eyes but it's good
it's like you know like Water Ice
water type ice cream
it's like asking about the 50 states of
the USA exactly like I feel like I would
have an easier time telling you older
European countries or learning all the
European countries
um if Japanese girls who are from Japan
have to memorize all 47 Japanese
Perfections I feel like they should
adjust it so that you know if you're
from Europe you learned all the European
countries if you're from America and you
learn all the American states if you're
from Canada I don't know what you do
maybe also learn the American states
if you're from Indonesia you what could
you learn maybe the what what does
Indonesia have that you could learn
that's an equivalent I don't know
um
it kind of doesn't have enough provinces
damn
okay then learn the American states
might as well
close enough
name all the islands how many are there
hmm
at least free
thousands
Away really oh my god wow
when are you playing I already finished
I've been playing for five and a half
hours and why you were you not here huh
why were you not here I have a weekly
schedule that shows you the time when I
start
you should have known you should have
known that I've been playing all day and
tomorrow I'm continuing to play all day
I know when you weren't here you tell me
it's always around this time that I end
my games and I start reading super chats
huh you should have known
if there's one place in Tokyo you'd
recommend the tourists well I mean
besides all the obvious ones
in Tokyo
udaiba
no I'm not gonna say like asakusa for
example because I would say asakusa is
obvious
but I would say odaiba because that one
is not so obvious maybe
and if you want to leave Tokyo a little
if you're okay with leaving Tokyo a
little bit go to enoshima
has a lot of nice places to check out
not only enoshima
um
what's it called again
I forgot but kamagawa
it's next to Tokyo so you just jump on
the train
it's a nice comfy train ride oh yeah
Kamakura for example
um
it's it's really nice to go there like
it can also get pretty crowded but it's
worth going I would say because it's
like pretty close after all
well that bothers me so much
oh well
yui gahama Beach I've been there but
it's such a
such a lame Beach not worth don't go
swimming there
hmm
but people Japanese people admit this is
kind of like a beach where guys go to
try to pick up girls
but it's not like
a clean very clean Beach it's not pretty
like yeah it's just because it's like a
close Beach to Tokyo close speech to
type as in Kanagawa
and if you want to go Japan has a lot of
nice beaches and they're not there
they're not in Kanagawa or Tokyo or
Chiba which I think I already deleted
the image but that's you know all the
like almost all the beaches from the
green area
around Tokyo but yeah those beaches
aren't so nice at all
you know they're like really gray and
um
but they have beautiful peaches you just
gotta find them I have
seen Fukuoka beaches
they're nice but they have even better
ones than that
like oh I want to go to Okinawa but
Okinawa from what I saw is like so
crowded
um
yeah
anyway anyway I I gotta read some super
chats before I go not many but let's
finish the ones I started yesterday
um
[Music]
oh Coco was playing
Pokemon unite training
is it really something I really have to
train for what do you think guys it
seems like it's just
you know
so such a simple concept
yes
let's see I should how do I move this
I I I I I I I would like to at least not
be like useless but
yeah
okay
how good are I've heard ID might be kind
of good
what about Japanese members I think
they're also pretty good aren't they
they've been practicing they've been
doing streams on it too
I don't know if we really have a chance
in Ian because uh only fauna is good at
the game right
okay will destroy it was good okay
pretty good
yeah yeah I've seen um training I've
seen them like getting
putting up streams to train
uh
I haven't played it before
okay
[Applause]
but are they I don't know if the en team
is taking this seriously besides fauna
because like no one's setting up any
training streams besides me and fauna so
far I think
I don't know
but I didn't even I didn't even know
this would be so serious I thought it
would be like a really like
chill
little collab with no pressure
hmm
please
carriers
I'm counting on you
okay what was the number guys for the
super chats where I left off
number
remember 354. thank you
so
here we are there's a lot of Pinks and
reds at the ending here so bear with me
um
let me just switch the bgm
what could we listen to
boom
maybe something tropical
or this one maybe
[Music]
nice
okay and the thumbnail
uh was
outfit reveal one
[Music]
why do I have that
no where is it
[Music]
really do I have to download it again
pretty sure I had it before
maybe it's in here
oh there it is
[Music]
okay here we go three five four it's
interesting thank you for the rest of
the chat did I read this one before or
did I stop before Jim Tracy
I feel like I may have stopped before
okay
your new outfit is so awesome can't
believe you got a tails off outfit that
absolutely so detailed and the
hairstyles are perfect I love it too
this sounds so familiar to me
sounds so familiar to me thank you Jim
Tracy
well see because I feel like I've said
uh it's not really a tails off outfit
it's more of a like a
final fantasy-ish outfit
but it is Tails office because
I got the artist
who drew the DLC right I did read it I
feel like I said that's what I'm saying
right now
Jim T is this your second account
interested
two accounts
right I did right okay okay
I told you
okay okay so a kiss for Jin Tracy again
though the main is
I feel like there's a conspiracy going
on against kfp on YouTube whenever
something like this happens
there's no other explanation
I love alter Kiana the colors and the
armor design are so beautiful I love the
lore video too you're beautiful Kiana
thank you yeah I love the details and
the armor and they're so shiny
um I think there were some drafts where
the 3D still stood out to me a lot but I
feel like in the final version it Blends
in nicely
yeah so I'm happy with it too thank you
for the feedback
refaction thank you for the recipe chat
nice weapon those fives are dangerous
weapon oh
was that when I was showing off the the
drafts
okay that was nothing against the weapon
we have now
[Music]
I'm still working on acquiring the the
PNG through management
um
but
Suave ended up drawing a really huge
freaking sick Claymore yeah
and then drew me with them
separately again carrying two of them
what the hell
I feel so much pressure on my arms
yeah
[Music]
the world wielding
eh
oh
you move weapon you meant the fires
okay
possibly could mean that too I guess
those are weapons too yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
you're misleading me I completely
disregarded that I just I just thought
it was two separate separate statements
thank you being faster
Brandon Powell Duncan Prince John thank
you thank you for the rest of the chat
I love everything about this so much you
look absolutely incredible you already
are the cutest coolest and most
beautiful ever but this outfit made you
even cute they're cooler and even more
beautiful I'm deceased don't die I'm
known please get a hold of yourself
please I need you don't die
what can I do should I make myself more
ugly
and unattractive
so that you can stay alive
[Music]
difficult too with a hard balance to
hmm
okay okay you're fine okay then I'm
relieved
thank you for the sweet words yum
I'm glad you like it so much you seem
very excited about it
is it one of your favorites
um
heart stream heart balancer
that's such a stretch I love it
thank you very very very much mwah no
bad thank you for a red super chat too I
love armor and a fellow armor and joyer
armor appreciator
there's many of those around us in our
circles thank you I'm glad you like it
wow
I'm more Adora armor is such a difficult
word to say I don't like it
I don't like it
we should rename armor into kerfuffle
kerfuffle is fun
I made my desk man 30 with all the caked
chocolate you
old set 176 thank you for the red super
chat the new outfit armor looks really
cool and amazing the new hairstyles are
also great especially in the long side
ponytail just love it thank you I like
it too it was so hard to decide
ah
ah but I I think next time I'll have to
go for only one out one hairstyle
um
I'm already planning it and seems like I
can't
fit in everything that I want for it
and do two hairstyles so I'm thinking
okay just one hairstyle and then maybe
later on you know for like anniversary
or birthdays or whatever I can still
request a new hairstyle if I want maybe
um
hmm
yeah
I I think for this one I'm okay with
just having one hairstyle maybe for once
it's been a while that I'm going for
something with just one hairstyle
um
I feel like I'm always aiming for two my
kimono had two
uh what the Casual one has two now but
it didn't always have to
the the dental has to
Empress had one yeah but that's a while
ago too
[Music]
thank you all that anyway Oozy
um
[Music]
I love the ponytail thank you so many
ponytail appreciate it I feel like
everybody
has been saying that the ponytail is
their favorite
but you guys like the other one too
right
you don't dislike it right
short hair my favorite really
okay as long as some people like it um
a professional hair oh both are awesome
both
okay okay so it's good it's just that
the ponytail is just even better
understood
thank you
and Marcus is
such a cool outfit and the hairstyles
are so amazing tender is now a warrior
not only in heart but also in looks I am
die yes I always was a warrior
moving my soul and in my heart
my mind always fighting
battles with evil things
hmm
yeah but now now I'm visually a warrior
as well
very cool
thank you for loving the new outfit so
much foreign
[Music]
thank you I am a tea
Jacob 47 out
thank you for the recipe chat
okay swap nailed it this is your best
outfit oh the best blend of cool and
cute and sexy and new presentation with
the video and the bgm is amazing it's
going to be funny seeing you play GTA
with this Fantastical outfit but I look
forward to seeing it last in the future
now I purposefully am not wearing it for
GTA because I feel like it doesn't quite
match
yeah
uh because GTA plays in the modern world
and yeah everybody's wearing normal
clothes so I just don't feel like it
matches for Minecraft I could still
feel like I want to wear it but
yeah but I'm I'm sure that in the future
when we play any jrpgs or RPGs or
download games
I feel like I would wear it
for these kind of games anything that's
fantasy
um
Final Fantasy 16 yeah I will play it but
yeah
problem is that at the time when we when
it like released and we had perms
I was
in Japan right
so I couldn't start right away
and I also didn't want to start in that
one week that I had in between
because I knew I wouldn't be able to
play properly
following that
so it's difficult
to start it now
because the release hype is dead
um but I also don't want to miss out on
it because I've waited so long
that we would get permissions to play
any Final Fantasy game
when it's so long
and now we finally have it for this one
and I never played a Final Fantasy game
besides the MMORPG anyway
so just for personal experience and as a
streamer I always wanted to play a Final
Fantasy game it's just like my interest
because of me not being able to play it
right away has definitely like
gone on vacation but I feel like once we
start maybe maybe I'll still have a
great time
right we'll surely have a great time
once I start but yeah
Baldur's game we're waiting for
permission
for that one I asked
[Music]
and Cali was like hey let's play
together I didn't even know you could
play together
people
in Baldur's Gate
F of 14 with Bijou
you know what I mean was thinking about
that but I
but I'm going to Buy
a copy of Final Fantasy 14. for the
fifth time in my life
no
[Music]
throughout my life for whatever reason
I've played I've bought the base game or
base game with uh extensions
like four times
I will not buy it again
nope that would be like so stupid
doesn't matter if I have the money I
will not buy the game over and over
again
just because I keep on like I think it
wasn't even me losing the copies
I think the first time I bought it again
was
something like
I don't know it was like
I couldn't use it because maybe
something was
could it be that the copies are region
locked I don't know
[Music]
something some there was some reason
that made them
impossible for me to use it or
or was it something like
I think yeah I don't know I had I had
several issues I probably also lost at
least one copy like I wouldn't know
where my most recent one was
count
data too right
too right max level character yeah
that's very very multinife I wonder if I
could recover my One max level character
do they delete characters after they're
enacted for a long time in Final Fantasy
14. did I do that
no
[Music]
if I recover my account
then can I download the game for free
what do I have to buy it again
[Music]
yeah
[\h__\h] with my account though
I don't think I know
[Music]
I just need to buy a subscription again
right
but like I mean I don't have to buy the
base game I know the base game is free
now but you also need the extensions
extensions cost something so in the end
you're paying for the game yeah
yeah whatever month monthly subscription
doesn't matter what I'm what I'm upset
about is that I bought the game several
times
uh
yeah so what I'm thinking instead of
playing ff14 with Bijou
[Music]
um
oh oh wait guys listen oh my God 2024
will be the year of me and Bijou playing
blue
blue something something
she likes Tails games I love Tails games
we like MMORPGs there is one that I've
been waiting for for a million years and
now in Bijou I have a possibly
guaranteed
partner to play it with me blue protocol
yeah once it comes out in 2024 in
English now it's already out of Japanese
but oh
relax
whoa whoa that's exciting that's
something new that's something fresh
K of Pebbles let's go
oh I'm sure she would be all up for it
because she likes like jpgs and Tails
off games and everything
this is an MMORPG
that looks like a tails off game
[\h__\h] exciting
I'm just waiting forever for this to
release in English
yeah I'll wait for that I don't want to
start ff14 no
Dean I'm so sorry if I would get a free
copy and an easy recovery of my old
character okay maybe but no
I don't even know if I would be probably
I wouldn't I wouldn't even be allowed to
use my old character maybe I don't know
um
I'll give it a try at least
[Music]
what's the problem with Amazon
does it
gotta give it a try when it comes out
I I would man
I
think I've been waiting to play a new
women such a long time and
thought I was gonna play it alone but
the photos may be playing it with Bijou
makes me very happy
[Music]
I'm really happy
an anime I'm a more picture I waited so
long for a new anime and memory that's
not on a [\h__\h] phone
I don't want to play stupid Batman
refugees on stupid phones I don't want
to play any phone games at all to begin
with
I want to play on my PC or on a console
but not on a phone
thanks for understanding
gamer struggles
I want to go back to the old days when I
was playing anime free to play anime
MMORPGs but pay to win no pay to look
good
all day during my summer vacations
and even besides my summer vacations
wasting all my time with them
hmm
hate to be fabulous I love pay to look
good
now I can actually pay for it
now I don't have to beg
[Music]
hmm
no
first anime was five
same same same same
to someone and they were they knew it
they didn't know the other ones I
mentioned but then you fly if was it
visual
or was it someone else I don't know
for fun fluff
in German we called it fluff
because the why
um when it's in a position like that is
kind of usually pronounced like uh
so fluff
oh was it was it
something it's just recently though oh
well anyway
uh
what was I
Aya Jacob
didn't get very far silver raggle thank
you for the rest of a chance
did you tease wolf hairstyle half a year
ago was this accidental also look
absolutely stunning This Is My Religion
now I don't know I would have to watch
the incident
what did I say when I supposedly teased
it
anybody here remembers Silverado here
but yeah my first MMO was also the World
of Warcraft but the first anime one was
Fly for Fun girl I think
told us to Google Wolf's hairstyle
maybe I mean if it was half a year ago I
was
possibly looking up hairstyles and and
suggesting them to swap
uh so maybe it could have been
just you know
oh
[Music]
we're not doing on Yakuza strand
between three and six probably
but I knew that you know even if I
mention a random hairstyle you guys are
not gonna really
[Music]
be able to do much with that information
but yeah I'm glad you like it wolf
hairstyle yeah
[Music]
hey I wanted something unique that I
didn't do yet
[Music]
and that would fit the the concept quite
well
hairstyle that I don't have done before
so
I thought of that one hmm
thank you Silverado for noticing Sean I
thank you for the pinky kfb Alto Kiana's
Fighters pop maybe
imagining cute little duck on my
chickens and armor now oh yeah Dacula
did end up drawing a chicken and armor
right
it was very cute kfp
um
yeah fight this Pub if there's I don't
know if there's any better idea
oh paladins
feathered cute I was thinking of the
word feather for f but I didn't know how
how to implement it that is so cute
piano's feathered paladins because you
guys are feathered
adorable
that's the Discord current name oh
I like it let's let's go with that
Slavic fellow thank you for the rest of
the chat my oh she looks so damn cool I
hope we can join her Guild you're
already in it congratulations you in it
by default
thank you and your school I look forward
to solving lots of quests with you
[Music]
I hope you will give me better cover
than those idiots in GTA
pretty pretty
counting on you
uh did I give you a kiss
ing for the pinky Lord Commando Kiana
I don't like being called that because
the only place where I've ever heard
that before
I feel like is in a handmaid's tale and
the Lord commanders are the most [\h__\h]
up people in the handmaid's tale
I don't like it I guess yeah maybe Jon
Snow is also a lord wait what wait yeah
I guess so but still
still
rearing it in the handmaid's tale just
[\h__\h] me up I don't like it
yeah
um You can call me
[Music]
um
I'm the empress I'm I'm the fighting
Empress Warrior empress
my finest
my violence
pilot
no
Empress
although that's really funny
there's it's definitely fitting
when you look at my thighs in that
outfit you call me
my holy finest
uh
we have too many Geniuses in the chat
it's not good the new outfit looks super
cool off the theme swap someone did an
amazing job Congress and I hope more
good things will come to you thank you I
hope so too I'm still waiting for
um birthday
accessories and at the same time
anniversary accessories
for them I don't know when they'll be
finished
uh I asked them to prioritize the
unleashing of my swimsuit
so that I can have it before summer ends
um
we'll see when I get it
that will be
legendary
the one thing we've been waiting for
because like last year they already
brought back whole life summer
and I asked yo now that whole life
summer is here can you let me show can
you let me take off the blouse and I
asked in summer and they were like
maybe not this time maybe not at this
time I don't know why
but yeah
so this summer for real is the
unleashing of the turquoise bikini
released in one ones
[Music]
at least that will be the hashtag
unleash the wild ones or Freedom Wallace
wobbly waffles
hmm I don't like wobbly things anymore
freak me out
um
killed kiwawa I will never forgive is
that short hair although
love the outfit Kiara looks so cool and
stylish well who are we invading first
my leash
first of all
she didn't kill her
they just switched that like
um Dimensions at the time when they
touched each other because only one of
them can be in the same Dimension at the
same time
they didn't kill each other or anything
like that
yeah kfp Mama is in the other world
whenever Alta Wawa is in this world
right now Alta Wawa is in her own world
just chilling doing Empress things
not my fault
yes
don't be picky
don't question it too much it just
happens
first time was an accident and maybe
every other time there's still an
accident because they can't control it
[Music]
or maybe maybe aldawama got along so
well with froggy Wawa that she felt like
she wanted to see her again
so
normal Wawa arranges for that to happen
by switching out
and going on the bench
who knows
who really knows I don't know
froggy lava doesn't have an altar no no
no
it's just froggy Wawa
there's only one of her
she's unique
[Music]
code no disgusting
Ohio
anyway thank you everyone
Ultimo MK thank you for the pinky so I
guess we got isekai too and our Guild
now and I'll get leader is this cool
Beauty who can also be cute on occasion
so absolutely love the new outfit thank
you
yes mostly cool Beauty
but also cute
Wawa is a chameleon
can do anything can be anything
I need a massage my back hurts so much
I haven't had one in a while
after traveling
so much
um
because like after Japan after I came
back from Japan in Japan I had a massage
but then I came back and then I went to
London and then from London I came back
to here wow back court very much
to go again
yeah but the massage that I got in Japan
wasn't even that good
it was like a facial and and a massage
the facial was really nice the massage
was just like you know
she had interesting techniques but she
wasn't strong enough
so yeah I didn't really feel much
unfortunately
yeah
I do like massages because it gives me a
brief relief of the pain that I'm
constantly in
yeah me and Callie when we got together
we just got a massage
[Music]
of course not of course of course that
massage didn't
it's nice but it didn't
clear my chronic pain
it's nice that I'm uh because like Arena
will also give me massages but I don't
even have to ask her for it if she's
like standing behind me she will start
giving me a massage she's so cute
so now mume I got movie to do it too
right so I am training my birds co-hines
to give me massages at any time when I
need it
Elena is so sweet she kind of
you know just starts it randomly and
then I'm like enjoying it and I ask her
to go stronger and she continues on and
on
mm-hmm
yeah narissa has to give me massages too
Marissa you're listening
you better go take a massage course
somewhere
a lesson on how to give good massages
um
and maybe start lifting
some weight so you can give really
strong massages Maybe
I don't think she's listening I gotta
tell her privately
I'm serious about this
uh
she said she was listening in like a
little bit before
when she wrote me that message
the two kilogram weights are not enough
of course not
Devin
fried squirrel thank you for the rest of
the chat oh Warrior Empress from foreign
lands who switched places with our
tension ingestion of good faith I swear
allegiance to you now I do not know the
customs of your home when it comes to
proper etiquette but I'll show always
drops down now would you step on me my
empress
huh
[Music]
man
fried screws
you kind of
got a little bit kinky at the end but
until that point I really liked your use
of words magical words
[Laughter]
I wish I could articulate myself like
that it's beautiful
you're role playing so well
thank you fried screw
step step
I like your funny words Magic Men
yeah
I do I do
signal yes thank you for the advisor
tattoo hi Baba wonderful new outfit
congratulations especially love the
wings they look beautiful with you
playing lots of RPGs The Outfits will
surely be appropriate for lots of
streams I'm already excited I think so
too I'm excited for it too
it'll be very visually fitting
because I play so many jrpgs so I think
it was a good choice to have something
for those streams yeah and just also for
personal satisfaction and and for you
guys yeah even if we don't use it for
games like that still
just nice to have
thank you very much glad you like it too
sigelius
Stone slash Junction
summer rose dances
Mrs Lulu Beth function
glass thank you for the pinky you look
so cool and cute
I love both hairstyles so much the video
is amazing too thank you man I've been
hearing a lot of Woos today
thank you class
[Music]
I put a lot of a lot of thought
time into this one yeah
I'm glad you like it
thank you soon
today all my hopes and dreams were
fulfilled it's absolutely amazing yay
so many people really wanted a like a
warrior armor outfit huh
hmm
I
seems like I hit jackpot
thank you Julie I appreciate it well
David Chan thank you
and Nathan cotton thank you for the
pinky okay now too guys about the
specific bits of the outfit first I love
the gauntlets though I don't know how
you will lift them with those noodle
arms eh
and the undershirt is so cute the
jacket's so cool and the chest piece is
very form-fitting
now the chest piece is the fabric though
hmm
it's just normal fabric it's uh
as far as I remember
I you we used to have like a chest plate
on it for a little while when we were
drafting it but
yeah I had it removed because I thought
oh it's a bit too much maybe
so the snail yeah it has a cc and the
folds of the cloves yeah you can see it
well thank you
it is still form-fitting I suppose
foreign
I would be angry if they made armor
jiggle like that
I am
very particular about the jiggle jiggle
jiggle wobble and wobble about things
that wobble
a lot of people thought it was a chest
plate
what
[Music]
um maybe the silver color
I mean you see the the closing Folds
no that's just uh I guess the shine and
the color I made people maybe think that
way but no
no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
no no no no no no no the folds make it
very clear
mm-hmm
[Music]
gonna look closely
yeah anyway thank you Nathan thank you
for paying attention to all the details
yeah
wait what
[Music]
oh wait you sent another one
continuation love the free layered skirt
uh with the pleats and the wings and the
shoes yeah the shoes are one of my
favorite things I think the boots that
can barely contain boots can barely
contain them thick thighs but my
favorite bit has to be the deep blue
highlights so contrast it with your
normal Orange right
um
I really really like it too and agree
with all of that
but I would say it's uh I'm gonna take a
look
I would say it's
um
[Music]
just shoes like ankle boots I guess
and then the rest up until the skirt is
just like attachments
you know
from my personal point of view
These Boots Are Made For Walking
that's just one Daniel
one of these days where I'm gonna walk
all over you or something like that
um
protecting the Legos
even the soup thank you so I'll give you
a choo choo
thank you thank you for looking at
everything
so so for rolly verbally
I think Hmm
very much appreciated
thank you soon for paying attention
because there was a lot of detail and
love put into it so I need you guys to
look at it closely hmm
Lego Wawa
ah
Lego is so expensive
can we not
looking fervously what what's that you
making fun of me or is that really a
word and respectfully okay good good
good
purposely or you mean nervously
I only know nervously it's a real word
what's fervously
so far
[Music]
even when I look it up it only shows
nervously did I write it wrong
no I didn't
you guys ride the phone
fervently
[Music]
yeah fervously doesn't exist according
to my dictionary
fervently
ah ooh light and shuffling
passionately
fervently no that was also passionate
oh [\h__\h]
all right okay
sorry that was loud I listened to the
pronunciation
mm-hmm
and navidadi thank you for the pinky
bless you swap my oh she looks cocoon as
[\h__\h] I'm in love with the details the
color scheme the hair armored Kiana is
real always wanted to see you in an
outfit tailored to your Warrior side
artists please give Kiara a huge spy in
there I beg you
but he gave me spy hander for TWY hands
try means too
yeah he gave a new meaning to try
Handler now it's basically a four-hander
because I'm yeah
I'm doubling the Spy hander
uh yeah I don't know about that logic
but you know
I'm using one hand
hurts my hander
so you would think no to try and you'd
think I would use forehand but
unfortunately I don't so I have to use
one hand purse by hand
yeah
but uh it's quite quite difficult very
very heavy
um yes my strength is that I have to
skill more into the strength stat
yeah I'm working on it
I am buying a re-skill scroll to change
all my stats I have misstated
it's calculated my stats unfortunately
even though I'm a warrior I accidentally
put it all into
what could it be
what did I put it into
cuteness Charisma oh yeah
yeah
laughs
why the [\h__\h] would you do that why would
you go all in on charisma
I get all in on ends I get all in on
crits I get all in on strength there's
so many builds where you can go all in
but Charisma what the [\h__\h]
oh yeah waiting to trapages is also the
the case right sometimes people do a lot
of Charisma and they're only good at
talking
yeah yeah
the speech check
persuasion just make everyone bend their
knee to you
you say no enemy Goblin shows up says I
will kill you and you say bend your knee
and they're like okay
well easy easy
maybe that should be my next strategy
whenever I play a 2trpg
that looks amazing might be my favorite
yet congrats on getting such an amazing
artist especially when connected to
Tales over rice looking forward to those
jrpg streams and it looks like you
learned last after all
last for ah the outfits yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I I have seen gudas and Ames
at least like progresses
I've seen them
yeah well I I can't say more than that
I skipped a few seconds ah I see it
sorry I'm going back there in a moment
oh yeah
yeah no no they do exist
yeah
they've been in the works I wonder when
they will reveal them I hope soon
I have a feeling AMA is gonna be last
unfortunately
because of the state that I saw them in
that is my personal guess
but who knows maybe maybe Nami Nabi mama
is gonna catch up but also it's not only
in the artists the rigging has to
you know
the raking has to be fast too
but I'm pretty sure am I gonna be last
I didn't think that she would be last
because I think I remember
when I
like still was looking
for an artist for mine last year I feel
like I already saw
like
um
I miss like concept or something like
that
[Music]
um
and when I when we started working on
mine I already saw a draft of Thomas
no I was really sure about it because I
had to get a new artist and at the time
where like you know it was like okay
myth you're getting new outfits this
year what do you want to do do you want
to go for a theme or do you want to do
your own thing and then everybody said
let's do our own thing and then
um I was still under the impression that
I was gonna get my own artist
but then everybody you know started
planning their things
and before like I was putting together a
plan
uh and I sent it in and then it took
them a while before they even got back
to me to tell me sorry
we can't do this Concept in the first
place
so I was like okay hmm and then I was
also told
um you can't can't go we forget Papa
this time because you know reasons
no and then I was like okay so that
already took
quite a lot of time until we got to the
point where they told me sorry you can't
work with hook at this time so then I
have to start start from scratch again
by finding an artist first and all that
also takes some time I tell them maybe
this artist maybe this is this and then
they go out to check and it takes them
like maybe two or three weeks to get
back to me to get the okay
you know they're like discussing things
and they don't just like go and send out
the the requests to do it I think they
wanted the the concept first
so I had to make the plan first and then
we presented to the artist and they
think about if they want to do it
[Music]
my
my rejected Concepts
um
let's just say I wanted something that
references something that hookah Papa
created
yeah and and the fact
um
that yeah
that it's like two that my what I wanted
is too similar to
what he created
even though he was gonna draw it was a
No-No
yeah
but I feel like even now
we kind of still went into that
direction kind of because I'm you know
dark armor I'm not as like
clothless clothless as the BlackRock
shooter characters but
no it's just because you can't like copy
like existing
yeah
things no
you know
Creations because of copyright and maybe
there's gonna be trouble you know
unless yeah I mean something like Corona
that was like a sponsorship thing so
obviously she has permission for it
some things might be okay some things
might not be okay it's a case-by-case
kind of situation yeah
um but yeah
in the end we still kind of got
something similar to that in in some way
um
but yeah since it took me so long to
even get to the point of finding an
artist
that's when everybody already
probably put like reached unless they
unless they just wasted a lot of time
but I don't think so because I saw I saw
drafts very early from Ahmed too
well that's why I thought I was gonna be
the last because I was so behind on
creation process
mm-hmm
swath must work fast
he was definitely working fast and he
was motivated
and he was excited I could feel it
I would ask her something and he would
implement it but the only problem was
that
what I would get back is the draft
overworked with the implemented things
that I asked for but he would also like
add and remove other things
partially things that I liked and then I
was like can you can you put this back
can you remove this I thought it was uh
fine
yeah
just like he was constantly overworking
everything every time I got the draft
back it looked so different to me
yeah it was a bit difficult because all
the communication as I told you I think
was going for management
so there was always also like a delay
in communication mm-hmm
but it ended up fine it worked out fine
yeah
yeah that holds up the process too yeah
what happened with my PGM oh there it is
I think I've called you every compliment
uh Under the Sun except cool really
well you're looking insanely cool I'm a
Wawa finally I'm not much of an artist
but my mind is exploding with ideas and
I'm feeling inspired oh I can imagine
I still want to draw myself too but like
especially next week honestly I could
already make my weekly schedule because
I think everything is pretty much set in
stone
for next week
so I don't think I can squeeze an art
stream in next week but maybe maybe
sometime within this month
maybe I can draw
alter Wawa
with narrista together because I feel
like visually we will look so good
together you know
the blue and the black
I want people to draw Alto Wawa with
narissa
yeah people I've been seeing people draw
normal wobbles with narissa but I want
to see alter Wawa with narissa
um
ah there you are see she's always
listening I can't uh
you too right
who knows maybe Mama Luna is cooking
something because it really seems like
she's cooking something she tweeted I
replied welcome back because she tweeted
that she's been like not able to watch
anything uh whole life related for a
long time and now she's trying to catch
up what a coincidence just now she's
trying to construct what a coincidence
and she posted a froggy Wawa clip of the
VR Easter stream that's ages ago
um
yeah and then I saw people you guys you
guys are recommending her some clips
including uh the nerissa one for example
um
and yeah she missed oh yeah it's just
people sent her the Kobo Cali Arc
stuff and I thought I thought you know
uh Mama lonely would enjoy me and Kelly
doing so many things and getting along
so well these days but she's just not
been around she hasn't she hasn't
noticed but but now maybe she's like you
know noticing everything and and
catching up yeah yeah maybe she's
cooking something who knows
I would be so happy to sing Wawa and
Mama Looney salad again I really I just
love her art style so much and
I miss it
finally the gacha has relinquished her I
don't think so
I don't think so but it's
she has been able to escape for a little
bit
there's there might be a reason why she
has been paying more attention
um not only there is some
um there's there's something I've I've
been I've been cooking something too
uh yeah well you will see
oh no oh no oh no you guys will be
[Music]
um
you guys will be so curious everybody
will try to
guess what we're cooking
uh
anyway
I'm gonna keep my secrets yes dances
[Music]
where was I
uh
thank you for the recipe I'm trying to
compose myself who this lore Edition all
of the video was incredible the new BG
area looks perfect yeah
I I was basically asking Eden to make my
office my normal office but in alter
version
and I also like the video the lore video
was already finished at the time when I
let Eden work on the background so I
gave that as a reference but for the
lore video I also gave Mazu references
of what I was imagining
yeah like a medieval office basically uh
but like a luxurious luxurious one not
like a really cheap one
like something in between you know so so
you would see that oh this person must
be important because
the office is pretty
pretty nice
yeah so
um the office the new office is
basically uh um alternative version of
the old office altar office
yeah
um swapped an amazing piano altar is
vlogging beautiful the theme the armor
buff hairstyles impeccable I love the
ponytail so much wow that's so good
another win for the ponytail I say I see
it's so Charming I know I get it
ponytail is irresistible
yeah altar office that's what it is okay
I will turn to them
[Music]
wait I read them and they were only free
from what I see
already done with them
[Music]
travertine I'm so happy that you're
happy
wait owl done camping your name now says
all done camping but this was at this at
the time when you sent the super chat
right you went camping oh fun
fun
I want to go camping too
only went camping when I was like a
young young child
[Music]
how was it did you catch some fish or so
how did you what food did you eat
[Music]
I want to know I want to know
I don't know when I'm ever gonna go
glamping
I don't have time for it but if I want
to go I should go before like at least
before winter
no fish
what what did you eat
yeah glamping is glamorous camping sorry
I'm late no problem hi there we're
ending soon
my throat feels kind of exhausted and I
need to cook
because I lied yesterday I felt really
so I didn't cook I just ate like a small
like noodle salad and a piece of the
cake and then I went to bed I lied I'm
sorry
steak and pork chop oh wow did you grill
it did you have like a portable grill
but yeah now I'm gonna make food no it's
still not expired today today the
chicken is expiring
I calculated everything today the
chicken is expiring and
um
[\h__\h] the the beef or whatever it is is
expiring on Monday so today I cooked the
chicken it's a Saturday on Sunday I eat
The Remains The Leftovers
and on Monday I cooked the beef and on
Tuesday when the new hellofresh package
comes I eat the leftovers of Monday it
was all calculated
chicken expiration date don't worry guys
you're not expiring
dates aren't 100 exact I'll be fine
otherwise I'll sue hellofresh no problem
thank gravity
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you for the pinky everything about
this outfit is a 10 out of 10 very
fitting for the whole Ian jar jrpg Queen
you and okay have been waited more than
a year for this outfit and the results
were Beyond expectations yeah we did
wait a long time thank you Wawa and swap
for this wonderful creation thank you I
hope that I can get like we were trying
currently or until now
to um
you know get the next outfit within the
year that's actually four and it was
going to be like December but honestly
that's kind of like if I really do my 3D
birthday concert in December then it's a
pack month anyway with Christmas and New
Year's and many other concerts that also
have been now delayed to December
uh so I wouldn't really want to reveal
it in December anyway and The Artisan I
asked for
um
because yes it's
not gonna be hookah Papa again
um uh says they can't do it until
December
so
who knows
you know
I'm sorry
yeah probably not
[Music]
it is what it is
but I'm taking advantage of it again
[Music]
Mariah Carey outfit wise
and a little sad but um
times change
ah oh because of Christmas season
no no yeah yeah I see it that way too
now
don't want to think about no it's any
other way because that's just sad yeah
foreign
anyway I mean look at this new one it
was awesome
and I feel like with
like getting like a new artist in to do
something like that for me it's their
first time usually I would say
to do something like this and
you know getting to work for whole life
for an outfit that will be showcased a
lot like it will be used a lot I feel
like any artist would be like so
freaking excited to do that so they will
give everything
they will give all their time and love
for it that's what I've noticed with
Suave
so and and I think they will try to
fulfill all my wishes
so it's they're very Cooperative
Co-operative and and
more motivated yeah
yeah and I can give Spotlight to other
artists that I really like that I want
to work with maybe
[Music]
foreign
exposure no no cover is paying them
they get exposure too but they also
surely I don't know how much they get
paid but that is calculated behind the
scenes but I'm sure they get paid a good
good sum of money definitely
um
[Music]
I really don't know though
serious actually
I wonder if they would tell me
yeah
because I only hear about how much
Indies pay for their outfits
I don't know how much we pay our artists
but I think it's a lot
[Music]
is
foreign
yeah that's one of the things that we
don't pay so
thankfully
yeah they get loads of exposure too of
course yeah
anyway anyway uh where was I oh yeah
thank you for the sweet pinky did I read
all of it thank you well as well for
this wonderful creation I think so I
think so I think so
um
[Music]
I'm gonna leave it at that because it's
already half past 11 p.m I I know I know
in my schedule I wanted to start one
hour early tomorrow but I might just
start at the same time because I feel
like it worked out nicely today like
that
um
yeah
please come to see tomorrow my GTA
stream again we're gonna we're gonna
clear that
camp that we died in twice today
tomorrow for sure
thank you for watching and in German we
saying and good night I love you guys
thank you for being here
hope you have a lovely rest of the day
or evening
good night
and
um
um let me see
[Music]
what Bijou will be playing Elden ring
the rest I will play
evera Kuda will play hula cure again why
is she playing so much holokia right now
she played six hours or so right
you're trying to farm for the new the
new
expansion
huh
yeah yeah yeah lots going on lots of
stuff going on during n a prime time
it's fauna doing what's that thumbnail
uh every DLC
oh raccoons
raccoons
there's raccoons
something for everybody
um
okay so I'll see you bye bye bye
see you tomorrow
[Music]
laughs
huh
[Music]
I would rate puamoko but I can't I don't
have perms which is weird because they
rated me but I can't read them
don't have red perms
[Music]
the only one
why can I read fauna
[Music]
I can read fauna but she's not starting
until a little bit later
and I don't feel like that makes sense
because you guys are gonna probably do
something else anyway when when a stream
isn't even starting yet
no rain today
yeah I gotta tell the Advent girls to
open up their rate poems
when I return to favorable rating my
project
okay bye