[Music]
do
hello everyone
hey
you god was uh it's quite essential
today hey what no listen i'm trying to
change
oh yeah what does a cherry blossom gus
sound like that's nonsense
are you soft and feminine and sweet and
pink
aha
wow that's what it sounded like
okay
interesting
i'll remember that i guess
thank you welcome everyone welcome
welcome to this read-along uh of the
manga bloom into you what is it in
japanese kusatori do you remember
by the way
who is this who is this chicken that is
on top of my head
chicken excuse me
what the hell listen you smell like
gravy dude like
that's why chicken comes to my mind
i hope you're not hungry
no i'm good i'm good
oh yeah so uh
[Music]
uh from home of english
and yeah today we're reading sievo
mm-hmm yeah
the english version of it
um
i was looking forward to this but i
didn't think that the audience would be
like so excited about it
yeah yeah i was really surprised because
i mean it looks like a fantastic manga
but as soon as you had posted about this
on your schedule um
all i all i saw on on my twitter feed
was oh my god i can't believe it's
happening oh my goodness oh my god call
an ambulance help me um people have been
waiting for this
yes it would it would appear so
i want to give one shout out to uh jolly
who a long time ago before this was ever
planned uh made um like redrew
an animation opening video of us
uh like
like
this this manga has an anime and she
redrew the animation opening video with
us instead of the main characters did
you see that i think i know what you're
talking about
i do actually recall
is the song
i remember the paper cup and the string
in between yeah that was so beautiful i
wanna go watch it again
yeah yeah
i think after one after reading the
manga it will be even more special cause
like i never watched the anime i never
read the manga
well it'll make for a very different
experience no no no i've never read it
before or seen the anime so i'm very
excited uh to dive into it
okay
yeah yeah we will by the way read only
until the end of chapter two that's how
far we're allowed to read indeed
hopefully that will give us some good
insight into the story and everything
already right i'm looking forward to it
and oh yeah we will be reading uh the
characters as i'll be reading the black
haired girl and you the twin tail girl
right as people recommended it
yeah that's how people recommended it
now i know that looks wise it's a little
different because i am a bit taller than
you kusatori and my hair is long however
yeah this character also seems to have
pink well actually it could be orange
it's like a combination of you and mine
peachy color
yeah
combination of our hair colors
so i think that that's uh that's how we
will that's how we will read the
characters oh man i gotta warm up my my
voice acting vocal cords
haven't used them
i haven't used them since dad youtuber
manga so
yeah you did that really amusing read
along before didn't you yeah i sure did
also that was um
very graciously uh allowed to us by
bookwalker you guys i should mention
bookwalker before we get started um so
on bookwalker you can read all kinds of
manga and light novels too i believe um
all kinds of stuff on bookwalker uh that
you may not be able to access at your
local bookstore so i recommend that if
you're a big fan of manga or maybe
perhaps uh this series for example if
you like it a lot go check out book
walker link in the description below and
you can use either my code or chiara's
whichever you prefer either one's fine
either one will make both of us happy so
go for it
please do if you want if you if you
don't know this manga yet specifically
and we read until the end of second
chapter and you're like i want to read
more then that's what you can do read
more
yeah you should do it definitely so
please check out the link in the
description below if you're interested
and with that being said let's go i'm
excited
oh
let's read it together
a long time since i've read uh a manga
especially on stream and a long time
since we've collaborated actually
interestingly enough so yeah yeah yeah
i haven't read a manga in general in in
millions of years yeah it's been a hot
minute huh i feel that
all right here we go this is chapter one
i cannot reach the stars okay
the words in shojo manga and love songs
they're always sparkling brightly
i don't need a dictionary to understand
the meaning but i've never felt them for
myself
[Music]
i kind of get that i have a bunch of
friends who are really into shojo manga
back in the day who had that kind of
feeling
i read a lot of shonen personally but i
can understand
the sakura blossoms have gone from pink
to green in that time i've gotten used
to the new uniforms
and the steep slope in front of the
school
but there's still one thing that hasn't
changed since middle school
this is you my friend
how many why is that actually
yeah
the quality is currently surprisingly
bad let me try to pop no
no
why
wait wait wait wait wait wait um well i
can't i can roughly read it i think
it'll be fine okay good luck
no
who are you talking to
oh no one do you have club activities
now akari
are you uh have you still not picked uh
a club yet
oh
was that me
i was supposed to read that right yeah
that was you
not not you the character that was that
was you was
kusa
maybe wait maybe you know what maybe the
quality is better if i read it on
youtube not on discord oh yeah
let me try
uh
morty
channel oh my god okay uh
wait the next slide not for me from you
anyway let's see uh let's see um
recruiting is going to be over soon
that's the side character
whose name i'm sure we will learn soon
but the next one is you i think maybe
track and field oh maybe track and field
oh we are on the next panel we're on the
next panel
okay let's see
maybe track and field or handball
badminton looks fun too or maybe i
should change things up and join a
culture club or gee
you're so indecisive oh nice nice new
voice come on
just join the basketball club aren't i a
little short for that hey short nah
you're fine
wait who is the next one you
excuse me
i know that's someone else i guess
who's saying that let's find out
let's find out oh it's teacher sensei
ah yes
yeah let's go do your best
if you're having trouble deciding on a
club why not join the student council
student council
what that sounds boring
oh our student council actually does
quite a few different activities it's
fun not so different from a club to tell
the truth really can i do like a trial
visit can i give the teacher a try
here we go
oh what
are you interested then
that would be a huge help sorry i wanted
to give a little sheriff's spin i love
it
okay let's see student council elections
are coming up soon and i've been looking
for someone to help us out thanks a lot
that's not me
i'm not saying that it's a
i little bit
thought that was your your me you
i guess i guess because the speech
bubble is not pointing to the character
the character's not speaking
we'll figure it out guys we'll figure it
out figure it out you just gotta feel
it indeed so the next one is
uh the next one is yoodal
all right let's see i feel like he
pulled one over on me ah so tricked by
the sensei i see sensei gotcha gotcha
good
but i guess i don't mind checking it out
i think the student council room's this
way
what the
it's so out of the way
where the heck is it
there's someone nearby
is it back here
yeah on the side characters when you're
when your character is is the man oh
you're right uh now now she's there toko
will you please go out with me
i'm i'm sorry but i can't
oh
i see
i guess a guy like me isn't a good fit
for you
don't don't say things like that
you shouldn't put yourself down for no
reason
it's it's just that i
oh
i don't intend to go out with anyone no
matter who asks me oh
no
um is is somebody there ah i'm so sorry
i swear i wasn't trying to eavesdrop or
anything i just couldn't find a good
time to come out i'm sorry
come on
hey cute
cute hey
just just keep what you saw a secret
okay
of course
[Music]
and the chat goes
hey don't you all get it twisted okay
get twisted do not get it twisted your
food hey listen
hey
now now hold on a minute now i've got
the feeling that you are now pulling a
fast one on me kusatori hey you know i
always
can i tell you about something callie
what
remember when you made the chocolate the
vent has chocolate for me
and the letters that you wrote on there
like your own name it looked like you
wrote cabbie instead of cali yeah and
you know how you always say hey listen
and you know how certain uh the legend
of zelda character is called navi and
always says hey listen oh
yeah i'm aware
i think you're navi because you once
misro your name is covey
okay
hold on
now listen i did [\h__\h] hold on hold on i
need to like my thoughts
one moment one moment please
okay we're good um you can't get out of
this all right well i don't really i
don't know really quite what you're
talking about i can't confirm it but
okay whatever you know what you can go
ahead and continue living on your little
fantasy land i'll let you i'll let you
do that my dude have fun have a good
time i guess next week
yourself but enjoy yourself i guess um
okay of course a red ribbon so she's a
second year
wow
yeah you're my senpai whoa
what what were you doing over here
anyway oh uh i was just looking for the
student council room
ah of course it can be pretty difficult
to find
originally the space was used for cal
cali graphics
but
later it was given to the student
council these days i think the only art
classes we offer are music and fine art
uh really
you really know a lot about these things
i suppose so
ah
yeah who's that that's you cause i'm a
first year oh okay
you must be the first year who's helping
us out today
oh
yes
but here we are
um i'm nana mitoco a student council
member nice to meet you
nice to
meet you too
did i do good did i do a good job
i'm doing my best
you did
i'm still like a little bit like unsure
of their like personalities and and what
voice to read them because your
character looks super super cute but uh
togo looks like more like a little bit
more mature and quiet i don't know yeah
which is why like i'm so surprised to
hear that yeah voice coming from you i'm
like whoa kusatori can do that kind of
voice
well i can do manual voices baby
hey hey
all right we're back in the classroom
sorry
well what's down student council do you
think you'll join seems like they're
pretty busy uh i'm thinking about it
there was a really cool senpai there
oh
whoa you are you finally interested in
that kinda
uh um it was a girl
oh i figured as much oh what
but
but she was really cool
she's nice and pretty and super good at
her job her name's nanami senpai
uh i've heard that name before
she's been more popular than the student
council president since her freshman
year
uh
when you said a cool senpai i was sure
it would be a guy
how was basketball club akari as if i
needed to ask
oh man senpai was this coolest ever
yesterday
i still mean you did choose this school
just to get near him oh my gosh
wait who's the next one
um i'm not sure i'm gonna help out here
koyomi if you join a club you might meet
someone too
uh i i uh wait wait koyumi is that
probably the last name of is koio me the
last name of you no chad help us no uh
u's last name starts with a k but it's
not it's not coyomi i don't think
okay this is confusing well i'll just
read it in some voice
i'd prefer someone older
seriously i'll help out with some of the
side characters as well yeah okay uh
the next ah the next one is not you so
yeah
uh i thought we were finally gonna get a
love story out of you should have you
should have known better than that why
they got a doer like that that's so sad
come on
hey they look very young they don't need
love stories just yet yeah exactly take
it slow you guys like life is life is a
nice little stroll until you meet me so
just like chill and enjoy your youth
enjoy being young you guys geez goodness
gracious anyway we'll continue reading
the story
hey listen
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
hey hey
i just
even the hey
okay never mind there's nothing to
listen to anymore
on the day of my middle school
graduation a boy asked me out i still
haven't answered him
i thought about asking akari and koyomi
for advice but
oh
oh oh is that me oh
i don't intend to go out with anyone no
matter who asks me asks me
that's senpai
would you like black tea or coffee
oh oh oh thanks uh black tea please here
you go sayaki senpai
oh
thank you we really ought to buy some
sugar soon wow that voice is perfect
who's saying that this room really feels
like a home if we're unsure i'll go
ahead and take it yeah
yeah it's comfortable it's comfortable
isn't it
so
toco is it true that someone asked you
out again
oh how would you know about that sayaka
oh you're calling i'll do my best
oh please don't underestimate my
intelligence network
but seriously the boy you turned down
told me himself
i got this but but seriously
it's okay it doesn't need to be perfect
it doesn't need to be perfect
it's all good it's all good here i'll
give it a try
okay
but seriously the boy you turned down
told me
himself wait what why
but you know
i don't think it's all that embarrassing
to have been turned down by tulko
there's been at least
10 since we started high school right
you've got nothing to lose by trying
really
if they're just asking for kicks what
would they do if i actually said yes
yeah like that would ever happen
she's even had girls confess to her
before
well now
so that sort of thing really does happen
okay you can stop talking now
okay putting that aside hasn't there
been anybody who's caught your eye
uh i feel a little bad about it but i'm
just not interested i see
is there a reason for that or
a reason huh
not particularly it's just
although they all say they like me
none of their confessions made my heart
go tokidoki
i like that picture right there oh
goodness yeah wow it's so so dramatic
i feel like i'm i'm going a little doki
doki oh okay jeez goodness wow the art
is so beautiful in this in this manga
it is it is i like the style the art
style yeah
so amazing um about that
oh excuse me
i'm interested in joining the student
council
oh oh are you a freshman welcome
okay
now we return to the we'd return to home
and it looks like there's a text message
coming
[Laughter]
that's that's what uh used phone sounds
like i made that up on the spot
who do you think is writing this message
um
i think it's oh it's it's the it's the
confessor
sorry to text you so late i'd like to
hear your answer soon is it all right if
i call you after school tomorrow
oh
and she writes something like i
understand sorry to keep you waiting so
long to
get it
forget it
back in school
oh
they're talking they're talking and and
then oh yeah okay you are you okay
um
i'm fine it's nothing i'm sorry
you seem to be distracted by something
mm-hmm i think we all know what it is
though
maybe
let's see opens the door
she's not here yet
i guess it was silly to run all the way
here but i thought if i could ask her
about it
[Music]
here early koito-san that's quite
admirable
senpai
sayaka said she has to take care of
something at home so she won't be coming
today
it'll just be you and me
you coming
um
that only works in english though
right if we were reading this in
japanese we couldn't make that uh we
couldn't make that joke
i kind of kind of like that um
senpai
oh
well
uh what ended up
happening with that boy
the first year who came earlier
oh him
uh
this isn't what i wanted to talk about
i know that's probably your fault i
think that's okay it's all right is it
probably not uh he's going to be helping
us out he said he'll come starting
tomorrow oh
that's great
um maybe he'll be able to help you with
some of your duties too
i think that was me the next one was you
i think
it's it's fine it's fine it gets a
little complicated
sure maybe
maybe maybe he'll be able to help you
with some of your duties too
sure sounds good
but how can i ask
ah
thank you very much i'm sorry i should
be the one making you tea
oh i don't mind luckily i don't have
much paperwork today so we can chat for
as long as you'd like
since your face tells me there's
something you'd like to talk about huh
really
does my face does my face tell you that
um
anonymity sounds like your face is easy
to read for some reason
what no
no
no hey no
um anonymity senpai
so uh
you ha so you have to respond oh this is
you uh not you this is takanashikiyara
okay so
you have to respond to his confession
he must be pretty serious if he's been
waiting for a month now
still
wait no that's you
still it's not like i know him so i'm
not sure if i can help you oh decide
what you have to do oh this is also you
okay
it's not like here i want to give it a
shot it's not like i know him so i'm not
sure i can help you decide what to do oh
it's not that
i already know what i'm going to say
oh
i
do
like him
but i think i'm going to turn him down
whoa
yeah at first i thought i was i was
freaked out because i thought eh it's
not like i know him you don't know him
and he was like hey let's date people do
that though
yeah never spoken before hey let's let's
chill
that's a thing that happened yeah i
guess still yeah i guess it makes sense
but yeah i'm gonna tear that i'm gonna
turn that [\h__\h] down for the sake
of having a boyfriend girlfriend
yeah it happens a lot i think at this
age as well
[Music]
yeah um anyway i'm turning that a little
[\h__\h] down so yeah
i was gonna
explain why i guess i was in the same
class as him for three years we talked a
lot sometimes we'd hang out outside of
school too we had a lot of fun and
and so
ah can i talk to you after the ceremony
yeah that's what he he sounds like that
it's probably a guy talking it
what's this about
oh yeah
they look they the love they talk about
in books and songs is always sparkling
i'd always longed for it for myself i
wanted to feel like i'd spreaded wings
like i was floating in the air i had
high hopes
oh well actually now that i think about
it at this age probably his voice isn't
that low any uh not yet anyway oh yeah
it might sound exactly like
takanashikira
you'd be surprised but i i dig it i
think it's great
that makes fun of him
yeah you dummy oh i kind of feel bad
and yes
my feet were still planted firmly on the
ground oh
i i kind of
it's interesting because i kind of like
i can kind of see
why she might feel that way especially
at that time as well
you know you read a bunch of shoujo
manga and you feel like it's it's gonna
be like you're you're floating on air
right but just like with life not
necessarily only with romance sometimes
the things that you read about in the
books they don't they don't sweep you
off your feet like you thought they
would you know
that's right
[Music]
deep deep [\h__\h] challenge hey i'm just
saying i'm just saying i think that
that's really interesting
i think it's a nice i think it's a nice
look at real at real life it's very
realistic anyway
but why why do you want to go out with
me
why isn't it obvious you're so special
to me i just want our relationship to be
special too oh man
uh
can you give me a little time to think
oh
it's all right i'm sure
my wings are just growing a little
slower than other people's but soon
any moment now
oh
i wanted to be able to say yes i want to
go out with you too but
i don't understand i've never met anyone
who's felt
special to me
i couldn't ask my friends for advice
about it but
none of them have made my heart pound
i thought maybe you would understand
anatomy senpai
so
pat it must have been hard to feel like
you had to fall in love
you had to fall in love sir
well you pat everyone loves talking
about love and romance sometimes
i wonder if there's something wrong with
me
you too
eh
[Music]
that's uh
you i think
yeah
i think so the long black hair is not
yeah it's not it's the bubble is in
front of i'm gonna shut up now i hope i
can explain my feelings as clearly as
you do
you'll be fine
just honestly tell him how you feel
the same way he told you
a girl touching my hand
oh my gosh
ah
wow
there's nothing wrong with the way you
feel
hello
i'm really sorry
thank you
oh thank you i think that was the guy oh
maybe
yeah
you too
thank you
thank you so much
i don't know how i would have done it if
you hadn't been here senpai
oh
um senpai
uh
you
[Music]
yeah our hands were still clasped
tightly together but it wasn't my hand
that was
was sweating slightly still holding on
quitting
yucky ain't got to go wash them hands
you said
you've never met anyone who's felt
special to you right uh
that's right
and you're sure you don't have feelings
like that for anyone
yes i'm sure
there's no one
i'm sorry i'm currently watching on
youtube so i always try to wait a moment
naomi senpai
vampire this is going so fast what's
going on oh my god
whoa oh my gosh you're you have your
hands on my shoulders you said you were
the same way oh
you said i will
yeah go go for it my my dude
i know wait that's that that is you that
is you you said we're the same way
didn't you
no
i'm different yeah because
because
i think i might be falling in love with
you
i don't understand what is she saying
but wait a minute a second ago
but you said i will not go out with
anybody no siri i don't think so i don't
want to do that and now it's like whoa
let's maybe i think i love you my dude
well
wait uh i'm invested yeah i'm invested
you already read the square bubble
yeah i don't understand what is she
saying i know that it may have sounded
like me speaking as myself because yes i
didn't understand what she was saying i
didn't understand why we have gotten to
this point right now but i'm invested
i'm investing
yeah
the left the one on the left side is
just uh
let's see
this is this is all the student council
has been longing for a person who can
fight those bugs it's not really a big
deal this room's full of them whack
wow i don't know how you can do that my
dude that's a strong mother f word all
right bloomington chapter two okay guys
we're going to read already no what the
hell oh it's okay already it's okay we
can we still get to read one more
chapter
yeah end of ch i know right it's it
seems like it's going by so quick it
goes so fast yeah
i'm invested
wow first blush
oh i actually saw um i saw a takamori
fan art that looked like this and it was
with us and the other holo ian girls
yeah yeah yeah yeah i've been seeing a
lot of generally a lot of uh bloom into
you fan night with us as the characters
especially today everyone all the
fanatics have been going like speed like
to draw as many scenes as possible well
i'm happy that everyone's excited i am
happy for that me too for sure
oh it's bath time oh my gosh in the
shower whoa
oh my god bath time oh my god why am i
here too oh my god okay
in my thoughts
i mean not in myself in those thoughts
you think about me when you're in the
bathtub the funny thing is um when i say
you it could mean both oh my god so you
you think about
okay no go ahead hey
i'm flashing back to your words where
you said i think i might be falling in
love with you um nanami senpai
huh i'm sorry koito-san i didn't mean to
blurt out something weird just don't
worry about it okay
anyway time to get back to work okay
[Music]
blah blah blah i mean
we are both girls i've got nothing to
worry about
still something about the way she was
looking at me
it's time to hand off our duties good
work this semester everyone
cheers
hi
yeah come by
she hasn't really said anything since
that day
maybe i was reading into it too much
uh do you want to do the math
i have an idea actually kusatori how
about for side characters you do uh the
ladies and i'll do the dudes
oh yeah that's better for me
and even
and even if like the the speech bubbles
like come one after another like you
have two speech bubbles in a row even
though they're different characters
don't worry about it just go with it
okay
oh okay okay
president uh
what do you think you're doing you can't
just waltz in here after barely showing
your face around here the whole semester
come on i've been busy with my club
activities and stuff
hey first years sorry you got plunged
into all this so suddenly you really
saved your butts
maki and
koito right
uh it's okay it didn't take too long to
get used to everything if i get lucky
maybe i'll become an officer someday
well that's up to toko over there
that's right isn't she the future
student council president
that hasn't been decided yet but the
elections are starting soon sure but
you're running for office right it's
practically yours already
you know it's not that simple
well
excuse me for believing in you
i like the sassy one i like this sassy
one
why why don't we get some more soda
and then someone says hey
hey listen
is it just me or does toco seem to be in
a good mood
you think
there's no way nanome senpai won't be
nominated for prez right
i mean even as uh first year she was
basically the face of the student
council since a certain someone pushed
all his students off on her
uh
i'm going to say this wait who's psyche
sayaki is the i think the the very uh
regal one yeah what about you psychic
senpai wouldn't you like to be president
no i'm all set like always i'm just
happy to start stay by toka's side and
support her what if she likes her
oh man there's going to be some conflict
oh gosh
what an election too of course
oh yeah i wanted to talk to you about
something
i'm going to need a campaign manager
someone to help me with election
activities and such could you do that
for me koito-san
ah
that was very cali huh
excuse me
uh oh yeah oh man that's a tough one
this sucks
what does the campaign manager even do
um i think i'd help her hand out flyers
and make posters and stuff
oh wait why did i stop moving oh yeah
and you're gone oh my god i disappeared
it's okay i'll bring you back to life
don't worry i mean it's kind of ironic
for me but yeah
it popped out
it's cool uh same as before
okey dokey one one moment
hey
there right back where you belong
because satori right back in the exact
spot
nice wonderful perfect smooth smooth
very smooth okay cool oh where were we
oh yeah you were explaining me what
campaign manager does yeah flyers and
stuff
well that doesn't exactly sound like fun
but i guess it's not too bad if that's
the only thing you have to do yeah i
know but i'd also have to give a
campaign speech in front of the whole
school act
that's pretty bad that kind of stuff's
uh pretty hard for you isn't it
uh
it seems like a lot of responsibility i
don't know if i can do it
wait do we go down until we go to the
left panel i guess the left i oh that's
a good i think it's down
okay yeah we go down why not just tell
her no
i tried but anatomy stamp i won't give
up on the idea
she's she's really taking a liking to
you huh i guess though i don't know why
naomi senpai already has psyche senpai
doesn't she
apparently they've held the top rankings
ever since school started here
they stand out just by walking side by
side oh yeah she's definitely the rival
oh
man it's real juicy now okay
interesting wow
uh she should be the logical choice for
anatomy senpai but
um
she's she's really taking a liking to
you huh
no way
oh no now you see the the the
like super cool appearance of er
volleyball yeah
oh yeah you're gonna fall in love oh
she's the sporty one oh man
okay someone shouts to tyson
ah thanks oh she's so jealous whoa
baby i'm excited to see where this goes
oh my gosh in the beginning i thought
she was just like a side character like
the the regal side character
[Music]
but toku generally seems to be like
super popular in school like yeah with
girls and with boys huh just a super
popular one huh um
sayaka
you're in fine form today
i i said i'm sorry how can i make it up
to you
i don't know
i guess i just assumed that would be
your campaign
she's mad oh man
i know i should have talked to you about
it first i'm i really am sorry see
but i still want koito-san to be my
campaign manager
why is that
i mean she's a pretty capable person so
it's not that i doubt she's up to the
task but
i still don't get it
uh you aren't taking the election
seriously right you're not letting your
guard down just because everyone's
saying you will win are you
i am taking it seriously
i just
think it makes sense to have a first
year be my campaign manager i mean i
think it's pretty reasonable
actually jk i i changed my mind it's
nice
definitely yeah because like the first
year we're like what would she know
right no and also because she said hey i
think i'm falling in love with you so
like you can't really take [\h__\h] like
that back uh you said it so
yeah
there you go i mean
me may it's awfully early i made a month
okay may is awfully early to hold the
election so the first years won't know
the candidates very well will they
i suppose so
they might end up feeling like it has
nothing to do with them but they'll pay
attention if they see a fellow first
year standing at the podium
and instead of having her sing my
praises the whole time i'm going to ask
koito-san to give her honest
assessment of me
wait do you want to read the
blonde girl for now i'll give it my best
would you like my voice please
here i go
let's see um i think you still have one
more
oh that way it will show i'm willing to
listen to everybody's opinions
pretty good don't you think oh we're out
we're out of that scene now okay
thanks magistrate
uh oh but i think those um square ones
are the ojo thing
they're my thoughts but they're also the
ojo samas as well because let's see what
she says here take it take a quick look
take a little peek
that was a pretty good explanation
but is that really how you feel
because to me it sounded more like an
excuse
i agree with that [\h__\h] she right though
besides if i win i'm going to ask
courtosa to be an officer what's an
officer a pretty high rank i think
like uh not vice president but like like
under vice president
yeah so
i think fighting fruiting election
together will be a good way to build
trust
then
in other words
you want your bond with her to deepen to
be deeper than ours
wow that's real straightforward all
right pretty blunt okay
[Music]
oh
yeah do you really think that sort of
thing could come between us
they're already like really bonded those
two right
yeah
is she a player hold on a minute
what
[Music]
i don't know
i wonder who she really should we should
read
i'm trying to i'm trying to read their
emotions okay
come on you're not playing fair
fine then i'll allow it for now
thank you sayaka
but i'm not gonna be happy with you if
you lose the election got it
just you wait i'll win for sure
and i look forward to you being my vice
president ooh
yeah
start
all right okay now
uh since he was in a picture i'll speak
the blonde girl again yes let's go
this is for you
is this a script for the campaign speech
uh wait okay uh i wrote it thinking i'd
be reading it myself so you'll probably
have to tweak some things
feel free to pick out parts of it or
even just use it as a reference
um i'm not sure i'm gonna be any good at
this
but i'm sure you would psyche senpai
i suppose that might be true
but there may be things that only you
can do
toco seems to think so anyway
so take good care of her
if you say society senpai
okay then
i'll do my best
do it
interesting i wonder if there's going to
be some sabotage
oh well we're now officially partners
for the election koito-san let's give it
everything we've got
i'll do as much as i can but you're
probably gonna have to show me the ropes
okay
no worries
you know i had no idea you could be so
pushy nanami senpai
i just really wanted you to do it but
why me
uh so um
yes
the other day
uh what was that all about
i think i might be falling in love with
you that
um that that was um
um
i'm really sorry if i made you
uncomfortable
i kind of just it kind of just came out
i wasn't thinking oh no i mean i know
you didn't mean it in a weird way hear
anything
and then the train comes
[Applause]
i can't do this
yes you are correct you are correct
nothing like that i mean
we're both girls right and well if we
somehow weren't it's it's still not like
i'd ever fall in love but
oof
senpai you can't just stop like that
somebody's head
oh i know what's uh
what
what's going on
[Music]
stop it you can't do that in my ears
you can't in my ears
in my ears
you know what i really kind of
you gotta admire the tenacity of this
senpai because
a second ago she went straight from
sorry if i made you uncomfortable please
forget about it say hey i'm gonna smooch
you right now
he's a bit weird
yeah a little strange but it's endearing
in a way
to clank
when i said love
i meant that kind of love
oh
no i'm with you
my heart pounds
though
i've never felt that way toward anyone
before
[Music]
oh my god
chatter chatter chatter did no one see
that [\h__\h]
no because that was the train we went by
oh we went to the other side i see let
me go look back real quick yeah so we
walked over the railroad and then the
train i get it
they were all behind the train hey nice
nice timing nice diving talkers pretty
good timing i will say senpai
that was that was pretty dope
what should i do
i
shouldn't i be the one asking that
question
hey no don't tell me this is the end of
the chapter is it
well let me see what page it is hold on
uh yep that's it
[Music]
that's it
right
i want to keep reading it
you get me to go so doki doki and then
you do this to me
i'm sad
what the heck
we can we can read more and we can only
write
technically yes technically we can that
is a trick it's so cute
it's so cute
gosh what a cute manga i'm a big fan
i have you said this before the stream
but like
they both definitely don't really like
have the exact the same personality as
we do so it's definitely a different
kind of dynamic but it was really like
fun to get into their characters and
react these scenes
as if we were them
yeah i feel like a lot of times the the
really like sort of calm and elegant uh
popular uh senior isn't really the one
who like makes the move i guess
um
i mean well that's not totally true if
they're a popular senior maybe they
might like the the quiet strong one
doesn't always uh make all the moves so
it was interesting to see to see you
become like very quiet and like uh and
senpai-like i don't know it was
it was a new experience for me i've
never seen you like
i've never really seen you like this
before even today a normal person you
were getting you were getting really
excited over these scenes kelly i have
something to tell you no i am a lover of
i'm a lover of um of of beautiful
fiction and sweet relationships between
characters um beautiful girls
yes very beautiful ladies i gotta say
though i am probably um the biggest a
big fan of the the short one
um you
i love that i love her hairstyle is so
cute and the hair
color twin bells they're really cute
the people have been
even though they told us to read it in
this kind of uh um like i should be
total you should be you even though they
tell us that i've seen a lot of fan art
of you with the long hair and
me with the twin tails i guess because
it's just cute to draw us that way but i
would like to request uh official fan
art with me uh long straight hair and uh
kelly with the shorts twin tails please
thank you yes yes def definitely um
though i can't i can say that i guess uh
actually no that's a lie i'm really not
the the strong quiet
it's not true i'm a bit crazy so yeah
though i would say that we aren't
exactly the same as um these characters
it was fun to embody them for this time
and kind of whoa you're going kind of
nuts there do i have to match you
well we totally can are we going crazy
now we're going crazy because we don't
want this cliffhanger to be here right
now but we have to we have to end it i
guess
of course this is where we gotta end and
of course it is
loading
loading ah
well unfortunate but it was really fun
and uh the art is beautiful and okay can
we just oh my god uh okay we give a
shout out to the offer who before our
stream drew us
did you guys see that on twitter if you
if you didn't see it guys you should
check it out oh my god i think we both
retweeted it
[Music]
you guys
who drew this beautiful manga
i'm actually really hooked now i want to
watch the anime i haven't watched anime
in millions of years but i want to give
it a try i'm really interested now
yeah i'm hooked 100
actually we might end this stream and i
might continue reading it well
just saying but already you can use the
coupon codes though you guys the coupon
codes cali or kiara and if you use it
600 yen off of your first purchase if
you're a new customer that's almost free
guys this first volume yeah it's like
five bucks yeah
that is a deal so i recommend you guys
go check it out okay yeah please do
yeah i guess uh our time together has
come to an end but i missed
collaborating with yakuza tori
[Music]
me too but yeah there's like just like
the time passes so quickly and one week
we collab with one person and next we
will collab with another person it's
just
if we would collab more often we would
have like five collabs per week so with
every girl so yeah it's difficult but of
course we will always
we will always be
friends and no matter who how much time
passes there will always be another
tacomatic collapse so don't worry guys
the crumbs you have you can't stop
picking up the crumbs there will always
be a big sandwich at some point of
course
and you know what even though we might
not be collaborating all the time i
gotta say like you know we're both busy
doing our own stuff on our own time but
you you've been killing it with stuff
that you've been doing on your channel
as well just just by yourself two i'm
like always constantly like wow
kusatori is killing it recently
because i can imagine like you being on
a on a like like conventional stage or
whatever like another doesn't have to be
a convention but like what at dokomi i
was able to hear everyone's voices when
they were cheering and i was able to see
their pen lights and all that so that's
like so different from a normal like
youtube stream so i hope you can do that
at some point like wrap your songs on
stage and hear everyone's like cheering
you have to do that that would be a
dream come true
yeah yeah i saw all the pictures from
your experience and i thought to myself
wow kusaturi is doing really cool stuff
you know i'm sure you'll get to do it as
well very soon probably who knows i
don't know yeah i hope so i hope that
someday we can sing together too that
would be dope yeah
i wanna
be waiting for it hopefully one day we
can do it again i mean oh oh yeah we
actually you know like recently i found
out about this yamaha sink room you
probably know it too yeah yeah yeah i've
heard of that before i use i've used
a karaoke stream together yeah
that would be so fun
i definitely want to
be happy
yeah
until then though yeah it really has
been a long time and i'd love to sing
with you again at some point rather than
just a game collab so let's see what we
can do someday um until then though hope
we can play more games and stuff or read
more manga like this maybe
yeah
yeah anything but i think we both uh
maybe because we both kind of suck at
games we both kind of enjoy music a bit
more than we enjoy games maybe right
for real so karaoke collab would be i
think maybe even the most enjoyable
thing for us
yeah i would love to do that sometime
because satori we should make some time
for it in the future
um yay
i always have time for you
ah
thank you thank you for i am also
excited about a future collab i will
make some time in my sketch i will
pencil you in
oh thank you very much thank you kindly
hey are you making fun of something i
say because i use that word a lot
no actually i i was just trying to you
know
be
be polite
okey dokey
18.
everyone thank you so much for coming to
watch us read this beautiful manga that
i love very much
i'm very thank you everyone
thank you so much you guys for checking
it out and um i guess i wonder what we
should sign off on but before we do a
quick thank you to bookwalker once again
uh for letting us uh use them to read
this thank you bookwalker link in the
description you guys check it out i'm
your mori hope you'll remember me um
should we sign off uh in in german
maybe we could do some goodbye with
takamoti
okay uh i'm not very creative so i
wonder what we should say
um
[Music]
that's kind of boring um it sounds so
long
talking worries way too long
a glory to takamuri glory to taco
all right
if it will if it will satisfy you in
chat i will i will let's go with it i'm
cool that's fine yeah
all right rhymes don't you like rhymes
callie i do i i do enjoy a rhyme or two
okay
sure let's let's do that then fine
on the count of three we'll say glory to
uh to the uh takamori all right
ready
three two
one
glory to takamori
goodbye everyone
see you later peace
peace
stream sparks
[Music]
do
you