[Music]
w
hello can you hear me I feel like oh
ever since I took out the bean bag out
of this room it's not very nice
Acoustics hey it's me again second
stream of the
day but I guess it's already like even
for me it's already the
17th oh my God freckles yeah did did you
notice MH also kind of cozy
today um because I feel like GIC phone
is kind of a cozy
game I'm really curious who the artists
are well well well I will be introducing
them so I guess we could get right into
it this is probably going to be a little
bit on the shorter side because well
it's midnight for me and I don't want to
use up too much time of these artists
you
[Music]
know yeah maybe an hour and a little bit
we'll see how it goes but in case you
don't know in case you're a little bit
new here I did this stream two years ago
but back then it was because there was a
garic phone hype and I was uh I don't
know I wanted to gu to do garic phone
with some good artists so that like not
everything that comes out of this is
freaking
scuffed while that has its own charm too
but yeah it's been like two years yeah
it's it has its own charm too but then
seeing like totally awesome Arts uh be
made in a short amount of time I like
that a lot so you
know H that was my idea and then I
brought a lot of artists together very
spontaneously
so so back then we had a lot of great
artists uh but uh this time I'm I've
been trying to get new
artists uh sure um I think everyone
except for one artist I think is
new um let me check really quick I think
we have one two including me no without
me we have 1 2 three four five 6 7
eight no wait
there's wait cuz I was taking screenshot
no that's that's okay no should be eight
it should be
eight okay okay okay I think I think I
got
everybody so let me introduce to you the
artists that are part of this today with
the eight that means we're going to be
nine
right okay first of all we
have
t Apple Blossom tea who I think the art
is very familiar to everybody who has
Twitter or or even I don't know even if
you don't have Twitter cuz there's a lot
of girls who use their art for
thumbnails I've been using it cuz it's a
a very special style very special art
style that is like kind of like childish
but uh sometimes I draw a little bit
more mature as well yeah but so
[Music]
cute and so thank you for coming here
today then next up we have have
Tang Pung M but this art that I chose to
show you guys shows they more actually
untypical art style because normally uh
I think most of the art that you see
from them is like pretty how to say like
chibi simplistic yes yes because Pon is
also uh working with us uh on Advent
calendar so they're really really active
and they're really fast they work so
fast yeah so so so so yes yes
[Music]
yes
Y and then we
[Music]
have
meu very familiar artist I think if you
follow uh if you look at a lot of uh
kiar fan art um maybe not So Much
Anymore recently
but was definitely very active as a
kiata fan artist in 2022 and 2021 as
well yeah yeah very soft looking uh
pretty gentle art
style very pretty yeah yeah I saw I saw
like their retweets of old the art
that's why I guess this was like pretty
much at the top of their tweets go check
them out they have really really gentle
looking smooth art m
and then we have
T I don't know should I call them fuu or
fading I'm not sure um but this artist
this artist recently has been going
really hard on the kiata fan art and I'm
like so honored to receive so
much beautiful art from them what the
and they even answered to some of
my requests like draw me with
Shion put Tales of arise yeah so so damn
skilled and also very fast yeah so I I'm
I'm looking forward to what they can
draw today
here and then we
have let's do Gia next
G Gia also has I think a very iconic art
style that we all have seen in the
community stinky rat
o and um is yeah I don't know it just
sticks with you in your brain but I
found this picture very interesting
because yeah they've been drawing me for
a while now but they're they've like
made so much progress too that I'm I was
really impressed with yeah and their
style changed quite a bit but you still
can recognize it cuz especially cuz I
was looking at it like like you know
throughout the whole I don't know one
two years m
so I got used to it I didn't realize it
changed so much in this time in these 20
months apparently I didn't realize until
I saw this picture let I'm like wow yeah
right oh
God okay okay okay thank you and then we
have
Duma of course Duma D is very prominent
in the kfb
community
this is the person who has been taking
care of the kfp cheis the Polaroids and
generally my uh all my chickens yeah and
the members emotes uh the members badges
mhm the god of chickens I want to see
some cute chickens please thank you and
next we have I wasn't sure what picture
to show um because mostly they're
animations and the not animations are
still art but Loot and I don't think I
can show them but we have caou in the
boat what let's go Caillou Caillou K you
yeah the goat that is not only the god
behind Holo cure but also a a amazing
artist why did I stop moving amazing
artist on their own uh in their own
League not only artist but also animator
like oh my God what a God I'm restarting
my app here we are okay thank you for
being here today mhm mhm and then we
have two more artists two
more we have P Papa wow P Papa we all
know Pak Papa oh why am I oh what
happened when I restarted the app oh I
just
noticed please ignore let me get rid of
this okay now it's my cat ears what the
hell okay P papa is well literally one
of the papa Mas of whole life and uh
works like even now still is very
supportive has always been very
supportive of whole life English
especially so thank you thank you thank
you for being part I am honored but I
also like kind of thought they would be
a great fit because um he speaks good
English
seemingly like from judging the tweets
and and them like watching so many of
our
streams and this is yeah this is bio by
the way in a in I think it's like some
game she played like you know a mix is
it Devil May Cry or something like that
I don't want to say anything
wrong yeah DMZ yeah yeah okay okay okay
okay I got it I got it so thank you
and then last but not least I have one
more oh my app died again I guess okay
not not doing very well today
T
Co who is maybe you recognize the art
style P Papa
Mama yes from Pomo but has drawn me also
before and has brought out this uh art
book before with like generally also H
life but also ni Sanji YouTubers Etc so
a big vtuber fan and artist of several
uh
vtubers what a lineup right what a stack
lineup so go the show go the show wow
wow wow my lineup now I will send them
the invite I think we're going to start
with normal and uh here slow just normal
I have some I have some
uh now they can join I didn't forget
anyone
right they asked why why did you make me
last because because I I don't know it's
kind of a sick wait it's not sending my
URL and URL maybe they think it's spam
let me send it with some letters
oh it it keeps on saying message fail to
send it's not spam I'm trying to get uh
do I need to write more um Twitter this
is not spam please let me send the
URL I have a DM group ah there it goes
there now it works okay telling Twitter
it's not spam apparently
works just tell just yeah believe me
trust me bro trust me it's not spam wink
wink wink
oh my God I'm excited wooo I I I will be
the shittiest artist out of all of us so
I am basically depending on you guys on
You Beautiful artists to draw good
[Music]
stuff what's
ABT
ABT apple apple apple apple cool
nickname that it
who wait wait okay I think they left no
did they wait oh they changed name ah
Mis Mis Mis okay okay okay okay I think
we have
everybody okay they they said they're
all pretty nervous there's no reason to
be nervous so just have fun and draw
some some funky looking art um let's
let's Galu uh here we go we start with a
prompt I'm nervous I can't draw so
either uh write a sentence okay so
because we have like mixed uh
nationalities I want to keep it
relatively easy with the prompts uh no
weird words but I did make some notes of
what I what of my
ideas yeah yeah yeah uh but let's not
say it out loud because they might be
listening and then you know have a
really clear no VC no no no no last time
we also didn't do VC let's do
[Music]
um uhhuh mhm okay it's kind of difficult
but I'm I'm proud of the prompts that I
thought of before cuz normally where's
my pen normally another sentence no oh
it's still the same okay normally I uh
when when it comes to this I I think of
it spontaneously and then I can't think
of anything
good my my thing is oh crashing
great great why is it crashing so much
today six out of nine once everybody has
their prompts in it will start or if the
time Runs
Out ah please don't give me a difficult
prop I can't draw so well oh I have no
no
confidence let's go let's go maybe the
blanket no that's should that shouldn't
be an
issue
one
more whoever is still riding it oh
dear Yahoo I love that I love that
prompt already let's see um
perfect oh I have a good
idea uh how to draw froggy Wawa small
hands small
feet big body and big
heart the ears the
eyes eyes not
ears face goes like here okay okay we
have so much time I decided to give them
a lot of time so hopefully we'll see
some sick
art I love how we have such a great
um how to say height difference okay
it we're just not going to be
moving today it seems um what was that
oh yeah frog frog bird I I I'll draw it
as if they were also they she was also
wearing like a suit like
me like froggy
wa but frog bird is really
lengthy let's put the
arm smoothly around
froggy
[Music]
waa wow I want them to sit you
know my art is very shitty there's not
even faces yet oh but we have so much
time frog is long very long longest frog
in the
neighborhood I wonder if maybe pom's
Pomo artist came up with this because
maybe maybe they watched it pus hair I
have time to look it up right pus hair
which which direction does it look your
poru rain
buff oh okay let's give her wait you can
choose the color like this right yeah
yeah yeah yeah let's
add this hair accessory to make her very
recognizable it's kind of like flappy
and um some people might say this is
cheating I say no I'm I'm just striving
for
Perfection and I am ready to do anything
for that she's so cute my
God and she's going to be
[Music]
blushing because she's never been with a
with a frog Woman Like Me
maybe the the little hair accessory
maybe we'll add that
too
oh her fairy
accessory a is she recognizable now I
think she's pretty recognizable but I
want to I want us to sit um on like a
I'm imagining like a picnic
blanket we're doing a picnic
date I feel like people should go out on
picnics more
often look looks like a checker board
now oh wait I'm running out of time now
and I still have no face uh uh uh uh uh
what do I look
like this is
me
enjoying my time
with this sexy frog
[Music]
man okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
M some grass here to make it clear we're
we're picnicking is is it clear maybe a
basket yes yes am I missing something
maybe my feathers uh what color uh
uh like this okay okay and maybe maybe a
pond this is my dream date P are you
[Music]
listening dream day
oh okay y pretty decent well with so
much time I think they're going to whip
up some cool stuff I'm done
six out of nine people are done okay go
go go go let's go now it's your turn to
describe the scene what is happening
here I am melting ice I suppose oh maybe
out of this maybe C is trapped inside
Kiana
melting ice
block cie is
inside I mean now I'm doing it as if we
were trying to do like an animation
where there's like progress in in the in
in the story but uh I'm just I'm just
making it even more interesting
okay Fire and Ice yeah fire I defin now
hot passion Never back
down I'm drinking orange juice I noticed
today all all I ate I think was the
cookies that I made guys cuz after I
woke up I pretty quickly cuz I stayed up
so late I pretty quickly went to buy
some extra groceries set up my stream
and then I
started that is plenty I don't know
about that cuz it's literally it's like
midnight now and I only ate like five
cookies or six cookies throughout the
[Laughter]
day yeah after this I'm going to make
myself some
pizza and then I'll be too excited to go
to bed kiaha takes a kawaii selfie ooh o
[Music]
M interesting interesting I do I do like
to take kawat selfies every once in a
while more in in the past than
[Music]
now okay phone but honestly the angle is
normally I would take pictures from
above but okay uh uh uh how to how to
see I I don't even I don't even drawing
under time pressure is the
worst I need to look at myself even to
remember what I look
like
ah I love to
wink I love to wink it's my habit
and then o how
about we make we'll make it a a little
bit
[Music]
loot bring out the the
waas
yeah
[Music]
nice does it look like I'm taking a
selfie maybe if I do like
P
whoa no don't worry guys this is just my
summer
outfit what does this look like a shark
mouth this is the eye and this is the
the teeth can you
see it looks like a shark mouth wait I
I'll try to reset my my thing again
maybe maybe it will start moving now
belly
[Music]
button let me fix this
boob actually let me I want to fix all
the
[Music]
boobs like this BBA I haven't drawn bbba
in a
[Music]
while
uh and then
armpits okay and the hand like this nice
now we can add some color I
guess after I've add some more
details okay
good oh my God I hit
selfie oh I got to add sparkles
that did it have sparkles and and hearts
too I I'm not
sure okay let's make the phone black
wait no I think my phone is W is isn't
my phone white I don't remember because
of the case but most phones are black so
let me do it like this and maybe
add like a
lens but nowadays phones have like 20
lenses so let's add a couple
more how many cameras does your phone
have guys not including the selfie Al
those I think even some phones have more
than one selfie lens don't they feel
like I've seen that before going
crazy four three I've got
three you already in the
past okay it's okay I I drew I drew some
quite intricate I would
[Music]
say let's give my swim the color that it
needs and
deserves how many lenses does the latest
iPhone
have cuz I'm not an iPhone user so I'm
not sure about that what's wrong with my
rip case still holy
okay oh I got purple eyes if I recall
[Music]
correctly nice nice nice nice nice I'm
done rip wait you don't say rip rip rip
cage did I say rip Cas I mean rib cage
Namy wa no not numy not Namy it's not
Namy it's me oh
cute wait who drew this I like this cute
it's Ki and Nissa sharing wait the is
the pineapple in the middle on a string
or something they're sharing pineapple
pizza right what of this big pineapple
in there's so many there's so much
pineapple and so much
pizza
a cute ah so like I think that's a
string and then eventually we'll we'll
be touching the pineapple but I don't
think we're going to try to eat that
with with its uh outer layer the
spaghetti scene but with pineapple pizza
I'm not sure how that would
work pineapple pizza on pineapple pizza
no pineapple on the pizza pizza on Pizza
on pineapple why Pizza on pineapple
why pineapple
pizza yeah I love this is cute I love
the the way my Beret is sitting on my
head like I'm a French
lady I guess I do have French Roots
after
all yeah I look so
French are we wearing like pizza clothes
too shaking hot with
kiaha so this is where the prompts start
to get a little bit like what happened
shaking am I shaking her or is she
shaking because she's scared m
[Music]
M how do you draw this like typical
anime shook face wa I need hatam my
reference why why would why would she be
[Music]
shaking
dama maybe maybe what what would she be
she's scared of nothing is she like why
why would she be scared scared of
me like certainly a tarantula would not
scare
her maybe the maybe does she does she
like pineapple on Pizza ah the pepponi
and I know she likes the
[Music]
pepponi intricate hair ah the
peponi but the peponi does the peponi
scare her I think the pineapple would
scare her I think I heard her saying no
to pineapple pizza which I was really
shocked
about like what that's where you draw
the line do you guys remember her
opinion on pineapple and
[Music]
pizza I'm not 100% sure but I feel like
she said she doesn't like
it what what what don't trust her food
opinions
[Music]
she clearly likes the peon she said she
likes pineapp oh really then what uh
what maybe she's just scared of me but
like why would she be scared of me
[Music]
right drawing hands let's go let's go
drawing hands like a boss cuz I'm not
scared of drawing hands no no
[Music]
M wait if she's shaking maybe I'll draw
her body like
shaky it just looks like she's wearing
fuzzy
clothes wait she has like long hair in
the
back let's let's make it like go up like
she's does she look
shocked so okay half half of the time uh
wait shaking shaking hat with Ki should
I just shake with her uh uh uh
okay I mean it does say with okay not
much time
so what are we scared of
[Music]
though I don't know if I should add
anything that we're scared
of orange hair orange hair blonde hair
blonde hair blonde hair blonde hair does
it look like
hat
[Music]
hat let's give her that that ribbon why
am I still working on hat I need to work
on
myself kind of
yeah uh
[Music]
okay
I'm just I'm just like this now okay
doesn't even look like
me what the is going on
here what's going
on I'm drawing my
uniform uh her her
outfit has
Ruffles speed speed speed speed speed
speed speed speed speed I got to be
speed when playing this
game oh what's this part in the middle
oh more Ruffles I
think so what's here we will never
know okay
okay okay a bit more color a bit more
color okay hopefully it's recognizable I
think it's pretty recognizable can't do
much more scared of Yago scared maybe
maybe the YouTube Bonk whatever it's too
late for that anyway oh this looks good
let's
go
[Music]
Ki
cooking M but not just cooking like I'm
really really M hungry when
cooking
chicken uh employee I hope that's
understandable for I think they said
they'll like if they don't understand
they're going to use deep deep
L should be
fine I forgot to click oh it doesn't
matter like it will just take whatever
is uh like at the end the the last state
of the
picture
jimmmy why is it always Jimmy is Jimmy
even still
alive poor Jimmy well Jimmy has had it
coming oh actually I think it I'm not
I'm not uh stopping to move anymore am I
okay we're all good we're all good I
guess we're stuck with the cat ears
though let's go let's go I think uh
we're round seven so I draw one more
time and then I describe something I
think and then we're done I
think I draw one more time what we good
K oh why would she do
that Gaa Gaa
[Music]
reference oh that's really thick let's
go for something thinner by the way guys
anybody here who's who hasn't stream uh
who hasn't watched a stream of me
in a while but it's here because I'm
streaming so
[Music]
late here Chef head for only because I
want to look recognizable okay that's
the only
reason Chef Let's Go na time yeah more
or less what time is it guys in 19
okay so here is going to be GAA trumping
on me but it's not going to look very
cute because how do you draw that in a
cute way if you're not a good
[Music]
artist 300 p.m. is
3:40 8:41 a.m. 8:41 ah wait you're on
the on the other side of the globe
you're not on the na side right so for
you it's like already morning okay
[Music]
this doesn't look cute wait maybe if the
eyes are like way
closer yeah closer is always better and
then make her pretty
small
Big Mouth
g science of
cute can I study that I mean if Harvard
has a uh if Harvard has a course about
Taylor
Swift then surely in some University
they could do like a course on science
of cute how to understand how to how to
replicate cute I mean especially maybe
when it comes to to like an
art artsy University right
[Music]
surely
jump There She Goes jumping on my head
and trying to get some of that
gravy there definitely is you think so I
guess it's not even that crazy of an
idea m
[Music]
wait I I have still so much time let
me or for like a full
color nice nice nice we have so much
time
okay and then good out well GAA
has white hair so there's not much I can
do um
[Music]
let me give it some detail though you
know yesterday I randomly got a
recommendation so I watched a a vlog
another Vlog of someone going to the to
Ouran concert last
year and and again it made me feel like
man so emotional and I I really hope we
can do that
again
[Music]
M let me give her some
hands she's going
like
cute I
think I think her clothes are pretty
dark blue oh but they have a white
gradiation
you don't look like you hate it though
yeah I'm i'msure I'm
unsure how much time oh yeah
[Music]
B attack GA attack cute it's still 2023
oh oh oh yeah almost next year but yeah
I I hope I hope we can do it
again sometime you know please is
management Ian management or whoever
decides these things
then what the I
am am I puking out the universe or am I
trying to get rid of the heat certainly
this person was also confused because of
the question marks am I am I trying to
is the is the universe so hot that I'm
trying to fix it but like why would I
spit water
[Music]
I would say my first impression even
though I guess it makes no sense
is spitting water at the UN but
like I'm lasering ah the blue should be
laser but what am I doing what am I then
why what is the
c um
ah
ah where's my
keyboard sucking I think I'm sucking in
the universe this I feel like it could
be a way of drawing a sucking
motion like I mean like like vacuuming
it mhm
[Music]
mhm I wonder if this like original
prompt was by puckle uh puckle say maybe
display mode U manual let's do manual
voice over off exhibition Flo will be
shown from the beginning oh beginning
okay let's start let's look at what we
got our first album together and it's
already 46 minutes a past minute what
the man and P are bringing the
daughter to school I'm looking forward
to this one let's go a cute wait where's
the
daughter misunderstanding mine is the
mother and she's is bringing her
daughter pekora to school okay okay okay
that's cute
too oh a
hi M taking P to school I guess yeah
that's that's what it turned
into on a bike oh cute that is very cute
I like how how smug picota looks in the
back as if she's looking forward to it I
doubt it but now there's nothing about a
school
so M and PCO and bicycle but PCO looks
sus oh no please do not bring amongus
into this punon punon do not disappoint
me please don't don't don't no
no okay thank
you what why is p first thing on M huh
we're in a different kind of universe
here
why what's going on P aiming at M's
boing boing see yeah that's what could
be happening in this picture but like
wait the bicycle is gone now the bicycle
is
gone oh aiming oh it's a gun oh she's
she's she's probably jealous of the
boing boing so she's shooting she's
about to shoot her boing
boing
to yeah interesting like very very
different pictures but they're all
really
[Music]
cute I like this kind of confusion this
is actually maybe it's better to do G
phone with like some people who don't
understand English that well because
then there will be even more of this
like misunderstanding scuff k p ah it
was you
Daka oh I wasn't even a pom
artist wait my AR isn't even that bad
compared to what the others have drawn
is it like I drew quite a lot of
elements and you know so it's pretty
intricate I would
say
yeah it's good right froggy mama and
frog pom picnic I really hope this gets
to uh uh uh wait are they wait which one
was it
[Music]
again which one
huh which one is a p p maybe the K right
the K it's hard to tell it's it's okay
right oh
wait a a we didn't even get a a pomu
artist drawn pomu face it's just
completely frog but that is very
accurate to the to the stream yeah can
eating cookie from a frog it's not just
any frog oh did you not watch
yesterday's stream did you not watch
yesterday's
stream that's just any oh wa this is
kind of cute
oh I think P Sensei Ki art is really
rare so I I need to save this I need to
download this cute kiaha eat froggy waa
yeah okay that I could see how that
could be interpr interpreted as
[Music]
that yeah we have to assert dominance
over froggy w I love this I love I love
finally the tables turn kiaha eating
frog kiaha
delicious yeah pom pom where did you go
this was so
T and then we're
eating
frogs we ate her frog bird is no more
frog bird is history
show froggy W trapped oh another froggy
W prompt in Coca-Cola oh oh interesting
prompt how did you come up with
that cute cute wait Pon where did you go
I'm going to send a new URL
afterwards or or you can join the same
one we're not done yet I want to draw
one one more round I I'm surprised it
took up so much time but we're going to
do at least one more round Kiana who
drank all the cola oh frog yeah I guess
she got so greedy for the Coca-Cola and
then she like got stuck in it I could
see that I could see that I forgot to
save oh should yeah I guess I should be
saving all these well it's saved in the
Stream oh okay froggy why want no more
because frogy W is gone
Quantum why the is it quantum I
don't understand you had to fully drink
Quantum what even is quantum a pun on is
back nice what is it what what is wait
am I the only one who doesn't understand
what's
quantum Fallout reference I wonder if
they all really understand it oh wait is
this the one that ends up with the
universe sucking that I interpreted as
this is cute cute kiaha drinking the
universe booze yeah okay see rather than
shooting something at it it was taking
it in so me saying sucking it is kind of
correct more than what you guys were
saying at least nice I'll save I'll save
I can't go back apparently oh wait I can
I can shut up there let me save this and
let me go back and save this okay okay
okay okay okay save save save
next okay pomu pom's artist says kfp eat
fried chicken oh no understandable
understandable wait they're crying while
eating one of their fellow well it's
okay guys it's okay this is you knew you
knew this was bound to happen it's okay
guys so cute gum Mia you need to draw
more chickens they're really cute
looking at Fried Chicken ah well who's
probably they're going to interpret as
me yeah yeah yeah yeah oh nice that
looks like M Kentucky Fried Chicken
bucket maybe ooh ooh wow I like how it's
like turning literally like the normal
our normal chicken is like turning
gradually into the Fried
Chicken empty ah ah wait so that I think
the the misu gets
shown this prompt again yeah yeah yeah
okay and that's how that happened okay
okay okay okay no problem no problem
don't worry about it it happened
sometimes in garic phone this is so good
y hunger and when cooking chicken
employee oh oh what do we get wait this
looks exactly like my my doll that doll
so good cute the chicken with the pan
eyes you got a cooking a chicken yeah
Duma not just any chicken the chicken
that you have basically
invented so it's kind of your fault if
you think about
it K and hatam waiting for Santa in the
fridge okay there's um there's some kind
of like inside of knowledge here it's
it's I think more or less the fridge is
a reference to what happened to me in
the studio when recording my
3D uh and then I kind of requested
someone to draw me inside a fridge um
and they were up for it but in the end
it I said don't worry about it don't
don't waste your amazing skills on such
a fan art but that's probably why it's
brought up
ah so that's where the hataki prompt
came from waiting for Santa in the
fridge
oh we're going to attack him or what
kataman Kiwa in view of Santa from the
refrigerator yeah okay yeah yeah yeah
very
detailed I like like that oh it's cute
it's cute but it could be interpreted as
Windows no it's just shaking hat oh okay
okay and then I was like what are we
shaking for oh but look it's pretty good
like I'm I'm I I was worried I'm not
going to be able to keep up am I am I
keeping
up we were freezing yeah because it's so
cold
K and hatam scared yeah it kind of
changed
here ah perfect Punks on punon never
disappoints with these like cute chibi
very expressive
Arts kie just won the best mic all right
though the V awards are happening right
now
oh oh best music video but no surprise I
mean could have been suicide too could
have been any of the other of course as
well
oh I know rule four but I'm actually
curious so keep me updated I don't think
I'll win the dong category cuz I only
really advertised it once and it's a
twitch event so it's probably going to
be a twitch YouTuber winning so that's
totally fine I don't I don't really mind
at all I I know I am the best d d
YouTuber of them all at least in the
English sphere I
know it's okay I win in my own heart
fire K melt us so it did have to do with
cie good that I brought back the cie cie
is inside oh big brain wa big brain
genius
[Music]
wyy me and punon we have the
telepathy see ah very good good very
good she looks kind of
dead are you okay
k w I like how I'm like I'm like
clenching my fist and I go like to
activate my fire
powers nice K's power to bring cie back
to
life yes that's that is more or less
what's happening yeah a cute ah with a
feather ah cute why is what's the that I
don't know why is the chicken
there cute revive nine does that mean I
have like nine more revives can I use
this feather to revive cie from Death
that was a very simplistic way to draw
cie but as long as you name tag it all
is
good oh
oh am I slapping her with the
feather that's really aggressive Ki come
back to life slap slap slap slap
can you can you even slap someone with a
feather like it's so
soft cute I like it K slps cie with her
feathers again is that even possible I
love it
though I like the gression mild
aggression next door there's so much to
look at wow only one round and we're
already in an hour oh my God I'm so
sorry but it took like 20 minutes to
like announce who's participating no and
K eat pineapple pizza oh that was that
was Paco sensei's idea
[Music]
oh yum yum yum yum oh that gets me so
hungry actually my my dinner for tonight
is pizza um frozen pizza but it's not
pineapple sadly they didn't have any
more pineapple pizza looks so good I
love I love the like the the Doodles of
Punk song I love them so much n s eating
pineapple pizza
yes this is the one that I saw it's so
cute I love the French
wow probably not on purpose at all but
so cute can I nerv a sh pineapple pizza
they went out of their way to like make
it into a romantic moment
too we're like sucking in the cheese and
the pineapple looks so good with those
lines and the pizza the shape of the
pizza is so
aesthetic oh wow never get a sucking
cheese out of pineapple pizza what what
what it that's kind of writing it like
that is kind of slang I'm actually uh
shook head to the core to see Pomo
artists use slang like that is that on
purpose or did they just miss out the
the double uh the the
H oh wait it's
Caillou
wait did
I am I are we missing p
s wait what the
wait wait
to
ah I just realized we're going to make
another round and bring you in here did
I 1 2 3 4 5 6 1 6
six seven wait it's my mistake I set the
number too
low I'm so sorry no this has to be this
has to be fixed we're going to fix it oh
no I counted wrong I'm going to
quiet there's one Intruder no I don't
think so no no no no there's no Intruder
anyway this is cute though K me eating a
me ah because of the black hair ah it's
narissa but yeah I can tell it's kind of
hard without the blue in the
[Music]
hair difficult difficult why did you set
a limit uh yeah good question why did I
oh my God I'm ashamed magical kiaha
magical
magical yeah I just didn't count myself
probably
this is so good this is so good I'm
so cute I can recognize p p sense's art
style oh is this my my idle outfit maybe
or is it a new outfit Ah that's ah we're
taking a selfie ah that's where that
came from and why did I loot myself we
will never know Ki taking a sexy self s
Fe
[Music]
mhm
nice that's that's not kiaha that is
Froggy waa we are two separate people
we're not the same like really no no no
no no we're you're misunderstanding
something we're not the same person fry
taking
sex thank you for
providing the prompt that the world
needed I I CL oh my
God Mis you're so good at
this holy froggy wa must have been
corset training her waist because that
waste is zero Ines holy wow that is
the waste I aspire to have
whoa
SC good to eat kiaha delicious yes oh I
got this prompt did I not oh no wait I
didn't yumy a that's so cute see this is
how you do it Ki pass Ki this is how you
draw it in a cute way gooda bites K's
head and Ki
cries I would I would probably cry yeah
a cute another example of how to draw it
cutely and then probably me next no
still not so we'll get another good
example of how you draw it
cutely and
then then you get my shitty
example it's not so bad it's not so bad
it's not so bad I like
yes okay all right okay okay okay okay
thank you marvelous round I hope
everybody is okay for one more round and
uh unless if somebody has to leave that
okay
[Music]
to I'm gonna do one
no
ads
ads now I have to edit the bot
no I have adlock but somehow it's not
working here
I've got a
Mor 10 right 10 okay um should we do the
same cuz I I still have prompts that I
want to use and classic is
fine okay oh my
God she was that wasn't that like a she
hit the floor she hit the floor got to
go L low low low low low wasn't that
uh
I think that was the same
Melody oh my God oh my God ads I
hate you so much Flow Rider Ena one best
artist let's go let's
[Music]
go the whole club looking at her she hit
the flow didn't my message no
Twitter no it's my
phone so sorry here is the new round
please
Twitter sending no failed X is over
capacity please wait a few over
capacity over what do you mean
um please Twitter let me post
this what's what's with Twitter again I
get the same
oh M
Twitter please please
please will it s no um okay that's kind
of messed up uh how much do I have to
write blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah test test test test test
test test
test help please new
link
I'll send it um
might
okay how about now oh okay I said I sent
it in separate messages now it's
working so
stupid I don't understand Twitter why
you got to be like that why it is what
they say I'm so
sorry the God is here the creator of my
beloved
Pomeranian I'm so sorry let I hope I
hope we get to see a lot of Sensei
now I'm so sorry okay I think uh one
more this who are we
missing cuz before we we had nine and
then wait no are we missing
someone are we missing someone now
before I set it to nine now I set it to
10 but when we were nine we were missing
someone right uh did somebody say that
they have to go or so no right
[Music]
I uh8 N no I think we're wait can't see
the screen oh you can't see the screen
right oh somebody yes
me okay
[Music]
Tada okay we're going to do same setting
so it's easy easy easy easy are you guys
ready y my show I'm excited I have I
have so many good prompts I don't know
which one to
choose um but
St maybe bit faster no I want to give
them time I have narissa ravencraft
buying Ki merchandise or Fu moku barking
at OKO or Ki dancing at her Freddy life
of chickens or Ena sleeping on the floor
or only selling her whole life DUI
makura is
crying I I had some thoughts before my
stream the narissa one but we I guess
maybe not because we already had narissa
appear in one of the
[Music]
proms for for working
at not one one bow
bow okay I want to use more of my
prompts the artists are welcome to use
my prompts I have I have some good ones
Ena sleeping on the floor Ollie selling
her whole life D makas
crying no rain punching you in the face
or L ton L tonic I feel like I in a past
GIC phone stream I certainly used that
prop
before need more GIC phone round for
real I should do more only one is Legend
right I kind of like the idea like she
she maybe she's broke she spent too much
money on the duim makas and then
realized she's now Adept so she has to
go sell the dakim makas while crying
I I don't know what's with my brain but
I have these these these big brain ideas
in my
head
yeah yeah I was thinking like I wanted
somebody to sell dakim makas and I was
like thinking who who who who could be
in this position and then I realized the
biggest s of them all Ollie Tak
together
I'm okay okay let's gum um how about we
we make a big plate and then we make a
Tacko dii just yesterday I realized that
the silhouette of a
takachi has the same silhouette as ena's
head and yeah that's just a realization
that made
me bum
Boozled they could pose as her in a in a
dark room situation or
so that also looks like a hat oh the
onion ring uh yeah well she doesn't
always have the onion ring on her five
onion
rings
[Music]
no and Taki face what does wait I have
an idea I don't really remember their
face
but
[Music]
this is accurate
right this is accurate I would
say it's psychopath
Tak nice needs to free F what Pac-Man
ghost they've seen things okay now me
drawing I'm in and and Ena will not live
up to the standards I think but um
okay wait I need I need am reference oh
biggest am Gosling needs arm reference
hey yo wait where's my Amelia
Watson
unbelievable unbelievable I I know I
know I know I'm
shamed m
okay I still have I still have half half
the amount of
time golin card for sended no don't take
it away from me oh what kind of
expression not that I really have time
to think about it I'm just going to make
them excited I wonder if if this would
activate am's problem s with like what
do you call it again if you have
problems with
[Music]
bread what do you call it again
uh gluten a yeah do tacis have
[Music]
gluten you tell me guys are there any
Tako dais here who can tell me
maybe we need to test them for
[Music]
science this is a hand with a knife is
it recognizable I would say
so and a fork from the back
oh T is really excited about
this
okay got a speed run in
a
okay she's she's also
excited you
know she has ears like this and
uh she will eat it with her bare
hands M ah
flaps see I I I can draw from memory I
totally
can some color some color some color
wait can we make the it's shiny can we
make it shiny yes nice shiny okay okay
[Music]
done I love the face of the taco
Nai
her squishes are yellow I know I know
but yeah I mean they they they have a
gradiation that goes into
yellow no onion wait do they always have
onions they they don't always they why
onion for
taco
oh wait what's happening with subu Senai
this is so cute holy she
she she's um
admiring dancing
Birds I guess it's cute it's
Strong by misu or what why is it so
cute M ah mes
mes there's this thing about like people
um wanting subu to be more like mesu
which is like more like feminine I
guess
or uh
subu
an sizes
about
birds
but feminine mesu Subaru I wonder if a
Japanese artist will get this prompt
then I think mesu will help them out
subu fiz about
birds I think I think that's okay keep
it
simple it's fine they're pretty good so
far we had no issues in the previous
rounds
[Music]
cute Rolling Girl
K
rolling rolling
girl is that a that's really random a
reference
to Waka I I doubt it Rolling Girl
did somebody actually make a reference
to waka's Rolling Girl the the vocal art
song okay I looked at up just now I know
the
song uh so am I supposed to draw it like
that there's there's several maybe the
the one where she lifts the hand the arm
there's a pose is that the a good
representation I I wouldn't if I would
have just seen the art I don't think I
would would have gotten new
reference it was a really popular yeah
yeah I I really enjoyed waka's songs I
haven't I don't know if they still make
music but I I haven't listened to them
in a while
[Music]
then oh yeah I was wondering like while
I was saying that wait was Waka the one
that passed away so this is a respect
reference supportive like you know let's
go like this and then I'll I'll I'll
give myself the same kind
of uh twin Tails should I get myself for
a future outfit twin Tails like
that oh she has like bandaids here
and
uh wow this is like quite the
omage you already have I I do I guess
but not as not quite like
that oh my God I look ugly about the
shoulders it's the shoulders why did I
why did I draw it like this shoulders
need to be lower
this not my best
work it'll look cuter with the hair I
think after the stream out of respect I
will listen to the song
again oh I love drawing fluffy long hair
like that oh my
God can you
tell
[Music]
come oh the head is way too big Giga
Giga
head got to fix
it it's still pretty big
whatever
nice okay one day one day we'll get hair
like this for a Wawa
that looks like a booty that part can
you
see looks like a booty wait this this
part of the hair is more fluffy than the
other one it bothers
me okay but now it looks like literally
hatu so let's make it
waa
uh quickly add some
[Music]
orange how to turn hat into Takashi
kiaro
the booty the booty
hair and then
some I need the feather I need the
feathers I need the feathers I need the
feathers uh okay we're good we're
good I will give a hint in case somebody
does no um uh
Rolling
Girl
kada Version okay let's sing it in a k
sometime cuz we we can sing it I have
even I even have the instrumental for
it let's even add the the
skirt
cheating it's a big head but like I
don't know I feel like you know you
know okay okay okay
okay I wanted to help them they if they
don't know the song they have no idea
like okay maybe they're listening to the
stream so that's already helpful what
the is happening I think that's M
and narissa and me um narissa is on the
ground like rolling again someone
rolling is that narissa is it I think so
and and M is pulling her and I'm
watching wait they're wrestling I know
there's the wrestling ring okay okay
they're wrestling M
wrestling
narissa kada
watching well that has to happen uh in
IRL yeah that that's a that's a real
wrestling move is it arm lock arm bar
see I wouldn't know what that term so
I'm not going to Rite it but not a
h Ian Birds
yeah M doesn't have point oh I guess but
I think it's m cuz it seems to be bird
fed and and wait is pomu ah
no well my wrestling pomu for K's uh
kata's love that's what's
happening that's what's it is p no that
you say it cuz she also has like a thing
like that on her head which could be
seen as that uh you know yeah kind of
holding M and F bow bow
them what kind of holding M and F bow
bow them me they're bow bowing at me
while I'm holding
them
maybe uh okay it was better with M no
it's fine we can have pom I think
they're competing for my love you you m
not what what I in the end I wrote Thea
and pom
or did I delete narissa
part did I delete the
Nissa I was stressed out okay I was
stressed
out okay I'm going to draw
something what how are we going to how
am I going to draw
[Music]
this let's just say I
stole I stole the dogs
so I'm very very
happy about
that I'm going to be like squeezing them
out
of
excitement Another Universe where W
loves I I do like toos I do like
them I I I don't dislike them but but
they're not my my first choice of
[Music]
pet wow sooy
hands okay but I want to I want them to
be like kind of in their Dogo form Fu
dog dog form oh there's there's there's
this art that they use for their fog
stream where they're like these almost I
think Pomeranian like dogs that are so
fluffy I love them like
[Music]
that a
dog and and then I'll add a little bit
of color to make them more
recognizable
cute actually kind of cute
and I still have time we're
good I love to squeeze cute fluffy
animals so this is very
[Music]
accurate
so I I take the dog I adopt the dog this
is my dog
now cute and then light blue color
ah cute
cute don't I look
peaceful H but I'm got to make myself
look a bit more like me I suppose so
let's add a bit more
color but when in doubted it's probably
me in a in a GIC phone stream by me yeah
when in doubted is probably
me
[Music]
yeah
wait
ow bow
[Music]
bow no
oh let's give them like the the angry
sign they don't like being squeezed like
this I suppose I feel like they would
like it though I feel like they would
like
it and I'm enjoying
it
nice
nice yeah yeah good I'm
happy don't touch ears or tail
well I raised my cats to tolerate
something like that like they they I
touch their tails and their ears all the
time these are like those are like my
favorite parts to touch and I got to be
honest when I get the chance to pet a
dog I do tend to like I can't resist I I
I go for their their uh uh uh when I
when I touch their face I slightly go
for their ears cuz I can't resist I love
I love how soft and but also chunky they
are oh this is pom pekora and me what
are we doing
though what are we
doing just group picture of like some of
my favorite people group picture pulo
kiar P or maybe in the right
order kiar p
P just a a nice a nice Pro picture P
looks so confused yeah yeah she
does introducing P to P
oh I guess that could be happening too
but okay I I'll write that K
introducing uh pekola to pomu okay see
now we have so many pomu uh uh uh
prompts to make up for the disaster that
I have
caused
got it does look like that now yeah now
that you say it it does it
does crossover of the
century No it's p it's pal cute cute
cute
H oh
okay
cute
m hory
hor horory is
amazing
[Music]
hor what do our bird forms look like I
guess I I'll I'll give I'll give them a
a freestyle attempt or so oh no wait
actually I have a I have something okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
eh I want to do like a
closeup oh of all of
us
um
okay
Birds doing bird
things this is mate can you
[Music]
tell how do I make them cute though May
some blush and the lashes make them cute
this is hor after they visited the the K
girls hog
salong cute eyebrows what eyebrows
there's no
eyebrows but we got to give like stuff
like that I
guess
oh and then and then we do way
now
cute and with like these free feathers
and then she's like most of her body is
white and then she has like blue blue
body we'll we'll get to that later me
yifi
yifi yifi oh
dear um if only I could give them
lipstick but I don't I don't know how
that works on a
on the
beak wait we're just Birds there's
nothing we're just our mascots now oh
well it is what it
[Music]
is it's okay we are trying to become
more burb
like I look so
Derpy and I'll just be orange I don't
really have much more than that except I
can give myself my my bow
maybe and then and then I was going to
do
shubar cute about some should have like
a
longer oh no that's not really
cute maybe lipstick on top of
this that's pretty cute that's pretty
cute oh I won't have time to paint this
will
I okay uh this is
doing I kind of like where where this
one went I mean it's not it's more like
our
mascots but that's
[Music]
okay okay
okay the lipstick is actually so cute
I'll give it to everybody I'll try no no
but it's recognizable I think it's
[Music]
recognizable y y
H
uh uh brown brown brown brown brown
brown brown and uh blue blue blue blue
blue blue blue blue blue and H so is
like mostly
white in this
form but I'll give her a yellow
beak
oops okay I'm kind of proud of this
is it cute
though cute enough to be worthy of this
prompt I don't
know yay
amazing I like it why is bald I don't
know oh wait this looks familiar this
this happened before why does it happen
so
often Kiana again uh cooking
chicken
employee again not again Yes
again another order we're really busy at
kfb well it's just yeah it's endless
cycle of kfp and
Jimmy we're busy we're
busy just a regular Monday no it's a
Sunday though
but yeah I
agree okay bring it on oh I think oh are
we already at the last the next one is
me drawing the last thing I
think I think so I think so cuz it says
nine out of 10 okay okay okay so this
round went down faster kind of cuz I
guess the the beginning just took so
much time for me to to introduce
everybody so we're good we're good we're
not spending too much time on
this okay
let's go last one Bring it on Bring it
on Bring It
On show me show me takon love on the kfp
sideboard
oh okay let me start by drawing the kfp
signboard I
guess is this was this did this happen
in the
MV
I don't remember if we were like I
mean
h fire and eyes de for life now hi never
town oh oh you know what would be cool
instead of drawing us
properly it would be cool to have like
just our like Silhouettes standing up
there like black
Silhouettes that would be pretty dope
like on I I imagine like a scenery in a
in a city uh like Tokyo or so in
nighttime and we're like on top of a a
really high like billboard like this and
we're just like you know
dominating okay then in that case let me
let me make this a
reality can
I
wait I think if I close it off here I
could fill everything
like this and then we do a little Moon
I'm adding a lot to ah now it's yellow
no wrong to I'm adding a lot to this the
moon full moon full moon and maybe some
[Music]
some and then some Stars why am I doing
the background first it will be fine I
only have to draw
cetes
let's give it a little bit of a
glow nice nice details it's getting
elaborate yeah and then the
lights giving it also kind of a glowy
effect we have time we have time we have
[Music]
time and then some orange for the
logo just imagine me running out of time
and all all there is is this logo in the
night sky nothing else oh but wait I
want to do more I want to draw like
buildings in the
back what if I really run out of
[Music]
time W nice
scenery and then it's got to have some
like
[Music]
okay okay okay now it's time now it's
time for us uh uh okay what what does my
Silhouette look
like something like you know like
this with my
sword
and uh yeah my head W my Silhouette I
was some people actually doubted whether
or not it's actually me from the teaser
picture because you couldn't see my hat
I
guess of course it's me guys of course
it
is okay they're not really intricate
Silhouettes but it's it's an ambitious
picture okay
I guess I guess we could be holding
hands and the like flowing in the wind
her skirt is like flowing in the wind
the answer my
friend is blowing blowing in the wind
the answer is that what song is that
my Bona Dons are standing out aren't
they let's go fire and I death and life
[Music]
now I could write it in the background
but no time no time okay I'm done wow
very very artistic
right can some actual good artist
recreate this
please a Bob Dylan ah random B doing the
answer my friend is blowing in the wind
the answer is blowing in the wind let's
go we finished
it thank
you let's go one most chaotic vable oh
nice I I agree with that I strongly
agree with that
oh wait oh wait that's I was going to
say oh somebody did use oneway prompts
let's go but no no no that's the one
that I put up yeah yeah yeah okay cute
somehow I really enjoy seeing like the
animal forms of fuok but also the OKO
animal form is great as well fuo met M's
doppelganger
ah it's a cat
but yeah I guess it could be similar to
to
M oh
same two
MOS two MOS no way for and M discover
they are
twins okay okay okay okay yeah go back
to Fu Moko that's fine that's good
that's good bring it back wait what you
are twins what what I am took it I
thought we didn't look alike at all no
no no R was scared that they are twins
so they bow bow all
over they're scared it's a terrified
knowledge yeah it's very
terrified wait that's like that's like
oh maybe their whole life they were
thinking like even when they looked at
each other they were fing they were just
looking in the mirror and this is the
moment where they realized it's not them
just looking in the mirror but yeah it
it reminded me of like animals looking
in a mirror and realizing it's them but
like normally that doesn't like my cats
for example never pay attention to
what's in the mirror I feel like
depending on the the pet they have
different kind of perception of that but
this could be such a
moment Bo at each
other stop boting me already you can't
do better
anyway I imagine it like that
oh wait what why
mean
become F become
K I am not a kiaa i
f or I'm not fuaa I'm
Kwa nice oh wait I should save them
again I'll go back afterwards me ah it
was it is so sens
came up with
me
yo yeah they they might be uh n Sanji uh
artist
but they are a big fan of whole life too
so oh me I knew it was you it's so good
it's so
good wait but like I don't understand
like the birds is that just like how she
wants to be as a bird or what I don't I
don't quite understand the birds but yes
this is
great miss m subu fantasizes about birds
okay okay yeah elegant she wants to be a
swan R than a duck is that what's
happening
cute D swimsuits that's not no she's not
fantasizing about them in the loot way
no but very cute it looks
so looks so good K dreaming about sexy
bird kada this is not
me this is not me but it's okay I I
think you're just really really um all
you have in your head is me that's okay
I I like
that
sexy wait I really love how Apple
Blossom has been drawing me so far like
this is so
adorable cuz like normally the way they
shade and draw like the coloring is like
always so so like I don't know how to
explain it's so intricate and
HD and this is how they draw in a
simplistic style I guess it's really
good I like it yeah I want to be sexy
Phoenix I I already am sexy Phoenix oh
oh
Duma let's go I look like a pinup girl I
like it yeah has a reputation oh do I do
I really thank you I'm
honored oh
oh don't hide it don't no wait let me go
in safe why won't you hide it go back
get rid of the chicken what a troll get
out of
here oh my God stupid chicken Jimmy
that's why I have to burn you alive enan
I'mma eat takachi together oh I got this
one it's not so bad it's cute I love the
chicken H chicken T taco probably taste
like chicken they probably do I'm and
Ena eating Taco D yes oh my God oh my
God
this is
terrifying this is
scary the poster of Ena and am oh my God
but it's takachi is still enjoying it
seems like we're all we have a common
ground with this idea in our
head I'm me Ina eat a big Toni but the
Toni likes it yeah you don't even have
to say that no
we all assume so oh my
God this is the most cursed thing you
have drawn today that is for sure holy
oh my God M Taki imagine being
eaten by Ena and I'm I is in their head
it's all in their
head a this is kind of more cute we went
back to being more or less
cute the pieces cut off
off what a what an exciting thought to
have but this is this is basically what
I want kfp to think like enan I'mma eat
tasty Tac
oh we we circled back to it I mean it's
always kind of been the same but here
here it was a fantasy but we circled
back to it being a
reality let's go wait wait they turned
uh Bon turned it into into takoyaki ah
more or less
Takaki
nice
yummy that's definitely the the better
way to eat a
t yeah f is taken to the usual room by
Ki ah okay I I understand this is the
one that I I drew me draw uh hugging
them
mhm come with me for
this
B on
Mo or is it feet I'm not
sure are they
Paws yeah kidnaps adops M I like the dot
dot dot here the change of mind away
from F oh oh I'm stealing M away from
F yeah oh that is so cute
W that is so cute that dog that dog
looks so much like a dog it's so cute B
don't steal my sister B no I I will have
M now thank
you yay holding M for B B them this is
where I came into the
situation you
cute what the so nice fluffy dog goes
everywhere Kira gently hugs and angry
for
M I am being gentle I'm trying my best
to be gentle
cute her Bubba her Bubba over the top
cute jeez they're so angry why why is
the why I just want fluff I just want
some fluff K and bikini yeah I look kind
of like yeah not so dressed huging angry
Lou and
Nissa are you just are you just starting
some chaos
here are you just trying to be chaotic
here I
[Music]
mean maybe they still had holot toi in
their
brain they's still H in their R oh W but
I mean aren't we thankful for
this aren't we grateful yeah it's
because of the blue and the pink I guess
mhm this this is a great gift I I I
cannot
complain looks like a
[Music]
win oh is this where P later joins in
like I wonder how that
happened
[Music]
cute pom and K got small
p is it a typo from puura to P because I
don't see any PE in
here but no problem let's add Pea in
very cute a cute cute cute cute cute
cute the hands look like rabbit head
heads
oh maybe yeah yeah looks like looks like
rabbit p k into this baby
P am again adopting first dogs now small
small
Peola ah oh you guys genius because it
really was introducing here oh
but originally it was a picture so me
saying group picture wasn't so far off
either nice oh that is
adorable look pom this is my oi wow
so I can imagine give a sales piture
about PCO to P
wow you should support peka as well I
don't even know like her thoughts about
P I should ask
her me
misu blows me away every time what what
what what Mis Mis
Mis so
wait wait wait wait I'm selling pom to P
now the the it has switched there's a
switch of we take it we take it I might
do that IRL
sometime okay here we go
oh now I also know uh where my my
citycape image comes from KY and K
singing on a
Ferrari oh Ferrari oh let's go oh I love
that that reminds me of pineapple cuz
like I'm in the car driving by palm
trees and all that like I don't know La
Miami who knows singing and then this is
like this is like Callie's hijacking
pineapple music
video K and Kelly driving around town
please don't let me drive though I think
Calli is the one between us who has the
license don't let me
drive that looks so dope I feel the air
I literally feel it look how swag we
look with those
glasses
sheesh m
cany and K driving day it's so cool I
agree I agree oh yeah let's
go there's a chicken stuck are we what's
happening what's happening is this a GTA
episode and me and Cali are kidnapping a
chicken or torturing
one oh no Jimmy not
again C A dated K oh oh spicy
spicy oh
oh wait that's so cute the chicken is so
cute I like how we kind of had a similar
idea because you're just drawing us like
looking towards the scenery like you
know and then I draw them with a
silhouette also on top of
kfp so we're like connected telepathy
telepathy look wow W wo wo wo wo wo wo
takamo
[Music]
takam this is good very
good
genius narissa and pomu fights to death
to marry
Ki yeah narissa and pomu okay so it
wasn't M and then I up even more
but that's okay this is GC
[Music]
phone
cute cute very cute k i watching pomu
pro wrestling Nissa yes yes well I mean
pro wrestling yeah let's go let's go I
want to see that yeah let's go this is
what I saw and I'm so
sorryim I was trying to fix it and then
I fixed the wrong name now mum is
wrestling pomu
but for Kiana's
love that's so cute that's so cute m is
is like like as if Pomo is like a plant
that's growing because of the leaves so
cute she's m is nurturing mum is my wing
lady she's helping M she's helping pumu
out to grow bigger I suppose very cute
watering
P it has become a whome situation mum
grows pomu and Ki falls in love with her
yeah yes happy
ending
Mama really this is such a
misunderstanding all all caused by me
because I brought mum into
this so unrelated but
beautiful finally Pomo meet Pomo and
kiar and oh this is where confusion will
be
caused but wait it came to the red
person it came to the red person m is
out of the picture narissa is out of the
picture it's just K and pomu and this
this is
beautiful drawn by pom's one and only
artist
yeah amazing we have three more albums
wow wow wow wow wow wow I was worried
that I wouldn't have enough artists but
I definitely have enough
artists sitting on a
tree there's a uh like a children's song
in German that's like sitting on the
tree kissing kissing blah blah
blah
cute see this is probably why they had
Holi in their
brain this was the first thing they
drew
cute we're just we're just hanging out
on a tree like BBS usually do and you
guys are bird watching k i SS i n g
oh oh in English you spell it out oh
yeah in German I don't think you spell
it out yeah I think it's just
a something
something cute is the middle one me
because I look like a
tomato since when am I so
red I literally look like a lree
tomato tomato B I'm blushing hardcore
yeah cuz I'm so happy look at the sub
dumpy nice H is in harmony yes yes we
are yes we are very
much good good good good drawing five
people is kind of stressful so good job
good job cute H yes we are cute hor
that's the prompt I got oh yeah yeah
cute cute good
God very cute I'm proud of this one H2
BFF oh I see the Japanese input messing
up real
writing
BFF
cute cute cute cute very cute I think
you ran out of time there but it's very
adorable and very recognizable hand in
hand nice
one yeah adorable I'm so happy I feel
feels so
fulfilled watching the movie cat's day
in
kfp oh that is a difficult prompt very
difficult wait
nice is that how it was for you guys
come on that can't be true why why are
you acting like this you're
overreacting can't be watching scary
movie in usual
room
cats is not a scary movie but yeah this
is I will show you stuff in the usual
room that you dislike so I suppose that
might be cats in that
case
wow
wo
wo I think that is the most insane and
like intricate crazy amazing piece of
art
today wow like that is I'm terrified by
myself
Co yeah I was going to pop out of the
screen yeah for
real that is really
scary chimpin watch a scary movie where
Kiana is the
murderer I I that is fiction let me just
say it's totally
fiction wait I look pretty happy and
like peaceful here but but what that is
um still a knife in my hand and still
something you don't want to mess with
and but they look quite oh chill about
it the chickens look quite chill about
it it's a biography excuse me that looks
like a cooking yeah a little bit it
looks like the cookies I made today a
little bit because they're all round but
you see there's a face here so how will
Duma interpret this ah chicken's
watching Kiana's kitchen okay it it
yeah murder is gone murder is no more
yeah my reputation is being fixed by
Duma thank you thank
you ah oh that's why we came back to
this
[Music]
ah yeah okay okay cooking chicken
employee
again brings us this twice fried Oh yeah
double fried M I think that's a thing
right like uh some some people like for
some foods I think I've seen it before
like people uh fry something twice it's
a thing right double dip oh yeah oh yeah
I've never had that before I think
double dip in
a Sak show that is like super crispy
super crunchy french fries especially oh
french
fries ooh yum you double fry french
fries for example so oh really
really oh that's not interesting good
knowledge for
kfp owner like
me here we go last one last one you
doing a cartwheel on a Mountaintop
oh wait now that's ah so I knew it
wasn't really that was so Random okay
but who says this thing we
rolling we rolling
rolling goia ah I don't think Apple
Blossom really was intending the
reference
either
so we really went in a completely
different
direction I no gy ball gy
[Music]
ball
what oh my
God what is happening am I stopping the
Sun from crashing into Earth or am
I pushing well I don't know what's
happening but that's amazing is this a
cult moment is this the end for
kfp the
Doomsday Spirit Bomb okay drag was I
don't know that reference but it looks
like the sun to
me oh but okay okay it seems to have
come across correctly super saan Kiana
using gy dharm with chickens holy
is is gumia going to get it am I the
only one who doesn't get
it seems like it
bro wow these two are very similar
they're just like one is red and one is
blue
nice
SW I am not this powerful but I love
this really good stuff K skanky
dama I said wait let me look up gy
d gy
d it is
blue kinky D it is blue but they made
kiaha
version
orange
[Music]
a cute the gy D is a c chicken sasuma
turning everything into a chicken
amazing oh I'm so sad it's over because
it's already 2 hours so that's probably
enough and I want you guys to get some
sleep before you uh check out my freie
birthday uh end of the year concert
tomorrow um but I think I might I think
I'll read super chats quickly though so
that we don't fall behind too much so
good that was so good so good thank you
thank you thank you it's the
end that was so good I wish I could do
longer longer can you not edit the VOD
um yeah I think I have
to I think I have to especially because
of the music uh but uh don't worry I
won't make it
private I won't make it private I'll
just edit it or I'll ask maybe JMA to
edit it yeah this was so good I'm so
happy thank you for all the cute
artworks and H I I want to advertise one
more time time before you guys leave uh
tomorrow
tomorrow is this i s this is my
advertisement in uh 12 hours J can go 12
hours 12 hours you guys got to go to
sleep sleep sleep sleep sleep see 12
hours is my end of the year 3D
celebration which is supposed to be my
birthday uh concert half a year late uh
but I call it end of the year concert so
yeah it's kind of weird but yeah uh
already stream reservation is up there's
also a members only un un part that you
guys if you have a membership please
please be there it's like an extension
it's also in 3D it's also like the same
like concert recording basically but
some extra songs and some extra MC and
all that so look forward to it it is
definitely worth it very worth it very
hype J gun in 12 hours oh my God can you
believe it what what so I won't keep you
guys for too long you know what I'll
even stay on the
screen I'll even stay on the
screen uh oh my God there's so much good
stuff happening you guys are welcome to
leave um
I will read some superos from I think
the baking stream and this
stream I'm at work I can't go to sleep
oh no go go fast fast work faster I
really anticipate me too me too thank
you artist for coming thank you so
much thank you so much to the amazing
artist I hope we can do this again it
was a lot of fun I I'm honored to draw
alongside these
Geniuses I'm I'm
honored so let me go to Super Chat time
let me I guess I'll write it on the
screen so you know what's
up Super Chat reading
time
I just put it here it was fun yeah I
hope it was fun for the Artist as
[Music]
well let's go let's go H superh wait
I'll write them a Twitter message last
but not least F
oopsie 24 hours of painting time thank
you so much for participating
everyone everything looked so
good thank you thank you thank
[Music]
you
but I I I was amazing
too very very sick stuff 50 number 50
memberships crazy simple generic entity
thank you so
much yo I see you're you're excited too
huh just like
me
I'm also excited I'm so excited and I
just can't hide
it I'm so nervous I really hope YouTube
will be fine I tested both latencies
today I tasted I tested ultra low
latency and I tested uh normal latency
both were stable today no lags so if
anything is lagging tomorrow I don't
think it's on
me I don't think so but I I will not
even open chat on my PC I'll I'll watch
chat on my phone because we don't want
something like in the past happen again
with my fancy outfit yeah I'll be
streaming it they asked me to stream it
I don't know if this is normal I feel
like I thought I thought they they
stream it they press the button but I'm
I'll be streaming it so I'm bit a bit
nervous about it I don't want the
responsibility yeah I'm I'm I'm
concerned but it will be
fine yeah if anything is lagging
probably in the vault it will be fine so
just rewatch the VA if something lagged
really hard do me the favor because
because it's everything has to be
appreciated
smoothly ah the pom a true okay okay
okay no problem no
problem I'll read those
too anyone who makes effort to tune in
can handle a bit of lag yeah I I guess
so but like who knows sometimes there's
there's certain days where it's just
extra laggy and I can't
really anticipate that you
know like the other day when I started
the stream the Minecraft stream it was
extra laggy but but that there it was
from the beginning so if it's like that
from the
beginning I guess we we'll have to make
a new
stream but it will be fine it'll be fine
that only happens like once every two
months or so three months that actually
that's the first I feel like that's
almost the first time that happened to
me a lag that bad that I had to make a
new stream I think that was the first
time yeah okay after this by the way I
will open the the chat the stream chat
for the live
concert afterwards I'll open it okay
[Music]
so we're going to read from VR stream
with
pomu Super Chat reading time Super Chat
reading time it's the Super Chat reading
the Super Chat reading the Super Chat
reading t let me change the
music you like this Jazz don't
you you like it don't you isn't this
nice a nice break from the exciting
cutesy
music I what this put this here okay
okay
you're like
jazz we need to watch that be movie
Jacob 47 D J Monkey D Murphy D Sky
d g d Jim Tracy D thank you but you are
you also Super C okay I was about to say
thank you very much Jim Tracy I'm glad
you liked it today we got some
references to that as well very
nice thank you for the pinky ah Mis fist
the biggest pomon fan pomy we love it
frog OES are unstoppable thank you for
being the best most talented and most
adorable menaces in the
world thank you very much for supporting
I think you have amazing amazing
taste so I'm glad I could provide this
to you I'm always happy I'm always like
excited when I hear like oh I I oi you
and your collab partner so thank you for
this my categories up it's okay I'm not
winning wait should we do a live
react I think I saw it uh on my
[Music]
YouTube how fast are they going to do
this one more I'll muted wait I need
to
oh I I don't want to I don't know if I
want to live react to it because I know
I'm not winning but I don't care it's
okay it's some ad going on right
now whole life is hella
sweeping was I the only whole life uh
person in the category I may have been I
voted for you thank
you well I I I it's fine it's fine it's
fine it'll be reading Super Chat till
4m. no no no no it will be
fast um y yum
yum
ads they knew I was tuning in so they
put up some
ads I voted for you too thank you only
two streams yeah yeah just uh today
cookie and this one and the VR from
yesterday it's not that much
probably wait is that
vbe that sound like vbe
iron Mouse said she wouldn't win to well
iron Mouse is kind of like different
League she even won in the game awards
so I'm I'm getting
hungry godic phone is awesome it was you
got this dangel no no no no no no I
really don't got this
but it's okay I don't care
anyway I don't
care I just F you know if they're live
now I might as well react to
it I looked up the there was a Korean uh
vtuber gusu that I didn't hear of before
so I checked it out and and she was so
cute like and the one of the nominations
was a Korean twitch vtuber that only
streams in Korean but and also only in
3D it seems like it she's so cute
though go
cute yeah but I did hear the twitch
Korean news so I
wonder what happens because I I noticed
a lot of like twitch has like a booming
Korean
Community you saw her yeah I looked her
up it was kind of difficult cuz I first
couldn't find her on Twitter
now now Korea has a few more other big
platforms um that are not
YouTube yeah it's so sad I read the news
um they tried really hard to keep it
going and yo did you see like top 10 you
uh streamers on Twitch where recently
there were a lot of Korean streamers on
there too so they were like
dominating she so it's kind of
crazy that they
can't be on the platform
anymore wait how long is this ad is this
even an
ad is this a
skit oh I think it's
done oh it's
done oh nice nice
transitions
she
fell
oh next
category just chatting
done I don't want to watch this I want
to
lose it's okay I'll be a good loser
because I I I don't
mind I don't
mind
[Music]
cuz also mat she's also great I remember
she was in the
category she's really good at talking to
like she talks more than
me this really looks like the like the
game awards damn they really worked hard
on oh
wow oh wow the Transitions and stuff and
the
graphics nice good job oh see this is
the Korean YouTuber she's
cute I don't know who the guy is what's
going on here I don't
know I wonder what clip they use of me
will they use a clip of
me
there's not there wasn't much talking in
that clip
though oh sh she's
German I think sh like didn't she vote
for me in the
clip I think she voted for
me nice nice turn nice
turn w w I think I watched that clip the
w w
cute there was also not much talking in
that clip though not saying that they're
not good at talking but the clips are
not showcasing they're
talking what if they use my puy tangent
as the
clip am I on T I'm not on the tally on
my side
yet
[Laughter]
oh oh oh this is me recently talking
about the rats and why is there the GTA
intro why Why That's So
Random I will never go to
Florida this is me talking about GTA
I will I will play GTA
6 oh that was uh decent
choices decent
choices I won't win I won't win I won't
don't don't don't don't uh spoiling me
chat you seem to be ahead of
me not
me
she's claim one for herself oh yeah
can't be me okay
okay good job congratulations
w at least a German speaking one
one just like me she doesn't stream in
German
though no I'm happy I was nominated in
the first place
yeah cuz like I mean chatting is like
something we all
I think do and something we all focus on
so you got to be good at it at a as a
vtuber as a streamer in general you got
to be good at talking if you're not good
at talking then what what the hell are
you doing as a
streamer yeah it's a it's a difficult
category it's fine it's fine I I think
yeah you obviously you you guys would
have chosen me that's all I
[Music]
need okay let's continue back to Super
chats BL
uh chocolate and sonnic thanks for the
pinky The Faded pomon collab is
happening again finally yeah it's only
our our second one-on-one collab and the
last one was also VR you know I just
like to connect with her in VR cuz we
can we can be closer to each other this
way thank you so much for watching I
hope you enjoyed it I wanted our collab
to be something special so yeah I think
it was very
[Music]
special ah
oh yeah that Meme chemicals in the water
these frogs are gay FAA thanks for the
pinky why am i o she so cute my heart
can't handle it thank you I know like
honestly froggy Wawa when I see myself
as froggy Wawa I also like holy
I it's so much cuteness I can barely
handle
it I I I feel you with that I feel you
fa your channel than thank
you not about thank thank you SE boy
let's go I told her that word for word
on the
screen I didn't know he Super Chat at
that why why did you expose me like that
she boy why did you expose me
hey
[Music]
I want to I want to yawn but I can't get
it
out you Mike anime lifeime life tempor
thank you for the right Super Chat
congratulations to the Frog couple here
a small tribute so you can defeat the
orange chicken or at least use it for
the baby shower for the Tad PS I know
it's not a gold bar but it's better than
nothing yeah Fring always on top anyway
T is okay I
guess
oh thank you I guess I'll I'll tell
froggy waa about this nice message thank
you so
much no really that's really sweet of
you honestly it was meant to be like me
and pomu already love each other and
then it just so happens that she has a
great frog Persona I have one we're like
made for each other you cannot deny that
thank you tempor mAh
I AEP d g d Jim Tracy d z d The Gamer CR
D that's it for that
stream and then we have
cookies today this stream was just today
and it was so successful oh my
God those cookies are so good I I've
been snacking on them I've been trying
to hold back because they're so good and
I shouldn't eat that much sweet stuff
when I haven't eaten anything else today
but they're so good and my mom wrote to
me she told me they know they look good
or whatever something like that she was
praising my cookies and and I was like
pretty proud so uh yeah I showed her the
picture and she was like yeah I was
watching so good good job and then I I
asked her if maybe for Christmas I
should make another batch for her um cuz
I asked her if she likes this type of
cookie and she says yeah she really
loves them so I don't know about cookie
baking stream next week I might just
like private bake another batch of these
for my mommy because I don't think uh
I'll have enough they probably will be
gone and I want her to have fresh ones I
want to bake those cookies for
her yeah I I'll look at my
schedule um I was I already currently I
have a baking stream in my schedule more
or less in there but it it's looking a
little bit
busy and it's always such a mess when
oh I do this kind of hand cam cooking
baking stream the table the freaking
table gets so messy I already cleaned
most of it though like I I put away all
the things again mostly the camera is
still kind of there and the light is
still kind of there so I got to I got to
clean a bit more it's not the floor
though I can't believe next time I'm
going to put like a note that will be
visible on the camera that says this is
not the floor or this is is a table or
so because I can't believe you guys like
really think it's the freaking floor why
would I be cooking on the floor
why why would I make cookies on the
floor that's disgusting that's
absolutely
disgusting I don't know V why V why
right I
know where was I oh yeah here beginning
um
jaob 47 oh frog cookies good idea I need
to get food coloring and make frog
cookies yeah
py
J for the red CH yes happy birthday to
me oh and soon one year membership to
tento oh rev you I'm full of Happiness
thank you for streaming I want to listen
to your birthday song to me and I want
employee number all right you don't have
an employee number
M looks at date of the day uh how
about 1
7 one
two your birthday might actually be 16th
but let's say 17 one two ha what a
coincidence I haven't given out an
employee number in a in a
while 1712 M please take this number and
happy birthday
[Music]
how do you sing this with the name in
Korean where do you put the name
[Music]
in that way
maybe happy birthday let me blow out the
candles for
you
[Music]
congratulations you say
ah
salang hanun name after that
[Music]
Han still I don't really know
still like
[Music]
that oh maybe like that that seems like
it makes
sense oh the other way around
[Music]
ah okay okay I learned something new
today that is very
helpful for the support and for always
being trying your best to be in my
streams thank
[Music]
you it's 2:30 now but I I I woke up so
late so it's all okay it's all right I I
kind of messed up my sleep schedule a
bit action it K okay than you soon thank
you oh hope hope you get well
soon M PB and K thank you for the pinky
kamita as you oh wait two pinkies as you
may remember I sometimes ask for
consolation for super chat whenever I
was mentally struggling and the words of
consolation from you and kfp gave me a
lot of strength now I have more hope
than ever and a new
job sadly I'm night shift so it'll be
hard to watch your stream o but one
change that I always roote for you more
than anyone else thank you kiaba and
thank you everyone who has helped me
there's a small token of my appreciation
thank you very much but oh that's a bit
sad but at the same time congratulations
for feeling better and for getting a job
let's go let's go you did that you alone
did that good job and yeah I hope you
can still watch the vods when you have
time or when I stream like outside of
your working hours I hope you can catch
the streams still yeah don't forget
about me don't forget about me
thank you pbnk and good luck in your new
job cast form thanks for the pinky hello
wa a year ago around this time I was
graduating from uni o and now a year
later I'm
going oh okay I'm going2 200,000 into
depth but at least I'll own a house for
myself yeah okay but that seems like At
first I was shocked but if it's for a
house that seems pretty normal right you
you take out a loan from the bank 200k
seems like for a house it sounds like
you still paid quite a big amount cuz
200k for a house seems pretty small so
you must have paid a good chunk yourself
so good job good job good job what a
year later after University see this
person you would think a year later
after University you're not capable of
buying a house but this is because this
person is from
Europe I I don't think this would be
possible in many other countries or
continents well well look at this look
at this example just
graduated and took out a loan probably
paid a big chunk themselves as well and
got themselves a
house oh I guess yeah cuz like housing
housing is like kind of difficult in
Europe too I think like getting really
expensive but I hear it's even worse in
America yeah but not only that but like
student depth hello hello
[Music]
so come to Europe
guys come to
[Music]
Europe yeah yeah housing is is also an
issue in Europe I think Bruce Jen Lee D
spank andhe thank you for the red super
chat thank you anything I've owned for
more than a month smells like cat I'm
not sure which one though probably
both smells like cat that's interesting
cuz I don't think my thing's smell like
cat they smell like me my cats smell
like cat but I don't think they rub off
their scent much on anything that I own
not even the
bed but maybe I got too used to it but I
honestly don't think so like cuz I think
cats don't even have like I think with
dogs this is totally possible but I
think cats don't have such a strong
scent that robs off onto
anything I think with dogs it's way way
stronger
I don't smell like cat I'll go ask my
friends next time and I'll prove you my
things and me we don't smell like cats
no get used to dog
smell I wouldn't be able
to yeah that's one thing that bothers me
a lot I think dog
[Music]
smell I don't like it I don't like it
yeah that's a big problem if I ever want
to get a dog I guess just got to go
strong on hygiene with the dogle connect
the world one let's
go as it should as it should as it
should it's the cat later that stings
yeah but that's the only thing really
and my cats don't smell like cat later
and they don't like spread the the smell
across the apartment
either
[Music]
no Chum but's one is fandom oh
really I found like that that category
kind of
interesting I guess yeah Hol
[Music]
sweep so now that we won best concert
hopefully we get another one as I said
anyway spam thank you M tell me though
like how serious is are you just making
jokes or do you really mean it Bruce
Jenny Lee J thank
you cgar 48 J thank
you yeah they're really easy to make
them I was surprised it went so smoothly
and they're so tasty W those must be the
best cookies I ever made Jim Tracy Dan y
Channel thank you Hu
I WaterOne
[Music]
F okay last one I love this thumnail yo
the art the artist is by the way the
same as can you tell as the this this is
the same
artist today gtic phone thumbnail same
as
my birthday
life this so good this is so good I love
I love this piece of art I was like
wondering this is so good for what
should I use it has to be a wory
[Music]
stream Jacob 47 India Taylor D
congratulations on your graduation from
uh College let's go oh thank you so much
for the sweet message
oh please continue to be part of kfp I
would be happy to have you around thank
you so much and
congratulations the
gamer than py
than thank
you are you were listening it's like a
podcast for you
today you have to look at it later you m
thank you pretty act right I'm I'm happy
with the artists I got like I reached
out mostly to artists that you know are
fan artists and have drawn me before
um so yeah and and artists that I
thought would maybe be able to
understand basic
English that's a bit difficult some
artists uh really turned down down my
offer because they uh were not confident
about their English skills I thought
they would probably be fine anyway but
they were too worried about it so it is
what it is that's
fine and then actually let me tell you
po po mama re artist was going to be
there too but then like yesterday or so
she told me like she has work after all
so she couldn't be there but that way we
have someone for next
time
hey next time next time yes cuz poy
Mama's English is also pretty good I
think like decent good enough for GIC
[Music]
phone
marinski D res D thank you yeah I see so
much stuff arriving these days the
plushies and the
figures yeah you guys are able to build
shrines
[Music]
now I actually also uh just received
some merchandise from Japan and this
time it did not get stuck at the Customs
what the it's so
Random
it was uh our bright
parade or or no it's I think it was
fifth Fest not our bride not necessarily
our bride parade no but that's the name
of the concert right our bride parade
merchandise like a big um
plastic poster
thingy um and then like a keychain and
the the blue
R fifth hasn't oh that was fourth Fest
oh next is fifth
Fest I wonder if they'll continue
calling it that because I feel like
sixth
Fest
seven eight
eight I just feel like it's going to
start sounding kind of
stupid I wonder if they'll continue
calling it that it sounds kind of weird
like Fifth Fifth F still sounds okay fif
F see
six Fest that at some point it just gets
stupid 11 Fest 12 Fest 13 F 14 F 15 F
how far are we
going I think just the main title like
our bride parade or so would just be
fine on its own but now it's kind of a
tradition right so you got to go with it
at the same time hexa
Fest Thousand Years
Fest probably using the year from a
certain
point a
2024 Festival 2024 something like that f
[Music]
24 Roman numerals n that would be kind
of cool but not quite our Vibe I think
po Fest Year we We are writing the year
3,200
71 now do the math which Fest is
this math go go go go go go go go
go I like that the titles are in English
yeah yeah that's uh I think you know for
Japanese it's kind of for stuff like
this it's pretty common to use
English cuz it sounds
cool what you didn't just say 3,000 what
did I say 3,471 I
think didn't sign up for math me Ne Me
NE
243rd
1,72 ah it's very
different can't wait for the live me too
sleep talking is in your head
same same same same anyway where was I
where dun moral imoral
dun ads getting feels like ads are
overwhelming then get our ad blocker
with it ads become a thing of the past
we do not acknowledge any information
stolen from the ad block I mean what
does ad blocker steal
information hor dance just showed up
why wasn't nominated was it for
anything
[Music]
interesting it made it to the year
highlight oh a montage oh
cool oh don don thank
you my group that's my
group Gan D we're all familiar with the
song 12 Days of Christmas but I've
always wondered which gift gets gift
given the most each if each gift is
given in the stated amount each time it
gets mentioned which gift would you get
the most
what you mean wein that song well the
first
one right ah oh no this is another math
question because some got like like five
golden rings like there's are
five ah don't no no no no no no no no no
no no no no go away go away with your
math question go away interesting though
why are you giving me a
riddle Studio Ro thanks for the pinky
sing Rolling Girl I've
asked what do you mean you've asked
before you mean ring
girl
wait
okay can I sing
it like i' practiced this
before I'll
[Music]
try
something like
that
[Music]
[Applause]
da
okay okay I can't sing it really well I
know it but I can't sing it so let's
practice it for next K okay
okay it's a good song though very high
like these Waka songs are so
[Music]
high yeah I I'll do my
best next next
k you sng Newton you sang Newton dance
you can do it yeah I I can also I I I
sang that one before what was it again
last
night good
night remember that
one that really o that really
high really high uh nice chill gentle
good night niku song I really like that
one oh that was members only right
that's a long time ago too
[Music]
yeah I really like that
one if that was me only we also got to
put it on the list for the next Koka
stream remember remind me
please P thank you for Super Chat I own
three of them and I still hug them for
the fluff then I die of rashes oh my God
God having an all allergy especially if
you get the allergy after getting the
pets that's really so unfortunate
man M Matrix free BC B anime beep
Anthony web thank you for the pinky your
drawing skills are better than you think
you thank you yeah I think for like
something like GIC
phone I I fit in like I can I can hold
uh how my ground or how however You
Stand My Ground I guess these artist
look at that like I mean yeah yeah I'm
proud I'm really
proud I'm quite proud so I I got some
more um confidence through
this I feel like I have a a very good
visualization that also shows when I
take
pictures but if I have to draw something
more seriously like more than just a
sketch like actual real backgrounds for
by the way for example like because that
that one um that one thing I drew with
me and Cali with the Silhouettes yeah
for the amount of time I had and the
tools I had that was sick but if I have
like unlimited time and I have to draw
like a proper landscape that's where you
will notice my lack of skills for
sure yeah
cuz I when I was more into art when I
was younger I also pretty much always
ignored
um backgrounds I most of the time I I
try to just stay away from
it if anything maybe I would draw a blue
sky and that's
it cuz a blue sky is pretty pretty
easy I could draw
clouds yeah just like me
really yeah just drawing characters with
no background and nowadays like for me
when it comes to fanart I appreciate it
when fan art had for me has no
background because then I can easily use
it for a thumbnail don't have to cut out
anything um um um but when I was an
artist I feel like it was like if if
what I draw has no background then it's
not good enough then it's not
interesting enough then it's not going
to get attention especially as like a
less known artist that is trying
to get famous on Deviant
Art in order to stand out you have to be
pretty good at backgrounds I think I
think that was kind of a thing but now I
look at Art on Twitter and I see so many
amazing artists just putting up art with
no background and it's still
sick it's still great and I actually
appreciate it
so I guess I would feel more okay with
drawing characters without background
now but at the same time when I was
streaming you know me drawing kobal and
and when I was drawing C and so on I
still felt like if I don't add a
background it's going to be like it's it
looks unfinished and it doesn't look
right and N I should draw a background
like I felt kind of obligated to do
it
no I wish I was better at it but I know
that like Ena and also a lot of other
artists uh use the help of 3D tools also
so if I knew how to use it that would be
pretty helpful I
guess
yeah also with like angles and all that
would be helpful with that too but I
don't really I don't even know how to
use that kind of stuff learn blender
no stock photos as a background that is
such a cheap Escape I wouldn't want to
do that I wouldn't want to use a
photograph as a background
no at least use it as a reference and
like repaint it but just using the
picture no no no can't can't do
that Ena uses blender oh dear no I I
don't want to get into
that no no no it's weird watching me
stream at this hour right I should end
it soon though don't worry I'm almost
done with super
chats
[Music]
Mr and refresh
refreshing
uh G no wait here uh oh what oh you guys
sent a bit more
[Music]
uh Japanese Bros name kind of hard to
say
[Music]
ja you
are is thanks for the pinky you're a
winner in my heart no matter what I love
you guys I am so fine with this I am
really I don't care I don't care I
really don't I'm I'm surprisingly don't
no I really don't like maybe if if it
was the game awards I would have cared
like
something like as big as that but this
seems to me like a like an individuals
event that's also mostly like twitch
based so I don't really mind like tunic
losing that that is something you have
to take
seriously but thank you for you sweet
words Isa stop talking about it it's
literally the Super Chat is about it so
I might will talk about
[Music]
it justice for tunic yeah
tunic maybe maybe I can get crony to
play tunic cuz like she played this
Portal game that I also
played do you think tun uh crony would
like tunic can I get crony to play it
for my
satisfaction she loved you really she
would enjoy it it's pretty difficult
though you got to get a little bit try
hard but like even if if if someone
someone like me gets into it that much I
think it's it has an insane amount of
charm bi Playa could be good as well
yeah but I I feel
like it's so so weird if I go like
please play
This and like I don't know how to
convince them to play
it I can see Cronin getting into tunic
[Music]
really you told am she should play it
and she never did of course she didn't
of course she didn't and I I will I will
not resent her for
that I never really expected her to play
it I don't know why I even asked her
like I don't think she would be the most
logical Choice why did I ask her to play
it makes more sense to recommend an FPS
game to her not tunic
but Sky I
[Music]
space wonderful than y or however I
should say your name y y thank you for
the red super chat for
takik your name says uh the the text
says takik as if you thought you have to
ride the person who is supposed to
receive it in there so true so so true
it is takas thank you so much for the
support kind of random but I appreciate
it thank
you g d d
dry thank
you sleep talking
oh oh I like that people are have sleep
talking stuck in their head especially
when they're trying to sleep looking for
the top
[Music]
d
hook himself told me so he told you that
in my OG outfit the sword has Phoenix
kada and
grabed
[Music]
N Al
WR I need to check it
[Music]
to
where is it in the
Fred on the on the tapestry what ah the
the the art that he created me okay cuz
it's not here it's not on the shield
either is it
no
enhance look at my
freckles
[Music]
look at my
freckles so
[Music]
cute
me
cute wa do you have freckles just yeah I
always I always had
freckles always always had
freckles oh my God I look so cute and
close up with the
freckles I'm weak to
freckles is that
so what a coincidence because I have
freckles I just thought my monitor was
dirty hey it's not
[Music]
dirt looking for the top D Al we space
waterful d little r d and Bo oh 723
sorry I I'm getting excited because of
the
concert H wait one more refresh Ricky
Dona sent a pinky thank you very excited
for the frd later today wa wa is yeah I
mean I mean it's not like I this year
you already saw me perform in 3D here
and there in my showcase and like in
other people's 3D lives a little bit but
yeah this is the first time I get to do
a cover
produced uh and yeah inhouse recorded uh
birthday concert and I haven't had an
anniversary yet either so besides my
showcase it's kind of the first
thing the first time so let's go let's
go I'm
[Music]
excited cuz like the one I made at
amed's place is also really amazing but
I was obviously very limited to like
guests could only really invite guests
that were also there like Ena and am and
then yeah it was like everything was
really limited and really like you know
rough but still that was like the the
the result was still like amazing
quality I will like definitely forever
be grateful for that like the way
everybody helped me put that together
[Music]
no okay and Galaxy D I think that's it
thank
you oh what the 14 days until
[Music]
2024 don't
even that is
terrifying that is
terrifying we did not need to hear that
now to weeks what the but there are
like many reasons for me to look forward
to January so I'm actually pretty
excited that the time is uh going by
fast pretty excited
yeah wait when did you get freckles it I
always had freckles what do you
mean see they're so
convincing I'm so convincing when we
yeah
[Music]
okay byebye the
J I see you tomorrow a it please watch
it
everybody please oh it's gone oh there
it is please watch it please please I
worked so hard I
[Music]
swear and let's pray for everything
to be streamed smoothly yes and German s
that's it today it's actually today
today today today today today today
[Music]
today me I I don't know I I really like
impersonating
[Music]
moo today it's kind of to did that sound
like
toad St St
[Music]
St
pap