[Music]
e
e e
[Music]
e
good
morning just f
[Music]
up good
morning hello everyone oh my gosh I'm
soy let me just do my
bed good morning
oh you doing
toy I need to just woke up and I have I
just had I mean I'm having coffee right
now
and uh yeah I'm still
pajama which is something I usually
don't like to
do because I like to prepare it for
stream and such you know but today it
was
[Music]
like I'm going to I woke up I I turn on
my no actually I didn't turn on my PC
because I never turn on my PC I never
turn off my
pc I never turn off my pc and but you
know like pass ra thought okay I need to
stream at 10:00 a.m. and and need a
collab right so everyone will be super
active and super energized caffeinated
and everything and then it's going to be
me super sleepy in 7 days to die so what
should I do and then I said you know
what I'm going to start an hour
earlier because I'm
smart I start 1 hour
earlier
and so doing this I wake up
I get to warm up my voice
too I get some brain cells together and
I lose some of them because of you
whatever that's not the story and
then and then in an
hour you know have been
[Music]
good
why M I haven't got my breakfast either
so I got like a little cake it's not a
cake it's
like what is this it's like a
pancake but I'm not cheese SLE oh that's
so good I haven't got it yet so I don't
know H how you doing hello you know um I
also wanted to chat with you because
this week has been very very busy for
for
me uh like are we're going to have tons
of collabs until I don't have much time
to talk to you and I know you guys have
separation anxiety so I'm here to fix
[Music]
you I separation anxiety too don't
worry
yipp thank you so much guys I'm going to
read this sua now oh my gosh
thank you so much
everyone thank you for the gifting
preach juo what so many gifts in preer
thank
you thank you thank you
Victor as well for the
time thank you so
much lordy welcome morning Mama and
morning evening day to fellow chatini
hello H good
morning what time is it for you now
actually it must be a very good time
for
[Music]
Merica yeah must be pretty pretty good
time 700
p.m. do you have an opinion
on buttercream frosting Italian Swiss
French buttercream frosting I have no
idea what you're talking about
[Music]
I'm sorry I absolutely have no idea what
you're talking what is this is a
football squad or
something a
football no wait it's actually like what
is oh buttercream frosting I know what
is buttercream
frosting yeah I think it's like
something you put on the cake I don't
know peek out here and yeah peek big
content here me me drinking coffee and
talking to you
[Laughter]
guys 800 p.m. 8:00
a.m. 3:00 a.m. here oh oh fellow
Europeans I'm sorry guys this collab is
not good time for you but it's okay we
have plenty of e you time
together living on east coast of America
it's 8:00 p.m. here
looking forward
for thank you so much everyone thank you
for being the spies in my morning
routine the the
spies SP am I the spise am I am I am I
the
[Music]
SP the spise in the morning
routine despise in the
morning the
as I am the spaghetti in your morning
routine today I'm more T them before
than
[Music]
usual you know that I don't know this
song I actually don't know the song I
don't know the lyrics isn't it in
English
though it's like an English
[Music]
song I was considering to order
breakfast because I'm lazy
today I said up for I stayed up late for
stream sleep get broken only to be fixed
again today M Bo
a my gosh guys you have such a big
stamina I heard some of you stay up all
night for stream sometime I'm like guys
how you do that like after like a few
hours I Collapse I literally die how do
you do
that voice sounds a bit different are
you okay I'm okay I'm just guys I am a
big cat but doesn't mean I am
not human as well like I when you wake
up when you wake up you have EP voice
that's how it
is
yeah God means beig tired to be honest
I'm pretty feel like I feel pretty good
right
now I feel pretty pretty good like I'm
very energized and very uh positive
because yesterday I've been to
all day I was so happy
because I went I've been to the
F special spot in Akiba and I was very
happy the donut I got my favorite donut
as well I know pretty basic I know I
know I know it's pretty
basic uh but I like chocolate donut I
don't know why it's my favorite but
that's how it is
um send H love from Brazil hello hello
from from from the Far East hello hello
hello what SCH you need
right thank you de de gold tell them
tell them tell them wheni wants jetpacks
tell them that they already have all
they
need well there is a one good thing
about being sick I don't need to get up
in the morning C oh my
gosh I hope you feel better soon lordy
oh my God for the question is St to
adopt you today today is
a
espresso that you do for 12 hours a day
no wonder mom is tired I'm not I'm not
tired I'm just woke up
understand yeah so yesterday I went to
the special spot and I was like very
was like very very emotional because
I've seen everyone going there and was
like I'm finally here too I don't know
where I never been before because
usually I go to AA pretty often like
it's something I I go pretty often there
um but I never got to this spot for some
I think it's because I never really
snack when I am outside you know I never
really sit down and eat usually if I eat
is a big meal so it's very very rare for
me that I take a whole like I I take a
moment to you
know to eat a
donut I us don't go with donut yesterday
was like I'm here you know what I should
probably
try just sit on the on the favorite spot
of
wles and knowing that this place is
going to shut down soon I I apparently
I'm I'm not 100% sure but
oh my voice but from my understanding
the place is going to shut down soon so
I'm was like I want need to stop
here it will yeah but you know like I
think there is also a chance that
they're going to open somewhere
else I think it's because
um maybe they're renovating the building
is it possible the
renovating yeah yeah it the the building
looks pretty um
[Music]
old so
yeah good morning Mama it's my birthday
today
tant
tant and I saw your post yesterday doing
B give me I to go there thank you for
the idea of the also taste your favorite
donut I know it's nothing really special
I think uh it's just donut with
chocolate on the top um I think they are
better Donuts but usually I like
Simplicity I like the design I like the
taste ah right now there is a Halloween
one but I also very like but it was sold
out when I arrived sadly it was sold out
was
like so yeah that's how it is you know
it's
okay happy birthday happy birthday
T
no thank you L for for the 50 what
wow it's
crazy
W that's a lot of gifts thank you
oh my
gosh should I order breakfast or should
I not get breakfast and Skip breakfast
until lunch
time what should I do I don't
know I don't know oh yeah yesterday I
was going uh around
aiom and I finally I finally
bought um a lot of whole Live friends
plushies but this small ones the small
ones you know the one that you put on
the on the bags I finally I finally
bought like a bunch of them I
got I got a few not all of them because
I you want to spend all my savings
[Music]
but friends to yeah that one friends
friends
too friends to
go um
you go to amyamy building you know
what I feel I felt so stupid because
I've been there but I stopped to the
second floor I haven't been to Ami I've
been to the one below which is I think
bookof oh I'm so sad yeah yeah yeah yeah
I was so sad
because I didn't thought about the
collab I skipped that one because I was
I was in a
rush I wasn't a rush I had to go away I
had to I had to come back streaming so I
wasn't a rush but yeah next time I'll
probably come take it out nice hat ra
look I show you a magic
[Music]
trick h
magic trick oh thank you lunar morning R
I wanted to ask you if you have any
movie look back if you haven't a highly
like oh look back if you haven't LC
comment it's the main about dring an art
so know you would great enjoy it no I
never I've never seen it before Oh guys
come on oh my God okay
fine oh
God guys what it what did it do what
happens if I have another outfit what's
going to
happen come
on
[Music]
huh oh my
gosh guys please
understand
understand no I never I never watch look
back but you know I'm going to put on my
list let me let me write
[Music]
down oh wait I've seen the character
somewhere
[Music]
oh I have seen the character somewhere
I'm going to watch
[Music]
it thank you guys for for the for the
membership to and welcome Ro air to the
new members
welcome oh my God it's cold here
starting to finally be
cold morning morning
everyone child I just realized it's my
birthday what do you mean you just
realiz
[Music]
wait
wait since when you don't check the
calendar don't get to cat your live
often but
uh
happy
today happy birthday you have to say any
t otherwise what why we do Italian Ence
here
Italian very good very good very
good I'm too TI to say it anytime no you
can do it come on and
lazy today I think I
had I has a weird dream if you want to
hear my weird dream I just remembered
you want to hear my my weird dream so I
was like in my
hometown and at some point I decided to
go on a train uh for some
reason and the train got me to a huge
Tower and this huge Tower was full of
like uh challenges
[Music]
and and you know it was like it was like
a dungeon you know like a tower and it
was like probably a treasure on the
top and
then I remember I found
um like a cage and in this cage
it was like some sort
of very I don't know like I don't
[Music]
remember I don't remember I think it was
like a old woman in the
cage telling me about something and
then and then and then I went to the top
of the tower and then and then I died
that's it that's all I remember I don't
know my my
brain my brain doesn't
bring yeah it was it was pretty much of
a short short short dream I always have
dream do you do you guys dream do you
guys have dreams I always have
dreams sometime sometime I have very
weird
dreams sometime I have very weird dreams
um that makes me anxious and give me
anxiety sometime they are so real
sometime they are
like they feel like they're real and I
don't understand what's reality and what
is not reality it's
crazy like
H I hate chasing dreams no I don't have
I usually don't have nightmare sometime
I had
nightmare oh my God yeah I remember a
few nightm but not really not all the
time that makes
sense
H you dreaming right now no I'm not
dreaming right now that's
real morning Mama we from c
m
eh would like to know
the specs of your wheel since you're a
big
car
um huh after what happened to someone's
friending the other day we don't want to
turn into a bike by accident during
servicing
huh I am a big car and you should trust
me and I don't know about my wheels I
think I have feet as everyone else but
when I transform into a
car I don't know what kind of Wheels I
have and I don't have enough brain cells
for that anyway
[Music]
feet Mansion oh come
on I have to exam tomorrow and then I
got to go home for break but mama is
more important no guys please this exam
is more important what are you talking
about go study for your exams what are
you doing
[Music]
here can always get up the
B go take your ex home
[Music]
oh my gosh I'm so happy I don't have
more a in my life I had a moment I had a
time in my life when when I had a lot of
exom it's finally over I'm so
happy I'm so happy I hate exom it makes
me feel so anxious and
[Music]
bad
huh exams are retable but not
mama what do you mean by that what do
you mean by
[Music]
that please wake up Raa we are worried
and have turned to contact you about
your car extended warranty okay first I
don't have a car extended warranty and
second I'm not sleeping that's real
[Music]
right I mean I mean I
mean I
mean you know you know what honestly if
I wake up at some point and ches are not
real and the fact that I'm here in whole
life is not real I won't be that
surprised it's a dream for me I told you
guys it feels like a dream for me I
won't be that
surprised but okay it's to be
expected it's like those kind of uh
underground stories where like I don't
know there's a character living like 20
years in the anime and then at the end
it was a coma and it was a
dream I was like okay but at the end the
character got a lot of nice stories and
a lot of Adventures so who cares it's
like
Inception it's like Inception like like
at some point right if you sleeping if
it's a dream in a dream who cares right
like do you actually care if you're
dreaming right
now what if this is all a simulation
what is what if this reality is a
simulation what if you guys right now
live in a
simulation
[Music]
huh how does he feel to be a plushy in a
simulation
[Music]
she figured it out turn off the
simulation quick check for the
Box sorry I already clipped out of
reality I I am I'm I Am the Artist with
the god eyes what do you expect from me
I can see
everything you didn't expect that for me
huh I am smarter than you thought
[Music]
I'm smarter than you
thought reset
reset you can't go back
now thank you Arizona thank you I'm a TR
tricycle cuz I'm always dirt
[Music]
willing I kind of like that one
I kind of like that
[Laughter]
[Music]
one all right I'm laughing at this
stupid joke
[Music]
anyway help
me living the best simulation the one
with you you guys are Soo
sweet a simulation with you is a
simulation worth
living a now
got
listen listen
in this
simulation there are no jetpacks so you
better find a way out our way out
[Music]
Mansion I never played that way out by
the way maybe I should collab with
someone is it a collab game right I
never played the game before
[Music]
yeah maybe I should play with someone is
it
[Music]
funny I think G and CCE played
it together if I remember I don't know I
I may remember wrong
[Music]
yeah okay my memory
Works what is h
Huh what Ultra chatini first cha
plane what is that what is this
[Music]
what is your
lawyer what is your laer when you need
one you dirty awake already at no it's
it's 900 a.m.
here luckily for me it's 9 a.m.
[Music]
L
Zing better for
them because today I'm going to sh you
for
[Music]
crimes
yeah I think it's very you gu you guys
know saying Merry Christmas to
me I'm going to show you for not saying
Merry Christmas to me today
Merry Christmas
yay it's Christmas
[Music]
time I love
Christmas I want Christmas right
now can't wait for
Christmas I just want to skip Halloween
I don't like
Halloween yeah yeah I don't like
Halloween scary
spooky
oh about spooky oh the lawyer is here
where are our gifts you have no gifts
you have me I am your gift that's more
than
[Music]
enough hi I'm a t if you ever need
jetpack ride I can help you no
no
no no no no jetpack here taco no jetpack
here I'm
sorry it is what it is but you're very
welcome
hi no not Bas no jetpack no I won't
allow
that anyway I was about to say something
oh yeah
a i organized something what along of a
horror
movie with
Justice wo we're going to watch all
together a horror movie this is a big
spoiler you know what I don't mind
spoiler this I think it's already
decided y I want to do a what long with
just this a horror movie I'm not going
to spoil the horror movie though
I'm not going to spoil the horror
[Music]
movie uh I don't I don't tell you which
one maybe okay is it the ring no it's
not the
[Music]
ring
uh I don't think
so but yeah when uh it's going to be at
the end of the month so I I I will tell
you Way in advance don't worry about it
yeah yeah yeah I'll tell you Way Way in
advance uh in the schedule
[Music]
schule so don't worry about it but it's
going to be fun I always wanted to have
a watch along with all Justice together
I love watch along makes me
[Music]
happy can't wait for
it what time um
I'll tell you more details later I think
we are still trying to figure out a few
things but I don't want to tell you
times and wait until it's confirmed but
I think it's going to
[Music]
happen and I don't mind okay usually I
don't mind sacrificing myself usually
for
[Music]
um
um um
what I was saying yeah for the time zone
like I don't mind staying up late or
waking up early if it's for
collabs like if it's on me I want to
collab with you but my only time out is
at 5:00 a.m. no problem I can stay awake
like usually I don't mind I I'm pretty
good at
[Music]
handling time zones and my sleep schedu
too
yeah so usually it
[Music]
depends whenever you stream around this
time that's very much appreciated you
guys know like every at least once a
week or once every two weeks I try to
sleep to stream at this time
anyway usually that's what I try to
[Music]
do wait can you hear the audio right now
can you hear the music
[Music]
right okay good um
I'm starting to launch the game just in
case I need to join a specific thing one
it's going to start soon I haven't
[Music]
realized yeah so I was saying um as much
as I can I will try to stream more these
time out you
know uh probably usually I do like once
a week I do also membership streams at
this time
sometime
so
yeah it's going to be
[Music]
fun don't push yourself mama I love I
love being here don't worry about it I'm
okay also I'm going to get I'm going to
take a day off on Sunday
yippe I think I'll go that some
grass we
[Music]
see yeah
finally I'm excited
okay I'm going to let me let me check uh
where's the
[Music]
game okay uh give me a second I need to
make sure that everything works
before the
collab I'm probably going to join the uh
the VC in um 10 minutes before the
stream just to make sure that every
everything
[Music]
works I can't believe it's already been
40 minutes I haven't said anything yet
I wanted to chat
[Music]
more hey favorite big cat sorry if you
haven't answered this before but have
you ever played Resident Evil
7 I always play it t and up I think the
voice acting is awesome maybe I like it
too a
you guys know I never played Resident
Evil 7 but maybe I can give it a
try maybe we can play
[Music]
together can't play
together is is it like a horror movie
I'm not going to be able to play
it it's like too
[Music]
much not
horror
[Music]
really I'm okay to play the
game but I heard good things about that
so maybe it will be fun to do the T in
the
uh but maybe if it's a story based game
probably is a bit
difficult it's a family friendly I don't
know about that I don't know about that
[Music]
okay I think my game is ready okay
good Big C means big
[Music]
preparation
yeah t t everyone
hello s days has no story oh no not
7even days guys uh Resident Evil I was
talking about seven Resident
Evil like in case we want to play
together because someone said that there
is a talent up um but I don't think I'm
going to do it because if there is a
story I want everyone to follow the
story with
me
yeah tent 2 remake game playay
[Music]
scary scary thank you so much for the
gift thank
you and now she's saying she thank
you thank
you Orton thank you so much hello Roy
here apologies it is taking long ER than
anticipated to set the many diamonds
into jetpack you ordered we are working
our hardest to complete on time
however no jet pug out here I'm sorry
you can't you got fired you just lost
your
job no
[Music]
more literally
fire this is what I mean when I say you
fired I said them literally on fire
[Music]
Crazy Fire
Fire exactly
[Music]
huh fire with fashion
mhm I can't wait for seven days to die
I'm excited it looks a
pretty pretty fun game I love big
collabs anyway what about ghost hunting
with the girls in
phasmophobia I played it for the first
time with friends the other day and I
didn't think I like it cuz I'm a big
scary di but I do
really H maybe I should give it a
shot maybe I'll give it a try
[Music]
H I think I will
try um I mean I mean f is a is a collab
game I think so maybe I'll organize
something in the
future myc is already pretty packed for
the next couple of weeks though so I
will see what I what I can do about
it I would I would plan something
maybe I think you so much for
recommending the game maybe maybe I
should do a collab now that um um it's
it's Halloween
[Music]
time you know actually and I Don't
Starve Together a lot I really really
lik
it they with
members M I think
phasmophobia doesn't allow more than
three or four people so maybe it's not a
good game to play with
members isn't
it and we're going to have a teini day
soon
again I think I'm going to do another
Cho day
yeah are you
excited yeah another Tino
day it's going to happen so we're going
to play with members during Teo day for
sure I want to play more um full guys
this time I really enjoyed full
guys can can we play more together and
Mario Kart I want to play more Mario
Kart I want to get good at Mario Kart is
a good way to train I I one thing I
realized last time I
played is that
probably I should play more did you
enjoy party animals yeah I want to play
party animals too there are a few games
I want to play with you so we'll
see don't
worry um let's say I always wanted to
prioritize playing games that everyone
can play with me more than you know
games that just two three people can
join uh because I
think I think everyone wants to play
with me at some point so I want to I
want to try to give everyone the chance
you know that makes sense
[Music]
letter
company letter company sounds good
too but again it's a game for like just
four people
Max isn't it how many people can live a
[Music]
company M you can mod I don't know guys
I don't think it's a good
idea also I don't know if I'm allowed to
use mods you
know I I play with like 20 oh maybe I
yeah I don't
know I need to double check
[Music]
yeah I maybe I maybe I need to ask for
perms sometime you need to ask anyway
and sometime it can take more than a few
days so I don't know if I can do it in
time if that makes
sense we'll
see I think Le company is a is a is a
game that is very useful like Sor it's
very funny if you play in vocal s too
you
know so yeah definitely going to play
you know what we can play Among
Us Among Us with so many people it's
fun thank you so much for my gifts thank
you I think I can play Among Us it'll be
fun maybe there is an option for it
[Music]
gtic
phones ah gtic phones is probably a
little risky because you guys could like
let's say let's say
someone joins and they dress something
very weird or very bad or something
right so yeah I don't want to I I don't
want to risk a BN because of that
I mean I trust you and I don't trust all
of you at the same
[Music]
time
yeah I have trust issues right now with
you you have to gain your trust on me
again yeah I have
PTSD I have PSD because of you
just want to remind you
mhm good morning
everyone good
[Music]
morning that is
99 M maybe I like Tre s is very fun game
I used to be obsessed with it
nice capucino I know right very
[Music]
me I need to join uh let me join the VC
for a moment one sec I'm going to mute
myself
[Music]
no actually I think it's okay I'm going
just
start one
[Music]
second oh my man
MH I'm
try moment the collab will start very
soon did you miss anything no we just
we're just yapping and I'm finally feel
more awake than before so I still
remember you're talking about pizza with
french fries and during lunch break at
work I've been missing out all my
life let's go
see it was actually great
[Music]
I was trying I ask some questions about
it
[Music]
okay wait what I was talking about I
forgot yeah everyone's starting now yeah
yeah yeah yeah was make making sure that
I'm ready
[Music]
okay okay okay I'm going to switch
screen now and we're going to spawn
together to seven days to
die yay and I'm probably going to join
the VC
I don't know if we're going to use the
VC in the game I suppose we
do stay alive I'll try my very
[Music]
best I'm going to join the VC as
well you
go
okay have
confidence I hope I'm okay I I mean I
tried the game a little bit and it's a
little bit like Minecraft where you
don't where you need to craft
and gather materials and I'm usually
pretty good at it
so we Justice yay for
justice okay let me just switch screen
[Music]
apparently we start on the dot so one
second let me just put down my plusy and
my
[Music]
Mark here you
go yay we here we here hello everyone is
there any music in game here I'm see
can you hear me all
good t t t t t t t test test test test
test one two three test
okay good okay so apparently we spawn at
the dot so right now I guess we
can
[Music]
uh okay we can start now starting game
good
morning
okay okay okay everything works fine I'm
going to move my tatini though sorry
guys I need to move you
here there you go touching grass
actually
so
apparently okay we here we all
here
uhhuh they joining they
joining music is so
sad no game audio wait no you cannot
hear the audio
oh what about
now can you
hear okay good thank you sorry about
that
[Music]
okay not sure how we going to find the
others but I guess we all going to
spawn in the same
area I hope
so
hello go that's a pink
car oh my God that's a pink car that's
my
car it must be mine
[Music]
yeah must be
it I'm gathering as much material as
possible
now must
be have to W te away
oh okay let me just make a wooden
cup and we need some Stone axe too so I
need
fiber oh no I need to pick Stones as
well yeah let's other
materials glue
[Music]
yummy welcome youo hello hello hello
ah I don't know what to
do can you hear me uh how can I
there a to spawn next to
them let each
other how do
I oh like that
oh they pretty close I
[Music]
guess I think I accepted
everything oh yeah yeah come to beo to
B you look pretty buff yourself
everybody looks buff I'm sure oh wait
well I mean you have to be certain level
of buff in order to survive the zombie
apocalypse I think although this is twoo
buff like you would want more fat but
maybe they can't because they don't find
food would make sense makes sense to me
[Music]
hello nice everybody everybody's joining
that's huge overturn trailer whoa hold
up
hold is this maybe a we should probably
get to everybody um do I have to find
you guys or am I going to spawn spawn
next to you you have to us you're going
to somewhere so come to De and
for well we'll meet where we're at okay
okay so I'm
going I'm
going next to
I
think meet at the
Rock I don't see them oh maybe I need
to people
here
oh oh they're pretty
far let's PL the tree together
okay okay yeah beep this
tree oh gosh yeah take the anger out on
the tree
yeah yeah already punching trees I see
that's good wa we're Gathering resources
while you guys try to arrive also did
you punch
me what are you
doing the Tre I wonder if there is a way
to
calibrate for everyone
CE can we
swim I'm so far away from everyone oh my
gosh you know if we can swim it's going
to be a
journey yeah sorry my M my mic was yes
you're good let's
go I tried changing Pusher talk and it
didn't work for some reason
that's okay I think there no like voice
activation I think it's just push to
talk yeah no no tried changing my
key you guys were in voice chat
already actually yeah we're using uh the
party chat but probably move to Discord
afterward okay byy took seven minutes to
die did you die yeah I died like 7
Minutes in ironically no that's
hilarious oh hello everyone hello oh
you're also big man what is that o
big a lady makeup
on Wow you
also hello dear sir I lost boing bowing
hello sir nice beard nice beard
nice
be also very clean and nicely shaven
head I wonder how much time that takes
you every
day yeah there is a lot of EO I don't
know isong I don't have hair on my head
couldn't a
long Me Maybe maybe we should hop in a
Discord hello beautiful
lady oh she doesn't see me
oh sorry what the hell l so Sor this is
not a
joke will
you I didn't know I could actually punch
you okay I think we're moving to Discord
voice
chat all
right
vience oh yeah I will say why is my mic
so low that's weird let me it's kind
kind of quiet oh
God run run run I think we're okaying
volume tag T
tag can you hear me byebye hear you okay
thank you yay we're figuring it out
together
together why is
Qui I'll turn up maybe that'll help it's
quiet okay uhoh
St who is there weight in this game too
like you like a a maximum how much you
can carry in ter in terms of weight nope
sorry guys sorry sorry sorry oh so you
can just carry as much as you want
that's
great it's there's inventory slots that
are
finite wait there's a house over here
have it the big goals for today are to
find a place to to ch chill out in
together um a base even if it's
temporary um well yeah can we take over
this house this looks nice this is
actually a really nice house we did get
lucky this is like a The Walking Dead
house what is happening they crouching I
don't think so to out the enemies here
though am I
crouching what happens if we died yes
you are quing then we respawn you want
to make a b roll really
quick thank you I thought we live in
this house there's a PC set up I can
stream from
here
what this bad sounds huh watch out my
zombies in the house so there's there's
baddies I let's kill
him I'm
yay zombie noises don't B me I thought
you was you do you want to come with me
to them uh I'm already trying to make my
way towards uh bi apparently that's
where we're meeting okay okay house so
I'm I'm slowly making my way there we
are we are in a a big house to be our
home base be our
home do you want to go upstairs with me
we should go upstairs for
okay what what are you scared are you
scared is that why it is a nice house oh
I call the bed but I have a giant hole
here I don't know I don't know about the
Integrity of this house may she didn't
go there not sure we might just need to
fill the hole and then we'll be fine but
yeah you're
right here yeah that's
true oi don't hurt my new friends
running out of s so
easily you went upstairs close
oh
isina still alive but they're dead
yeah where they
go I don't know he's got a bit of reach
on him okay it's just Dark Souls it's
just Dark
Souls oh he fell I get the stones I may
need
them F bunk beds down
here I'll take the couch is there a way
to improve the stamina
somehow you might need to level up or
something oh oh oh oh this evil stop
being jump scared by me thank
youing the I material on the cart there
I'm going
to Temporary
mute so because we're I'm not with them
yet oh my God this character was
temporary
okay
fine let's see the
infiltrator I would like to survive
so e
e yeah
I'm muted to avoid too much confusion
When we arrive to the others I'm going
to
unmute you need to complete the mission
first open challenges
window well
there you
[Music]
go
items leave me
[Music]
alone oh there is a bridge I think I can
swim good morning everyone hello
ping has a lot of stamina
[Music]
oh that's why I was luing out of thank
you are you guys ever did you guys ever
play this game before is the first
time let me check how far am okay we're
getting closer
nope
okay answer Adam's R Riv
raver I wish I could just drive the
car but I don't think we
can bone knife Oo we take
everything you
know I'm going to build a stone kn
and can I build something else
no let's see uh this is like
points when you level up okay how do you
level
up hello
zombie how's
going I heard that the at night the
zombies gets very f pass so we probably
need to either
find a place
to you know rest on the night I don't
think I can reach them before night well
maybe Yes
actually I got
um wooden
Club can use
it oh I got a friend
invite do I accept
them oh like that
okay
done now there zombie
it's time to swim can I swim or do I die
no I can swim you're
wet
oh you want to Bon the I mean when we
did the rehearsal they told
me like I never played this game so you
know we had like a test to understand
the base of the basics of the game
together and the first thing they told
me is like defeating zombies is not
actually very
convenient because they can damage you
pretty quickly and like they're pretty
difficult at least at the beginning so
probably they they told us to pretty
much like skip a skip at the zombies
that's why I'm skiper skiper the
zombies that make
sense like it's better to oh what is
this huh it's better to try to
[Music]
don't kill
them
oh oh
de should I go
up no it doesn't make me
to I want to see if I can find uhoh
oh well let's
try
tutorial not going to
die oh my God please die already
[Applause]
I'm
dying
[Music]
uh-oh yeah it was not a good
idea 10 HP 10 HP in a
dream yeah I told you it was pretty
difficult
oh I see people am I here oh actually
I'm I think I
arrived sometimes so great then let's
have like a magazine crate or something
I personally am going for
I think
welcome
wel I am hello s there you go Beat It To
Death guys there's a Farm close by
okay we're going to BU something
here I just got a chicken I just caught
us
dinner what do I need to build my
first
cting my first my clothes this is a good
spot
potato my clo dinner time
baby I
see you can make a bone knife soon
too uh-oh if you find corpses on the
ground hit them ladies hit them oh wood
oh I
can zombies kind of cute I need more
wood okay let's go need a little further
away kind of a strong zombie I don't
know
[Music]
let's
go by the uh I have an
infe how do
you fix the infection cut off the arm oh
you're infected I am infected oh I guess
bye goodbye nice Dark Souls time to put
the C
down he where are you hey I am here I'm
here wait where is she I am here hello
I'm here I'm here where is here where is
here IND hello hi okay I'll help you
with the infection no no no no no no no
no stop stop stop actually might be
worse at the beginning she's wait
where's she going to respawn is she is
she going to respawn no no she might
respawn all the way in the beginning
don't kill her no no I worked so hard to
be
here okay where where are you been I'll
just tear off that limb you we can talk
about it I okay listen no fighting no F
we can talk about it okay okay listen I
want to help I want to get materials I
want to I want to help you guys to fight
zombies and I behind you behind you a
Zombie
B is that a trick is no it's it's
literally right there don't want to
sleep in the bathroom hello oh okay but
maybe you guys are inceed oh well
kiaha them K
them if you hear me that big a of it oh
I'm doing my I'm crafting my my
my get him get him get him back we'll
get him in the
booty figure out how to leave this other
party I'm in that I'm currently not
talking
oh I'm not I'm not muted I'm not
muted no we hear you we hear you
you boy nice
one I'm not sure I have to leave a party
that I'm in I am hurting I can tell
should but I made a a bow and I got us
meat you guys I got us meat so I'm going
to make a
wait I have a question how do you
actually wear the outfit uh you click on
the item and press W
oh our
house you have the best house
ever freaking rocks just got to figure
out how to fix the door right
click how do we put a crate here oh okay
I'm not Naked Anymore good yeah don't be
naked naked's
dangerous you make two two crates this
my bed
now I'm getting some cotton
plant for
medication could have sworn I made too
oh here we go all right I'm finally
where you guys are I think I I'm I'm
there I see you she's here welcome
you here for now right yay is it a like
yellow the papa residence yes the papa
that's a streamer house oh
welcome will it fit all of
us
okay
[Music]
pooton I more
Hello H did someone put that building
block down there and I accidentally take
took it yeah it's just a block the door
okay corn even the corns are Dad here oh
there go place is awesome so we put our
uh bed rolls in here somewhere did you
go do that already yes you should Tiara
oh the bed right anywhere there's actual
beds in here there are
are oh where did you build those beds or
were there just bunk beds by
default h put your put your you have to
craft a bed roll and then put the bed
roll where you want to spawn so I'm
taking the master bedroom hey the master
bedroom I'm going to make it
too how do we does anyone know how to
make like chests or something yeah I
just made them they're in the living
room living room where oh they are thank
you what the I wonder if I can put right
something I'll just put all my garbage
in here yeah sure just materials and
such oh maybe I should on this couch you
get to sleep on this comfy bed
nice lucky right oh there's an
upstairs uh I think I got building Cube
from the house I'm sorry that's
okay I'll Rec I'll recog it how do you
place a bed down right click oh okay but
I don't know I don't know how to turn
it oh I guess I can't place it on the
toilet a mky
water if you guys find Murky water you
can uh you can boil it in a pot over
fire to clean it what I see oh Network
timeout I got kicked out did we all get
kicked out not me no not me it said you
disconnected okay I'm going to sleep
next to the PC then I sleep next to the
laundry so I can put them in the washing
machine
we making
sure have to rejoin water
water maybe I do want to burn some peee
water
huh plan block oh we might need that
what there was a thing we could do
outside
oh there's a visitor at our humble abode
a
visitor yeah
someone are they nice I don't know but
they're not talking perfect is R NPC uh
is it the shieldy group
shieldy F group did you just attack me I
like this room I've claimed the land
oh
nice press to use
um anyway we claimed this land with this
block uh what are you doing stop
beautiful a
[Music]
see
ADH took us so hard stoping
me we have someone evil this this
personing me stop stop I have no control
I don't have no control of my
li
ja C you look beautiful look this is my
this is my PC setup do you like it oh
nice oh I can sleep on top of it
actually
opening or maybe I
cannot can I SLE got this place it's
pretty Co should I sleep I'm going to
find do you like it very I mean yeah
yeah it's
co yeah yeah
yeah I like it I have some privy
too to does anyone want to come I want
to go try going to a
farm okay wait let just set up home here
really quick let's go I come I actually
know where
then let's wait for shy shy did you say
you want to you will come with us or let
me just my bed roll okay okay got to set
that let's wait a second I need to is
there a tra near here or you guys Trader
lless pry what did you say is there a
Traer near this
house found one yet we haven't done
anything I like that even in the
apocalypse Trend thing and we all
wearing the same style I accidentally
clicked fashion fashion by the way if
you guys open the map you can set a
marker for where home is open the map
right we are you can set a marker that's
nice I'm sorry every time I all tap back
in I punch someone oh that's what
happened I don't mean it stay away from
truth truth please don't touch me you
don't touch me truth
okay on guys be careful don't hit each
other guys
don't all right I'm going stay back so
you guys
don't probably yeah get him get him get
that oh yeah oh legs lift we're crazy
this way I think was the farm Yep this
way wait wait who am I following
everyone looks the same I'm a little
hungry just follow
everybody follow this the the the flow
oh dead corn okay but I'm going to have
ADH on the way that's okay you can have
at any point you
want oh there's corn
[Applause]
cornn Pi the corn
can cook cuz I got some meat and potato
so there's like dead corn and green corn
I think the green that was real corn me
I'm ding
already there is some good corn too
ladies I feel like we should probably be
oh they're dead o let's go yeah there is
real
corn can we get can we get seeds to
replant them already stole that from me
I think so but I I don't know how to do
that kind of stuff got to be a good
farmer I I'll be finding
apocalypse with corn that's all I need
I'll survive most of the Corn are dead
though yum
corn just can't eat the the people oh
what this one is different I mean
they're just zomes people yeah that that
is this area has three three skulls on
it I don't know if we're ready for that
oh oh does that mean like Danger going
to die yeah I get the green ones the
loot probably really good but I just
don't think we're ready surpris there's
like skull images so I noticed that the
green corns actually contain seeds too
probably oh they do no there's a ear
corn they have something different we
could set up a little farm by our
home yeah let's do that can we that's a
seed here
I
see this is be careful this is the three
School area yeah it's a pretty
intens there's zombies everywhere run
run
run you got run going to do it's okay
I'll us fine what are they going to do
huh eat us so much
[Laughter]
corn all right I hope the corn be like
do
supplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of hopefully
did
that I'm going back home I think so
nothing I don't think it give you
anything can I eat okay we can eat wait
why there is so we just need the be
wies for the green ones
[Music]
found who wants to focus on getting food
maybe we should split into like yeah
good idea food gatherers this is just
like Gathering and then let's stay at
home so far
time let's go Oran I found a land claim
block do we have to destroy this oh I
think someone put that down I just put
that there for the quest worry not oh I
don't what my land claim BLX is so if
you put a land claim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage on something
apparent so like you're safe in the zone
I guess or something like that or the
player who put it down is safe in the
zone it's like your L
now by the house yeah we have one of
those I put one in the living room oh
okay awesome oh we're in the same uh
Ally group too so we should be good to
go it won't be harder for us to destroy
each other's things if we need exactly
goodness that I have a question um um no
party six how do you level
up not important I think he got to kill
oh killing zombies okay yeah we find a
traitor he gives Quest and he gives a
lot of exp from the quest does anyone
want to go with me on an adventure to
see if we can find the traitor I know
where he is he's really far already find
the I have one on my map to yeah oh okay
is it the wide river yeah yeah should
this way point if he wants to trade he
should come to us that's right he's not
going to do that I think but then he
won't have any Vision not going to be
our face by the way or he's going to
stay
hello I found
people welcome welcome welcome welcome
welcome wait you guys are all wearing
something why aren't you wearing where's
your hat there's a hat yes put your hat
on what you should probably to
it a house kill
it hat your head I will crack you a hat
oh wait no I see a hat oh thank you yes
put it on Oh yay oops
civilized y I need TR so what is the
Traer why um he's far I don't know how
to share the way Mark with you guys what
what if you send like a screenshot oh I
I can send a
screenshot gloves I'm missing gloves pie
oh that
works craft anything just yet
there's a c land claim
box S I can make us charge meat for
guns meat meat meat is this our Base by
the way this is our base
yeah we should probably do
M what is this land claim block uh it's
so our home base now basically zombies
won't spawn around you you see it I put
it in the channel of the map what if we
all put our land claim blocks like
around each other so they won't spawn
within a yeah let's protect the house
can we
get
where how to make land claim block oh
this is oh I have a land claim block um
I don't know where to put it though uh
it won't let me put it
anywhere they claim this land claimed
yeah is there a maximum to can only one
person claim a
land I how are you cooking oh this is
Mor that's me oh here Tre maybe right
there tring to figure out where to put
this oh yeah I can't put the land clim
oh yeah it's a pretty it's a pretty
large put here I am dying of hunger
maybe I'll put it here oh I found the
place yeah I need to eat some all right
W has claimed this lands C
by the
river see if we can cook some more for
everybody maybe here oh we need cooking
items oh oh I like the the placement of
this fire
right can't put another one we play
some just anywhere these days you just
put at the fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying
okay yeah oh I found a I found a cooking
a grill outside the house I
don't put in the house then honey you
can get from
stumps near trees is there a town nearby
oh uh there's a town very far
away oh that's
water oh that the hell that's I'm going
to eat scary
food by the way night time soon everyone
um oh you guys have a nice campire out
here wonderful for the idea that I have
is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions together oh that's
a good idea nice idea yes that would be
great sorry
sorry I'm here
River she's here I don't know what to do
what it's about to
be does
any I want to go I want to
go I'm going into Che too if anyone
wants to go on an
Excursion time stroll I'm going to
collect items I'm going to gather stuff
so
I'll
hello night time stroll time yeah night
there a little night check out M I am
infected so if I die at any moment do
you have a bed roll yeah okay then you
should respawn at the bed yes indeed
okay so yeah if you die you'll respawn
where you put your bed roll down okay
maybe should I die here then and respawn
so we can yeah okay I'll kill you don't
worry Sirah we'll help
you can put it
in no
hesitation you're welcome it's fine
anytime anytime you need for help we'll
help you don't worry no hesitation at
all
wow Mur we can put our stuffs in our
inventory yeah there's a box here in the
living room oh in the okay here these
two okay one moment we go
okay should we check out the area East
to where we are it seems to have like a
little yeah I'm alive or something oh is
that the farm your stuff is where you
die okay I'm going to pick it up
yeah thank you for helping okay I'm
ready actually that's where the farm
is okay um should we try the one West
from us then
people ow ow zombie ah how could this
happen to me a zombie in the zombie game
no is it inside maybe let's close the
door oh oh it is
inside
perfect be
it's over yeah M
[Music]
NE I don't
know breast it doesn't sound
good how much corn do I have to eat to
not be hungry I think the corn just has
one I don't oh yeah we need to make food
we need to like Grill it
probably okay let me check I have I have
a few eggs maybe oh I got some chicken
soup okay I'll just eat that oh oh yeah
in the
can
yummy it calls me will we so creep
you okay I got some eggs and I don't
think you can do anything with the eggs
yet we need like a pan and stuff yeah
yeah oh my
gosh okay were we were we heading out by
the way yeah I'm outside scared a little
right okay don't be scared let's go a
new um
it is
time oh we need a new
one make uh you can you can repair your
Axe by the way yes let's repair it
then oh I can't oh we don't I don't have
the Mater we don't have the materials
right now second give me a moment we put
it all
away
mhm we need some rocks prob also if we
had a toy to be a it little be easier to
feed them I can make boiled eggs you
should have one when you spawned or is
it a torch we have
one oh
clay what need
clay oh gosh what is that what is that
help help help
help I
see no wor I got it I got it
don't touch
the oh my gosh is it that I think so yes
yes yes yes thank you you saved me let's
go you're
welcome not you f fou okay we
going yield the violence
yay okay is everyone here yeah this
way is in the house we in the
house okay let's try going for the the
the area that is left of this down the
street okay watch
out it's going to be back up maybe we
should run run away from them
oh he got
me they're fast I need more ston maybe
everybody
away no they outrun Us in the night than
us
okay nice does does anybody have extra
Pebbles I want to make a spear oh oh
yeah I was trying to do that actually I
have on my inventory are very hungry our
maximum status is stamina is reduced we
should have some of our food M but you
don't want to eat
it there goes our food
okay hungry still hungry yeah I don't
know the beginning is really hard
because there's just no food so yeah
you're just going to be hungry I don't
know be hungry be hungry okay there
might be like a way to make food from
the very beginning but I don't know so
figure it out try finding stuff it's ooh
cell tower number one what what's
this are you guys are you guys outside
right we're inside the building that we
just oh if you're in the
party ra go towards the pink the
pink Okay pink uh pink triangle can I
can I go past you please oh sorry am I
on the way thank you
it's
okay it's okay let's break stuff I think
I'm starving I can there's water empty
water nothing it's empty it's empty
water cool oh oh what
scratching
oh it's okay you're you're cat you're on
the
prow maybe the game has like
Communications or something uhoh I hear
some put I want to climb on up oh I
can't I'm coming oh there we go I think
I found of this no this is how do I go
up the ladder how do I the lad you just
go press
W be careful there's a zombie up here
though so just watch out are going to
get him uhoh oh zes I think he ran off
the cliff never
mind close the door yeah
ah my leg is sprained guys it's over I'm
going to be your dead from now
on
yeah my leg is brok oh my God
face
strong no no leave me
[Applause]
alone okay okay okay okay okay let me
let me c this
here oh my God my leg is
broken we have 15 Health we good we
going to die it's okay I'll climb down
I look down look down is there outside
I'm going to fight them come on oh
Gody don't go down don't go down they're
coming they're
coming
the kill him in the hole Yeah kill him
in the
hole go
go I'm D I'm I'm I'm okay not
not not a smart
yet how do you go
down you just you just like look down
look at the
floor I have I have six
HP go back up
no well I'm going to stay inside the
house to the Bri okay it's right there
uhoh
yummy we're not very fast oh our stamina
is really bad what's the what's the
little it's not very
fast that one to I use this point do we
have
one scary I thought it was zombie okay I
have a spear do you guys want a spear I
have an extra one uhoh uhoh here they
come we make pleas I don't know how to
do that take it
oh is that a weapon yes take it get the
weapon get the
weapon avenge me they are they ining
invading they invading uhoh we go we go
attack
attack what the
heck nooh
oh my
God
St I'm going to fight
you I really need a
spear a lot
of on my backed on my backed oh that's a
big one I don't think we want to go
back come
on thank you
I don't have any
stuff no
y no no hi guys
hi I'm good I'm good thank you
B yeah
okay take turns take turns take turns
take
turns where you going almost
done this is one that's very r
uhoh I'm n y for this okay
good okay sorry
Dad
downstair
theing watch out
ouch out
you you
okay one of them has red eyes it's
messed up because it's night and they
stronger yeah they're stronger oh they
run away from us oh
no I'll try burning them he's burning
he's
burning burn them burn them die let's go
but then if they come in here what are
we doing how are we escaping this
guess one near my it's okay it's okay
I'm
okay burn
burn bur the full moon oh
oops
no the night is almost
over
wa come Rock
uhoh oh God okay okay okay okay may I
don't know I I'm
[Applause]
not oh there's no
door
okay I sa here I don't know we'll
see I guess it
is really no no okay no it's not
really
uhoh uhoh uhoh okay I say a plant change
of plants everyone go back home okay
going
home and R back
home okay run home yes run back home
pick up your backpack don't forget to
pick up your backpack and then run back
home backpack it's gone this back I
think we need to craft some better
weapons before going in adventure
well it was still a nice Adventure it
was just not oh I haven't said that it
was not a nice
Adventure there's blood everywhere no
it's it's nice it was
nice okay okay let me see this
way hey the the sky is coming
up da Upon Us
yeah okay need a door it's pink outside
there you
go okay I need to medicate did anyone
find anything was this like successful
in any way no I find I found some food
but that's pretty much it what did you
find food that's good yeah I found some
juice and some
peas be careful be careful be
careful everything no I don't want okay
I'm going back to the uh others
I'm at home right now there's still
zombies out there let's make our own
wooden crate and put it downstairs in
our room and then nobody will get
confused
yeah uhoh I can
craft
arrows arrows arrows yeah maybe range
might be
nice this
we should do it sooner than later maybe
maybe we should do it sooner than later
put oh there we go put the
on put
on not what's going on behind me put it
in put it in I want what's going if
we're at home do you guys want to go
back to the main
tat have knif oh yeah the main voice
chat cuz went back okay that makes sense
okay
[Music]
too no it didn't
work that welcome back you did good is
this really our
home the good news is I found a house
that cilia oh really yes why did you
backpack I brought that was from the
zombie oh my God committing sex in
daylight no no I thought it was from the
zombie I thought oh my God this guy has
a lot of loot
wow was was still
decomposing I read your I read your
magazine tra again huh you read
the okay okay if I find now you know if
there was a backpack that's survive
probably well yeah if I if I find two
more magazines I'll give them to you
I'll donate them to you no worries no
worries it's I have a question yeah how
do I get aight iron how do I get
IR for IR not sure about that probably
have to find a rock and iron M maybe
maybe like do I need a pickax or
something of stuff in here or just a
stone pickaxe is fine your junk in sry
stone ax I guess we can only makei walls
though yeah Community chest or something
maybe what a cute frame oh I can make
grill for now I go find iron then how
can you make the grilled corn baby um I
used a magazine to learn cooking skill
and now I have cooking skill up oh maybe
you can like make all I want to find a
magazine
oh okay
I I need a cooking grill but if I if we
have a cooking grill I can cook the corn
I think
they leave the the cooking grill at the
fire so everyone can cook then yeah I
think the best way to go about the
magazines is probably to like share them
in the sense that like oh okay one
person does all the cooking one person
does this because otherwise I'm not
actually going to level
anything I have I have two skill points
in cooking already so I guess I'll cook
she's going to be all cooker let
me I have cor I'll drop so give give me
your I will the chest the chest Camp to
come with me I'm
looking no
points how
window I'm going to the farm if anyone
wants to come to the farm with me uh
come to vc2 I'm going to get materials
if someone wants to come with me come to
V
nothing
okay am I supposed to be punching corn
do you
think and then you get it I can ask her
but they have like my axe is about to
die though I don't know how to repair it
okay can can you can I ask a question uh
can you make a another
vat if possible another one how many VCS
do we have maybe we have like three ah
they did not make another one huh let's
see if it's not enough I can ask
iFly okay I can ask myself don't worry
about it I'm so sorry no problem I I
seen
a oh my
God I'm it turns off I haven't read your
magazines oh really okay you can have
them back here I put them in this crate
here oh than you something that
anybody did they disappear afterwards
yeah they disappear afterwards here I
see thank
you wait you know what here wait
one sec whoops what didn't mean I'm
asking for more VC right now so we can
split
better we don't have enough VC so I'm
asking for another
one in the meantime I get materials I
think that's iron I believe
let me
check uh no what is this is that lead
what we need lead
for okay but bullets oh okay I mean it's
actually useful what about this one
this one is mainly Stone I
think okay that's Stone we need to find
iron I need to find some
iron and I'm exploring to find more
stuff around
yeah so this is iron no this is Stone to
I
think yeah better to find iron
ASAP venture
time
yay am I crouching oh
yeah I will scratch
I'm going to
vc3 and if someone someone would join
me
okay iron sometimes is in the ground oh
really day two yeah we have seven days
to die
title
Mansions what about this one still a
stone I think
so if you can find like iron
in the ground do tell
me
drop can I go the coton plant by
just yeah I can okay that saves me some
time I get there as much material as
possible like at the end of the day
I don't know the red is scen oh I see
okay walking
around on the map you can find IR am by
looking at the pizza Colors
oh
oh oh I see
two two red ones what is this
trash okay glue for some reason I think
we're going to need glue at some
point oh there you
go that's
iron
[Music]
yay let's go tatini
sweep it's got as much as possible
good job you guys I'm proud of you I
mean I'm proud of me proud of
me let's get all we
can it's not that much
anyway okay and there was more iron next
to me right should be like
around do you see it or I'm just blind
or maybe it's
gone okay there is another one
here craft iron axe
oh you guys actually
right iron ax harvesting tool
[Applause]
what wait sorry it's a bit confusing so
iron I need skills yeah how do I oh I
can buy
it
a spear master there animal
trucker
uh what
about oh oh I see here I see
you I Cann not unlock this yet how do I
do that
[Applause]
need a workbench first for the more
advanced item
okay I need to unlock work St oh my God
that's
complicated I need to find a magazine
okay oh come on
yeah it's raining not very good I'm
going back home going back
home is all good
so
mhm what is this oh wait uh so how do I
get the workbench
again you guys mentioned something
before ah do I have a do I have Toritos
magazine or something Journal maybe is
like an item I can just find around
or magazine
okay maybe I can find
it oh br
[Music]
a I took out my backpack
so yeah
maybe I'm going to maybe I need some
help it's going to be hard to oh hard to
take all okay thank you that's very
helpful yeah I'm going back home and I'm
going I'm going to join the VC later
this is because
like uh when you you when you when
you're not playing with anyone you're
not like you should not join the PC
otherwise it's
too
um okay
good I need to find the books
it's empty oh so we can also check
inside the house the the cars
interesting about this
one maybe someone already been here by
the way the Traer is here so we can
actually go to the
trade and get
something I could do that I'm going to
ask if someone wants to
come yes I need to find I don't I'm just
put find a de
carass Let's Travel toward the trader
and
then someone wants to come with me to
the trader oh we go oh I'm going there
right now
okay I'm at the home okay I come home
and we go together okay let's put
there are
doors I'm coming home I was a fire away
okay I found a town thank you it takes
two minutes can I just make a maze put
it all away and then we'll take what we
want yeah I don't know what to do
here no no no no no out the flesh we
need to cook the water Bamboozled
they'll be like why is there so I have
to find some iron if someone needs by
the way there you go
everyone will
be
I'll what's up with the doors what do we
need it for again
for I don't think
so stress crafting crafting Under
Pressure oh god oh we can plant
trees FL is for
[Music]
planting okay okay we'll do that is we
going go out without us I'm so close
yeah I'm so close to home I'm coming
okay let's just find some resources for
now done all right I see everyone to
split up oh this is a building block
okay
I okay find that house here we go what
are all these storage crates are they
all just like stuff that we can call our
own it's from probably yeah I think
everybody has their own little storage
crate for now I'm I just put the I put
food in one storage crate since we'll
all be like
hungry so hungry we are
starving do you want
to so
long seems like I can name it we have a
lot of rocks we can repair it if you
guys go near the farm please collect
more corn okay you find a
okay a pot yeah oh we
can how are you cooking without a pot ah
oh we can label the
crates let us know down you're I'm do
you want to go to uh V treat okay let's
do okay let's do
it
hello you're so big on my screen down
[Laughter]
where are you oh I'm I'm um I'm I'm in
the house right now oh okay so where are
you guys we're just outside the house
yeah just outside okay I'm
coming outside we should have enough
time so I know where is this oh there we
go
hello
know I'm
here I'm going to C the spear oh okay I
can also craft Spears if you need okay
let me where is the
spear Spears a stone spear Stone spear I
also have
okay fibers I give us 5 Seconds no take
your time to prepare don't worry I'm
making think we're now more
arrows
uhhuh in the meantime I'm going to put
your for
Miss oh I don't know oh there we
go okay mhm now we're ready okay give me
also one
second mhm
mhm
okay perfect on our map the way point
for the Traer and that way hopefully we
don't get lost okay I'm ready
I know what is the trader so the White
River citizen Trader yeah that
person okay let's go okay it's a little
far away so let's go let's
go it's good it might be the other way
though let's just let's just try our
best I think it's it's this way I I
think I saw him on the
map it should take a little while but
yeah I hope deer on the way that would
be helpful
too any sort of go there the stretch out
zombies and if it gets night I think
we're going to be okay but if it gets
late or it starts to rain we hide
somewhere be in trouble yeah yeah it's
not risk it if we notice any flesh let's
get flesh yeah oh yeah if you notice any
like cars to you know check or some
boxes yeah let's get every materials we
can
yeah oh yeah yeah also iron we're going
to need iron oh I I got a bunch of iron
earlier good
job yeah iron is
important let's keep on moving we're
going here oh don't worry don't worry
there is time there is
time so good we have to keep moving oh
there's a car over there let's go check
it out yeah oh there's a bunch of Co too
we can water yeah it's safe okay I don't
know if water is good
B wish should we there's a whole house
here actually
W there's nothing other
cars I wish we could just use a
car why
oh oh you found
something yeah we got something from we
got some flesh y yeah we got FL y awes
nice awesome okay we hear
some that sounds there a zombie don't
worry don't
worry just ignore it just ignore it come
here come here come here it yeah yeah
yeah ignore it come come with me it's
better to run away from zombies we have
faster down there yeah
better oh my gosh where'd you go where'd
you go I'm here I'm here I'm here you
ninja way yeah there you are okay there
you go there you it's good it's it's
good I think it was so L it look very
impressive though this oh wait there's
something cool here that take take it
take it yeah let's hit
it oh do you do you want to attack this
too oh I try now's see ball good stuff
we're getting good stuff I think pretty
shiny look it's
cool
oh yeah very
good we may need coal
later I need to find a magazine magazine
to to to learn never r magazine I'm
scared of drawing uh uh you are
wet wet
dogs do you shake us well when you wet
we're not really used to the water too
veryy so it's not really the
best can barely do a doggy
paddle a
yeah you're probably better suited for
the water that I no no no I don't like
water I don't let's stick to drinking
water then yeah don't be it's another
Farmhouse
corn
corn oh
bodies on the road is there any bodies
on the road bodies on the road oh oh oh
that looks like a
garbage garbage b b bones should be good
what about the garbage next to that is
that no that's is there are two more
cars here we can check it out is there
stuff in cars I never see stuff in cars
this
n Nation Forest
oh Nation Forest where go I'm here I'm
here SK with all I'm here I'm
here I'm getting my tin oh that was I'm
here I'm
here we thought we heard a
zombie no we found machete Parts maete
part and electrical
traps that's cool electrical
trops mushrooms Bo mushroom I found a
Rotting Flesh
ew is really helpful where are you oh
I'm I'm right there let me find you
again okay we got split up a little bit
I think and I'm scared a I come to you I
come to you okay let's take the
car yeah
search okay that's you pick up truck fu
fu pumpkin
seeds take it take it take it oh there
you are there's a gum there's a gum
there's a gum there's a gun I got a
rifle awesome and now now is with us we
got a rifle yeah let's
go oh you got a gun G I think it only
has two bullets though so I'm going to
oh my gosh I think I have some materials
for the
ammo let me che where you go I think D
likes to be oh maybe it's just us no
maybe it's just us we just lose of you
okay we get we get really fast I think
this is a FLH on the RO n oh yeah let's
get it FL oh if is garbage I do oh maybe
if it's garbage well if it's garbage
it's garbage it's so good oh it's
garbage yeah oh there's some Crush
sand
part we're saying it's
helpful we're pretty close to where we
need to go yeah we're very close let's
keep on going let's go we're very close
down there
I think that was that not
a okay okay let's go over the hill here
let me get
this I need this uh feather for feather
for for the
arrows oh I see we have a bunch of oh
yeah oh yeah we should craft an arrow
for you then a
[Music]
bowl I don't know what four but feathers
are cool I guess so oh my we still we're
good at going up them yeah let's go
oh we can see them maybe it's very close
it's very there's somebody on the road
oh yeah someone else is going to
okay my leg is
broken broke my leg a that's not good
there's some other Shiny Rock over there
m i want to get back I broke way like
only we had a car or something what what
is
this I need to practice a little bit of
medication one second am I
bleeding
uhoh not a good sign M I need to break
my leg maybe the tra will have something
for our
leg can we live at the Traders for a
little bit
[Music]
L okay one second uh we're going to go
on ahead a little bit here cuz I wored I
will die before I get here yeah it's not
really Happ right now
okay he kicks us out at night okay then
we better get in here my leg is broke a
your leg broke too broke like
oh yes made it
here
e okay you found the Traer we did he's
in the house here I'm coming don't
shovel let's
come may I I'm very slow because my my
leg is
broken oh he has jobs for us should we I
guess we should take them I don't know
my leg is so
broken can you fix my leg for me there
you go I'm not a dog if you break
it he's kind of St kind of me you still
have
money make up your mind or make your way
out I got some work what are you
standing there for don't you have fine
take a look
he's
worse okay so I got a quest did you got
a quest
too ah no not yet okay so if you took to
them you going to give you a quest and
we can do the quest together okay that
sounds good mhm let's get the quest the
quest special job the bird
supplies okay let's accept it maybe
supplies okay that sounds good you're
going to need a shovel he said he gave
us a shovel thing
before let's make the shovel oh you're
right he did
give okay shovel we're ready to go now
okay uh do you have a
shovel give us one okay good I'm going
to make it's raining outside though I
think oh yeah if it's raining it's more
dangerous so let's be careful let's just
close the door we could just close the
door
vending machine oh vending machine
vending machine has water oh my gosh
wait do we have money
no oh you cheap son of if we did that
would be good there so good so much
stuff
here
a I don't know how can I fix my
leg Yeah I I think we have to wait but I
I noticed it's an hour the 2 hours that
we have to wait right but it keeps on
going back up the more we use our leg
yeah
oh was that right
or okay should we try digging outside
his St yeah let's try to look around
oh try going outside and digging a
little bit over there but
fine of stamina keep on digging good try
it I unlocked something oh really yeah I
I think I
found like a magazine I think
oh
really yeah but it was like it was like
an item that got um I got to use it I
don't know if it's one per player though
you can try it to go to one of those
little houses here and see if you can
find it too
okay I see in a little houses here I
still have skill points it wasn't a
luggage it wasn't a um yellow luggage
M see a yellow Lo if you can find it
then it was one Perle here okay it was
in here I don't know if you can see bab
house I don't know this one this one but
if you cannot find if you cannot see it
then it was just one okay yeah maybe it
was just one then let's check out our
skill points and I'll walk thing oh it's
not raining anymore good
[Music]
okay let's
see
[Music]
skills I
like being able to be a doctor would be
a good
idea I would like to be able to
cook you know we both have broken legs
right now wait wait we should try it
fore fortitude I think is measure of
your physical resilience I don't have
this heing heing could be
good that oh oh for do you have any Glue
by I've never seen glue I I got blue
glue but it's on my is a is a home and
probably we can fix the legs if we use
the
glue I crafting something else we'll see
you
later yeah let's get the
cardio one second I want to see
Stu harvesting more crops that could be
good
too we want to we want to do clops right
coming fast
it's good is your light broken too it's
broken okay so I think we can what we
can do is we wait 2
hours without without sprinting or
jumping and it's going to heal a before
it wasn't healing like it heal a little
bit and then it get B again but now I
see it's only an hour and 37 minutes for
us maybe that's because we haven't been
running around as much yeah maybe you
shouldn't if you don't run around
it show heal but it takes a long
time I think we should get
cardio I wonder if this is two hours in
game I don't think so though the timer
is not going out a little while we have
two points still
available the Harvest oh my gosh two
hours in real life oh no oh 2 hours is 2
hours oh oh no
that's not
fair okay we can just go walk slowly
yeah take it
easy oh my it's going to take yeah I'm
watching our our animal tracker might be
good our bones and it does seem to
change with the real time passage on
that that's not
nice we need to make spings apparently
and to make spls we need
glue so if you can find
glue I like to kind of look around
together with da as we head back I
think should we we need to finish the
quest first what is the quest again so
it should be um can you see your on the
top of your screen there is like an
exclamation mark and it's yellow you
should go there okay
okay I'm trying
to
there's we digging there I don't know I
thought that I could find something here
but maybe
not okay I'm going to the yellow
exclamation mark it's not
exclamation do you see
it head to Rally
Point we don't see it on our map no oh
okay maybe 380 you got the quest right
we got the quest okay okay uh I don't
see it in my map then okay let me check
it out oh yeah um can you try to uh
press Tab and next to
what the cup there should be like a
quest mark which is an exclamation mark
can you click on it we have that yeah it
says objectives head to the rally point
it's in the map let's check the map
again maybe we're just really bad at
reading map which is
pretty I wonder if if we have different
quests what's the quest say it was a
what was it called H here it is oh it's
really far away
not it's it's
gray I don't know why it's gray my quest
is pretty close maybe it's different
Quest okay well let's head over there
then H I think it's the same Quest it's
the intro to
[Music]
something my quest is um how to really
point oh oh let's see is
that intro B yeah yeah the objective is
the head okay okay it's the same then
let's go together I'm going to pick you
up rain now it's raining we'll just have
to be careful maybe I come with you
don't worry yeah if we're together it
should be okay we
down I'm just right outside the Trader's
place oh I found some glue oh oh really
yeah but just one oh there you go can
you see me
yeah it's 5:5 in game
oh it is it is it's 5:20 now oh is it
getting dark it's going to get late soon
so we should have back or maybe he's
going to kick us out of this we
can so okay what we can do
is we can either go back let's go back
home we can come back in the daytime
let's go back home we can do that ins
time yeah let's go yeah I don't have
much stamina me neither so we go slow
let's
go let me let me do the CR Point okay
yeah let's go
okay one kilomet
away going to have to do our
best take your time maybe I have a
gun I wouldn't use
it not on
me I feel I did kind of think about got
the moment we got it
what oh when um when we arrive home uh
we're going to we're going to build some
splints for for us for both of us that
sounds good yeah okay is this the right
way yeah this is the way
yes no way we're really bad at Direction
I don't worry I'm bad at Direction
okay just be careful
here yeah falling was a mistake H
yeah set up the map but I think we can
do before night so be careful here yeah
go slowly be bad if we both
way
no no this a really beautiful house here
yeah
actually I think we should invade it or
something maybe someone
here
home that' be nice actually I'm going to
I'm going to write this on the on the
map on the map so I come back later YY
yeah I think it's a nice big home it
looks like there's a farm too it looks
well kept yeah yeah we should come back
later maybe right yeah well we're going
to have to finish that Quest off right
time if you set up your map then it'll
be easier and if we get separated from
now we still be able to make it oh don't
worry I can find you don't worry okay
okay it's 6:15 in game it's okay I don't
know is that our home no
no it's still pretty far away like 800 M
away
oh yeah it's going to take a little 22
22 is night time okay 22 night time
okay so we might be okay might not be
okay I like this car this car had the
gun in it yeah I think there's a lot of
good items to be had around here yeah
it's a lot to explore right if we can go
maybe in the morning right when it's
bright oh yeah we can go in the morning
to go complete the quest and in the
meantime we explore around right that's
a good idea job yeah we need to fix our
legs
first that first and then make sure that
we don't break
them yes
yes M's getting scared it's okay don't
worry don't worry M we we got this I
going to protect you I a bow I think my
leg is doing worse than yours a yeah we
get time you know okay worst case we can
okay we can kill each other and we're
going to fix the
the don't worry don't worry the zombie
ignore them okay ignore
them might just look walk with me you
got
this
okay
halfway
okay we get tired quickly to the
stamina go slowly it's okay oop
[Music]
if we cannot fix the leg we kill each
other at home and we revive that's a
good idea I don't want to drown
here no don't drown here take breath
before I go in the water
don't okay let's go
almost out of stamina uhoh uhoh
I'm okay this is it for me this is it
for me
can't breathe here no you can come here
come here okay okay good job water
dangerous it is that a box box box box
is there something here oh I found a
tape we can do
the a tape like a V yeah no like a duct
duct tape oh is that better than glue
yeah like now we can make the um stuff
your leg wait let me try to do it now
okay um what was the name again
uh one second no we're
watching okay oh I can make it no wait I
need do you have cloth
fragments oh yes cloth fragments oh we
did FR I can make I can make them yes
please okay one second it's I need like
four of them okay I have more than four
thank you do you want do you need
eight uh yes we can make
eight it's getting it's getting oh no
it's getting really dark oh no it's
raining okay Ling l s yeah they get time
take your time I'll get you the items
I'll drop them okay yes please Ro it I
dropped them thank you
okay let me do it now I can make those
and we can p ourselves
up W I thought you said it gets dark at
22:00 it is not even
20 okay I made one you take you take the
first one I'll take you get it okay can
you get it here we go okay use use
use
use yay you made
it nice okay I'm going to make one for
me too
oh no I need way more clo fragment it's
okay let's
go we have more we have more we have
more I you have more okay I need 10 more
10 more yeah 10 more okay okay one two
take a little bit of time but I'm making
them oh thank you good thing I picked up
all the cotton you know yeah I thought
it were come in handy thank you
[Music]
for we can make it back okay now we have
thank you so much going to drop it yes
thank you so much okay I'm making it
okay
yeah okay don't worry don't worry we go
home now
okay I'm good now yay let's go
home thank you so
much yeah okay now be
careful no more breaking
legs no break Papa let's go
SC we're very close we're going to be
home before night time okay and if you a
zombie don't worry you keep
running okay it's good with you have
stamina
it like thunder but not when there's
zombies and thunder
no we just need to find some food when
we go home
[Music]
yeah okay be careful here there's a
river stamina there's a river be careful
can you do that yeah I'm going to wait
until I have enough stamina to cross
okay take your time I wait for you okay
let's go M no no no no let's go let's go
m
SC with the
Thunder
179 okay just meet
it I'm happy that we finally fixed the
leg much better knew that it was in
there H
[Music]
right it's dangerous to swim in the
Thunder is it we're very close to home
I can't wait to make it through those
doors
down put away this what
is home s
home okay follow the road and we shall
ride home okay okay yeah you already
supp to get corn we didn't get corn but
we got a gun gun better than corn better
than
corn I got some flesh too we got a lot
of items yeah I can't remember why we
wanted the FLH anymore foring for
fing okay let's let's go back to the VC
with the other then okay and and
tomorrow we go explore more yeah good
and
then we back back hey welcome
back has home been
good home has never been
better we almost didn't make it
back let's C the eggs cook the egg we
don't have our egg
cook oh yeah do we have a cooking po no
it seems like I do oh
yeah nice and I have gas can
too treasure honey yeah we got a gun too
yeah okay let's put it all in there have
some Marky
water oh I guess we need can we boil
that the mky water maybe maybe we should
boil that yeah yeah do we have any mky
water
oh what about that what about that what
about that what's this no water water
yeah should we drink that we're
thirsty we have
water K can you do you know how to cook
the spoiled meat
spoiled spoiled flesh um if it's spoiled
it's probably not a good idea hello
rotten rotten flesh Maybe not maybe
maybe not I don't think so FL can only
be used for farming maybe oh farming
okay okay yeah makes sense looking for
it I
put what should I
do I have an N too I found
somewhere cors those are seeds oh it's
[Music]
okay okay I'll just put it
right
here can't make it yet can't make
it that's we wanted to F the
C okay I'm going to they can bam oh we
need to swe the S and farming
[Music]
magazine disappointment sick how do I
find the magazine why is there dubstep
okay
what's going on
there need tra powder can I find
magazine mailboxes okay um I think it's
dark now it made it on yeah it's night
time now why I got to keep
dying I hear hising I hear
hising I hear zombies here are they
outside the
door hey can you guys boil some water
um yeah maybe not right
now are you
okay no not yet but hopefully
soones it's okay don't worry I need the
door break out the door
no
uhoh a
darn uhoh well I go find them well too
late you can't just give
up oh that's probably not a good
idea oh
goder it's not it's not everybody they
need to be here to protect us I
[Music]
miss be
feasting
uhoh okay my backpack spawn on my
bed let's do on my
bed my bed oh maybe I shouldn't have
spawned on my bed
oh
God the
weapon doesn't look
good I uh I
I I um I would help but I don't have
anything it's okay
the and they are here yeah we have the
upper ground yes we have to call B pop
Advantage oh no use the spear not the
axe oh god oh no there's a
spear thear okay I think outside is
safer
now f bage
oh my
God maybe a knife would be
good oh yeah I have a
knife oh much better much better oh my
God that's not
good oh no everybody there you go come
on that's all part of the process
yeah home sweet home eyes no one can
stop me you want to come and join us in
the bunk
B
the that's not
good I can't see where I'm going oh
it's very I think this is upstairs why
did zom go away
whoa not
really dying is so much
better
yeah I feel like where is everybody else
they should have
been protecting the house you know night
time let's go the
[Music]
loser here we are the
be let Go's
go hey protecting the
home of the
bunk oh what the heck
I'm just want to cook my heads leave me
[Music]
alone not here yet I have can I
eat oh I
can't
maybe I want
my I do like it HP bunk combo yeah other
people
yeah level
two let's spend this skill points while
everybody else
is oh it's pretty bad uhoh can it build
a door o let's build the door take stick
the door oh okay maybe I made the door
we have no sticks where did the sticks
go oh I think I car them what this do I
don't know how to oh it's a
okay oh oh I can also T like that that's
cool right cck oh oh oh oh is friendly
fire on can you attack me yes yeah ow
okay thank you you want to die oh I'm
dying a
[Music]
actually no this is a good idea ra come
back here I'm
coming can you kill me of course my
pleasure kill me ah wait
yes double door oh we don't need a
double door just a wood door
sorry no thank
you that way I can be completely cured I
did that say I'm pleasing the
door that's
okay do work all right there we go I
don't know if that's the right kind of
door oh I need to repair
my
axe that's kind of effective right click
with the axe
on why
click just need one more
oh let's break the
door I fixed it
get what are we doing
here yes what what are you doing I'm
breaking this door oh cuz it's kind of a
funny door because I misplaced
[Music]
it what do
I there you go I can't get in the house
now I help out
that finally yeah okay good job making a
new door look at that so cool y the
other door maybe we should try to make
like let me Che that is
like
is better that
door everywhere
I want to fix everything now can I fix
the
window
yummy we have coffee seed so the fact
that we have a coffee maker means that
there's a possibility coffee could be
consumed at some
point maybe I should
just chill out for a
bit well maybe I I okay yeah wait this
was my
bed yeah this is my
bed put
a I know that I'm infected but um oh
you're infected you want me to kill you
oh no no no no I'm okay for now are you
sure
yeah it's okay you can just ask I can
kill you oh do you want to do you want
to kill me K I'm
okay but if you if that's your only
desire in your life I can make it I
don't have any
desires well in that case I'll keep my
life for now okay let me know when you
don't want to live
anymore
okay I'll tell you when my time
comes okay that's
[Laughter]
good let me just take some of my stuff I
got boiled eggs
yummy oh it sounds bad yeah I think we
should probably get the door going M
what door the door that you just ruined
because I wanted to put a door on our
room yeah I don't think we can can you
just put it WR you sure yeah I told you
to spin it around you didn't spin it
around day yet I'm not sure you can no
it's still not make a door you made a
door okay good good
good have no points available no no now
it's wrong it was good for a second yeah
yeah yeah there you go that's a good oh
B's dead
oh well it happens I guess everybody has
their moment
see and now we're even more protective
yeah do let's put it more doors other
plac then like a door over there you
know lots of hiding spots
doors got x a door there too there's a
lot of doors that we didn't even know
about ah this is this could be repaired
door dark how do I make it brighter in
here wow it's so dark at night we had a
[Applause]
turn on turn
on what
[Music]
about weapon oh there you go I
can much
better I'm trying to level up my I don't
understand how that works
[Music]
let's um which one's stronger a
sledgehammer or a
spear Hammer spear has distance the
sledgehammer with the big one
has I need to use those
skills I want the
skill I see
you're
must yeah I want to get better spear C
the
[Music]
magazine what why am
I breaking things faster oh SL is very
good
then I feel
like oh
oh I'm good now okay I'm
you it's horrible outside it's raining
too upstair should we the brawler oo do
we
have oh you got to punch for
more let's fix the
why is everyone dying I don't know maybe
they're fighting
[Music]
something kind of want to go to the snow
area
but there's a castle there yeah there's
a castle
there yeah maybe it would be a good
place to take over but I'm not sure if
it's worth it a I see
well maybe this is
where I go to bed for tonight and we'll
see you all tomorrow
tomorrow we're for now oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I
hopefully I
hopefully everything look so
cute oh
yay
night good
luck K Senai if you want to go to the
castle we can go together apparently
that one's really difficult oh yeah well
we can go later in a few days when well
let's go
explore somewhere else of course let me
just I'm not sure where but like we can
go to have you been to the
trader have you been to the trader I've
been to the trader oh yeah I've been to
the trader I was I still have to do my
quest but oh okay we can go to the
trader then sweet let's go okay okay uh
it's close yeah yeah yeah yeah and then
we can probably explore from there yeah
where you at I am at home I'm in my
room I it's time to get up okay oh what
a coincidence I I have all my stuff
there
too yeah yeah see this is my corner oh
really yeah we share the room together
it's weird W you're nice
what where is your bed you don't have a
bed huh you don't have a
bed I have a bed I'm carrying it with me
because wherever I'm going I'm already
home oh that's smart yeah no it's not
smart if you die you just die
it's okay okay I'm coming I'm just going
to bring with me some glue because last
time I
needed and okay okay I don't think I
need anything okay let's go let's go
let's go let's
go where is okay I'm outside let me can
I make a party with you my bed cuz
they're all already taken okay you
silly anyway party yes let's go party
yeah party uh can I'm going to make a
party with you I'm not quite sure maybe
you have took steps or something
ah I see I have no idea how the party
system works okay never mind no no no no
I got it I I think I got it this oh CR
left the party you left the party now
what yeah wait let me do that but I
sent but I sent it to
you
weird I don't
[Music]
know uh k
please do me a favor yes kill me before
we start what why because I have low
HP okay
bye see you soon see
you it is what it
is come on let me respond okay I respond
with my bed
yeah I'm ready to go do you need to
die oh no I'm good I'm at full health
let me know okay let's go uh
store is over no store is this way okay
I'm coming wait no store is not that way
sorry uh store is is this way this way
this way Trader yeah Trader we're going
to the trader right yeah we're going to
the trader tra I mean yeah I need to do
that quest which is very close to the
tra okay let's go let's
go yay very nice very is so apparently
you have to leave the party and then I
invite you okay let me just do it how do
that
party
uh uh
I don't get
it so Tab and then uh
players and then there's like
um party thing yeah oh leave okay I did
it I did it yeah woo
woo yeah let's go y woo that's what I'm
talking abouto
nice I got to be the players here I got
a
knife yeah bone knife very good it's
very
fast yeah it seems like the durability
isn't that good though yeah but I think
it's pretty easy to craft so not too bad
you need like five
[Music]
bone yeah I don't know where to find all
that though like I think I got by
killing a
zombie
ew
[Music]
e why are you out of
stamina we're
live I'm I running we're still so full
of life there's nothing for you to run
out of stamina for I like I like the way
you think about it yeah I like your
mindset
exactly wow you like the way I think
yeah wow not a lot of people tell me
that thank
you yeah it's nice
wow you think I think positively or
something I think you're very positive
person that's actually crazy wow I don't
even know where you got that idea
whoa oh wait there's a house here oh
wait where are you I'm going to come to
you
now oh this this
place ah you're pretty far from
me oh no oh there you are Oh no you're
not far from me oh there you go thought
you were on the opposite side oh this is
iron oh take it take
it we can share sharing is scaring Cony
yeah
yeah oh my God we're going to make so
many great things with this wait uh oh
yeah this is no this is lead this is not
iron oh well we're going to make so many
great things with this regardless do you
can use um you can craft armos with it
so still good what the
heck oh yay okay now let's go kill some
stuff yeah I'm looking around to see if
there's something we can can steal from
this
place no
nothing oh that was dead nice Rusty oh
oh
no everything is go probably someone
already been here oh everything's
already looted n no so
sad they're so selfish they took
everything for themselves
I know sharing is caring and they did
that yeah what's wrong with
them it's messed up it's messed
up yeah okay we're very CL we're going
to go
back taking a bath in this
weather it's
beautiful it's like the little things in
life you this apocalypse you do you like
going to the Sea and have a bath no I
hate it me too
I oh good yeah you know I like looking
at the ocean I think it's pretty but I
don't want to be in it you know no same
I don't get people enjoying the bath
yeah cuz your skin gets kind of dry and
like it feels kind of
icky yeah and like you don't know what
happens
there true
true
like yeah um I was talking to my friend
um oh wait yeah I was talking to my
friend and was like oh you know maybe
Hawaii would be really nice to go cuz
um you know we were just talking about
vacation spot since uh uh Kiara pitched
the idea before and I was like oh Hawaii
maybe Hawaii and then my friend was like
yeah there are sharks
around really yeah I don't think sharks
can I mean sharks are not that dangerous
as they yeah they're really not that
dangerous but you know just uh just her
suggesting that that's a possibility I
oh yeah yeah what is not exciting what
is your favorite vacation spot or like
your ideal
vacation oh I found my bed o oh your
bad yeah I can do anything in my bed
that is pretty true as suppose yeah like
you know if you get really lazy you can
probably I don't know door Dash or
something and then you can you know play
games in bed
uhhuh oh my God there's a snake oh my
God
ew everything kills me here ew okay it's
oh it's dead it's dead I'm going to lose
the snake yeah I got something I got
leather and meat yeah meat not
bad nice nice look at us go that's cool
oh I got water too but it's dirty water
yeah but I mean that's still something
why was there
one uh because I found a body do you
want some bones by the way I have some
maybe you can craft o can I just have
one yeah uh I don't know how to I I I
gave you all of them that that's way too
many give me give me the the ones that
you need back sorry once you use them
give it back to me oh okay uh I don't
know how to split
them you
know that's
uh okay uh how many did you give me
again
okay okay here you go thank you thank
you bless
of the quest is very
close it's find the bir the bird
supplies oh so I have to use the sh
wait where'd you go here where's here uh
wait I come I come to you no you're
running away no no no here behind you
there oh okay
okay there you
go okay let me start de CL
oh okay what is this
I need to use my sh oh you're
terraforming wow yeah that's the quest I
have you dug in a square
hole Yeah I'm very precise I like to do
square
holes wow so
specific
oh I need to dig around to find supplies
of
probably it may take a
while this is my
hole well don't
move you can you can't see there the
entire game it's fine the entire game
like this yeah yeah what is CR in their
hole maybe I can make it bigger
really no this is already quite spacious
oh but you cannot even lay down what
about your
bed no I like I like sleeping like
this feels like I'm in
space okay oh I found it no I found no I
didn't find it oh my
gosh am I doing the right thing I don't
even know
oh it takes a while
are you sure this is a place yeah it's
like a big yellow circle around this
[Music]
area let me
see not
yet do you want to help
me what if I steal your achievement
though is the thing a I think I it's
like a
loot or is it chair I think that is like
a chest or something because it
says it says
oh yeah find the
supplies we got to dig
deeper thank
you
yeah dream
team this kind of
therapeutic oh I found it no oh what
it's here you're getting closer to the
treasure says yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh I found
it I got Sandwich Water flashh and
waterer
supplies
W oh okay not bad that's pretty good
let's go now we go back to the
Traer yeah let's
go there are zombies around Let's ignore
them
yeah are you sure that food isn't
expired or anything the
food is rotten so we cannot eat it
unfortunately but but I have some meat I
have like six row meat if you hey that's
something yeah and then we can cook him
later
yummy yum
yummer okay we go this
way I want some we kill him no now I
just want a steak Yeah you can kill him
no don't don't kill the trader no don't
kill the trader we need it put away your
congratulations here's your reward oh I
can get pistol bundle R rifle bundle
machine gun bundle button bundle shotgun
button
bundle what should I
get I don't know I think I'll
peek shotgun is cool
I mean a shotgun would be
nice but like where would you get ammo
is a thing you craft that
oh oh granny do you want do you take the
do you take more jobs from this guy or
you just
like oh that's my second
time oh what is your quest now my quest
is just whatever goes name's not
important it's a deal disappoint me and
you'll find yourself on the wrong end oh
now I find the buried supplies okay okay
we can we can make it it gives you a lot
of stuff like OS and my my quest gave me
a shotgun so we shall make yours
too yay thank you
mm that thing is really rude yeah who do
you think you are he keeps swearing at
me oh yeah he's a little rude that's
fine kind of want to kill him no no no
we need them it's the only human here
gives us
stuff
okay all right where is this at tracking
Quest where do you see your quest
actually uh I think now mine is
different so
oh where do you see it okay let me
check
so
429 M away which
is how do you find
it let me
check oh yeah I see it there's like a
little exclamation mark on the map do
you see it ah I see oh intro buried
supplies and tier one buried supplies
yeah I have the tier want bird
supplies okay I guess um I follow you
and then I don't know if it's the same
place so let's go yours and then we go
mine oh thank
you okay uh we going to farm these yeah
get a
lot does it yeah like the shotgun is
pretty good for zombies and everything
uhhuh
so it's uh more beneficial for you to
complete the quest yeah I think at the
beginning is very good to complete the
quests because we got materials that
usually
cannot
ah by just crafting also we need to find
a magazine uh to probably unlock more
stuff for the shotgun oh yeah that um
you have to loot the houses more
yeah I think I'll will go
later
yeah okay don't don't do that yeah yeah
okay I help oh thank you
yay it's quite it's quite relaxing it's
like power
later just I love power wash I'm really
excited for the new update actually oh I
never I never I never tried it but I you
never tried it oh my God okay so I've so
the thing is I always watch people
streaming it because it's so relaxing
for me to watch but I never actually
streamed it so maybe I'll give it a try
maybe yeah like it's really nice it's
like a good like zatu kind
of oh man I'm out of stamina oh
yeah I'll
try
yay I love those kind of
games I love like no thoughts head empty
kind of games they're my
favorite yeah yeah yeah like you don't
have to think about anything it's just
therapy
yeah you know what I mean I don't like
games where like there are too much
stuff to think about yeah yeah you got
to think to too much it's like man are
made for relax not for stressing
out you know you would
think you you would think yeah but for
some reason I play a lot of games that
are
suffering
yeah I I bet you do
anyway what do you mean I bet you do
like you you you you you play games that
you need to suffer even though you
prefer games
that they have brain
empty
yeah for some reason I the heck I play
horror games when I don't like horror
games is the
same do you get scared of it though I
hate it yeah really yeah
dang it's kind of kind of bold
do you like horror
games I don't but like it's October so I
should probably play a
bit oh my God what is your
supply apparently it's oh sorry oh you
found it I found it
nice
okay what oh There's a Zombie behind you
have a neighbor okay it's okay don't
care about him let's go let's go yeah
it's a waste of our durability let go
let's go to mine as well so we go back
to the Trad oh yeah yeah yeah yeah uh
let's see it's right
there pretty close oh wait
this yeah let's
go
okay wait what
what what why is it not tracking track
track um okay oh it's tracking okay is
it the same position as mine I hope so I
I hope
so well make
sense
yeah oh okay maybe we are going the same
direction
probably oh be careful here don't break
a leg please or break a leg you know
break a leg I'll not breaking your leg
don't break your
legs
funny I am pretty funny I am very funny
actually don't say
that don't actually say that oh okay
sorry you un funny you you're very thank
you yeah yeah I'm like one of the more
funny and unfunny people that I have met
in my life yeah I got
you do you really get me
though
no okay it's here okay same position
okay okay good oh hungry
again it's okay if you hungry kill you
so you the hanger the oh thank
you I'll just like put down a bed oh
wait you don't have your bed never mind
I can craft
one oh yeah actually that's right but
you can also spawn next to your bag
but I mean I can but I don't know if
it's going to be good for
you you don't have a place why is it so
Square too many question question for me
too many
questions well if I don't question
things how would people
know they don't
know I'm thiry is a
bless
oh that's also one of my favorite things
one of my favorite quotes ignorance is
bliss sometimes you don't question
things and something sketchy is going on
you turn a blind eye yeah yeah
yeah I don't want to
know sometime you too much is worst it
is it is you have to like stay in your
lane otherwise like they're going to get
you like something's going to bite you
back and it's like oh you know things
could have been normal things could have
been better if I just didn't know
anything kind of thing you know oh yeah
it's like yeah it's like when you eat
something it's yummy and then you don't
want to know what how they made
it yeah or like it has way too many
calories or something yeah yeah like I'm
not looking at
this wait getting closer to treasure you
getting closer oh it's over there then
maybe I don't
know man why do I have to be so hungry
oh God get away
ow
oh y
[Music]
[Applause]
die
ew die stay down it
y yay
woo
nice what do you get out of it uh
something time you get F rotten flesh or
I think I got some bones out of it but
I'm not I'm not quite sure I may be
wrong oh H there there is people here
oh
hello my stamina man yeah I need to
drink water but I don't actually have
clean water yeah I don't I don't have
normal water it's just murky and that's
going to make me sick when did I have so
much okay
whatever can I do something with this
many
clay what is this treasure oh my God I
don't know man taking
forever I'm out of stamina
now h
open oh I have a pipe shotgun and ammo
cool I opened the box right
now hey
nice there was a box so like when you
deliver the quest to the Traer they give
you a box with the gun
ah okay you get to see in a
moment my stamina is where the heck is
it
man do I have any food with me can I eat
Ro meat
no I mean you can but it's better to
cook it I mean better than probably get
sick you here
oh oh good job oh my God no no no not
yet not yet not oh I I'm clipping
through wait I'm going to kill those
zombies okay hold on I will
help no
[Applause]
problem why are so many zombies I don't
know
ow oh my God I'm dealing with two
zombies here
hey well I'm dying I'm also dying I'm
dead you're dead
yes
ew stop eating
me ow dude I can't even kill one zombie
come on
why are they so
rough is
this I'm getting my backpack again and
help
you right really yeah yeah I come to you
now so I get to help you a bit there you
go
nice yay
what oh it's still alive yeah it's still
alive let's
go oh
they're they're coming this
way H there's there's more behind you no
worries
uh did you craft do you have a
spear yeah I think a spear might be
better yeah I'm using the
spear nice
okay I use both oh I need to
repair oh boy
[Music]
yay oh she got
ammo what yeah some jumbies they drop
items woo oh that's
[Music]
good okay okay now they
dead nothing
okay oh it was my arrow oh never mind
then oh it was my
arrow never mind okay where were
we uh here oh wow we went
far wait I don't see the exclamation
mark
anymore yeah I don't see it where'd it
go did we lose it I oh not
it says we
failed we
failed
oh no wait we
yeah never mind let's go to the trader
let's wait can we redo it or no maybe
maybe if we talk to the trader we can
redo it
a man
oh because because I died it
failed I mean there were way too many
zombies as the thing so or maybe there
is like a time
limit
maybe I
mean because is it asks you like when do
you want to start the
quest but it's okay I
mean
like we can do another too many yeah I
mean there are too many zombies man like
I don't know yeah like either way pretty
sure one of us would have died
anyway uh
yeah oh is that iron yeah that's iron e
I'll help good job oh I have coffee
means this I need more space in my
inventory
I'm G throw this
out man I get so tired I'm so tired all
the
time oh so someone says the treasure
hunting Quest spawn zombies as you de so
that's to be expected appar
uhuh yay nice
why'd you drop the cloth fragments oh
yeah because I didn't got enough space
home uh in the
inventory yeah I had to drop
something what give me a better Quest
now Trader or CR is going to kill you
I mean can you actually kill him no I
cold but it's an
NPC
a at least wipe that off your boots
before you come into my shop
oh apparently the quest disappeared too
so we cannot repeat it that's not fair
what
that's man this guy I think we should
kill
him I hate this
guy
well I think we need to kill this guy
apparently you can also like get the
same Quest on all day so maybe if we go
back tomorrow we can find the same quest
ah so it it resets over time but in the
meantime which one what do you want to
get like now I have here zombies Fetch
and fetch I don't know what fetch means
exactly
um well like before you accept or well
like go to the quest area can you kill
me later after I hand over this quest of
course thank you you should you should
oh yeah yeah I think oh no yeah I'm okay
I can kill you my pleasure sure thank
you well like they're all busy talking
so going to have to
wait him
anyway really
yeah just need to find the right spot
it's a little
buggy ah
shotgun ooh
rifle oo
cornmeal I don't know if I should get a
shotgun or a rifle
M I can show you the shotgun and you
tell me if you like
it I'm equipping
now so this is the
shotgun
yeah it looks pretty
good it's more it's a more
worry okay let's get this one then okay
do you have any
jobs buried
supplies oh wait there is a buried
supplies Quest oh really yeah I don't
think I have I have just cleared
zombies fetch clear zombies
fetch oh a
which one which one do you want to do
then clear zombies or
fetch we can do clear we can do fat I
don't know what it is though
okay we can
try or
oh that's kind of unall for you got it
oh no no no she she was just
being really rude
okay so what what if we do try clear
Z okay it's the closest one it's like
500 M away I'm going to make you an
offer you can't refuse okay well good
luck by the looks of it you're going to
need it do you guys doing a fet quest oh
we're
doing we're
doing oh wait wait zombie wait first
wait zombies zombie first
then you want not Jo
not oh
wait okay um so when you die yeah are
you able to spawn near your backpack or
something yeah yeah yeah oh okay sick
okay I don't have to put out a bed okay
okay nice
is eliminated
crony
sick I hope this doesn't fail the
mission or anything n no if you have not
started it doesn't
fa okay
sick
okay wait can we accept like a more than
one Quest at a time so we can go with
Mor maybe let me check uh maybe oh yeah
no no no we can't oh we can't oh we
can't okay never
mind
okay
uh
where
are
my wait hold on what huh what am I
wearing armor oh yeah I am yeah when you
get the things from the okay sick all
right let's go yeah oh one second let me
just um oh wait wa wait K's coming with
us right no Kell's doing the fet quest
right now and we cannot accept multiple
questions in
time okay
so oh
wait oh
this hey okay this one
[Applause]
uh 400 m
away I don't know what it is let's
see uh oh there you go I see
it it's over there let's
go I'm going to the question mark h I
shouldn't have jumped too much I'm just
I'm so used to
it take your
time you can have multiple quests but
you can help with the quest oh can we
have any
way wait there's a level system in this
game I don't know that yeah like
apparently I still have to understand
better but there are also skills skill
SKS um tree that you can
improve and you can upgrade so like if
you press Tab and you go to the you know
the little guy with the graduation hat
yeah yeah there's like this kind of
skills tree and point system ah yeah
yeah and I still have to understand what
it is so right now I'm upgrading the
spare and oh yeah yeah yeah perks but I
don't actually that would be a good
idea I do I have two skills points so I
should probably use
[Applause]
somewhere where's your
go what where'd you go me oh yeah oh
okay there you you were on the top of
me why is are you jumping
yeah oh okay
okay okay I don't question
it are you ready yeah
[Applause]
okay oh I I got a skill that allows me
to see
animals oh yeah I did that too pretty
cool I know but I haven't found any use
for for yeah oh
really
well let's
go yay when you
crouch yeah but it usually just says oh
no
tracks I to be fair I haven't seen any
animals around so oh is there no should
we this house
yeah let's
cool it's a very pretty home oh wait G's
G's lives here oh really
yeah oh that's
cool uh I guess there's nothing to loot
then yeah maybe she miss
something no I don't think so
okay yeah no I don't think there's
anything around here
no yep it's clean what if I steal her
stuff you
can yeah you can I
mean let's see
yep empty empty empty empty
empty are you in the house or no I left
okay yeah yeah okay okay there you are
okay yeah let's go yippe
Yi I can't wait to shoot with my
shotgun PE pew pew
die
[Laughter]
murder oh CH house there's a chicken
there's a
chicken come here
oh my God come
here yes I got my first chicken wow
hey
congratulations
man oh my God
give a lot of meat I got 11 no six meat
waa hey y let's
go are you Looting the
house uh yeah but but uh there's a place
where we can start the quest oh yeah
yeah yeah you want to
start yeah it's here it
says I don't know how to start e Oh
e okay so we need to clear the
area how do we clear the area I guess
what the zombies are going to arrive and
um I guess we need to kill the Zombies
on is
it oh no
uh let me just check the
quest head to mushroom mining company
and clear as the zombies this location
could be useful to our oh clear the
house oh so we have to ENT the house
okay okay
oh I hear him
yeah yeah yeah maybe it's in the
basement oh yeah it's right here oh
hello
oh oh my God this weapon is so
low
E wa this thing was not
die okay it's done that takes so
long okay they sh the super
nice okay should I shoot
it oh never don't waste it don't waste
it okay okay let me like find it there
you go
there more
here
upstairs yeah there's more
up e get out of
here
okay fast
dang oh Char be careful this is one is
fast
oh it's not dead never
mind why is it doing a ballet I don't
know
yay yay it's so impossible to kill him
they're so durable oh all
right is locked let's go here
bathroom I found M de water
e yum no yum
yum let's
see
food oh wait never mind
I need this no think so not I thought we
cleared the area what what else is
there uh I don't think so
because there is another door come here
come here on the
kitchen oh come here up up up
oh what
yay oh my God there's so
[Music]
resistance whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa what what got to no bro I can't
move bro you
so it blocked me
you
died
no does it say it
fail not to
me no I think I did
it okay that's good do it says it fa to
you yeah it probably failed for me but I
don't want to spawn and then ruin your
quest potentially so no no no it's done
for me so you can
spawn what if I spawn back and then it
it suddenly fails for you no it's fine
don't worry okay
okay okay so I'm going oh I found some
cool items some nice loot
here so my
bag
um my
bag do
I
[Music]
and what else what why is it locked oh
oh yeah
basement oh
what
what what what what what H you
okay
oh yeah I'm good okay oh oh first a
bandage okay what's the point I'm going
to die anyway oh I found a medical
journal cool oh nice you can read it
[Music]
why is the music ominous oh my
God okay wait where' my bag go wait you
don't have your bag yeah it's gone wait
is it on the other side no wait what
where is
it you died here though do you can you
see the the the bag
on on your on your map oh it's floating
oh
okay okay well that's
okay okay so I actually already looted
here and I found uh a head
mod I don't know what we head mod it's
called wait to head mod I don't know
what it is and then I can show you I'm
going to drop it for you so you get to
see it
and then I found a pip
button oh hey that's really a good
weapon and then I found some medical
first aid bandage
oo you
go is that
could be like a head gear that you can
use way it's night so maybe we should
either wait or we can yeah we should
probably wait
wait we can also you know what we can do
with this house because it's pretty
close to the no it's not close to the
Traer but like we can probably craft
something and here to go
down know if that's a good idea we could
use this as a second base maybe could
now that we secured it and the doors are
locked
so yeah it's like pretty secure for now
let's see oh there are more loots here
more oh oh sick there is a Dye
thingy oh yeah yeah
yeah and
Bones oh food
yay yeah let's loot
everything what is the
sound
Ambience oh
sorry okay let's yeah let's check the
skill
points and see what do we are I have no
skill points available
dang this place is pretty nice
yeah it's pretty big too maybe I should
have this place as a
base this seems
nice I'll have it in the
Attic
okay why the music got to be so ominous
though I don't know it's quite
suu uh
athletic bir
oh also I wonder I don't know how you
can um up uh like get more points for
the skills honestly it's quite weird
maybe should we should kill more zombies
but I don't really get it I don't know
[Music]
here
oh okay I guess it needs more
space
[Applause]
um okay so XP from kills or building and
crafting oh okay okay so it's actually
pretty good it's pretty convenient to
craft and good
stuff okay let's do it
I guess technically this can be the
inventory spot so don't need to
necessarily destroy it oh yeah by the
way we have to do a land claim block so
I'm going to make it now so we can claim
this land Oh
yay the music is still
on I place it here
damn it
yay yay it's ours now
woo let me see what I can
craft surely I can put it here
[Applause]
I don't want to place it in the middle
of nowhere
though
[Music]
[Applause]
oh fine going to make some
chest what did you position the
chests um I'm just using like the one
that I already have at the top do you
want to have your stuff here too in the
Attic it's
safer where here upstairs oh
upstairs
okay uh empty oh I'm going to put
everything
here
yeah we can just share it
how do we upgrade the the trap
doors oh we need to close the
door yeah W hatch oh it's not that
secure it's a very nice
spot yeah it's
peaceful what is Rec call oh this
medical I
think oh you need iron I have iron oh
you have iron too I thought I had iron
too I have iron here I put it here oh
yeah right click with a hammer I don't
have a hammer guys let me check what are
you there's an axe
[Music]
H oh I can craft I can craft a
hammer I craft ah reinforc yeah okay I
reinforced the door good
job
yay wait do you have extra wood by any
chance I do can can i b
some yeah of course I have quite a
few that's
cool and to make a Hummer
is it outside yeah yeah yeah
that's
oh there a lot of things around we can
kill them as well and get some exp later
like if we die
here nothing happens true actually I'm
going to place a bed
as yeah o we should have like a cooking
pot here too we can like totally have
some stuff going around do you need
something for the cooking po I don't
think I can
C okay
okay it's still
struggling oh this is kind of difficult
um you can maybe put it on the other
side here um can you help me destroy
this thing yeah yeah doesn't make
me use a shovel on this there you go uh
shovel oh yeah you're
right what happened yeah and then you
might be able to place your stuff in the
in the middle oh I did the bed here I
put theed here oh nice
okay does this
do oh yeah kind
of wait did it climb up no no no no okay
I just heard something struggling can
climb
right this a really nice spot yeah I
like it I like it it's pretty safe
too okay
sick all right let me put some of my
stuff here
too
uh building
blocks this this do you have anyal anyal
F animal fat I don't I don't even know
what that
is
this yo this is oh I can kind of
peaceful yeah I can probably make a
parts let me make
oh I think it's trying to come
in hold
[Music]
on
yay y
Yay good free
exp
yay okay and then where were we um
Iron oh I
need where I did I use up all the iron
no no no I took it I was trying to get
the I I can put it back one second oh
okay okay can you I canot interact with
the
okay I put it back and I was trying to
do the cooking pot but apparently cannot
oh why I don't know why uh maybe I need
a magazine to learn the
recipe or do you need a
campfire
oh I maybe you need a campfire first
hold on let me like small Stone I made
one oh you made one yeah I'm going to
position now
is this saf to position here should
be yeah put it
here
go oh this so cozy
man uh
oh need the cooking pot now
uh let's see cooking
pot oh yeah we can boil water oh wait we
need cooking
pot oh how do we make cooking poie I
have like forged iron so I thought maybe
that
could do collector o do collector
pots let me try again pot oh cooking pot
okay there it is iron oh 31 iron and uh
six clay I we have oh oh no no no
doesn't mean me do it for some
reason wait can you give it to me yes I
I'll put it here back wait look it done
I wonder why it doesn't work hold on
what oh man them again don't worry I
take care of it no it's okay we'll worry
about it when they come
up oh we need a forge for this
oh
Forge I think it's
and hey where is my shotgun works
careful oh that's a light uh where's
work work station
work
work you good I am okay
you're you're kind of choked up man okay
I feel better
now why can't
I is it because my shovels
broken I mean my axe uh let's see I go
downstair I want to check the
situation okay you feel free to close
the
door okay PL
fibers and
wood oh there's also TV
cool the
couch oh it's so
cozy I'm going to put the camping T
back okay and then okay morning here oh
hey let's
go I'm mm
ammo H
yeah and
[Music]
sort yeah oh this is so nice Okay okay
okay oh we can also close
this what is this no cannot use
it there's a do you see any cooking
Parts no
Dar okay let's see let me reinforce
this there's a key next to the
door
[Music]
and yeah you're right I canot get
it and then
this did something happen no like I got
the
key oh I got a key of the door and I
could I could open it but no I don't
know how to put it
again
um I just take this and then coffee
beans I don't know what I'm going to do
with that and then
this I can probably just die honestly so
I'm just going to put everything
here his back my
let me check I can probably build
something around to
protect
yeah oh man this is so
cozy it's like home yeah it feels very
home I just want to the the cooking
partt so I can cook
too
yeah no we need a
door yeah I I I I'm crafting
doors
okay oh oh iron Cellar Door that's
cool can need do iron
door
yeah oh all the doors are broken I need
forging iron but okay I'm going to put
like wooden wooden doors anyway
here put it
here I have five forged iron oh really
yeah uh it's in the crate upstairs okay
I could get it now I'm going to position
this door first I need to break this one
oh how do you lock it uh so I think it's
either backed or
I want to break it
anyway
because bug
[Music]
it don't worry I'm going to put I'm
going to put more doors new
doors
oh oh
[Music]
cornmeal he there you go there we go
okay new
door I'll make a new door on this side
yeah except I put everything God damn
it it's difficult to
[Music]
position is he okay I'm don't
know it should be okay
okay oh yeah yeah it's okay it's okay at
least it's
locked okay kind of
works um I'm going to go make some iron
uh iron door
too
okay why is it pink
[Music]
cuz I'm up cats no not
[Applause]
you here oh God
no oh I need more forged iron how do you
make forged
iron uh you need a
forge and we don't have a forge
yet yeah
is that door already reinforced I don't
know we need more iron I I have the iron
I think let me oh if you right click you
can take half of the supplies a
sorry okay no thank you no thank you
okay there I can find it anymore I'm I
lost the iron do you see it in the
inventory
what iron
should
be I don't have
it do we use all oh no no I see I see
okay I need to unlock the workstation I
I'm going crazy I need
workstation wait oh this is already
improved oh it is already station I need
a magazine I
think oh we got to explore more more
then okay yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah let's go visit Traders can we
go back to the um uh Trader first yeah
yeah yeah let's go okay
[Music]
okay oh yeah go
magine magazine I need the works if I if
I unlock the workstation we have a lot
of things we can do yeah and like a
cooking po would be really good then we
don't have to kill each
other here's a
solution that's another house is this
looted
already I don't no you want to check
yeah oh wait I think I no no I think
this is where Gigi was oh oh is the same
one yeah I think so oh okay never
mind
yeah oh yeah yeah I recognize the with
the
track okay let's
go I hope the tra is going to give me
something nice this time the the the the
weapon was so helpful
though yeah the shotgun yeah yeah the
shotgun though like I feel like it
doesn't do that much damage no but at
least a long distance weapon
so oh my
stamina it's a relax
hey
hey okay this very close on to me
there's oh
oh here we are oh by the way you can
mark the wayo on the map just to let you
know so in case like you don't need to
you don't have to check them up all the
time oh yeah the Waypoint yeah you can
mark the Waypoint so you like find the
way pretty easily yeah yeah oh my God
is
that oh
it's hi cute guess I have to pay you now
that you did it okay rewards what do I
get Crafting skill magazine
bundle oh I want this
one tracting improves weapon
[Music]
handling grilled meat Chop Chop dumb
probably this one honestly
did you just call me damn
[Laughter]
some days I don't even know why I
open the
doors okay so I don't like you either
let's see what did they got which one
should we clear oh my God they got so
much so many so many um
magazine oh I got home cooking weekly
okay let me use
it and then I got I wonder if I can
share one with you because I have
two oh wait who I can share one with
you how do I abandon my
quest a what did you got what quest did
you
got I got I have tier one clear and tier
one fetch
okay let me check if they have any quest
for me they don't have any job for me
what
why did the list is empty maybe it's
back or
something it says I have no work at this
time
huh ah CR uh I have take this uh take
all of this hold on H why the magazine
because I have more I have extra oh no
no it's okay it's okay like if I finish
the quest I can I can get him so that's
all you because I already I already used
them I'm not going to do anything with
them yeah you can later nice stack
though no no no take it take it take
it it'll be useful in the future no I
already read
them you you read them
again it it Stacks oh it Stacks yeah
yeah yeah oh really I think so I don't
think so I I I thought it did no nothing
happened
really oh well I'll
try
okay oh yeah you can actually start yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah right
okay okay okay think you I didn't know I
thought it was
extra
[Applause]
yeah
nice nice okay uh let's see the quest I
have I just have oh no I have the F oh I
think because you got the
quest huh and we are in the group it
shows to me as
well oh maybe because I haven't accepted
the quest but I can still see on the
quest
list so I have tier one Fetch and tier
one
clear right
now nice
okay okay we can do the tier one
[Music]
fetch I
think sick let's
go hello there Travelers hello oh hello
hello are you classed in yeah yeah you
want to class together yeah heck yeah Co
let's go he says he doesn't have any any
quests right now though oh it's it's
says the same for me but then I joined
uh like in the crony's party it shows
the
quest in my list as well so maybe if we
make one
party oh we can share the quest I yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah let's do it okay I'm
going to invite you
then
cool
[Music]
uh and my
okay I sent
your
okay
um I have to leave the party first uh
can you invite me one more time of
course oh God it's so
expensive okay I'm in my I think you
have to leave your party as well to join
us leave it yeah yeah okay how do you
leave uh so click on the party icon and
try to click on leave
okay oh no I'm not in a party right now
oh let me TR invite
again
yeah I got I got a quest just now as
well oh yeah Quest started yeah Quest
started okay okay I see them now
[Music]
mhm yeah if you click on your quest list
you're going to see like everyone's
Quest
okay why won't he let me see his
inventory are you glitched again I don't
know what's going on that's fine let's
make more money together and then maybe
I'll try and buy something okay yeah we
got about 30 minutes after all so let's
do something hi gather okay
okay how about I empty ladies ladies
let's
goo go this
way is this a clear Mission we're going
to kill
zombies heck
yeah let's go oh yeah I finally found a
cooking grill so I can make grilled corn
what is this like Tik Tock boom
effect I don't know what you're talking
about you hear something strange
wait uh my can you kill me first because
I have very little health and I'll do it
I'll do it I'll do it all right well you
sound oddly excited about that she's a
murderous type tell you what oh can you
kill me actually I'm also low okay yeah
I'll do it thank
you awesome this is why Friendly Fire is
on
Friends very helpful sharing is caring
sharing is scaring you don't need to
kill me though I'm good I'm good really
yeah I'm good although I could be at
full
health think about it
died yeah you know you could be at 100
HP yeah you know go ahead take me out
grony take me out back
really what's your what's your health
right now
okay 69 thank
you oh my ladies I can always trust them
I can always count on
them now I understand why you guys were
killing each other it all makes sense
now yeah yeah we were doing it out of
Good Intentions oh wow how what a what a
kind world we live
in all righty on my way
back yay oh are you guys doing a little
handstands together making a little to
totem
pole it's very cool
yeah maybe I can join it's a little
difficult with three
people but I bet it's possible oh why
don't you jump on me and then you jump
on people oh good idea yeah oh yeah oh
okay here I go oh that was an awesome
idea now look we're
three can I can I jump with you guys on
can you
oh wait wait let let me try
Okay no look at us effing around when we
have a
freest can't be helped can't be
helped also oh there's apparently an exp
debt from dying
actually oh what does that mean pretty
sure that you have to get a certain
amount of exp Before You Can level up
again but I don't know if they took that
off for our
server hm oh so we'll have to
see they might not
have only after level six okay yeah be
careful after level six you take a
penalty it's okay lose X we're level
three yeah wait how can I check my level
uh if you press Tab and go to your
character oh okay thank
you all right we're here
we're here C yes this the mines the
mushroom Mining Company my gun ready I'm
is low for some
reason okay oh we here oh yes ladies I'm
ready oh yeah okay I'm ready I too am
ready let's
go let's
goo let's
go happen e it's like a blood big blood
bag bursting yeah it's like
gushers didn't we just do this one
people yeah we did just do this one but
I guess be careful be careful be careful
watch
out
out yeah killing zie my
favorite yeah hell yeah be careful to
don't die because I think you're going
to fail the quest if you don't die if
you die die very bad ow oh nice one okay
oh there's still another
one yeah good job
ladies y teamw yeah what the heck where
do we go next down here who knows the
way
what oh it's
crawling o
mushrooms oh no I need to repair my Bon
stick hold up I I love
mushrooms oh what oh
Yik good job
team we
Harvest oh yeah you can Harvest uhoh
here's another
boy another boy Mario actually doesn't
like mushrooms or anyway
what you talking about no no nothing
nothing wait Mario isn't Mario the guy
doesn't like
mushrooms Mario doesn't like mushrooms
oh I mean I guess that makes sense
because he keeps like killing the people
yeah it says so in the Mario movie yeah
oh makes
s ow
I have some shotgun parts for you you
can have them than
you
y man that was rude team cuz we can help
each other with the things that we all
want to individually excel at
you oh I guess we can go up from
here wait what wait what where are you
guys there's a ladder there's a ladder
oh wait oh oh mushrooms for
ouro
okay
uhoh
sorry a little bit of Friendly Fire oh
we got to do it's okay my vision's
blurry oh I'm losing blood a lot wait
what the heck I no it's okay it's okay
my guys make people
bre I got an achievement for killing 10
zombies nice yay goodies ladies wait
wait for me a splint
oh I don't think there oh we got to
destroy this one this one gives you
Goods you think so yeah this one you got
to break
it oh nice motor tool
Parts pears oh there's a lot of shotgun
ammo here Cali
look in thex yes thank you these do
armor parts I'll just keep collecting
them thank you
y good job everybody we completed the
quest wait
really let get the F out of
here ow
oopsie
ladies I'm on my last leg oh God
it's okay we'll be fine there should be
no zombies on the way out it's not night
time yet or even close so we'll be okay
yay please I want to go down the hole
okay there we go nice job ladies
first okay wow I'm a
lady that's
right just just ignore my giant beard
and
bald it's just a look right now you know
it's the highest fashion at this moment
for a high class
lady let's go get some money let's go
get our rewards yeah I I want I want to
I hope I can get the magazin to learn
the workbench workstation oh yeah that'
be very useful I'm looking for it maybe
the reason I can't accept any more
quests is because I already accepted
this Quest yeah you're on you're on a
quest already probably I don't know how
to no I didn't go Quest
either I don't know why
well it says return to Trader now yeah
it says to go to the trader so let's go
I guess why is it still exclamation mark
yeah but I think we did the the quest
anyway let's go to the Traer don't worry
yeah just back the
proc yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's cool it's cool place of
interest is on cool down oh top right
okay gotcha daily limits to Quest oh a
oh I see can't have us getting too
strong too
fast guess it makes sense o w all the
wood we got to really fortify our base
tomorrow before the rush that's going to
be the biggest thing we got to do for
yeah I think the first thing I'm going
to do tomorrow is just cook a bunch of
corn so we just have a big supply of
food oh yeah do you have any
recommendations of what to do
tomorrow yeah so there's going to be a
rush I think that we need to stay at the
house that we've already established and
fortify it so try and just protect it as
much as we can gather as much ammo as
possible and pray we don't
die and tomorrow it starts an hour
earlier correct yes
okay okay okay thank you for letting me
know problem Oh hour early I thought it
was an hour
later no it's an hour earlier so that uh
kiaha and Cecilia can join a little
easier you can Jo whenever you want it's
just that's when the server will open
okie dokie okay
okay I just
wiring well you prove me wrong really
not a lot of stuff in here re and get
the hell out of
here get the harvesting tool yeah I need
that do we
do I I can pick another Quest what got
the clear zombie maybe or fetch what is
fetch I don't know we tried to do fetch
but we died before we could figure out
okay I do clear zombie then oh look
who's what are you standing there for
don't you have work to do large pipes
Plumbing fixtures appliances ooh a real
stove to cook on maybe
someday okay that' be nice okay nice get
a
beer okay
I'm going to hold on to my
money there's nothing I want right now
you already have all this
stuff wow he cursed at me yeah he's
really
[Laughter]
mean you say that so
casually he's just a mean
guy s off shotgun mods schematic that'd
be really
awesome well need a little more
money who wanted to be a farmer did you
want to be a farmer Callie yeah oh right
here I'm dropping this for you oh thank
you what's
that oh a fing book
oh yay I've unlocked tier one cotton we
can grow
cotton stone tools quality
too
oh three out of 20
y a paintbrush
nice oh I got two points
available
lucky lter is
good okay I'll get this one
then o Harvest more crops that's big
this is also big pain
tolerance need them now this is also
big a pack mule n I'm just going to make
pockets that's skills Yay good job do we
have time for another
quest uh what
time what time is it CL and a little
over for 15 minutes I think we can do it
didn't take too long yeah yeah I just
can't I can't collect any more quests
sadly oh I have another Quest um okay
let's do yours it's
uh to
clear you want to follow me heck yeah I
do okay let's go let's go it's not too
far right no it's like 600 M away away
that's not bad yeah
all right let's do
it yes for
survival what kind of weapons are you
guys using I'm using the bow I like it
oh do you want bow crafting books I have
if you have it I like okay I forgive I
forgive you for being an
Archer very nice of you thank you's got
she's really Scavenging she's got all
the goodies yeah yeah I'm picking I'm
picking the crafting books as
rewards so we can up our
skills smart did someone kill me oh sure
yes I love right I live B yeah no I'm
not I will give you an honorable death
oh wait a gun would be a waste of ammo
okay point
nice sick thank
you I'd love to be able to punch zombies
in the face yeah but I'm more of like a
club girl or of a shotgun
girl what's wrong with archers well when
you're far away and you're trying to
attack them and they shoot you with
arrows and then all dudes fly forward
with big swords and there's a freaking
archer in the back it's like you got to
aim for the Archer first you
know I don't like AR I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm just really not an Archer fan
oh I like
why yeah yeah you play a game and an
Archer is like do I
have and they're in the way back of the
pack and they send all their buddies
forward with their swords you're cool
with
that yeah as long as I'm on you know
their side oh well yeah if we're on the
same side that's one thing
but isn't this the same one we just did
is it is
it yeah is it
oh where it one further that way
out of range and we fail that's not true
they're all right here but let's go
toward the one you have the one the one
the
ra
has is is a different place it looks
like on the map follow me G follow me
okay you think we can eliminate the
stuff in
there could look at that cool TR
try goodies are in there
oh this would be a nice place there's
nothing there's nothing here wait wait
for me I'm a little bit
behind it's okay I'm behind you the
trailer the trailer doesn't matter I'm
also behind oh yeah it's here it's here
I think we're all behind right now I got
I'm over CU cumbered so I might be a
little slower that's
okay wait no the quest is actually over
here what yeah my is over here orange
exclamation point right it's over
there
what follow
me it's another wait no I'm in the wrong
group what the
heck it's another area oh yeah these are
different people yeah I was like they
all look the same so I was
confused oh I probably made it there I'm
going to wait here for you guys where
are you guys at oh
uh over here this way this way yeah yeah
yeah where is this way oh you guys with
uh who else is there is that Kiara okay
and his FAA with them I
think I wait for you guys here yeah
we're just chilling here all good fell
for the same group that's really funny
oh that's why they said hi hi a you got
confused with other people so
[Laughter]
silly that's
okay eye out for bird nest for Mass
producing arrows oh yeah if you like if
you like to shoot uh arrows as an Archer
just keep your eye open for for bird
nests cuz they've got all the feathers
yeah yeah I got all the FEA yeah yeah
yeah I will take any 9
mm bullets I will take all your shotgun
shells
guy oh this should be pretty easy The
Smoke
House we got to smoke them out oh yeah
I'm going to hit him in head this time I
promise guys I promise let's smoke them
yep oh yeah I think we're all here I
think yeah I'm I'm I'm withing here
here are you wait where are you oh there
you are we're up here there we go Quest
marks are right here yes exactly let's
do it yay okay maybe we got to get him
to get
angry they're walking around getting all
up in their stuff up in their Turf
maybe
oo stay within the
air oh there we go there they're the red
points on the map I'll take everything
and show you later
what oh red points on the map there
zombie Birds oh okay oh boy hello
grandpa yeah head shot
drank oh not the birds I need to get the
ammo back okay nice o what's
this ooh scary
nice there should be another one around
yeah there's there's one in the tent I
think oh this one maybe oh this one yeah
yeah this guy this
guy P shotgun I found some 99 mm bullets
B will give you oh thank you B which uh
sorry which which weapons are you using
I'm using pistol so I need 9 mm okay if
I find I'll give
you I have bullet K casing hey bioo I
found home cooking weekly oh that would
be useful
o there a pip shotgun here if you guys
want I already have one so I'm good but
thank you let me dump some
trash hobo St okay we're done with the
quest by the way yeah vehicles
throw that throw that Bo hey bi boo
where are you yeah I'm behind you okay
right here so you don't get confused
with the other items this is for you uh
let's see six
n cooking
thank harvesting more light and Brass I
can make I can make tea now we can have
our tea yay tea like Wasteland Treasures
Volume
7 I don't really know I think it's about
constructing things does anybody like
building
stuff building stuff any Builders
here I'm not sure chocolate level two oh
wait what is it a better one oh we get
honey from this this is awesome a where
by chance did you find the shotgun from
before from the quest oh did you get it
as a reward yeah you get to choose which
weapon you get to have oh heck yeah
that's what oh there is a pipe shotgun
in
here oh where' you find it B uh here in
the tent yeah on this armor pile or yeah
ammo pile is it level two it is level
two oh not
done get that that
repair there we go wow I didn't know
there were different
levels interesting oh okay we'll hold on
the shotgun so we can give them to maybe
people that don't have weapons tomorrow
during the big yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay nice job everybody we can clear
this uh Quest back to the TR team yeah
let's go back to the trader okay good
job team we did it we
saved yay
yay
y
y got to find a more reliable way to get
ammo though for sure y
yeah if we can craft it that would be
good oh surely there's a recipe
somewhere craft ammo you just got to
find the magazine for the specific type
of
ammo that would be nice to be able to
have a
forge yeah maybe we can build one though
there should be some time maybe
tomorrow oh apparently you make shotgun
ammo with paper so I guess Callie
collect paper but dang it I didn't know
that I just threw some paper out of my
inventory dang
it oh well we'll get him next
time oh we have some paper like at the
main base oh yeah yeah paper and what
else I wonder maybe we need the recipe
for it
yeah I wonder like if there's a fastest
way to uh Craft um sorry to raise your
points for the skill tree like maybe
farming zombies is a good
way that that's to level up your stats
stats but like for like skills like
crafting um and unlocking crafting like
recipes that's
magazines yeah what about um the
challenges though the daily challenges
they not daily challenges not dailies
but if you press y all those challenges
if you complete them you also get exp
for your skill trees
well spamming spamming these quests seem
good too because these these quests have
uh magazines as
rewards
yeah quests are the best that's the
that's the thing to remember is quests
are the
best very funny to do with friends
follow it like I think doing quests with
part is way easier and funnier yeah way
easier fun way easier to level up I
think ha gunpowder I'm finally here
yeah TR the rest taking a
look what you got big hitters I could
use that for my club wielding I want
magazines if they could you to me do you
think you're pry smart
here's your P gun powder I got we're
going to have paper
eventually
pets wire post that could be good nerd
[Applause]
outfit I got just a job don't just stand
there with your thumb up your ass get
the job done get the job
on and then shot oh I'm level four woo
yay does anybody here needs bullet
casing this definitely give you
diarrhea not yet but I feel like we'll
need it if we were to craft
ammo yeah going me get some bandages I
got tomorrow cooking weekly cooking
magazine B Bo if you need oh okay I drop
it
here D I wanted to give him a present
you're going to give him a
present I know that guy
sucks I I met I met the other Squad oh
but I think they're a little bit weary
of me cuz I pointed guns at them
understandable do you have
any you going to buy some food or just
stand there like stuff I wonder when we
can make ammo though
yeah that change the game did
you drop the thing yeah I here it's here
one of them is just trash so don't they
get get knuckle wraps I'll take bullet
casing just in case it can be used to
make bullet oh yeah yeah I have the
inventory full that's why I had to put
it
there Place good job everyone today
yeah we about 4 minutes left but good
job everybody yeah
doing
great
wo that nice getting some good
money p p p p p very excited to continue
playing with you guys
[Music]
yeah well I'll see I'll see I'll catch
you guys on the flip side
then see you guys tomorrow okay see you
guys tomorrow see you guys tomorrow
bye byebye bye
by cute I'm so
happy okay
okay
nice good do we did good today that was
fun okay
okay oh okay everyone thank you for the
FY not thank you
thank you thank
you thank you I'll see you guys I I'll
catch you guys to tonight um I may
stream a couple of hours
later if I don't
know I think I have a collab tonight so
but I need to
like do a few things you know before the
collab so maybe I'm need to stream a few
hours
later depending on bioo as well so we'll
see later we'll see how I
goes IO you now I go organized now thank
you to for watching I'll see you guys
later thank you so much take
care thank you for watching it was fun
bye
everyone we going to I think everyone is
ending right now
yeah I see you guys later Pape
[Music]
T see you later byebye thank you thank
you thank you thank you
T bye
[Music]
l