[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
yeah it's cute isn't it i like it too
hello
hello hello welcome
uh
i feel like i haven't streamed in a
while it's been like 48 hours no
it feels so long
[Music]
how are you
i am currently feeling a little bit
weird
but i'm generally fine how are you
let's put out my hands you yo
yeah it's been like two days
i missed your ten job ah
come on
did you really
wait we could we could do these ones too
i like those but i'm using my controller
today so it's gotta be this one
like a year
[Music]
is that is the delay it's so long
i say ah i say number one and you say
number two okay go one
[Music]
two there we go
kind of long
is that normal i guess it's normal
yeah i don't know my my head feels a bit
weird today uh
only when i sat in front of the pc maybe
i really have some issue with the
screens recently
uh okay you're fine you don't have to
spam
anymore we're playing part time you for
today
uh it's like a little cute game but that
i don't know i thought it would be fun
to play
uh in between of all the other things
that we've been doing
um yeah and then today will be a short
stream because i don't know this game i
think is short anyway i don't know is
there even an ending to this game
is there even an ending
let me pull myself a little bit lower oh
i feel so weird i really feel weird i
feel like i don't have a fever but i
feel feverish you know that feeling when
you feel weird you just feel weird but
you don't know why i drank a lot of
water i ate through to have breakfast
i i even took a nap i got enough sleep
but i feel
weird right now
maybe i need to
get naked
as in maybe it's too hot
it's not that hot no it is not actually
one second
[Music]
okay
how weird oh well we will see i'll
probably feel better later after a
little bit of
playing
so
another week has started august is
almost over
next week is our one year anniversary
and i've been a part-time warrior
and a part-time idol
in whole life for almost a year
it's time to look for a new job it's
time to become a part-time ufo
mtf in ufo stands for
fried unidentified fried object yes
and i've heard wait i think i think you
guys told me before you don't say ufo
you say ufo but i say ufo what the hell
of course it's ufo i mean it stands for
something and that's why who you ever
but i say you fall
you fall
the song you know the song
bump
so you better get used to it i don't
want any complaints here today
okay let's play this game um
there's an old dude right at the
beginning who started talking to me
even though i didn't even press start or
anything i just opened the game so let's
go
did you hear the pcm enough because
you're gonna make it louder or maybe a
little bit louder because it's like very
very decent anyway
[Music]
there you go okay
my precious giant oranges
orange
it's destined to be my job
[Laughter]
these old bones can't get them back on
truck
[Music]
you
the young man drifting around could you
help me
of course i was born for this put the
cargo on the truck put the oranges on
the truck let's go okay
okay
um
[Music]
object you want to grab then press right
or down to lower your claw
if the ufo gets too close to a grabable
object you won't be able to bring out
the clock
[Music]
to let go of the object you are grabbing
press right or down again
[Music]
what a cute song in the background
okay so
i go here
[Music]
yeah yeah
linking objects are important
work is done when you load enough
blinking cargo to reach the goal
you can get a bonus for loading the
other cargo too
but if you don't finish in time you lose
the bonus that's right there is no
reward for working overtime
you heard that you heard that camping
but you got to work overtime anyway
[Music]
let me go
let's go
grab the orange oh good stuff you fall
good job
[Music]
everything is cargo maybe to do this
cargo too
oh he's happy i have it
let me grab the orange i'll do my best
to grab everything here dude
i'll help you trust me
[Music]
damn that's like a mutant orange yummy
imagine all the juice you can get out of
that orange the coca-cola some old
engine
[Music]
it's too heavy it's too heavy
but nothing is too happy for me
[Music]
you know i love me some games with some
good cute music
viba bowl 10 out of 10.
you can get medals by completing secret
goals while working
as you earn more medals you'll open up
more job opportunities
and that's not all earn all three medals
in a job and you'll unlock a more
challenging star star version of the job
whoa
then let's continue this was just the
intro yeah
[Music]
put that money in that thingy
mm-hmm
i have a letter why do i have a letter
is that my pay oh
ah no that really helped here's your
pain go ahead and take it
this is the first time you've ever been
paid for work
you younger and stripped around doing
nothing with your lives well i ain't
gonna stand for it
it's not your business dude
to help this alien drifter settle down
on earth the man uh ah the man hence the
ufo magazine with job
listings and so begins the ufo's life on
earth ah how do you i want a backstory
how did the youthful come to earth
anyway what the hell
how did that happen
[Music]
we have a room we live in a single
apartment room
hawaii
you don't get paid okay if it's [\h__\h]
that you you do
you you you there's a salary you just
prepare to meet us that's it
[Music]
so cute okay anyway oh there's a little
like menu here cute there's a shop
[Music]
first gotta go shopping
what is this
[Music]
welcome to the first earthquake of the
cosmic battle shop
i tried to make this place fit
with europe scenery but it seems like
only kids shop here
oh you found us yeah
and i can tell that you're a big
generous spender
we've got all kinds of stuff even
outfits that will make you fly around a
bit differently
[Music]
oh perfect haley this is for crony
the the helicopter cap
oh cute i don't have enough money for
that yet
[Music]
but that's like oh dear ten times what
we have now
space suit yo why does a ufo need a
space suit explain that to me
okay no i cannot do that now
okay then i guess we should just uh yeah
[Applause]
ocean one catch the fish moving all
around easy let's go
cute game cube game cute game
fish on board and then we sail away all
right in five fish
oh it's so cute
i saw this one oh my god am i not
supposed to go into the water i saw this
when someone else played it
some other hall i remember am i the
first one in home live english to play
it why why has no one played it yet
[Music]
it's so cute
big fish you guys know what those fish
are called cause i don't know
i got you while i was moving
surprise beach
yes i'm gonna fry you real good
french fish is an option too at kfp
[Music]
i was a bit too messy there okay let me
get another fish
this one looks like uh you know those
air balloon hot air balloons
we're already done
i wanted to get more i finally can do
over top
[Music]
show up your awesome work to everyone
who's not working
in my chat everyone's working y'all are
hired at kfp okay no needs here
just press class to take a picture of
your successful effort
and then upload it onto social media or
not if you're not on social media
share a photo and you'll get to view a
special instruction commemorating that
job
no no thank you
no
thank you thank you thank you thank you
what is this
advert advertisement no no no no no
you're already on my social media right
now you're on my youtube channel
[Music]
i should have read the whole thing i
hope i don't make the boss man put up
the pillars and add a roof
let's build a temple
okay who can build their temple faster
me oh good
i started later and i will finish early
and good out just watch him see
watch and see a temple
i don't understand wait i'm building on
on the right side aha
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is uh-huh
calm down calm down calm down it has to
wait does it actually have to look like
a
temple
wait
this is difficult
okay
ah it only has to be two parts though
i want to grab this can i
yes okay
let's go
good are you watching this
good luck with atlantis i guess
and we need a roof that's it
usual well i kind of want the dude there
okay drop it i want to do
now now i can't reach him
can i have the dude will he give me like
extra points let me try to catch him
i'm too close
just so close
no
oh god
i got him this is the god that we will
pray for in our temple
aka me
oh i got the extra points i see
that was an extra point huh oh heavy
happy happy happy
okay
oh
it's so heavy
okay
chill chill
nice
beautiful temple
[Music]
what a horrible temple excuse me
kelly kelly's in the chat uh
for realtors
let me see
thank god it wasn't good
rome wasn't built in a day because the
dog but i did build it in less than a
day
so
yeah
so much for when i wasn't building a day
i guess they were just lazy
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
kelly you like to speak could you wrap
this
a
[Music]
actually a phoenix but they don't
understand me what do i do oh baby what
do i do
you're the only one who understands me
or my boo
[Music]
[Laughter]
my rapping career
is about to start
it's five minutes i have to redo this
and get like medals from them
oh
okay let's retry the first one because
we can't continue i was not good enough
apparently even though it cleared them
what the hell do you want from me so you
want me to do it faster
or do you what is more important getting
all of the stuff in there or doing it
faster
[Music]
i guess this
wait is this this is not considered
cargo right today
but all of these give me extra points no
[Music]
i'm pretty proud
big orange i'll check your ah there's
objectives okay okay okay wait i'll
check them
but at least nothing oh it's wrapped oh
because i put it all into one thing ah
so that must already have been better
than before she didn't oh man kelly is
scared of my potential
she's just scared of my potential i
understand
[Music]
okay so
metal
i think the first time we only got one
medal right
ah is there also one for like putting it
um
putting the the boxes uh upwards when
like when that is ever i was pointing
upwards and i should put it like
a film i understand i understand i
understand
i understand completely and i do agree
[Music]
now hold up we also have 7 100
monies
can i buy something
[Music]
yeah i'm back space down
so does this make us faster
does this have effect on us
i have 7 000 the best that we can get
is oh we can get a witch broom
a sailor outfit so cute
i want the same outfit maybe
cloud moves much more quickly that will
be 5000 wait let me see what the others
do if it does the exact same thing
all you can do is fly in the air that
will be five okay and that doesn't sound
much better the sailor cat sounds better
than that
no no not today
oh [\h__\h] okay what does this do grab fish
quickly and tightly
ah
for the fish quest
because they were so heavy maybe i don't
know ninja where fast is the wind that
will be five thousand
okay now i'm gonna go for sailor cannon
for now
again
oh there's the quality stand
[Music]
doing a job something cool happens
and what happens changes depending on
what you're wearing isn't that fun give
it a try
okay i will try to remember that bye-bye
oh my god i'm so adorable oh my god oh
my god that is so cute also i like that
this is like a japanese style apartment
so pretty i used to live in one of those
[Music]
oh
let's go high school oh help out the
cheerleaders
white tower of infinity how high can you
go i'm not holding there this is like a
challenge no no we're gonna continue
with high school one i should i should
have read those things damn it
something about 35 meters let's go
ets go let's go cheer squad let's do
this take it 3.5 meters high ah
damn she flexible the girl in the middle
she do be flexible
oh we have some girls over here as well
[Music]
is
as tall as possible
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah and the girl
below like that
[Music]
and then see where it goes but let me
try to build on
this what happens
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
but wait now we have a nice and firm
base to build upon
[Music]
[Applause]
can you just stand straight for god's
sake
okay
um there must be a way to improve those
yeah yeah i know i'm not happy with that
damage
[Music]
we failed
everything is set to time
so we want to do that again
i want to do that again i don't accept
this outcome
kiana is bad at organizing
[Music]
no
it's not true
i do it again three point they want us
to build in 3.5 meters i think
to get another medal wait why do i start
with you again who should i start with
maybe review
[Music]
i can't imagine like a country banjo
version of this song
i think that would be amazing fabulous
[Music]
now we're talking wait no drop her
drop it like it's hot i wanna first face
you
hopefully
the exact way no chill chill no
why is it heavy oh my god
you're really difficult to lift so this
is beautiful okay
and then on top of that we want to put
you because your
spread legs will help me
to put the last
to girl the last girl on top of you but
you're in a bad position right now it's
difficult
yeah drop it no
[Music]
drop it now like this i want to grab you
again
yeah
should be fine
okay
[Music]
like this oh my god genius and she has
her hand spread out like that it looks
really really stable to me oh god look
at her eyes she's like she's freaked out
wait let me bring you down again
yeah now she's chill again i wanna i
wanna have you ah from i wanna grab you
from a better angle yes yes yes okay
um hi
okay yes good very good very good
[Music]
it's very important to grab them tightly
smoothly
i have it no don't have her head
she can still fall down
what happened
ah
come on come on
[Music]
wow
wow genius
look at her jumping yo
best cheerleader in the team
come back
[Music]
hmm
oh
[Music]
we almost made back all the money that
we spent on my cute sailor out there yo
hello
what's up next put away the toys and
don't forget to put the lid back on
and
wait is there a way to see like i see
the i see the things in here like
what does it mean is there is there a
text for that
ah do they want me to put some rings on
some kind of like um
okay
i will try to do what they want me to do
without knowing what they want me to do
but i think i know what they want me to
do
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay i'll go
get ah out of lr oh
oh okay
okay it's closing time put away the toys
make sure to close the box well but
first i have to open the box right
[Music]
that's the problem i can't reach those
toys
[Music]
we put that on the very right so we have
some space
ah
i guess wait if i could turn that around
it would be even better probably
um
but no matt doesn't matter let me put
that in like
like this
yeah
oh my god
freaking there's the chicken
we're not done yet
before we close the lid no [\h__\h] no i
can't reach that [\h__\h] again no wait but
when if i put like the next toy in there
[Music]
oh wait that actually doesn't really
oh my god so cute
let me put you here for now oh i wanted
to have you in the box
no
wait we will have to replay this this
one
i'm not happy with my uh strategy go
away stupid there
oh cute okay so i want the ring thank
you
[Music]
[\h__\h]
the bear is the last item they want
so oh yeah
don't touch it don't touch it okay okay
no no no no no
no closing the lid i want the rings
because the rings have to go on that
iron my side and that picture
[Music]
i got both
but i can't put them both at once on
there
i got none of them
oh wait
two at once in this position is easier
okay chill
[Music]
now we down that freaking stupid-ass lid
once more
and also
i wonder if the chicken oh god we don't
really have so much time but it's okay i
wonder if we got extra points for
putting the chicken in the box
i don't know maybe it's a secret
okay okay go
yeah like that wonderful
[Music]
can the chicken turn around
maybe not oh
[Music]
oh that was the oh cute okay anyway
we're trying again i understand now
i understand
yaddy now see
okay first we do the rings
because they're right here right now
come on now that's better because then
we don't have to move the lid around yet
this will be much faster
efficient guys
watch your boss working and learn from
it oh my god what the hell what what
[Music]
that's not supposed to happen right
that's not supposed to happen
what
[Music]
i think i glitched the game
i don't think that that's supposed to
happen
okay
oh that was weird
oh
she did it again
oops i yes
now
[Music]
yes okay okay hello
good job you fell nice
doing fine with the time
okay now on to the um okay let me move
the
move this boy okay
no don't say you're carrying that thing
now i got it i got it i got it i got it
i got it i got it i got it i got it
okay okay now wait actually wait
let me
move
bear chum
[Music]
i just didn't want to move the lid
anymore but maybe that was unnecessary
no cute oh my god not as cute as you
guys though you guys are cuter than that
chicken
i mean look at the look in the mirror
guys
i know you guys are cuter
i don't know about you guys but i have
confidence in you
[Music]
so we want to turn this around
yourself put the chicken in the box
possibly like that
i don't know if it matters but i want it
to be
perfect
yes
if it fits it sits whatever this should
be fun
and then there uh wait let me do let me
do this one
now we do it on the other side i guess
like this
no [\h__\h] that was not how it's supposed
to be
[Music]
it might not be the perfect placement
but we'll be able to close it properly
right
[Music]
[Applause]
oh wait i got extra time it's all good
you are in the most stupid position ever
because i can't when i'm so close i
can't grab him but
okay let's do it let's open up here and
then there we go okay
okay i moved him
okay
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
and
yes yes yes
[Music]
one more
no
i will not move on
even though i could
not
i don't i can't accept this outcome
i'm better than this
[Music]
we were a bit unfortunate in some
situations but i'm better than this
look at me i'm a [\h__\h] part-time ufo
you're telling me a youtube
of course i can
i'm an unidentified fried object
i can do better than this
come on
okay you can come with me there
i'll just drop it off
did you see that
[Music]
only the pros can do stuff like that
oh sorry chicken
i'll take care of you later
just wait for me
[Music]
oh i can actually move them
oh i will remember that that's useful
okay
why is that christmas music oh my god
don't make me feel like it's christmas i
love that
it's not christmas yet it's just almost
september
right september right yeah
[Music]
can you believe it no i don't uh
if i put that bear in there will it
count as uh it's already over
i'm not sure
okay
come on chicken
it looks so cute when it's lifted like
that with its wings
oh
wait i want to put you here for now
[Music]
wait i don't even need all medals right
because i just need the time medal now
or
or not maybe not maybe i do know maybe
it only counts if i
get them all at once
[Music]
yeah somehow this is christmas themed
oh my god going to
[Music]
toy store
during christmas must be stressful
um can you not do that
i thought we had something you want me
[Music]
calm down calm down
calm down yeah okay i'll cook it don't
drop it
[Music]
there we go finito
now the lint okay
hi
beautiful
[Music]
adorable
oh my god
yeah i got them all i got them all yeah
down kevin what happened what did i do
what did i do
what did what why is everyone telling me
to calm down what did i do
[Music]
do the museum now
everyone don't forget to hydrate
[Music]
can't bear it ah you're funny you're
funny
you're so funny
you're winning hell yeah i am
chosing i could even buy a new outfit
right now but oh well
oh no i knocked it over please help me
with the exhibit
uh
this looks like some zelda
skyward sword thingy you know those look
like oh god is it supposed to be oh dear
a certain order
oh god
those look like the the ones um
in the oh wait on the left side i see it
ah this is the lowest one oh god okay
wait wait
there is a guide oh no [\h__\h] way i can
do that you really think i can do that
that's a big statue girl
how the hell did you drop that down
oh okay
uh next up
next up uh this this is the candy corn
thing
[Music]
the grandma in the background is like
shush shut the [\h__\h] up man don't make so
much noise yeah cuz she
she flipped this over
okay now this one
let's go
[Music]
oh balance wait oh no don't it doesn't
have a cheerleader thing or is this
going to be a bit more stable
[Music]
so much for being stable
i guess not
ah how did i turn it here
um i'm running out of time [\h__\h] this
try again
not too difficult
i'm a perfectionist right now i can't
help it
i can't help it
[Music]
okay perfect uh
candy corn
right now they're all in perfect
position to grab so i don't want to mess
that up
[Music]
it is this one right yeah
no no no
don't mess it up
[Music]
i'm scared too lady i'm i'm freaking
scared too
i think i i discovered a secret by
accident
i didn't really want to do that okay
does it really
maybe just the order is important but
not really the
actual
placement so we'll put this thing on
there i wanna put you on there naked men
are you freaking out the lady too put
you on the pedestal
okay uh
uh uh
[Music]
come on come on
put it there
[Music]
does it really have to be like this
drop it there whatever whatever i don't
care i don't care i don't care anything
is fine at this point
it's too difficult you have it
[Music]
just go somewhere else don't stand right
next to this lady
you're in the way you're ruining
everything lady you ruined literally
everything
oh god i ran out of time
i ran out of time man
oh god oh god oh god maybe we need an
upgrade on no
maybe we need an upgrade
[Music]
music
stay there okay okay okay okay
[Music]
this is this i don't know how to balance
this yeah this is horrible oh god um
[Music]
i could already finish the statue i
don't need all of them
but i want to try
now that the time ran out anyway i'm
just gonna go for it i'm just gonna
make it one full statue okay okay can
you
drop like i don't know
maybe
this one doesn't go on there anymore
how do i
[Music]
no balance
i don't know yeah it's impossible
now go away go away
okay fix this
i don't care about the order anymore
does this come with a statue of course
it does
beautiful spatula
[Music]
oh this is better actually on top of
that i want to put this but in the right
position
[Music]
okay nice nice nice nice nice candy corn
let's go
on top of all of that
or we just put it and we could put it
somewhere else maybe
maybe here
[Music]
oh come on
make me mad
you make me mad
[Music]
angry ufo
wait that counts as it's on there but
this one i want this one on there as
well
maybe maybe it really doesn't have to be
like you know
all on top in the right order
[Music]
okay wait so i'm gonna eat this one
yep yeah almost had it eat
eat
[Music]
i want to eat it in between eat
nope
[Music]
you guys understand what i'm trying to
do
[Music]
look at that would you please look at
that and then i'll put him on there
[Music]
you can do it again i'll do it again you
want to see me do it again want to see
me do it again i will i will i will
trust me
myself
[Music]
could do that again what a pro
what a bro
now you little baby carefully carefully
maybe maybe lock in the ear over there
[Music]
disgusting baby you know that
i hate you
i will not give up i will not give up
just take a seat
take a seat how about that
[Music]
now to the final part
where do we put this that the this one
doesn't look very stable uh
the the lower part looks rather stable
if the head comes down and doesn't
wobble anymore there you go
[Music]
no i'm not done thank you thank you i'm
not done
i don't want you to give me the results
yet
[Music]
i'll pull it again i'll do it again i'll
show you i'll do it again
no you didn't
ah
i'm gonna burn this [\h__\h] down once i'm
done
unbelievable you made the phoenix angry
um can we turn this thing around
this this one
maybe we don't have to it doesn't make
much of a difference
okay okay okay go go get
[Music]
stay
nice
uh
now baby
weird human uh long
adult baby
stay oh this is it this is it i feel it
now we're just gonna place the head
correctly this looks like a pokemon
doesn't it remind you guys of a pokemon
as well
something of jay i think
okay why is
[Music]
beautiful
[Applause]
we did it finally finally sorry it took
me so long i really wanted to finish it
oh
so it actually has to be
balanced in the right order like that
you're kidding me
that's
impossible
unless you ignore the time
okay whatever we can move on even
without that medal
we have lots of money now
let's see what else we have i cannot
combine them though right fashion show
oh wait no no no no no oh my god how
cute look it's like a fashion show now i
want to go to the shop
[Music]
yeah i'm here to buy some stuff so these
are full outfits right
um
what's the best i can buy now
no
ah if we if we do a little bit more we
could get like one of those
yeah okay
we'll just we'll just
do a little bit more
earn a little bit more money
maybe uh wait we did museum we did that
okay so we can we can try a toy shop too
[Music]
uh
i don't see i approach the buttons but
it doesn't give me extra info so uh it
looks like five
five items or so have to be in there and
something with the wagon or so
and the time okay let's try
let's try yeah i want to save up a
little bit more oh dear cheeky it's you
guys what the popular stuff toys on the
wagon
ah
does the order matter here
oh my god how adorable
they wanted me to do something with the
chickens though
they saw that
[Music]
one chicken
another chicken that is so adorable it's
the members
i forgot what it looked like look
i forgot what it looked like it looked
like two at the bottom of five at the uh
three at the bottom hmm
maybe yeah make some space that's cute
that's cute
maybe big chicken on top or something if
only i knew what it looked like
i forgot i have short-term memory i feel
oh my god that is so cute oh my god so
cute oh my god
there we go
[Music]
pause menu
oh
okay so i think they really just want me
to put five
five on in there and the other challenge
is to have all of them in there
uh five chickens and all of them okay so
all of them
you want me to put all of them in there
no problem
exactly my chickens let's
[Music]
i'm go you guys sorry sorry i'm trying
to be gentle i hope it doesn't hurt you
guys
yes yes yes just stay there
stay there
baby
grown chicken as well be careful
sorry you're you're fluffy it doesn't
hurt right
you got all that fluff
to protect you [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
all right i'll fix that i'll fix that
i'm running out of time but i'll fix it
anyway
[\h__\h]
[Music]
can we pull it up a bear on there and
all now oh god give me some give me some
good points sometime please
[Music]
there it is there it is there it is
20 seconds
[Music]
but we have five chickens in there
five chicks that must come for something
right oh god
[Music]
okay this is perfect
this this is like a puzzle piece here
the red part can
yes can perfectly go in that spot
[Music]
what
that's a perfectionist
[Music]
can you just
come on don't be such a
oh my god
[Music]
oh my god okay we try it differently we
put the bear
and uh
we put
we put we put
we put you
five years later
um
what is
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's staying right now but it's very
unstable i don't trust it we have to
secure it with some weight
that's that's maybe not the one
[Music]
how how is this fun for your lives
being thrown around like that is that
you don't you like it you like it i hope
you like it because otherwise i don't
know we're gonna have an issue
get used to it
[\h__\h] it
okay plan a plan of change
uh
let's change of plans
[Music]
i have lost it
i don't i don't trust
in chicks anymore
yes
bye
[Music]
oh two egg ones no
okay the world didn't want me to have
two at once
[Music]
[Laughter]
this will
feel it's kind of like it's perfect to
commemorate uh
[\h__\h] you
membership uh anniversary but
yeah the game is more than just chickens
unfortunately i wish it was only
chickens
even though i don't like them right now
oh my what you're staying like that
really
oh i'm sure you'll move if i drop that
on top of you huh
[Music]
can't believe it grab the document by
the air okay
don't show up
no
actually since that counts you know what
[\h__\h] it
put that there
oh no you're supposed to stand there you
useless chicken
oh my god you're gonna be
you're gonna be a horrible employee once
you're old enough to work at kfb
horrible i tell ya
[Music]
like this
and then it should work
[Music]
whatever i don't care anymore
i i know i know i know that those are
the bottom line count that's okay that's
okay
but wait dude
does that it yeah i don't care
i don't care i want to finish this i
don't mind i don't mind no
wait you tell me that the star is
absolutely arrested yeah
this is my suffering end it now
[Music]
what
you want me to remove the chicken
suffering there
[Music]
[\h__\h] the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] there
you [\h__\h] that you know [\h__\h] boy well
this is a [\h__\h] bear
oh my god
you're just playing with me stop playing
with me
i'm supposed to play with you not the
other way around
[Music]
it
i still gotta get on this kiddo
okay fine i'll do it myself then hi
no
stupid
[Music]
yeah
finally okay okay okay okay
come on
[Music]
come on give me a christmas miracle come
on come
[Music]
oh
that won't do it
[Music]
oh
that chicken likes it
a bit more rough it seems
will you stay no
of course not
[Music]
come on come on
okay okay yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
do
hello
[Music]
uh
do
[Music]
these idiots
stole
20 years of my life from me
[Music]
but
i guess i i'm not allowed to complain
because i'm a phoenix or something
because it doesn't matter anyway because
i'm eternal that doesn't mean you can
annoy the [\h__\h] out of me
see i'm just gonna get that medal real
quick
if the bear is not being a little [\h__\h]
come on
come on it can't be that difficult there
we go
hey
at least we got one medal
actually two
[Music]
oh i guess five is just in and those
four four four is just the minimum huh
yeah
okay okay i wanna i wanna
[Music]
wait how much money do we have uh
no i don't want to waste that money just
yet
wait no
let's do the five chickens challenge i
don't know what the left one is it's
probably just like
having everything on the wagon literally
everything
i can't do that i tried it's like
impossible
okay let's get five chickens and and the
main objects because they have to be in
there but i tried i tried that as well
and it's like
suffering it's just suffering
this this stream started so happy and
cheerful
i thought this game was happy and
cheerful and it kind of is but it kind
of deceives you
kind of it just wants you to think that
it's happy and cheerful but it really
isn't
so um how about we drop this like like
so
yeah okay whatever
and
maybe the big chicken
not exactly how i want it but yeah it
won't stay like that anyway
[Music]
it doesn't want to be sold it's like
it's like that movie well the toys who
don't want to be sold which movie loves
that i don't think that was toy story
that was not that's a great position by
the way
that is a great position
perfect perfect perfect stable stable
stable stable ah no
ah
okay
then we want another of those chicks we
have more we have so much time right now
this might be a good run
oh yeah
oh
that's one two three
we need
[Music]
that that chick over there doesn't count
right it doesn't count as one of those
chickens
so wait that's one two three
oh no no
[Music]
just put everything on the left side
with howl
wait i need you a little bit different
maybe that maybe not
does that work maybe not would you like
that
[Music]
yo show yourself okay
let's give it a try and then only the
last
the shelf eggshell chicken
[Music]
soft softly gently
and that will fall off i think what she
saw close that up
but at least that those ones on the on
that side didn't fall over
but they're really close to falling over
come on calm down no no no oh my god
come on
[Music]
how is it still standing over there
oh my god oh my god come on come on this
is the one chance
[Music]
i was so close
i feel like the small chickens at the
very bottom are a good base though
because they they seem to like
they don't have a weird shape or
anything unless if you put them like
that then yes they have a weird shape
sure
come on
do i look like i have time for this
[Music]
i've become too serious about this
i've been i've become too serious
[Music]
i think if i have three chickens in a
row
i think the base is stable rather stable
you'll go away
and then that means already that i have
three chickens in there anyway so let's
go
let's go
that's right
okay okay okay okay three of the
chickens that we want
now you actually you know what i want
you
in that exact position right in the
middle of that yes come on come on
okay okay not bad i like it i like it
looks good
sorry
still fun
[Music]
okay just stay like that whatever i
don't care
now put some more chicks on top of that
[Music]
put it down
wait this is actually good i think this
actually looks pretty pretty stable
pretty good this could be it this could
be the
the one
perfect run yes now we got five chickens
now star
or this boy i think start and then on
top
that boy
could work both ways
could work both ways wait just calm down
come on you're too fast you vote
calm down
[Music]
what no
soup
thought as we like to say in german
you just stand on top of those legs yeah
oh
it's not moving it's not moving
[Music]
okay okay come on this one if i if i put
it a little bit on the right side of the
star then it should um actually help the
star to stay on on board
[Music]
or not
or not or not or not or not let's try to
check
uh no i think i think the star is the
way to go
i just should like land it a little bit
more gently right
no no that won't stay come on come on
come on yeah
yes
oh
that was a soft landing now i i need you
i need to get out of there
i needed to get out of here
yeah
i don't have time for your [\h__\h]
[Music]
i only had eight seconds left
it was impossible
i will not give up
i'm doing this i need to assort my
chicks
i am inside of these chicks
i will i will take care of them actually
you know what this is maybe good
maybe that's actually rather good okay
[Music]
i will not
give up
also these chickens by the way those are
not stuffed animals those are real kfc
employees just acting as if they're
stuffed animals so they don't have to go
to work for kfc which i think is
ridiculous because like that's this is a
boring life why would you not want to be
part of kfb huh huh
[Music]
why would you not
i'm gonna try a little bit different now
i'm probably gonna regret it but i'm
just gonna take what i can get
oh my god
yeah that's that doesn't look stable
yeah i'm already getting in
[Music]
we start
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't [\h__\h] around with me i'm yours take
me seriously don't be a freaking rebel
if christmas is like this i don't
like it either
i don't want to have christmas anymore
if it's gotta be like this
you can't fit four chickens into the
bottom for real
for real bells i'm gonna try
i don't know there was some leftover
space there indeed but it was just not
enough i felt like but maybe
um
[Music]
i don't i'm not sure
i'm not sure about this all right
[Music]
okay whatever
if you wanna go there
i will not stop you
i
mean it could work
it could work
no no
did you see that did you see that me
adjusting
professional maybe we can fit a tiny
chicken on top of the chicken on the
right
oh [\h__\h] look at so much more to place on
this this is not happening
i don't know about that one chief i
don't know about the sunny
but
[Music]
don't make me happy like that no
no it's not just don't don't do that to
me
[Music]
feel like i'm on the roller coaster oh
my god
oh god
oh god oh my god
30 seconds and time is ticking crony
come on help me help me out here
crowley please
[Music]
we can please it okay come just don't
just make this one the perfect move
one two three four five
[Music]
i can't believe
okay let me place you sideways yeah
yeah maybe that works
one of them or maybe all of them i don't
know i can try to get more than one
sideways
will will that be stable though
[Music]
absolute pain
[Laughter]
increases volume what you want to hear
my suffering louder
louder for the people in the background
crying louder
i don't like this
ah
no
no no this is not no this is not it no
[Music]
promo
we want to share in your suffering oh
thank you
you're welcome to share sharing is
caring i see if we if we place them all
like that it might actually really help
uh be able to fit four in there come on
come on come on
yes oh yes let's go
oh
wait this kind of gives us like one more
centimeter of space
but not not the star
kind of gives us like a little bit of a
bigger base a little bit only a little
bit
wait but i'm running out of time i'm
running out of time i can't [\h__\h] grab
the [\h__\h] chicken
no no no this is so perfect
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
okay okay
okay okay okay
okay it gave me back some time okay
gotta work faster gotta work fast
don't don't drop the bear
oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
not the star yet i'm not ready for this
i need the chicken
yes yes
we have a stable base guys
[Music]
it's happening
time doesn't matter but don't i need
like all of them
don't i need like all of them at once
does it not matter then i can try to fit
everything in now maybe
that's one medal as well right
okay okay
let me try
[Music]
now i will try to fit everything
uh i don't like how this looks like i
don't know if i can fit everything
can i fit one chicken
in that in that corner
maybe
i have i have a really bad feeling
i know
no no calm down calm down
[Music]
wow wow
wow wow okay okay let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go
this is beautiful we have a beautiful
base
[Music]
yes
yeah baby
all right
[Music]
i hear i hear no applause i hear it
i hear you guys clapping in the distance
[Music]
this is beautiful this is beautiful
give me my [\h__\h] medals give me them
all of them hell yeah hell baby hey baby
[Music]
was that worth it was that worth all the
suffering
i don't know
[Music]
i i enjoy this we have 16 wait we can
bite
we can buy
wait a second
[Music]
what does it do though monster
is [\h__\h] even useful right now that will
be useful for like a
well
[Music]
kitchen thingy maybe not worth it right
now what does this do
don't let heavy stuff weigh you down
wait does that mean it it
have yourself a dozen
let it
let it weigh it down or does it mean
just don't what
what i should no no i'm not
[Music]
thank you guys for the super chat though
thank you
watching this in the shower wow
hello
i see you by the way
i see you through that phone camera
oh
yeah yeah
nice nice feathers you got there what
does it say cargo suede is more than
usual
uh-huh wait
does that mean i give myself a handicap
beautiful jammies tired eyes make it
hard to stop what does that mean
are these to keep my cell phone pet cap
dropping box left and right
who's that me
what does gentleman do a fancy suit to
suit your fancy okay so that doesn't do
anything
what is this
copy or a dorm shopkin
oh
you are adorable you are nervous i could
never beat as cute as you though
even if i copy you like that a tiger
suit
grab or force up a tiger that sounds
pretty good actually
i think i'm not sure
should i get this one
should i get this one that sounds the
most
helpful out of those
it's a safety helmet
stop quickly and safely
[Music]
that almost sounds better than the tiger
i can't combine them though right so
what does a postal worker do
delivering lettuce and smiles that
doesn't do [\h__\h]
[Applause]
nickel you [\h__\h] where did you see out
because of the tiger i guess so
i'll try it is worth really
safety tiger
tiger is good let's give it a try
okay
but oh my god i look adorable
i look amazingly adorable
it doesn't add up the skills though does
it cause like i'll only be wearing the
tiger outfit right
oh yeah
this is so cute
[Music]
this one's a bit tricky you'll need
perfect balance no problem
i'm i'm i'm good with that
i'm good with that
[Music]
yes oh it tells me to not break the eggs
this game keeps on talking to me in the
language that i understand very well
okay something with uh turtles on top of
each other okay and the egg don't don't
break the egg okay
i can do that
okay uh when an elephant he can carry
five animals like it's nothing are we
sure about that
yeah
yeah okay
[Music]
okay okay
i don't know if i noticed any change in
the
uh grab
grabbing grabby grabby oh turtle
this turtle has to be on top of papa
turtle though oh yeah oh my god oh my
god
uh here's the big papa turtle
let me place papa turtle uh
difficult
[Music]
you for real i can't start with that
baby turtle but i want your papa
i want your papa
okay you should just stay here for now
[Music]
on that
even though it looks i mean yeah no it
looks terrible totally believable
remember for the custom pies um oh no oh
no oh no oh it does give take away time
oh my god remember here and debut stream
at a 3d debut stream
with all those totally
realistic and believable
uh tricks that you did
oh god oh god
okay okay okay
okay hamster is freaking adorable oh my
god
no no what the hell
[Music]
stay there
now don't go sure sure why not
dogo seems low-key stable
oh we got the big turtle already nice
stay there
big turtle has to be
the base
[Music]
that's good
hey
[Music]
it but he's so heavy like
oh god no oh god oh no
no because then the right side will drop
up
[Music]
unless i put the llama on top of
the turtle
[Music]
okay i see i think i understand
i think can we not battle the baby
turtle okay
don't go i think
both the hamster and the dog have to be
on one side
um yes okay
um
and then the llama on the other side
possibly
that should make up for the weight but
um that's difficult because it will drop
now no okay okay okay
now we got the big turtle
it's a donkey whatever
[Music]
or put the llama the donkey on top of
the elephant's head and put the turtles
here that's that's we can do that too
[Music]
i
know it doesn't count as if they're on
top of one another does that count
will i get the medal or not
i want it
please uh please oh no
come on come on elephant no no no no no
come on
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i think it doesn't count
they look really happy though
it's productive unlocked okay wait does
it count does it count
on it
ah the egg is just don't drop
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's
not bad hello we can do ocean
there was wasn't there one outfit for
catching fish
[Music]
maybe for that one specifically we go
take that outfit if it's not too
expensive
[Music]
which one
this one oh we can afford it
grab this quickly and tightly
yes thank you itadakimasu
[Music]
let's go get those fishies
somebody want 10 fish
some
ina you know my innerness and
all kinds of fish what is that when you
want that i catch all kinds of fish
okay
let's do our best
starboard and porch but bowel and stir
and catch fish for three minutes and see
how much you earn alrighty
[Music]
yeah i feel like that really helps
i think they were much heavier without
this outfit
[Music]
there it is
i was like is it coming back or not
and i waited a moment but then i was
like whatever it seems like it's not
coming back no it is coming back
actually okay
okay scrap something nice
come
on no escaping
no escaping
[Music]
we need one of those one of those
jumping ones
interference oh hey
in interference enos
i don't want this one i want you i want
you i want to see you i
no
you get rid of my time we must come from
here next what
[Music]
hey i gotcha
you cannot escape
me
[Music]
um i want the blue one
yes
cause we don't have this one yet
[Music]
okay i think now we got all different
sorts we just want more of everything
[Music]
we have this one
we do yeah we do yeah i think we got
every color
we still have time so what the hell that
seagull is so happy
[Applause]
[Music]
wait let me catch another one of you
come on
[Music]
what oh
[\h__\h] you're not coming anymore
[Music]
okay i'm done i'm done what do you say
about that
could i have gotten this sea urchin
thingy too
don't tell me i got all three whole free
medals don't tell me that
[Music]
ten do i need ten fishies how many
orders one two
three four five
six seven eight nine is that nine are
you kidding me
ten
[Music]
wait what is that metal what is that
metal
[Music]
wait we have a restaurant oh my god make
a salad using oh
but i want to i want to get that medal
was that nine squid isn't the fish okay
okay
let's go get let's go get 10 quickly
then
peanut was not a fish is that really so
is it is a squid really not considered a
fish
really
that's
[Music]
is that like
look up wikipedia everyone open
wikipedia right now
look it up for me
and that's free
[Music]
lunch up
about inaudible right now we're talking
about squish
yeah okay
nice
that's so fun
don't hit me don't hit me
that's gonna let you hit me
no no no
that's six
[Music]
foreign so that's not a
not a fish apparently oh no no no no no
no no no wait
okay good job good job i'm not getting
hit good job
[Music]
anyway
anyway i don't care
well i don't care i want the squid
anyway though i want i want the extra
money because i'm guessing i'm getting
extra money for that
[Music]
okay
i know it doesn't count but i still want
it i think i'm getting extra money for
that
next one spawns where i think we have 10
fish now
come on
[Music]
all right over there
okay we're done here
my job is done here
you were efficient
[Applause]
[Music]
okay give me that extra cash
the eyes of that piggy bank
i can't take it all right let's do the
resting one but maybe we should we
should change outfit
uh let's take down
hell yeah
yeah i love this game this is so cute
so make a salad using a variety of
ingredients for well-balanced meal so we
gotta predict the time we gotta do
something with ten uh ingredients i
suppose and something with a dog in the
eggs what the [\h__\h]
bring the bell once you've made the six
ingredients out now i'm making a 10
ingredient salad
egg
[Music]
hey can someone make a
case be a game like this
[Music]
that's an apple
is the carrots in the shape of a star
i like carrots i like broccoli as well i
like tomatoes as well i'm gonna take
that onion too
this is really easy
right now
why was that toy store such a pain in
the ass
and these ones are all easy
[Music]
uh
i guess i'll take that oh no one more no
no no because that ends it right or do i
have to actually ring the bell
am i allowed to
continue
when i put that in there
[Music]
oh apparently i am okay i have to
actually ring the bell okay no i'm not
ringing the bell they got pineapple
[Music]
i'm taking the pineapple hell yeah let's
go
um
[Music]
let me get the shrimp as well
i wonder if the 10 one um the 10 the
gold with 10 ingredients accounts
for
only the shiny ingredients
also
the not shiny ones
hmm
i don't think any light any of them how
many is this einstein rafael from sexy
ah 19
oh right we already have ten
but didn't the dogger wound wants eggs
as well
pineapples enemy now
[Music]
pineapple is not the enemy
yeah hey that sounds like a really good
um summer salad
[Music]
i saw that coming when that was falling
down
okay
what do we get what do we get
huh yeah that was not ten
but we got the other ones wait so
does that one only count for like it has
to be 10 unique items
oh
we can do that we can do that i guess i
had two avocados in there huh
ah
pineapple not the enemy no no no
[Music]
okay i want to do it again
i am talking to kiana aka
working at a restaurant
an easy task for me
[Music]
oh
i don't really like avocados gotta be
honest who in the chat likes avocados
and who dislikes them
say
tell me tell me which one is it
this game is cute it really is
i love it
this is the kind of game i will play
when i'm boarding on the train or
something like that
they're okay
i hate them i love it green jungle
[Music]
wait i can't place it properly
no that won't work don't push it
i'll choose something else
[Music]
okay let's just get the money i guess
you accidentally i also egg yeah
[Music]
well whatever okay i'll just go to the
museum now
no [\h__\h] i hate the museum so much
want it
hmm
what
[Music]
i
i don't know i'm not looking forward to
this
there's something moving there i
there you wonder what the [\h__\h]
i got you
uh
you are now arrested by it by the time
kiana police congratulations
[Music]
you can't hide
you can't run you can hide oh dear
there's an order for this one as well
do i really uh
wait does she have to be on the credits
we already called her right
does that count as like
ah yeah no she has seems like she has to
be on the pedestal
okay well then let's just um
put everything we can
on top of the statue i don't care about
the order
this looks like something uh
sana
from
council
would have in her uh what's it called no
this moves so slowly [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] no
you messed it up in her observatorium or
something like that what's it called
that was the end of the sentence
[Music]
they disappeared but i got an
achievement for that
well
wait that thing broke no i broke it
you're kidding me
quiet on this kid
observatory that's what i mean [\h__\h]
oh can i restart what the hell
oh that's hell difficult
okay we sat with the purple eye
let's see
[Music]
i wonder if there's a outfit that is
really good for museum work
[Music]
no [\h__\h] way that that is going to
stand on top of the eye like that
it's a tiny soil
[Music]
how
what
[Music]
oh no it actually does kind of stand
like that yeah
it does like it balances like that oh
wait but i need you to
i need you to
yes
what
it's working
unbelievable
[Music]
oh hey this is not so difficult actually
oh god drop it um
but i don't know should we ignore him
that one yes let's ignore him
i guess let's just finish this
[Music]
okay
yeah whatever
now we're talking
[Music]
okay guys
that was two hours of gameplay i
wouldn't mind continuing but i will stop
myself there because i said i wanted to
be a short stream
[Music]
here and maybe we play this game again
and like what whatever uh whenever we
need a small game again maybe in one
month for two months whenever i feel
like it again we can revisit the game
it's actually quite a lot of fun
it's the time i've seen this skittle
we can have this music for the super
chat reading unless you guys don't like
it do you like it should i should i have
it running for the super chat reading
we could also there was a different
music there right
[Music]
that's so cute
the lyrics change from
oh my god working you fall to a changing
clothes
[Music]
i don't know which one i like mate
wasn't it was there shop music too
i like this one
we can switch in between but the super
chat rating won't be that long
so let's just uh play this one for now
[Music]
it's a bit too loud though isn't it
i just noticed the cat now you guys
weren't talking about me we're talking
about dad cats
very very cute
[Music]
i'd prefer a different bgm for real
this sharp one is i like this one well
it won't be that long really super chat
reading will not be that long but we'll
move over to the kitchen
let's go to the kitchen recently we'd
like to chill in the kitchen oopsie
recently i like being here
wait what does that say when i'm in the
shop this doesn't say shopping you fall
let me listen next time it sings that
part
[Music]
is it coming
that's so adorable how they change that
i don't know why but i don't i don't i
really like that
thanks my stream thank you for watching
tomorrow is zelda by the way but now now
let's make some super gentles and hang
out together
yeah
help me out
you guys are petting this movie but
smoothie ain't here
hi
[Music]
i dug out a really old um
piece of art for this thumbnail
and the artist was really happy i saw it
on twitter sometimes i checked the
artist's reactions to me using their
thumbnails i go on their twitter
afterwards
and then look like how they reacted
and they're often very happy and they're
like what the [\h__\h] what what she used
and this one in particular was like
really really old because i have this i
i save every um piece of art that i feel
like i might use in the future maybe
i save each
piece of art
in my in a folder a fan art folder
and um
[Music]
that's why sometimes i use some older
ones and sometimes i use some newer ones
but i save i save everything
everything that could be somewhat useful
[Music]
i currently have uh
approximately
[Music]
oh my god so many really
really so many
[Music]
it's about
uh 450
images which allow okay
450 images
[Music]
when i when i use a thumbnail that's
like really old uh or when i use a fan
art that's really old
that um come
i saved like nine months ago
and
i actually you know you would think that
you know if you save them from twitter
they get random file names and i
wouldn't know who made it right no
for each i'm really organized when it
comes to this for each fan art i um put
in the the twitter the twitter name
of the artist so that if i use it like
months later i still remember who drew
it
for my um credit section yes smart
so
all right so
let's see super chats let me get my
oh my god you guys know what i purchased
today
with the help of amer
i made a really expensive purchase
i wonder i wonder if i can write it off
because it's supposed to be for working
equipment
i bought a whole vr set
with trackers and and all that kind of
[\h__\h] try bugs trackers vrs set
everything
[Music]
so
i didn't know like i didn't know it
would be that expensive but i guess
there's like like cheap vrs and
expensive vrs
i want to do the thing that emma did
with the with the tiny model
i want to do that too
and ahmed will help me set it up yeah
about fiona yeah 3dw let's go
well you know sometimes you just got to
do it yourself you know if if your
company won't give you a free dw you
just have to do it yourself
just kidding it's like it's not like
that but
[Music]
i thought i don't know it would be
really cute i really like uh liked it
when um i'm gonna use it did you get the
volvo one i wanted to but like i have
some issues with steam
um like with using steam properly like
my payment options they don't get like i
can't use my like anything as a payment
option i have two accounts one is like
it's
it's really complicated i have
i have this steam account
um that is uh
supposedly sets to australia
and the payment option as well
but when i try to pay for something it
tells me
the payment option is invalid like
it doesn't matter it can be paypal it
can be
um my my card but they won't take it
they just don't take it so i was like yo
what the [\h__\h] so i made an account
um i made an account that said to japan
uh and see
wanted to check if it works there but no
i can't use my table or anything with
that one either
so
i i tried getting um
a gift card but the gift cards don't
work on the australian account for some
reason and they also don't work on a
japanese account
the gift cards that i would get here so
i had to get
genma
to buy me gift cards in a japanese
convenience store
those don't work on my australian
account but they work on the japanese
account the second account that i made
so
this is my only payment option currently
for buying steam games this is the only
way it works for me at the moment
and
no other way i've tried so many other
ways but unless like my actually my
rmt's credit card
worked
for
using um the store
from the first account from the
australian supposedly australian account
that won't work
but my debit card that is also supposed
to function as a credit card somehow
doesn't work and my paypal doesn't work
either so so i got genma to buy me a
[\h__\h] ton of uh gift cards to use
whenever i need them
no my purple is not empty no no no
that's not the problem
it's so annoying it's so stupid
ah it's so stupid did you ever ask
support email steam support
uh i don't know what no i don't know if
i could help i don't know i don't know i
mean
at the moment i still have the gift card
so i just buy games on the second
account and then
if i wanted so i could even gift them
from my second account to my first
account and then just play it on the
first account but it's fine i can also
play on the second account
it's just so stupid man
it's just so stupid but jenna did all
the scritchy scratches for me of course
she's uh using my money nuts not her
money of course yeah um yeah did you
create your first account when you were
in japan uh
i
i think i did but see and that would
maybe explain why my australian payment
thingy doesn't work but i changed it to
australia and it still doesn't work the
store like i have an australian store
but still like if it was really because
of that and it's still sent to japan for
some reason then why do my japanese gift
cards not work on that account
you know what i mean
[Music]
you understand what i'm trying to say
needlessly complicated yeah
it really is unnecessarily complicated
i have a similar problem support does
not help
the account got flagged oh
[Music]
oh well at the moment this is how it
works so i don't really care
um steam doesn't like you changing your
region
that's so weird though that's so weird
like i changed the region in the
settings and nothing works except a
credit card so i guess i really have to
get myself a credit card these are the
times where i really really regret not
having a credit card i need to set up a
credit card
yeah i understand that the gift cards
are
tied to
the country where you bought it in
but
i don't know
yeah so that's why i have bees and they
cut my stick oh so
is the medium so loud really i turned it
down a tiny bit more
get a debit card no i have a debit card
and that one is not working
[Music]
anyway anyway anyway anyway blah blah
blah doesn't matter uh let me open my
super chat uh
super chat
thingy
regarding the vr i really hope it goes
well so i can use it soon
um
i wonder we could play horror games with
that but i'm honestly like really not
good with horror games so
i don't know if i really want to do that
maybe maybe for halloween one horror
game that is not
that
scary like like a like one that is
bearable
in vr cause vr makes the whole thing
even scarier
[Music]
shooter games ring for the adventure huh
ah you may love the small
good idea good idea
yeah that might be nice
uh ring for the adventure
cause i tell you guys i don't think like
for me personally
i don't mind um playing ring foot
adventure in general like i i want to
play in but then like i feel like it's
kind of awkward with
some some people just really want to
take it out of context that's what
worries me
and then
problem number two is like with live 2d
it doesn't really show anything anyway
so
i i felt like if i were to do it i would
want to do it in 3d
emily wants to play i know that one i
think yeah
[Music]
i wonder how much movement it actually
picks up though like i would have
trackers on my on my
hands on my arms and on my belly
but i think not on my legs
[Music]
so
i mean you can do like a low-key
choreography right like a really low key
if if i have trackers on my hands i
could do otake
let's go
i wonder if the person who made the
small kiara wealthy chiara model can
give me a version with um light sticks
in my hand
pen lights in my hand i wonder if if
that would be
troublesome uh
to ask or if that's something
i could ask
i don't know how that stuff works like
maybe if i commission it as a like
separate item from someone i don't know
how how i can make the character carry
that in their hands i really don't know
anything about these kind of 3d things
but yeah
where do i subscribe subscribe to the
subscribe button let's go
turn on the notification bell
they have a proof of minecraft vr oh i
don't know about that
i don't know about that it can track
legs with infrared oh
so it did look like it picks up quite a
lot
of the movement it glitches a little bit
but
um you can pick up penguins in vr chat
[Music]
yeah and if the
movement is decent enough
i will dance for you guys
i will do some proper dances
[Music]
minecraft we are with elytra
that sounds
[Music]
um
yeah pretty debut at home
in chibi style let's go
the model that i saw it was really
really cute though the wealthy 3d model
i want to use it i want to give it a try
[Music]
the jackal pose oh well
i think
in in that 3d um in the in the
chibi-free version
if i do it
you guys won't even notice
if um
like there's not much
they don't have very long legs so
even if i do it really badly
i don't think you guys will really
notice
but that is a good idea
[Music]
or maybe the
legs will just glitch out yeah probably
before i get into the super chat let me
also tell you i was so productive
yesterday
i i um
i first of all i got up and i um
i gave smoothie her cat her wet food
obviously she likes wet food she will
not uh be quiet until she gets it
then i did i cleaned the kitchen i did
the dishes
the kitchen was really really chaotic so
i cleaned it all up
then i um
i i
finally
emptied my uh dokomi suitcases
because yes my dokomi suitcases were
lying around still
so i empty it does finally
then i uh
i i
i i did the laundry
i did my laundry and then i uh vacuum
cleaned my whole apartment drunkers
[\h__\h] freaking out yeah
trunks was so scared
but my apartment is pretty big so vacuum
cleaning my whole apartment is quite the
commitment
yeah
then i got rid of the trash
then i uh went out to get um
at the post office to get a package uh
with that that has all the fan letters
and stuff
[Music]
uh so finally i picked that up as well
and um oh yeah i also made an
appointment with the doctor
and
then i went uh grocery shopping as well
yeah i did a lot of things a lot of
things yesterday that were really
important
[Music]
is
chunker's not used to the sound well i
mean chocolate should be used to it by
now but trunks is just still so scared
of it
i opened up the the my closet my
clothing closet for jonkers to hide in
it and yeah she made use of it
yeah super productive doctor let's go
yeah
they didn't have an appointment for
today because originally i wanted to go
today i told you that but they didn't
have an appointment so
uh i'm going on on thursday
but that one is just a normal general
doctor who will then
um
tell me to which other doctor to go yeah
it's like a main general doctor and i
tell him all my issues and he can like
handle other stuff like if i have for
example headache he can probably
probably give me stuff for that um
some basic things he can handle but
stuff like my neck and all that he'll
probably uh send me to a different
doctor
yeah
but uh yeah he's like a middleman
that's definitely the necessary first
step
[Music]
yeah
yeah he will send me to a specialist
hopefully
so
i'm looking forward to finally going to
the doctor hmm
[Music]
i will hopefully finally
like i don't really i gotta be honest
like i probably [\h__\h] up um my body so
much that the chronic pain will never
disappear like at least not on its own
like
like i mean um
i feel like i feel like it will always
be there and the only thing i can do is
medication maybe but we will see we will
see
we will see hopefully i can do something
about it still i feel like i ignored it
for too long
can you tell us which vr setup you got
ah oh yeah because i couldn't use steam
to purchase it i i bought it on amazon
the most expensive one i could get
ami said that this one should be fine
like the one on on valve on steam would
have been better but the one that i got
is fine as well
um
let me see
[Music]
it's uh it's like blue
it's called uh
[Music]
where is it
v
i v e live pro
yeah c e e u v r goggles full kit with
base stations 2.0
for like the one that costs like 950
euro
[Music]
gold plated with diamonds no no gold no
diamonds unfortunately
i hope this one is good enough five is
fine by the pro five pro is blue yeah
that one that one
yeah yeah yeah yeah i hope it's good
enough
be careful with painkillers so you can
get like yeah i always try to not take
paint colors
yeah
five pro ride is solid that one is a
good one
what what is the difference between like
this super expensive one in a vr set
that's like 150 bucks like the oculus
rift for example i've heard of that one
well where makes the where's the
difference between those
they're super expensive ones and the
cheap ones where's the difference
refresh rates
[Music]
body tracking resolution
vocalist is heavily subsidized what does
that mean
[Music]
frame rate is higher
frame rate in what i see
in front of me
or what comes out
[Music]
different resolution refresher different
ways of tracking oh better tracking
better video
the display
video quality frame rate tracking
[Music]
how well is tracking and the image
reduce ratio
[Music]
okay so i guess i got a good one
hopefully
looking forward to using it and
surprising you guys with it even though
it's not much of a surprise because i
already told you
okay superchat time
pedro chen
oh my god and i'm a real player
i was completely shell shocked
to hear that in your korean stream you
told everybody about the secret
relationship between me and mrs inanna
is
for months this was hidden but now my
family has disowned me for dating a
squid who is pretending to be a human
100 not human i agree thanks froggy
frankie
me froggy
so much for the code of respect between
amphibians this is the last time i trust
a frog
i'm no longer inviting you to the turtle
x squid wedding you've made a powerful
enemy today takanashi remember we
channels may be slow but we always win
the race eno says hi by the way oh my
god
i love that
thank you ninja turtle why does he think
i'm a frog though
oh
i mean i made a video saying m frog but
i made a lot of videos saying i am
something that i am not
[Laughter]
what does he think of a frog
i am a fr i'm not a i'm not really a
frog
[Music]
interesting
the plot thickens wait he wrote even
more
what
oh that one's raphael and then there's
ninja turtle leonardo what the [\h__\h] wait
oh my god
wait what the hell so leonardo says
yeah please excuse raphael we never
kicked him out he's just going for a
face where he wants a girlfriend and
thinks he doesn't need a family you know
and raphael comes back and says leo you
never supported my relationship with my
blessed god's wife who i must remind
everyone isn't the human at all he's
talking about inna
go back to the sewer oh my god
i've i don't know what i've
come in between
um
i'm sorry for
listening in on your
conversation
you two ninja turtles
this is awkward
you said so did you lie well well well i
mean
hey i didn't i didn't lie at that moment
i was after a turtle no a frog but
the moment the video was over it was a
frog no more no more froggle
no
does he not even get a say in this no
oh my god
what the hell
you guys are so funny
my name is serrano dancing
oh wait what the [\h__\h] it's okay can i
have martial arts experience 12 years
and two black belts i will protect you
from raffle the deranged turtle
and then he follows up with another
super chat saying leo we accept your
apology can we suggest rav take some
time and visit the kfp certified romance
and grief counselor we wish him the best
we have
do we even have a kfb certified romance
and grief counselor what the [\h__\h]
what is going on
another one my name is saron indankeshin
rafael we just installed a turtle size 3
education pod in the usual room to help
you with your grief isn't that radical
happy healing
guys
what are you on
oh my
god this all one person
is this all orchestrated by cerrodine i
i don't believe it i think saron is
playing with these
ninja turtles
what is going on
feel excel thank you for the rest of the
chat
saying unidentified fried object no
pencil i promised i plucked myself
before i jumped into the
fryer jokes decide i have a new employee
education tomorrow and it reminds me
that we should also have a new employee
education session held in the usual room
[Applause]
i mean
in the one-year anniversary yeah we
could do something like that where the
one-year membership anniversary we could
do something where we talk about the
future goals of the company where we're
heading and how the company has changed
in the past one year
and how our sales are looking like stuff
like that
and then i'll tell you what i expect
from you now
from now on and continuing um
which reminds me my dear members um i
have something to discuss with you
can i discuss it now because we don't
have a members only stream
this week
um
so
dakoma
dakuma
has uh
contacted me
trying to help me with my situation
of the member
um
badges
and sent me the following
and i'm really tempted to use them but
i'm not sure because a lot of you guys
are like
keep the same ones and others are like
yeah change them i don't know so let's
talk about this
what do you think about this so we
started with an eggnog
[Music]
this super cute updated
version of the almost hatched
baby egg thingy chick thingy baby cute
then still not changing
updated version
of the chick
yeah cute
i love it already
then still not changing a full-fledged
employee but actually wearing clothes
that's my style very cute
[Music]
now this is uh
one month
uh
three
three months i think
six months i think
and one year
i think
no
no no no no eh one month
i don't know i don't know the next one
should be one year the next one that
follows up should be one year
ah this one is two months i guess
and this one i don't know
[Music]
huh
one two three six ah
oh okay
three months six months
and now okay next up we skip the
fries
chicken leg stage
but i'm gonna still put you into a
bucket
wouldn't this be adorable
and now listen listen listen listen
listen listen to me listen to me
this is the one-year stage
you become a bucket
and
let's just say you're you're basically
fried in this thing you might not look
like it but you're fried you're in a
bucket okay you've reached the stage of
being eaten however
let's say you have been eaten
and danny
you come back to life
as a phoenix
like your mama
i have
made you
into a phoenix chicken
what do you think of this
will you
accept this
or do you prefer the previous one now
let me make a poll
let me make a poll i mean i i think
maybe i'll do it on the community board
as well
but i want you to listen to my thoughts
about it as well so
so okay
do you do you accept this change
[Music]
uh
no no
i prefer previous version
all right yes
i'll become as phoenix
please
[Music]
special
let's see what are you guys thinking
percentage-wise
it's cute you guys seem very happy with
it i i like them they look really cute
[Music]
yeah really
i totally accept the comments phoenix
becomes phoenix becomes meaningless
except i agree
hurry popcorn chicken oh that's such a
cute fog oh my god that's so cute you do
look like that looks like a popcorn
bucket a little bit
your popcorn chicken
[Music]
so for the people who are really really
really into being eaten
you can imagine in between this one year
and two year stage you you are being
eaten but then you come back alive as a
phoenix which is a bit ironic because i
said you guys can't like i can't come
back alive after being eaten i said that
before i know i know i know but for for
you guys it's different for you guys
it's different what do you think
[Music]
is there
no hoga
[Music]
i wonder i want to hear the opinions of
the seven percent who say no
why do you say no
what's your reasoning
isn't this adorable
make a member pull i will i will make
another poll what is it i want to hear
why not
[Music]
does this make sense
ten percent here i want the one year to
be fried chicken
like the current bucket more
ah i said day one member i'm a big fan
they like the crispy chicken skin
[Music]
the seven percent just want to see the
world burn
uh uh
[Music]
i prefer the old one here but everything
else is good the old one here is uh just
becoming a fried chicken you mean
i want to be fried
[Music]
you all wanna be fried
i don't i don't wanna you know
i don't wanna like change when people
don't agree with it but of course some
people are not going to agree with it of
course
uh
it was a missed input okay
seven percent is marginal error
territory
no i think there's definitely some
people who put who who put it into no on
purpose
[Music]
new one please
maybe a slight design change for the
bucket here i need it cooked okay okay
maybe we can
make this
should it just be this one
but just like the skin is completely
fried but still has the eye
still has eyes on the beak
or is that too
too weird
like basically like this
fries but with uh
with eyes
and the pink i don't know
yes please okay they really want to be
fried dakuma
maybe you can try adjusting this one
they just really want to be fried
chicken
[Music]
that's a bit dark maybe maybe a no
face version i mean that's basically
just a normal bucket
and then return to
kotori return to
phoenix chicken
[Music]
okay i will continue thinking about it
thank you everyone for your inputs
[Music]
here and
there because why the hell not
just gonna
put them
[Music]
kill it
totally not dangerous
[Music]
where do i put you
throughout the kitchen
[Music]
no it's in the corner it's not on it's
not being cooked don't worry
it's in the corner it's safe don't fall
and
yeah
it fell no crap
why wow i liked it so much
i like this one so much
her name was gonna be maria
maria
come back to me
okay maria is back
okay yes let me read super chats
for real souls so thank you felix
[Music]
can you make a kfp fan nickname for me
oh
ah
wait there's a little bit of korean text
here and
i want to read what you
wrote there
[Music]
[Applause]
it says i'm a watson fan
but it also says i'm not a spy
and now i'm becoming a fan of most like
kiara
ah
halloween watching time is good rest
time for me thank you thank you thank
you okay kfb name
um
how about
[Music]
kfp
afp
kf
kfp
[Music]
okay
detective yeah oh yeah that's it
can't be detective
you are the kfp detective
congratulations
i like that because i was looking for
something that would be kind of related
to ame
i was almost gonna say like blonde
fetishist or something like that
because she's blonde i don't know man
but no it's gonna be detective
[Music]
do we already have one
i hope not otherwise i mean i guess
we'll have two
do we already have a detective
it feels like we would already have one
salt miner oh i like that one that's
funny too but no you're the detective
sorry the delay in the chat is pretty
pretty big today
[Music]
i like that one too it's so specific
you have been degraded officially
degraded from detective to salt
dispenser
you are now
what's aim the kfb salt dispenser
s-a-l-t
space
d-i-s-p-e-n-e-r
salt salt dispenser
congratulations
who says that's a degradation maybe it's
not is that even a word
maybe maybe it's a promotion
i haven't had normal latency today oh i
knew something was off i knew it
thank you
[Music]
my name is
happy birthday to iris
[Music]
brian hichner and ravenna thank you for
the red super chat good and i'm
intentional i have a small request now
that being showed that she's an
excellent chef most of the time in her
recent stream can you hire her into kfb
after all
i'm sure she'll fit right in and rise
even higher under your sage guidance
please
[Music]
if anything i can't just hire her
through you she would have to actually
apply to kfp
and i will have a job interview and all
that but at the moment it's looking bad
maybe this can be our first collab
streaming job interview
thank you raven house
for the support i appreciate it very
[Music]
how to much do i read this n87
uh
empire seashore
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i've decided to
give myself a race this month here you
go
you understand this system at kfb very
well i see
that i appreciate it thank you thank you
congratulations on your salary raise
that you were giving to me
thank you
mr
[Music]
nocturnal zombie interesting
ash ash bait happy birthday thank you
for your support congratulations on your
birthday
[Music]
thank you
oh thank you for watching my archives
thank you soon
[Music]
thank you so much for providing such fun
content this past year with august
ending i'm living on my own for the
first time on college campus ooh so i'm
really excited and nervous so thank you
for using my anxiety as i wait for a new
chapter
nice i think you're gonna enjoy living
alone it might be a little bit
complicated in the beginning
to put everything together
and yeah take care of everything on your
own but i think
yeah in the end it will be worth it
you'll enjoy it like i don't i don't
want to go back to living
with anyone besides
my cats
i don't want to go back on that anymore
this pgm is so cute it's like an arcade
game yeah right it's so adorable
it's the part-time ufo btm
[Music]
thank you
the privacy is just um
yes
good stuff privacy and
and i don't know having all the space to
yourself
and
not minding how long
uh you're doing your makeup in the
bathroom stuff like that
being able to use the bathroom whenever
you want
take a bath take a shower whenever you
want
yeah
no drama true true true yeah you don't
have to get mad at your roommate for
like or your family for leaving the
dishes out too long or no one gets mad
at you either for doing that
you decide when you do the dishes and
when there is a mess and the mess is
because of you not because of someone
else so
yeah
mhz
[Music]
yeah that would be a cute
cute outfit for the future
maybe one day that will be an option
maybe maybe maybe maybe
i wouldn't
i wouldn't dislike it
papa thank you and spyro please blame me
thank you
pudding channel
and peter
[Music]
[Laughter]
in
[Music]
thank you so much for the applause
hope you had fun today watching my
stream
black friction thank you
[Music]
pudding pudding um that's a
that's a no for me
just kidding no you can be whatever you
want you guys decide that on your own
normally black friction daisy duncan
jacqueline duncan
[Music]
um
what the hell adobe
really i thought i had a one year
oh wait one year might actually be uh
over soon
my subscription is ending
don't take photoshop away from me i
needed to make my thumbnails
uh gym tracy thank you for the pinky hey
ken i just wanted to say i'm glad you
faced your fears and made a doctor's
appointment that you really hope they
can help you solve your health problems
i and the rest of kfb care about you and
just want you to be happy and healthy
thank you very sweet of you
everyone gave me such sweet supportive
messages i actually only tweeted it out
because i felt like
um because i told you guys i would go on
tuesday and if i wouldn't go you guys
would be like
making excuses again why the hell did
you not go so i i was like okay i gotta
tell them that i made an appointment for
thursday so that they will not complain
to me
that's the reason why i tweeted it out
but then everyone sent me these uh
supportive
cute messages and made me really happy
thank you
[Music]
thank you everyone thank you jim tracy
um
this is just the beginning though
i'm still still gonna be very nervous
and scared
yeah
but i'll try to i'd rather be calm
[Music]
we just want you to be healthy and happy
i want to be healthy and happy too man i
i want to i want to
one step at a time yeah
we are proud of you thank you thank you
no need to be proud of me for doing that
there's nothing to be proud of but
for me it was a big step
i'm glad you guys are so happy about it
if i can make you guys happy by going to
the doctor wow
you guys care about me don't you
oh i care about you guys too
no
oh man
[Music]
in
i already know i'll be humming this
beauty and little week nice
maybe you should get the game as well
while you're at it
yaga thank
you too bad this game isn't about
organizing your fans because you would
have aced that no problem exactly yeah i
got those organized definitely
i think uh like clippers would be really
thankful for my for my folder
clippers um
could like really use my my fan art
holder it has so much
good kiana fan art
and you could use for your thumbnails
but ask for permission
that
i uh would be appreciated i saw that
like i saw a tweet coming up in my
timeline
from some artist
um saying that
for clippers they want them they want
clippers to
ask for
permission to use their fan art so i
would recommend that to
clippers there's a lot of artists i
guess who don't care that much but then
there's a lot of artists who do care
um
yeah so
yeah if you're a clipper then
i guess maybe try to
get permission from the artists
using the art for the thumbnail
[Music]
and actually there's a lot of artists
who have uh that
written in japanese in their description
this is this basic phrase that says
please don't use my artwork anywhere
without my permission
so
if they have that in their profile you
can bet they're gonna be mad if you use
it anyway
[Music]
what
credit of course yeah but even only
giving credit is not enough either for
some people so please respect that yeah
uh anyway continuing
to mess up brainstorm
and we're almost done let me just
quickly refresh
[Music]
okay there a few more came in there okay
okay
did you guys see the schedule for this
week
[Music]
i hope you're gonna have fun in all
those streams
we're gonna cook again on first date
i'm looking forward to it but i'm also
really nervous about it
lightning liquor thank you are you going
to play taste over rice when it comes
out of course i am i'm the taste of a
ambassador to the english region
oh we say it to the english region
yeah of course i am what kind of
question is that
[Music]
randall's channel is angus and jacob
let me try singing during like suicide
what
[Music]
that sounds interesting
peace lights duncan
[Music]
i might have to change my
my office layout a little bit for the vr
stuff to get a bit more space behind me
but i was actually not really 100 happy
with my layout here anyway
in my room so i might actually do that
[Music]
i'm kind of in a
lengthy room here
so i want to change my setup a little
bit so that i have the whole length
behind me
so that the table the tv the the pc
setup is like on one side of the room
[Music]
because now my my my whole
setup is like in the middle of the room
why does the btm keep on bugging out
like that i don't understand
stupid
[Music]
thank you for the pinky oh ron hubbard
would be proud of you kiara who the hell
is that
everyone hubbard
why
once again i don't understand your
references okay i'm googling it right
now
l ron hubbard
[Music]
it was an american author of science
fiction and fantasy stories who founded
oh
why would you be proud of me
[Music]
what what what because of my oh because
of my membership badges
[Music]
uh there's nothing yummy about my
membership badges come on
[Music]
phoenix okay there's a difference
phoenix is not a chicken phoenix phoenix
chicken phoenix chicken you're gonna be
a phoenix chicken chicken phoenix not a
phoenix okay not a full-fledged phoenix
close though it's like a it's like a
crossing between a phoenix and a chicken
which means you can revive once but only
once
yeah you get fried you get eaten
and you revive once
but only once
[Music]
that's the difference or isn't that nice
you're gonna next another chance
[Music]
is that what you are no i'm a
full-fledged phoenix champ
thank you
[Music]
we are becoming phoenix feast upon us
that we may ascend oh hell okay oh hello
thank you
wow wow you were really excited about it
i'm glad you are thank you i hope we can
implement it
without uh some what ah no the game
ended oh no
i got uh i think my switch turned itself
off
shinda okay until the end we go without
being no i wait i guess maybe i can uh
yeah no we're going to go without bgm
it's not much longer
so yeah thank you seasons i'm glad you
i'm glad you like it so much i hope the
others will not uh stand up against me
in protest hopefully not thank you
thank you trevor
uh crispy and thank you black roots and
duncan
i feel there should be an in-between
batch before we can become a phoenix
chicken yeah i don't know i wish i could
add more but it seems like it can it can
only be um
uh one year and two year and nothing in
between
dominican ancestry this look maria thank
you for the pinky
estimate all those nearly one year
employees who signed the contract to be
fried
you are you're going to be friends and
then you're going to be eaten but then
you arrive isn't that better it's like a
nice circle of life
you get a you can have the ending
in so many ways
who would say no to that
black friction dankester and ezekiel
ramos thank you for the red super chat
love you just got here and in a few
seconds you make me smile ooh
i'm so happy and you are such a big part
in it you are the greatest stencil in
the entire world love your sweetness and
the energy you bring to every stream as
your honesty also love the new member
icons thank you
they're not 100 implemented yet but i'm
glad you like them thank you for your
feedback and your sweet sweet message
thank you
wiki tunes done kashan this look area
thank you for the red super chat as well
go red or go home well maybe not the um
poop idea
and there's nothing weird about my
member badges
but yeah the fried
full like complete chicken
in the bucket is gonna look interesting
you can't force me to wear clothes what
you have to you have another one in your
uniform will work what the hell
of course you will write your uniform
thank you
a critical thank you
channel lightning legal duncan
i've been reminded that i never had my
in my own resume here's a list of my
talents oh
number one i can cook pasta okay number
two i can lick my own elbow
number three i know numbers number four
when people make fun of me i almost
don't cry
almost
please let me know if i qualify for any
titles or promotions
you do
okay logical fair dogs are you asking me
for a title right now
you are now the kfp elbow licker you
kind of did that one to yourself so
don't blame me
thank you
[Music]
i like your talents you got what it
takes i believe in
your show
in korean letters
what the hell man
who is this who is
thank you this never gonna give you a
thank you thank you very much
thank you soon
you want me to princess scary hallie i
want cali to prince carry me what the
hell man
should be the other way around also i'm
so [\h__\h] hungry i'm gonna make a pizza
after this
um wait
there there i am okay motion thank you
soon
i've been thinking about this recently
but what exactly is kotori
are are they the mascot an employer they
have phoenix or college oh please don't
ask me you please don't ask me i don't
know i don't know
are they related to you is culturally an
actual physical being or concept i'm
confused
shouldn't have read this shouldn't have
read the super chat i don't know either
okay well originally it was supposed to
be some kind of mascot that ina came up
with but
um
i would now say that
kotori is a
um
kotori
is
a phoenix
chicken
the first phoenix chicken hybrid that
sounds good let's go with that
the first being chicken hybrid you know
i'm a little bit worried because there's
this kotori super chatter he he might
come up and went to me and be like yo
i'm so disappointed
my father what's up phoenix mama
you are you are you are you're a very
special one
at that
lord new lord well there you go
i might change it later on i'm not sure
about this
i got i got put on the spot okay
he's the assistant manager
no
kotori
[Music]
um
mental support pet
[Laughter]
whenever i have to deal with stupid
customers
i get mental support from kotori by
throwing kotori right in their face
yeah
thanks to kotori we have gotten rid of
many many many many many many parents
and maxwell the first thank you
landsmith
uh
thank you thank you thank you
felix thank you
sir thank you
wait what doesn't fails you want me to
read read zero why do you want me to
read it i watched i watched the first
season
should probably watch the second season
at some point but i kind of got i don't
know sick of it
it's a great great anime though and i'm
sure that the manga is great too
bgm nah it kinda stopped so we're just
gonna read until the end which is in two
super chats
thank you they'll start for the pinky
can kfb headquarters be in phoenix
arizona us also can we add chicken
burritos if i die and get eaten you want
to be wrapped around the warm floor to
tilla when i go
are you you want me
if i die and get eaten
i want to be wrapped around the warm
floor to tilla oh yeah chicken burrito
sounds [\h__\h] good let's add that to
the menu uh approved
and uh no the kfp headquarters are in
phoenix australia because apparently no
wait no
keanu was the city in australia right
not not in winkle australia in australia
right wait is there wait is there a
phoenix stone or something like that in
australia australia
phoenix
do i if i look that up do i come up
no
hey but there is a city called phoenix
in australia i think
no
what is this
in melbourne
oh
it's a
it's not a city it's like a
thing
a center for post-traumatic mental
health
that seems like the place you would go
after leaving kfp
highly traumatized by what you have seen
here and in the usual room
um anyway uh
if we
yeah i guess i guess we have to
i will not give out the location of the
headquarters right now because i have
people
stalking me and trying to take me down
a certain
company is trying to take me down
so i will not give out my location right
now
[Laughter]
yes
um
[Music]
oh you're happy about it nice karen
slayer hell yeah let's [\h__\h] go you're
strong
destroy them you're like my pokemon i
throw you at the cairns and you destroy
them you're a pokemon
[Music]
thank you everyone for watching today
hope you had fun in this fairly short
stream three hours and 10 minutes
like
a place in austral australia
yeah i'm gonna visit it sometime
thank you
tomorrow at zelda
skyward sword skywatch
[Music]
yes
so i hope i'll see you all there i hope
we make some progress tomorrow as well
it's probably gonna be a long stream
because i want to finish
zelda in the next two streams if
possible
i will do my best uh
almost seems impossible though
we will see what we'll see we'll
definitely want to finish one dungeon
dope mm-hmm
hi hi
[Music]
oven i think
it says yes
how you feeling by the way i'm feeling
much better much better than in the
beginning of the stream
yeah it was it was a little bit of a
weird feeling but now i'm fine
thank you thank you for
giving me energy kfb
i hope i gave you some energy too
much
[Music]
foreign
thank you and i love you all very much
[Music]
no you
you