[Music]
you
me
[Music]
do
hello good evening
[Music]
hello wow you said this is the first
time
it's 8 p.m right now and this is the
first time i'm using my voice today
oh thank you for the super chats thank
you for the memberships hello hello
hello hello
sorry i'm a bit late i'm still preparing
the questions
um i i i it took me like uh
three hours to go through all the
questions that you guys sent me i had
the
marshmallow uh open a little bit too
long
[Music]
so many questions guys but i went one
minute before the stream should start i
i finally uh finished going through all
them nice timing nice timing
[Music]
oh my god it's so many
so many but um i want to say first of
all
uh many of them were
very similar to others so uh
i'm sorry if your question is not being
chosen
but instead you see a similar one
chances are
i did see your question as well but i'm
just choosing the one i saw for
like the first the first one i saw that
is that kind of question whatever so
i'm sorry if i couldn't choose yours
thank you for the membership
ah i have a frog in my throat a frog
it says
wait you can't hear that oh [\h__\h] i have
a new uh i have a mixer now and
uh the noise gate is um
is uh i don't know is that keeping me
you heard it
it's keeping me from doing like small
noise it doesn't pick up when i do small
noises god damn it
you actually heard something okay
interesting
anyway uh today we are
doing some q a we haven't done that in a
while
[Music]
but first of all i didn't really talk
about this yet and
i guess i chose a question where it kind
of comes out but thank you for the
membership thank you for the super chat
i got them i got i got
i got a go xlr the big one i
got myself a going tomorrow i wanted it
for a long time but it was sold out
everywhere
and now i finally have the cool xlr for
the people who don't know what it is
it's like
it's a mixer it looks like really fancy
and it's like made for
streamers because um it's like really
useful
um in many ways and it just looks fancy
and amelia helped me set it up of course
because she also uses the funny thing is
emma uses uh go xlr
and amma apparently recommended the go
xlr
not only to me but also uh
to goura and ina and then apparently
gouda and ina gonna gotta go xlr as well
and
amelia like help them set it up and all
that so now she also helped me set it up
and sent me her profile and presets and
everything
amen literally deserves a commission for
that
for for selling free go xlrs you know
how expensive those are especially right
now they're like uh
having quite some markup price quite
expensive right now okay
quite expensive at least where i bought
it on amazon japanese amazon was quite
expensive
she deserves commission okay
she deserves to be paid for selling
me gura and ina a ghost large
thank you ahmed for helping out by the
way
oh so
[Music]
by the way in two hours uh there's a
so i will not be overlapping uh the la i
will i will try to do as many questions
as possible
but uh if we reach uh the time where
um lena is apparently a fake the right
pronunciation
it really stressed the right
pronunciation in the last two weeks
i'm so scared to mess it up thank you
for the membership so yeah
it will not overlap so yeah
should we start i i this is kind of
scuffed because i i spent so much time
choosing the questions that i did not
save them all yet
as pictures so i have to do that while
i'm doing it but yeah i saved a few ones
uh during the loading screen
anyway let's just get started woohoo i
have a few ones there we go
let's start i'm just going to choose
them randomly now
scuffed q a here we go everyone you
ready to
to get to know me better
did you do you notice anything different
than like the
cl clarity in my voice
or nah by the way
do you
[Music]
you don't wow
you don't awesome that's good
that makes me think it's worth it
thank you i'm happy to hear that
[Music]
oh that's not that's a japanese one
let's just throw it in there
[Music]
again
foreign
[Music]
we actually talked about this before
because i think someone um
requested this in a super chat i think
uh because right now the focus of how to
holo talk is to um
introduce japanese members to the
overseas audience
uh because otherwise you many of you
would probably not understand what
they're saying and i wanted you guys to
get like a deeper knowledge of them
but someone uh previously and this
person as well
uh requested that i would maybe do it
the other way
and introduce the whole life english
members to
the uh japan bros and i thought it was a
really good idea i don't want to do it
right away i'm gonna continue
focusing on the japanese members first
and eventually yes
[Music]
what is this one
there was a bunch of questions like this
hmm
i wanted to answer this uh is the back
of your uniform closed
back or open back i have seen it in fan
arts both ways
and it's confusing are they different
uniforms like for winter and summer
uh so um some some artists wanted uh
uh wanted this to be clarified
uh to be honest
there is no official source yet and even
i don't know
because i only have eyes in the front
and i've never seen my own backside
[Music]
i've never seen myself in the back but
um
you can for now just draw whatever you
think would be the right way
and maybe one day papa will
release maybe
[Music]
i don't have a mirror i cannot see my
backside
so even you wait for that oh we wait for
my
um 3dw
[Music]
just for now draw whatever you want
[Laughter]
even the mamaloni artwork
for my music video for hinotoni is
nothing official
it's just uh an imagination of what it
could be
ask callie
yeah sure i guess we could ask kelly
[Music]
[Laughter]
well i know it's a big mystery
but i i understand that you guys are
curious about it
i myself am also curious about my
backside
no papa if you're watching this
please help us clear up the mystery
eventually
[Music]
next
uh back view of me but that's that's not
not necessarily
uh how it really looks like so but you
can dry like that
i think it looks good
[Music]
on achieving many of your dreams and
goals that you have set since debut
with the release of hinotoni we'll talk
and collab with many senpai's and 550k
thank you
i am a crime investigator that wished to
investigate
the reports that recently crime family
under the cover
uh has recently hired kfp stencil
and kiryu yakuzas evidences has shown
that kfp has been engaging in cult
activities
watch only kiana long work hours
unfair employment practices and false
advertising of phoenix burgers that has
chicken patty instead of phoenix patty
please address these allegations as
potential of kfp
is campfield cult we've connected the
criminal organizations are elected over
this
fast food restaurant secondly let's care
if we serve chicken or feeding cinder
birds
shut up objection
objective this is what you call um
what's it called again
huffman vs of english
wolf slander yes it's slander what the
actual
how dare you first of all
don't don't don't say it in front of my
employees the burgers
being experienced totally phoenix meat
no no chicken inside no no no no no no
no no
no no no how could i possibly do such a
thing to my employees no no
no no there's a slander
if we have no connections with anyone at
all
the only connections i might have is
maybe with burger king because
apparently we got married a while ago
um but that that's the only kind of
connection we have of any other
organizations
possibly uh we might have some
connection with um
amelia watson watson what was it what's
in construct what was it
what's in uh industries industries
industries i think went
yes yes yes yes yes once in railway
railways it was in industries but
nothing bad
okay i'm just i'm i'm
shut up objecting no do not listen to
this person ridiculous
slander unbelievable
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you very super chat
he doesn't know what he's talking about
he has no idea what he's talking about
don't don't trust anything
next
oh will we ever do a serious attempt at
a speed run of the game or an rta
challenge like minecraft or
super mario sunshine no not super mario
sunshine definitely not super mario
many other games that's something i've
been looking forward to since the never
rta does not
that never really happened right
i mean it didn't happen but we didn't
get far especially now you got a better
pc
speaking off
but i don't think canada's good enough
at games for that alamo lmao
shut up you know nothing about oh i'm
i'm really good at games okay
rude and i'm good at some games okay
but yeah what i want to say uh today
today today i'm not using it yet but
today my new computer has arrived
um
[Music]
i didn't even unpack it yet
because i was busy picking questions
but um yeah new pc
is there and i have some plans with my
new pc already
uh next week i think
[Music]
yay welcome to the family
new pc beef cuisine
and we're not calling chicken pizza i
prefer chicken over beef
can we call it chicken piecing
[Music]
maybe maybe the p in pc
always stand it stood
always stood for wait a second
phoenix chicken does pc stand for
phoenix chicken
[Music]
i see i see i see i see
so i i have received my phoenix chicken
today in a big big box and i will try to
set it up i think tomorrow
ah yep and then we'll try some things
with that i hope i hope
i gotta download so many problems that's
the most annoying thing about this
process
me having to download so many things now
so many progress will probably forget
some stuff and
everything will go wrong anyway as as i
know my
myself and my luck about rta
i want to try rta in minecraft yeah
i'll probably take many many many hours
but
actually i mean up until now i've been
quite lucky in minecraft don't you think
like i went on that journey the other
day and i found a pyramid
i found a stronghold and i i agreed to
go down
i found another broken navigate
yeah i have quite the luck so
it might be fine
although i mean there's a bunch of rtas
that you can do in minecraft right not
not
only the ender dragon rta but like and
uh the trident rta i mean there's
anything i suppose
oh yeah i want to try that i want to do
like i want to try that
you got to try it and ha ha and i want
to i want to do something like that but
super mario
rta na uh that's not happening
i don't think so
probably not gonna happen
thank you for the question
next song thank you for the super town
what's that
[Music]
minecraft world for the rta is there a
world border
is there i do you want to find the
the border okay there we go double
double english and japanese question
i read the english
no 13 million blocks away well that's a
yes not a no why are you guys saying no
don't say it's impossible when it's
totally possible okay
who should tell me something that you
care about in holotalk
i love it because i wanted foreign fans
to know more about hello live japan
members for a long time i'm grateful to
you
i'm still studying english so sorry if
the sentence is weird it was perfect
don't worry about it um
yeah for me basically
um i said this from the beginning i
didn't want
questions like um what's your favorite
food
what's your favorite game what's
up
so i wanted some deep questions but
i mean there's a there's a limit of what
we can talk about
with uh the members we cannot get
to you know too detailed with some
things
um i think i think um the first holo
talk
was close but the second whole talk
was much much closer to how i wanted to
be
because i mixed in and i think many of
you noticed this
i mixed in questions for
people who have absolutely no idea who
she is
and people who know a little bit of who
she is so i got because i got questions
like 50
questions or like 40 questions
from uh english speaking fans from the
youtube community post that i made
which were more general you know the
questions you guys gave me were very
general
and after that i got like 40 percent of
questions
from twitter replies which were from
public fans
and those were more like um like
like hinting on stuff she did before
like that
um doki doki whatever line sentence uh
contest
stuff like that is kind of what i was
going for
because um it kind of shows what what
kind of stuff she did until now
it gives you like um the opportunity to
talk about
like um funny experiences
she's had until now and uh her
activities until now
yeah so i was like 40 40 and then 20
when maybe
um me myself i think that was a good mix
[Music]
yes yes yes yes that's basically
uh but i think um i think the
money set by collab was already pretty
good but i heard a lot of feedback that
from you guys that the second one was
even better
or much better many of you guys said it
was much much better which i'm very
happy about thank you
i'm glad that you guys think there were
some improvements
um and some people said because they
enjoyed like
uh hearing fubuki senpai doing like a
voice impression and stuff and acting
um uh some people said that they would
like to have like a
segment in the interview where they do
something besides uh
answering the questions and i think
that's a good idea but i have to think
about what to do
because i don't want to copy anything
[Music]
but if you have good ideas you're
welcome to
send them to me and also think about a
special segment segment that we can do
in between the questions because
i guess like fubuki zamba is a really
special case
she has so much to offer so much to talk
about
and so many impressions she can do so
many contests she has won
so she's a very special case but there
might be other members where
i don't have so many i mean i would
all of them are special but there might
be members where it's a bit
harder for me to get that kind of stuff
out of them
so for that a special segment would
might be
it might be very helpful yeah
[Music]
anyway thank you for the questions
oh yeah hidden talent that's a good
question by the way
do you have any hidden talents write
that down sticky notes kfb sticky notes
write it down
why is there no member yet that called
themselves kp sticky notes
i love how you guys give yourself names
like pfp
trash can and stuff like that why is
someone called kfb sticky notes
there's the nutella shelf kfbit support
team
kfc eva unit kftit admin if we hold room
air circulation fan
kfb lazy casual kfb software engineer
kft way to carefully work this union
has dehydration control and writing i
love it so much can't be cherokee
basement garden
can't be inspected because i just love
these all so much
i love them and you're
you're also creative i love those ideas
okay this question is asking me why i'm
using the key as
a reading
[Music]
okay and i know that kikiki
is a german it's a german uh
way uh it's a german it's something that
german
how do you call that it's just what
chicken in german would say
but i am a phoenix okay you have to
understand that
now the reason why i'm using this
do you really want that yeah
my employees are all chickens they just
don't really know it
they think they're phoenix's mamie i
know i think many of them are weather
chickens
but in order to communicate with them i
like to greet them with their own
[Music]
language
you guys are all chickens that's why i
greet you
with a nice and beautiful
that's how it is my friends
i like to play around with my echo now
because now it's um like right next to
me i have my mixer and now i can play
around with these things without like
flicking stuff on uh with my mouse and
uh potentially destroying all of your
ears but now i have like these controls
and buttons and stuff
i can do like a beep now whenever i
swear i can do a beat but i wonder how
that sounds to you guys
oh god it might be um i don't know how
that was sounding
like you want to try it out
oh
did you did you hear my voice or did you
only hear the beep
i turned it down a little bit but
was i muted
was that you holy you only heard the
beep oh my god
but i don't think i can control myself
to
like always push the beat buttons
[Music]
[Laughter]
we were watching
[Music]
uh came into the discord and she sounded
like a robot like much worse than this
robot
she's not like a robot constantly and
she couldn't fix it so for the whole one
hour
while we were meeting up talking
normally
uh and without normal voices you know it
would always be like
in real life she would be like
[Music]
it's saying words because she was like
i don't know what was poking out but
something was wrong with my microphone
and we didn't understand that it was
just rubble on robert i am
yes but she fixed the lane around after
restarting her pc and there you go
there you go thank you for the
membership there you go
this once once again proves that i guess
have you tried restarting your pc
turning it on and off again off and on
again is
not that bad of an advice
because it actually did work
terminated
i'm picking up so many japanese ones
right now don't know why
[Music]
i told you many times before so this
this person is asking
if they should comment in in english or
in japanese and he's like
so um worried about it that he's
not able to comment at all and i told
him
don't worry about it told you many times
it's not a comment in japanese
don't be shy
[Music]
japanese people like really uh tend to
hide in the shadows
[Music]
how does the whole being reborn thing
break do you just wake up and go ah man
i died when you go see kelly
when did you see kelly uh when do you
see him oh that's a separate question
uh so basically let me explain this for
you
i die for whatever reason
usually i just live uh out i'm just at
the end of my lifespan after like a
thousand years
and i go up in flames blah blah blah you
know the whole thing
and i i turn into ashes but
until i get like actual
form again it takes a little bit of
time so i'm not exactly dead but
i like something in between and in that
time i can visit
cali in the underworld but now she's not
doing her reaping job she's on hiatus
so i don't care much about dying again
but everything yeah before i previously
i really liked dying and checking out
the underworld so i could meet her
so yeah i go i go to the underworld and
i say hi kelly i have about five minutes
do you want to go for a coffee
and and then and then we're both like
[\h__\h] we both hate coffee
wait did she had coffee i think she i
think she does
at least i do uh and then um
yeah and then we go on the coffee or
actually we say we go on a coffee but
uh we go for tea and some cake and
whatever
and then she's like uh i'm not really
enjoying this and i'm like oh come on i
know you're enjoying this blah blah blah
blah blah
and i give her a hug and i say bye bye
see you next time and then i
i i get like i i feel like a
weird tingly tingly
something in my body i don't know if
that's love if that's
my body turning from ashes into an
actual body again
it might be both of it
but i definitely do love her so that's
that tingly sensation yes
so and then i i i get my body back and
i'm usually i always end up in a
different dimension every time i get
reborn
normally phoenix's stay in the same
world stay in the same dimension and
just get reborn in the same dimension
but i
like i get reborn in a different
dimension have to start all over again
get to know new people right i'm still
so quiet what the hell okay there we go
now i'm peeking though so
interdimensional chicken no i'm a
phoenix
[Music]
i am a phoenix
shut the hell up now
i will be using the reverb a lot from
now on
actually maybe you didn't hear that
maybe you didn't really hear that maybe
i should use my megaphone
[Music]
i am a phoenix do you hear my megaphone
does it sound like a megaphone
i am a phoenix are you listening
does it sound like i can still tweak it
[Music]
louder louder are you sure about that
my face
[Music]
is
i'm enjoying my i'm enjoying my mixer a
little bit too much thank you for the
membership
[Music]
that's how it goes that's the lore my
friends
[Music]
uh wait one second cali messaged me i
gotta check my schedule for cali
[Music]
okay baby girl
done
making plans for a collab next week
very important okay first things first
gosh next one
what's the what's the best worst timing
moment you've ever had
i feel like this is an interesting
question because normally
bad timing when does that ever end up
being
good and then i thought about it for a
moment and i realized wait
2020 is exactly that for me
because i came to japan again
this year i've been here before but i
came again this year
with the plan um to be here one year
and accomplish many things do many
things and
i arrived in japan uh around
when uh you know deceiving me
was breaking out in
in not not not just yet in japan
like it was really relevant
and um i arrived
actually with uh two of my
real-life friends who were coming uh on
a holiday
to japan and i was gonna stay longer of
course and
and we were you know having fun and then
they left after a while
and after that i was trying to settle in
and i was hoping that
the sea thing wouldn't spread too much
and because i had so many plans but even
then i was like okay yeah whatever it's
gonna be fine until summer and then
i'll just chill until summer that's okay
i mean uh this one year
i can never get it back but a few months
okay or whatever i'll get it done anyway
um but little did you know
it was not over in summer it was
definitely not over and all my plans
were cancelled everything i wanted to do
was not possible
the chicken thing exactly
[Music]
yeah so that was a really really bad
timing because um uh i mean this is
kind of a real talk situation but i'm on
the visa that i can never again again
never ever it's a once in a lifetime
visa
and that's only one year i cannot extend
it it's not extendable
so and even if i would leave i cannot
stop it and then come back later
it continues i cannot stop it i cannot
pause it
so i was feeling very very regretful
about that
and very sad about it and i was like wow
i'm wasting my time here why am i even
here
i mean as much as i love japan but i
came for
reasons and i couldn't do anything about
it
and it was not getting better at all
everything i mean even the olympics
that were supposed to happen in japan uh
this
year this summer i mean i was
obviously yes that was my goal for 2020.
i was going to take part
in the olympics i'm gonna be honest now
this is
i was trying to stay quiet about it but
i came from a different dimension you've
seen my sporty shoes you've seen my
i mean
i mean look at those obviously i'm a
professional runner
obviously and i was going to participate
in the olympics or australia wink
uh
uh yeah they got cancers and that
[\h__\h] up everything
so i was very depressed about that and
the thing is they moved to olympics to
next year
but my visa is already over by then
[Music]
so
i love this so much
i'm the torch yes i am the torch why
would why did you tell them
don't tell the champion on the torch
god damn it goddammit
yes well that it's true it's true okay
it's true
so yeah but but then after
i've been like spending weeks and weeks
and weeks and months
chilling in my bed watching netflix
waiting for this whole sea thing to end
so that i can finally
read the torch the torch that i always
wanted to be
run all these kilometers to
hold fire where it belongs
i don't know what i'm saying i have no
idea what i'm saying
uh where am i going all this
i just wanted to run okay i wanted to
run and put fire
on on the other torches i don't know i
don't know what i'm supposed to do
i didn't really read the manual you know
i don't i didn't really read the manual
on how to be a torch but i really wanted
to be a torch i wanted to
i wanted to be part of the olympics
so yeah
um but then i saw the auditions for how
live english and i was like okay i mean
i it seems like fun and i don't really
have anything else to do
so i guess i can try and i tried and it
saved my life
and with that i must say
that is the best
thing that could ever happen to me in
such a horrible situation
the timing of me coming to japan was
absolutely horrible
it could not have been lace um
but it turned out into a happy situation
i mean i must say that i could have done
this uh even without being in japan
obviously it was not necessary for me to
be in japan
and i don't i don't think that me being
in japan played much into their
decision of choosing me um
so i guess still being here is uh uh
doesn't i mean it's it's not exactly
necessary
but it does help with some things like i
can do off collabs and stuff so that's
fun
um and i can see kelly whenever i want
so that's also fun
and i met i met diago so what else do i
want
yeah but that's uh i'm really i'm really
grateful
that this happened because otherwise
i i would be so
[Music]
devastated i would be so devastated
no for real um real
i would i would have lost i talked about
this before but i would have lost
all hope and all motivation and would
have not known what to do with my life
ever again
fedex needs a visa
[Music]
that's real in this world apparently you
need a visa for everything i've been in
other dimensions i've been in other
worlds and they weren't that strict but
okay
okay earth chill
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
next question
[Music]
hey buzz what was your inspiration or
thought process when you were making
hinotori listening to it and reading the
lyrics felt like hinotoni was something
you pulled out of a deep emotional
memory
any history to it what direction will
you go with your next song
love your first single and we can't wait
to hear more of you
much love and respect your feet for life
thank you
kfb for life indeed yes
so um i didn't i didn't make the song
i i um had meetings with the
composer gojo and told him what kind of
song
i would like to have i told him i want
a song that is um uplifting motivational
strong shows that the
the strength and the power of the
phoenix
and the braveness i wanted it to show
how brave i can be
and how strong
[Music]
i didn't want it to be too too cute of a
song i wanted it to be more badass as i
told you guys before
the tuning lyrics
they were not my idea but i thought they
were quite fitting
since the lyrics were written by someone
else japanese lyrics
um they they're very good they are very
good but very true nibio
which is a i think very charming
and then i added some english lyrics to
it and uh
i mean people people like to
uh i guess um try to find
deep meaning in lyrics and i guess the
lyrics that i sang for the bridge
uh i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray
if i go wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please where i need to
go
i know that like it sounds very deep
and it kind of i guess reflects a little
bit with myself
but it wasn't really on purpose i was i
had like five minutes to write those
lyrics because we were in the studio
and uh we were recording the song and
the bridge didn't
exist just yet and i was like talking to
my composer and was like
i know this is really sudden and the
song is basically already done but can
we add a bridge
right before the guitar solo and he was
like oh
sure i guess so
we um really spontaneously while we were
already recording the song he
composed that little part of the bridge
and i was at the same time while i was
listening to him pushing those buttons
those piano buttons making down those
sounds i was like
trying my best to write live lyrics
quickly
and uh even though i had uh problems
before
writing lyrics when i was riding that
bridge
i wasn't thinking much about it but it
just like
stream streamed out of my brain oh kelly
thank you you're listening thank you
kelly
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you
yes it makes so much sense i am the
olympic torch after all
[Music]
everything is on fire everything that i
touch is on fire
i am the olympic torch
oh yeah um i i i came up with that
at the spot and i didn't think much
about it but i guess
in some way i guess it's maybe maybe it
is really
some some deep feelings that i had
inside of me
because that that maybe that's why it
came so easy out of my brain
i mean it's true industry i had some
um i had many moments in my life in my
life where
i i wasn't sure if i was going on the
right path and
um i mean yeah
i can't see it i can see it probably
with my probably probably like
my how do you say that my consciousness
kind of made that happen
[Music]
but anyway speaking of what kind of song
i want next time a subconscious thank
you subconscious yeah might have been
that
while i was writing and i wasn't really
thinking about it
i tried to fit it to the japanese lyrics
for the next song i'm i'm already
thinking about it and i was thinking i
won
um something different but i will not
tell you
i want uh definitely a different theme
and i already know it exactly
[Music]
and we're gonna i think start working on
it sometime soon
[Music]
what is that oh
hi kara you seem like uh you like idol
groups a lot
uh when i see your set list for kind of
okay but you don't talk much about it
for some reason
is there a reason for it a bit of fear
of rejection and the animals are
generally disliked by the fan base
this is something i do not know is that
a thing
i i i don't think so actually so that is
definitely not bad
and i really wanted to know your
favorite groups
i don't i don't think they are disliked
by the fan base at all
i think many of the many uh many people
who like be troopers probably don't know
much about idols
and like japanese idols
probably that doesn't overlap that much
but i think there's some overlap anyway
but i don't think i don't dislike them
at all it's not that um
the reason why i don't talk about it is
because it doesn't really come up
but i um i was a i was a big big big big
idol otaku
i went to so many uh concerts in japan
before
not this year but before many many times
my favorite adult group
[Music]
so yeah i've been to many many concerts
in japan of my favorite idol course my
favorite one was betty scobo
and smiley um but i also like the other
grips in hello project
i have to say i kind of grew out of it a
little bit
um i mean
probably because my favorite groups are
gone by now
but i still enjoy uh singing those songs
in karaoke
and uh jack what the actual hell is
going on in the chat are you are you
even listening to what i'm talking about
even listening
[Music]
so like have this dream of
like collabing with hello project
eventually
i don't know if that's something that
will ever happen
[Music]
i will try my best to keep keep up
my perfectly innocent idol image that i
have right now
so that i can collab with those
perfectly beautiful
pure idols in in hello project i think
i'm doing fine right now don't you agree
okay guys just don't tell them just
don't tell them okay
we have to on the inside you can tease
me as much as you want but on the
outside
please help me in my endeavors of
one day collabing with um hello project
so
out on the outside we gotta start like
advertising
takanashikiyala as the purest idol on
earth
okay i know it's all lies and
inside the community we all know it but
on the outside we gotta fake it until we
make it
that's cool thank you guys thank you
guys for your support
so uh sorry i have to um download uh the
images of the other questions these are
all i saved um in the loading time
oh yeah oh yeah i want to talk about
this
let's go with this one
[Music]
next question
got anything exciting plan this month
you feel like sharing us about yeah so
um
i got a new pc today as i told you
and i want to test it out and i guess um
[Music]
you don't necessarily need a beef pc a
chicken pc for what i
i want to play but i guess it helps
so i have a i have a happy announcement
for everyone
i have finally
achieved not a team i finally
when you got gotten received
permission for one of the game series
that i was waiting for for ages i
finally got permission for
all utterly italian games
[Music]
give me permission to play all the
afternoons whatever i want to play and
they even kind of said i can play other
other korean tecmo
america games as well but i i just
specifically asked for atelier
and um after here raiza
maybe you guys have heard of it uh
it has been quite a big topic um
because of the sexy ties that razza has
is so next year in january or february
was it january not sure anymore in
either january or february
ryza 2 is coming out and i wanted to
play riser 2
at the release date but
before that since i haven't played it
yet i want to play
riser one on stream and even though we
have a lot of projects ongoing right now
uh i will start playing
until you're risen uh
actually not next week but the week
after um
[Music]
and i know many of you might be not so
uh
about it as i am because i i know that
many of you don't
know the atelier series or never played
them before
um but i'm personally very excited about
this um
atelier games are so beautiful
so so beautiful so cute so adorable and
after arizona especially has been
um getting a lot of
positive feedback a lot more attention
from the media because of uh
well the fake ties
which i first i personally liked atelier
games uh
much before that before rizzo
but i'm very happy that atelier has
gotten more attention recently because
of the extra x-axis
and they made her even thicker in raiza
too
holy sh
[Music]
thank you so much they're so lovely so
easy to talk to
[Music]
so easy
oh yeah that might actually open the
doors to many other koi tech mobile
games that i wasn't able to play until
now
uh so yeah look forward to that but
specifically now i'm just looking
forward to
uh atelier a lot it will probably be
another really chill rpg that
uh might not get the best numbers but i
don't care
i'm telling you i don't care i'm gonna
play atelier i don't care what you think
about it
it was on my favorite games list in my
debut
stream as well so i do not care you
better just appreciate the aesthetics
even if you don't care for the game you
better just come for the thick ties okay
thick tie
save lives that's what it is hell yeah
oh and besides that um
i can tell you about this month sorry i
already
deleted the question
[Music]
there's something special about
christmas and i can't i cannot tell you
about
actually two maybe even three special
things around christmas that's gonna
happen
i will not tell you about and uh
i will also do uh unarchived uh
christmas karaoke stream
[Music]
i think i'm gonna do it on the 20th
japanese standard time which might be 90
for many of you
and uh what else was i planning uh i
have a
i have an off collab with a certain
senpai
[Music]
er very wait is that next week
oh my god it's
it's next week oh my god oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm a bit nervous
you want a clue i'll give you a clue
flat
[Laughter]
chested
[Music]
but i will not tell you anything else
no no no look forward to the schedule
actually isn't today sunday
oh yeah today is sunday so
i will upload my schedule tomorrow
because we have a members movie
watch along after like actually in
um two
two hours in two hours we have a member
movie watch along
check the community board if you
remember and
and then we watched the movie for three
and a half hours and after that
i might wake on the schedule and then
upload it
it's quite interesting she had an idea
of uh
what she wants to do and i i
i'm very nervous if i can um
perform well
she wants to do something very special
uh
yeah i'm worried
pretty pretty bye so yeah there's
so many things oh and one more thing
um
one more thing
i'm not sure when exactly i'm releasing
it but
at the end of december around the end of
december
i will be uploading
um
[Music]
a song cover not an original but a song
covered
yes yes yes yes more details
following soon
okay
[Music]
next question which one should we do
um
[Music]
oh yeah i mean that was uh that's kind
of like
i just wanna i just wanna acknowledge
that i i saved this question as well
what are your plans for this christmas
any special broadcast let me just say
of course we are applying something for
christmas
of course yeah um
this and that but i cannot say anything
so that's that
is
um next question
i wasn't sure if i want to answer that
but i guess whatever
next question is uh tiara you may be
aware that this question has recently
been answered by all of the whole life
japan 5th generation members
and ame and we are collecting data from
the rest of whole living yen
when you shower which part of your body
do you wash first your head doesn't
count
oh if you really
need to know i think
i think um
[Music]
this is embarrassing
i think i take the shower
head with my right hand and i i wait
until the water is warm and dye and then
it
[Music]
can't do it i cannot do it i cannot do
it
i can't no
i'm sorry i cannot do it
i am sorry to disappoint you
i'm very sorry
[Music]
i tried i really tried but oh no
i'm not that bottom left after all okay
you guys think i'm like super lude and
jump at every opportunity to be bottom
left
that's not true next question thank you
for the membership
[Music]
is there a takamoni situation or as a
costume that kiala wants
i want to make you wish come true so i'm
waiting for your answer
and finally i'll be rooting for you all
the way keep up the good work i love you
thank you i love you too
how about how about i mean summer is
over
but how about a summer picnic where we
are both in like
white dresses and uh both wearing like
summer crowns or making each other's
uh flower crowns and putting them on
each other's heads
or like or like i'm feeding or cali is
feeding me i don't know which one
is the best but we're feeding each other
uh grapes and stuff
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
oh like um winter how about um
me and callie on the christmas market
oh wait wait wait how about me and
callie um
in in uh yukata uh looking at a firework
how about how about how about them oh
how about me and kelly
at the christmas tree like as as if we
were living together you know and my
fantasies were living together
under a christmas tree like together as
a family
and opening each other's presents
and wearing like christmas hats and
stuff oh my god
and if giving each other like christmas
sweaters
oh my god mistletoe yes please someone's
wrong mistletoe situation
the thing is like mistletoe is not
something i've ever done before
like it doesn't really exist in in the
culture of where i come from so
i didn't really think of it immediately
but that's a good idea
so many good ideas okay chill well
that's a few ideas
if you need more ideas let me know i'll
get just tweet tweets to me on twitter
and i'll give you all the audience
[Music]
let's go with this one
how do you choose your guest for hello
talk show and do you then just approach
your senpais and ask them directly
up until now uh there's only been two
episodes so yeah i've just don't
been thinking about who i want to be on
my show and just asking them to start
dming them or
messaging them on this card um
but actually uh
recently uh
senpai's have been approaching me
and saying they want to be on holotalk
and i'm like of course yes please please
so
i'll let my schedule you
so um the upcoming guests
the upcoming two guests are already
decided
i feel like a popular kid i don't even
have to ask them by myself
anymore they volunteer themselves yeah
i'm so happy i'm so happy because that
to me it means like they
enjoy like my show
and they want to be on it they
acknowledge that it's a
good show and and they want to be on it
with me
and i want to be they want to be
presented by me to you guys
on my channel i'm so happy about that
ah oh i'm so happy
today today against uh a certain senpai
messaged me like
yeah kiana i wanna be on the show that
you did with fuki senpai
yeah i wanna be on the whole talk and
like
okay yes yes yes yes
there were some correct answers in the
chat actually in the comments
good guess good guess but i will not
confirm anything yet
[Music]
so basically the guests are now choosing
themselves i'm not choosing anyone they
choose their own destiny
okie dokie next one which one should we
call
oh this one
[Music]
your streams have been pretty
entertaining and i really love you
raging in super mario sunshine uh-huh at
least someone's enjoying it
these past few days i've been uh feeling
a little down but watching your streams
have been
getting me through it thank you very
much oh thank you as well for watching
thank you thank you thank you thank you
are you gonna play a way out of kelly
[Music]
yes
a way out with kelly
is a collab that has been scheduled
already please look forward to it
thank you
[Music]
let me drink some water
callie wanted to play with me and uh
i've seen that um amen could have played
it together and apparently it was like
very emotional and
uh a really good game but i know nothing
about it so
i didn't even spoil myself i have no
idea about the game
but yeah now that i have my new pc i
think it's a good idea to play that game
i mean i don't know
does that game require a good pc maybe
it doesn't well still
good that i have a new pc now wait is
that even on pc or is
on console yeah no spoiler i just know
that it like ended up apparently very
emotional
apparently it was uh very sad in the
underwear
i don't know a piece of um okay okay
yeah we'll be playing it on pc
and uh it's already scheduled so look
forward to it i have no idea what this
game is
what kind of game is it is it like a
shooter game or what do you do what
genre is it
oh thank you for the super chat thank
you for the rest yeah i'm very excited
it's a it's a
i mean to be honest um since it's a
whole life indonesia
it doesn't exactly feel like i am their
senpai
uh but apparently that's how it is so
yeah it's very exciting i've been
watching the debates and also gonna
watch it in half an hour
again it's an actual co-op
third-person shooter is it hard i'm not
good at shooter games i never play
shooter games
is it gonna be difficult
because i think both me and callie are
not the best gamers
from what i've seen she's not the best
gamer it's not a shooter
it's a puzzle
[Music]
it's not that difficult fairly easy okay
okay
shoot a puzzle what the hell is that
well it will be interesting um i i
wonder if we can even finish the game
because amen gonna finish it in one go
right
from what i've seen i i i i'm not sure
if we can do it like i don't have much
confidence
in in shooter games or two streams ah
okay
[Music]
well yeah both me and callie are not the
best gamers so it's gonna be interesting
i hope it doesn't require too much skill
but i'm looking forward to like uh an
emotional story
and it seems like an interesting game
like co-op is very interesting
[Music]
um
let's answer that question so
[Music]
he's asking um if i ever was gonna like
cook for another yen member when i would
be cooking for them
and he's asking if i would be cooking
shark fin
or gouda but no i actually um
i offered cali before and i could make
um
french toast for her because for i i'm
not a good cook but i know a few things
and uh french toast is actually um
one of my one of one of the few
foods dishes that i can make
so i offered that to her before and
maybe one day
for breakfast i'll make french toast for
her
after i slept over it haha
[Music]
okay let me answer this question i want
to try it out
and when will i do a helium voice asmr
so i have no idea
why you would ask such a question but
since i now have my mixer
i want to try and uh satisfy you
as soon as possible
let's see
your voice
[Music]
like
around
[Music]
how about we make some rice now
no i'm not going to help you to kill the
fields you gotta do it all on
[Music]
oh my god purse
well this is uh the new me i hope you're
happy i hope this
satisfied you
what do you mean real voice this is my
real voice
[Music]
oh
uh
[Music]
me
yeah that's a very helpful tool
don't don't don't it's not my fault it's
the fault of this marshmallow i mean
whoever asked a question
please send your complaints to that
person
was that a dolphin maybe maybe my inner
dolphin
i blame amelia i guess yeah you can
blame amina because she kind of gave me
the recommendation for the go xlr
oh my god oh no
how about okay
do we wanna do um
i gotta i got a really long japanese
marshmallow that's like
life advice do you wanna do you wanna
help that person
[Music]
i'm not sure how much i can help but
there we go
oh my god um
[Music]
so this person is in love with someone
from apparently a long long time
okay
and he has been hanging out with her
like after school
and even like once they become adults
they
um met at a marriage
uh ceremony of a friend and even there
she was the first one to uh come up to
him and talk to him
[Music]
so yeah and recently um in the in the
um years after that uh wedding
you never met her ever again but
recently he's been dreaming about her
mother
[Music]
so the rest of it is um yeah up until
now he was never able to tell
that girl has real feelings uh
and he was holding back on it uh but he
don't he doesn't want to regret
it and have it end uh before him telling
her his feelings so he's thinking about
maybe like
apparently he's able to contact her
because he's saying he wants to
um have to like offer her to meet up
and hang out and then he wants to try
his best
and be brave
[Music]
oh
robot what
oh what
i didn't do anything is this the thing
like
i have before you don't
static noise
[Music]
see
oh
one second
[Music]
what what
what well at least it's fixed now okay
okay okay okay okay okay thank god thank
god
where did my bdm go though wait well i
can't hear my do you guys hear my museum
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
okay i understand because everyone keeps
on going on about
bringing sora's invite to the show but i
personally i
i was thinking like um she's like like
something i want to keep for a little
bit later
[Music]
m
um well she already agreed so maybe
sometime soon she will be on the live
talk show as well but
for now i'm more like i don't wanna i
don't wanna give you the pleasure of
seeing
so doesn't buy on my talk show just yet
it has to be a little bit later
um
i will translate all of your charms and
everything you're saying
into beautiful english language and let
them all know how amazing you are
final boss no i don't think i don't
think she really likes me
like um like
resp i guess i mean she's been saying
that she doesn't want to be seen as a
goddess
but i mean she is very special
so i want to keep this special
special guest for a very special moment
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
so yeah basically my advice to him was
uh to
never give up like it seems like
even if they don't have coptic now they
had like
kind of like i mean they were friends
before so she doesn't hate him
i suppose we don't know if that girl
ever had feelings for him
but she didn't hate him she gave him
like they hung out in school and they
met
again in a wedding and they they talk to
each other
and if he's really like if he really
wants to tell
this girl his feelings i think he should
go for it so go for it
but always keep in mind she might
turn you down but i think it's still
important like if it's really something
that you've been
that you've been having on your mind for
a long time then i think yes
go for it try it try your best and also
thank you for watching my streams
[Music]
yes
thank you but we only have like 20
minutes left so
let's see uh what do we have left what
do we have left
um let me get some of those shorter
questions
we can uh have some shorter answers as
well
what has been the most challenging thing
that you have had to overcome or
overcome since your debut
i think um my viewers my fans
know that i've been struggling a lot
and with confidence and um
very much with that so that is uh
definitely something i had to struggle
with
yes uh i mean
i think i think i have more confidence
now
than in the beginning i think you guys
definitely helped me with that
and i mean uh making stuff like making
my own song
and uh making holotalk become a reality
has definitely helped me
gain more confidence but also one thing
that is really really hard to overcome
is
uh not caring about people's opinions i
think that's a problem that not only me
but many of you probably have
uh i mean it's easy to ignore if it's
just one or two opinions
like if you're not like a public person
as much as
we in whole life are but if you are
someone that has a huge audience
there's gonna be a lot of opinions
a lot of opinions and ignoring i mean
i think i think even the haters
sometimes
have a point i mean they have a very
wrong way
of addressing those points but somewhere
in there
there could be some good criticism
to be picked up which is um
something that i personally think and i
wish i could ignore
them completely but in some way i i do
try to see some positive
criticism in the hateful words that they
spit out
i try and make some improvements on
myself as well but
but i have to remind myself that the
important thing is
to don't lose track of what i want to do
and who
i want to be so if it's something that i
completely don't agree with then yes i
will ignore it
and i will keep on being the person i
want to be
and i mean there's enough people here
and this is something i had i have to
realize and keep reminding myself
there's so many people here right now
and the 550k
subscribers that are my community
who appreciate who i am and who like me
for who i am
and don't want me to change anything now
there might be
many other people who don't like me the
way i am
but there's also enough people who like
me exactly the way i am
oh i'm not always that positive thinking
but i try to be i aspire to be more
positive so one thing i had to overcome
is my
my lack of confidence and caring too
much about people's opinions
i'm working on that i'm working on it
[Music]
but yeah thank you thank you all i have
to say
the kfp grill is my all you sweet people
out there
are are the reason why i can still do
this
i mean it's only been three months but
you know
like it's a it's a huge thing like
suddenly suddenly out of nowhere having
such a big audience is quite
overwhelming
even if it was only positive even then
it would be overwhelming but of course
it's always negative stuff as well
thank you i love you all thank you
i love you i love you
next question oh
kiara what is your favorite piece of
fanart that you've received these past
few months
oh i mean i generally like to
go through the art tag every day and
check out all the lovely arts you make
for me thank you all so much
it's so lovely so cute sword over all of
your arts
but you know i'm a big sucker for
mamaloni fan art
oh my gosh babaloni father holy macaroni
so good oh every time
or also um for example scotty
recently drew another fan out of me very
recently i think maybe the day before
yesterday or something and i retweeted
it
uh and i i really loved scotty's art for
a long long time
so i was very excited about that scotty
draws like a whole live
fan arts pretty much every day
[Music]
my
the source of of so many good thumbnails
for me
yuna is actually
she she did something very special for
me that i cannot show you yet but i will
show you this uh this month
top secret but i appreciate all of your
beautiful fantasy i would like to
mention all of the names but it's
impossible so i'm gonna
stop there but please please keep on
continue drawing kiana i'm very happy
about the artwork and it's like it
actually
really helps because uh for thumbnails
fan art is so good because if i keep on
using
this face it will get boring after a
while but the fact that makes it so much
more interesting some really awesome
thumbnails
are only possible because of your
amazing fan art everyone
hmm thank you
next question let's do as many as
possible we have like 12 minutes left
[Music]
me
this person is asking about uh if i went
to
if i went to like japanese festivals
in japan because in in summer they like
to do a lot of festivals with
fireworks you know how you guys see it
in the anime and you wear like your
yukata
do it and just stroll around and look at
the
look at that um look at all the
food and eat all the food and i've been
to
actually only two festivals
like summer festivals in japan even
though i would have expected to
go to many more but especially this year
there was absolutely no festival
and which was kind of lonely
[Music]
um
maybe next year um when i come back for
holidays or something
i get another chance to go to a summer
festival in japan
because they're really really nice
they're really crowded
which is uh not my favorite thing about
them
but i like dressing up with my female
friends and cute yukatas and doing each
other's hairstyles and stuff
yeah i'm taking cute photos
[Music]
time
yes
[Music]
unfortunately this summer absolutely no
summer festivals
[Music]
unfortunately
let's answer that one
nine minutes left speed run marshmallow
speed run
have you ever sent the super chat to
piccola yes
on my private am i not yeah
on my private account i can't use the
kiana account because it's like
obviously connected to cover and i will
be using your money
but yes i have a super chat
hi hi
it was before before i i became
who i am now
but i feel like the moment the moment
she read my name i was like
i was like she just said my name she
just said my name
i i'm like when i read your guys's super
chats
to me it's like i real i really want to
give you
like the biggest thanks ever i wish i
could shake your hands and give you hugs
i feel like only by reading your name
for a second and adding a thank you soon
after that i feel like i'm not doing
enough
but i guess i was also happy just by
having my name read out loud for a
second so
i hope i hope it's also good enough for
you guys
i wish i could thank you more than that
but yeah
okay there we go next question
wait that's uh she prepared something
for that question uh wait a second
uh next question
one second let me get that one
i prepared something okay
maybe that's the last question we can do
this again of course
hey kiara a kind of mean question from
one of
uh your kfb employees here as a as
employees of such a well-established
business
do we get any benefits packages of
course i'm sure all of us kfp
at kfb are happy to work here forever
but i thought it couldn't hurt to ask
well um recently
i've noticed some of you uh keep on
asking for more and more benefits and
you do not read the contract but
honestly of course i want to get i want
you guys to be happy
but i mean
you get what you signed but okay let me
make it obvious for you what you're
already receiving
okay there we go kfp
employee benefit package this is what
you're already getting okay so stop
complaining now
huge imaginary girlfriend to watch
movies with we have a movie once along
and one and a half hours
we're watching a lot of the rings
together i will come help you
if you have beef with someone and i will
beat them up either with my fire
or with my sword and shield and you can
also get
unlimited chicken nuggets for life i you
just i mean if you're working there
you just take them out of the freezer
fry yourself some chicken nuggets and
take them home
i do not care we have more than enough
don't waste the food okay german lessons
whenever i feel like it
but you better do your homework and
entertainment gaming kind of look at
tangents almost
every day i mean what else do you
[\h__\h] want
what is it what else what else what else
can i give to you aren't you already
happy haven't you already reached
maximum happiness with that
i mean i don't know how else to make you
happy
stop complaining
[Laughter]
about
thank me for being your imaginary
girlfriend to watch movies with
chicken nuggets well just go to work for
god's sake and take them out of the
freezer
just take them out of the freezer and
fry them
this is that you can also have burgers
or whatever phoenix burger young burger
whatever you want just eat whatever we
have in
in store you can have all of it
[Music]
no if frozen no thank you to frozen
excuse me
use your brain you can fry the frozen
nuggets and then you can eat them then
they're not frozen anymore not telling
you to eat the frozen nuggets
[Laughter]
thank you for the oh there we go here
are the members
wait i didn't plan to wow see these guys
these guys seem
seem like that was convincing apparently
that was convincing the kfp employee
benefit package seems very convincing
it's actually true everything that's
written on there is true except the
except maybe the chicken nugget no no
let's say it's true it's everything here
is true thank you for the memberships
talk to your advertising okay enjoy the
kfb employee benefits package you are
welcome
and you get the kfb employee benefit
package
and you'll get the benefits kp employee
benefit package and you'll get a kfc
employee benefit package if you get a
perfect
[Music]
wow
thank you for the memberships
i did not expect so many members to join
now
thank you guys thank you for joining me
welcome new eggs welcome welcome welcome
there was one more um and one more uh
question that just came up into my head
i didn't manage to uh uh
show it to you guys but someone asked if
we can discuss
that members will be eaten after two
years
well i'll we can talk about it
once we reach that point if if kfb still
exists in two years then we can discuss
it whether or not i will eat you or not
or i will sell you or not but for now
the goal is to become
food oh my god thank you for all the
memberships
thank you oh my god what's going on so
many green memberships oh my god
wow wow wow wow wow wow guys thank you
thank you
holy holy thank you guys so much
wow
and uh with that we have to end the
stream thank you guys so much for coming
today we're having
as i said we're having a member watching
like thank you guys oh my god all the
memberships
enjoy the kf employee perfect package
enjoy it
uh eat all the chicken nuggets you can i
don't care you'll get fat but that's
your decision let's be fat together
so yeah after this says whole life
indonesia second generation debut stream
from rain
rainy town and let's watch it all
together and after that i have um
members only moving on
remember
[Music]
thank you for coming thank you for all
the questions sorry for not
uh being able to pick many of you but uh
we can do this again
thank you for all the memberships
oh my god stokes
see i will i never want to hear any of
you complain ever again
time to watch the debut together with my
generation mates no i've english discord
bye bye hope you're jealous
[Music]
foreign