[Music]
hello
hello it's one year hello
[Music]
i'm nervous
and excited and nervous if we have a
long day ahead of us
full 12 hours of things happening
hello
hello thank you everyone that's all i
can say thank you just thank you just
thank you
i'm sure we'll get into it at some point
in the street but i've been seeing all
your amazing messages in the chat and i
appreciate it so thank you very much
today is the
12 hour marathon stream in celebration
of one year of streaming wow
i'm gonna be serving for 12 whole hours
today we have a packed schedule full of
bunch of different things we're
basically doing something new every hour
just about
so yeah i think that will keep things
keep things fresh keep things
interesting keep things moving
[Music]
um but first before we get into our
schedule don't die on us
i won't probably i'm a little bit
worried
i
couldn't sleep very well last night
because i was too excited and i kept
waking up every few hours of being like
oh is it time to stream yet is it time
to stream yet
but now it's time oh gosh and we're here
for 12 hours oh gosh i hope i'm not dead
by the end of it
i tried to eat before the stream but
i don't normally eat at this time so it
was kind of a struggle to
get the food down
but i managed to eat a little bit i have
more food that i can eat later
if i need it but i don't like to eat on
stream
don't worry if i don't eat much uh cause
i'll eat after the stream
i'm sure the adrenaline will keep me
moving
i do have water we'll also do lots of
breaks i feel like every hour i need to
stand up and stretch and maybe do some
squats or something
but first first first before we get into
things i have something to show you
what could it be
what could i have to show you
let's take a look
if we just go over here
[Music]
look it's my very own bedroom
it's my own bedroom
my very own
no one else but mine
my own custom bedroom
it was made by 7m digital and they did a
great job on it
oh i feel like i'm in the way
do you want to see it
without me
in the way
but a mom see look i have so many
plushies
big plushie collection can you spot all
the easter eggs
[Music]
look i even have my very own animal
crossing switch
very important
yeah look you can see my cute forest
outside my cute little cottage in the
forest
yeah
thank you very much seven mm digital for
making this for me it turned out amazing
i'm very happy it's very cute and now i
have my own house
finally i no longer have to just sit in
the green void or that beach house that
um i don't really own a lot of people go
there
but this one's all mine
[Music]
don't burn it down i won't come on that
happened one time that was like two days
after debut
i have changed have i not
[Music]
um
public beach house it is it's like the
rental beach house
that's fine though
yeah i really like it i can put the chat
up too but
i didn't want to block
everything
also i could put some pictures in this
frame over here but i didn't know what
to put in it yet
i have to figure out something to put
there
i'll figure something out
[Music]
but yeah okay uh first up on our
schedule
is
spore
because spore was the first game i ever
played
for you
they're singing today there is it's
gonna be unarchived though
so yes the void of this stream will only
be 11 hours
because last one hour is going to be
an archived singing uh i think i have it
set up
so that this stream automatically will
redirect into that stream at the time
but we'll see
i would i did want to do a japanese
karaoke but i
was not feeling confident
so we're doing english instead
[Music]
all right all right we're not gonna
return to not pickle though we're gonna
do something different i have an idea
but
um
is it okay if i just mess around in the
the character creator is that fine
because we don't have too long of sport
i kind of just want to
mess around in the character creator
[Music]
totally fine okay i have an idea
also i need to look up the
spore cheat codes
oh you probably can't hear yet but this
board music just started and it was
scary
um there's like a way to unlock
everything right
um
oh
there's a lot of cheat codes
um
cheating
always
um
well let's just see i guess
okay let's go
i'm sorry to leave this beautiful room
so soon
but we must play spore
um
okay
i was having trouble getting spore to
work properly as always
i think everyone is
it might be in like
480p but that's fine
um
so loud
these flutes
immediately my
hat's died okay
oh try i should put the photo
sensitivity warning up although i think
it will be okay because i'm using
a certain mode
that i don't think will cause the
graphical
glitches
i'll put up just in case
um
where can i put this
oh
i don't know if this is big enough
people i know for a fact that no one
reads the text that's on the screen
unless you make it like this
no one's going to read it even if you
make it like this people might not read
it
okay
um
[Music]
i want to do creature creator
please
oh baby
yeah my screen is really small my sport
window
it might be
480p
oh my gosh the music it's so good is it
loud
hold on i need i need to get a reference
image but i don't want to spoil what i'm
making yet
i'll just start look at this shape that
we got
it's kind of
kind of shapely right off the bat
okay spoiler okay spore
hold on but i don't want this
um it's so small
my window whenever i had it at the full
size it was really like i changed the
resolution but it seems like the
resolution did not change
i don't know this is going to work i
want to zoom in i feel like i'm looking
at the tiny screen
[Music]
um
oh
what have i done
why did that happen
hold on
hold on i just want this to be good so
far it's not good
[Music]
i don't know if this is gonna work
like my image
the sport crater might be a bit limited
in its scope
we'll see what we can do okay
[Music]
um
let's put some legs on
that was one of you
oh yeah i have the dlc
the insect legs
non-grasshopper
um
[Music]
but i think we just want this
it's too
too big though
different feet
hold on
be smaller please
oh
geez what's this
these are weird oh no
please
stand straight oh no
undo
oh geez
[Music]
wait there's a way to do this i forgot i
remember someone once told me does
anyone remember
the the magical keybinds that make you
only move in one direction
[Music]
any spore geniuses in the chat
is it shift
[Music]
oh i think it is shift
oh maybe
[Music]
maybe not
is it not possible
the anime girl
legs
[Music]
oh all this copy
control
i think does nothing
oh my goodness
that's fine maybe anime
is fine
um
[Music]
so far so good
can you tell what i'm making yet
we need some arms
[Music]
oh geez
but not the arms like this
[Music]
hmm
um
it's a little bit muscular
maybe we need these arms
his arms are a little
less defined
um
[Music]
but not so long
we're creating a proportionate creature
here hold on
very proportionate
[Music]
um
great oh
get the hands
um do we want hands
i mean hands are kind of necessary oh
that's perfect
whatever these are is perfect
oh how cute
cute little hands
they're good
okay can you stand up straight
yes good
good posture is important especially
when you're doing 12 hour stream
[Music]
okay
see the head is wrong
but i don't think we can make the head
right
[Music]
maybe
wait it looks like that one scp
you
know can't be shorter
i need like legs that have one less
joint
can you do that
you know they're like folded in on
themselves
i wish to create a very small creature
[Music]
you can take off portions of limbs how
how
please help me
spore geniuses
[Music]
um
i guess we need a face this is where
it's going to get really cursed
control or
off that's coffee
why are you floating
oh my gosh
stop floating
it really looks like an scp i mean i
guess that's fine
we have cute eyes right
[Music]
what the heck
what
that's not what i thought that was going
to mean
oh wow
[Music]
is that cute
um
hubba hubba
oh
when she gives you that look
[Music]
what's this one
i think hubba hubba is good
[Music]
more like this
yes
[Music]
very good
um do we have a mouth oh geez the mouth
is also
going to be a sore spot
um
i can't tell if these are supposed to be
the cute mouths or the scary mouths i
guess this is cute
[Music]
that's cute
oh wait this is actually cute
this is actually cute why do i like this
creature suddenly
um
it's like a parrot
i thought it was gonna be like a scary
fish oh no
[Music]
um
it's not quite
right oh
that's an interesting idea
uh-huh
is there a nose
well i don't really need a nose i guess
it's interesting
um
this will be good oh wait how do you
break symmetry again
[Music]
not copy
oh
should i just look it up
hold a
[Music]
ah
yes
oh no i'm sorry i'm lagging
oh oh oh
will the stream be okay will the stream
survive
i don't know
[Music]
this is perfect
no
it looks like um
sables evolution
[Music]
supports two and we know
not this game from 2005
when does four come out
why am i lag
why
can i fix this
[Music]
i don't know
sometimes it just happens
we just have one funnel per second
okay
now this we also need
i mean at this point you must know what
i'm creating right
if you didn't before
this sort of gives it away right
um
so maybe we can get the reference image
on the screen
[Music]
because i need it
oh there she is okay now we can fix this
because we can look at how it's supposed
to
look and honestly it looks nothing like
this so far
three phones on the screen
how come only one phone is lagging
[Music]
can i fix this
i don't know if i can fix this
sometimes it just happens
i don't think it's my computer
[Music]
we can try to fix it
how was i sitting before
like this
oh
not fixed
it looked better for one second and then
as soon as i turned the screen it's
worse
i don't think it's my pc but
[Music]
my computer's only added 40
cpu that doesn't seem that bad
only 40 cpu 40 gpu but we cannot spare
any more frames
i didn't restart my phone already though
i already started before the stream
should i restart it again i don't think
it's gonna fix it
but we can try i suppose
[Music]
oh no i've picked a bad
frame to
freeze on oh
oh i'm still moving haunted by then
by the magic of
dying phone
[Music]
okay um
this creature is very beautiful
needs more hair though
what do we use for hair this
[Music]
maybe
they're cute
um
oh there we go
beautiful long hair
[Music]
looking like a pineapple
little bit of pineappley
[Music]
the noises
i feel like the hair should be
i don't know
[Music]
oh no
don't do the splits
get back to the ground
the arms are just getting longer and
longer
there
hold on can i unfreeze please
[Music]
please
maybe
[Music]
okay we'll see if it's better now it
looks better for one second
but i did restart it before the street
right before the stream okay um
more hair
what should we use for hair
is this good
hair i cannot be bald
at the top
no
wide fondant baldness
yes perfect it really just looks like
there's a bunch of plants growing out of
my
head though
is also not what i want
who's coffee get coffee
why both spot do you see this
oh i have a classic bald spot
oh no
um oh no now i have a beard
[Music]
we can fix this
um
there we go
[Music]
now this is hair
luscious hair
oh my gosh it's like the that
dinosaur from jurassic park well it's
probably from real life too
and dinosaur from real life
it puffs out
perfect beautiful
[Music]
beautiful
wow
cute creature okay is there a flower
[Music]
dead the spikes
what's this
twiggy
[Music]
oh it's like the the more detailed
version
[Applause]
whiskers
oh my gosh like a catfish
i don't think we need those
there's a flower i think
i feel like i'm blind here right here
oh
[Music]
oh no
this one please
adorable very cute
um
[Music]
maybe we need one to cover in the bald
spot on the top
that's good right it's like pikmin
[Music]
it's a pokemon
no this is me
can i have more hair
[Music]
um
that's great
oh it kind of reminds me of like bug
wings actually
now that i thought of that it's kind of
freaking me out
[Music]
oh not the bug wings
like a roach
[Music]
you see what i see
lots of beautiful hair though
looking perfect
could use a little more hair at the top
i think
[Music]
yeah yes
excellent
[Music]
maybe a cute leaf
oops
to go along with the horns
oh they're like ears that's kind of cute
looks like a cronie
where do you get that from
um
oh i'm running out of money i need my
cheat code
i need
whoa
we're hacking
thank you
i used to do this as a kid and i really
didn't feel like i was hacking
even though it's literally programmed
into the game
um we need to put clothes on her but
really you're supposed to do that in the
other stage
can we bring this creature to the other
stage
to to clothe her she's a bit indecent
right now we need to
color her too we can
okay
does she need any other
other base features i always give them
wings so they can fly
[Music]
head wings
like louie
oh she doesn't have feet does she
i mean why fonda doesn't have feet does
she need feet
can we take her for a test run
she can move sort of
oh oh oh oh oh
hold on let's color her
[Applause]
[Music]
this part might get a little sensitive
but don't worry about it
like a barbie
it's like barbies isn't there one that's
like skin
actually aren't there some like
disgusting ones
what is this is this one like skin
is this one like hair
that looks so bad
i'm so bad
[Music]
um
is one of these supposed to be skin
[Music]
in fur
oh she looks like a
moss monster
he's kind of cute actually
[Music]
oh yeah these are the creepy and cute
ones
i can't tell what they're supposed to be
what's
[Music]
uh this don't know
oh is this supposed to be like that game
little big planet
you know
um
[Music]
is this one like shiny oh my god it's so
shiny
that's great that's perfect
can we change like the hair color though
is this the hair
oh that's the flower
the flower should be like white or like
light yellow
[Music]
okay
can we change the hair
[Music]
please be the hair
oh
[Music]
it's not the hair
does the hair have to be the same color
as the flesh
she looks emo now
she looks goth now
um
we could do like a little pink
little cute pink
pink lipsticks oh very cute
[Music]
can we not change the hair
is there no way
to do such a thing
oh that's weird
does this one have creepy parts too
are those veins oh gross we really are
making a cp
can we make like blue veins
ew
[Music]
this is graphic this is like true crap
it's really too graphic
[Music]
oh my goodness
so edgy
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't think i had this oh it's like a
spine
i don't think i had these parts when i'm
playing before
wait is this a belly button hold on
oh
two belly buttons
i thought this was gonna be a cute belly
button
[Music]
only one
[Applause]
what's this
hexagon
nice hexagons
i'm scared to click on these i feel like
i'm gonna get banned but it's just spore
it's only spore okay
it's a game made for children
[Music]
this really doesn't change the hair
color
hey exactly it's just nature
it's just nature
is there anything creepy here oh it can
be patchwork
[Music]
oh
that cute or creepy it's kind of cute
like a little doll
what's this
um
i don't like it i don't like it i don't
like it i don't like it
i don't like most of these
[Music]
okay polka dots
very nice
oh this one looks like stitches
[Music]
oh cute a little belly oh you can make a
little teddy bear
that's cute
maybe should she just be green
[Music]
that's pretty cute
maybe she should just be green
the flesh color was too cursed
oh is she crying
that's kind of cute
[Music]
cute
does she need feet
oh my gosh she's doing the side step
she's so shiny
oh wow
just look how she moves
does she
this is dance this is the actual wide
fauna dance
it's real
[Music]
oh
what is that she have a hole in her face
this makes me very uncomfortable
stomp
oh break it down
it down
hot foot
[Music]
i think we should give her feet
um
are there any cute feet here
[Music]
whoa
it's actually kind of cute
um
but maybe something different
oh my gosh these are little little
stompers
[Music]
but we could just do
do this
i think
yeah
[Music]
these are basically my feet
they go
what are these noises
oh she likes you
she likes you
oh
[Music]
um
is she good
this is wide oh no no
the fauna
the wisest
of them all
she ripping or is that someone else
did we do it
[Music]
can we put clothes on her
oh there's not pickles
not pickle is still alive
okay we have to do this fast oh no did i
freeze again oh my goodness
[Music]
is that gonna be a theme for today
hello
um
why did her voice become so deep
[Music]
it's cuter
that's good okay
nice skirt
um is there a shirt
[Music]
wait this is supposed to be the shirt
this is chest
i don't know about that
[Music]
maybe this
um
patting your chest there a little bit
that's okay
[Music]
and then like suspenders in the back
is this good what kind of shoulders
[Music]
that's kind of good
she looks like she's ready for battle
[Music]
why the noises
why why would this creature make these
noises
i don't think this creature would make
these noises
she's like
[Music]
please please
symbol
[Music]
a mustache
no no no
[Music]
hearty is that a beard oh i like the
beard
[Music]
now the voice makes sense
oh
[Music]
there you go
i know she's like a dwarf we don't need
that
[Music]
can we color their clothes oh
what is this
complete style no no no
is this for the clothes only
wait no it's not
can we not color them individually
[Music]
i just want them to be blue
that's okay
[Music]
i think
ancient fauna
yes this is how i looked
back in the day
[Music]
this is perfect i think
so civilized
can you still dance
oh yeah
oh yeah let's see that red animation
really putting your head into it
um
[Music]
oh no i don't like this i don't like the
sound
you're supposed to be cute wide fauna
when did you become so
so burly
is this gap my way
is this the kind of gap louie that you
love
[Music]
she's just like me
happy
[Music]
that game was always so cursed to me
what have we done remember when she was
a creature and she just went like that
[Music]
oh my gosh
you don't have to put the grunts in
there
i'm scared i'm scared
the back flip
hey bro
what happened to that voice the voice
like music to my ears
the squat
the slaps
stop this stop this wide fauna
stomp
hot foot
hippity hop
oh where did your neck go
did we look at all of them
[Music]
oh wait oh
what this one's called hey baby and does
this not look like a peach i'm kind of
disappointed
this is not what i thought this pose
would be
hey baby with the peach
come on
give us some fan service
[Music]
only in here flex oh i guess they're all
fruits aren't they
this one's making it
happy
[Music]
i oh like sad
i really like sad
oh my goodness
the casper the sad gasps
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my goodness
oh here you go here you go
saplings this one's for you
[Music]
wow
she likes you
she loves thanks
she likes what she sees
oh do you like her bag do you want to
take her on the date
[Music]
you show up at her house to pick her up
for her dates
[Music]
energy
oh my goodness
[Music]
all right all right all right
i think i think we have achieved our
goal in spore
what a baddie for real look at her
look at her makeup
hmm
all right
[Music]
just like old times
never change spore never change
oh
i just sound scary
okay okay
i wanna go back here for a second
next game
we are one hour in
so far so good
and next up is
my old favorite
none other than getting over it
[Music]
how do i launch getting over it also i
don't remember if i'm mentioning it but
prepare for scuff today there will
certainly be
much scuff all of this stuff in fact
[Music]
um
of the extreme variety
we love scuff
12 hours of pure scuff
[Music]
okay i think getting over it still works
that's good
i still have my golden pot
but hold on i think
[Music]
i might have to make a
slight change of plans
[Music]
oh
well i just have to check if i can
get a game on my switch instead of pc
[Music]
oh
hold on sorry for hours and getting over
it for a second
hold on please wait
[Music]
to try to fix scuff yes for one of the
collabs later
we might need to play the game on the
switch instead
[Music]
um
but it's actually on sale right now on
the switch
so that's convenient
[Music]
i'm getting it
i think this will work better anyway
because i was having problems with it
too
yeah uno
uno
okay
[Music]
you have uno on the switch you are games
on your phones
hold on now i have to i have to ping
people now
[Music]
okay
and everyone it is time to play you uno
on the switch not yet okay
okay
thank you for waiting
um
it's time
to play getting over it
maybe
if the game will work
yes it will work
hold on
[Music]
oh and it's cut off
look i promised scuff did i oh wait we
need music don't we
i mean into music
there
today i am providing scuff of the
finest variety
there we go
okay i haven't played this game since
the last time i played it on stream
which i don't even remember when that
was
we'll see if i still got it
oh
it seems like not
i'm not going to reset because this is
the warm-up run
oh it feels good to be back though
even though i didn't forget how to play
how many times can we beat this game in
one hour
probably zero because i'll spend the
whole time resetting to try to get a pb
oh no
don't
reset oops
i remember how to play the chimney
actually
i do
it's a good thing i'm playing this early
before my brain completely deteriorates
later on
because i remember i think the only ooh
12 hour stream i've done
it wasn't mine getting over in stream
right
it was about 12 hours
when i got the golden pot and i was
definitely losing my mind
by the end of that stream
but that's why we're not doing 12 hours
of one game again
because that's kind of
mind numbing
oh no especially if it's getting over it
maybe like 12 hours of skyrim wouldn't
be fine but
like minecraft even but
12 hours i'm getting rid of doing the
same thing over and over again for 12
hours
oh no
my slide skip
please
i remember how to play this game
oh almost
yeah at least i had my oh
my friends at the end to help me
survive because they're playing jump
king i want to play jump king again too
there's so many games i want to play
though
this stream is like 12 hours of
games we've played before mostly but
[Music]
we could have a
stream where i play a bunch of games
that i've been meaning to play well i
should do that stream where i finish all
the games that i started and never
finished
okay
like sucker for love in hypno space
outlaw and
i'm sure there are others
where am i
where am i i'm at ikea
oh
many creams hot butter ice cream
take the hot butter mix it with ice
cream
going
i'm climbing
we're getting over it
oh we're getting jump scared
that was kind of scary
i almost fell off the
church there
that oh was really fast though
that orange hell
almost
i remember watching me do this part
and do the anvil i hate the anvil
apparently i'm not the only one
who hates the anvil
anvil is the run killer
okay
[Music]
i know mummy is really close though
she's gonna beat it
[Music]
without a doubt
i'm scared i'm scared i'm gonna launch
myself hold on
please
no launch please
[Music]
okay
oh bucket please
oh man it feels good to play this game
again
this game is like i know
i know the meme is like the controls are
so bad
and like that's why it's frustrating
but once you like come to understand
them oh
it's so satisfying
it's like i don't know
kind of comforting in a way
don't speak too soon though
maybe it's also because i'm not playing
for pb right now
oh i'm just playing for fun
i had no goals for this one hour oh
no for this one hour of getting over it
my only goal is to play in for one hour
get one hour closer to finishing the 12
hour marathon
[Music]
oh no i'm on the bucket
this is fine
it's not fine
ouch
though i want the pb i don't today
because then i'll get stressed but i'm
just having fun playing this game that i
love again
and i know i'm really out of practice so
like i got that pb
oh no
i had my my peak getting over at
performance
but that was months ago
i'm all washed up now
we're just playing for fun
oh
i should keep track though
of how many wins i get in one hour
so far we're looking at zero
please ice mountain light me up
i'm still pretty bad at ice mountain
that's what i'm learning oh no
it's slippery
i don't want to fall anymore
i want to climb
i want to fly away
oh
[Music]
should i no
[Applause]
should i remember where the notches are
i'm playing too fast
far too fast now
oh my gosh playing fast is fun though
see
you can fling yourself like that
even though you run the risk of flinging
yourself all the way to the bottom
[Music]
okay space
okay tower
[Music]
the tower is not hard but
somehow it is
oh
it's just cause you're almost oh no to
the end i think
but how can you not listen to this
soothing bossa nova oh no
and just to feel at ease
i don't want to be here
no i didn't want to be there
see i'm rusty
[Music]
it's been too long
no longer getting over in master
should i get into getting over it again
should i become
get a sub two minute time
[Music]
what
i don't know how that happened
i should
should i finally achieve my well we're
gonna watch it later my debut goal of
like becoming a speedrunner
well minecraft speed ones didn't really
happen that much
because it turns out they're hard and
you have to learn a lot
oh no
but maybe i could learn getting over it
but in general speed running is really
hard oh
it takes a lot of time and i don't think
that's new information for anybody
[Music]
oh we're going we're going slowly but
we're going
i'll take it
oh no
take me back please please
oh
please please
i hate this part
oh still bad at this part
some things never change
don't just tell me i don't want to know
11 minutes all right
[Music]
next run
well let me check something
um
okay
one win
count them
[Music]
oh so i got my sub 5 minute but
the real game starts after that i feel
like
i'm already this is already really slow
you know
for like sub oops too
and then you have the
well i think pretty much it's just like
one person
who holds the world record and is still
going for
a um
sub
one minutes time oh
cause there's the the tool assisted
speed run which is like 45 seconds i
think
but the human time is like one minute
and one second or something
which is crazy
well but when will
humanity surpass the tools we'll
probably never supposed to pass the tool
assistant just because that's how it
works but
okay this chimney way worse than the
first time
i don't know what it is about this game
that's just really satisfying to me oops
i think that's what cali said about
jump king we were talking about it a
long time ago
she said like at first you fail a lot
but you get better
each time you fail
can i do tub jump
i don't think so
um
[Music]
and then eventually you
oh
oops
what was i gonna say eventually you
learned that you are in control of your
own actions
maybe that's what's satisfying
something like that
[Music]
oh
i knew that was gonna happen it's cause
i got nervous as soon as i approached
orange hell i got nervous
[Music]
you can't be getting nervous
i have nothing to be nervous about
because it's not even that hard
if you don't think about it you'll do
fine
also did you notice that my pot looked
kind of like a mango
with the orange the golden orange
i'll point it out again when we get back
there
it looks like a mango
ah
slippery hammer
it's so slippery at this part
okay good chimney
that was pretty good to me
yup use your brain
that was kind of funny
[Music]
pump
i should learn to do slides get faster
too
i'm still like lining it up every time
but
really i should just learn to do it
i don't know it's gonna be really hard
if i do
learn to speedrun this game more
it's been pretty fun let's see look it's
mango it doesn't look like a mango
this golden red
orange mango potato
[Music]
not again
i'm panicking
on the inside
it's been pretty fun to learn to
speedrun this game so far but
i think
i'll have to like really
grind you know
no my child died
again please
[Music]
um
okay
our modernity settings are different no
not right now only
only in the ikea
only an orange hell with the orange
light
it looks like a mango you know how
mangoes are like
yellow and then they become like orangey
red on the outside
or like those parrots oops i forget
which ones
i feel like there's a famous parrot like
that named
mango even
[Music]
mangoes are delicious i forgot where i
ranked them on my food list
[Music]
they better have been at least eight's
here
because they're good
[Music]
i am a fan of tropical fruits especially
whoa
whoa that's not how i usually do that
section
they should be s yeah but i don't know
because i feel like you have to keep the
sanctity of st you're only reserved for
like the best
three fruits you know
because you guys could say that
everything should be asked here
which is nice like this is a good
positive attitude to have but
i don't know i'm not trying to spare the
feelings of every fruit i mean fruits
are delicious in general but
that doesn't mean you cannot pit them
against each other
and find out which is superior
[Music]
i will do just that
orange
ft here
see it's like oranges are not like an f
to your food
like obviously
it's just that like compared to other
fruits
they're not as good as the other fruits
but fruits in general are really good
food you know
actually do you know what
i can't say this word well i can say it
but
you're gonna laugh but it's not what do
you think it is okay it's a real
food
it's called
i can't say it i can't say it i know i
know that it's
i know what your reaction is gonna be
hold on you have to be mature it's a
real food
um
i feel like i'm gonna say it wrong but i
don't know how else you say it
and
s pic
you know
it's like a savory jello basically and
you can put stuff inside like liver
or eggs or something
that is an f-tier food
okay sorry probably it can be good i
don't know i've never had one but
uh
just like the thought of like savory
meat jello is i don't know
with my liver inside it
[Music]
doesn't sound that good to me
and it's served cold too
i think um
it was really popular
in the united states in like the 50s
they were putting everything in jell-o
for some reason
um
i don't think everything needs to be put
in i mean you guys know how i feel about
jello in general
i guess i guess it's already been known
i did not rank jello very highly
but yeah that is like an f-tier foot
well i don't know i feel bad saying that
because i've never tried it and i
probably never will try it well because
it's made from like meets normally
um
but you know like compared to that
oranges are of course
delicious
[Music]
i watch this video of someone making one
and i don't know it just seems like a
waste
because he made this delicious broth
with like a ton of like
meat and veggies in it so you know it
would have been like a delicious
flavorful broth you could use that for
so many things like a soup or
i don't know what else you use broth for
probably many delicious things you
couldn't even just drink it on its own
and probably be yummy but
but then he turned it into jello me to
jello
and of course he probably spent like
hours boiling it all you know
putting like herbs inside it
no
[Music]
just like if we're gonna go through the
effort of making this delicious broth i
feel like you should just use the broth
and not turn it into meat jello
but i don't know
i've never had it maybe it's good
or maybe at least there's a good version
of it somewhere
oops oops
give me a hub
you're dumb ice mountain letting me up
i shouldn't yell at the ice mountain no
oh shoot oh shoot
this is my karma for yelling at the ice
mountain
oh my gosh it is it's my karma
karmic justice has been served
first i talked trash about aspect and
now
i hate the way this feels this actually
makes me feel
claustrophobic
i don't know if that's silly but like
it's oh my gosh it's cuz i like i can't
move freely
it makes me feel claustrophobic
for real oh my gosh i hate it i hate it
i can't touch my mouse
i want to reset but i don't want to
reset because we've only beaten it once
please
ah i hate it i have to keep
my mouth i don't know why it gives me
like a physically bad
sensation
i don't know okay
i'm not making this up it actually
triggers my claustrophobia
this part
you're feeling good too
oh i have to like massage my arm to
remember that i can actually move
i'm real human
are you the same
oh i hate it i hate the i hate the way
this feels
but thinking about it is just making it
worse
oh no
please
oh okay
oh my goodness i'm freed
please don't do that again
oh my goodness oh my goodness
oh now i like my arm feels all weird
i think i was tensing it up too much
when getting over it becomes way too
serious
no
i was so close
[Music]
no
happy anniversary thank you
thank you i'm happy i can't believe it
though i mean i keep saying this but it
really doesn't feel like one year at all
i don't know then when i look back
we're gonna watch the debut
later today oops
i'm kind of scared because i know
i mentioned oh my gosh i need to beat
this
i mentioned this before but um
i didn't feel like i did too bad in my
debut like i remember after it was over
i was like yeah that was pretty good you
know
i was satisfied but now i feel like i'm
gonna watch and i'm gonna be like oh my
god you're why are you so shy why are
you so
nervous
why are you doing that
why did you think that was a good idea
at the time
we're freed
oh no
right under the rock
really
no i don't want to go this way
okay it's fine
it's fine
also i got a bug bite on my arm and it
itches i don't like it wait this was
like the same length as the first one
actually my mom bought me this thing i
think it's literally called the bug bite
thing
and it's supposed to like
uh suction
the
the saliva out of like the mosquito
saliva out of the bug bite
and make it not itch
i don't know where it is i lost it
i'm sure it's somewhere
it does not work really
but my mom said it worked
fake but really i don't think it's fake
if you use it right after you get bit
it makes sense to me
because the saliva is what causes the
reaction
and then she uses a vacuum to suck it
out
yeah you have to use it right after you
get bit i think
[Music]
i think it works i mean you know in all
those movies and stuff they always like
suck the snake venom out
you know
oh no
i was bit by a venomous snake
its venom is so lethal i will surely die
unless
[Music]
and then in the anime they put the
finger in the mouth they always do that
i always thought that was weird
like when
when an anime pricks their finger
and then they're like oh
my finger
is bleeding
and then someone else is like here let
me help you and they stick their finger
in their mouth
i don't know i don't think you should do
that
there's some germs in your mouth like i
don't know what that's supposed to
accomplish
i don't know i mean i guess it's just
fan service but i don't know
it's how you get an infection i think
[Music]
the real romance would be
if someone pulls out some
um
saline solution
and sprays your finger down with that
and then gives you a band-aid
that is true romance
not whatever this sticking fingering
mouth is
he has some neosporin maybe
[Music]
i guess maybe it's just like flirting
imagine
i don't know imagine you heard your
finger and then someone just takes that
as an opportunity to flirt with you
though
i guess if it's just a paper cut it's
probably okay but
i would be mad if i were like actually
injured
now is not the time
yeah now's my chance
she's bleeding now's my chance
i don't know
[Music]
that was awful did they actually do that
in real life does anyone do that
is that just an anime thing
i don't know
then the finger in mouth
i guess it's like to stop the bleeding i
don't know that
it's weird it's weird
drinking the blood
there are other ways you can stop the
bleeding like applying light pressure
with let's say a band-aid or like your
shirt maybe or even just
your hand
i don't know
a thing from before modern medicine
yeah when they use like leeches and
stuff
oh no oh no
i'm so sad
i mean if you can use a leech
then sure why not
why not use a mouth
is my bug bite thing just the modern day
equivalent of a leech
at least it's more sanitary
maybe
are leashes unsanitary they feel like
they would be
i mean who knows
where the leeches i mean don't they come
from like
[Music]
creepy lakes and stuff
i want to read the chat to see what
you're saying about leeches but i have
to focus or i'll fall
again
oh no
oh no would you be
how would you feel if you went to the
doctor and the doctor just
brought out a
bucket of leeches and was like here you
go
where would you draw the line
of the weird things your doctor could
bring out before you are like no thank
you
you might try it once
well what about like those fish that
eats the dead skin off your feet
i've never tried those it kind of freaks
me out
this sounds fun those are popular ah
kind of scares me
feeding the fish with your dead
foot skin i don't know
she's kind of creepy to think about
you know
no
[Music]
the rock
i'm missing them i keep scratching my
arm
now that i know i'm scratching it's
going to be itching
all stream
all 12 hours
freedom
that was faster right yeah seven minutes
the fish that nibble your feet don't
actually do that naturally
really
oh no
poor fish
that's sad that's gross though
oh
i don't like it
okay
was that two
or no that was three i can't count three
wins
piranhas do that
do they
i know in movies like piranhas are
really scary but
i mean i don't know
don't most fish
wouldn't most fish eat you if given the
opportunity
i don't know
is it cause piranhas have really sharp
teeth
will they actually like
swarm you
i don't think they do right i think
that's just a movie thing
but they might bite you i guess
um
if they're hungry if you're bleeding
really
i thought that's a myth that sounds too
dramatic to be real
like sharks you know
like they don't actually like smell
human blood and like come running like
oh
i've always wanted to eat a human
fish blood maybe though
[Music]
well didn't mark roman do a video on
that
and they tested it
and the shark did prefer the fish blood
[Music]
taste bad apparently i mean i can see
that if you spend your whole life in the
ocean eating sea creatures
like mostly fish
i can see
the land creature would taste bad
like how a lot of people don't like the
taste of fish like fishy fish
[Music]
we're going
especially with our lotions and sprays
through all that waterproof sunscreen
probably not delicious at all
i don't know maybe the coconut likes the
pina colada suntan oil
dang it
we'll get a taste
that's my bad b movie idea right there
shark who has grown
to have a taste for
pina colada suntan
oil
people can't figure out why some people
on the beach are
i'm being brutally attacked and eaten
but some are spared
and there's like a little
old lady on the beach and like a creepy
little hut and she sells the pina colada
suntan oil
and she knows exactly what she's doing
[Music]
and she's actually like an evil witch
and she digs up the bones that the
sharks eat from the bottom of the ocean
to use for fiendish purposes
there you go free movie idea feel free
to take that one
if we have any
indie filmmakers here
that one's free you don't even have to
credit me
in fact please don't
but do tag me on twitter when it's done
i want to watch it do a watch
sounds like snakes on a plane
well there's a plot of snakes on a plane
i only know that there's like you know
well snakes on a plane
but that's pretty much all i know
[Music]
is there actually
a villain in that movie who's like
putting snakes on a plane that's so
funny
because like snakes on a plane would not
be a problem at all
like what are the snakes gonna do
they're not gonna do anything they're
probably terrified
i don't know
maybe if they're like super venomous i
guess that would be pretty bad
i guess if people start panicking then
that's also going to be a problem
snakes are evil there are
cause i mean a human verse is a snake
the humans oh no no
i'm so bad now the human is pretty much
always going to win you know
i feel like even the really big snakes
you know well like they can be really
powerful but
it's like it's only really dangerous if
you don't fight back you know
oh if you like let the snake completely
wrap itself around you
also i think
even like the biggest of snakes humans
are too big
to for them to eat so they probably
won't try but maybe they will i guess
it's happened before
i don't know i'm trying to imagine like
oh no oh okay so on snakes in a place
they're like an evil person who releases
the snakes who brings them who sneaks
them past airport security in their
check on luggage and then he's like
alright
we're 10 000 feet into the air it's time
to release the snakes
and then oh what if then it was like a
murder mystery we have to like find out
who did it who done it
who released the snakes who let the
snakes out
they're trying to kill a witness
and this was the best plan i mean
yeah you shouldn't think about it too
much
you're not meant to think about it that
you know
you're just supposed to accept the
premise
and then have fun watching it
oh
in which the best way to assassinate
someone is to
sneak snakes onto an airplane
i feel like it's just like someone who
made that movie
had a very specific fear of snakes and
airplanes and was like oh
i want to make a really thrilling movie
how can i accomplish that
i know what if we combine the fear of
snakes with the fear of flying
no i can't do it i cannot beat orange
hell because it would be pretty scary
is it just a joke
based on me really
[Music]
i mean like if you have a fear of flying
the last thing you want on your plane is
like a bunch of snakes
probably
i know that snakes are really not that
dangerous
for the most part but
it'd still be scary same if there were
like a bunch of spiders on the plane
or worse for me like roaches
like it's not dangerous but
being trapped in a
in a small space where you cannot open
the windows with a bunch of roaches
would be
a nightmare
movies
it's gonna be like snakes on a plane but
with the um
oh what are they called the like
true traditional
plagues
like there's like the plague of locusts
what are the other ones
rats
it's gonna be like that a series
oh no is youtube dead
did you hear my my genius moving idea
[Music]
um yes frogs
repeat the idea i'm gonna make a series
of movies inspired by snakes on a plane
but it's gonna be the i forget what
they're actually called like the
traditional
plagues
like a plague of locusts
and a plague of
of rats and frogs it's gonna be like
that
each a different movie with a different
focus
yeah the biblical plagues
oh
oh yeah and then the finale it will be
all of them at once
how is that that locust was the worst
one
i was scared because it's real right
well like there can actually be those
locusts that are only they only come out
like every eight years or whatever
and when they do they absolutely destroy
everything and they're
just like
dead on the ground everywhere
and the sky is dark with locusts
that's very scary to me
oh no
i can't play anymore
i'm too distracted
darkness would be pretty bad too
if you live far north or south enough
you can experience like three months of
darkness
but also the converse like three
months of
of sunlight
i can't i can't play
a key is not supposed to be difficult
just just go
[Music]
just let me out
as a firstborn i think the firstborn
thing is the worst what is that do all
the firstborns die
but you have to like put something on
your door right like blood or something
that's so scary
oh no
help
i can't
[Music]
lamb's blood
only first born sons dang it
oh wait i shouldn't say dang
i just mean isn't that a little unfair
um
[Music]
that sounded way too suspicious
um
i promise that i'm not trying to get
revenge on any first-born daughters
oh
what other movies are there there's like
sharknado i didn't watch that one
that one felt a little too on the nose
for me
was it actually
good or bad or so bad it's good
i don't know
and there's birdemic which i always get
confused with the birds
which is like an actually good movie
like a classic movie
and in my brain they've become conflated
i know i've seen both of them but i
cannot
remember is which
because aren't they both about like
ravens or crows
is the classic
that's true i don't really remember it
again
i don't really remember it
bird emmick no i mean the birds is not
the one that's filmed from the rear view
mirror that's that's a rear view mirror
right
i feel like i need to
watch more movies
i don't know a lot about classic movies
i've never seen
the matrix
or the godfather
[Music]
or
jim carrey's the mask
wait what's the one that people say is
the best movie of all time
oops
[Music]
the mask right right right
citizen kane that's the one i've never
seen
no i thought i could save it
i've never seen citizen kane
i watched only the first half of pulp
fiction
and i didn't get it at the time so i
just stopped watching it
i feel like now i would i would
appreciate it more
there's all these movies oops i've never
seen
[Music]
fight club i've never seen fight club
i've never seen what's the other one the
one where he runs up the stairs rocky
never seen that one
[Music]
i did watch forrest gum by washing in
school for some reason
[Music]
um
this is fixable
it is but how many hours of movies have
we listed off
i was mean to watch these movies like
when i'm on a plane
you know
but i'm really bad because
i just get tempted by watching a movie
i've already seen
a hundred times and i just end up
watching that instead of watching
something new oh no why'd i do that
i'm in trouble
[Music]
why risk it with
bad mood but it's like
like one time i was gonna watch the
matrix but i think i just wish like
well actually i've watched it was like
pirates of the caribbean but it wasn't
even
the first one
it was like one of the weird ones
and then i just stopped watching it
because i was like wait this is what i
thought it was
and i think i just read a book instead
we skype in three minutes wait really
well i didn't realize it's been that
long oh no
i have to finish the run we have to play
skyrim
i have plans for skyrim
i was zoned out
thinking about movies and losing over
and over again i'm getting over it
we must go
oh no
but now that i'm thinking about it now
i'm not gonna be able to do it
yeah i we should play skype because i
have plans we shouldn't be late because
there's something specific i want to do
and i think an hour is enough time but
i'm not sure
[Music]
fandol isn't vinin
we're not going to abandon him yet i've
been putting it off because i know
the next quest i want to do
we have to abandon feindle
[Music]
help i can't
now that i am like i have to finish i
can't i can't
i can't
but i don't want to leave this run
undone
[Music]
also did we talk about
the council song yet rise did you listen
to it
you should listen to it if you didn't
yet
it was fun to make and i'm glad that we
all
had the chance to sing together
not yet what are you doing go listen to
it ah
it's okay i'll still be streaming when
you come back you can go
go listen to it and come back
i give you permission
[Music]
sing it
do you say steam rice
steamed rice
that's right
uh-oh
[Music]
help
ah
i don't think i can sing it because i
only know my part
[Music]
they wraps how am i supposed to do that
i do not know
bae's part
i like that the song was kind of
tailored to match us
i was happy that i got to do like a
no
a soft
section
no
and like oh my gosh
mermaids like ad limbs in the
the final part are so
beautiful
beautiful bird singing
beautifully
help
i can't finish it we have to play skyrim
we have to play skyrim
i can't let the schedule get behind
or else we're doomed not really
but
okay we're good
one way or another we're making it out
of here
please
no
that was such a slow push
give me a better push than that
that's a fake rock
oh no we're not even going up we're just
going to route it around
it's like an infinite loop right
okay
15 minutes oh nice though nice nice
extremely nice
okay
skyrim wait oh never mind
[Music]
i panicked because i forgot
if i prepared my controller but i did
well it's not plugged in
and i wrapped the cord all around it so
now i have to unwrap it
okay
hydration check good idea
[Music]
i have to plug in the controller
oh the controller vibrated did you hear
it
sounded suspicious it was the controller
um
you heard it
[Music]
it was the controller
um
okay
we play skyrim
[Music]
oh i still have my music playing hold on
get rid of that
what monitor is skyrim going to appear
on i have no idea oh that one huh
okay that's fine
you can be on that monitor i won't fight
you
i've learned my lesson
about fighting
the screen the
most of the
monitor the game wants to play on
[Music]
okay and then
i have to set up my screen
um
oh i hear it
i know you can't hear it yet but i hear
it
on
[Music]
is this where i go
hold on
[Music]
i forgot how to get to the place i want
to be as well
[Music]
um
there's a bald child
in the loading screen hold on
wait
oh no okay
let's go
hello i don't have my hat on
sorry no hat
no hats
oh wait you can't hear still hold on
hold on
got to keep my eyes open
damn dragons could swoop down at any
time
true true
okay wait i think we just
ah
right
right right i remember
i remember
do i have my old hat hold on
i have my old hat
there
am i small
i promise scuff and
i deliver
on scuff
the old hat has some charm to it i think
okay um
i
yes i do have this quest
we have to do this
i forget how we do this
this is a quest i want to do today the
mind of madness
because it is one of the most fun quests
in skyrim in my opinion
and afterwards we can give the staff to
fedor
yay
he's gonna love it
yeah we have to go to solitude
and what do we have to do
do we just walk around
do we have the hip bone
how do i play this game oh i love skyrim
boy do i love skyrim oh no
um
wow i have a lot of soul gems wow i have
a lot of soul gems i should enchant
that's a lot of soul gems
we do have it okay
let's go
to solitude
this is solitude
the solitude
let's go
oh skyrim i always miss you
when i'm not playing you
i forgot i'm a vampire oh my gosh
i forgot i'm a vampire oh shoot
no one will know though
um
oh he's right there she spare some gold
for a better hello it's so exciting when
newfoundland come into town i bet you've
had plenty of adventures is she okay
i need to get into pelagius wing it's
not allowed besides it's scary in there
that's fine
fog asked me to check it out i suppose
in that case it's okay to let you in
but only briefly
be careful and come right back
okay
i need to get back to the palace soon
anyway
okay
wait is this forward going
yes
i'm not gonna fast travel though
children is my child here my children's
i mean my multiple children
i know they live here should we visit
them we don't have time
sorry children
mommy has to finish a quest in one hour
no time
no my children live here now isn't this
my house
this is this one
no no that's briley's house wait is it
this one vandal excuse
me how long is this quest i think it's
short
isn't this my house
that's the bars college
isn't isn't this my house
yes
this one for sure
children i'm home
oh the basement's kind of scary ah mama
ah
sophie
oh shoot
what would you like
i'd really like it oh shoot oh gosh i
forgot about her feral
fox pants
[Music]
um what is it what is it
here you go
thanks
you're welcome
[Music]
her pharaoh fox bed i forgot
i'm glad it's still here
it was really scary isn't it isn't that
what feigned all is
wait maybe not
i don't know
do we need to to teach our child
fanduel is bosmer
is the farmer the ones who live in the
cave
and they go
palmer
oh
sophie you cannot be saying stuff like
that
i'm gonna get in trouble
oh it's an order of high elves okay well
then maybe it's fine
oh
sorry sorry sorry i just wanted to look
at you fandom
i can't believe that lady just let us
come in here
oh
okay it is pretty scary in here
if you don't like spiders
especially
ouch
the baskets they hurt me
oh entry
oh wow
kind of like it though it's kind of you
can tell it would be cozy in here
especially during the winter when it's
snowing outside
can't you tell it'll be cozy in here
if you get it cleaned up it would be so
cozy with stained glass
oh
oh i couldn't it goes right through me
besides i have so many things to do
so many undesirables we made it
naysayers
buffoons detractors
who are you talking to the third was he
the one who was murdered surely even you
know about pelagius's decree
on his deathbed oh and this was inspired
he forbade
death that's right death outlawed
how can you forbid death
inside the mind of pelagius silly his
mind lives on is it
oh is it because he forbade death but he
was killed so now his mind is is trapped
eternally
tormented
i'm here to deliver a message
oh
what kind of message a song a summons
wait i know this guy is pretty quirky
but somehow he's still not as quirky as
cicero
well
spit it out how about a hip bone
eternity
i was asked to retrieve you from your
vacation where are you now
you don't like that you're staring at
the mammoth trunk i know isn't that kind
of sad was it molag no no
little tim the toymaker's son huh huh
the ghost of kingly
kind of does sound like mr krabs
but more to the point
do you
tiny
who do you call it time who are you
calling mortal i'm a vampire i'll have
you know actually think
you
and i'm the dragonborn and i'm a cat
because that's
crazy
music
is it actually mr krabs we really see me
really
all i know is that your people need you
to return
yeah it does sound kind of boring i
would rather have tea party here forever
too
do apologize it's just that i find
myself suddenly
oh not the same
i mean really
here he
sounds like is chewy dream it is
madness
i want to become a daedric prince i hope
in elder scrolls six they let you
that would be great
so does this mean you leave or no that's
the real question isn't it
because honestly how much time off could
a demented daedra really need
so
here's what i'm going you can't in
oblivion
oh my goodness
you have to find the way out first
good luck with
that okay what's the catch i do love it
when the mortals know they're being of
course i'm very perceptive you know
not like i've played this quest before
no it was so many years ago i don't
remember
i guess that's why it's deceptively
verdict
of a dead homicidally insane monarch
was he homicidally inclined to watch her
thinking
can i still rely on my swords and spells
and sneaking and all that nonsense sure
sure
or
you could use
the wobble jack
yes please
i got it
should i look around first do i really
just escape with this
is it really that easy not this is a sad
path pelagius hates it let's look around
many things assassins wild dogs is this
his childhood
maybe he's not a child but the deepest
keenest hatred was
is
i like his anger
[Music]
you have nothing to say
um
[Music]
oh
yes balanced
i'm all ears oh watch behind you behind
you
oh he's still a little small huh
well i don't know that could be just how
tall he is you never know
he doesn't seem too bothered
you seem to be having a small problem or
perhaps it's a big problem
oh
you think
isn't a problem
oh
how about this
[Applause]
um
not me not me
wonderfully
all right
okay
goodbye
that's good
one of the quests of all time
what is happening we're inside the mine
plagueis the third
the homicidally insane monarch you've
headed down
the path i like dreams oh unfortunately
for you pelagius
from a young age
all you need to do is find something to
wake our poor pelagius up you'll find
his terrors easy to repel but persistent
oh
what can i feed him
whoa
oh
oh that's what it means
oh i see i see
[Music]
i'm i'm i'm feeding on him i see us he
find myself
what have i done
he's not gonna wake up now
oh
this is some premium stuff you know
this monarch blood you don't get this
that often
good morning
good morning good morning
[Music]
look
it's not so scary right wake up
oh
is it finding the goat
look
it's fine
if you die in the dream do you die in
real life
i didn't know you could die
oh my gosh you die in real life
fandol
i didn't know
i got one shot
oh no
happened to you two what about you
oh wait that's pelagius right there
i see you see desirables
i'll take them and snout
oh seriously
you have to find the way out first
jack
didn't see that coming did you
you like my cat claws
can i become vampire here
although it's kind of sunny maybe
ah
not this is a sad path i can do i just
hate it and feared many things assassins
wild dogs the undead pumpernickel
pumpernickel but the deepest
keenest hatred
never should have come
on himself
this the correct answer
you must bring it on
how do you pass me
show grad
what do you think
no
[Music]
um
oh okay
sure
wait is it good
wait
i don't know
is finally ready to love himself oh is
that your
best okay i don't know what i did
sometimes you just have to spam it until
it works
that's fine
just keep blasting
i'm starting blasting
wait wait wait wait
the path of dreams
unfortunately for you
suffered night terrors from a young age
do you think i should still feed
something
you'll find his terrors easy to repel i
mean you should right
imagine how strong you can grow from
doing this will he die if i keep feeding
on him though
how much blood does he have in the dream
world
wake up
[Music]
wake up oh
don't hit the goat wake up
okay
hold on hold on
i'm about to meet one shot again
hagraven was that hat raven before
[Music]
ouch
did i not hit her
i think i did
oh she became the campfire
dragon priest now that's something
to say oh something about
good morning
who are you
soul tree maiden
she looks concerned
anything good in here is playing the
dramatic music
wait did they eat the goat
oh no oh no they go just fine
music
it's overlapping
they don't expect you to go so fast as
me
can we get triple music oh
good choice well good for me
i find everyone being out to get you so
terribly entertaining
you might find it
less so
is this one the one where i fight
pelagius's mother was
well let us say
unique although i suppose in the grand
scheme of things she was fairly average
for accepting
that woman wielded fear like a cleaver
wow she wield a cleaver and make
delivered
are you my enemy
well really i think you're my enemies
or maybe you
oh i thought you'd never figure it out
is under the oh
that he's safe which means you've helped
him out sir
he said he thought i'd never figure it
out but i don't think it took me that
long
where's the girl here
oh no why didn't guru say
mr krabs
everyone thinks he's mr krabs
he does kind of sound like mr krabs i
can kind of hear it
you're a goofy grouper yeah
oh goofy coopers yeah
money money so what he sounds like
um
hello
do you mind i'm busy doing the fish
stick fish
here's mr krabs
um i've done it i've fixed plagiarism
it's such a subjective term
i think no i fixed him
i fixed him
like one does to a rash or an arrow in
the
face ah but no matter heartless mortals
i'm not a mortal i'm a vampire
dragonborn cat i am forced to honor my
end of the bargain so
do i get to keep the wobble jack as my
consolation prize i
have been known to change right now
what's up
i want to hang out with
sheryl grathmore
pelagius septum the third one is he gone
real sounds so boringly
i agree with you i want to sit at your
tea party
why am i wearing this hat
i guess you took my stuff or no it's
pajamas i get it i'm not forgetting
anything
how cute i am look at my cute cat ears
luggage
now where did i leave my luggage can i
eat this
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
you've taken me back does this mean
we're going home it's ace happy times i
can't wait to
yes yes that's quite enough celebration
let's send you a headshot
as for you
a little immortal stop calling me then
feel free to keep the wobble check as a
symbol of my
i'll just think of something
you take care of yourself now and if you
ever find yourself up a new shayo do
i want to can you do that in this game
can we go
are they just lying to me
i want to go
i've always loved the daedric princes
oh
they know i have a gift for you do you
want me to carry only an oblivion okay
sounds like i should really play
oblivion then i mean a lot of people say
it's better than skyrim
here go fanda look we did that so fast
too
we have time to spare where can we have
fandol test out his
his new staff
do you think he's gonna use it
i want him to use it i don't know if he
will
oh hello
just tidying up are you gonna get in
trouble maybe you need a partner
just picture it two women the dusty road
strapping men at every tavern a fortune
and gold to be claimed
that does sound pretty good i didn't
realize she had such feelings for me
where were we are we friends did i just
forget who she was
oh i'm a vampire that's right my
cousin's out fighting dragons and what
do i get
first meeting actually
she must really like cats
what is this
oh i remember yeah
yeah
serrano
serrano how come serrano won't ask me to
run away with her
moth the priest
[Music]
we could do a contract
we could do or we could do as a guild
because we think we need to do thieves
guild to advance and eventually
we could do a quick little
thieves guild
a night to remember i think i did that
one didn't i
and then we can see if fandom will use
his wabba jack
[Music]
um
is there skilled in here somewhere
where is it
um
oh wait is it this one
the heist job
did i not do that already i guess the
thieves killed though you're not
supposed to kill people so i don't know
if fandol can use his
his thing
should we just go fight something do you
think he'll use it
where shall we fight something
like a giant
[Music]
into the woods
where's the giant camp
ghoul dawn rock is that a giant camp
yes
oh trolls
close enough
well you know i remember being here yes
i died so many times here
hold on
still here is he gonna use his stuff
uh
i want you to use this one
i have to take all his stuff
use the wobble jack
oh he has so much stuff
why does he have so much stuff
he'll use an all right
let's get going then
oh but where's my stuff
all right fandom
[Music]
oh the horse
wait where'd he get that bow from
no feign doll no
no i thought i took that from you
did he spawn it in oh no the horse oh no
the horse
oh
oh is he gonna do it
what's he got there what kind of dark
magic does he got
do it
bo is default will he not use it
i've got your back do you think he's not
gonna use it what do you want me to
carry
because i think i took everything away
and he just used his default bow
huh
i'll use and then
fine
if you don't want it faint i'll use it
don't worry any armor oh
you're right
that's so annoying i don't want to put
my armor back on
did did nothing happen is he too high
level
oh
oh the horse the horse
do it
the horse is tanking though
oh
we actually killed one
i guess most of the time it just does
something random
oh my gosh
oh my goodness
i'm actually strong
i had no idea
it is strong
how come fandom won't use it
but do we even want to stay in this
timeline oh who am i kidding
we're evil
we're evil in this world
and he's got so much money
he had a glass maze
wait is the horse okay though
wait hold on his fandol okay
wait
um
fandol
the horses um
the horse respawns right
[Music]
is the giant's toe count as food
just a little snack
delicious
did we get a disease from that
oh
cause i'm a vampire
but i'm also a champion of the night
oh and i'm 25 harder to detect when
sneaking oh wait i can't get a disease
because i'm a vampire i can eat all the
toes i want
perfect
wow
is my horse okay
um
oh
need you to carry some things fandol
thank you
[Music]
you can hold on to
this i hope you use it if you don't i
will though
oh he has too much to carry too oh no
oh wait if i quit my stuff maybe i'll be
okay actually
what i am
wear
this
sometimes i wear this
um
no equipping stuff did not actually help
[Music]
um
how cute i am
what is
that that rock
oh i have too much stuff
how could this happen
try to drop this
it's not worn that much anyway okay
drop the clothes i need those clothes i
need them
is my horse here
you're my horse right yes beautiful
shadow man never dies
oh i never noticed
the shadow mirror has
rectangular pupils do all horses have
that i thought that's like a goat thing
a hell spawn thing
beautiful hell spawn horse
my beloved
[Music]
okay
i should really sell some stuff
but selling stuff is not very fun
oh we know but i should put it at home i
think actually
i think i was leaving all my stuff
in here
at my house
my lakeside manor
this is 12 hours long right yep
oh no
is there a dragon
can we just go inside
pretend it's not here
[Music]
in
15 minutes we're switching to fall guys
right i believe
um
oh i do have fine clothes i don't know
where i got those
[Music]
um
strange amulet
[Music]
i don't need to carry two bows with me
right
[Music]
um wait do i have two of those wait
dwarven bow
i can enchant that
and this one
i don't need
that um
the music why is the music so dramatic
sorting music goes hard
the most dramatic sorting you'll ever
see
um
wow he has so much stuff
i feel like he doesn't need all this
stuff though
[Music]
okay
let's get going then
oh wow
nice blade i have
don't have any dragon bones in here i
don't think this is where i keep them
this is my junk drawer
just put everything in oh no
the sorting music again
[Music]
this one
and
um
this one this one
this one
[Music]
all right
let's go
[Music]
oh
i cannot fast-track oh can you never
fast travel from inside maybe you can't
oh geez
it's like the walter white meme
when he is in the desert
this is me every time i walk outside now
oh
i have vampire seduction
wow
maybe belfor will just give me that
amulet
well what am i stealing
gemstone
hmm
there's quite a lot of people around
um
what is the quest exactly
flawless garnet
okay
don't kill anyone or get caught okay
well luckily i'm extremely sneaky these
days
you think this guy's gonna leave
they're gonna be here all night
maybe
that's fine
i'm very sneaky
and good at lock picking too
see
oh
they know how did you get back there
you know how did you get back there
um
i don't think they care
wait where oh wait is it's on marker
it's upstairs
oh geez they're upstairs though oh geez
you're not supposed to be in here
what do you mean
he's judging me
click
save but wow what if we need our other
quick save i know
he's gonna
snitch geez they're sleeping it's fine
it's fine
they're deep in sleep
i can't believe it
fandol's really changed
you're not supposed to be here well what
about
you about you then
huh
oh my gosh oh my gosh
are we friends i'm right behind you okay
okay
after all we've done together i didn't
think breaking into somebody's house
would be the thing
where he draws the line
where am i going now
oh wait all the way back to thieves
again right in riften
hud for you not for anyone he's just
trolling a little maybe he is maybe he's
just teasing me
you're not supposed to be here
you're not supposed to be here feign
doll
good to see you again
oh see this is how you treat someone
with respect you can learn a thing or
two with or do you just want to talk no
i don't even want to talk actually
none of the above actually i'm good
professionals have standards
that's true
since this target was much too weak for
us
hello vex
i've completed the highest job make the
client happy
next time i'll take a real thief and
don't get caught i didn't get caught
i
i didn't get caught did feign don't
catch me did thanos snatch me i don't
want to settle i like things the way
they are come on
let me take care of you
i can take care of myself
you little
he's
do you know what they say about snitches
feign doll
oh my god
where do we even go
fame doll
[Music]
top 10 anime trails
i can't do it i can't do it not to faint
off
oh my god yeah he's like my rival or
something
um
this one i guess
oh my goodness
[Music]
he's so snake
he snitched on me
[Music]
still here wait here please
actually heading out let's get going
how about how about you wait all the way
over here
wait actually there's a back door i
didn't realize
i've got your back wait here you go you
don't got my back
obviously
okay
music was profaned all along
[Music]
oh
no you think you know a guy
after all we've been through
after everyone we've murdered together
you're not supposed to be here
can't believe it i can't believe it
um
[Music]
the music why is the music just won't
stop
i want to listen to my oh
there's a shortcut that's called a
shortcut
um
is there anything else we should steal
i don't know they don't have anything
good
[Music]
hey
potato
[Music]
all right vandal ready to get going yup
let's get going yep
not supposed to be here
now i'm not going to feel bad next
skyrim episode when we abandoned fandol
briefly momentarily
to hang out with our
beautiful vampire waifu
who will not question our evil deeds
certainly
all right no more failure please
even feign dog doesn't know
music though please i want to listen to
the relaxing skyrim music being
connected to a criminal
client happy
next time act like a real thief and
don't get caught
wait but how confused
you scared the sunlight or something
how do you see my skin i have fur
um
you can offer but i may not did fandom
snitch again
was it not faint off
what happened is it buggy
or did i do something wrong
todd
[Music]
todd himself snitched
is it because fandom was there
check my bounty how do i check my bounty
how do you do that
is the cutter fee glitched
general stats
next in six
days is a vampire seven that's one neck
per day almost
i feel like those numbers could be
higher though
um
crime
oh geez
oh jeez
look at my number of assaults oh wow
okay uh
no wide run though
right
monster
no white run though right
it might be the same reason the music is
playing oh
[Music]
how about we do it load
this one
and then how about we just like chill
for a while
game thinks i'm in combat
well
what if i just go to sleep
yeah maybe we just try next time
did faint not really not snitch at all
[Music]
bugged permanently no way it's permanent
i'm sure it'll be fine
but i will
leave it there
for today
[Music]
i think
that was great though
[Music]
we had a great moment i think she shall
growth just cursed us actually
cursed us with madness
yeah i'll probably take a little break
for a couple minutes
stretch a break
[Music]
they're doing something new every hour
really works because i don't feel like
it's been three hours
it still feels like i just started
you know
okay bobby are back
man i love my bedroom isn't it nice
doesn't the lighting look so warm
inviting
yeah
i like and i have my switch and my cute
keyboard
[Music]
um if i could move nemu though
well she's pretty good here but she
could be a little bigger maybe
[Music]
okay i'll be right back
and then we'll play fall guys we're
gonna play together okay it's a collab
with me and you
[Music]
together
okay be right back
where's my br b screen there it is
[Music]
hello
let's play fall guys
but i have to set it up first
oh we get to play my favorite game
which monitor will fall guys show up
in i don't know
let's find out
oh
[Music]
what's it gonna be
oh epic games is updating
[Music]
i have to wait and find out
it's a mystery
in the meantime we can enjoy this lovely
view
of my room
[Music]
thank you for the happy anniversary
mistake thank you
yeah one year that's crazy
[Music]
i'm nervous to watch the day oh oh it's
gonna be this monitor okay okay okay i
gotta move all my windows again
it's okay because this is actually the
the monitor that i prefer that it'd be
on but
i have to scoot everyone over
again
okay
[Music]
this stud screen things up i don't know
i wish every game
had an in-game option for which monitor
to display on
but it's actually pretty rare i think
for games to let you choose
oh fought guys is not happy right now i
might have to restart it
oh nevermind it's going it's going
i know monitoring audio
i wish
i wish they had that
[Music]
okay let me make
a i'll make a fall guy's room
um
it's kind of loud
okay i'll make a room for us
do you have your fall guys open
did you open it and i can't hear it or
see it yet
we'll get there
[Music]
no you better get your fall guys open
because we're playing it together
it's fall guys time
[Music]
it's time for fall guys
no it's summer guys
you're ready okay if we're ready for the
code i'll read it to you i'll read it to
you slowly
the code for fall guys is
s
h
v
e
seven
oh
[Music]
there you are
oh wait hold on you can't hear again
love the scuff live for this stuff
scuff his love stuff is life
[Music]
cursed tall guy i like the tall guy it
is cursed but i like it
[Music]
you guys make it in
let's go
[Music]
i haven't played fall guys in a while
well i hope we can play some of the new
maps like the races
but i feel like they never show up
for some reason
shave was the code shave did it look
like shave or something
are you guys telling me to shave i don't
think i need to shave i think i look
perfectly smooth
my head okay maybe i could shave my head
i guess my head is not perfectly smooth
round
egg
like
got a little five o'clock
no that'll be me at the end of stream
i'm still pretty fresh
well okay i'm playing really badly
though can i please play the game i know
how to play this game i'm actually
really good at this game
that's why i fall and roll like this
oh i'm actually really good at this game
oh wow
okay i might be bad
something horrible has happened and i no
longer know how to play ball guys
but like i said my brain is basically
functioning at peak performance right
now
definitely
a hundred percent oh no i'm sorry and i
bonk you up i'm sorry
nothing to worry about
only three hours in
that's basically the length of a normal
stream
okay get your head in the game
gotta play this game properly
is
uno in three or no three in uh 50
minutes
i think
[Music]
yes okay i have to keep that in mind
because that one is a collab
i'm kind of nervous because i have to
bring my guests on but that's why i
allocated an hour and a half for the
collab
sections so that uh there's a little bit
of extra time
for setup and stuff since normally we
would set up before the stream but there
is no before the stream
there is only the stream
so it might not start exactly at the
hour it might start a little late
because we have to set up
[Music]
we should be okay
until then i will
try to win at fall guys
it's not going so well so far
oh please
i thought there was no door on this side
i see an axolotl but it's not the tv
axolotl it looks like doctor is his name
doctor funk
it doesn't sound right somehow from
animal crossing oh no i'm like at the
very end it's not fair
i don't think i'm gonna qualify
one of the beans has cat ears
oh no
i didn't qualify
that's okay it means i can message my
lovely guests
about the unknown
[Music]
okay i'm that's why i'm messing
now you guys are the streamers you guys
get to play games for the the crowd
today
this stream
okay
should be good
for uno
why am i nervous
i think it's because
i don't want to inconvenience anyone and
it feels like a sort of inconveniencing
people by
having the what is the little bit i
think the right word is like
kitty kitty right it's a little bit
kitty kitty
when you set up for a collab while the
stream is happening
but that's okay that's the fun of it
right
it's okay if it's just me who's being
inconvenienced
but i don't want to inconvenience my yes
they'll be good wait that guy has a long
hammer i really like some of the new
outfits they've been adding
to fall guys
but they're expensive
and somebody had cat ears and there
really is axolotl
oh there's two axolotls oh and there's
the cat ears in the top right
i want
wait aren't they adding wait a minute
this was a week
aren't they adding miku too
i think they're adding miku
yeah there's pusheen too
[Music]
miku's skin looks good
they're kind of funny though
because the beans are
a little bit
chubby
but not in like the normal like chubby
chibi way in a very like bean wing well
they have no neck you know
they're shaped like a minion i guess
so it's like a minion miku
i remember the
the minion piece in the eye
and the minion 2b from here
turns your waifu into a bean
don't say that but it's true
they're a minion shaped
although i said like there's not a
pokemon that are the shape too the first
one that came to mind is
oh i forget its name
the pikachu from sword and shield
the electric rodent from sword and
shield
it's like grumpy and happy
more pickle yeah that one
that one
is also shaped like a minion
there's more is japanese name
but
does it make sense in english does that
have an english meaning
[Music]
it's the same in japanese
or on the finals
i didn't realize until very recently
that they actually put a pikachu in
every generation
i thought
i didn't realize it was an intentional
thing
like they actually put an electric road
in every generation
[Music]
you guys are
musicians
[Applause]
yeah but some of them are more pikachu
than others um
well like
which one was really pikachu hold on
look at all them
electric
rodent
pokemon
i mean
like pulsey what is that called whole
sand
they're very pikachu well they look a
lot like pichu actually
i guess for after there they've started
making them a little different
i don't more peco really is like a
minion
shaped
i like the new one
oh but i remember because the new one
looks a lot better in this bright art
than in the 3d sprite
and the 3d
in-game
art
i
[Music]
is not an electric rodent though
but i agree i love mimikyu
i mean mimikyu is like
he's actually supposed to be pikachu you
know like very self-aware
the other ones are just electric voting
that also look like pikachu
[Music]
they tried their best okay
maybe your best pikachu
that's true i mean
pikachu is kind of spoiled i think
kind of a brat a little bit but that's
why you love pikachu right because
pikachu is always beating up ash being
so mean
shocking him he has to wear the the
rubber gloves oh no goodbye
chubby pikachu best pikachu okay that's
also true
the one that says pee
[Music]
good job
good job captain drake
very good
okay let's
i'll open a new lobby
[Music]
hold on let me move
where's the code
probably right there
look you can now play as wide fauna and
fall guys
can you believe it
all right i'll read the code for you
again it is
p
sorry just one p
q
six
zero eight
that is your cone
welcome
okay i'm gonna do better in this one i'm
gonna make it to the finals this time
i know i want to be your fault my skin
that would be fun i want to become a
minion i don't even mind
they can turn me into a minion shape
that's fine
accept it
[Music]
okay i'm gonna make it to the finals for
sure and this time i'm gonna get the
crown actually only if it's hexagon
if it's hexagon
guaranteed win only
but i need to go back into my my smurf
lobbies
to win
is that a challenge yes i see a lot of
cat ears wait is that what is this
helmet
i'm getting distracted
don't get distracted by everybody's cool
skins
oh no i'm already in the back oh shoot
i'm really bad
that game suddenly
first it was getting over it and now
this
oh no
don't grab me
that's what you get
you get indiana jones
i gotta go
oh
just a little bit of a bunk
that's all
it's okay it's okay oh it's not okay i'm
not coming okay i have to go i have to
go have to go i have to go
please i want to do well
oh shoot oh shoot
it's going real fast
this is kind of a hard variant of the
game we actually made it though
not too bad
but closer or less close than last time
oh
oh that's a hard variant of that map
it's good though
bring it on
give me the challenge
i should change my skin
i should wear the cute flower necklace
instead of the weird
[Music]
the weird tall guy
oh
i don't feel so good about rolling out i
have to pay attention from this one
no messing around
[Music]
i'm the tall guy right now wait that's
like a door
you can become the door
that reminds me of the
is it from labyrinth
well i know that this is like a common
puzzle in many pieces of media
but it's like the one door that always
tells the truth and the one that always
lies
you have to figure out which door to go
through
there's a way to solve it i don't
remember this don't you just ask them
like what would the other door say you
ask them about that and then that's how
you know
if you're ever in such a situation oh
[Music]
oh
i want to read i'm trying to feed the
chat that i have to focus
i feel like i talk about labyrinth too
much how come i've launched labyrinth
but i haven't watched this citizen
or the main
or rocky or fight club
only labyrinth the only movie i've ever
seen
every movie is just a derivative of
labyrinth truly
i'm just kidding but i do like the
puppets
and the music
oh see that there's a minion right there
we actually or are you a minion or are
you
homer simpson
do you see it you see what i mean
see this lobby is kind of intense roll
out goes forever because no one dies
scary
the gamers have logged on today
oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
i go
just one more
cute cat ears i want the cat eating
did you have to pay real money for them
i told you i'm gonna make it to the
finals
maybe i hope maybe
if you just believe you'll make it
that level makes you motion sick yeah it
makes you dizzy right
especially the final version of that one
always makes me dizzy when is it going
really fast you have to go on and off
and on and off and i don't know
have confidence focus
i can't focus
maybe i can
i like this sushi roll
i want a sushi roll
with lots of veggies inside looks i'm
focused
just follow the sushi roll in front of
you like following
a carrot one stick
oh i think i went the wrong way
gotta go with the crowd on this one
don't fight the current oh
i've elected to not fight the current
but i think it would have turned out
exactly the same either way
oh ouch
i don't like this part
i don't like the donuts
[Music]
hey
made it made it
one more
level through
avocado roll that sounds yummy
i like avocado i like a fried avocado
or like fried avocado tacos
those are really yummy
i know now i'm hungry too
i could have a snack
i don't know
i don't like to eat
i was thinking i'll eat something when i
really do my
debut rewatch
i mean i'll do some commentary but i can
also
just be quiet sometimes oh god it's not
a good situation
it's not a good situation
i can't get out of here i gotta get out
of here
no no no no not me not me
watch me please please leave me alone
leave me alone
please i've never got so much aggro on
this one before
please leave me alone
they keep locking on to me
i can't deal with this
oh my goodness i've never had this much
aggro before is it because there's not
many people
in this map right now
usually you can share the aggro a little
bit oh my gosh it's so fast
i got so lucky
that was the hardest round of that one
i've ever played
okay well there's four people left
[Music]
i think i wasn't the only one who
struggled
oh my goodness
never punished what oh no we have to
play infinite ball guys now
no i know what a plane when it fall guys
i have to play ooh no no
not infinite fall guys
no
[Music]
i'm playing infinite fall guys
one person's getting eliminated
oh geez oh geez it's gonna be me it's
gonna be me
i'm the one person
i don't wanna play it with this ball
guys
not this again
not this again ah
i don't wanna be eliminated but i don't
wanna play in for the fall guys either
so what do i want
i want to win that's the answer
i'm doing okay
i see someone in front of me though
i'm try harding
oh thank you majesty thank you thank you
thank you everyone very much you are
being extremely generous i appreciate it
very much thank you
oh
i'm sorry shark i'm sorry
[Music]
infinite fall guys
infinite fall guys you want to play fall
guys you really want to play ball guys
do you want to play fall guys forever
i want to play four guys forever
do you think anyone's going to be my
daddy with this one is it going to be a
1v1
oh my goodness want to be one man fall
guys you won't
you won't
nope it's we can all qualify all right
all right team are you ready for
infinite fall guys
ah
the round where no one is eliminated
the stakes are lower than they've ever
been folks
that's right
not a single elimination this round
you'll never believe it
and yet i'm still
try harding
i always thought this way i feel like
the punchers are faster but
they're dangerous
this cat ears is really good
i might be in trouble
against cat ears in the future
let me
all right
do you think they're gonna give us a
final
i want to see you final
please
let me leave here
top three guarantee it's true it's true
you did guarantee top three
three repaint pre-qualified
wow
let me leave here can we have a final
please please
please fall guys may we please have a
final
please
may we may we please have a final please
not a fruit shoot
please
let me play uno
too qualified okay the stakes are high
now
it is gonna show 1v1 finale i don't like
such a high-stakes fruit shoot though
oh no
oh that was pretty good oh shoot oh
shoot
oh shoot oh shoot
my good launch what was it for
for nothing
i don't like fruit shoot
oh i hate fruit shoot actually
i hate it
[Music]
did they change it
the logs can roll on that
um
[Music]
okay
it's a 1v1
[Music]
1v1 me and fall guys you won't
oh no what's it gonna be though
i don't like this too much
pressure 1v1 i don't want a 1v1
i'm cowardly
[Music]
is it gonna be a final even
party promenade great great
do you think it's gonna be too hard to
qualify
what's it gonna be
never finals only race
race forever oh too qualified wow
it's time to practice your fall guys the
stakes are once again
very low
inconsequential even
[Applause]
wow
out
i would be upset that i'm in second
place but it does not matter folks
it doesn't matter at all
oh
i'm going
i don't think this was faster
can i go this way
i'm gonna get second place that's
basically losing
how could this happen
wow
can we have a final please please mayor
please request the final
pretty please please
just one final round would be nice
last place
no
infinite fall guys infinite fall guys
do you like fall guys do you like pipe
dream
i hope you do
we're playing forever
you're here forever never leaving fall
guys can't quit the game two out of two
qualified wow
wow
is that a strat
i'm gonna pretend that's a strat
i don't like all these balloons
i'm going
have you seen the video
the person playing lily leapers in this
game and they're just going wild on it
the pro level lily leapers
skills
it's really good
no i'm on the wrong side
probably could have went to the other
side but oh well
once again the stakes are
pretty low
[Applause]
one more race
one more race one more race one more
race
what do you think is it gonna be a race
or finals
what do you think
one more one more one more
it wouldn't fall guys
never uno
only fall guys
i can't believe it it's a final
it's actually a final i can't believe it
it's really happening
i never thought the day would come it's
actually a final wait it's really small
what the heck what it's actually a 1v1
[Applause]
i thought it was gonna be the whole map
which way is it even spinning
this is dangerous
i don't feel so good about this
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm just making it harder for
us in the future we gotta end this
somehow you know
this is gonna be brutal
oh
oh cheese
oh it's brutal i'm sorry
assassin's creed
that's me
oh my goodness oh my goodness
[Music]
i did it
what did i say
i said i would win
that was really close though
okay i'm gonna make a new lobby
okay your code is
z
r
one
e
then go
oh maybe we should find one though i
think now there's 60 we have to do this
one
if i remember if we have time we can do
a fun one if it's not infinite
fall guys again
[Music]
i hope it's not infinite fall guys
we're on a time limit now
we have like 15 minutes
30 minutes was it really 30 minutes i
guess it probably was
at least that one
thanks for playing with me
especially those of you who played
infinite fall guys with me thank you
[Music]
you can throw if it's infinite but
where's the fun in throwing you know
i need to win i have that competitive
spirit inside but i don't think
this game is going to start
we are connecting to the server for a
while
gamer brain
i mean
oh yup
yup
i have been playing fall guys
no i mean
i'm playing games
all day today for 12 hours
what could be
more
gamer than that
oh well now we can do sorry everyone who
made it into that one
um
wait let's play lily leapers because i
talked about it
let's see if we can do the crazy mode
okay your code is
one
four
o
s
y
oh very fast
okay do you guys know the strategy from
this one i don't know it
but i'm gonna try
if there's someone in our lobby that
knows it i'm gonna die
i want to see it happen
i'll try to do it myself but i don't
think i can do it
but i want to practice by these bingo
numbers
i've been watching better call us all
and i watched the bingo
scene
better call saul is interesting so far
i think i just made it to season two i
know it just ended so no spoiler no
spoilers please i have to watch it still
i heard it's very good
[Music]
i feel bad for saul
i saw mean there was like salt and it
was like i'm gonna make my life the
worst it can possibly be you know oh no
no
[Music]
is fall guys dead
i think fall guys is dead
spoiler they call saul he's not even saw
yet but i am spoiler he becomes the saul
what
maybe we can just try the regular one
[Music]
see if it works sorry it's not together
lobby
i'm sorry
[Music]
oh it's working
i'm sorry i feel bad it's not custom
lobby but we only have 13 minutes so we
probably should get a move on
probably
nine hours left
that doesn't sound that bad
wait there's more no there's less than
that
there's like eight hours
i can count
little more than eight
[Music]
we're a third finished
and i
am going strong
i could play ball guys all day to be
honest
oh
[Music]
oh wait i forgot i'm like smurfing but
that person has the ice cream outfit
which means they have like
100 wins so
i can't be smurfing that badly
i take it all back what's the ice cream
up there
that's the prestige skin
they're the ones who are smurfing
if anything you see them up there
with their swirly
icy cone
i think the saplings are a lot better at
all guys than the average
populous though
the sapling lobbies are kind of purple
what does that say about saplings
it means you guys are great gamers
that's right that's right
i wouldn't expect anything less
hmm
we've all got a little bit of
competitive spirit maybe
[Music]
there's gamers in here
in my gaming stream
no
about 10 minutes
[Music]
i'm replying
next round please
do they put you in infinite fall guys if
you're in the public lobby
sleeping
yeah i'm just a little bit
that's not how i sleep i don't snore i
don't think anyway
but doesn't everyone think they don't
snore
until you go to the off collab and then
someone's like hey you were snoring last
night
i don't think i sleep talk either
i only get the
hypnagogic hallucination
that's my only quirky sleep thing
actually i got one this morning it's so
weird
because i never think that they're a
hallucination i always think they're
real
but i don't know what i thought i
saw it was like an abstract shape
and it was like
coming at me
like a spider web or something
and i was like i gotta get out of here
oh no
oh
i hate the donuts
i lost
why did i get an achievement though
why did i get an achievement called
flawless victory
are they just rubbing it in
[Music]
what the heck is that all about
is there anything good in the shop
free
oh
not free oh i hate
i hate the donuts
okay
[Music]
i like this minty face
okay
ten dollar sushi
oh yeah here we go the kudos shop that's
what i mean
um oh
this is cute
i don't really like this
i don't need any color that's not green
though
the gloves are kind of funny
i don't really like them though
for me
the shoes
they're okay i don't know though
oh look i have nothing
this is all i need though what are these
oh nice
kind of like peter pan shoes look this
is all i need
look i'm perfect
perfect bean
sausage skin doco right
okay i think i might
should i start setting up for uno now
mayhaps
i don't know if everyone else is ready
yet
but maybe
yes okay i'll start setting up i'll go
to brb screen it might be
several minutes though i apologize
please hold while we set everything up
yes another stretch break
okay i'll go
do that
i'll be right back
[Music]
so
hi guys hi everybody thank you guys for
joining my uno
party my 12 hour party stream
yeah
i just don't die i'm really hydrated
i'm hydrated i have a big bottle of
water and you got caught some snacks
[Music]
have some snacks prepared in the fridge
too if i get hungry
oh good
kill it thank you thank you but yes
right now we're going to play uno and i
have prepared a botsu wheel my very own
creation
i don't think it's too bad this time i
didn't put too much on it
actually can you find someone else to
take my place
this is just the beginning i saw a clip
of your camera where you were
you were doing an impression of me
and at first i was like
but then there was one moment i think
you were you were going like ooh and i
heard it and i was like wait that's me
though
that's me
it sounded perfect i don't remember
it was like one one moment it wasn't
i couldn't even distinguish it from my
own voice
[Laughter]
um do you wanna i don't know if you guys
can i have the wheel it'll be on my a
stream actually stream it for you guys
hold on
so you can trust you if you if you tell
us what it lands
on yesterday
and here is the wheel i'll just show it
for now
it sort of
hurts your eyes it's very impressive
oh wow
we have a southern accent for next round
whisper
for the next round do your best
after
[Laughter]
valley girl
and ubu voice
that's what we're working with today
can i get a sample
yeah can we get a sample yeah yeah
please fauna i just really want a sample
i feel like you already know
yeah like baby baby
voice okay okay okay
you can make your ours into
[Music]
oh no
here we go ladies
let's go
yeah
yeah this is uh i'm really good at this
game classic
very classic does uno involves skill
or is it just lucky
[Music]
oh gosh gotta go
okay
oh oh plus two already i'm sorry
so you have what it takes
oh nice
well we just started this means nothing
true reversed everything can change
it's a ruthless game oh
[Music]
okay
we're off to a good start
thank you for all the donations
of course anytime do you want more
remember payback's a [\h__\h] so
[Laughter]
waiting for clark
i'm knocking on the door so hard to get
through my cards from one side of the
other windows
oh wait did it just oh did you just give
me a ah there was a time limit oh it was
oh you could think i got an extra card
because of the time limit
on you
oh no
it's not my round huh
but it goes over to the next card so
slow
it kind of does right
it's really hard to reach the other side
that's pretty lucky
oh man we could like we can see if we
can like raise the time possibly maybe
yeah
oh no
now
you've got to say it or else do you lose
the game
explode
i chose yellow
[Music]
okay
because it looks like it's not actually
like pranking us um yeah actually i
don't think it does we just need to keep
track of how many cards we each have so
that can be a warm-up round
no no no
no it's because i left i gotta change
the rules okay okay okay okay
how do i leave uh quit
match
okay classification and then uh reset
score limit stacking how to quit
oh i found it uh yeah the plus plus mini
one should i get a punishment now
no i don't think so
it was a friend match anyways i mean
what was that what was the box wheel for
oh yeah
it sounds like someone wants a
punishment sorry guys it likes being
punished
[Music]
you can tell me when you want me to stop
and i'll push stop oh you can't raise
the time
i think you can scroll through the cards
faster with um with the joystick instead
of the d-pad
oh oh oh it stops immediately i love
confession you can confess
i don't like vegetables that much but
if it's you i
i guess i i wouldn't mind
making a smoothie out of you
what the [\h__\h] is this i can't believe it
that's what i'm doing
but it's like it's i think it's more
like
even better
i must make something up oopsy
there's a valley an effort though i mean
i had the theory part but um
thank you
i could have made it work i had
something different in mind first so
anyway this movie one is the best one
for now thank you very much
that's the best part
yeah i expected her that kind of
responsibility
i'm really surprised are you really
yeah from someone who turns their fans
into trees
they like
forever they like it terrific a simple
life being a tree don't have to worry
about that sorry beginning again
the cards
[Music]
could i not stack it
can you not do it
no sure
oh it depends you can stack it if it's
the same card
like completely the same part
or not completely just uh if the color
isn't the same that's fine
i might have pushed the wrong button
oh maybe maybe
must have been
so far how's it going you haven't uh you
aren't even halfway through right no
yeah i'm about four hours in almost four
and a half it's not bad so far i mean
four and a half hours is not easy
pretty normal
actually
just just the other day i had a stream
that was nine and a half hours so i
wouldn't mind doing another 12 hour
marathon either
i haven't done that long streams in a
long time but that just kind of happened
when i was trying to finish what is this
what is this again
challenge
[Laughter]
so what challenge means is that um
you're calling the other players bluff
that they don't have a different card
they could have played
okay
oh you're switching again
blue
yeah no no no thank you wait what what
i declined why did it give me cards oh
because i have to have is it a change
color and plus four yes correct it's a
powerful card
i didn't even let me put a blue card
down though
is that just not an option even though i
had
i mean
what's going on this game is ranked
winner winner oh that was so fast
i'm gonna be the only one getting the
games today huh
[Music]
okay what's the next spot sick yeah
yeah come on
bring it on
bring it throw us into the next match
let me know when you want to stop
so for you i guess it would be
me
i think you already did that with you
i'm really proud of the impressions
oh
i don't know what you're saying normally
but
i love my cats so today i cuddled with
them so much and then and then one of my
cats they jumped on my lap and it was
really cute i couldn't move oh
no
i'm really bad like
at the impressions i wish i could do
them well because i feel really funny
when especially the the japanese members
they can't do so well and they have
really funny streams they like games i
love that
i think we still have very different
voices though
i saw
a youtuber recently who did like 60
different youtuber impressions and they
were all spot-on
oh wow a couple of them did our voices
see different impressions
yeah they did a bunch of us too
oh
we were like actually spot on like i
couldn't believe it
yeah i guess some people just have a
really good talent for that kind of
thing
going on who's not playing i don't know
what is going on i already put down the
card
no timer's on
i just put down a car thing's happening
who's whose turn is you see or something
because
his turn after you put that i'm stuck
i'm stopped at the reverse card is it
kiara's turn because she's glowing
oh oh the cards were dark i thought i
don't know oh
i'm confused
um
it
doesn't
it doesn't
yeah i have a color changing ones and it
shows me playing when i'm on them but
i'm pressing play and it doesn't place
them this game's broken all right nice
thank you uno
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna make a new one
all right god damn i don't know
oh wait no that's because it's not you
it's a it's ai pudding
i think even the ai is frozen
possibly
all right ladies i'll make a brand new
um
great match
of course
play with standard you know deck
yes enter lobby
okay i call upon you now you know lords
might work better
just let us play for uno hour please
yes
this is a lot easier to get than the pc
version which is ridiculous yeah still
not working for me so
it's like it's almost just not even
worth it
yeah
i mean we're just missing fun huh
oh
can you invite me again maybe yeah i had
to invite fona a couple times for some
reason before
my game was frozen i think
i might need to restart my game
i keep inviting fana okay i'll restart
oh no please we just want to play a
little bit
i mean wow you would think for a game
for four dollars that it would be high
tech and not full of bugs four i feel
like i paid twenty twenty probes four
bucks it was it was on sale for this
switch to sale
oh
oh my god
can i use the european store
no
ah keys
[Laughter]
the game hates me
that's okay fauna i'm not fond of i'm
gonna say fauna pretty much
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and off we go i love your ipod it's very
fitting for you just like mine is very
fitting for me a huge monkey
[Laughter]
they're all very fitting do you like the
deer up
yeah i do
donkey kong he is the i don't know the
rap leader of the punch something like
that
he shoots yeah
yeah
the yeah crew something like that i
don't know yeah it's that's all i know
i acknowledge its existence though
mm-hmm
[Music]
is it on purpose
no no man we're just trying to survive
oh no it's ruthless tough world in here
yeah
yeah this game is more ruthless
honestly brutal
no mercy the unrest are not yet the holo
rust server has been pretty
well at least for me it's pretty cozy so
far
yeah
yeah it's because of me i've been
promoting peace and
harmony throughout
that's right
[Music]
oh i see you can challenge it oh that's
fine and yes i tried it by accident
before
i see oh
well it's for you
[Music]
like i'm gonna get some cards
[Laughter]
unless
you're too good
[Music]
well i'm not last wait who had them i
think it was me
i'll close my eyes
why does it give everybody the number
one uh medal
because everyone's a winner
everyone came special
you cannot challenge me at this game
that was great actually you did
wonderful
needs a bit more arrogance but besides
that more
[Music]
again
no
[Music]
no oh my gosh
now i know how it feels
[Music]
no god what oh no what happens if i
challenge you
do i just lose
oh you get even more cuz yeah
are you supposed to
oh wait are you supposed to choose the
color of cards that you have
you don't have to you can use whatever
color you want but if you challenge uh
even though
wait um cali explained it so well before
cali can explain it again
yeah i believe that if you play it then
you're supposed to call the other
person's glove that they
that they like couldn't have played any
other card or something like that
so the snare
sword isn't it
goddammit
[Music]
of the year tell me yeah
of the whole year
of the whole year i don't know you
remember it's hard to say there's been
so much
i think that
off collabs are definitely a highlight
[Music]
who did you not meet
um i haven't met everyone iris or sana
am i the only person that's met iris
oh yeah i think yeah i didn't see her
because she hasn't left so yeah japan so
and we haven't been able to go to japan
so
[Music]
hold up how is she like tell me the
sweetest person i've ever met in my life
and so innocent same thing about iron
man
oh yeah
but you know i don't have blue fonda
i just want to pick her up and swing her
around and just uh
she eats so slow
[Laughter]
she's very dainty sometimes
[Music]
goddammit
everybody
yeah
well soon you guys did you hear that
they're opening up japan to people that
arrange visits through travel agencies
at all unless whole life suddenly opens
a travel agency which they could
wouldn't that be such a big brain move
right
that'll be cool
[Music]
it looks like steps are being made
because you know
um
it's been a long time
you know you trigger
[Music]
get back over there i love it i love
blue
oh no
cards oh no
come on
i'm really lucky with these straws
though
maybe i don't actually love the flowers
[Music]
not the flowers
after thinking it over let's not choose
blues
yeah
until someone gets the color change
oh oh oh how about yellow
oh okay okay okay
[Music]
fauna
this is what you get for blue
[Applause]
okay retribution
we gotta stop here
is this the day is this the day where
are you going
i don't know
oh no actually just kidding
i had no other cards
set sure sure
all right so green is the card to play
wait did that still count as i didn't
have to say uno again thank god okay um
[Music]
you know i keep on playing red because i
like the fire
that makes sense
[Music]
oh
oh give me the win come on come on
no
oh you too
oh
yeah
do something
[Music]
this is a tough one
to play the card i drew
it's a fun game
we have to be ready
okay okay okay
[Music]
sorry
oh
[Music]
the others were so fast this is the
never-ending one
oh we're saved
come on man
make the difference bigger okay this
game can go on forever
not like that
[Music]
okay
what are your goals for the year here's
a topic
i don't know i feel like she's trying to
do the same no i'm just trying to just
[Laughter]
all right during an intense game of uno
[Music]
3d become 3d would be great
i hope so second year come on
definitely
positive thinking
keep learning
but that was also my goal for last year
oh
well that's a bit
i mean a goal is a goal until
no forever really
always get better
but what about you guys what are your
goals for this year you're an animal
she's
very soon as well very very soon
well i also kind of want to do a
a 3d concert like a proper one not not
on youtube only one you know yeah
but it's uh
um
a difficult matter
but hopefully with one year time
i will get my turn i pray for it
i believe
[Music]
and also full album is one goal yeah
yeah
oh no
[\h__\h]
okay
[Applause]
[Laughter]
you really wanted to make sure that they
knew that
say stop whenever you're ready oh i get
a medal
[Music]
um
oh another impression do impression of
the person below you of ena
[Laughter]
don't save him
don't say it we forgot you
i just like building things
like chilling things
[Laughter]
soft and comfy
awesome
[Music]
that's a recorder
[Laughter]
yeah i was thinking the same thing today
i was thinking about the song just today
i was like does that count which song
i know we can't sing it but it's not
disney from what i know oh so i don't
know did they license it
oh well better be safe
by mickey mouse
cali i still sometimes remember the
goofy
impression you did
oh yeah it brings me back to life
um as goofy
oh that's great
yeah it was good should i put goofy
impression on the boxer wheel
no yes i want to hear kiara's goofy
voice i mean
i don't know what that is
oh no
he must be stopped
oh nice that works too
mm-hmm
so does she have are you happy enough
oh the mind games jesus i'm sorry i
can't
yeah
[Music]
all right back in the game yeah
yeah another close one
yeah i'll take it it's fine
i want my favorite color
yes
you're giving me
many cards
[Music]
yeah there's the college one and the
vacation one college one
yeah
they're like a bunch of like frat boys
like frat
dog humans yeah
and there's a guy named uh bradley
uppercrust the third what
and he's my favorite character he's such
a dick
oh
no god that's a fun movie but i like the
vacation one more
i don't know if i've seen the vacation
do they actually sing in those movies or
did i imagine it yep they do not know
the second one isn't the musical the
first one is oh
yeah that sounds rather interesting
no that's good it's good music like
they're good songs
i'm sorry
no
oh
haramah
[Music]
i guess you can't see what
you're getting too close oh thank you
i could use these
yes
i will use these
oh no
i'm scared
so that's all part of my playing aura
it's just a game
on the line
i mean true but they're kind of fun
how do you feel about me about the
squats the 10 squats
oh
yes
i want that one
yeah i love squats that's the worst one
[Music]
oh shoot you don't like squats kiara i
messed up
i am
[Music]
i think
yes
oh
midnight here almost 1am so i shall
whisper from now on oops
comfy potential asmr
everyone's feeling blessed now this is a
wheel of blessings
whispering
love forever
i'm like i've laughed forever see i know
i know you said you don't like asmr but
you'd be so good at it
um
if i mean if you it could be like it's
sunday
yeah like doing it while not enjoying
doing it yeah yeah
whisper in your ear you weirdo
it's not like i want to make you fall
asleep and
slam you in the back while you're
sleeping
the hair is soon you're hungry
[Applause]
blessed combination oh
i have a
first for blood these days
i mean how far does the tsundere have to
go like surgeries can be bullies but
when does it cross into yandere
i always thought that sunday it was more
like it's not like i like you baca so
it's like
you're like mean to them but like you
secretly like them so you'll be like oh
you're so stupid why are you such a
dummy
and like insult them in a sense it can
it can vary how much you insult them it
could be mild disdain to like full-on
like you are the worst human being i've
ever met oh you're so annoying why do i
love you so much like that kind of thing
kelly you seem like an extrovert
what if you start like you know
like slapping a suitor who slaps
is that still soon right does that count
like some little bullying like step on
your toes kind of thing
i mean i haven't really seen a sunday
that like really like slaps someone
because then that like
okay okay would you consider
kind of in that character she is and
also
louise from zero not skyma definitely
[Music]
but she still really likes him right yes
she doesn't admit it though
she's not true to her heart
i see
yeah i guess
[Music]
but then at some point there there
becomes a line of of threatening and
fear where you can be in the soon yonder
[Music]
wait did i make a mistake
yes no no no
no
[Music]
oh it's okay i'll use these cards
that's so threatening it's like no i
will use these cards
oh no oh yes
so we know she has no red in her pocket
i'll keep it red
i'll keep it red though
video
[Music]
sorry
oh i saw your card though i saw your
card how did you see it
oh when i challenge it it shows um what
card they have
what oh
well it doesn't matter that's kind of
smart actually i just want to see this
little [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh my god it's a bloodbath oh no it is a
bloodbath
no mercy
decline
i won't challenge
[Music]
recently released a song called you
little [\h__\h] it's now in the charts
please yeah i saw that
okay okay
[Music]
oh yeah
every man from stealth out here
all right she doesn't have green
you're always paying attention to kara
but now callie has the same amount of
cards
[Music]
i'm not doing anything i'm just playing
a little card
you guys know me i'm getting yes
yes
oh come batty games
the good thing is when you block
someone's turn they can also not get
a new card
so
ah now i don't know which characters
left
so am i really the enemy
now both of you have to hit me
it's up to
[Laughter]
is it my turn
[Music]
ask
southern accent for the next round
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm throwing some apples out there the
mighty fine real sweet
i feel like this should have gone
kelly isn't too good at it she's natural
i don't need to go to cali because she
will do it without the bat's wheel
[Laughter]
it's your true self freaking out let's
do what's the whole talk with vina so we
get her to talk as much as possible
[Music]
are you sure you want to do that i can't
i can't give you i can give you heaven
or hell right now it doesn't sound like
cell phone accidents i can give heaven
or hell
there you go
for real yeah there we go
is she did you miss your turn
she was too busy heating and hauling
i was too busy
the cowboy is worth it
you could have played a different card
what's your favorite pastime
is a
riding
i don't know a cow
[Laughter]
in the field where do you write
yourselves
in the field and the road
it's the pastures
they go fast
you ride them out in the past
like a specific
species of cows that let you ride them
and are like good at it
uh
is it called a cow fauna perhaps
no
no no that's this is okay
please don't do not give them
[Laughter]
i'm ideas
i think any cow will let you ride them
right they're all pretty docile right
they will not lie
will they enjoy being controlled by
the thingy that you put around their
mouth
most likely no
you're not made for it
that's a hyena is oh no no
that's fast i'm so sad for a cowboy
yeah let's go
oh no
okay
i um
have yellow
you totally do i believe you she's using
reverse psychology yeah i don't know
i definitely have blue yeah
[Laughter]
i'm just going to go ahead and change
the color to blue real quick
[Music]
you probably have blue too right
okay
i have blue yes
[Music]
blue friends
friends friends
hey
a real toxic
game better worse than monopoly
keep on getting the good cards
it's not better than monopoly on nothing
yeah
oh
i definitely i don't like sitting next
to ina
please lock me
south for an accident
oh no no no no no no no no no
uh-oh oh okay thank you
that's fine we're just resulting
inevitable
we're delaying it as much as we can a
little less obese
well really the goal is not to win the
goal is just to not be in last place so
you don't have to do the boxing right
i do specialize in not coming in last
which is fun
[Music]
okay okay okay asserting dominance on
the battlefield you really are
we need you know to talk a bit more
do you like that
or what about like
peach peaches
please why my favorite
i can't
no you're doing great
uh my switch is done let me find the
[\h__\h] charger
oh no i'm kicking you while you're down
while you're searching
for a switch charger
okay
we're safe now
okay i'm not safe or peach cobbler or
peach iced tea that sounds really good
right now
i love peach stuff me too
what's your favorite fruit
i guess i would have to go for the
strawberries i know it's basic but who
doesn't love strawberries but i like
so many fruits yeah me too strawberries
are up there for me too
hell yeah
how about you ina favorite fruit
pineapple oh i love pineapples really
good um
yeah one time i ate like a whole
pineapple by myself and my mouth hurt so
bad afterwards
when your tongue starts peeling
[Music]
sorry oh thank you
oh no yeah i like blue
i like it now i didn't the past game
i don't like the blue
it's interesting how quick
these
things change
true
truth such as the way of uno
uh oh and the timer
ah damn it i was not looking at that
what if the game just never ended
be kind of fun kind of like gucci cash
money
playing fall guys before this and
there's a glitch and fall guys that
makes it go forever
um
experience forever in one game or um you
just get like infinite race rounds and
there's never a finale
this is like a nightmare
yeah
it's part of the dark fall guys
no
[Music]
no big bully in a vibes right now
let's see right
[Music]
damn it
can i just like play a six and see if no
one notices
a computer
computer nozzle
it should be included in the computer i
think if we can fold a computer
that would be nice
that would make it realistic i think
that with monopoly too isn't a big part
of monopoly cheating like pocketing
money from the bank
nobody's looking
not in my world
but i see who i'm not gonna play with
will not live anymore
imagine imagine that that becomes a rule
and then you just have people beating
each other up playing monopoly saying
this is the real world [\h__\h] i can just
steal your money yeah we're moving in
fauna you have to be more careful oh i
didn't call uno again
you're right oops
what the [\h__\h] it didn't
register it
i can't even be mad
have you ever heard of no rules monopoly
no
it's basically just monopoly but there's
no rules so you can cheat you can
you can bet real money
is
makes no sense
the game just doesn't work
maybe we just want to play with it
actually forgetting it though you're
actually forgetting it right
no
i would always remember
i pushed the button
the game must be broken
yeah
certainly certainly mm-hmm
demands uno we play uno
uh-oh the power's the bee they want us
to continue
let's see
is real good at that she's so on alert
man
damn that's how i do it in the shelf
you know what go for it
oh
[Music]
she would have had another option
i thought she's gone again
[Music]
yes
i kind of have no choice but oh it's
like me
um
no
what could it be
okay
[Laughter]
no blues we continue
[Music]
um and on and
a wall of cards
[Music]
that's what you get for calling uno on
me
oh
finally worked
oh i'll use these
oh
yum yum
ah
one two
four
oh maybe if i play red it'll be obvious
what color card i have so i should play
a different color so they don't know
oh my god you know
oh thank god it's over fun i had the
most times in the end
maybe i just wanted to do
everybody will enjoy you doing more bad
swings okay
is true true
stop
oh no
or should i stay on your own
[Music]
why is god forsaken me
okay i'll accept your four cards
[Music]
no fauna
no
[Laughter]
they just they just don't give a [\h__\h]
not today you're not getting the lolly
no no no candy no no
[Applause]
you have to eat healthy to stay strong
for the rest
of your career
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh you should um well
damn it okay i'm suffering here
everyone is quite literally suffering
yes
we can all suffer
together and uno
oh
okay
that's pretty slick
it's just in time
i found this documentary about cats on
netflix did you see that one is it
called the secret life of pets
is the one where they try to prove that
cats are pretty smart and don't lose
against dogs oh pretty much
even i don't believe that one
what the [\h__\h]
are you kidding me
it's just so obvious no i'm joking i
love dogs neurons
brain
i think they're even smart they have
more density than cats i think they're
neurons symphony is always two times the
amount of cats
well but but the thing is they haven't
done as much research on cats yet
that's the
argument yeah
yeah yeah well cats are more fair one
and dogs are dogs are quite domesticated
really so
wait what i have cats they're very much
not feral at all no
that's compared to dogs cats are a lot
less domesticated than dogs
bro have you seen wolves
exactly
compared to a chihuahua
[Music]
anyway i just wanted to recommend it to
you because it's pretty cute you know
yeah
the documentary
i've seen the one called why i didn't
watch a lot of his secret labs of pets
where they film pets when their owners
are away for the day oh
definitely
that was awesome netflix
[Music]
oh i think i've seen it in the
recommendations
there's also one i think is called like
the secret world of fungus
oh what's the secret of the fungus then
they are magical when you don't work
most people knew that already
just really pretty shots of
mushrooms glowing in the forest
[Laughter]
[Music]
well i i spent a lot of time with vanta
song
oh
[Music]
that's right yeah
yeah correct yeah rubbed off on you yeah
thank you sensei
yeah you're welcome
[Music]
i don't
unfortunately i can't finish it yet
[Music]
legendary
you have to push the button you have to
press the button
my little brain can't remember
too
[Music]
too much information to the brain
small memory card
only no
color card match color card play game
match number
no even magic number a little advanced
for me
this is bad
there we go
ollie
sorry
i gave you more chances to say
gotta remember someday
after enough attempts
will she make it this time
well callie will show him good job
i remember
no
i don't wanna oh
okay
sorry wow
[Music]
well i have the most cards once again
the wheel for you
oh again
there's not that many choices here
already have a couple that's true
stop
how about wait what did you do an
impression of callie instead
oh dear
come back you can do it
sound like a fool
ah
oh god um
the only thing i can think of right now
is making an impression of cowboy cali
just doing a cowboy
it's my native accent
oh
no
i hate impressions can i give can i just
choose one of the um batsu's that
haven't been like
haven't come up at all do you need to
see them or do you remember
what's going on besides
what squads are fun
what is the blue one um hold on let me
look
what is that i know that self an accent
what didn't we have we had
oh oh can i do valley girl yeah
okay so let's do this i finally want to
win like i totally deserve it oh gosh
why am i wasting my time here anyway you
guys don't deserve my presents
i like already
[Music]
i'm pretty sure
i'm never wrong anyway
it's perfect valley girl kiara is
perfect
i need to see the fan art
yeah i can actually kind of imagine
right with some star bees
with like a ton of like shopping bags
starvies yeah like sunglasses on her
head like a long nails like limp like
lip plumping
lip gloss
has eyelashes long nails
i think i would use a lip plumper my
lips
to begin with oh my god
well i mean you wouldn't that's enough
uh perfect face i was making plenty of
plenty of people with huge lips use lip
plumping
uh lip gloss anyway
any bigger than this and the beauty
standards are gonna change in this world
okay
she sets the beauty standards herself
next level
it will be like that girl
oh my god girl
oh
no oh
doesn't like a valley girl just need her
bestie like oh my god
i need my bestie but if my bestie always
has to be a little bit less attractive
than me you know
can't have anyone on my level almost
have to be below off my level yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
if you're like the most attractive
person in the room i just like leave
like what's even the point
attract me right
now
i'm just i'm just enjoying their prints
of course that's something all right
very beautiful what's your favorite
hobby valley girl
chihuahua my favorite hobby
is choosing a new butler every day
because it's just so much fun choosing
new people to do stuff for me and then
they they i don't even do any hobbies
you know because it's a waste of my time
so i let them do my hobbies
yeah what happened
to the old butlers that you fired or
what happened to them
what happens to the old bug if you get a
new butler every day what happens to
yesterday's butler i don't understand
the question
oh no
i can't deal with this
all right all right i'll i'll
ask your butler
yeah okay that's what he's here for
you didn't call him wow
he had one freaking job please
[Music]
a little bit longer
she's so good
it's like hard to remember to like push
the button you know like i'm not used to
putting in so much effort in something
you know like
wait you have to push the buttons
yourself i have my butler do it oh girl
that is so smart
i wish i could be more like you guys
all right
who had the most power
no more
who was that that was the problem why
did you i was gonna i was gonna die with
without that enough air
i think two people had four cards in the
end i don't think there was a clear
loser
no i think i lost
oh should we do one more
let's do the last round
one more round each round spin
spin for cali let me know when you want
to stop
stop
oh
it's ten squats
yeah all right one sec
i'll do them properly too with my knees
all right here we go
okay
let me just position myself shoulder
width apart all right
one
two
three
[Music]
four
five
i can keep going i'm gonna keep going oh
it's okay
she's going off now
and then you're probably gonna do it
like you're supposed to like hold like a
weight in the middle of this
i'm doing some more today actually is
callie currently the fittest
en member
oh
it releases endorphins it makes you feel
really good dolphins
[Music]
you must be really happy
yeah yeah i mean dolphins
[Music]
i need to go to the gym
but i am too lazy
that's okay only when you're ready i
just met everyone
dancing and i go swimming sometimes
that's so slimy
[Music]
dance dance dance dance revolution
yeah it's a great way to like do the
cardio to get your heart pumping when
you're dancing do a fun song
you can just like play a horror game
to get your heart something
nothing i mean i guess definitely i
guess that works too
oh she
did said
job
i remembered
thanksgi and i win
oh
that was the speed round
[Applause]
[Music]
do we have one
who was it all right what's the last one
wait who had the most cars was it me
oh my god please don't you wanna do one
together in solidarity
hell yeah let's do it
i don't know if there's any way i've
been done yet though
we could come up with a new one chad
come up with a new one yeah let's go
down here
maybe a batsu that fauna can do for the
rest of the stream
for the next segment or so i don't
know the next 10 minutes
all right so the stream is pretty long
indeed
i'm seeing a lot of different things
yeah
a lot of them want the otter on them but
i already made you doing i don't know
i feel bad
yeah yeah yeah
ten push-ups
push-ups i can't even do push-ups in
here
i could do wall push-ups like somebody
said
fan of french only you speak french oh
friends
oh they call
it
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
that was good i think speak french yeah
that was good that was good that was a
good box
okay thank you guys for joining me i
appreciate it
good luck for the rest
thank you
we're cheering for you
you're gonna do a two twelve 12-hour
marathons
oh just like you did with the super chat
reading
is that the super chat rating will be
around 12 hours too just like
i had myself
good luck with that so i can force you
in
thank you
all right thank you guys
[Music]
oh i mean i left too fast i think hero
was saying something
sorry sorry
sorry sorry okay
let's go back here
[Music]
yay that was fun
i'm glad it worked even though uno is a
little bit
sometimes
[Music]
okay i have to remember what's up next
on the schedule
oh no we have to watch the debut
oh
[Music]
shoot it's that time it's time to cringe
oh no
[Music]
they debuffana oh no
try get snack for the
debut watch a lot
i want popcorn but i don't have popcorn
that would be a good snack to watch
though watch the debut with popcorn
but i don't have popcorn
but now popcorn sounds really good
cringe time
you shall make popcorn for yourself you
should
you should
[Music]
okay
my brain is
frazzled now
i don't know what's happening anymore
it's weird to do a collab and then like
keep streaming
afterwards and we have another cloud
later
in
oh just two hours i guess
just two hours
we have kind of a lot of time though in
between now and the the next collab
um because we're gonna do some tear
lists
but i don't have
i have only two
planned
and they might be short so i might need
you guys to
give me ideas for more tier lists that
we can do
[Music]
yeah
12 power switch sports
thank you too this weekend thank you
thank you
power cheerless i don't know i'm scared
to do anything this
um
actually
ranking people
i mean power level is
i don't want to make anyone mad if i put
them in the baby tier
i was well i won't tell you my plans yet
you'll have to wait and see i do have
some planned
[Music]
more power level
fingernail tier list
that would be interesting
[Music]
but i don't know
okay
um
i do think i i think i have my
debut
prepped already
[Music]
but i'll probably go
be right back and get some more water
and maybe some snacks my water bottle
made it sound like a ghast
in minecraft i don't know if you heard
it it was like
panda streams tearless that's a pretty
good idea
[Music]
but i didn't plan that far in advance
wasn't moomin going through her her
streams that was a good idea
i really liked moo man's debut yesterday
i mean the nazis debut she's a great new
streamer really confident for her debut
really excited to see where she goes
from there
[Music]
okay okay i'll be right back i'm gonna
go get a snack
and
more water and then i'll be back and
we'll watch
my debut oh gosh oh gosh
i'll be right back
[Music]
hello i got a snack
and i fed my cats
they got a snack too
i was one of my earrings fell out though
and i couldn't find it
so i have to like look for it
oh oh
oh
that's for future fun and to worry about
i have a soup
yummy soup
i thought soup would be good because
it's easy to eat
on stream
because i don't like to eat on stream
soup
[Music]
okay i guess we have to watch my debut
now
that's fine i can just sit and watch and
eat soup and silently cringe and also
react
audibly
not silently
[Music]
okay
i don't know if i'm ready
um
where did i put it
in here
over here
[Music]
the music
okay
all right debuff on them
time to impress me
okay
let's fast forward
if i can
[Music]
oh oh my gosh we're going to watch the
trailer oh my goodness
it breaks the cringe
[Music]
how's the volume by the way
the manipulator is active once more
even with the powerful gods the destined
end cannot be denied and if the good
okay is already sealed
you may feel weak and helpless
thus
[Music]
hey that's my apple
weird to think about
space
where does the difference lie between
zero and one
the only way to save the point is to
validate the existence of space
nature
intellects have long been receiving
blessings from mother nature who are
they it is all intellect human nature to
abandon appreciation who's abandoning
appreciation
not you right since when have you
realized the flow of time
ever since
all life forms have been trapped and
tortured
civilization
civilization is proof of humankind's
footsteps
we cannot advance simply by building
never forget you know what
the world is not it's very bitter sweet
because i just can't shoot him not being
bound
forever part of my debut too
[Music]
we'll watch it together
it's very nostalgic it's very nostalgic
oh
[Music]
i haven't watched this at all
since back then
[Music]
it's very nostalgic isn't it
four and a half billion years ago
gravity pulled gas and dust together to
form i love sauna from the debris of
empty space
came a planet where nature could thrive
single celled organisms
microscopic this is pretty cute and
giant redwood trees oh gosh that art is
kind of bad though communicating through
underground networks
animals that can adapt i made this
pretty fast
life
we didn't have a lot of time to prepare
for our debut surface was morphed by
tectonic plates and erupting volcanoes
my crayon drawing
nature
persisted
space
was no longer alone
she's still not alone
had claimed her place
in the universe
along with nature
my
[Music]
to heal and protect all living things on
earth
yup yup that's me up
and today is a very lucky day oh this
part's so cute though i'm coming to you
live right outside farfa's window
that's right
today we have a rare opportunity to be
far far in a natural habitat
let's see what the beauty of nature
herself is
[Music]
ah
um
that's me
real picture we should come back in a
few minutes
hey
do you want to see me without my size
limiter
i remember i wanted to like do some kind
of explosion animation
but i didn't know how
i have time
to figure it out
hey
oh do you say
wake up
it's time to wake up
is it quiet for you or just for me
well
sana really did a number on you guys i
i had to go and revive the whole earth
and all of you
using just a bit of my my golden apple
powers
the lord the lord
you're wondering who this this strange
woman is
who revived you um
she
i don't mind telling you a little about
myself
and i think i have just the way to do it
one second
confidence
what what the heck
come back
why did she go i wasn't listening
i don't remember this at all i'm not
realizing
why did you go to that screen i was uh
just wandering around in the woods uh
like i do
and um
funny
this is such a youtuber debut
uh oh my god wait
[Music]
there
i found this big book
it's heavy
um it claims to be
the field guide to fauna
but i was reading it and they got some
things wrong they did so i had to make
some changes um you'll see but
you know they got most of them
i like how calm i was talking back then
to be honest
and also i should talk more calmly i
just want to say thank you to everyone
for coming out
uh thank you for bearing with us oh the
ian she's so calm it did strike us
but we're here today and uh thank you
for being flexible with me and us and
coming to see me anyway
so
let's let's see what this book this book
has to say about who is she let's see
what the game is
we she has the cute awkward charm of a
freshly debuted youtuber
sanders fana
by serious fauna why did i say it like
that oh my gosh i'm embarrassed usually
i go bye
i love that
which is okay if you want to be extra
formal that's okay
but wouldn't you i don't mind i don't
mind i prefer fana so fana chan
uh
anything works
[Music]
details here huh
they really just reveal it all in these
field guides i guess that's the purpose
my wrist i'm a curing
on the mythological
keyring
you'll have to go do some more research
on your own but that's why i have these
horns
they look like branches um they're not
dear antlers
i feel like i'm watching a different
person
i told you i'm not but i feel like she's
cute and i'm kind of jealous my age
see this one is a little i feel like
i've become a gremlin like a god you
know i know even i feel like my voice
sounds more goblin can i sound like her
if i try even
the stream title seems to say mama i
don't know who wrote that
you wrote it i was you talk like her um
a big sister
but hello i'm serious
it's really nice to meet all of you you
can call me mama if you want i am mother
nature after all so maybe it just comes
with the with the territory
but you can call me see i'm not that old
i'm only four and a half call me uh four
and a half billion
so
i can't think of anything funny to say
oh my god that would have been a good
place but you know i feel really tall
compared to a lot of a hollow men
but whenever i go out into
you know whenever i leave my forest and
go see humans uh sometimes i do want to
go see what see what you guys are up to
i feel like i've become more energetic
so 100
i won't forgive you she sounds kind of
cute well
maybe maybe if you ask me nicely i'll
forgive you but
you might um
[Music]
i know now i'm just like
i'm old i'm a little worn
[Music]
they had a lot to say didn't they they
were a whole
hole i say they sure did please don't
read that whole book even i don't think
i read that out loud please don't i
think you've done this before so
we don't have to go through this
next
this page is a little embarrassing don't
you think
[Music]
field guides really do show everything
this is so awkward we have um
[Music]
i think every day
you can see here some uh charm points of
my anatomy
we have um asymmetry you can see my hair
if i'm not cute and soft-spoken anymore
and i still
have these same charm points and uh
see they're trying to reveal so much
about me so i had to scribble it out you
know a lady has to maintain her modesty
right
uh
a lady
is that when i thought of myself as as a
reason do you really expect mother
nature to wear shoes
it's just so i can be connected to the
earth you know you know you don't have
to explain it you don't have to explain
everything you know
like that's what i would tell her
you don't have to explain why you're not
wearing shoes a mark of
a
distinguishment
[Music]
uh and of course distinguishment
not dear aunt
please wanna explain to me the beauty
mark
please
and
next
my mama
i am so so thankful to her
still true
such
an amazing artist and i it's still true
grateful
still true
it's my mama so thank you so much
thank you my mom thank you so pretty
[Music]
thank you
oh my god for being so supportive she's
so supportive even though she's busy and
has busy schedule and is doing so much
she's so supportive of me i love all the
clues she gave me and how soft her art
is true so detailed and so pretty
so thank you thank you true
and
we also have my papa
thank you mom
thank you so much
allowed me to wait wait look at
i have some great physics which i'll
show off later great physics what do you
mean by that look at this
and move like i can
so thank you
he also did
uh the live 2d for a bunch of my senpai
way more and moment in this book
and islands i included just a few up
here and including uh ina ina senpai
from hong kong i think as well iris
senpai i believe
we have
some ian membrane
she's so innocent though some more
personal
personal details
[Music]
is it funny
so here are some of my likes and uh just
a few dislikes
i love animals i still like these things
i love animals with my whole heart
animals
just make the world a better place i
didn't realize i talked about this in my
day beach i'm sure you should talk that
much about my love for animals but it's
true i i really to me animals are like
my
i don't know if they like spend all of
my days with my favorite thing in the
whole world
and um
you know i know that there's more to
nature than just animals there's also
plants and fungi and
uh
protists
etc but
yes yes don't forget about
my name is rk reason and not flora so
you know maybe a mother shouldn't pick
favorites but um
you hear that just what that is
not flora
[Music]
and um i did the little art for my intro
video and i did all my layouts and stuff
too but again i'm no pro
i know i'm learning and getting better
and i think the layout i mean is okay
but i think it's also kind of sloppy
and i keep seeing like
i can't post like gifts on twitter so
fast of me from my debut or from the
early days when i had this background
and i keep seeing the background and
just reminds me of my
shoddy handy work i hope to do drawing
streams in the future um
and i hope to show you my true drawing
powers and not just draw like a cute
it'll only keep you like a year
strong please draw something serious as
well
so look forward to that um i also like
playing kalimba i love my kalimba
it's uh if you don't know klimba is like
a little thumb piano it's this little
instrument this little amazing do you
have it
it for you um hashtag
i'm not the best i only started learning
earlier this year so i'm still a
beginner but um i've always been
a bit musically i'm still a beginner
but a columba isn't like my speed you
know so um it's been nice to work on my
music skills just a little bit
so i hope to do some coimba concerts
it's a really really amazing a relaxing
little instrument
i also love tea
uh i will probably drink tea during
mostly i might have to make a cup of tea
but i'm a bit particular after this how
i take my tea as i think most tea
drinkers are
i drink it just hot tea no milk no sugar
that's true perfect but now i drink
matcha a lot and of course i won't judge
you
i won't judge you even if you uh
pour in like 20 packets of sugar
upgraded to latte it's for a couple no
it's just because it's like still summer
i also love co-op games um so i want to
drink i like to play games but not
really hot to you
sometimes i get lonely when i'm playing
a game by myself
so i prefer to play with friends um
and i'm not a competitive person so i'm
not a great person shoots co-op games
okay well i and that's kind of why i
stand by that i mean as well because it
means i can't i don't
well i think this is the problem what
kind of team well i think the problem is
that i am competitive but i don't like
competition
i think that's the problem
peaches are like i don't like probably
to play a highly competitive game
against my friends
like monopoly or something and it's just
like brutal
that's true i don't like i don't i just
hated sorry
the monopoly collab was fun but i think
monopoly is a bad game it's not fun to
play with people
but um
but you don't play don't into his code
you guys don't understand yeah you guys
playing to his club you don't play
against your friends you play with your
friends together
i like co-op games better than me it's
insane twice that'd be lots of fun
[Music]
is it like an apple edible of course it
is you guys don't understand how to
shove you can be competitive without
wanting to compete with your friends
understand that
it's it's a bit of a process but you
know nothing nothing i can't handle
was that's um surprise or maybe it was
just depending on how cool you guys
it was just me on twitter um especially
psychological horror i'm gonna smack you
guys i can't understand it
but i'm a bit of a baby when it comes to
horror games i get scared so
i usually need someone to hold my hand
but i want to i want to undergo my
training arc so that um
i can i can learn to play by myself with
without fear i sort of did that
and um
i don't know i think i'm better
well i guess we'll find out i want to
play outlast another minute i don't know
it's important that i mention this that
i love cats
uh as for my dislikes um i don't like to
eat mushrooms i love mushrooms and i
think they're really true and people
still don't know this about really cool
they still like show me pictures of
mushrooms they're like ha ha look and
i'm like
that's so cool i love that spread their
spores people don't get it and that's
really cool
even like them the largest organism is
the honey fungus yeah mushrooms are
great i mean i have a mushroom in my
loading
square miles maybe more
like eight square kilometers
[Music]
yeah they're really cool but i don't
like
the texture of them
eating them
i prefer to observe them
instead of eat them
and um
also
i know they're part of nature
and i should love
all of nature's creations but
grasshoppers are scary
true
grasshoppers are scary have you seen
them
they're sitting on the grass offering
your faces
but i was
being misleading here
because i didn't want to reveal my true
from the ground using their
my debut back legs
because i was scared people would like
tweet me pictures of
roaches or something grasshoppers if i
said i hated them and i i tried to i
picked grasshoppers which i also dislike
but not as much as i dislike
you know cause they're spooky i like
spooky uh spiders i can i can chill with
spiders i like spiders as long as
they're not crawling on me
but but grasshoppers
scary
[Music]
alright
yay
now here is why i wanted to mention cats
because i have two cats myself
their names are clover and snail and
they're kind of both old men
old man cats they're my sweet boys and
you'll probably hear
uh snails
at some point
if not today then another stream because
he likes to come by this point i had
only had a snail for about a month
when i didn't think i only adopted him
like a month before extremely old man
um
he
that's the equivalent i don't know
what he does
so just think about a like 100 year old
grandpa when you think about him when
you hear him and you'll understand
you'll understand why i spoil him and
i'll let him complain and indulge in his
request to
come inside and outside the
my bedroom
um
and uh i have to help him get on the bed
and stuff
i try to spoil him as much as i can
and um i have snail as well snail i only
recently adopted but he is just the
sweetest cat
ever true i love black cats
he's 10 years old so he's about middle
aged um and he's a sweet lab cat he just
loved to sit in my life
all day and that's all i really the
worst part of the 12 hour stream is not
beginning to snuggle the cats
we'll see we'll see
and my favorites
it's really hard for me to pick a
favorite game uh these games are all
very near and dear is he a cat or a
snail he's a cat i guess i should
explain why his name is snails i was
talking so because he's shaking like a
snail
because he has a very round
body
so it's like a round snail body and then
his head
that's the reason
i don't do it
i don't know
my favorite games um i see some people
liking 999 already
999 is so
special and i love kotaro uchikoshi so
much
this game the fangirl is coming out
i can't i can't get enough i'm closer to
the mic now i might be other works
either it might be my setup was kind of
scary
yeah and i know renee has been playing
them and that's been amazing and i used
to not listen to myself either when i
talk i won't want people to play it so
if i put it on my way i just love it it
has everything i like
psychologically
anime
it's very good
incredible incredible truly i'm glad to
see some uh fans in the chat that makes
me happy
um i also have animal houses
a good mix of um creepy hi everyone
welcome
[Music]
i sounded so cute back then it's so pure
what happened
i became a grandma
just turn on okami and just like run
around
run around as a wolf in this beautiful
world and
i don't know okami really shows you the
beauty of nature i think
um i also love soma which i know uh i do
love so much playing this week
and i know ena recently played it as
well uh soma one of my favorite horror
games against psychological horror it
gave me many
uh
existential crises but in a good way
truly anything that still does every
game is so much i love soma um also
super mario odyssey just a fun game i
don't actually use a different mic my
microphone is the same it's fun
that's the microphone i have
it's pretty good microphone like
how can you not love that
[Music]
okay and for anime um i have the shure
sm7b to be honest these are like my
all-time favorites and i think there are
a lot of people's all-time favorites
yeah you see a lot of dark stuff here
yeah you can tell i like
i like but i think it is way closer
because i used to have really stuffed
you know beautiful
um
hunter hunter so good
and death note oh and made in abyss
almost skipped that one perhaps the
darkest of them all made an abyss that
one like i almost couldn't even still
love this anime it's so good and the
world is so good i don't think my list
of favorite anime has changed if you
have any anime recommendations i guess
it has
oh god taxi wasn't here yet oh never
mind
i take it all back a taxi favorite
authority is like the best show ever not
really they're all good but it's 10 out
of 10. i don't i don't know too many
animals that are that are like this i
like them
i like babies
and i like characters and i like
psychological
hi callie hi kelly said bye
i was also shy about a show
i wasn't shy about my music taste
that's just i did not include anything
it can be quite emo or alternative
um there's a bunch of other stuff i
listen to but uh i really like relaxing
music um well i like realizing
a lot of times i just listened to
alternative music but oh i guess i did
stuff i like to play relaxing music like
bossa nova
i love bossa nova
some people call it elevator music but i
think that's an insult because elevators
are scary
people even now i have a song with the
she buying it
terrifying that's crazy many nights
that's crazy i don't know what it is
there's so many things that can go wrong
in an elephant i have my own they're no
good my own kawaii bossa nova
i don't want to put my sweet bossa nova
beats to be
uh correlated with scary elevators
[Music]
awesome kinky i still don't like it
there's so much that can go wrong with
an elevator
[Music]
um i came up with a few things but um
i was struggling with some others so
uh you will want to fast forward like i
really get it get up
which if you didn't know it's a play on
online fauna online i think some people
still don't know that online online or
general tag um you guys have been
putting so much art in this is good i'm
thankful that i know how to tackle no
this is torment and torment like
i i i'm just so so thankful for for all
of all of the fan art and all the kind
messages you guys have sent me look at
that little fauna
and i'll stop gushing but thank you
thank you for for everything
yeah that's my general tag um i don't
have an art tag yet
i figured you guys would probably know
have some good that is your tag and i
guess i didn't think of anything better
some people were saying fanatics i think
that's pretty good
but maybe there could um
be other ideas as well and also my ocean
mark is it's called the herb
but to me it doesn't really look like an
herb it looks more like a branch
than you remember i just i'm explaining
everything that's why i picked it
so feel free to uh
this emoji it's called it's called the
herb
but um actually it reminds me more of my
branch which reminds me of my horns
which look like branches so that's why i
chose it because not only am i nature
and it's a plant but also it reminds me
of my branches you guys
are fine this is tag
that you're coming up with
[Music]
oh no don't acknowledge it just ignore
it just ignore it
close your eyes pretend you don't see it
in the exact spot for bonking
[Music]
you're just giving in to what they want
they want to be bonked
[Music]
come back i should write that one come
back my keyboard is really loud oh yeah
i got a new keyboard since then
it's like she's looking at me thank you
you're right i'm extremely staying still
and pure
and
uh innocent of all sins
see you guys believed me when i said
that but even back then i was trying to
hint that i'm actually not
[Music]
that's pretty cute phong club
that's cute
she's looking at me
fantastic
fanbase
that's pretty good too
i don't know maybe maybe we'll have to
have to think about it
we'll have to think about it
[Music]
why
um
feel free to write anything about the
debut you want in first font um and also
in the hollow council tag first fun like
first dawn
stop my first phone
in my online tag
but i'm not really picky you can put it
wherever you want
[Music]
saplings i mean that's pretty cute
saplings are printed my saplings hello
my saplings
oh she's beginning to believe
[Music]
the genesis the genesis apples
sprouts
sprouts is pretty cute too
[Music]
he keeps looking at me
in the corner
okay okay we'll come back to this though
this is gonna take some some how much
longer is this to actually decide
and i have some more stuff it's only
half over oh my gosh
like my goals
and future streams oh no this is the
shameful part um i haven't completed my
final evolution yet i'm missing
some skills that i wish to learn
in my obstacle skills
i want to learn japanese um i haven't
been speaking japanese because uh i
cannot
i'm sorry
but i want to learn
a little bit um
but i would like to learn because i
really want to talk to my senpai
and collab with them
um
yes so i better study hard you better
hold me weekly it's mostly weekly
don't bully me because my k-100 is
broken because i'm gonna cry
i mostly do it weekly when my
i'm not a good singer but um i do have a
song for you today
but i'm not good so don't get your hopes
up
but i would love to like maybe take um
voice lessons you guys don't mean to
because it would be so much
fun
again i have to send it in for repair i
think i could make something i'm sad
about it too
maybe something
relaxing like something i used to
do it weekly
mostly
um i also i want to do offline collabs
with my gen meets
i'm hoping it might be more possible and
now that we have more en members
ah
because i know and then complete the off
collab goals that's good
um unlike a lot of our japanese senpai's
who can do offline oh god i'm having to
listen to myself saying i just realized
that that would be possible
bye you can't say that you're gonna make
my heart explode
she did make my heart explode many times
um
i also want to learn to speed run games
i think that would be i kind of did that
when you guys make fun of me minecraft
but i speak over over and over and over
and over
just like over and over i did beat the
minecraft in one sitting though
so maybe it's a speed run it's just not
a very good one and maybe some others
like uh i think it'd be fun to do like
um
gamecube games although permissions
might be hard for that one
yeah i don't want to play
i want to play billy
i don't know about speed running i do
want to do like billy hatchery endurance
because it's not that long i think i can
beat it once sitting you gotta shoot for
the stars right and that goes for you
guys too
don't be afraid to dream big
you got true i hope that one comes true
still make the most of it okay
no slacking okay you better
uh
go grab your dreams buy the horns and
um i don't know where this is going
make it happen
do your best i believe in you
you can do it
number mine is to voice out in a video
game um i've always wanted to do that uh
i do like to voice act uh
i'm not a professional by any means
though and i probably have a lot to
learn still but i think it'd be so fun i
don't mind if i'm just
a
little uh npc who gives you one quest
uh
that's okay with me
i just think it'd be really
cool i still want you know for my future
streams um
i want to do weekly asmr because i am an
asm artist i do asmr
a lot of people have said my voice is
relaxing and i really appreciate that
because that's kind of my whole
goal i guess what sorry
what was that drop down to my phone
your phone yeah i want to do them oh but
that's the other thing about asmr isn't
it i'm a little bit clumsy
i'm a little bit clumsy so i'm sorry in
advance if i accidentally destroy your
ears during asmr
i do much
but that does happen from time to time
fauna nissan
uh
always drops things and trips over her
own feet and
scrapes her
knees true
yeah i hope to do weekly asmr uh i want
to bring more asmr to hollow ian
i think i did that
i didn't do enough but i think i did
enough especially collabs would be a lot
of fun i'll still i would i just had
trouble with my setup for a while i have
trouble with it but i trust you guys
i want to try to do them like maybe once
a month um the kind of games we can play
might be a little bit limited so you'll
have to forgive me if we end up playing
some of the same games over and over
and over and over and over
i'm just kidding but definitely stuff
like mario kart could work and also um
uh like fall guys um
maybe like guard to phone that kind of
thing we could play together perhaps
um and of course just games and art i'll
probably do lots of those
uh i haven't done a lot of art streams
that's what you can mostly just remember
in the future
[Music]
here's some more collab with noel
because i'm so conscious
noelle senpai i love her so much and i
look up to her so much
and still trying to learn more japanese
i did ask her for help with the k100 and
she didn't help me
so but basically i have to send my k100
and get it repaired
yes
oh
it looks like that was um the end of our
book
another christian thank goodness the
book is done maybe sometimes the book is
torture i don't want to see the book
anymore
okay
we don't we did it we read a whole book
put it away congratulations
you finished a book
now we don't need this anymore get that
out of here
[Music]
um
now
now one think
it is time
to have a closer look
hold on with me
time for pictures being fun
don't look in my hashtags only look at
me
let's have a closer look at
but um look respectfully respectfully
yes i am acquainted with my own feet i
understand starting from the feet
as is tradition
yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes for any weird
reason because i'm mother nature yes and
i have i have one i don't think anyone
thinks this is in here i want to make
sure my toes are
properly
pedicured if they're going to be on
display they better be pretty
yes yes yes and you can see
my overcoat
it's really pretty i love it it is
pretty it's pink sparkling and sparkly
flowers
pink is one of my favorite colors along
with green true so
it makes me happy to have some pink in
my clothes
thank you mama for giving me springs
huh
my niece
i know it is it's my big princess dress
i guess you'll see it in the
yeah the reference sheet when i show it
and
my dress looks like a princess dress
from behind because it's big
pretty really close so i'm really happy
that i get to wear these
yes i have cute frills and
you can see my hands so much details
i have one glove on
not two
this is what did i say holding gloves
oh one glue so that the power of the
golden apple can be properly contained
[Music]
um
so many pretty details do you see these
gems they remind me of water droplets
which of course water is essential for
life
at least here on earth
and
my sleeves
my floor i like my sleeves too they're
poofy
um
[Music]
i have this pretty ribbon and pretty gem
and lots of flowers it is kind of a
shame
i'm always like this that's oh about it
so you rarely see my full outfit
am i too close maybe i can become a
pixie stream
like this
big fauna and tiny and
i'll give you a look of some of the
faces i can make
how about this one
[Music]
what face is that funny
what face is that this face is very
special
[Music]
why
oh that one
what
you are hanging out with civilization
instead of mother nature
huh
and
this face is reserved for a special
someone
and maybe you you don't respect nature
[Music]
disgusting
and
the face that will break
all hearts
[Music]
i can't believe that you
threw that can away into the forest
don't forget to recycle
[Music]
and i can blushy
when i am
embarrassed or happy
like like right now
[Music]
and
normal
and i also i also can show you something
very special
what another very special thing i'm just
full of
i love
treats for you today
don't say it like that that sounds so
weird
oh here we go it's covering me a little
see
it's princess dress
my residents
isn't it amazing oh and the overcoat
comes off
wow
oh my mama
she made me so pretty
thank you mama
i love i love my poofy skirt because it
makes me feel like a princess
a princess of the force
i hope um
this helps you if you ever if you ever
want to draw me which i'm so honored
thank you everyone who has ever drawn me
i appreciate it uh it means a whole lot
that you would even think think about
spitting your precious code comes off i
wish i could take it off
let's just show it what it looks like
underneath but no
i cannot take it
[Music]
okay
oh i'm
stuck okay
now
i think
i think there's only one more thing to
do
i think i know what's happening now
i see i know this part
like i said i'm i'm not
good at singing
but but i spent a while practicing i
didn't listen to this recently though my
singing at least because i didn't do it
with myself give me a minute to go to go
uh
switch to my singing room
and and then i will i will give it my
all for you okay
okay so we have to go into the brb
screen again
let's go
oh this was before i had my
screen transition too i guess
this is almost over yet
please spare me oh
what's happening
i'm scared
[Music]
went out uh
my microphone too
uh
just a second suddenly oh what happened
final audio
is this the ian chris
were you convinced by my acting
[Music]
i
don't know what's going on
um
maybe they'll come back on in
you don't mind sitting with me in the
dark for a bit
okay
i don't want to watch this
i don't want to watch this i'd rather
play outlast this whole time
stop whispering in my ears
kind of awkward right
you mean human and all
and
being the keeper of nature
this relationship isn't so
straightforward you know
stop
humans are part of nature too
what at least yours
things are pretty different now though
you
view yourselves as separate from the
animals
separate from nature
oh the slow pan in i guess you have
civilization to preoccupy yourself with
so
you don't need me anymore no
don't get me wrong
i'm not mad
i could never be mad at you
i love humans with
my entire heart after all
but
it just doesn't feel right
you get out of my head get out of my
head
come on get out of my head
and
i am not going anywhere
until i win you back
i'll be here
streaming
changing your heart
day by day
to return to your widgets
get out of my ear
i promise
mother nature would never betray you
right
[Music]
scary sound effect
the lights came back on
i think i can finish my song now
just a second okay yeah yeah
so you have to save
[Music]
this one
wow were you surprised
were your expectations subverted
wow
[Music]
i don't wanna watch it the singing's
gonna be bad too
well maybe it won't be so bad because i
just listened to it recently
[Music]
those made me want to write another
yandere asmr script though
[Music]
when i give my k 100 back i can perform
it okay for real this time
[Music]
i have nothing to say about this woman
no
i'm cuter and i'm better at singing
[Music]
i
oh
[Music]
yo
show us your moves
ah
and recently i was able to perform my
own original song
3d this is small 3d
[Music]
it goes forever
it never ends
there's nine minutes
[Music]
of left
don't even know the lyrics
[Music]
that's true
i'm really annoying because i'm jealous
because she has this
cute innocence about her
and i'm just jaded now
i cannot capture the same pureness
anymore
[Music]
immediately the loading screen
is not the end right i feel like i want
to find some wild ride how many loading
screens did i put in one view
i think i was nervous and i didn't
really know how to use obs that well so
i felt like i had to go to a loading
screen between every screen
so i could set it up properly
so
you survived
[Music]
i survived okay
uh i hope you're not too scared you
shouldn't be because you should know
i'll take good care of you no matter
what
[Music]
you guys are smiling so much i'm so
happy to to be here you're right i can
look at the comments back then i wonder
if there's anyone in the comments who's
here today
let's see we do have just a few more
things to discuss real quick
we have uh
i remember
back then it was crazy back then and
answer a bunch of questions everything
was crazy i didn't know what i was doing
or what was happening and then on
tuesday we'll be playing sport which is
a game that i love and it is beautifully
cursed and
uh it
uh exemplifies the beauty of nature and
life
true because
i'm doing a collab with maymay yay we're
gonna be
[Music]
nickname person
mostly i just call everybody by their
names i don't know a couple of them i
think i was one to be a nickname person
but i'm not i'm just not
it's so cute and sonic is
uh
i'm a little nervous i'm a little
nervous but it should be fun
look forward to it and then on saturday
we have a whole calendar
[Music]
and
now what we have nostalgic sport right i
don't know i'm kind of a nostalgic
person i really love nostalgia games
that's true definitely fits the bill
also it's just a great game
you guys have helped ease my nerves a
lot just by all your supports i
appreciate it that's true i was still
pretty nervous though i was in autopilot
mode this whole stream
so it's awesome
you say i just stole all of these
nicknames for everyone i wanted to use
them
[Music]
and you are in for a treat
cronie is cool
she's so cool she's just like ah she's
like
i really admire people who will just be
themselves and are not afraid of what
others think about them that's true
that's very true about christ
she's also really funny like her memes
her means are killer and i'm kind of
jealous because i'm just like uh
i don't know
[Music]
mama doesn't have good memes
i'm cringing i'm cringing i'm cringing i
don't want to turn it off stop it
stop it just stop it she's um
hip with the kids
as you
did i make you cringe yes wow i guess it
was intentional
so good so good
uh hearing her i got to hear her read a
little bit and it's just like i don't
know
sleep every night
i don't know i shouldn't have it looks
like there's a little had more
confidence down there because i do know
memes
and i am going to put myself in this box
and i'm going to stay in this box i
don't know flustered about something
because i can't play cute i can make
memes i'm not funny
i'm just a soft spoken asmr girl and it
is
good it's not good to put yourself in
boxes like that though
so i think that's all i have but that
was like how i understood i can't
believe it
already you know
i i hope you enjoyed your stay like when
i was surrounded by such talented people
i like it means a lot i sort of felt
like i needed to be so i will that to
fulfill my role because everyone else
was so talented and good at what they
did that i feel like i
[Music]
everyone can have multiple things you
know i'm trying to see one on my channel
you can have many things
and i hope that you have a great day and
take care of yourselves and um don't
forget that
you belong to me now
try
[Music]
is it over
is it finally over
[Music]
it's over
oh my goodness
that was more painful than i thought it
would be
i don't know
[Music]
we know
at the same time
it shows how far
i've come and we've all come
so that's good
that's good
we're free
that was a whole hour huh i don't know
why i thought it would be short but like
an hour is a long
time what time is it now what do we do
now do we tearless now
yes
but i'm going to go
run and get more water first because i
drank all my water
and put my bowl away because i ate all
my soup
it's gone because i drink all my soup
i'll be right back again
then it's time for tearless
be right back
now i'm the funnel with the many loading
screens
[Music]
hi again
hello again my little sprouts
in it all turned in the universe
hello my little sprouts
it's so good to see you again
um
i also i didn't even realize but we made
it way past the halfway mark already i
should have
celebrated we are at about seven hours
now
way past halfway already
i can't believe is that flora
maybe
must be flora
wow
short stream
[Music]
i've still got some energy
left i don't know if i will by the end
of it
we got we're seven hours in
five more to go
whoa
oh
it's 700k
marathon or wait you just mean a
marathon when we get to 700k
we could
[Music]
okay i have to set up the
in the tear list
part
i don't have it set up yet
usually i do the stream setup before the
stream
but there's no before the stream
there just is stream it's all stream the
stream never ends
okay um
[Music]
let me find what i made i don't know
you guys have to help me come up with
some
ways of categorizing everyone
because i only have two ideas
[Music]
isn't this real nice i really like it i
want to sit here
it's so comfy
but
um
we have to go do the tier list
pokemon cheerless wait that's good we
can give them pokemon
types which type would they be we can do
that that's a good idea
[Music]
why is everyone saying 3do
is there a three deal
um
where am i going
i'm lost
[Music]
um
don't i still have it it's also broken
if you recall
[Music]
crop
okay
oh i need music too
hold on
i'll get the music
the classic okay
here's my tear list it's currently blank
i have
i have ones here but
the scroll bar
um
have you seen this one
it's kind of an alignment chart of sorts
the premise is when children are yelling
mcdonald's mcdonald's mcdonald's is
where does your response go and it can
be anywhere in this triangle there's we
have food at home
there's mcdonald's mcdonald's mcdonald's
and then there's pulls into the
drive-thru as children she orders a
single black coffee and leaves
[Music]
so we can we can place everybody
where we think they should go
on this list
um
oh i forgot to name my layers here i can
do that
it's not too late
that's iris
that's sauna they're all out of order
too
that's me
oh
that's crony oh you can't see it's fine
just trust me
they were there
mommy
good
and cali okay
okay i guess we'll just go in order but
i don't know it might be hard to go in
order
all right cali
so
this very much suits cali but i know
that cali also likes
kids she has a soft spot i think
so i think she wouldn't be quite in the
corner
i think she wouldn't be quiet in the
i think
she would be
sort of here
i think
maybe a little more
[Music]
kiara
all i can imagine is her
her song right now
um i feel like it depends who
who's asking
for kiara
is it kobo you know or is it
i don't know some some brat
[Music]
you think at um top i don't know
i'm just imagining her song you know
that she just released her song has
really has this kind of energy
[Music]
we do have kfp at home though
i think she is on this line
ina
i think ina
is pretty responsible
[Music]
you can't imagine her saying all of them
i think
she can go
here-ish
we can always know
rearrange it later
definitely
i don't think she's quite in this corner
because i think there is part of her and
they would do this
[Music]
so i think i put her here
maybe even a little more i don't know i
can imagine her doing this too
see compared to like ame
i think ame would be more
in the corner
than guru
i think
[Music]
maybe
iris also
i think would be somewhere
down here
is iris i think iris would be more in
the corner than guru though
i think
[Music]
i restarted the chant
she might
do i need to put her completely in the
corner
[Music]
corner is getting crowded
it's all about the relative placement
anyway though
but sana is also in the corner
though
the corner is getting crowded
i think there's none of sauna that would
do this
[Music]
um
who belongs in the corner
sauna or iris
so i can see iris sliding
this way
a bit
if the sauna could be in the corner
[Music]
it's a fight to the corner
um
[Music]
me
i'm probably up here
i don't know i want to believe that
there's a little bit of me that also
wants to go to mcdonald's but i don't
know
and i wouldn't do this either
look i don't want to put myself in the
box of being just a mother
i never really considered myself that
way anyway i just felt like i had to be
that's why i kept
talking about it all the time because i
felt like i had to be like i had no
choice but i never really felt like in
myself
um
[Music]
we have a crony
i mean cronies exterior says that she
would do this but i don't think she'd
actually do that
[Music]
i feel like she might be like up here
even
[Music]
she does seem like that we have food at
home type though
like she wouldn't want you to be eating
unhealthily
[Music]
moo me
can probably go here
well i don't know though mummy does
cook a lot but it's like for herself
i don't know if it's for
for others to enjoy
[Music]
maybe here
should order the black coffee
i don't know
not like to be intentionally mean though
i don't think
[Music]
she's evil she is not evil
i'll put her
[Music]
i think here is okay
um and bae
bae's persona is here but man actuality
is
[Music]
well she's probably somewhere over here
um she is very responsible
did you get the cup but it's not about
the coffee it's not about the coffee if
you think it's about the coffee or
misunderstanding
this one is about making children sad
that's what it's about it's not about
the coffee
you could replace the coffee with
anything and it'd be the same
yeah it's about the spite it's not about
the coffee it's about the spite
it's about the message
i maybe there's a little bit of that in
bay but i don't know
i don't know
i don't i can't really imagine it like
if bae is babysitting you know
i don't think it's a trolling either i
think it's like
the children will genuinely be sad
there could be a fourth option of you
you do this and then they cry and then
you also go back through the drive
through and the end
it's trolling you guys if you do this to
your kids they're not going to feel like
they got pranked they're going to be
really sad
i think
oh you're right chad didn't break has it
been breaking
can i refresh it
i think it's just broken oh maybe not
[Music]
okay
all right how should we adjust this
um
i don't want it to overlap
you're surprised crony's on the bottom
left that's the that's the the area that
she gives off but it's not how she
actually is
she's actually very considerate of other
people
she is always looking out for other
you might think that
she would do this based on looking at
her and how she presents herself but
it's not how she actually is
[Music]
i don't know
i feel like this is probably as good as
it is gonna get
oh my candy bread it's not about the
bread
please you must understand
it's not meant to be taken literally
it's not actually about mcdonald's it's
not about the bread it's not about the
coffee
it's not about that
please please
put the coffee though but bae loves
coffee she would totally order the
coffee
coding in subway not mcdonald's
oh
right i'm gonna go in this then
this is my answer
you may disagree if you want
you can feel free to make your own
[Music]
mine is based on rich psychological
analysis though
mm-hmm
[Music]
not about coffee
yeah maybe mermaid could go more left
but
i don't know again it's like
i do feel like the the
the movement that i know is different
from the movement that you know
you know
maybe on the outside that's how she
presents herself but i don't know on the
inside
on the inside
mummy
mummy sweet mummy considerate i mean no
nothing mummy murderous mummy murder
evil owl
hmm
okay
[Music]
i have to hide it for a second i need to
reset it
because i have another tier list too
[Music]
oh wait but i didn't label oh and i just
like deleted my layer
labels that's fine
okay what i want to do
is
i wonder like
a stereotypical anime
tropes
like
childhood
friend oh i wanted pokemon too
spelling childhood friend
um
you guys have to help me though
come up with all of the different ones
we can have like soon dairy
[Music]
what else should we have
the rival
sure
class president sure
[Music]
the transfer student is like the
mysterious transfer student
[Music]
oh gosh karine
mysterious transfer student
is that what you mean
like homura
the chuni
we're we're out of
we're out of boxes though
is this enough
um
mysterio almost you're right
mysterious
help
[Music]
more boxes but i don't want to put more
boxes
i think we should be able to
um
what's the word
boil it down to the six there's a better
word condense it into six
because we could do dairy types as well
but this is a little different from that
[Music]
delinquent
we have no protagonist
are we supposed to
the protagonist is just the
you know
you know him
the the boy with the the brown hair and
the brown eyes
yes
[Music]
who has no defining features at all
whatsoever
[Music]
okay let's just start with this and see
where it takes us
okay callie
um
[Music]
i kind of feel like callie is your rival
she's kind of like gary oak i feel like
she's cool and confident
but she's not like evil
cuny you can say anyone here is chunin
though
[Music]
kiara is
she could definitely be the class
president for sure
she's popular she seems to have it all
together
she's smart
she's sometimes
you wonder if you can be perfect like
her
um
inna
she could definitely be the mysterious
transfer student but i call sarah's a
childhood friend
she's like drawing in class
dude you just think everyone is choony
no more chuni
let's replace it
you can't say chuni for everyone i'll
make your list for you it's just
everyone goes into chuni
um
it depends on the type of transfer
student
you know
[Music]
she could be the mysterious transfer
student because now i want to put
everyone
in myth in these
because then it will be even and
beautiful
but i might have to rearrange it
and then
um i can definitely be childhood friend
you know you kind of tease each other
you've known each other for forever
[Music]
um i mean could be the sooner if she
wanted to be
that's probably fine actually
that's probably
fine you can imagine it
[Music]
okay and then
for council
and iris
well it's not going to fit perfectly
because i deleted
[Music]
let's move everyone
um
let's think about this
[Music]
i feel like it could go a lot of ways
well first of all
sana really feels like childhood friend
i think
but a different kind of childhood friend
army well maybe they both beat you up
in pokemon or video games
um
[Music]
i think bae can be
the class president
they could go in a few different places
though
i think she fits in class president
and then
i don't think this is gonna fit
perfectly i'm not realizing
i don't think it's going to fit
perfectly
soon soon
maybe if you're iris
[Music]
i guess guru isn't really soon either i
kind of just put her there
to fit
[Music]
because the cronie could beat sunday
and then
move me
it could be like this
um
why did i sort them based on hair color
i think this is okay it could be moved
though
it could be moved
because crony would make a pretty great
mysterious transfer student
i should label my layers again
i don't know where anyone is
um
nobody i deleted it
here you want me to make
i'll make your
your ideal list
here you go
do
are you happy now
is this to your satisfaction
perfect
okay okay okay
we can do pokemon types
but there's a lot
of pokemon types
i have to expand my list
[Music]
some of them will be very obvious
or we could just assign types
individually we don't want to make it in
to your list
okay
okay here is everyone
now i assign everyone
pokemon types i have to look up a
reference
um
pokemon types
oh no not the type chart
i'll probably just start with single
typings and then
we can think about other things
so obviously
water
if we disagree here then
we're in trouble to be honest
i don't know how the rest of the list is
going to go
if we disagree here
um
okay and then let's think about it
well here's another obvious one
again if we disagree on this then
we just have to end the stream now
because how
okay
um
i think
[Music]
this one
you're gonna have to hear me out on this
one
[Music]
um what color is this
we're going by lore
because you know you might say oh she's
watering but i um girls are in water
right now
because she is a disciple of the ancient
ones and she is an eldritch creature who
makes you lose your mind
that is why
okay let's do another
this should be easy one i think
i
hope she could be flying time too i
guess she's burned
fighting fire
fire makes sense
we might dual type people
but right now i'm just gonna start color
coding
now look you know it's purple and this
is clearly magenta it's different
it's different
[Music]
and then
i think
[Music]
i think a ghost
this one could go
anyway really
could be
could say dark but i think ghost makes
sense because death ghost
i think it makes sense
okay now i have to think about it
for the rest
these were the easy ones
let's think about
[Music]
it i think
i mean i feel like you have to make iris
and dual type because of
how she is
cause she's a nephilim right
so i feel like you could do
[Music]
do this
for iris
to encapsulate
who she is
[Music]
i think i know
cronies too
[Music]
i think ronnie will be steel type
because of her blades but also her cool
exterior
[Music]
i'm thinking i'm thinking
i kind of want to give sona a dual
typing too
maybe
it's hard to there's no space type
well what is
the one
cosmog we can just steal cosmog is
typing
[Music]
i don't know flying really makes that
much sense i'm just flying because in
the air in space
but fairy i think makes sense for sana
i think it's good
what is palkia
it's palkia dragon
she could be dragon too i agree
it kind of suits her
oh my equals electric now you're just
color coding now you're color coding
palkia's water dragon
she could be dragon fairy i do kind of
like dragon
it sort of suits her because she does
seem like she would be
very strong
typing
in pokemon
okay
there's no chaos type either
um
oh i think i just realized something for
ami
[Music]
i don't know if this is fair
or not
it kind of works
i don't know i don't want to do it just
for the meme but
it kind of makes sense too
sort of
because ame is
very grounded you know
a grounded person
and it does seem like she would use
physical attacks
i don't actually know anything about
pokemon do ground
mons use
physical attacks i don't know
maybe it
depends
um
oh i guess
from mummy
maybe there's also an obvious one
for me
i don't know
[Music]
i don't think it fits her perfectly
you could give her flying because bird
i feel like there could be something
else there
maybe
and then bae
i think for bae
i don't know do i just want to give her
this for reasons
i don't know i want to give her this but
it doesn't really make sense
i might be color coding
but but
but
just hear me out
electric ice is a chaotic combination i
think also it matches her clothes and
her colors and sprite colors
and also she can be
an electric rodent she can be this
generation's electric rodent
we've never seen bay like use elemental
magic though
i think that's like the thing is a lot
of this like elemental magic which we
don't really see
[Music]
boom boom
there is boom boom
but i send
electric are kind of add-ons with
another you know like fire and
fire and ice will electric and ice
it could be fire
for boom boom
make things explode
[Music]
normal fighting
i don't know though
why
she is like feisty
but she's also chaos
dark type but she's not very dark you
know
[Music]
like when i think dark i think like emo
on the emo pokemon
and they is kind of the opposite
like i think movement could be dark type
[Music]
dark flying
but then we should make kiara flying as
well
[Music]
oh wait this is wrong
i have to fix it
[Music]
should baby i don't know
she could be normal ghost because it's
chaotic
[Music]
fire and ice
chica bee
that also kind of is color coding
[Music]
and chaotic it matches mr squeaks
it's kind of satisfying
or you just like make her just normal
type because that's like the most
chaotic of all
but i don't know if she'll be sad if she
gets normal type
just to like subvert the expectations
you know
but i don't know
kieran are dragons yeah kind of i could
be dragon type
but i don't like the idea that everyone
needs to be dual typed
[Music]
normal so cool i like normal too
but i don't want
oh no
i think this is fine
overall
not everyone needs to be dual typed
i think
only some
grasshopper
no
this is fine is everything fine
is it really fine
we have a while till the
the next um
put up everything planned though
[Music]
we could squeeze something else in too
if we wanted to i didn't know how much
time we would have how long things would
take
[Music]
20 minutes i think we have
50 minutes
i think the quick game of rust
true
more power rankings
[Music]
i don't even know where to begin if we
go with lower power rankings
[Music]
um
i don't even know
it's like
i'm probably like a sauna
because she's huge and also nothing can
exist without space
[Music]
balls like crony because nothing can
exist without time
um
yeah
and then
like bay because chaos
is like a
force of the universe
this is what we call power creep
um
[Music]
iris has to go to the bottom because
no one has hope in their hearts so she
cannot exist
i'm sorry iris
it's just this this is a generation
um
i mean mummy
scissor herself that she doesn't control
civilization
[Music]
she's just there
she just watches
and then
i mean cali is pretty strong too
literally the grim reaper
is pretty strong
and then maybe like you have like ina
and then
you're like kiara
ahmed is a human
[Music]
guru is like a shark
um
i don't know where i would go
i don't think i'm very offensive
here just like this
oh you can't see
i'm sorry
this is rigged how is it rigged
banana next to bay yeah i guess it
depends if you're considering like me as
a concept really me as a person
no i think i have to be below bay though
because nature only exists uh on planet
earth that's true though i guess death
cannot exist without life
so
maybe everyone goes down one
[Music]
um
it's probably like this
but i don't know about mummy
is she is she does she really mean it
when she says she just watches and she's
not involved at all
otherwise i think she goes up here
but i don't know
just a lost owl
this is fine
how strong are atlanteans
maybe they're strong
i mean she's like a shark
but sharks are like not that strong you
know
i don't think she is even in grade white
and she's small
just like a little strong but like ami
has time travel powers which is really
strong but not as strong as like being
able to be reborn infinitely
or as strong as having commune with the
the eldritch beings
the ancient ones
i don't know i don't know
oh that's true though do the ancient
ones exist without life on earth
what are eldritch beings how are
eldridge beings formed are eldritch
beings alive
we need to answer these questions before
we can get a
a definitive rank
at the top
i guess you're right huh
but that's not real
[Music]
you know
maybe it's real
where are they where are they
no but ina is just a normal human so she
goes to the bottom
because she's just a human you know
yeah she is also not the asian ones i
don't know maybe the ancient ones go up
here but
inna is an apostle of the ancient one so
she goes somewhere
somewhere else
i don't know
i don't think you can rank it
properly
[Music]
kara escapes death
that's true
i mean does death really have power over
anyone or she just like reaping souls
you know like can she actually cause
death or does she just
does she just reap other people's souls
that have died due to the natural order
of things you
know i don't know
i don't know
you can argue any sort of list that you
want i think
[Music]
it's not possible
you can't
[Music]
enhance
pixel art yo i love pixel art
look watch this watch this
[Music]
oh no i'm on the wrong layer
hold on watch this
[Music]
i'm a pixel artist
do you like my pixel art
i'm really
very talented
at pixel art
i can make it in just a second
looks like a minecraft painting
i made this in minecraft it's actually
made of a million individual blocks
and i did not use a computer program to
make it i
placed each block myself
pixel art is actually really hard
you cannot just put
put a pixel filter or something
to make it
[Music]
okay i
need to go to idle meeting
i'll be right back again
and then we'll do something we have a
little bit of time
to kill before in the next collab
i wonder what we should do
what could we do for
how long 40 minutes
let's see right farm speed run yeah yeah
yeah
okay all right back
[Music]
hello
sorry the bmb screen was a lie
we already did the tier lists
we already did them
[Music]
what should we do for
40 minutes hello 40 minutes
30 minutes
i don't know i'm indecisive
[Music]
i'm indecisive
rust
yeah we could do rust but it'll take 10
minutes to vlog into the server
i should though because i should gather
materials
on jump king is a good idea
[Music]
um
we're getting over it
want more getting over it getting over
it
would be good though
because then i wouldn't have to edit the
description of the video but it's not a
big deal if i have to edit it
[Music]
jump king
did holocure have an update
recently
[Music]
um
q a you want a q a
[Music]
we can do q a all the time though what
are your questions i'll answer any
question maybe
[Music]
any day
i'll play holi care when it updates i'll
wait until then
i think
[Music]
what does clover smell like he doesn't
smell that good because he's really old
but i try to clean him the best that i
can
[Music]
what goals are for year two i feel like
they're the same
i want to
i want to learn japanese
i want to learn to sing
i want to get 3d i want to go to japan
i want to meet sana and iris in person
[Music]
another original song maybe maybe i
would like to do more
music in general
especially if i keep
practicing singing
[Music]
oh yeah voice act yes i want a voice act
too i really want to
[Music]
one outfit i want but we'll probably
never get that's a good question
because you guys know like i want
an emo outfit but i'm
i better get it one day
[Music]
but what's one that i want but we'll
never get probably it would have to be
like too niche to bother with you know
i don't know
the cow outfit i mean yeah but i don't
really
i'm not that crazy about the cow outfit
i mean
yeah i could say like
i don't know i don't know
a suit i prefer other girls in suits
more than i like to wear a suit myself
so maybe i do like suits but i wouldn't
want one myself
i don't know
like
[Music]
all the outfits that i'm thinking of are
things that i really want one day
nurse outfit yeah
yeah
but again i don't want to say never
never say never
it could be
like what if we get infinite outfits one
day and then i'll wear everything you
know
made i already have a mate sort of it's
not trap
not a traditional mane
it's just a
a kimono made which is also great
which outfit
yeah that's true
maybe that's the answer is like a
halloween
costume
but i would one day
it's just halloween is not that
applicable because you can only wear it
for one month of the year
post maybe
on rare occasions otherwise
but yeah maybe like a halloween witch
outfit yeah
default fun without the overcoat no
don't say that maybe i can get it one
day maybe one day i don't know maybe
it's impossible but you're right you're
right
i would like default funnel without the
overcoat i don't know if it's possible
to ever get it but
it would be nice
it gets hot in here sometimes be nice to
take off my sleeves
[Music]
yeah also like a cherry blossom
fondant like you know cherry blossom
miku
yeah cherry blossom fauna
probably would never actually get that
but i want it
like pink hair and then like pink
pink outfits
i would really like seasonal outfits
but again it's like
there's too many outfits i feel like no
one in hollow life has that many outfits
i have to choose wisely you know
[Music]
feigned doll outfit
crony outfit no
no crony looks really good in her outfit
but i don't think it would suit me
[Music]
um
christmas outfit that'd be cute but i
think a winter outfit would be cuter
and more general i'd really like a
winter outfit
like a nice
coat a big coat
[Music]
a spy outfit
are you just thinking of you're from spy
family i mean i can't blame you if you
are
she's really cute
but i don't know
[Music]
pool party yeah
i want pajamas too but i really want
pajamas one but i want a lot of things
one day
i want pajamas i want
uh emo
god
what kind of pajama outfit i don't know
yeah something cute and comfy
cute comfy outfit maybe something with
like a fuzzy
hoodie that has like animal ears on it
you can put the hood up
that would be really cute
um
yeah i would like namu to be able to
move
that would be fun if namu could also be
come live 2d
instead of just png
mushroom outfit that would be cute
like a fairy tale
mushroom outfit
that would be cute
[Music]
i think um
wait how much time do we have wait do we
only have oh no we have
we have 30 minutes
is that no time
to do anything
shrine maiden yeah i love shrine maiden
a onesie yeah
i mean i just like every outfit that's
the thing i'm not gonna say no to any
outfit
because i love fashion so
i like anything
anything at all
none
yeah that's probably the real answer i'd
probably never get a nun outfit but i
want one
i really want one
clown i'll be okay no i don't want a
clown outfit
no thank you
i don't like clowns
except for polka but she's not really
clown
she's like a ringleader right it's
different
[Music]
sexy clown
clowns are scary
they're scary
focus the whole circus
i love polka
[Music]
really funny and really sweet and nice
yeah i saw that clown that everyone
fell in love with on twitter
i don't know these things just get
recommended to me
i don't really like her
i'll be honest
but i don't really like
like clowns
they're scary
they're like it
actually i guess i like hisoka but he's
scary too
you remember the clown in resident evil
7 dlc that one's scary too
she's a murderer see she is clowned or
she's she's scary i mean
clowns are scary
they're really scary
[Music]
oh the joker yeah he's scared too
but he's kind of a meme at this point
you know
um
sorry i'm gonna play getting over it i'm
not sorry but i'm just letting you know
i'm setting it up
that's why i started coming
um
[Music]
it's the time killer it's the time
killer
sorry crony
don't listen
just a quick little
getting over it
wow we chat
about clowns
is my chat weird
i'm like inspecting it i feel like it
looks different
isn't my chat normally
transparent
why does it have a white background now
i'm inspecting you sorry
what happened
why did this happen
why did you change why did you change
your background
what's going on oh
oh no
i don't know why i always insist on
doing it that way
um
what's your favorite and least favorite
halloween monster
i think i like most of them
well clowns are scary though but i guess
that means they're effective you know
oops
they're not scary
i can't play
wait did i say they're not scary
is my brain broken is that what i said
do i really believe that clowns are not
scary
i'm just consciously
contradicting myself now
i think i was what was i thinking of
this not scary i think i was thinking
the ladder
a lot of halloween
monsters are not scary
like a vampire you know
i feel like a vampire is supposed to be
scary
like a clown you're right
nope
i'm restarting a clown is not supposed
to be scary but they are
but a vampire is supposed to be scary
but they aren't
i think it's because media made them too
cute
there's too many cute vampires
like rosario plus vampire or his
ex-vampire
she's really cute mocha is really cute
my skyrim
waifu
serrano pepper is really cute
no longer are we afraid of vampires
marceline
true she's cute
yeah she's not scary at all
edward cullen he's
he's not scary
that movie is funny i need to watch it
actually oh no
i'm bad
i think this is the part of the stream
where my brain dies we're eight hours in
all i remember when we were eight hours
in with kirby
it felt like a
millennia
it was so long
and i was so dead
i don't feel nearly that dead
i think it's because we're doing
different things every hour
keeping it fresh you know
but also my brain is starting to
i feel the effects
of eight hours of
streaming spider monkeys are scary yeah
it was actually really scary when edward
said
hold on tight spider monkey
i would be terrified if i were bella in
that situation
it is funny i did watch the scene where
they're in the
this oh the scene where edward sparkles
i watched just that scene
and it's pretty funny because he's like
i'm a monster bella
and she's like i don't care
he's like i kill people
she's like i don't care if you kill
people i love you
and i don't know
that's pretty funny
she probably should care
i think maybe she should care
oh for use the baseball scene don't
people actually like that scene though
maybe just twilight fans like it i
believe they're they're called twyhards
like die hards but tryhards
um
not that i wouldn't know anything about
that
don't they like the baseball scene when
they were playing baseball together and
it's like thundering out because that's
the only time they can play baseball is
when it's thundering because they're so
strong and super human that if they play
baseball it makes thunderous claps
so they can only
only play it
in thunderstorm
and then the evil vampires come and they
play baseball together but really like
they're not just playing baseball
they're playing baseball
for bella's life
help
me
me help
please do a watch like i do want to do
one i want to do it with moomae
oh
i want to make it like the real
i'm just going crazy now
[Music]
i'm crazy with the hammer
i guess we know eight hours in is where
i lose my mind apparently
brain turns to mush
but it's not an unpleasant mush
it's just mush like mashed potatoes you
know
there's unpleasant emotions like
when someone chews up your food and
spits it back out you that would be
unpleasant but there's some pleasant
emotions too like mashed potatoes
and right now my brain is mashed
potatoes
that also reminds me
i've been watching along this game i'm
trying to get permissions for it
it's called plate up
it's like overcooked but it's a bit
different um
it's the same kind of thing as overcoat
like a co-op restaurant
oh no restaurant simulator but
it has a lot of depth to it and it has
like roguelike elements to it too like
each run is different and you pick
different upgrades and different
well different negatives too
it's really good and i really want to
stream it
but i've
i've been watching so much of it
that game
i could play for eight hours straight i
think
well i don't know maybe without it being
painful
i mean minecraft wasn't painful
when i played it
i only played it for six hours i guess
i want to see a list of my longest
streams
i know my longest one was the
uh getting over in golden pot
because that was just about 12 hours i
think
and then probably my second longest was
um
the kirby
64 endurance which was eight hours
but then i know
minecraft was like almost seven hours
recently
i think i've done a few six hours skyrim
streams five or six hours
oh no
i can't do orange anymore
help
if i have to do it slow
but i don't want no
but i want to go fast
oops
so much for going slow
it's
slippery
i can't do it anymore
bgm doko wait you didn't have bgm the
whole time
oh my god i thought you did i'm sorry i
forgot
that's why people were sending the no
audio sign i didn't know what that meant
i thought people were just trolling me
i thought you were just trolling
[Music]
i thought people were talking about
themselves like oh look at me i'm
watching with no audio
it'd be so audio i don't know it wasn't
like a lot of people saying it
i don't think maybe it was i wasn't
reading chat that closely because i
gotta look at the game
oops
weird
i don't know
sometimes people just
join the chat and say the darnedest
things
i've seen it all at this point
sorry i just had to listen to me and my
fan that's awkward i'm sorry
me and my fan
you couldn't even hear the
the nars in the
the grunts
told your brain is potatoes
[Music]
okay
can i even defeat defeat
beat this game one time
before it's time for jack box
i bought that new jack box by the way
well i didn't actually know if it's new
actually
now that i think of it it might not even
be new
i bought jack fox number eight actually
i think it's not new it's like a year
old at least
new to me
i bought it just for this stream oh no
i think there's one mode in there that's
really funny where everyone like makes
up
phrases and then you have to like stitch
the phrases together
i want to play that one
or nine is out soon
[Music]
oh no
is it called blather round or something
that sounds right
ah no i don't know how to do orange
anymore
i'm not an orange girl
[Music]
you shouldn't even swing the hammer
oranges
i even told that to moomin but i can't
follow my own advice
because i am like i can handle it
i'll catch myself
i won't make things worse for myself
shirley
but i did
i did make things worse for myself
i know at least like the early part of
this game is really soothing
i like watching people speedrun this
game
because it's just soothing to watch them
go fast
just climb the mountain
the elegant hammer movements
satisfying
okay now you're doing the oh
oh no no no no
the launch
[Music]
very nice
i don't really play this game anymore oh
my gosh i'm going crazy i'm going crazy
i want to play this game anymore but i
thought about playing it like while i'm
watching
moomae
play it
but that might make me a distracted
teacher i don't know
i don't want to be a distracted teacher
especially not for my
protege
prodigy
oh
there we go
i knew i spoke too soon
try to go too fast
it's okay
saved we're saved
oh
have just enough time
before
checkbox time
i don't know if i'm just allowed to
steal his script i don't think that's
illegal actually
actually when i made my
um
skyrim short
one of the staff oh
what is that
stick
one of our staff
members
oh
asked me
oh this is just dialogue from the game
right
and i said no
i wrote it myself
oh no you think i would just
take dialogue from the game
no no no
[Music]
there are
bespoke
lines of dialogue oh no
written by me
[Music]
for me to read
to you oh
oh oh not the shopping cart i don't like
shopping cart
[Music]
no no no i don't like tower
no that jumps hard i'm not good at that
jump
i realized oh
what time is it do i have time is it
time to go
[Music]
wing a winger
oh
i missed a rock
let me help i'm so close oh they're
gonna send me down
dang it they're gonna send me down
they're sending me down
[Music]
i was so close
how was that
nice six minutes
best run of the day
nice night nice not bad
not bad
pretty good
okay
um
back here
goodbye getting over and getting what
really does make it
make time pass quickly unless you're
getting the golden pot
then it's not passed quickly
[Music]
so i'm looking
thank you for the collapse
um
let me see what jack boxes do i have i
don't have seven you guys like seven
i have two one two four five six eight
[Music]
i don't have all of them installed
let's play
wait which one is this one called
an eight
i remember there's a weird one in eight
the wheel one is weird
wait is this not the one i think you
know where you put the words in
um
[Music]
hold on is it
oh it does job job okay
you guys like three and seventh invest
the ones that i don't have
how did that happen
[Music]
i think six has trivia murder party
i like role models a lot
personally
role models is funny
my favorite is the shirt making which
one is that
is that in three
um
that's in three i don't have that one oh
no
it's okay
we can play
oops
the other ones
it will be fun
i think still
[Music]
um
okay i don't know if everyone's ready
yet
or not
um
oh am i lagging again
a little
[Music]
here i'm gonna freeze for a minute again
phone very hot after eight and a half
hours
oh shoot do i have to play outlast after
this
[Music]
i just realized
oh no
[Music]
we shall ask the first one
right now let's meet doom feel weird
i'm going to die maybe probably
we only have a little bit left though
let me unfreeze
we have a new jackpot that is happening
in a few minutes
okay i will
go to br b screen
again
and then
gather everyone
and i'll come back and we'll play jack
box okay sound good
okay sorry i'm new to myself
okay
okay i'll be right back we'll be back
with jackpots in a minute
[Music]
hello hello we actually started the game
so we're diving right into it
oh they did the funny
where's someone you can join
the audience
[Laughter]
icebreakers
lots of butter baby oh
wait are we supposed to try to be funny
i think it's a joke
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh wait are we going
oh yeah we're riding okay yeah
oh my god is anonymous
okay it's not
it's not anonymous i i don't think i
think it'd be revealed at the end
[Music]
oh
sweet mercy
[Music]
five words oh
what
mine was only two
i had three
[Music]
oh almost two
i don't even know what to
[Music]
okay
i don't know
why do i have to be so
the words
um five words
oh the
motivational posters that's that's
pretty nice running out
i think you don't have to be that funny
at this part i think the next part is
where you have to be funny
but it helps to be funny in this part
[Music]
sadness
no
yeah confetti
now that we're pals i'm sending some
tough
questions your device oh sorry i'm not
quiet
[Applause]
yeah also improvise to rearrange them
well
can't find the right words for what you
want to say can babies eat buddy and say
something else
if a baby
oh this is a lot of of
words
mucho text though
i need to know who wrote this
i think oh
[Music]
wait what
oh you have to drag it
oh thank you for the comma
[Music]
um
okay 80 seconds no problem
no i'm
can you undo is there an undo button
click you can re-tap the wood we tap the
wood
how long do we have
i don't know uh 65 seconds
[Music]
oh no
oh oh no
oh oh
we have to do more than one
oh
yes
oh nope
okay
we're doing it
30 seconds oh it's a snook there's one
more i got a little connection
interruption
waiting for ame follow me
i don't know
you should be able to rejoin if you
refresh maybe hopefully i'm just
panicking so much oh no i don't even
know
what we should do another round i'm
doing this wait no this is the warm-up i
told him yeah yeah show me what you got
but good
think it's too late
[Laughter]
[Music]
what does it
mean
oh
hey
how do you handle conflict
[Music]
[Laughter]
fast
thank you
me higher
please
[Music]
so it's it's words from other people
that you guys put in i see
i got some house
oh
shame shame
[Laughter]
oh man this is one of mine i forgot i
didn't have enough time to hit the enter
button oh no
hey
oh fauna
i'm getting this
uh i think synergy just counts uh how
many words were borrowed from other
people
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
uh
i like all of these i like how
this one makes no sense that's really
good
nice korean
oh nice
very nice
[Laughter]
[Music]
i'm gonna bring it back i just got
disconnected
[Music]
okay same as before round two
again another icebreaker
please be good
proms oh okay welcome it's gonna be like
three of them again i guess
uh
buckle up stevens it's gonna be another
all-nighter i'll make the popcorn you
download more ghost stories off the
internet
[Music]
oh there's only two i'm here
oh god 40 seconds
[Music]
oh man well now that we know how to play
the game it's so it might be
yeah yeah my answer a little bit yeah
that was just the practice round
[Music]
oh no
eight seconds
[Music]
sorry whoever gets that i already have a
job
that's how it feels i'm sorry
it's sponsored
try grabbing a word from the question
itself oh so it's the same thing
from the question too
that's pretty cool
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
so many different variations of [\h__\h]
in my uh word bank
[Music]
[Applause]
enough i guess
oh wait are they the same
words i think so i think so
60 seconds
oh
[Music]
hmm
uh 40 seconds
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know
oh this is pretty funny it's pretty
funny it's pretty funny
[Music]
this feels like i'm having a stroke and
i got no money i don't know it's a good
retreat everyone shared a vulnerable
secret and now it's time
what do you say
am i echoing choose your favorite
[Laughter]
no wait you can just have three words
yeah yeah
i should have just done that oh
even
more of it
those are the only like good horses
you accidentally broke the shared
microwave by ripping the door off its
hinges what do you do now
what
my father's door
wait wait somebody wrote this
oh
[Music]
just about any text you see them
i don't know what it means popcorn
intel that there is an extremely
luxurious office
oh please tell me
why is that always mine
this is taken is significant
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're welcome
i think these are all my words
i'm so sorry
[Music]
i'm sorry
oh my god
oh nice 40 000
unless you're thinking about traffic i
become someone i don't like on the road
oh gosh
oh we're studying
okay
[Music]
oh it's just one
oh nice oh
okay
[Music]
i guess you get to keep the words from
the earlier rounds too ah
[Music]
god if there's more again
i'm sorry i encourage you
i didn't say [\h__\h]
it's nice [\h__\h] this time apparently
it's
probably my fault i can't stop making
confetti
but you know what i need resumes
oh
what happens if you shuffle i don't know
[Music]
uh interesting okay
oh
oh more than one word
is it just we just write anything
[Music]
i guess it's different for everyone
oh yeah i think we actually differ
do i go from the lowest common
denominator here
[Music]
oh
this is how i wrote this word
[Music]
[Applause]
no there's two
[Music]
i like mine
it's on 20 seconds
[Music]
beautiful
just pick the most interesting words and
it doesn't matter if it makes sense
hello
happy anniversary by the way counts
[Music]
thank you
oh my god oh my god oh my god
why
[Music]
your devices now
so much [\h__\h]
what do i do with all this [\h__\h]
so disappointed in myself
[Music]
[Laughter]
you can never escape
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
oh father how are you and the taste of
chip what
amazing can you read that one get up
what
never
which one
that's a meme
oh they're a grave cheddar
ah
this is the problem brains
[Music]
should we try a different one
i feel this might have been the best one
in this pack though we could try a
different pack too
we can see what's
[Laughter]
don't have to look at that one don't
have to look at that one
oh we could try the drawing one
door
oh is it like
a
draw
what is that one that everybody plays a
drawing game oh like stand in the no
it's um
jp just played it the other day
guard take phone
calls
yeah
well i have to
i think i have to hide the
code
don't let yet don't look
[Music]
what
oh i haven't said the code out loud
[Laughter]
i might be
oh okay they're explaining the rules
okay oh who gave me blue
oh i see
oh okay no eraser
no eraser
[Music]
oh this is an animation of myself i see
oh
a spongebob looking ass
excuse me
okay
[Music]
there is no eraser
oh
oh it's like
oh there's another oh you have to redraw
it
[Music]
how does the cool penguin dance go oh
yeah okay guys
i think you're gonna need more than two
frames
[Music]
okay mine's ready yay how much time do
we have
i think we have oh
this part right we haven't started the
game yet yeah
oh
[Music]
animate yay it's time to make fun of
your friends for doing bad art with this
many players yeah i have time for two
story of my life on your marks get set
draw
uh-oh okay
oh wait where's the room come on
disconnected
you'll get points for each player that
guesses your prompt correctly you're
smart you got it
[Music]
oh there's no undo button oh
yeah
[Music]
i hate it
um
remember you're always welcome in the
audience go to jackson i don't know how
to draw on this
it's okay no one does yeah
[Music]
we're not allowed to write stuff right
that's probably cheating yeah
no words no words
[Music]
this is abysmal
same
[Music]
oh oh
no what screw this i don't even care
anymore
absolutely atrocious
hey it's a shark
shark owl shark
there's an owl at the top i can't tell
it looks like one
halfway point start thinking about that
yeah because think that mascot is an owl
different draw from your kids it's like
the duolingo owl
it is
[Music]
i love the animations of the icons
god
i draw so good
let's see it let's go let's check out
the first animation
[Music]
or what you think will trick the other
players oh
[Music]
oh okay
oh
[Music]
yeah it's cute it has so many weddings
orgy
one that you think is right
the real title the real title oh i feel
like it's oh yeah
[Music]
okay who picked what
there's no way computer would come up
with big boy flexing
you never know
what oh yeah oh
what
how am i supposed to draw that
that is good
love
oh i can't use your device to jot down
[Laughter]
[Music]
it said write an answer below that will
fool the others so i thought it was
supposed to be like
an obviously wrong answer
[Music]
type now replenish your electrolytes
later
he's almost to the end no he didn't make
it oh
the right answer is somewhere time to
vote
[Music]
um
okay
oh
i think i misunderstood this game
yeah you have to try to fool people
to pick the computer generated one
what yeah
got it
i don't understand this game
there's one real trunk chrome
yeah this is the actual problem hey what
an actual title how do you draw a fajita
without making it look like a taco
or like something else again isn't that
just cooked or
[Music]
what
all right
[Music]
okay
i know what this is
for sure really
yeah
definitely
what i put was the correct answer
no matter what the game
oh
that makes sense
well this is what
whoa
who writes these peely dog
[Music]
i'm going all in
double down or you're a giant chicken
for these reveals
i wouldn't
oh this must be it yeah
[Music]
i thought it was somebody like trying to
set a burger on fire
i thought it was lips at first
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
um
what
[Music]
it's a really good drawing
yeah
wonderful
that's amazing
really
who drew this i don't want to buy this
why you do this
what
what these are all the same
[Music]
oh why would it be an owl with good
vision if they're getting glasses that
would mean their vision's bad your job
is to vote
did the person who drew it think of that
though
i can't wait to see what happened i have
no
idea who drew this
does it say ever crony right it must
have been
yours
what was it oh my god it's actually
the game
[Applause]
why
[Music]
is this
all out
what
it's one of those parties
party things
okay
i didn't say anything
sorry crooney insinuated what generate
content stoke the flames of capitalism
it looks like uh you know cucumber
yeah
a fruit roll-up
[Music]
it's whistling right
their tongue is green
oh well i yeah we have them
i don't know this is a good animation
though yeah
yeah oh
yeah this is really nice
did you draw this one too crochet
oh no
i have no idea
it's a it's a uh it's supposed to be a
party favor you know them
yeah
that's why
hey
you know what gave it away punctuation
[Music]
meta gaming figuring it out
final round
[Music]
how do i draw this i don't think you can
draw this in two frames
uh
what
[Music]
by the way girl i hope you're not
you know
excuse me
you know i you know
you know i wrote that in the beginning
you know just in case i don't i don't
know
what
oh i don't know oh you forgot okay
[Music]
yeah it's so good i forgot
i
i forgot
everything oh no this is so bad
[Music]
we did it what do you what
don't leave me hanging man what do you
think
is done get over it
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
that's this pain
oh
oh there are some pretty good options
oh my god is that a reference
oh a reference to feet
is that a foot reference
hey
[Music]
punctuation no
wait what was it no belly allowed really
ballet emergency
[Music]
what are you supposed to put there no he
wasn't good drawing i thought the prompt
would be something longer
oh friends type of title
[Music]
oh
let's go
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go
oh give me your
points it has to be this one
yeah yeah
hi
nice nice nice nice
the way this game writes
[Music]
it really looks like spaghetti but is
that just because of the colors
what
uh
[Music]
okay oh
okay
[Music]
it's not that hard make a choice
okay i'm actually curious how this one
turned out
oh
that wasn't it
oh no that was it
that was really good you're so good
it's not a plate of spaghetti
it is a plate of spaghetti
what is
[Applause]
[Music]
indigestion
yeah
i was like i'm in second place that's
impossible and yeah it wasn't
minority but this animation makes me
feel wonderful
[Music]
i'm sorry
i don't know
[Music]
oh god what's wrong with my brain
uh
you got this
if i put this in though
you need the points trust me you can put
it in
no it'll be fine
no no
no do it no i didn't do it
no
way
no i didn't
oh these forgeries pick the real deal
god i think i know which one it is
[Music]
and
i'm going to say it's
terribly unfunny i hope none of you guys
put it
[Music]
vote now think later
honey i'm checking out the results no
i voted for it though
[Music]
it's terrible
it's like so random none of us would
think to write that
yeah
i think we drew
that's true
what is this
[Applause]
did i use
capitals you actually can't it
uncapitalizes everything
this is awful
wait who had the green pen
um
[Music]
crystal shin boys
[Laughter]
oh my god
[Applause]
i don't know
what is this
okay here's what happened
oh no no
i wanted to believe it wasn't
[Laughter]
i pull on your keys
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
i don't know if any of the other games
in this one are
good or not
which one the weapons one
oh is it like a mile yeah
should we try this one
okay this one okay this is fun i've
played this one before who have you like
the monster
date one
uh not really so what it is is that you
have to hide your letter which is your
clue and you have to hide it inside of a
drawing and then everybody has like a
specific letter
and then the you have to find everybody
guesses on who left the clues as the
murderer i guess
[Music]
the gestures are dancing for one second
why are they holding a candle
fancy to make it more romantic
why you just bring the candles
they don't have a table they can't
afford a table so they're just gonna
hold the handle yeah
[Music]
just bring a candle everywhere just to
make it more romantic exactly
you never know what's gonna happen
[Music]
all right let's go
okay
give me blue
i don't know
[Music]
oh there we go
there was a gathering of the world's
most brilliant detectives who by chance
were also the world's most duplicitous
murderers
oh yeah you see that oh my god oh wow
competition where they earned points for
solving crimes and on the sims hard
this does seem hard
yeah it's equipped with two murder
weapons i guess this one's all right
it's not the best jackpots game if you
guys want to switch now it's kind of i
think it'll be fun to play
[Music]
if your calling card is too obvious your
fellow detectives may spot it and trace
the weapon back to you
oh clever guns and hide your calling
card now
this makes you want to watch british
bake off
wait what are we doing
so you you have to hide your letter
which is from your name
you have to hide it in a drawing
i got the worst letter
wait did we have a prompt at the time
you've played before you can turn off
tutorials in the settings
i promise you just have to hide the
letter personally
i don't know how
you can you can turn turn it around and
how much time do we get
uh
160 seconds
[Music]
all those
sons of bunzas
just gonna scribble over the whole thing
but they don't let you
it's
oh that's smart yeah
[Music]
what am i supposed to do with this
i got the brain
i got the the worst letter
get creative
i didn't bomb but how many do you have
to draw
three well you have to draw three why my
god what that's a lot yeah
oh [\h__\h] oh god okay
i i can't hide this
where are we gonna start our first
weapon it's about time to move on to
your second yes we know who the murderer
is
oh it's just two okay
see to it
oh okay
i don't think i did this right
time is running out
oh geez
oh my god look at my portrait it's
literally doesn't that just look like a
freaking like 12 year old spoiled brat
she's like
maybe
it's red though
true
oh god
[Music]
all right
waiting on one more 40 seconds oh it's
me
it's me
it's more too much
believe
25 seconds left i want to start over
it's okay just two drawings you can do
it
i actually left the game two times
oh
you can you can rejoin reset my drawing
uh oh oh
quick
three two one
oh no i just scribbled a loyal
accomplice disguised as a party guest
use your device to give your girls a
name
but don't leave any clues to your own
identity
[Music]
wait so we're just coming up with the
name
yeah
i'm actually sweating with you so bad
[Music]
contain the sauce
this is kind of scary
yeah
too soon it's like the disney haunted
mansion
yeah
oh my
[Applause]
i'm your host lord tibbetts thank you
gifts you can set them down anywhere
looks like one of your drawings is out
in the open oh as well
these gifts
[Music]
i know who that is
oh i wouldn't be so sure
detective brought them to the ball oh we
have to guess what your fellow
detectives
right i see you're the first to figure
out who brought a guest your murder is
successful but your weapon will be left
behind as evidence and get on with it
before the lights come back ah wait oh
wait what what's happening
uh i guess we should take this and then
you have to
narrow down the letters that were found
murder weapon of
i don't know
[Music]
investigation board
we've found the murder weapons let's
start by focusing on just two of these
ducks
thanks to science we can tell how many
awful attempts were made on each guest's
life
and if you brought one of these guests
each of those attempts earns you points
if i didn't know i'd say these weapons
are the same as some of the
gifts wrought
imagine that ah fortunately we really
only have time to solve one of these
cases
for now examine the evidence and talk
through your theories choose the case
with the best chance
[Music]
okay so we have to find the details that
are in the gifts that might be similar
to each of these evidence
so now
[Laughter]
i see some letters there
[Music]
[Laughter]
no one told me
at once
exactly the case i would have chosen
since you brought up this guest i'm
letting you borrow my lucky magnifying
glass
use your device to move it over the
evidence for a closer look what
now you have to compare the letters that
are hidden in everybody's drawings and
try to find which person might have
killed
raven the victim
what's
[Laughter]
[Music]
she was trying to throw people off her
trail trying to blame it on someone else
just doesn't have a quiet end
ah it was the first woman that came to
my mind one of your fellow detectives
was the murderer what's up detective are
you innocent or guilty of this crime
something to restrain you but your
outfit is quite nice so what the tip is
an idiot
that's considerate
i'm keeping track of who votes for the
guilty party and awarding each of you
points when you're right
even when the rest of the group gets it
wrong there's one pair of murders left
to investigate
oh that looks like i wish there was
something
for those of you who brought these
guests
i'm sure there's something i can do
[Music]
[Laughter]
summoning sir oh i think i know very
well
why do i keep thinking that's the submit
button
which um
you guys feel confident about
yeah
i definitely do i've got it i think so
that's an interesting calm i demand
justice for squid
control of the magnifying glass
how could your device to move it around
the evidence
yes why did why did all of you want to
kill frank what did frank gonna do
be named frank yeah his name pisses me
off
you have to be quite frank here
okay so searching closely
there's an o
what possibly
what do you have to say for yourself
[Music]
as for the murders we didn't get to i
promise we'll get to it later oh yeah
did i
draft
time to oh okay
okay
oh
no device
oh there's prompts okay yeah i didn't
know that either
wait is it are we supposed to draw it
like the prompt
i guess so yeah i don't think there was
one before
[Music]
okay now i'm in business
oh
[Music]
we have to do the prompt
oh damn i did not see the problem oh
okay wait do we have i guess
yeah i guess so i didn't see one before
but
maybe there was one
[Music]
oh oh wait we are supposed to oh i might
have cheated
yeah me
but how do you choose
i'm interested
i'm joined
not follow the prompt
[Music]
oh this looks like
hello
excellent
[Music]
we know
oh
[Music]
80 seconds left
first rate
i tried
are going to be harder though right
because it looks like the font was
different
i don't know if i'm i can't press giving
it away
[Music]
no
i have to redo this why sorry
uh
[Music]
by entering another name remember an
accomplice that no one tries to murder
doesn't do you any good give them a name
with styles
[Music]
gee i hope nobody gets murdered
[Laughter]
[Music]
interesting
pick one of our remaining guests and
guess who brought them if you're right
the dark deed will be done
[Music]
ah so you have to guess who do you think
named that person
yeah
and then if you get it right then you
can kill them you're not dead
um
[Music]
ah i see
oh no
when it comes on with the notification
three murder attempts though
wow
[Music]
to this party
right but i'll let you all handle it
huh
which case
the victim the case of peanut butter
goblin or bentley oh boy
oh boy
ah okay
okay
what a letter
oh
a dolphin it seems like a oh maybe
um
what do you guys see on that one
a lie
an s
you can't draw over the line
out of time really
[Music]
who do i think
i have no idea by the way yeah i don't
see any letters in that word speed up
the timer i see a letter but i just
don't know
let's continue
uh
come on
what is a baby
[Applause]
v is
a letter in their name i think
i uh
oh that's cute before the crew
the right one not the left one
i like the left one
is he a double is that a w
interesting could be a w
i see a w and w
i see
all right go on with it this one looks
so simple like you'd be able to find it
yeah yeah there's an a wait
a w
only one person
among us has a w in their name
oh
wait it's oh it's a letter in their name
oh yeah the hidden letter i think so
[Music]
that makes oh easier
is this a sideways w or is the o the
letter
it wouldn't be hard to draw a w that
perfect maybe yeah the computer looks
perfect now let's take a look over here
there's a w in this name
w though
what if it's that name i think it's
crow right
yeah
necessary
there is an o
she's been awfully quiet
this looks like something she might draw
it
that's true oh no
i
[Music]
is a
murderer confused
no
i just
do murderers
just two people to kill left i see i
think this is the last round probably
[Music]
what does chat do in this one yeah what
it what are you guys voting on
i think they're also voting
because there's like a there's like a
vote on the side of the name
oh now they're calling neither one
they stab each other apparently but now
i suspect it will be overshadowed by the
murders
[Music]
[Laughter]
a
red herring
an
i don't see any letters in the other one
do you guys oh c no b
it's a b
wait but that b doesn't look like the b
in like the game can be different now
yeah
might be oh
what about the other one though hold on
do you see the letter on the other one
it couldn't be anything
yes yes
oh f is that an f
uh
[Music]
i have no idea um v
g
oh
yes
oh there's two people with
[Music]
hahaha
what the hell am i supposed to do with
the bee
[Music]
what am i supposed to do with a bee you
can't draw over it
dance off i can't make it into a butt
well spit it out
[Applause]
midnight if we don't solve the results
this is the last one i guess
look just take a guess at all of the
remaining cases i'll give you points
the other way and i'll give murderers
extra points for every detective they
fool into voting for someone else
you just have to vote no matter what
oh yeah okay
who kills you
uh how much time do i say
no much yeah it's already a halfway less
second
okay
i see o's so i'm gonna go
for oh
[Music]
oh
what is this supposed to hide now
maybe
a big a or a u the o looks good more
like an f
what's this
[Applause]
no
did anybody guess it i would yes
[Music]
what was this
oh yeah we couldn't figure this out
um an e
o
e
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
yeah you hit that really well that was
really well
this
wow
looking a bit sus uh
chrome
oh
i mean that's absolutely obvious oh
oh oh oh
oh
like a pony
oh oh there's mine oh
[Laughter]
yes fine keep going
oh oh
it's hot i see
i would not i see
oh
[Laughter]
i can't see any in this one is it o
there's no w i guess
huh
[Music]
there's a u or an f in there somewhere
maybe i see it can be lower case right
no a maybe
yes yes
[Music]
oh i didn't vote oh
[Applause]
[Music]
is oh um
look out
double whammy double whammy
[Music]
[Applause]
so popular
wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think out of out of letters like fauna
had the best ones to hide like yeah i
think so too
yeah i got lucky
damn that's fun
yeah i get it now i get it i get it i
get it i get it
yeah thank you guys for coming to my
anniversary stream playing jack box with
me
we should do more jack box collab
yeah yes yes
this is
bam yeah this one's pretty i heard seven
is really good too
oh yeah i have seven i think a new one's
coming out too already
i think nine's coming out
[Music]
all right thank you guys for joining i
have to go play outside now i guess
thank you thank you
anniversary
[Music]
i guess
that was fun though i want to play more
in jackpots it's so like casual too
yeah i like the the mad limbs one a lot
[Music]
you're here with me that's true
that's true but you're not in the voice
call with me i cannot hear your
beautiful sampling voices
um
okay
[Music]
i'm not ready to play out last i'm
scared
okay
okay i'm gonna be right back first
before out to last
i'll be right back that is our last time
also thanks everyone who came to stop by
for the column thank you thank you
okay i'll be right back or we just have
we have two more hours we have one hour
of outlast and then
actually it's
it's less than one hour of our last if i
keep talking like this
less than one hour of our last and then
have unarchived karaoke if my voice and
brain are still functioning i think they
are
[Music]
uh after that
all right i'll be right back and then
we'll play our last we're back
be right back
[Music]
hello it's me again
i didn't i didn't set up outlast yet i'm
gonna set it up right now
i can handle one hour right
just one hour right right
why did i choose this game
i don't know
just one hour i'm great at horror really
you think so
i don't know if i would say that
oh
[Music]
okay okay he wants me to adjust the game
brightness hold on
we can do it together
[Music]
let me just let me let me let me let me
let me let me let me
um
capture the game
you can't hear it yet but i hear the
scary noises
okay
i'm not going to forget to turn the the
desktop audio back on this time
oh boy here we are
there it is
the desktop audio
all right
it does look a lot darker on obs
than it does on my monitor
should i use a controller i like
controller
how light do you want it
um
where's bae here
still here
you can do it you've already seen
something anyway it's true it's true
that's why i chose to play ls because i
already know the start of it
so maybe it'll be fine
um
oh wait you want the character on the
right to be barely visible
do you want it to be this bright
is this is this good for you
you guys
darker you guys if you guys complain
about the game being too dark you can't
see anything
if you say i can't see anything then
then i'm gonna be upset
darker is good okay here we go we're
gonna play the game like this then
i don't think darker is good because it
looks really dark for you
[Music]
i think this is good
okay
normal please
um
please be aware everybody in the
audience
we're playing horror game now
oh baby when driving
i don't have a license
this is illegal
we're committing crimes
who wants to commit crimes at the insane
asylum
oh
just like the startup resident evil why
does it always start in the car
[Music]
oh
oh i like this though
it's like watching
it's like watching a movie
i don't have to do anything
very nice
how that's just like all jump scares why
did i choose this i thought about
choosing another chillas art game but i
thought it wouldn't be scary enough
but i'm
i'm already doing the 12-hour stream and
now i'm tormenting myself with a horn
game you know i'm going to read all of
this
because it means less time to play the
game
september 17 2013 from one zero two six
zero one one zero seven five
six at mute mail.com
two
miles up sure gmail.com subject tip
illegal activity at mercoff psychiatric
systems you don't know me you have to
make this quick they might be monitoring
i did two weeks of software consult at
markov
psychiatric systems facilities in mount
massive all sorts of ndas i'm very much
breaking right now but seriously
freak those guys terrible things
happening there don't understand don't
believe how things i saw doctors talking
about dream therapy going too deep
finding something that hadn't been
waiting for them in the mountain
people are being hurt and murkoff is
making money needs to be exposed
all right i'll do that oh was that
someone
or am i imagining things already
could you actually read slower i need
time to understand yeah sorry sorry i'll
read this slower the next note i'll read
is slower
sorry about that
are we going
all right
it's kind of pretty though
i like places like this
well maybe not insane asylums but you
know like um old
old architecture
are we hacker man
we can dance
we can dance if we want to
is there nothing in there
a knock
anybody home so it's pretty the sun is
setting
but why do you always have to come to
these places at night
actually that's one thing i like about
amnesia i think it's daytime for at
least part of the time you're playing
oh sorry is resident evil 8 actually i
think
oh
knock knock
my knock
okay i think i remember you have to
parkour
you have to parkour your way up
do i have infinite stamina oh
uh-oh
we're really crouching under here
no one's home let's leave i agree let's
leave
okay
got it
i am hiding in the corner
i am
huh
are you playing the scare music
already
that was ridiculous that's scare noise
what is it
first person's assassin's creed
i can handle that
oh
[Music]
or does the regular camera not use
battery life
oh
i don't wanna
i don't want
can i stall some more
how much longer do i have to play this
why did the book scream at me
am i about to die
i'm going to pass out
dang you debut book
[Music]
okay
hello
i'm squeezing
blood
why did i choose to play this oh my gosh
you have to grab it so
so forcefully it's okay you don't have
to
you don't have to grab so forcefully
okay
[Music]
oh hello
ah
is it a note to me oh
wait is this it
markov psychiatric systems project wall
rider mount massive co case number 174
patient initials wph billy consortium
consultation dated 2012 october 14th
initial date of patient consult 2009
april 12th
patient age 19 gender male observing
physician dr carl houston dbnr what does
that stand for
aren't you usually like a f
m
therapy status patient claims to have
progressed to self-directed lucid dream
states morphogenetic
is that a 999
oh no just morphogenic
never mind engine activity observed at
unprecedented scale continuing stage 4
hormone schedule
diagnostics spirometry revealed no
bronchial accumulation
hematocrit centrifuge again failed to
separate erythrocytes highly worrisome
mri revealed a rhythmic rem and rem
cycle laughter in interim state to
review notes
billy asked about the status of his
mother's lawsuit against murkov in the
asylum this represents a catastrophic
breach and security despite billy's
claims that he discovered the truth in
the blood dreams of dr trager note that
only traeger is on company records one
richard traeger is an executive from mrd
already licensed security personnel must
be questioned in video securely security
improved i can't mean to include
analytical biometrics markov psychiatric
systems project wall rider mount massive
seal
all right
and you are muted okay okay
here you go
just kidding i won't
okay
you want some privacy i understand oh
am i supposed to go
they're just scaring me right now
oh what's that
little snack
oh snack for me
a little snack
delicious thank you
[Music]
oh boy
hello
i don't like this music
[Music]
somebody's over there
oh i'm scared because
fighting getting to the part that i
watched bane do like
i only know
i don't know much beyond this point
[Music]
oh no i use a battery i didn't mean to
i just don't know the controls
no
oh
all right these dudes are gonna yell at
us
hey
they killed us
get caught out the very
you can't fight them
you have to hide
you can't unlock the main door
if i make it oh if i make it quieter for
you i'm making it quieter for me too
though
tiki
you have to get
it was fun
i can't
i can't deal with so many
dissenting opinions
hey big guy
okay
hey hey
hey
do we go where he went
um
it's quiet oh my gosh i should have just
left it where it was before
i shall just left it where it was before
is this the part
is this the part i think this is the
part is that why you wanted me to turn
it up
little fig
i don't like that guy
you know
jack has way more charisma welcome to
the family son
you know
oh hello and who are you then
[Music]
i
i see and merciful god you have sent me
an apostle
guard your life son
you have a calling
i don't trust this guy either
i don't trust nobody here
he looks trustworthy
man it's looking like emperor palpatine
oh escape the asylum that would have
been a lot easier like
three minutes ago
proclaim the gospel
you
you squishy
another document
can i read this one too
is the document
can i read it
the murkoff corp united states office
warned for seizure case number 294758104
in the matter of the seizure of mount
massive psychiatric center murk of
psychiatric systems look i really care
about the lore in this game okay it's
really important to me that we fully
understand what's happening we need to
know the lore
it's very important
in the matter of the seizure of mount
massive psychiatric center murkoff's
psychiatric systems mount massive
wilderness area country road 112
affidavits have been made before the
board of directors by murkov heartland
security who has the reason henceforth
referred to as mhs who has reason to
believe catastrophic security failure of
psychiatric center with imminent danger
of environment contamination
we are satisfied that the affidavits and
testimony establish sufficient evidence
to require urgent action on the part of
mhs and grounds for the issue of this
warrant you are hereby required to grant
mhs full access to all facilities and
surrender complete authority to its
agents by accepting of this document you
and any surviving relatives surrender
all claims of litigation against the
murkov corps or its subsidiaries for the
actions of mhs or the circumstances with
which require their actions regardless
of responsibility
oh i didn't even notice you there i was
like whoa i have two feet three feet
three feet
um
all right
oh
there's somebody
isn't there something in here too
i don't like it
i want to go to the least scary place
it's all scary though
huh
god why did i why did i do that
get it how do i get it
pick it up
how do i pick it up
um
e i don't know e
x i push
x oh
i see i just had to crouch down
okay
understandable
i'm not even halfway through this
segment yet this was a mistake i don't
want to play it
i don't want to play it
i'm not strong
this game is
cheap
it does jump scares
i hear sound
i don't want to be jump scared i don't
want to be jump scared
why are they telling me i can peek
don't tell me such a thing
i don't want to know
[Music]
ah a document
the only thing saving me
the only thing saving me is the copious
lore
murkoff psychiatric systems project wall
writer mount massive co case number 136
patient initials clw walker consultation
dated 2013 may 28th initial date of
patient consults 2011 january 28th
patient age 32 gender male observing
physician dr rudolf wernickel
notation by dr walsh therapy status
morphogenic engine activity plateaued at
roughly 2000 ppm
pp unsafe to progress beyond stage 3
hormone schedule diagnosis spirometry
revealed light to medium bronchial
accumulation mri scans consistent with
patients reported dreams interview notes
walker was interviewed in restraints
following his self-inflicted inflicted
mutation mutilations restraints have had
to be altered to accommodate his
enormous size oh is this the one we saw
extensive dental eruptions as consistent
with failed morphogenic engine cellular
activity he claims the skin ripped from
his forehead allows for a truer way of
seeing seems to have some boyhood
experience with
tuatara lizards in their parietal eyes
he has expressed anxiety about his flesh
specifically around his lips and nose
attending orderlies should be advised to
watch for further self mutilation the
mental traumas he sustained while
serving in afghanistan seems to be
um
i'm not gonna need the rest
[Music]
hello
oh so now we're on the other side
but the lore i know the lore
oh
not you
not to you
i know he's gonna jump at me i think i
know this part but i think he's not
gonna jump at me yet
only later
[Laughter]
hello
oh
[Music]
it's the homies
are we watching the game tonight boys
we watching the game
with the homies
oh
who's that
dead
don't dead open inside
why do you have to grab it with such
vigor
you don't have to
what did we get
a key card for security control
what if i don't want that what if i
don't want that
i'm scared i'm scared
[Music]
now it's time to be grabbed
even the jump scares i know are gonna
happen are kind of bad
[Music]
what if i run by him so fast he can't
give me
[Music]
now we're all
dizzy and bleary-eyed
[Music]
oh man
man
what's that
is that the bronchial infection
look i know so much about the lore i
know everything there is you can quiz me
on it
i'm basically in master of outlast lore
if we want to escape can we just like go
through the window look it's right there
i guess it's made to not be escaped from
the huh
are we safe
is there nothing in here
just a jump scare
you like how last more recite all the
documents by memory
don't think i won't
you see it says proclaim the gospel and
the person we saw was sort of dressed in
some sort of
holy
holy garb
it's thematic
do we have to go in the basement now
we're in here
so we went over there
we didn't go in here yet what
what what what what what what i don't
wanna look behind while running
[Music]
i don't wanna have to run
oh no
i can't do 30 more minutes i thought
that this whole part would take me one
hour
i spent a speed ran it spent spent ran
it sped running
a speed ran it
running time really
[Music]
do i have to run
i don't want to run i don't want the
action i don't want action well maybe
action is not that bad actually
find some documents to read are there
even any documents
i don't like that sound
i didn't like that i didn't like that
you see this is like the worst type of
elevator there is
this right here
awful
horrible elevator
that's horrible
[Music]
make some more notes if you use the
camera really
oh i guess i am supposed to be filming
it i mean isn't this like enough
like this right here this scene right
here
combined with maybe just a little bit of
this for
to be certain is this not enough
i think that's plenty
i think you don't need more than that
stop stop i don't want to go in there
but i feel like bailey got jump scared
by a paper in here but he told me to run
run
i'm scared
it's gonna make me run here
oh
what what
is he is he going after me
hide in here please
he won't find me in the toilet
can he see over
can see can he see over here
i don't have to run yet
really
oh i see holding it open slowly
no i can only slam
i'm sniffling
i need to stop he's sniffling he's got
problems he's freaking me out he's
sniffling
i can't he's sniffling
he's sniffling
oh you
is
what was that
why'd he do that
[Music]
hey buddy
my note
oh baby i'm already beat all too heck
picking broken glass out of my scalp
couple cracked ribs nearly killed by a
deformed giant looks like somebody tried
to oh no
i don't want to read this either
okay
he's so mean
the priest is writing these notes
ah
head in the toilet
i can't these noises are too scary oh no
it's the meat room
i don't like the meat room
[Music]
[Applause]
why
why they'll never find me in the meat
room if i just hide here
no why
[Music]
it didn't used to be a meat room
yeah it doesn't seem to be refrigerated
properly
the meat room is the first place to look
no no no no
they'll never find me here
oh
[Music]
why did i do this to myself i don't know
but i have regrets i keep looking at the
clock being like can i leave yet
is it safe yet i'm gonna go really far
away
wait do i sound like debut fonda if i
talk way over here
if i talk far away from my microphone
[Music]
why does he have to slam it
are we hacker man they lie
uh oh
oh oh oh
is it when it happens is it
[Music]
oh
he's looking at me
no
oh let me let me let me let me let me in
let me in let me in let me in
he's gonna look in the locker
do we have to run
is he gonna look fine
oh he's leaving okay okay
[Music]
quick the journalism right right oops i
missed it
oops i'm
did i miss it yet
yeah let's just stay here
i like the locker
how much time can i can i spend in the
lock
do i have to run yet
do you have to run yet
i don't know i don't know
i don't know
is that a plant
oh no it's a wheelchair i think
i don't like it here at all
not at all i hate it
i really think
[Music]
she knows
okay
hypnotic experimentation and research
my favorite lore
on wednesday 10th of february 1954
hypnotic experimentation research work
was continued in building 13 of the
mount massive preserve in colorado using
the following subjects
material abridged one a post-hypnotic of
the night before
what
pointed finger you will sleep
you will sleep
i will sleep after the stream
[Music]
i will sleep soon was nighttime mrs
jackson and pierce immediately
progressed to a deep hypnotic state with
no further suggestion miss pierce was
then instructed having previously
expressed a fear of firearms in any
fashion that she would use every method
at her disposal to awaken miss jackson
now in a deep hypnotic sleep and failing
this she would pick up a nearby pistol
and fire at ms jackson
that seems very ethical
oh she was instructed that her range
would be so great that she would not
hesitate to kill jackson for failing to
awaken
miss pierce carried out these
suggestions to the letter including
firing the unloaded pneumatic pistol gun
in jackson and then proceeded to fall
into a deep sleep after proper
suggestions were made both were
awakenings best complete amnesia for the
entire sequence miss pierce was again
handed the gun when she refused in an
awakened state to pick up or accept from
the operator she expressed absolute
denial that the foregoing
sequence had happened
okay
will there be quiz at the end yeah what
if we do a quiz right now how about we
do a quiz right now what if we just go
read the outlast wiki instead
oh it's too dark
[Music]
oh shoot i know this part actually
you have to hide at this part
i don't want to hide
where can i hide
anywhere in the dark
oh no
i don't like this part
i know this part sucks i've seen it
before
because he's like patrolling the area
he can see in the dark no he can't i
don't think he can
i don't like any parts it's true
why would i
why would i like any part of this
at all
[Music]
oops
he's gonna come in here afterwards right
can i hide
i'm not here
nope nope i'm not here i'm not here
there's a bed there's a locker
he won't hear me
he won't see me
i'm not here
he can't smell me he can't
he's sniffing
oh god i hear his footsteps
get out of here get out of here get out
of here get out of here
is he
gone
do you think he's gone
well there are a lot
he's not gone he's not gone he's not god
he's not god he's not gone
he's not gone he's not gone he's not
gone he's not gone
he's camping
it's really spooky in here
not fair not fair not fair
don't mind me don't mind me
i hear footsteps
here footsteps
footsteps footsteps
he definitely didn't hear it he didn't
hear it
he did not hear it
we live here we live here now for the
next 13 minutes 13 minutes of pain
he was breaking down a door really
how do i know if he's there though now i
can't know if he's there
when i leave uh-oh
where is he
he's there
[Music]
can he hear the battery
should i change the battery
why am i homing don't look back in anger
because when the guy looked back at me
the thing that popped into my head was a
stone to look back at me in anger
and now it's in my head
he's not going to find me
nobody is watching the stream he's a
sapling
no way
i'm
i dead see anything
[Applause]
i can't see anything
he found me
he actually found me i was hiding he
couldn't have seen me in the dark
does he have dark vision too
me
[Music]
i'm gonna use strategy this time
strategy this time
no more from here
no more fear
is he
is he there
that's him right
how do i know when he's gone when you
stop sniffing me
no more sniffing
thank you very much somebody saw thank
you what else could it be
no footsteps mean he's gone i gotta feel
it
i don't feel anything
i feel
pain
that's how i feel
did he say
he was hey
he's camping
he said cool fun now
you said happy anniversary
[Music]
i'm stuck
oh my goodness oh my goodness i keep
actually turning my night vision off
i'm trying to run
i can't do it i can't do it
it's actually not that bad when you get
over the fear
hold on
i can't remember my buttons
who's that
nope nobody
is what him oh shoot that's him
i thought i was busting through
wait i'm leaving i shouldn't just leave
is he still here
is that him
what's happening
[Music]
i think it's a good idea i agree
i agree
why the music though
where am i going anyway
how many of these are there
how many buttons do i have to push
[Music]
one more
two
three
just another ghost
that's right that's me i'm the ghost
probably five or so
maybe 20 more
about
um
is he coming i thought i heard him
i thought i heard him
around 87.
four really four
i hear him i hear him
i hear the noises
i know the music is just bumpy
oh wait i was right in here already is
there no one in here
don't open
dead inside
is this not just where we came in from
oh hello
is there a place to hide in here
nowhere to hide
can i not hide in here
these are not lockers right
is this a locker oh that's a locker okay
i have my plan
my plan is also to waste battery because
i won't need it
after
three minutes or however long we're
streaming for
i do need to go to the karaoke stream
it's true
but after i have to weigh either i'm
late to my karaoke stream or
uh this vaude is only 10 hours long
which i don't feel is wrong for it to be
only 10 hours
long i mean not to 11 you know like 10
59 or whatever
oh only 10. i already know people are
going to comment they're going to say
the title said 12 hours but you only
streamed for 11 hours why why you can't
call this a 12 hour stream
[Music]
30 minutes more no
i can't take 30 but it's more of our
last
[Music]
can we be done yet
this is that room again isn't it
i don't know
oh oh clutch hide though
hopefully you can't see my camera light
in the dark
that was very clutch
clutch bed
one minute
can we be done yet
oh
my chad died i have to refresh it
i have to pause the game and refresh my
chat
don't do it yet did we do it yet
i'm free am i free
time's up i didn't beat this section
though but am i free
can we be free
freedom
i always i play it a little bit i
definitely stalled
a little bit
i played a little bit though
oh i don't know can i even do md after
this oh [\h__\h] usually not that bad
though well i don't know
[Music]
okay
now it's karaoke time
so i have to end this stream and i have
to go to the next one hold on let me
um
open
the chat though
on the other stream
first
before i send you there
it might take me like a few minutes um
i have to
change my audio setup a little bit for
karaoke
to make sure it's properly synced
[Music]
so it might take me a couple minutes
to get over there
i'll do it as fast as i can
yes you should be
redirected
i believe
there yes
i think i set it up before
well thank you to everyone who watched
so far
and thank you
um to those who are watching the vod if
you're confused why is the stream only
11 hours well we didn't the last hour
was unarchived karaoke on a different
stream
so sorry so sorry i hope you were able
to see it
hope you enjoyed these 11 hours and
thank you so much for all the
anniversary wishes i really appreciate
it okay i'm gonna meet you over in the
next stream in a couple of minutes you
should be sent there and i should be
live momentarily thank you guys so much
okay one more hour let's go bye bye
bye bye
[Music]