[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
assistant
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
this is
thank you
[Music]
foreign
this is
kick it again
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday Jim
Tracy
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
Jim Tracy
saying now because until I get to your
super chat it will be
probably a year later
where are you where are you where are
you
I don't see you in the chat now
are you crying from happiness
you're welcome
[Music]
unless
okay welcome welcome welcome
uh
what you gonna do
what you gonna do what you gonna do when
fruit come for you oh wait
um
I forgot to tweet number one uh
number one
on it
what eh
I thought no I didn't realize I messed
up my my stream tweet I didn't put the
thumbnail there
oh man
I also didn't do art by
um
why did I not do it Ally
five something
what there was an ollie rape when I just
started but during the waiting room
uh during the loading screen because I
don't think you can rate a waiting room
can you
preacher you can do that
oh
I didn't realize
starting
have started
title
yeah
ah
you can even ride your own waiting room
well yeah I mean if you can ride the
waiting ones then no it makes sense
oh hold on uh
it is time for Celebi
Sparks
turned from Full cocoa to something else
to
[Music]
where is your Evolution there you go
oh my God
shiny version of that is also still pink
fascinating
so this
ah
scale up dirt that's a weird name
skm
it's also your birthday are you two
twins happy birthday to you Mama
[Music]
happy birthday to you then scam
wow maybe your separated Twins and
didn't know it but now you know and
you're gonna have a super emotional
reunion isn't that wonderful oh God
moved to tears this too
so nice you found each other through my
stream
hahaha
and finally
uh separated above life is so cruel
cruel
oh okay anything else was supposed to
change here
think
right now we good but I wanted to
I wanted to give my
um
I don't know if you're watching this I
really appreciate it but
I don't think I can use those I'm sorry
oh my God blue mate
Starbucks stuff oh my oh my that's
amazing
oh my oh my God that is good stuff for
my burps ah the ostrich I don't know
about the ostrich
well anyway let me in this time
ah
Starbucks ended
um so cute
and these where does this one come
oh so cute I wonder I wonder if I can
attach it like that
um
cute let's let's go for the
so cute
okay okay let me put this on my burps
real quick
my dad
[Music]
gotta hide myself
boobs are embarrassed when they're
changing you know even though you
already saw them naked you know
and my throat is not really I don't know
like in the morning it felt uh better
than last morning because well
[Music]
um
ah
I did I did something
right before
falling asleep I took a fruit candy
oh that looks lovely lovely lovely
um so that helped a little bit but uh
just really minimum Improvement
and then yeah
um well it is what it is I don't know
what to say throat hurt so much
how how why why
I'm almost done give me a woman's brain
slow
burn very slow oh
that one I
uh the
the the candy thing I can't attach it
I can't
that's too bad because
um I don't know how to explain this but
with this uh pngs
um
it's like
when uh it takes like the I think the
middle of the image as the base point to
attach things
to uh
I can't like take the edge or whatever
I don't know how to explain this
I'm just I can't my brain is not working
oh oh but the hats work which
oh my god
look look look look look
cute
[Music]
look at them
oh I know that maybe wait
see like for example I can't put it I
can't attach it like like here for
example
it has to like my ah you actually see my
mouse oopsie
I think you actually see my mouse so
when I grab it on the on the edge it
will always automatically go down the
middle
and then I have to
like I also probably can't yeah can't
put it on the heart
um it needs something
to work with oh God don't shake so much
what the second is where are you
continuing
oh
[Music]
I think it was better before
oh that works I mean I'm gonna be
smaller so you don't see it so well
anyway the star books
so good oh my God
okay
okay sorry sorry I'm sorry
hands of surgeon
you should have this as merge the
Starbucks cup well copyright problems I
don't think they
they would allow this or anyone
um
okay
how are you guys feeling
that's cool
genki.com
[Music]
I've restarted the game this time
because I heard that if you don't
restart it the ram
fills up like crazy for this game
on the switch and the more the longer
you have it running the more legs you
will have
so there we go
um
almost dying dueling on my shift
dwelling wow that's like so old school
why are you doubling who are you dueling
and what happened did you did he slap
you with a glove in your face
wait
[Music]
I'm waiting for your answer
do well
foreign
[Music]
well whatever you have I hope it gets
better soon
is the music too loud guys how is it
you find a shiny no
sending my shiny luck follows you today
thank you
that's fine okay
okay
[Music]
um
I have tea next to me
also I even I I
[Music]
said don't worry about it
uh it would have been funny
um what was I gonna say oh yeah I I
cleaned another humidifier
free freed it from the when you call
that an English calc the residue of
water
cleaned it completely and set it up in
another room so I have two running at
the same time trying to get my apartment
like a sauna
not gonna work but oh it's calcium
oh
okay uh
for sure I had to clean them though
because they're yeah there was a lot of
calcium
you place like a subtropical spot no I
would like it to be like that but it's
like really hard to get it to that level
I wanted to feel like the summer in
Japan without the heat just a human the
humidity
um
[Music]
sprained your ankle almost how do you
almost sprain it
[Music]
milk in the humidifier no
no
[Music]
one humidifier in every corner yeah I
mean the bigger they are they say in the
more space right they can cover mine are
like pretty big they're they're not the
tiny baby ones I don't know if it really
covers the whole room properly though
but I have it at least right next to me
when I sleep and right now when I work
as well it's right next to me
so hopefully
I am inhaling the humidity
come to me
also I cleaned my apartment in general a
little bit more today tried to get some
[\h__\h] done and I played with my Cactus
and I took a shower
yeah
oh on yesterday you know you know how I
said before I ended the stream that oh I
hope past kiwawa was smart and ordered
uh one at least one hello meal that is
fast to make and yes basketball was
smart very smart one of my recipes was
supposedly 15 minutes of time calculated
I think it took me 20 minutes my butt
still
it was really easy I didn't post a
picture because even though it was
really yummy
it didn't quite look it didn't look bad
but it didn't really look like you would
look at it and know what it is so I
didn't post it but yeah good job
basketball so smart
so smart I'm getting dizzy
if we took you out what's with future
Chihuahua
eh
I'm drinking a mallow tea
which is supposed to be good for throat
problems is it ready to pour I wonder it
needs like 10 minutes actually
I'm not sure if it's been 10 minutes
I think maybe
for a little bit I
I forgot my freaking spoon again
I need to get it
wait has that really properly
worked I shot the tea bags
into the tea
[Music]
what's hot
so hot
yeah of course I have an electric kettle
a really cute one actually
oh this brings me to attention
for like a bunch of my kitchen
appliances I found a brand on Amazon I
think it's an Italian brand
um that kind of has a it has a line of
kitchen appliances that that
um is
um
90s Maybe
it's maybe inspired with some pastel
colors
uh although not only possibles I think I
also had it in red normal red
um and and then so I bought a toaster
uh an a water cooker uh
a juicer
and possibly one more thing
from the same line yeah
[Music]
yeah because I really like the style of
it and the quality isn't that either and
they actually have so many more other
things that I want to buy like they have
uh they have um they have a pizza
a really really hot oven like a
relatively small one though but you can
make pizza within four minutes three
minutes in there you know like the
proper proper pizza oven and they have
um a crab maker and they have a popcorn
maker they have everything
um but not everything was available on
Amazon
but it's quite a while ago when I bought
those things
but I wanted I wanted them and now I
have a bunch of matching things it's
really cute and then in Italy you know
when in close to our um accommodation
when I was walking I was looking inside
the store window and I noticed you know
the store had like all kinds of things
but right at the window they had
um displayed a bunch of Arrieta and
kitchen appliances from the same brand
and that made me realize oh wait this
brand is Italian
they had so many of them and I didn't
realize it was like actually pretty well
known and common I just thought I bought
a pretty freaking random ass
uh kitchen appliance from a random ass
brand on Amazon but then I see it in
real life
I was I was fascinated that that thing
over there is so funny
it looks so funny yeah yeah I can
recommend it if you guys find it
um
quite a solid brand yeah honestly I
think it's really solid I have
absolutely no problems with it it's
really really
I'm gonna grab a spoon now
[Music]
here I am
you know I just fart continuing my
attention I just found it so much nicer
to have something like that with like a
neat design in terms of kitchen
appliances and having everything in like
a boring silver or black or whatever
[Music]
honey
yeah so I can recommend it if you're
looking for some matching nice kitchen
appliances Aviator that brand has like
everything and you should find it on
Amazon
hmm
yeah so boring all the kitchen
appliances are the same
pushed okay
[Music]
yeah the Tumbleweeds are so funny
but I can imagine them being a pretty
weak Pokemon
I wanna know who knows maybe they're
actually pretty strong anyway what's the
plan for today let me look at the map
what are we
we we took care of him we took him down
what is the recommended next place to go
this this Titan
[Music]
or this gym it's a gym right why is he
turning around
is that is that the normal gym oh my
throat hurts oh
tied in a normal gym
um
foreign
so that's that's the normal gym that
dude
why is he why is he facing that's so
weird mysterious
oh
[Music]
um
how do we get there
oh we're here now that was the
little thing
do we have to go from there
[Music]
oh that's a weird path
from the Water Gym town
[Music]
I said gym this time yeah
normally only gonna say Arena and we've
never been here before it's about the
poppico
I don't think I've ever been here before
okay I'll go that way because I've never
been there before
[Music]
normal Arena that's so weird when's the
last time we had a normal Arena
that rock is only so smooth now because
I ran over it a million times
fifth gen okay what about a while ago
I'm a little boring Arena normal normal
is it's so boring
normal Arena what the [\h__\h]
uh was I supposed to take the upper path
or
does it not matter
oh wait there's a TM up there
sun and moon had a normal trial Capital
really
[Music]
is this look
look
maybe I can just
oh there we go I don't think we could do
that
uh I'm
single what the [\h__\h] is for me
I guess we'll enter from the wrong side
funny name
geek
love warmth
or warm
sounds like some kind of English
uh accent which English accent would say
or swarm to earthworm
room
[Music]
Dennis
what happened I didn't pay attention
what is that that's supposed to be
Spanish
it's an or for dogs
or form was raised orthodox
why did I miss him again
what oh
[Laughter]
it's important
no
oh five times right
I didn't even did I give him that item
yes he has the item okay it makes sense
Nanny what is this
up
that's a secret entrance but there would
be an item
okay I'm actually still gonna enter from
here
you have something for me please give me
something
[Music]
it's all right
an item to be helping a Pokemon just
protecting the Boost to power up the
whole punching moves and presents it
prevents direct contact with targets so
it has to be a punching attack
oh
so like what I just used to takuma but
that didn't look like a punch it looked
more like a slap more like a push
that's very specific how do I know if
it's a punching attack
Thunder Punch does it have to be in the
in the name of the attack
Fire Punch I said ah okay
did I fight you no I didn't
[Music]
it could stop
anything with lunch okay
once you get a Thunder Punch oh
my God I just got a random shiny
good for you you are hereby banned from
the kfp chat
was nice knowing you
bye-bye
oh you also knowed from the animation
okay so even if it's not called punch it
might be a punch okay
all right all right all right
uh quill finish is that also a water
Pokemon then consistent speech
ah this one's poison though
but it still works
[Music]
still works
guys today is the last day of November
do you remember
today is the last day of November
tomorrow is gonna be the start of the
hollow in an advent calendar
foreign
[Music]
mentally ready for it yet but here I
come
oh wait that's
the puppy cool
but it looks
stylized it looks like
ah but it's not the same it looks like
that other city that we went to
the name though cool cool cool cool
thanks for organizing calendar I'm
excited
[Music]
I hope
I hope there will be no delays but to be
honest I think
um you need to expect and I also am
mentally prepared for
delayed submissions and then not being
available at the time it should be
available but
um that's just you know
could be expected this is part of the
experience
especially since it's a project
um that is organized by a member and not
by management and freaking last minute
it'll be fine at least the first today
has been ready
Day free is also ready day two I was
told will be recorded on day one
hmm and that's probably gonna be like
how most of these videos will happen
one day before its release date they
will be recorded
but what is this
who's supposed to fight here is it just
there's no no no gym battle here
just for decoration Maybe
[Music]
living life on the edge yeah this is
going to be standard and precious yes
yes unfortunately
you know last year I know this year this
year was this year at the one year and
the two-year anniversary I said how
about we
deliver things faster in the future but
well it's inevitable
um
a good joke
yeah nah it's okay I think you know for
this project it's
kind of easy going as long as the videos
eventually show up
then it's okay
but date day two for example hopefully
will not show up on day 20 like that
means that delay would be not okay
I would just
if if you notice you know I mean there
will be some doubles but if you notice
that chihuahua has a lot of appearances
in this whole live English calendar then
that might be because I'm trying to fill
for some
video that has not been delivered in
time
oh
[Music]
um more killed on it
um
[Music]
how does this go
thank you
you look you are you do you do
[Music]
that is such a fun anime man
huh the ground Titan is there well I
didn't see him
I feel like he should be there if he was
there then he would be there
logical thinking
if he was there then he would be there
[Music]
you that's not right you bullshitting me
it sounds about right
I lost it
hello
la la la
yeah
One More Story today
[Music]
will this be right on and how many Cuban
appearances will there be so far
this won't be red for a while
how are you feeling today teacher
hopefully by them
selves I have read it now you didn't
expect that um
you did not expect it
uh oh wow holy [\h__\h] everything's
effective knuckle stack I want to hit
him with a metal claw
I'll read it again will I will I will I
am
[Music]
blackout paste
yeah if you took you while we're looking
at that and we'll think oh I already
read this like uh two weeks ago so
um for the sake of my throat I'm not
gonna read it again
but maybe I'll give you an answer but I
will not read it again Clarion
is the fire Evie
I'll stay let's dig
yeah okay
it looks like tronkers damn
it's so fluffy
[Music]
you know fully my throat not born
we will never know
never never never
uh
[Music]
I don't know let's keep and see what I
have
because it's fighting good against
fighting because you know you need a
fighting partner partner
let me try oh thank God oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
well now you can tell me that would have
been a bad choice anyway
it's neutral
um
very psychic
excited verb let's do it
we have to use that Bub
how's your voice going
um
it's painful oh my God look at all that
fluff
Les
like lazy's dress because you guys watch
the Super Mario movie trailer
last night
it was a good trailer I guess
I watched a Japanese one as well
and for the Japanese one I bought
Peach's voice was still
kind of low but a little bit higher and
better
than the what's her name someone Taylor
she's really really pretty and I think
her voice acting itself
it's not bad I just don't think it's
fitting oh dragon tail or the character
there's also people who are disagreeing
with me and there's people who agree
with me but honestly like
I feel like they just chose her because
she brings in Fame like they literally
every single voice actor
it shows is freaking famous
and
does any of them all of them are normal
actors none of them are actual like
voice actors right
which is no problem I guess because they
do their job decently well
yeah I think everyone's happy with
Bowser
Japanese Bowser even better though gotta
tell you
[Music]
speech from Mario and we all know what
location exactly she's like
oh and one thing that maybe they
considered but I can't imagine them
considering that I feel like they just
chose it for the sake of having a famous
um voice actress but one thing I would
understand is if they would say that
um well this movie is gonna be watched
by a lot of people
and you know
if it's uh let's say a two-hour movie we
don't wanna annoy everybody with
um two hours of oh
that kind of voice
if you consider the fact that a lot of
people who come in to watch the movie
would
[Music]
um be more normal people who don't like
that kind of I don't know I don't know I
don't know how to explain that but
proudly you know in little phrases like
in the games
if you just have it in small doses maybe
that's okay but if you hear it for the
whole freaking movie
maybe then it's like too much so they
wanted a more normal voice but
but I'm really not
getting that far
that
oh yeah appeal to a wider audience so
that's kind of what I meant yeah
but I think they just wanted to appeal
to a wider audience by choosing famous
voice actors or actors
um she's really important though
hype it's more of a Japanese thing yeah
but even in English peach always has
that voice
she's supposed to have a high-pitched
cute ass voice
look at her face look at her design I
just don't think uh a little voice like
that fits but whatever
I'll get used to it in the end you gotta
get used to it and then it will be okay
it's cool though she seems to have a big
role in the movie
foreign
I thought she would really just get
kidnapped judging by the first trailer
but then
in this trailer she seems to have a big
role and she seems to be quite involved
which is really cool I'm happy to see
that
your faces though oh well
their face is so they're not the typical
Nintendo
um style anymore
they have that I don't know we talked
about it before
they have that style to it what is it
again
Oh I thought I would find you here
yeah illumination style I guess it's the
studio
which also is a thing gotta get used to
it
gotta get used to it and modern pretty
animation faces yeah yeah
it's cute but just like you you used to
the Mario and Peach faces Etc from for
like 15 years or whatever how long
you've been following that franchise and
suddenly you see them like that it's
like um
something's very off
but they're pretty like I don't I have I
don't have a problem with that kind of
art style
um
oh no poisoned
oh no
where am I going am I I'm not going the
right way huh
I'm going the opposite way
one one
so it looks good
yeah toe looks good cute and also Toad's
voice uh now I already forgot the tall
voice in English but I think it was good
but also the Japanese voice is perfect
but I did not expect
anything bad from the Japanese stuff
might have to watch it in both languages
when does it come out again
they had a release date right when is it
okay Pearl
oh those are those those things
so weird was it the size again
oh that's your evolution
oh oh
[Music]
uh high level
April
March what
41.
I tried to catch it I don't know if this
will kill him I don't know
fighting territory
school will be really effective right
now
oh okay that's nice
I'll catch it
there we go it's not fighting anymore
I guess you can have a gray ball
ah you can't one shot them anyway
[Music]
they have to return to their original
form
oh that's actually a good
um strategy for
generally like competitive right
it's like a focus belt
oops no
Focus belt
that was easy yeah why what the [\h__\h]
what do you want you ran right where I
respawned 37.
[Music]
it doesn't work like that in competitive
yeah
what the [\h__\h] is that
that's new right what is that
is that bell peppers
[Music]
still right
the grass
what
is
fire illusion of the tiny grass one any
grass
the cup sockets what
yeah it makes sense that they're those
two colors though because they grow in
different colors
um I don't know let's try pluck
it's super effective oh damn
oh no I'm worrying
see I don't wanna
um k o u even though my title says that
but I am too strong
but that didn't do 50 right I did a
little bit less than fifty percent okay
let me try again
they're pokedex entry is hilarious okay
I lied in my title or not
chaos
instead of their mouth looks weird
do you not want to go into my ball so
the Pokemon in the back is laughing at
me
why does it not even consider going into
my ball
oh
[Music]
my God it's just making fun of me
balcony
foreign
[Music]
converts spicy chemicals into fire
energy and blasts the surrounding area
with a super spicy stream of flame
spicy but why do they completely ignore
the green head hey they don't even talk
about the green head
but grass fire is really rare isn't it
um
does it have another evolution
must be in violent
oh wait it didn't that didn't look like
there was space for another evolution
wow
oh
this is my job did you copy closing on a
nice year but now I've already got them
oh no that sounds good then isn't that
a nice development
[Music]
what
no kicks
hey
a song Overkill
the green hat has turned vicious due to
dude
oh they're like manipulating each other
two heads
Shadow Ball
oh Dark Moon
or ghost
now it's Coast
oh very good
[Music]
um should I get rid of round
uh-huh
nice we're done the ghost attack now
[Music]
oh yeah I'm one of your top artists I
should be the one and only top others yo
just kidding thank you for listening to
my songs on Spotify
thank you
you know that Pokemon looks like a
Pokemon that Sana would like oh my God
they have different forms depending on
the gender
oh
that one the middle of the male one oh
really reminds me of um
the sword and shield Shields Pokemon
I forgot his name but
Hyrule
the wrong Pokemon
um
how many shiny ones does Kiana already
have why are you asking that it's like
you're trying to make me cry
let's try let's start Shadow Ball I
don't know how that works on fire
I'll catch it I guess
oh it doesn't affect oh [\h__\h]
well
it's normal fire
okay that makes sense
but
I mean I'm gonna try to
catch it let's see is this better
oh
he's trying to use the normal attack on
me and that also didn't work
[Music]
and you self-destruct no that's so mean
when a Shiny Pokemon has a attack that
destroys itself
that is so mean
oh that's that would make anyone really
salty
okay now it's perfect
didn't mean to open them
well the other ladies are so
Angie
[Music]
huh
you guys know
how it feels
yo yo why is that lady so aggressive
she's she's
um spawn camping
Spa camping on me you see that
Bob can't beat that [\h__\h] oh
my God
you're so mad I took one of your sisters
I'm leaving I'm leaving why so laggy I
restarted the game
but I like the snowflakes uh
in the
grass area
the book
cute oh I can take it down oh you're
actually only one level
no we don't die ah never mind
all right uh
oh
you're you look like a old Pokemon
you're like familiar looking
wait a second
whoa
what looks like I know like a base form
of those two Pokemon sword and shield
Pokemon the legendaries
ah I can see that okay that that of
awesome Rock rub ah makes sense but it
really looks like it could be like a
normal form of
the legendaries
and
I should kill my Pokemon which one
another picture
wait so it's normal
you're normal
right away okay
let's catch it it's rock type oh oh
yeah you can have a great ball too I
don't know why I'm catching so many
Pokemon
[Music]
so they're all stretch is over there too
hey
hey don't waste my time
don't you dare
[Music]
night form is cool it has a night form
do you have Rock coverage but I have a
Pokemon that does Pro rocks yes
I've got that covered
like and Rock
a taxi spray with his trap claws in fact
literally Elvis instructions of trainers
and shorts
um nice design but
a bit boring too too bland because of
the colors
but it's pretty and it's
actually from looking at the
pre-evolution
it's really good
at least now we're on the right path
finally
it's got another evolution
no no
watched so hard to stay with that [\h__\h]
oh
evolution
[Music]
I wonder what you will use
uh for a wild turkey
[Music]
how cute that thing is kind of cute
did I no I didn't catch one yet
orange Evolution will require what
what that sounds cool I want to look up
the color
okay
what did it just do something to make
itself invisible
okay
like did it take or it jumped it bounced
oh okay well
all I can do is wait right so let me
use my time wisely
uh where's poison heal do I not have a
poison heel
oh antidote oh
ah
there you go
come back now
cute
let's try this you're so round you fit
perfectly into this bottle come on
yeah
it's cute
it's so cute oh how come I learned
something entrainment not entertainment
that
never heard of that
nah
cute oh it's ice oh
seems to be closely related to Wilmer ah
cute
no
but it's very cute Kawaii
the more I look at it the more I like it
especially when its mouth is open
honey
[Music]
you need them braces your teeth are
[\h__\h]
I'm assuming it's planned
oh it's dragons
um
foreign
[Music]
great evolutionary line
I believe that but uh I'm not interested
in using it I'm just gonna catch it all
right
[Music]
please
thank you
[Music]
no
no no
oh [\h__\h]
wow me
[Music]
who would resist what he's doing
lizard murder's entire family
not psychic Amiga
and I'm just gonna give it a [\h__\h]
Ultra Balls whatever
the deer's just chilling over there
what's its problem huh what do you want
I don't even want you that badly at all
well this one worked actually better has
a really low cat train
why
[Music]
okay at least that's really weak on me
go hide it
don't resist
[Music]
oh
why are we such a little [\h__\h] do I have
anything I can uh like you know
paralyzed or poison or so without
hurting it until
I don't have anything
thank you
okay
way too annoying
I don't live in Japan currently I used
to live in Japan
um
it's nice but depends of obviously where
you live but um
it can be very nice got a lot of good
food
public transports in
and the people are nice lots of fun
things to do
Leaf mountains
thing to crack what thing
what
I keep on
pumping
[Music]
and yes I'm traveling back to Japan soon
I am indeed
looking forward to it
[Music]
air cutter
ah huh
no leg
[Music]
s
oh hi there
oh
is that the new Evolution or something
[Music]
like a snow form
it's so pretty it has like wings
Sephora well has it always been a thing
it's so pretty
[Music]
oh wow
today
oh hello there is this the right path
seems so oh yeah
what is that I've seen I've seen that
before
I'm kind of tired today I don't know why
I slept a lot
slept pretty nicely considering that I
had throat pain throughout
[Music]
you will paint with that
you know the feeling
I think it's also I'm a type of person
who does not drink coffee at all
so I also don't drink energy drinks
so you know what my problem is I don't
really have anything that really
effectively wakes me up
tried like different teas before but
they're not really that effective at
least not for me
so I wish I wish I was a coffee person
I need to force myself to like it
eventually it's not like coffee is bad
let's do drinks I will gladly stay away
from
coffee coffee is not bad right
what the [\h__\h] is that
no no what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
what the hell what is that and those
like koala knows but then the back is
like a runner no dragon or so
Dragon Eyes
what
it's cute it looks funny
follow me it's rare and it's really good
mmm Dragon Eyes
hmm maybe I have a little train it
please don't die I might die
oh my God
you know what I'll catch it and I'll put
it in my cream because we don't have
dragon we don't have eyes
and I want to see the evolution
[Music]
do I have a
now don't have a like a dark ball
let's try a great ball first
two Evolution so this is the starter
this is the starch
exciting yeah
why does it look so funny
it looks so funny the things on its
hands look like Snot
chocolate tasting coffee
[Music]
it's going to KO what's up what can I do
I have to
I have no choice but to throw balls
oh
[Music]
nice little Play-Doh Play-Doh
no I don't think so
convinced of violence
three bucks
for us absorbs heat through its doors
will Fin and converts the heat into ice
energy the higher the temperature the
more energy for the e-back stores
who should we replace
and the team
we've we've seen a lot of Amiga so maybe
it's time for Amiga to go even though
you know I know Amiga is really strong
but we want to see different Pokemon
oops [\h__\h] what
yeah yeah okay you guys actually agree
nice too
well goodbye Omega Amiga maybe it'll
bring you back at some point when I need
to
um
but
for now
dakuma overlaps it nah how it's just
dragon and ice
cute
oh it's one of the last ones
I've noticed that a little bit but the
fighting moves yeah
um we're looking kind of hereby
so
take care of that
[Laughter]
for you
okay let's fight you
down
[Music]
can I have first of all have the next
level up oh it's already ready oh nice
oh she's cute
I got what you got I need something we
can use our baby Pokemon no but I like
this one what is that cycle
ghost
poisoned gopherita
Gothic Lolita what is that
I'll try um
well I was a psychic itself
[Music]
strong against psychic
um
I forgore
how about this little boy
[Music]
darkened bug
s
[Music]
let's go
foreign
let's see how much does that do now
[Music]
did not even feel it
yeah yeah
did I skipped the trainer somewhere
outside I feel like I maybe did
whatever I don't think in this game like
if we really fight every trainer and
then also make an effort to you know
battle
and and catch a lot of Pokemon then you
are so easily over leveled so
not too much of a problem to leave some
trainers behind right
oh
I wonder maybe those
oh big toggle Togo Evolution damn he
looks even more
like done with this [\h__\h]
time to
go
into a
old people place in June
time to retire retirement home that's it
[Music]
bye
ever gonna lead towards
where I need to go
thank you
or is it gonna lead me to the mountain
I hope not you know what I'm gonna go
left here maybe that will help
bring me to where I need to go maybe
that's two paths
I'll show
about first
there's a t in here oh wait there's a
that's a dead end anyway and up there
there's another item
I wish the jumps were a bit faster
[Music]
nickname
you have a nickname what should we call
them
um
any good ideas
this thing is like I have no idea what
he's gonna look like later and if it's
still gonna fit whatever we call him now
Godzilla
Godzilla why
oh it will be it will be a Godzilla
Godzilla gorilla
[Music]
it's funny
yeah so I will actually call it
frogtilla
uh Hudson name
yeah there we go
ah maybe is that why it starts with FR
freaky box frog frog frog
[\h__\h]
ing it's kind of lame name
in my opinion
but okay
welcome to the team
did not expect
ing School
find someone like you here to join me
but why not which way should I go
foreign
[Music]
please
let me look at the map one more time
[Music]
seems fine to get out here is wrong
zero we'll only need four
there's a bunch of like different places
to go though last Seattle mountain path
we're not going there I'm about here
is that not where we came from
yeah
okay
not the mountain path
okay I'll go back
wait what
two metals
is that what that place is called yes
okay
foreign
[Music]
well that's kind of cool to have a third
type covered oh hello
the fruit type covered
[Music]
it's nice
but I have this one now
so I'll keep this one
[Music]
and I will not
not spoil myself ah you got the dark
Chrome
I will not spoil myself with uh how it
looks like later
what's effective too dark
learning about the way
that was not a fact it's still inside
okay
but you're also dark and flying aren't
you
[Music]
oh
you were telling me it's time not what's
effective against it
[Music]
we need to avoid these misunderstandings
you're supposed to tell me
what I should use not what it is oh [\h__\h]
but nasty now I'm so manipulated in my
mind that I chose metal clock anyway
ah
okay electric
so still a good Pokemon to switch to
also that Pokemon in the Back the
dinosaur looks so cool
but I think that's an older one I think
I've seen it before
charm
I don't think we need it but
Ashley lowers the target's attack set
is Tropius ah Jen free wow
senpai
Senpai Pokemon and there's Pokemon
oh
pretty burp
I'm so tired
wake up
[Music]
it was like the wave was lying it was so
lion like
the way it was lying down was so lying
light
look
I mean I guess it's just how a cat lies
down
give me those lion vibes
comedian but I'm
tired
I'm tired I'm tired I'm tired I'm tired
why am I surprised wake up wake up wake
up
can't wake up Wake Me Up Inside
[Music]
around it
cheese puffs
can't wait to go to the ice area later
not probably not today I don't know but
I love my syrians
it's so pretty
much
[Music]
love love
I need honey normal Tara Shard hmm
all right
I don't know if I fought enough but
please give me a reward damn it that's
what
[Music]
where was I fighting like what area was
I fighting those Trainers for in the
cave
do they not count to anything
so hey he's already the answer to the
gym what's going I guess
what that's a lot of shirts and I just
got one right
how do you find 50 shards of one type
there's a center in the cave
what
I didn't find that
I saw you going to the gym and came
running listen I'm really sorry I
couldn't battle you last time we ran
into each other
wait don't get me wrong I didn't chase
you down just to battle you then again I
guess I wouldn't mind a battle or
anything if you wanted to
what do you say uh did I heal
fighter yeah I actually feel like she's
fighting us less than trainers or like
Rivals and other Pokemon games but maybe
that's my imagination
we're meeting outside or what
half dead let's hope we don't need
ah oh we still get some time to fix
ourselves up
wait where did she go
did you go to like some kind of
battleground
where where is this
Battleground after the gym
that girl I swear
can I fit
ah alone I can
alright then I'll do the gym
[Music]
that's not what I wanted to do
okay Sal tell me all about it welcome to
the medully gym
let me register it was a challenge but
your name is Kiwa right
[Music]
great now in order to face Jim leader
Larry you'll first need to pass the gym
chest
hit here at the middle gym that means
ordering a special secret menu item
What
specifically a menu item at the treasure
Eatery A much loved restaurant here in
madali order correctly on your pass
okay
Rihanna challenges around town
attempting this gym test each Challenger
has been given a different clue that
will help them discover the secret dish
you'll be given a clue as well please
find and battle the other Challengers oh
the loser must tell the winner their
clue okay but I don't have to your goal
is to gather Clues and use them to
determine the secret dish then order it
from the waiter
hmm
okay
you're close to find out how the
regulars season their dishes
huh I suggest you start by hearing what
a regular at the treasure Eatery has to
say okay
got it
wait he didn't talk give me a hint right
so what I get my hint at the treasure
Eatery
[Music]
it's a big restaurant
Japanese restaurant
what do we have oh it really is Japanese
food oh my God
some rice balls or what
ah
this actually happens area
oh
with tatami
yeah
I mean I mean
[Music]
not bad it's nice some counter seats
even
munch munch munch
okay let me talk to you
are you a regular here yeah oh you're
supposed to do come here often the most
good gym because Challenger here's the
tip for you we're not squeeze of lemon
gives you any dish a refreshing kick
well is that not already it
lemon
is there more to it
Okay so
[Music]
hey
what if I guess wrong
because I kind of want to use grilled
fish because I feel like lemon works
perfectly on grilled fish
it doesn't seem that there's a an escape
now anyway
all right grilled fish
oh there's a serving then I have to
order as well a correct one
large
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
um flame first
lemon but lemon is correct lemon must be
correct
oh
the one's a regular dish
okay so we learned here that it has to
be lemon where are these peeps that I
have to ask for hints
um yeah I saw the chat already spoiled
it well I will just ignore it and get my
hints to Fairway
um
okay where where where are they didn't
they say they were somewhere else
I didn't see any more of them inside
so there must be some wait that one
looks suspicious
Taco Bell and Taco Bell
I don't know what to fight with
you're gonna fight with that verb
uh it's gonna go Sparks Rock
he fights with rock or I wait it doesn't
it doesn't actually it went he doesn't
want to fight with me
never mind
what about you
no
[Music]
how about him
what's up
no use Philippines
Santiago you got a good place but not
good enough to be the champ
dance bars
smash
I'm so tired wake up
just like me for real for real
[Music]
um
we just did like a surprise tattoo face
you have to tell you the clue yes sir
stop clapping and tell me
this is really close to the blue bird
Pokemon
uh-huh
that one over there what is that
something
ah well now it says something else I'm
listening talkabilly Taco Billy
so
uh-huh is there more
no think nothing
head empty medium
medium medium
medium size okay
yum
yum okay I get it again it took me a
moment though
three seconds
[Music]
trainer let me heal by the way
very slow
[Music]
I Choose You
guys
um I guess
I am on her side now
or I am her Pokemon or we're doing a
double fight against my own Pokemon or
Pizza
[Music]
come on when I'm standing right next to
the one I'm supposed to attack it will
attack me and stand oh no
thank you
oh it is super effective damn
what level is that
my tech fell
already poor that's not too high
uh free hits really yeah
I've never seen this happen before
it's like I punched it
Rock smashed so weak
yeah I'm pointing out very obviously
this this is where you need to hit right
here right here because my candy is
getting pretty old
and it doesn't see [\h__\h] right now
it needs glasses but insteads because
glasses are expensive I'm just helping
it out
find this you know
oh are you on the last one I didn't
listen to what they said oh
for a moment I thought I just clicked it
away but now I have to ask again right
so medium and lemon
the clue I was giving is to look for a
dark spot surrounded by stairs
[Music]
uh
well this smell
you were really close lady
but what am I supposed to see here
[Music]
is pigs was that one of the
click oh oh
there's some paint right in here it says
fireblast oh okay so lemon fire blast
medium
[Music]
now we will hopefully find out what dish
that's the most important I'm a fire
blast medium lemon five less medium
lemon fiber blast medium
uh oh yeah you guys said rice I guess
but I don't know that yet
I don't know
could not possibly know that
nice
so quick I need a better attack
even weak against this Pokemon even
though it's super effective what's going
on
Rock smashed the way to add them better
Rock attack
[Music]
gradient I don't know what that is I
switched to
Tacoma
[Music]
more for defense down okay
oh yeah I mean it's fighting it sounds
like a Rock
Stone attack and there we go this should
this should be good
and even with five
almost killed
have a look
I'm just digging my way for now
strong after oh yeah
yeah no nuts not November that wasn't
It's Over Now Ryan today was the last
day
see you soon
[Music]
don't be so sad
the odd one out at one of the ice cream
stands
one of the ice cream stands over here
this one
what
what made you think that I wanted to
talk to this squirrel I was looking at
the this lady
[Music]
the odd one out would be these two but
Teriyaki and salt
so there's another one
this one
oh it looks so good
which one could have been
which one could it possibly be
check your team
[Music]
yes I will
uh can we sort by it ah sorted by number
stored by I can't sort by type
I need a fighting fighting fighting
fighting like
like things I think
I mean don't really need fighting anyway
because Takoma has fighting we could
also just teach it something completely
different
[Music]
oh we can learn power gem
just in general like for the future
what do you think would work
he got impact
Kika impact
ah I wanted to I was considering you
know what I'll give it to the mice
I know it can't attack the next turn but
if we know that the attack will kill
then it doesn't matter
[Music]
or should I
not that one
[Music]
but no not for this fight no no I mean
for the future just in general
can you know
[Music]
Dragon Balls
I wonder if I should bother with
teaching my bubble Bubble Dragon
something now when it probably will
learn these things later
I don't even I didn't even look at what
it can do right now
foreign
physical moves
that's psychic
special special
right
the physical attack okay
[Music]
I'm so tired
oh I don't know these hams are always so
disappointing
okay that would be something fitting
don't teach that it's a
physical oh my God we can do dragons
dragon claw which is 80. oh that's
actually a better version of dragon tail
not good moves it's all right
style is better than bite those it
but wait I can't even learn that never
mind whatever
I'm supposed to order
[Music]
the grilled rice balls
and medium
with fire blast right
extra crispy fire blast Style
and a lemon garnish please
my blood style of fresh lemon on the
side
please
[Music]
oh the paint ings on the wall are nice
Rumble Rumble oh earthquake again
it is where did all the people go
what happened to the people
are they stuck underneath
I don't think that's where we save
um
[Music]
they were they were just I don't know
hopefully just teleported gently outside
okay so we can find in here now it's a
big space that's why this space was so
big huh the I was wondering that area
what they were eating
it looked you know the design looked
accurate but the space how it's like
such a big area is kind of weird not
normal
but now I understand
[Music]
I passed the gym test yay
all right let's go with uh takuma
do you want to Facebook exception on
every man himself generally the Larry
oh wait is it the businessman that's
sitting there over there
oh
Larry you're up no way
Pokemon because he because he's so
normal holy [\h__\h] his eyebrows are like
melted to his eyes
every time he blinks he must feel the
top of his eyebrows at the top of his
eyelashes
foreign
oh Larry looks like for 40 years he's
been working at a black company doing
over hours every freaking day and having
to go drinking with the superiors every
freaking [\h__\h] night
quotes
[Music]
foreign traditional
oh I understand I understand I
understand everything he's just an
overworked
Japanese dude
businessman
anyway wait I wasn't reading at all I'm
so sorry I was like well my mind was
fading anyway my boss will dock my pay
if I spend too much time today
let's get this battle over with I'm
surprised he's even allowed to eat
outside here
and doesn't have to eat in front of his
desk while working
okay
thank you for doing business with us
today I Larry will be at your service
[Music]
Larry Larry finally you're doing
something fun instead of working
[Music]
wow wow look look how motivated his like
Pro was down
so let's not go too hard
cute oh it's sleeping it's sleeping cute
wait does he also only have three
Pokemon
can I Justina correctly
the two
gym leaders
after
you know
who had four
all only had three
[Music]
why this is like we're so far into the
game they should have more by now no is
this normal
I didn't do it out of order look at the
levels
yes
well I'm staying in
you're gonna have to work after this
okay
that's so weird I want them to have more
Pokemon so we can fight more whoa that's
uh evoked isn't it
damn
don't do that much damage
I should crystallize
oh man too late
[Music]
what
you little [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
okay let's take them apart
ah we are personalized before
[Music]
sorry
foreign
it's going to matter because it will be
a bit stronger and I'll be more
protected for the next enemy
star Raptor
um I'm obviously staying this is still
better than getting pointed by my boss
yeah that's what I thought
so we should drag it out as long as
possible Right
oh is there a catch
that makes it so I can't use fighting
you're pretty good I might have ended up
losing this
come on Larry step it up a notch
oh come on
come on up now because hungry customers
waiting give him something to cheer for
you here
oh she's cute
oh what oh
the people who were stuck underneath
were able to escape for underground and
are finally here to cheer for us now
what you got Larry and you two kids
well you heard the good folks I suppose
I can put on a bit more of a show
why doesn't wait so long after I clicked
oh Larry go Larry it's just a normal
dude I actually think that's so sweet
because all the
um gym leaders that usually
funky people but he's just a normal dude
who's trying to balance
like his normal job with this [\h__\h]
because he doesn't make enough money
from either this doesn't seem very super
effective it is
it's gonna kill me now
I think it's time to show you that the
real life isn't all just being true to
yourself
[Music]
oh wait wait what I thought you guys
said you can't die if you're
crystallized
does it just not count if on yourself
but only on your enemies
yeah
only Wild Ones what the hell
not there not there what am I supposed
to use now
um
what would you recommend Sparks yeah
this will handle it
[Music]
let's sing in the song
oh this time I actually got an animation
for that I didn't look at that a lot of
times like animation I mean the camera
the camera kind of followed it
nicely
[Music]
I guess I gotta go back to work today
and looks like I'll be working for like
18 hours Non-Stop
why couldn't this have gone on for a bit
longer
oh man someone please
get me out of this job
it really looks like a frog koala
[Laughter]
frogzilla evolving
what what is it gonna look like please
don't disappoint
Ed
[\h__\h]
not bad not so bad kind of cute
the mouth is a bit weird but the body
shape is cute it's got the ice stuff
everywhere
at the backs
where's the air around it protecting its
face with an ice mask oh now that you
said it does look like a mask
to protect them from the pandemic
um
oh there will be one more
nice when when is the next evolution
54.
[Music]
that's quite a long while to go
you rather strong aren't you enough to
bring out my poker face even
[Music]
I lost so that means I have to give you
a badge but
can I also give you my job
that battle made me a bit hungry
character join me for a meal oh yeah
let's go I guess we just ate but why not
step around
yummy
yay rice balls rice balls rice balls
onigiri
having a mother mobile
having five Gym badges in hand makes it
easier to catch Pokemon Alpha up to
level 45. they'll actually even listen
to you
unlock my boss you'll never listen to me
this is for you though hopefully a child
like you has no need to put it on his
name
[Music]
oh maybe something for the mouse hold I
don't know if but yeah
it's normal so
[Music]
don't worry about the pill I do earn the
salary after all unlucky but still
you're making so much money than I do by
battling people outside having fun while
I work 20 [\h__\h] hours today
[Music]
destroying my body and my life
for what for what
um we have to free him we have to hire
him
you have to steal him
ah okay so
oh
another gym leader defeat that well done
I think I informed me that there was an
unusual trainer worth keeping an eye on
seems she meant you I'd guess this much
I had the pleasure of observing your
last match I was impressed by the
Fantastic skill you showed if you
managed to keep your momentum and
Achieve Champion rank I will be very
interested in inviting you to the
Pokemon League and
hey hey hey come on
my team all picked up let's go let's go
let's go kill him I'm gonna fight oh
they're fine I saw you battle on the gym
leader you just keep getting better
oh good to see you again Champion the
Mona it has certainly been a while
wait left
[Music]
oh my God
uh is she that important
wait did I forget to give you the full
explanation everyone calls Mrs gaydala
Primerica because she's just that she's
the real number one even higher than us
regular champions she's a top Champion
I joined it I I do indeed hold that
claim alongside my role as a chairwoman
of the Pokemon League that is
[Music]
I thought you were too busy to spend
your time checking in on gyms
I'm not here to inspect the gym I've
come to scout some rather promising
young talents
[Music]
you're being scouted for whole life damn
you're really special okay Wawa
stealing her from me
I suppose I'll have to get in line
because she would sound really good if
crony voice acts with her that's right
monkey Mama time for a battle
[Music]
one moment please
I would very much like to observe this
match if that is all right I thought so
sure I would totally be fine with that
not embarrassing at all because I know
I'm gonna lose um yeah let's do it all
right please go easy on me so that it's
not too too shameful
thank you kindly I'm already excited to
see you to face up
[Music]
let's be on our way then
yes
I'm doing sound effects now
my throat is still shite
oh well
you remember how that works right once
you get bags from all the gyms you get
to throw down against the strongest
Pokemon trainers around
yes you must face the Pokemon League
it is located to the northwest of
messagosa
the Pokemon League is where the trainers
are born as Champions the greatest honor
that they might dream of
collecting eight gym badges sets you up
to take the champion assessment if you
can face the challenge of the final
accident next to mind examiner and win
you'll become a champion
just imagine how that would feel try
getting into that champion mindset
Now set your sights on reaching that big
important stage and let's battle
excuse me one moment what now
I believe give I was Pokemon made oh
hard to
hit all right
I was thinking actually the same
sorry I got a little caught up in my
battle hunger
well you should be all in great shape
now thanks a lot Primera
okay time to put our game faces back on
let's have another fruitful battle
shoot vegetarian or what
her hair
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
was watching but no need to get worked
up just stay cool
yeah yeah no problem uh which one do you
want
served
a goal of this
[Music]
quick attack that comes before digging
oh no I didn't do late night steam deck
gaming I didn't
at all
actually recently I fell asleep so fast
that's actually a blessing
while cuddling with the ketocatos
well critical hit right on the counts
locks on your side for sure
[Music]
okay whatever you're saying yeah yeah
yes Burger King Oreo shake please wait
what's coming next [\h__\h]
Gumi
uh very poison or something like that
dragon
[Music]
oh
well I'll do the same thing again
[Music]
oh that means
come on
what do we use against taco man
what should I use again
[Music]
okay
so I guess we stay
[Music]
it's not even involved yet she doesn't
know that she has to walk
maybe somebody should tell her
but I do wonder if I missed maybe some
pretty cool pretty good attacks
that it would have learned before
evolving and it won't learn because I
evolved it it's not a thing
[Music]
thank you
now you'll make me make me eat that God
damn it
but I still have some food for me
yesterday I have to eat that
another day another day
uh oh they don't do that as much anymore
it used to be a thing
[Music]
okay
um
that's the the grass cat right
foreign
[Music]
oh
it looks cool
I like it
the dark Parts make it look really
something and elegant and
[Music]
fierce
told me I like it
whoa
it has quite the attitude
okay while I used yawn
[Music]
um
I mean I know people complain about it
standing up
but I can't really imagine this design
when it's on its four legs to be honest
why did you survive that what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
flame Pro is actually stronger what the
hell
but this one boosts my special attack
[Music]
oh
that attack by the way is its special
attack right its own special it looks
cool
but mine's cooler
[Music]
I guess it's because
we got people
[Music]
yeah I understand
but with with my starter it's the
opposite it was first only on two legs
and then bye
bye
um
evolving it it ended up on four legs the
other way around
people are gonna start playing more and
more attention to you I just know it
deep illusion I mean that's actually if
you if you consider Humanity
then you must actually praise the cat
for standing up
and be very concerned about my crocodile
who was standing on two legs first and
then forgot how to do that and went on
four legs
you know
Superior if you're on two legs that was
a splendid match I enjoyed watching it
very much
now even La Primera things you want to
watch you've got so much potential the
way you're going I better watch my back
you know since the first time we met
I've been weirdly sure of one thing
you're gonna become a champion no doubt
about it kiwawa the rest of these shoes
you can take them 100 no problem
I agree in fact you should take this
consider it an investment in your future
[Music]
um
Tara blessed
not me it's a normal normal attack if
they used to have slices unleashes
energy of its Terror type
just move and flicks damage using the
attack or special yeah
is it like
um
that seems familiar but it says it just
has whatever type
your crystallization is
that's very
uh flexible I like it
but wait if you can you not use it when
it's her uh when you're not
terrestrialized
[Music]
and then it's just normal type okay
the Pokemon uses that move was the last
the moves type will change the terror
type of the Pokemon
one day okay Mama you and me are gonna
have the greatest battle in the world I
know it I'm gonna go train up even more
than I already have been
good luck
she shows you such support and
friendship or perhaps
[Music]
okay perhaps she hopes you truly might
rival her
I thought she was gonna say love
no I think it's no mere hope she seems
to have complete faith that you will
catch up to her
at any rate allow me to return you to
the gym where I found you oh thank you
for babying me
Mommy
all right
now
[Music]
is it time for the Titan next or do I I
probably need to grind a little bit
before that though but order wise
the next thing to do would be to tighten
this one
okay
I'll be fine you think so
what level will never lose the Titan
honestly so far there were like no match
actually embarrassing 45
40 45 then okay A little bit of grinding
would be nice but no problem we should
be able to find some trainers that we
haven't thought yet and actually I'm
kind of close
I made like a oh
circled the the crater
well so I'll walk by foot maybe we find
some more trainers but let me Mark it
though
[Music]
grind some chancy isn't that what we did
in Arceus Arceus
ah ah good stretch good kitty cat cute
oh I'm Healed even okay
all right
[Music]
and bye bye
goodbye
[Music]
I want to sing some music songs
oh
evolution
[Music]
yeah I don't think we've been in this
area before anyway so I'm sure I'm sure
we will meet some trainers
no no we watched it like a year ago so
I was gonna watch it again oh wait I'm
already level 41. level 41.
[Music]
I love the one standing like it's a tree
you can do it you can be a train I
believe
who can my
can I think but maybe
um ice versus plants should be good
right
good guess me
I was also planned right
nice
[Music]
that's not planned it wants to be
planned but I mean the trees
oh that one was that no no
I'm sorry to hurt you
at least you tried oh what's that
another
seasonal form what
good
looks kind of weird
but uh it's cool that even the
evolutions have a lot of different forms
I'm so tired guys why am I so tired is
the team making me tired it didn't make
me tired yesterday
[Music]
oh man I'm so sorry I'm sorry
what did you do who did you find I
didn't tell you to find the danger boy
[Music]
whoa
the evolution of those tiny bubble
bubbles
did you eat something yeah I had
breakfast and I also had lunch before I
was eating a berry
oh nice good job
we also had a sandwich before
on fire
anyway I'm excited for the calendar to
start
I hope that we get a lot of sweet lovely
messages
from the girls
oh wait
yeah
also when I asked them to make some
groupings
a bunch of them were really motivated
and we're like oh yeah let's do this
group let's do this group let's do this
for you
and then I realized wait I don't really
have a group
it's nice that they are very eager I
hope they
make some cute videos
no group Pokemon
there's there's chat guys there's snot
was there something else
no no
foreign
[Music]
but I'm thinking more of like two plus
three like one like anything after three
people is a group two people is just a
pairing so
[Music]
but pairings are good too we'll have
some pairings
some groups some solos
anything works
my battle skills five stars thank you
I'm so tired
[\h__\h]
I actually have an energy drink in my
fridge but I don't think that's very
good for my throat right [\h__\h]
Ed up
um Persian that's your name I didn't
know that
any of this one
[Music]
no need to rush the game of course
there's a need to rush the game motion
you should know that
[Music]
in that few steps okay
how about that's fine
oh my poor puppies
dude I like the color of my dragon
[Music]
February
what
what do you guys know that and I don't
know that
[Laughter]
who's who said that
mama said it
oh I just assumed
let's
it's not really still I have to check on
that
you guys know too much
you're all knowing are you God
call me someone
[Music]
thank you
do you guys ever watch this is really
random but do you guys ever watch your
like winter coats or so
it's up until now
honestly in my life
I didn't use the same coat so
been like more than like two or three
years in a row
uh so it was kind of fine without
washing it
but now I have a lot of coats and a
couple of them I kind of want to like
wash but I know you're not like if you
wash it in your yourself you kind of
have a high chance of messing it up
so I'm thinking I should probably bring
it to a cleaner right
I don't want to buy a new coat this year
because I have so many and
it's kind of a waste when you have like
10 different quotes
okay not 10 but I'm oh
[Music]
come on wait a second wait a second
don't run
dry cleaner but pour me on his English
name
how to not okay oh you
[Music]
I spine is bad for water right
oh okay we're fine we're fine we're more
fun wanna resist size
[Music]
it's not effective oh
I'm scared though to hurt it so I'll
stay with dragons
[Music]
I'm so tired
oh it's healing itself oh
nice veil of water is that like its
ability
I'm Gonna Catch You
yeah cause right now I mean I have the
dolphin
but evolving a dolphin seems to be a bit
annoying so for
um for now
we could use
this one
and then until we see
um an evolution of the dolphin and the
Wild
we can
get that one but for now this one
oh that's not it's just a okay yeah
[Music]
foreign
well
well well
[Music]
I've been using a couple of Ultra Balls
on you why do you refuse to join me
um
[Music]
thank you
net volume
yeah we could use the net balm
is that so much better than the Oakland
Mall
oh yes
finally
finally finally finally
[Music]
and the next Titan
is a ground type then right
but it's not like water is effective
against it is it
is it is it
it is oh
well done you look like smoothie foreign
[Music]
but it's a boy
like no it says it's a girl because it's
smoothie all right
then I replace uh Connie
yeah
we're switching up the team quite a lot
let me update it
oh
guys okay
goodbye crab I love you though
you might come back because I love crabs
and vaporation
yes oh the shiny of that is also pink
[Music]
and like like Sparks
I'm just gonna
a Year's movie
um
movie Welcome to the tea
[Music]
and then
we have a
what's the frogzilla called again
in reality
free free free free free something
[Music]
artifacts that yeah free something was
before artsy facts thank you
[Music]
about what
also so blue
okay
and your name
uh where is it
what
[\h__\h] I can't find them
[Music]
what
oh that's so weird okay uh
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
oh wait wrong oh [\h__\h]
out there on the top
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
oh oh it's fainted well that explains a
lot
I know Pokemon now
come on apparently has the same name in
Japanese that's that's not very common
but they have the same name
[Music]
camouflaging
Jolteon
[Music]
the electric one right
if anything it would remind me of it
more of smoothies
probably
history
[Music]
that's so cool
that was not little
[Music]
how come you get that item
was it was
[Music]
it wasn't how the [\h__\h] was I supposed to
know that
disguise
wait do you ever find an actual normal
video somewhere
they're always disguised
oh that's so hard to find to them
[Music]
if you find a shiny little it won't be
shining over what the [\h__\h] well that's
why why
ah if you read the name then it says
dinner okay I never do that okay well
that's at least a little bit helpful
but if you have a shiny Ditto and it
transforms into a Pokemon does it always
transform into the shiny version of it
that would be amazing
then you have all shinies at your
disposal
oh it doesn't yes no no
oh wow
what I guess it's because it transforms
into what you see
and that Pokemon is not a shiny if it's
a shiny doesn't then it transforms into
the shiny huh
okay okay you are ghosts
um
[Music]
of course is effective against ghosts
but besides that I don't remember
do I still have a ghost sometimes yes I
do
ice oh
oh I didn't realize
I spent dark
I fell for the taunt well what do I have
to attack well no problem
[Music]
oh
but like I would talk about dinner
is also not what it looks like
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
about it I'll just use it again
[Music]
does the same with the Doodles what is
the difference
where's the difference in Zoro and
doodle in terms of their skill like what
they can do it's just the same
they ran ahead and this script is not
scripted
it copies the last Pokemon in the party
oh
ah because she has three flim necks
until you start a fight with them
only a visual illusion
Just an Illusion Peter transforms into
the enemy also Dido actually also knows
the moves of that Pokemon then but
zodowa only has her own moves but still
is what she is okay okay
Coolio
you pulled us all lady
respect
that's so funny
oh
level up hyper boys
that's the normal move right
I don't think I want a normal move for
from this Pokemon
[Music]
but it does use special attack
power 90.
could get rid of snarl
a is pretty weak in comparison
all right
foreign
yeah
okay okay
but honestly we have normal coverage
already so
you saw right for my Illusions no I
didn't you showed it to me I didn't
really know but I mean if you want to
give me the credit
I don't think it's fair but thank you
it's very entertaining
oh
ah it's area yeah we've kind of been
here before
am I still going the right way though
so
[Music]
let's see where I missed some trainers I
did all of them in here I think
Timber
what if I go
what if I jump down here
is that even the same direction
whatever I'm doing it
but I also think I've been down here
before by accident
bye-bye
[Music]
I found an opponent
let me think I don't have my phone with
my notes Here well let me think if I
have any other
tensions to offer
do you guys know anything I should be
tangenting about
[Music]
my lack of Chinese I'm going fishing I
don't know
um
[Music]
okay uh what
ah we already talked about the Super
Mario trailer
yeah uh I think I missed something about
this about the road trip I remember the
other day but then I forgot again
so we just have to wait until I remember
again also I still have some notes on my
phone but other the phone was not with
me now
Japan plan yeah I'm thinking
you know I booked a hotel already
but I can still cancel it and I'm
not sure if I should even keep it
because
it's kind of expensive the one that I
picked because I mean it's a whole one
but I kind of needed to be that because
I think the soundproofing will be at
least decent but besides that I'm
wondering
if I should maybe also
[Music]
for 902
but I can't really
hope that yet because I don't have it
planned out yet
but I do think I might want to go on a
little trip but I'm not sure should I I
don't know
because if I go to Osaka I have
at least one really really good friends
there
[Music]
I are I'm a friend
my school friend
if I could say hi to her
and whoa whoa look last time when I went
to Kansai area that's where Kyoto and
Osaka and so on is
I went on a little little Spa to work
with her
I think I invited her
I'm thinking maybe we can do that again
because it will be cold Seasons or maybe
on Onsen
kind of place would be nice
but I'm not sure about it yet I have to
like sit down and
plan everything out more properly but
like I don't I don't want to have a
booking for like a month in Tokyo
and then overlap it with like two or
three nights somewhere else because then
I'll be paying double and I want to
avoid that
so I'm not sure about my accommodation
situation right now
uh
but I'm getting there
look member's not your sleepover some of
them maybe but I'm definitely not gonna
rely on it the whole time
because yeah
even even if I say okay this day I'll
sleep over at Madison park's place so I
don't book a hotel for that night then
uh
it kind of sucks because if I don't book
a hotel for the night I have to bring
first of all I have to bring all my
luggage
away from that hotel and bring it to
Martin Center and I'll probably bring a
lot of luggage for a whole month
and then the other problem is what if
she moves it what if she says oh can we
move it to another day and then
I have to book another hotel for just
one night and currently Tokyo Hotel
situation is pretty crowded so then I
probably wouldn't even be able to get
the same Hotel so I'll have to switch
hotels just for one night and all that
kind of sucks
so yeah
not ideal
why not just Bank of Cali no that again
I didn't need some privacy she truly
wants some privacy
and
I don't know how many rooms her place
has but
no
I want my own place I'm sure she doesn't
really want and she would maybe even say
yes out of kindness who knows
but a whole month no
a week maybe oh this one goes to
terrestrialization type
interesting
but I did not really want to bump into
you
[Music]
well I will try to catch it
yeah speaking of Minecraft tomorrow
playing Minecraft with fauna we're gonna
um
we're gonna prepare I think for the
weather
I'm not gonna try for a weekend see if
it works what if it doesn't work it
obviously will not work I don't want to
do it anyway and if even if I try to do
it and then oh [\h__\h] I need a hotel after
all then every [\h__\h] decent hotel will
be sold out reserved full and I can't
find anything so it's not a very smart
idea no
it's okay
I don't want to do that anyway
[Music]
what is even what do you even have to
prepare for the weather I didn't look
into it you know originally
I was always thinking I'll do the
weather someday and then I'll look up
what to do and you guys will help me and
so on but
now you know me and fauna are doing it
and she seems to already have a big idea
of how it will go down so
I'm kind of like leaving this to her
just schools you have the gear already
preschool systems where that doesn't
really sound like
we need a whole stream for our stream or
so for it
that sounds like it's done in
20 minutes
skulls
wait how do you get gold
[Music]
and I will do everything don't worry
well actually I mean
that's nice and all but I don't really
want her to do everything then I'll be
useless why would I be there then
[Music]
it's tougher than it sounds
right pretty low okay I'm gonna post
only something
2.5 drop it okay okay
so at least that will take up
a little bit of time
I was here before right
okay
how's the level looking
these two are pretty low
uh
I wanna kind of level them but like I'm
very unsure what Pokemon to
game four excuse me oh yeah you speak
candy I could just give them something
speaking no
huh
[Music]
power rates for candy
is that over there camera right looks
kind of far away is it on the hill or
under
maybe on
push up
all the family
you're the kind of struggler so you want
to have a good location yeah I mean we
could have done like a Cheesy easy
version version on the ground but
we kind of decided to go for the less
easy version
so
hey hey
bug isn't ice good for bug
think so
no
[\h__\h]
oh
whatever
hopefully it will be fine anyway
[Music]
foreign
oh it's so weak
I guess I'll catch it
I don't think I caught it before
[Music]
nice at least here I can use my normal
Pokeballs because
will be a guaranteed catch
[Music]
yeah I caught Godzilla yes yeah I found
the baby version randomly and I was like
well you know what why not
why not actually
since you guys said it's really
strong and rare
let's see how far we get with a couple
of
uh exp stuff where are they
[Music]
here
I have a lot of tiny ones
[Laughter]
you can have 12.
[Music]
oh okay 40. I thought that would do a
bit more
okay and then you
[Laughter]
nine
okay okay
maybe I'll Farm some exp candies off
screen
but I think normally like our level is
pretty decent so
not such a big need
to forcefully catch up right
okay 40 is okay right one is fine I
think
Jim is level 41.
the next gym
muddy water
1985 accuracy kind of low
[Music]
attack 93. ah she's a special special
attacker right and that is so special
should I get it
ghost gym around 41 to 42.
hmm
[Music]
let's just teach yourself true I do have
surf
um
I want to see
ah oopsie wrong
surf in comparison to the other attacks
chilling water
power 15.
oh
I see wind no
um
or we could even teach her rain dance
to make her water text even stronger
I mean it's not a bad thing to teach in
my opinion
right but will I actually use it
hmm
[Music]
wait surf
foreign
1900.
such a classic move and it's like even
even besides you know back in the day
what did what did I just do
you remember besides back in the day
when you needed it to go swimming
there we go
you almost had statues it's still very
very useful
hmm
an actual strong attack
yeah
solid move
okay you guys say go to the ghost Arena
now but I'm so close to Titan where is
the ghost Arena
which which one is the ghost Arena
that looks like ice to me that I don't
know
foreign
[Music]
yeah I probably would be able
he'll go there
tab one is the ghost okay
[Music]
then we'll go there right after and then
we'll have two gyms One Titan
down already maybe one
maybe one more thing
uh we can do maybe
I don't die
[Music]
yeah
good opponent
[Music]
you know what will surely wake me up and
and move my approaches Jack
I don't think there's any argument
against that
maybe maybe maybe maybe I just need more
sugar
I'm not now
um
[Music]
oh so good
um
yeah baby
that's your good stuff does that work
well I'm so surprised
how about that oh
nice
oh
the burp so big
on
[Music]
okay try I guess
Frank Kinder chocolate was the best
decision I made
Kinder chocolate and everything from
kinder is just
a gift from heaven
the bug is a really good fire bug
maybe that's a bug then yeah maybe we'll
pick it up isn't it
it's good that's the Titan huh isn't it
doing um
like I saw her thumbnails and it seems
like she's doing a bug team only
which is cute because he know bugs
she likes to collect bugs she's so cute
because that seems to be another dial
now oh bicycle
[Applause]
yeah she's she's making a bug
team
which I really respect because bugs
tends to be weaker oil come back come
back
no come back
thank you for listening to me let's
fight this dude and then we fight the
Titan
bugs are super powerful now yeah pretty
decent notice oh
I deserved
21.
yeah the batteries from Energy's bag
speaking of bags
um
I have a bunch of
Hollow back submissions
already ready to go
[Music]
I actually started collecting
some submissions a while ago
I wasn't sure when to do a stream
I'm about it but
um
[Music]
hmm I want to do one before Christmas
are you getting any sneaky none of
exercise wow wow I don't know oh baby
I haven't like organized one yet
so far it's only Hollow backs but
you never know
you can't be sure now can you
all right what what
um I guess we fight with this movie
right because you guys said water is
pretty noise here
[Music]
so cute
that's a lot okay perfect we're just
attack it or what
what I wanted you to do
it would just like calmly walk up to it
and say hi
wow
it looks really cool big elephant
[Music]
hello this is Professor Sada great test
because the Pokemon that came from the
Greek creator of paldea I ask that you
do whatever is needed to subdue it for
me with all due caution of course
oh from the crater
how do you know that it came from there
what's up
get on the surfboard
who's so strong I mean look at that big
boy
holy [\h__\h]
I didn't see the damage didn't do any
damage
we almost had one hit
I'm relieved where'd it go
where'd it go let me see it on the map
[Music]
oh I guess now it's over there
which is where
[Music]
always have to
set as destination because even if wait
can oh there it is
I wish that the mini map also wouldn't
move
[Music]
oh there's a trainer
uh you good over there
Escape
you cannot Escape
the munchies
looks like you found yourself a Titan
well that is really Titanic holy [\h__\h]
like unlike the the boat this is this is
not a boat is it uh it's a Pokemon right
it must be trying to get pumped with
that little snack
time to show that thing what you and me
kaduki Wawa
wow
I like elephants
oh I'm attacking him
oh
I didn't I should have healed before
before I guess we're trying to kill my
partner
well I still have ice
that's okay
[Laughter]
I would have liked to see how much
damage surf would have done on his
Pokemon though
um when I terrestrialize it gets the
dragon type though right not the ice
type
[Music]
so I'm not really worth it
the [\h__\h] is that don't you have any
Pokemon that's like that has something
effective against him
I might have to revive
my smoothie cat
because uh
uh frogzilla doesn't seem very defensive
feel that
uh
but that's only Reviving I didn't want
to use the master off because I only
have one
[Music]
attacked the other one
oh she's not in the team anymore
didn't realize oh
there she was
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry for not considering you I was
paracelized and crash that [\h__\h]
[Music]
let's just do some good damage hopefully
[Applause]
PPP
whoa
all is good all is well
[Music]
a nice pose
I don't wonder like she used to be a
she's supposed to be a Cleopatra
reference right but what does that have
to do with Spain
beat up beat them up beat them up beat
them up
oh a dark move
the music gets all party Pokemon to
attack the target the more party Pokemon
the greater the number of attacks oh man
it's never one of those
with your current party members beat up
would do a maximum of
up to 76 damage 76
[Music]
um
that's not
it's like super good
just normal right
that's going little buddy what even was
that thing go
I kind of feel like maybe I've seen it
before somewhere
I meant to reference I know I but yeah I
would have been
more fitting
if the bird was I don't know
everything more
something Spanish or they kept it
for future region that's
supposed to be like Egypt I don't know
if they ever gonna do that
anyway I bet if we head inside it will
be the exact same cave that we've seen
before with the exact same sparkly
flower that we've seen before and we'll
make exact almost the same sandwich that
I've seen before
just this time it's not spicy and it's
not salty what could it be sweet
hmm
come on come on wherever you are oh
that's a Pokeball
wait are we ignoring the Pokemon
did you guys say that was a Pokeball in
the middle
what
a bug what oh oh I was thinking you mean
like an actual bug not a bug
hey
[Music]
look at that one like a wild bug here
uh sour okay I guess maybe sweet is last
I don't think we had sweet yet
this shape this shade it looks exactly
the same as the others let's go but it
tastes different trust me
um sour Urban minced you guys chock full
of nutrients it is great for boosting
over World Health says here it works
wonders whether you tried physically or
mentally perks you right up
I need that I'm tired physically like my
my eyes are fading away
oh you've gotten in every one of those
cutscenes yeah I think I got it for the
first time
[Music]
uh my face is so neutral
she's also not looking at the camera nor
at the sandwich what is she looking at
hmm okay can we retake this picture you
didn't do a good job at posing and
smiling
she does not care
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah yeah
take give
[Music]
me this is the one I really care about
What's it gonna do now
what's he gonna do now oh the ball is
still there
[Music]
chunk
s
[Music]
would you look at that it seems like
someone's got a proper appetite now
[Music]
[Applause]
careful when you Chomp that away from me
[Music]
oh
Glide
I thought we would maybe be able to
climb first
seems like that fellow is also slowly
regaining its original strength so it
doesn't look like it's anywhere close to
her turn into his battle form
gosh
seems helpful enough physically maybe
it's got some kind of mental block
that's preventing it from returning to
its true form no it's just the plot I
need it as a bicycle until the end of
the game
that's it that's all there is to it
[Music]
I've read about it in books before
mental scar like a psychological trauma
you know I think that's what you call it
has it been bullied by the other bikes
because it's all about bullying
maybe it had a terrifying experience in
battle where is the sad music cue the
sad music
so now it's scared to battle at all well
don't worry make sure both that brute
and my boss death will make a full
recovery eventually how do you feel with
bubble stuff how is it working
[Music]
well
oh
no pressure no like it's fair to expect
every kind of urban mystical to have
some huge effect right it's not like the
effect has to be immediate either oh
[Music]
so nothing really obvious this time
okay well why not I'm gonna make sure
you write this rain we've got one more
up to go and I bet it's the best of them
all
it's just gonna be well it will be it
will be don't worry
Michael's therapist
I need more tea need more hot scorching
tea
no more water
[Music]
hang in there yes please hang in there
we can't lose steam until we're done
let's keep our momentum here we go oh he
should have voiced Mario
[Music]
why is it
why is it right where he would sit
huh
he dropped it when he was sitting down
he dropped the ball when he lay later
like an egg
hello piwawa this is Sada
I decided that code item has regained
more of its original Power after it has
jumped into the air you should try to
press the B button again it should Glide
now
haha is that the flying in the game will
not actually be able to fly properly
you must continue helping kodai don't to
recover
hmm
let's look at the pokeballs wait I can't
cut I can't pick them up I can't go
inside
but the Pokeballs
no
[Music]
no that's not good for me the RPG player
I saw pokeballs I need to pick them up
and you're keeping them away from me
just kidding I know it was a bug and I
know you can't go inside
okay
go Serena but that was kind of fast
everything's happening so fast guys
oh wait let's try
um
that doesn't really help me unless I'm
on a really really really really really
really high spot and that really mostly
only will happen when I'm able to climb
up the mountains
so
on it
yeah no yeah
[Music]
oh this one can fly oh maybe it's a
different one oh no I don't know
you probably fly better than my bike
does now
[Music]
effective here now doesn't mean against
its normal form or against flying type
that it is now
okay okay
well then
I'll Take You Down
for those sweet sweet EXP
elled
you little [\h__\h]
I attacked after huh
I will not let this movie die now
playing Pokemon
[Music]
they die you know
not all there is quiz
um
oh yeah I need to Mark a new goal on the
map
and it will be so far
that one comes before that one
how do we
do we walk through the city and just
ignore the gym and then go there next or
what
what what is that the best path where
where is the path
hmm
among the very greatest she's a
legendary rapper who has performed
around the world and her frailing live
shows rattle the bones of devilish beats
and stuff
I started because I want to renounce
them but I was forced to retire from the
sport due to a previous injury his
formerly very passion now remains look
locked away
behind a beneath but it doesn't say like
how strong they are
but you guys say ghost first
ice cream last
and they should have written this is the
strongest
recommended as last
but okay uh you know what I'll actually
fly this time because we have a Pokemon
Center
close by or as close As It Gets
I think this one right
that's quite easy since we do almost
everything true yeah I says ice has a
lot of weaknesses huh
do I still disappoint you
once right now where are the owners all
right maybe now we'll find them I think
uh this path
because and we have to go to the
mountain that's like
here right yeah I thought I picked up
the game Eagles Before He'll
I need healing Shiny Stone dusk stone
they respond what
to find them here
[Music]
what
still so hot
I didn't know they respawned
[Music]
um
whoa layers
guys
you know how much I love layers
what kind of Pokemon do you have to
offer
foreign
[Music]
okay that's a really big moment for me
really big moment
what's up
you know like I don't understand the
logic that plant is effective against
water because plant needs water to live
anyway
and water doesn't need plants so I don't
understand
critical and four times effective and
this okay it's hit several times
because otherwise I would have cried
okay okay
but not all of it if you if you water
plants too much you can instantly easily
not insulin but you can easily kill it
the plant you can drown it and then that
will not be good for the plant either
so
it should be it should be
um neutral because it can both help the
plant and it can also destroy the plant
uh she just wants me to see the two
forms of that Pokemon huh
thank you for showing me
thank you thank you thank you
speaking from experience perhaps oh
it still works
[Music]
I'm rewriting time matches I would like
to do that
actually it's um
could even be a stream idea
rewriting type matchup by kiwawa Logic
oh
but if Q awwa have this
news program that I mentioned before
what should it be called just kfp news
is simple but maybe it's too simple
maybe too boring
what do you think
piano News Network
k n n is that taken by anything because
you know things are free letters
could also be like political parties and
we obviously don't wanna you know
name that after some
it could even be a Korean News Network
oh
Medici or whatever
[Music]
um
sandal with them for next cheap lava in
the morning
um let's do so much
can you press oh I like that
I actually like that one thanks news
[Music]
I like half press but I guess I would be
more feeling if it was uh
written form
ah
I kind of
expected to be like ever against a
fourth wall
or
[Music]
yeah
an invisible wall or be respawned once I
jump I didn't know this would lead here
what the [\h__\h]
am I going the right way
where am I you did that too
I'm done God damn it
okay
I just noticed
the kiwawa report
um
[Music]
cave broadcast podcast
it's not a podcast
[Music]
Front Page News ah camping news
some good ideas
[Music]
off the tongue quite a while that's true
maybe I'll ask you guys again in a
community post or so so that I can look
at everything calmly
scroll through it
calmly
but actually
and um
background for it it's already finished
I could already start
but I don't feel quite ready
I'm not sure where to start when to
start
yeah
but you guys you know I think kuyori
Senpai does it that way too you guys
will have to help me we're gonna make a
hashtag
um because I especially also because of
time zones I'm obviously not gonna be
able to
uh know what's going on with all the
girls at all times so we're gonna have a
hashtag where you guys tell me and for
example
[Music]
I'm gonna do a handstand when you tell
me what's up what's up you guys and
other fandoms hopefully
other girls fans can tell me hey my Oshi
did this and that and that's why it
feels worthy oh she
[Music]
um
I don't know help
[Music]
find it
one punch bear
here we need you haven't used it in a
while because I need to level the other
girls
sorry
it's only four and girls yeah I wanted
to be only for young girls to be honest
because we already have news on the
Japanese side and only can cover ideas
um the reason why I'm doing this anyway
even though I was worried about all
these programs I talked to her and she
told me and I also kind of saw I guess
that it's supposed to be more like a
radio she plays songs in between and I
think that's a really cool cute idea
yeah actually
it doesn't seem to be so news focused
and yeah I want to have like you know
like scoops
huh close combat oh Scoops like oh
oh
did this in her stream oh my God
unbelievable
when will she stop
should I get rid of arm Frost
pretty
strong
[Music]
damn under 20.
then we can give it a different item
later on besides loaded dice you won't
need it anymore
only 550 oh yeah
[Music]
but let me go let me go
oh
I saw something
when I was walking up to her
what was that ah that thing
did I come out of that
hole
this is so confusing no I came
around what was that electric
don't look at this
[Music]
I did I did come out
all right
and we gotta go up up
ground oh okay it looked yellow to me
well makes more sense as a ground move
but these trainers come for that uh
poker Center dude that we talked to
and I gotta go back
a little more respect please pull up hey
yo you're not turning the mountain of
the respect and deserves
is it really a mountain when it's Hollow
I mean look at the right side
if you fill it up then I'll respect it
with actual stone because right now it's
paper fins everyone is paper finish that
doesn't really seem like a real mountain
girl
sorry I'm sorry you probably didn't even
know it you walked in here and thought
it was a real mountain well it's not
but someone had to tell you the truth
am I not
[Music]
yet she was right
yes she was right
[Music]
she wobble back that was what it should
be called program
[Music]
you can't see fact everything is effect
everything is 100 true it's a fact
[Music]
okay
endurance News
why why do we need an endurance for
those news
they won't be so long anyway I think
maybe each uh episode will be 20 to 30
minutes depending on how much there is
to
to tell to talk about
I can't believe
imagine right now anyway
I wonder it will definitely not be a
bull hour
left or right
I'm going left because I'm I'm Lefty
yo this girl is being pregnant
I will help you all feel
ings
only 30 minutes the fryer I kind of like
that
foreign
[Music]
damn
fairy type oh damn I kind of was hoping
for
[Music]
um
fine though
I'll burn it down nonetheless
where is my Pokemon
wow I saw the bird flying oh that's
barely did any damage
there's not a ton of news for Halloween
at the moment why
what
um hey this member released this song
what should I do guys
what should I do which one
[Music]
Spanish version okay yeah just um
instead of like this member released
this song uh
more like you know coyote also does it
like just random [\h__\h]
random funny [\h__\h] or rumors uh yeah some
cool stuff some bigger collaborations
some first time collaborations I don't
know [\h__\h] gossip yeah rumors all that
kind of stuff
fun little things
from other members streams
like for example if fun and me killed
the Wither then the news would be fun
and kiwama took down the weather in
their stream together in a very dramatic
find blah blah blah
mm-hmm
clearly sometimes get together yes I
know
um but not enough that's why we need one
but what's coming yeah
[Music]
I can't see my Pokemon
wow
I will not focus on Japan me because
that's already what coyote is doing
and I mean the argument that people will
know anyway for clips
if you use that agreement then you don't
need any of these shows any of them
but they're fun and then you get all the
info from one week in one stream in all
the important info the fun info the
highlights in one stream compact
[Music]
I don't know why some people are trying
to
um make me believe that I don't need to
do this
[Music]
we're doing it I already have a
background yeah me and Senpai also does
it they have two people on the Japanese
side doing it
is a little bit different though but
yeah
yeah what is cream Style
that's doubting it
fulfill
fairy
what place was very dark
foreign
that's a good question
[Music]
if I
include en Stars that's a good question
[Music]
all right
I'll think about that
you have challenged me
I will show you who is the ghost
[Music]
s
foreign
[Music]
they all want to come at me and punch me
in the face
let me go
continent is milk
Let It Go
[Music]
es
let me go
go away
[Music]
not good for my throat to make me so
angry not good not good for my fruits
foreign
[Music]
somewhere else where you originally
stood
and
my God
it's so annoying when you spawn in an
enemy
so annoying
[Music]
and then I did it three times you know
what
how is it possible
I don't want to check out what's up
there but I suppose this is a ride is it
is this a red path
yes yes
I think so
I steal
useful
for
later maybe in the ice oh cute stuff
where's Penguin even the Ice Arena at
some point
will be quite useful
oh yeah
difficult trainer
what are you doing here
you see
no I don't
want to get when you sneeze little boy
oh fire Inspire when you sneeze
right now
see I thought I'll be fine without her I
will not revive her but now she would
have been really useful
I'll dig I will dig
you have to put your arm in front of
your mouth when you see your arm not
your hands
did no one teach you yeah a lot of
people don't understand this oh my God
it's so strong
a lot of people don't understand it
[Music]
yeah damn
wow
[Music]
oh my God
um
yeah boy
what else does he have he has free
Pokemon man
[Music]
[\h__\h] also the size difference between
those two is like in princess mononoka
big wolves and the girl riding on it
they could reenact that cool little
sound should I stay is that the
steel Pokemon I can melt it right
[Music]
oh Rock fire what the [\h__\h]
I can
revive
I can revive I can stay and then revive
[Music]
um
holy [\h__\h] it's the big one
[Music]
can you buy these in the shop by the way
because I'm just gonna use this one but
[Music]
um
oh how friendly now when I switch in
my smoothie you know what will happen
to get the nice welcome gift
[\h__\h] where do you get them
one
I don't even remember where I fought
where I found it
oh I feel better oh that thing is really
big so probably really slow there we go
thank God
[Music]
thanks
it would have been fine I'll just stay I
think that sounds like something I could
take care of
oh it's the elephant
uh
so pretty
still
[Music]
goddamn so fire
doesn't work really
[Music]
cool
nice critical
oh that boy has some huge purple every
single one of his Pokemon was like five
times his size
no
they're probably carrying him everywhere
so he doesn't have to walk
but it works
oh what are we gonna find
good job
okay where now
don't think this is the path
Lord so bright
let's do it it's so bright there's no
texture whatsoever
especially on my screen
here it gets a bit better but holy [\h__\h]
I mean that's somewhat realistic though
because damn when on a sunny day a Snowy
Mountain
blind you
chances exp pinata that's actually a
really funny thing to say about it
let me go back and try it for myself
[Music]
oh wait I just like flew back up
where's chanting
[Music]
see come on give me another chance
pentagon
[Music]
maybe now
no nothing
okay
well next time I stay one I'll find it
I'll remember that
Santa oh is it a city up there but isn't
that where the
um ice gym leader is
who's done
I can't
see I'm in danger
[Music]
oh we can make shaped ice with this
I like that one fight that one fight it
fight
foreign
are you blind
come on that's so cute no I'm running
[Music]
just not fight the gym yet yeah okay
it's kind of weird that you walk through
it because if you play this game without
looking up on the internet where you're
supposed to go
then normally judging by how far the
game has worked now
when you go left right left right left
right that looks like Santa Claus from
the back
and you would assume that this one comes
first oh my God I never realized that
oh my God
yo but ice gym will be such a freaking
walk in the park with my starter
kyrus's least favorite Pokemon
can you not see the Daily Bread episode
of Pokemon no is that what it was about
this Pokemon doing like Santa deliveries
or what
I didn't really watch
Pokemon anime no
maybe a few episodes from the first one
or two seasons when I was a child
basically oh oh that's fun that's cute
I didn't do the thing
oh oh here's the ice ice one oh
I like it
[Music]
so many EB Evolutions but they're always
alone so sad
yo I can find everything here without
thinking about the time
I'm so glad
come on
so easy everything's iced here
okay well thank you no problem no
problem
um
no
[Music]
all the Santa Clauses I didn't know
there were so many I thought there was
only one
why do you sound like an elephant
[Laughter]
oh
okay we're done we're done we're done
now we don't I can't stop
at least we don't get like insane
amounts of
the XP but still like a little bit to
help us out
we're not being over leveled what the
[\h__\h] is that new I've never seen that
before is it a steel ice or something
like that
cryo now
and five and it's eyes oh okay you could
have made it still eyes that would have
been cool
that was that tiny thing
[Music]
foreign
oh Dragon trainer
golf oh I should have should have
probably put someone else
in the front but let's see what you got
it's kind of fancy outside
we bought this one before so the game
will tell me
what to do thankfully
yes I got ice and I got Dragon but then
that means that if they use a dragon
attack it will be also effective against
me
oh but it's passive agility okay
which will probably mean you will attack
first now but
oh
[Music]
the dragon dragon trainer not teach her
Pokemon a dragon attack
[Music]
what
I mean she would have used it right if
she had it because it would be effective
weird
foreign
I guess so
what this looks like
like skiing place
oh
I can totally imagine scares just skiing
down here
always gotta go like left right left
right to not be too fast oh yeah this is
perfect for skiing
oh my old roommate would love this
[Music]
wow
oh that's an ice cream
ice rink ice skating here
bye
well I wanna go guys
nice oh don't fall down
is this the gym but that's the ice gym
where we don't want to go okay okay
I mean I feel like I could probably take
her down too but you know
better not go inside
you can safely delete I mean with my
fire starter
I could probably write what level is
that Jim I'm not gonna go but
I'm curious
47 yeah that's manageable but I prefer
to do it in a proper order
yeah we can fast travel here but wait
how else was I supposed to get to the
other gym if not walking from here
trainers do you wear all day
[Music]
what is it I heard it
blind chill
I heard it
[Music]
so
cool
basically straight to North
okay so down here
to imagine just imagine I'm wearing
skiers right now
but honestly I don't think I'll actually
go skiing this season
because I'll be busy in Japan for most
of winter
and well
last time I went skiing I will stay it
was fun but it was also suffering
and it was exhausting and cold and
I'm Austrian so I really want to enjoy
it
I wanted to be my thing you know I want
to become good at skiing but it was
just exhausting last time
and so scary too I was always so scared
and I felt so stupid you know because
like
oh no everyone around me and rnt too
would be like So Pro at it and then I
would feel so embarrassed and I was like
so scared of even the tiniest little
Hill
in the in the road
um
I would be really nervous trying to ski
in all honesty have we never done it
before
I'm gonna keep doing it in order to get
it because you always have to wait for
the winter season and now I feel like if
I get back into it but I do have my own
skis right so I should use them
oh maybe maybe instead of going pretty
far like last time maybe this time I can
just go to
some place close by and only go for one
day go back on the same day
and see how I feel about it then
and if it was a lot of fun then I can
just go again
yeah
but the thing is with like if I go on
the trip like last time where I booked a
nice hotel somewhere far away in a
really cool snowy region
it's like three nights or so then I feel
like obligated I feel like it's a waste
to not
um go skiing every day and that makes me
feel so pressured
but then I feel exhausted from the
previous day or just mentally exhausted
because it was so scary
I have to say that one trauma
is still deeply engraved into my brain I
think that is one of the problems
um
[Music]
did you go skiing with the girls in
Japan
I think probably 95 of them never been
skiing before and don't know how to ski
I don't know if they would go with me
but that's also quite something to plan
and I don't really know being regions in
Japan
I mean it would be fun to build a couple
girls if they're motivated to do it
wasn't it snowing in Japan kind of bad
well they're surely good still too it's
just the the place where we went to
probably be considered decent snow by
good skiers
hey
because my arm tea my old roommate she
told me right that she prefers or like
generally like as good skiers prefer
Hearts nose
rather than powdery fluffy snow
apparently it's better
but I didn't feel like it would be
better for me because I had no control
over my curves
so I don't see how it's better I don't
get it so the problem at that place was
we were in Hokkaido and we went to the
closest
we went sampled we went to the closest
uh skiing area
and I mean I don't know how much
difference it would have made but my rmt
also told me that one issue would have
been probably that we re-rented
our equipment everything
and the skis the length of it is very
important but also
um
like how the quality of it is and how
much it's been used and if it's from a
rental place
you can guess it's been used a million
times especially because we when we were
there we saw
huge a huge School group
renting stuff from there
like I think it was like it looked like
150 people or so
so if that's a normal thing there then
imagine how many people use those skis
before and yeah
that might really impact
it's I need to
confronting Christ is a common problem
for you yeah wait what you mean my own
curves
[Laughter]
they may have not maintained it yeah
yeah it's just too much to maintain like
I saw the selection they had
they had a lot of stuff but uh
yeah I also think the shoes that I got
maybe were a little bit too big
that's also a big problem if you don't
feel like you have
perfect grip in your shoes
that can ruin everything
so oh
I killed the Pokemon I know it
it's funny
well at least you know with my own
equipment you will think that I would be
fine but then you know at the store I
bought I bought the skiers that are like
good but then I learned later on if you
remember that
smaller skis would have been shorter
skis would have been way better for me
they did feel way better when I tried
them on
because long longer skis are better for
pros but shorter skis are better for
bubble bubbles like me mine were way too
long way way too long yeah Mr yodel let
me try like several different smaller
sizes that he had
and that was that made already a lot of
difference
but now I have these huge suckers
I probably wouldn't even bring them
if I went to skiing again because I'm
not ready for those not ready for them I
have to grow into them by becoming
better okay see there you go my skills
should be the reason and the motivation
to go skiing again because they cost
good money you know
foreign
by the way is this not the place this is
like a this gate looks like a World of
Warcraft
where are we
oh it's there it's over there
where the gym building is also not here
oh wait not here
oh up there ah there it is
[Music]
that doesn't want to make me go into a
snowy region
those houses with the icicles everywhere
the big layer of snow on top of the roof
and the style of the house
oh it's not quite like the Austrian
houses in the Alps but
that's an interesting similar vibes
ah
what a tease
on the music
it's nice here
I feel like in previous Pokemon games
recently the ice areas always the ice
cities always had like a calm cling
clang cling clang kind of music
this one's a bit more has a bit more
instrumentals to it
something behind here
the desk Stone
all right let's go in uh how are we
looking here
[Music]
yeah more than just playing blood oh
hello I haven't seen you in ages who the
[\h__\h] are you again
uh
who is he
huh
who
duck
ah The Home Room teacher
hello hello
how goes your treasure hunt figured out
what you're hunting for yet
uh
[Music]
no idea
I'm gonna direct the club doesn't like
questions with easy answers does he man
he's doing a shiny shiny
shiny when he's doing his shoes to make
the chamber circuit a part of their
treasure hunt
it's no easy to feed but even making an
attempt is a worthwhile experience
that's why I was waiting here to make
sure you know your homeroom teachers got
you back
you're so colorful
[Music]
you remind me of Vino
the purple you have the mad scientist
lab coat
remind me of you know
egg
this should be handy for your treasure
hunt I I hope you'll keep working on the
Pokedex of yours too since I did make
the app and all oh speaking of I need to
check them
you'll be all right will I be all right
oh
but it only counts for the ones I caught
right oh I almost have 50. I need to
catch one more
[Music]
mm-hmm
so close
lucky a good item for leveling up yeah
who here needs leveling actually no
they're
pretty caught up actually when I put a
new member in my team I'll give them the
lucky egg that will be useful uh ghost
Arena right so we have ghost versus
Ghost
what else I know I asked you a million
times but what else is effective against
Ghost presents ghosts
mm-hmm
oh dark oh I think Sparks No we got rid
of the dark attack didn't we
and bug bug I don't have any more dark I
think someone has a dark move
start with my fire starter
I'll probably be a nut butt okay
probably the fun
we'll just uh ghost versus Ghost the
whole thing
ah you got the funny I like those
Pokemon
I like them
we can remember yeah
[Music]
oh I need to give them any and okay okay
I will give them any item
[Music]
I will I will choke
foreign
[Music]
cool
it's just a wedge
change weather
oh we can give him Focus sash when in
doubt egg but I don't really think he
needs this anymore
no I don't want to use it myself
[Music]
wait no one has items what the [\h__\h]
who here uses special attacks
the most
I think our starter uses special attacks
right
spot box yes okay
and who here uses physical moves
[Music]
okay
is there anyone who would use the the
loaded dice now
um
I don't think actually anyone has a
attack like that right now
caspers
really
I forgot
[Music]
I suppose love the loaded dice
okay you can have
but later okay
oh
I mean that's good for anyone
[Music]
give wait let me see if there's
something more useful
grass type ground type
P quick claw
[Music]
cool
is
um the leftover Pokemon who don't have a
item yet they're both somewhat slow
maybe who's slower
I wonder
let me see
uh
bird is fast really
uh where is your hey speed 75
oh yeah Burgers fast yes
so I will give the the the quick claw
whatever that was to the cartoon
and the other thing I had left over to
is
[Music]
at least for now I guess this is our
team for a little while so
why not what was it
quickly
no that's not what I meant
oh
yeah I don't want to keep the egg
at least not now
oh HP
why not
[Music]
why not why not
and then
if I bring back a dark move I can still
bring back hyper voice again later right
[Music]
snarl
guide
oh
that's why we were using snarl because
fight is
physical
[Music]
Shadow build feather
we're gonna have Shadow build I guess do
I not need dark then
um
[Music]
okay
let's just hope we move first and that
there's no weird catch
what about the gym challenge
I need to go to idle meeting soon
wow are we gonna do a rap battle
hey you opening act
all right should be the main act I'll
show you
you'll regret
yo Trina you're the one performing the
opening hour today my name's MC Sledge
wait wait wait
this is the stage right here so here's
the deal we're gonna have you do some
double bed oh
Ah that's when you have two Pokemon
fight on each side
don't let your Sledge out double the
opponents and get the audience twice as
you started the venue will be so hot
it'll melt a month and never snow once
you get done it's worked up and ready to
go that'll be the cue for a leader to
take the stage that's how you pass our
gym desk yo
ah the gym tests are double Bells okay
you're opening that begins as soon as
you get up on stage there'll be no
backing down until you win three times
in the world so make sure you're ready
you're good on the dates for the opening
at the new our gym dance ready to slash
them up
uh not yet wait if it's double battles
let me see it
[Music]
um
foreign
okay
then I guess this could be okay
let's point
fine
I'm going to an idle meaning
I'll be right back
foreign
[Music]
I saw that
I saw that chat
[Music]
foreign
um
yep
why
why is there
why is the audience partially tuned
are they already dead
what
what's up what's in the Vera today's
opening it will be free back to back
double Bells by hour
will what our Challenger here keep one
one and the first of their opponents
will be a young performer who makes it
look like a breeze
hey
it's a [\h__\h] toddler
double balance that means one plus one
right can you do that now
listen here you little [\h__\h]
I will teach you math right now
my Pokemon
against your Pokemon which means that in
the end you will have no more Pokemon
they cancel each other out
you think about that
first I take your doggle
well I know it's sad I know
and then I take your sock puppet which
is your only friend
[Music]
don't make fun of me no
oh
one plus one is two right right
yeah
[Applause]
oh
you forgot to turn on the lights until
now
hmm
the monster in the very stages all the
latest tech the more excited the
audience gets the more the stage will
light up and then also we have bugs
where people disappear and come back but
immediately they come back immediately
don't worry about it
did he heal me
and oh challenge is next oppona will be
a musician with a bit of a unique style
it's Lanny
oh country music
[Music]
yeah
it was that angle I didn't even see half
of the Pokemon
I love mysteries
blah blah blah blah blah blah
oh you got to move first oh no
nice
mysterious
no idea
what's like
exclusive wear
um
wow
what do you mean I had to shiny one of
those in archaeos
you mean
through a quest right
wow cool
now even the floor is light lit up
noise
no I'm just getting excited yeah um
um half of the audience is still dead
should I be worried what happened here
your openings you're opening up throwing
the cheering and the stage lighting up
to 11.
with a surprise for a new Challenger
who'd have thought they'd sledged it up
this much
next is your last opponent me
as the hits
being an embassy isn't my only thought
that I can battle too I'll Sledge you up
real good in the double battle
all right all right a little weirdo
serious now
[Music]
easy clap
it's the music yo
it's kind of good
I like it well
because
it's funny I think I'll have to remove
caspers from my Teamster because
as much as I love it
it's been
it's just not fitting for the team
ironically
I like him no he's so cute
I wanna hear with him you know
wait a second
why stable eye
oh is it dark ghost herself
oh wait why did it get so barely any
damage
oh my god well no matter it's going down
now
huh
okay
um yes
now I'm MC sledgehammer
whoa
now get the bus
I don't want to fight anymore against
these amateurs
will it be a double fight too though
congratulations you best gym jazz
one of applause
I feel a scary good sense of unity in
the crowd Perfecto we're ready to go for
the main event
come on everybody stay with me this is
what you've all been waiting for
rip
e
whoa rip you
what
off rip what is Rip
[Applause]
Ryan
I I
[Applause]
obviously Cali
what's all this noise I'm hearing yo
dude this crowd's so loud I could wake
the Dead
because I'm the Grim Reaper let me tell
you what I want to hear you're feeling
good
thanks for the killer opener uh she
doesn't call me baby
she calls me dog there's a killer open a
dog now I'll get this started for real
thanks dog
you passed
can I listen oh
it's rapping but we can't hear it
oh this is one problem
why am I only me this is bullying
oh man
foreign
[Music]
looking promising
interesting
very interesting
[Laughter]
believe it
the rapper is like ghost and death
themed
bomb on Game Freak are you subscribed to
Cali or what
[Music]
wait am I healed
was I healed even if I wasn't
not that I needed
it's so funny
yo yo yo
yo
hey yo
sounds like there might be a wrap up oh
yo can I finally listen
a a this is my time and this is my day
you're not gonna stand in my way eh
listen up rhyme your rain ends here
you're gonna get rung up by this Pro
cashier cashier
boom booms
broke cashier well I'm about to check
out must got your rhymes on deep
discounts please you think you can step
to my game fool I got rhyme right there
in my name I'm a specter from which
there is no protector and victory on to
me you will render when the crowd sits
around me Pretender oh
you want to end my irania keep dreaming
by a book of Rhymes kid and start
reading
my baby after my next shift oh that was
also a rhyme sick hold on wait going
that's all you got [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] you're
scary
look at her face
why is she so scary what
after my next shift seriously bars over
jokes come on
that was over way too fast it gets
boring wearing the crowd if no one makes
me fight to keep also another irony you
know how Kelly
in one of her first songs sings about
welcome to the Mountaintop
and this [\h__\h] is literally on the
mountain hub
I don't think you guys thought about
that reference just yet
oh
can't can't deny it
ah
that was overrated fast blah blah blah
blue
um
was back you're here for a rap look at
your shoes
what are the dolls honestly Cali would
buy those yeah
oh you ain't for a rap battle Lord's gym
paddle
huh you got jokes we both know why
you're really here no wait I want to go
rap battle
Kelly what happened to our rap battle
idea
I thought we were gonna do that
you were captivated by the show I put on
huh I wrap what's in my soul baby
weaving words into a symphony of poetry
oh yeah she does do that don't try it
with me you won't last one round I'm
like save alive I mean look look down
like that you feel me
yes
he's so funny well let's get to it you
know Pokemon trainer so follow me and
show me who you are
my music got all that top charts my
skill with Ghost types are the best
around
do you blessed you forget it my name is
rhyme and I'm known as the MC of R.I.P
Dead or Alive let's make this survive
so I told myself something Kelly would
say
if the microphone doesn't look like Cali
microphone
you know what the oh it's just even like
Kelly's outfit because of those golden
like
Florence
around the black body is literally like
what Kelly's outfit looks like
[Music]
okay I'm not actually thinking
a dad's game freak did this on purpose I
don't think so but it's just a lot of
funny coincidences
laughs
isn't it
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay finally for Pokemon but they're a
double fights
should I terrestrial us
I will
[Music]
I don't know
some battle rhyme on YouTube student kid
oh you'll see you'll see your idol be
smashed by me
[Music]
apparently moving we can still goes oh
it does oh because
I'm now only fire not Ghost Fire or fire
ghost
[Music]
this basically got rid of my weakness
I alright you have to hit mimikyu once I
should have terrestrialized apple
right I forgot about that that was a
thing
just coming I'm a Pokemon
's HP already looking like [\h__\h]
not going to survive the whole battle
probably unless I heal it
[Music]
a lot of stuff just throws
okay take that mimikyu
take down the net and then we should be
fine oh
anyone horse box
is that
oh I got Bob for The Crowd Oh what
[Music]
okay nice sweep hmm
what you got that
on the ground huh
okay
[Music]
do I get to attack uh
you know are they
not fair oh hello everybody
we were down for a moment well nothing
really happened I was just waiting for
her to switch in her Pokemon
and now I was just wondering like why
even in double battles when the enemy
switches someone in
they don't get treated the same way as
we do
like she gets a free switch right
[Music]
Castle pounds don't fly
not there
[Music]
what does it do
kick back relax and enjoy this last
Frack turn it up for a great rattling
good time
oh
they finally show up to support their
big mommy
the Dogo I mean
I'm on the mic keep the dead rise up
eastern gray full producers feel like
how cute
oh if Cali ever gets a doggle but I
think she prefers castles she should
call it CJ grave like that one
oh it's a rave in the grave
it's a rain so hot that even the people
in the grave stood up
what was I supposed to be careful of
if I didn't take him down immediately
would he have done something nearby
oh
that's AOE
[Music]
finally we're here to track a little bit
longer
[Music]
gets stronger for each banded Ally oh
interesting
oh
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
it was perfect to wrestle eyes
should never move be forgotten and
replace with Ice Beam
perhaps yes
Ice Beam
oh when ice cream is not special see
finally I actually understand this and
look at it so we don't really want Ice
Beam huh
it's very strong though it's much
stronger than ice fan
[Music]
in theory
um
we are
physical attacker but this is a special
attack
wouldn't recommend it
okay we don't need it then
okay yay
[Music]
giving up the ghost snot really my style
I'll let you have this one tough baby
where's the rhyme where's the rhyme it
didn't end it in a rhyme and my body
running it in a rhyme I was like rhyming
myself
ah great battle chilling and thrilling
you've got the spirit kids you are in my
gym badge all right
and how about a VIP pass for my next
show too
[Music]
oh of course yo
that's also very Cali like
really captures the spirit
with six Gym badges it will be easier to
catch Pokemon of up to level 50 and then
listen to what you have to say too
I'm feeling so good that I think I'm
also gonna let you have this
Shadow Ball wait I already have that
attack
[Music]
too bad so but make your way back to my
stage sometime maybe next time we rap
battle instead who knows I'm sure you've
got some scary good Adventures ahead
I'll be cheering for you later
cool very cool very funny
oh
as a whole life member
that was
just super special more special than if
someone else plays the game for us it
just makes sense and we chuckle while
looking at it
greetings once more kiwawa I was
watching your battle the dream leader
from the sidelines and I must say I
thought it was simply excellent for Marx
gold star extra credit even hardly had
you sent out skeletons before you
launched into your strategy
that unrelenting offensive the flurry of
attacks when an efficient way to Corner
the opponent and would artfully train
Pokemon such a vibrant ballot of moves
you always use the same moves though I
do beg your pardon I didn't mean to let
my emotions run down look like that
um in summary I simply wanted to say
that you seem to have gotten even
stronger I must admit I'm eager for you
to gather all the gym badges as a member
of the Elite Four I awaited today you
come to face me with great anticipation
do we only have one gym left
the ice one
[Music]
and one Titan
um
two gems oh okay
[Music]
we got the very bottom exciting psychic
supposed to be last and Ice comes down
one thing don't let your studies Fall by
the wayside be sure to come to the
academy now
oh oh I haven't gone a single time since
I left
hmm
[Music]
oh
the ghost was supposed to be seven the
ice was eight okay
psychic was four for me excuse me what
the [\h__\h] what a weird Flex
are you flexing on me
in delinquential
I did Ice and ghosts last yeah
well then what are the levels
you know what I'm gonna look it up
oh I have Pokemon
Scarlet gem levels
[Music]
Okay so
um
this
is the recommended order Buck gym
Stone Titan grass gym
Sky Titan dark Bass
electric gym
fight
[Music]
I think we did a dead order fire
uh base we may have done Firebase before
the electrician I'm not sure anymore
steel Titan
Water Gym
poison base
yeah
normal gin
Ghost Gym Dan Earth Titan okay we
switched up something here a little bit
but that's okay
and then sat down psychic and then ice
Jim
because the side
Ghost Gym that we just had was 41 to 42
the Earth Titan is 44. the psychic gym
is 44 to 45 while the ice gym is 47 to
48.
and then the fairy base which is 50 to
51.
I know I can do any order but I will do
it this one because it just makes the
most sense in order to keep my level
like scaled to it
oh
okay and then after the fairy base
the Dragon Titan
and after that
the fighting base
it seems to be like that
[Music]
I don't want to be like on a level that
I don't want to be over leveled and this
way it just makes sense bro
oh yeah otherwise you know that's really
it's really stupid they should have just
had scaling if they really want us to be
in an open world and tell us you can go
anywhere you want and it should have had
level scaling that's just my opinion
[Music]
it is what it is though
so I'm just gonna ignore
that
[Music]
wait what did I say what's next
um after ghost the Earth attack that we
already did so
I'm excited though
because it's purple and I like it it's
perfect pretty pretty purple pretty and
purple not Pretty in Pink Pretty in
purple
oh
but I'm also kind of sad to leave the
snow area already
but like we didn't spend so much time in
here
[Music]
oh look at them a little family
ghost Terrace
what the [\h__\h] no
yeah I'll explore explore a little bit
see when I missed
but it's good that we're making so much
progress do you guys think maybe if I do
two more things
so two more gems
next part
could potentially be the last or is
there a lot of content after those
things that I've just mentioned
tell me tell me
there's a lot afterwards oh yeah right
you have to fight the the poor and all
that right
okay so maybe two more Pawns
depending on how long my streams will be
with my throat horde
surprise I can go up here just pretty
steep oh oh that's where it ends yeah
bye
wow
I like the snow area the texture of the
snow is pretty good
I like it I mean
there's only snow in some trees and
that's pretty pretty much it so maybe
they could have I don't know put
something somewhere
a bit more interesting stuff but
you know it's all right
we're gonna go let's go over here
over to the other side
oh snowstorm
where am I
isn't that accurate though well I'm in
still they could have I mean accurate to
a random Snow Mountain yes but they
could have put some more stuff anyway
that whole area is unexplored
right
yeah yeah
and again hunting Shiny Pokemon doing an
outbreak with the shiny show but this
because at the end of the game why why
would I hunt the shiny when I'm not
gonna use it anymore I would have wanted
it
like
while I was actually properly playing
the game
I just I don't know I'm different
I don't feel the motivation for it
um
maybe after today's episode
until the next one
maybe I do some shiny hunting privately
and I maybe find something that I
actually want to use
that would be ideal oh yeah what's that
[Music]
French that's what the one that you guys
were talking about maybe
oh but I already have mine I'm okay with
that
dude it's not so rare here oh there's
another one I think yeah okay they're
pretty common here
if you're looking for one
sounds good right yeah because I just
don't
see the meaning and getting a shiny if
I'm not gonna use it
if I'm done playing anyway
the end of the game what is that it's
too [\h__\h] bright oh
the last thing
trouble
hello everybody what is this
one star what is just one star
oh
oh oh this Pokemon is so pretty the ice
move
I think I it already existed before but
it's so pretty I love it
hey y'all
[Music]
yeah last time oh it was last one that's
actually pretty fresh
No Escape
[Music]
I thought you were going to escape
it's so pretty
you want one of those at home as a pet
look at it it's also So Graceful oh
[Music]
this is so fluffy oh baby too wow I mean
I guess that's not so far off from me
[Music]
I hope it doesn't kill it but it
probably will I kind of want to catch it
good design right
oh man too bad
[Laughter]
[Music]
I know sometimes sometimes I expect
myself to be weaker than I am
tired
tires no I'm tired
now here ends the snow
what's that mushroom no [\h__\h] way shut
up
no but by now it will be already be gone
anyway it looks
no way that was no
I hate you guys
that was actually a Pokemon I liked
it looked great how green did it need to
be
[Applause]
what's what was the name again
no it would have not shined
I hate you guys I hate you guys
no
green it's just the eyes are a little
bit of the Shadow oh I caught up
[Music]
oh
it might have been
bad no
it could have been I I I I I feel like I
saw it that way too
everyone just thought it was normal
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
oh no I can't be
eh
I didn't catch anything
they don't Sparkle when they appear what
are you gaslighting me
in this game they don't Sparkle and
that's the problem
Oh you mean ah I thought you meant the
one I ran by afterwards not the one I
was fighting
you meant the one I was fighting I I saw
another moth after that and I thought
you were talking about that one and that
looked now that you say it a little bit
shiny to me
well if you're talking about the one I
thought no that one was of course not
of course not shiny
are you shiny
nah
oh evolution
lots of relief is it though is it though
is it a relief that something was not
shiny
I don't know
[Music]
did I come from you
it's kind of shiny that's so fitting
though because that Meme is with a
butterfly and there's almost a butterfly
why are you so mad why are you so mad
why are you so mad and it's running at
me Pokemon now
[Applause]
[Music]
she brought 1500 vocals bam
Nico Senpai brought 1500.
it's got a lot of time on her hands
oh level up level 50. let's go
um
oh it's the pretty snow ghost
s that looks green to me
[Music]
oh man that looks really green that
looks also green to me the eyes look
green to me but not anymore
[Laughter]
yeah
now I look at them all the mops so
closely
and that you know it's kind of easy to
miss
the cutie pie
this is another one of those areas where
you
could easily get lost and have no idea
where you are and where you're heading
towards
foreign
[Music]
down there now
psychic psychic what's uh strong against
psychic guys
um it was shy you were hunting a shiny
Frost man everything looked green
oh
um back goes dark
ghost dark
[Music]
um
okay
[\h__\h] was dark
level 12.
[Music]
I think I can catch something useful
close by dark Sneasel
41.
it's still a little bit low
[Music]
foreign
Sparks doing everything alone
a little bit
sorry
okay we set
as destination and let me heal once
foreign
well in that moment we will just um
switch to our
eh
rockzilla for a dark move
or we can burn it something will work
we'll be fine
[Music]
we'll find a way
razor clubs uh-huh these are cool do I
have a razor cloth
which way
is this the right way
I'm just following my marking nut but I
can't get up there
[Music]
I mean it's dragon type thingy oh
ah I have to go over there
[Music]
is the elephant you want to talk to me
about
it's probably really low levels trainer
this will be boring
[Music]
a tunnel from the north side okay
what I want for Christmas I don't think
anyone would really give me a Christmas
gift
um like in person
uh
my family doesn't really do gifts
anymore if anyone I'm the one gifting
um
you guys can't give me physical gifts
and that's also
something
it's a tunnel like if I follow this path
or
[Music]
just follow it for now because I've
never been up here before
[Music]
um
had to say let me think what would I
want for Christmas
possibly
some improvements for my apartment
probably like
or my PC maybe a new graphic card
I was starting to think about getting a
new graphic card when I talked um with
my friend about it
getting some advice
that would probably make sense a
graphics card
and well I have a steam deck now so
I'll need to wish for steam deck
[Music]
um
yeah 4019
[Music]
um up
it's hard to think of something
maybe it's ripped to a spa
[Music]
but all these kinds of things I can
obviously just give to myself of course
but it's always nice to have someone
gifted to you right
[Music]
um
you think I need a processor too
[Music]
fire hazard really
I was wondering if you know if I buy the
most latest one if that will have some
issues
and I should buy one before that
I will remember that
good that I'd talk to you guys about it
Burning For Real huh
for real zones
yo
no I might need materials from these
guys even though I never built TMS but
you know while I'm here
they're low level anyway
what are you doing
oh you don't want to do it because
you're in a fellow Hollywood
crystallized one as well
I doesn't want to
[Music]
foreign
that's really the reason
power supply
and
ready on the 7900
[Music]
is that even better
you can consider it
1490 is a scam money
is good
what's he there oh we've been here
before where am I
no what the [\h__\h] I'm totally going the
opposite way I wasn't looking
[Music]
well the road South Orange
this is why I'm a cat person
leave me alone
okay
let's follow the road
like normal people do
already an awful freight train thing
that's the 7900
[Music]
oh God you guys have too much knowledge
makes me confused
I don't even really know what Ray
tracing is
it's over hyped overrated not a little
don't buy 40 90. okay
thank you for your advice I will um
I will follow it
sorry child
so I'm following the road South but this
is where it would go to complete
opposite
so I will ignore the path now
maybe down here is where the
where the Cape is can I see the cave
somewhere
on the map
ah maybe yeah
[Music]
I know
this is a cave
probably
okay
was up here before
wait I need to
don't I need to get one more level
higher
uh I understand that probably getting
the Titan first would make this a lot
easier but
okay
[Music]
all the all the PC Geeks geeking out in
the chat
telling me info where my brain is just
question mark question mark question
starting to piss me off really badly
stop it stop stop running into me
[Music]
I'm sleeping
okay maybe I don't know if I went there
before but if I walk up here is that I
was looking at the mountain
[Music]
maybe up there
is there a way to go off
no
I can't make that jump either
huh
look for a little boy in front of cave
near the sea mount what
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I don't know where to go
oh the road which one
go south from the Pokemon Center in the
West
this one
okay okay yeah that looks like it has a
road that goes down there
hey
[Music]
foreign
I feel like I would destroy his dreams
and his hopes but you
you I will I hope he hopes he doesn't
fall
well wouldn't it be all right so
terrible
if he would fall
right that would be terrible
[Music]
a lot would do it this way
oh who scared me what happened
should I be worried about this guy
oh
[Music]
who could ever know
um
[Music]
I could switch to this and an attack of
fighting but will it not like try to
become me and then fighting will be no
more
well I'm very close to the cliff I
see well
[Music]
but
I use this dig first do you also use
dick
will it also use a thick
it doesn't
you asked me
little stupid
[Music]
used to dig and we both have the same
wait does Diddle
also transform uh to get the same stats
or does diddle keep its own stats
because then I wonder like who is faster
would we have the same speed or
a [\h__\h] shiny pancakes
every stat except HP then who would uh
come out of their dig first
[Music]
50 50.
oh my God my water thing [\h__\h] scared
me it looks like one it's not it's a
normal one
[Music]
whoa what is this supposed to look like
it looks normal
this is the old man shiny
your mom is shiny
I know it because
I met her last night
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh snap oh oh [\h__\h] but it's kind
of a compliment saying your mom's
driving
it's a good word
how was she doing
oh man
what
[Music]
shiny Panthers identical to normal
shiny
[Music]
um
what
I don't see it what
it's just a bit brighter
yeah well
it's another bamboozle
ah I think after the evolution it's more
noticeable
[Music]
outside
is it just me or does it become a little
bit more greenish rather than blue but I
don't know I'm looking at like a couple
of different references
so shiny Gatsby no it's not
you're making me look anyway
no it's not
[Music]
no no no no
you won't make it on foot
what do you mean I won't take it on
but I'll make it on my bike right
was that one of those magical
no it's just a torch
oh
alfornada cabin
wow I like this place
it's better than the other caves
oh what is this weird water
[Music]
I mean the water part is weird oh there
you go the reflection helps
that makes it look better
but there's no like splashiness when I
walk in it
they had it in that City
in the desert
with the water you know that really low
water
it was good
it's got up work how
[Music]
was work
um
it's something exciting happen
did Joanne
tease you again
or did you let yourself get teased by
Joe and Kim
told you you have to stand up against
her
and let her tease you
Domingo there's so many scientists now
oh
then nice lock
horror Pokemon to come across
uh I don't know what's effective to be
honest
here we have some hyperbliss
oh oh it's levitating
um
what it's sound proof what do you mean
it's soundproof
you don't care for oh because it's a
move
what
what on Earth
doesn't have beers
first house yourself from do something
wait oh
that also doesn't work soda foreign
them
that's interesting because it doesn't
have ears
well my uh fractilla also really doesn't
have ears seemingly
it doesn't have that
hmm
[Music]
I kind of thought it would be easier to
get that area
is doing a sit
good set who's a good boy who's a good
boy
you good boy
where's the goods again who's a good
skin
can I go down
let me see what's down there
[Music]
chicken
I mean I guess you have like a little
pointy
thing on your butt
it's not quite a tail I wouldn't call it
a tail chicken doesn't really have a
tail
you can flap your wings
oh [\h__\h] you I really thought I looked at
the other one
one of them is a shiny
this stupidest game
it's not like I would blame with this
stupid Pokemon anyway because it's
stupid it's not cute
wouldn't want to use it anyway
[Music]
like for real
so whatever
man what
foreign
[Music]
just different color
so I made a pun by saying well the color
is different so it's so shiny right
color is different so the color is
different right you know
[Music]
ch
you know it's color and chigal is
different but chigai would be like kind
of making it
in uh
from an adjective into a
snowman I only know it in German
noun yes
[Music]
at in the back hey oh
God
it's like you know those those um
jackets
where you have the hoods and then you
pull the strings and you can make your
face literally like that
is it a reference to that
you can cosplay this Pokemon just by
doing that with a parka
um
[Music]
side effective
maybe I think I remember something like
that
too was my mom shiny because oh
Harry
well I mean we'll make it work it's only
level 40.
okay okay
let's Dragon fairy
yeah dragon's dragon is known as a
dragon dragon yeah Hey listen
no I'll switch I'm assuming that there's
a dragon so I will switch over
um
is doing a good job
ah cute slimy
[Music]
it's poison dragon
we're just drowning
just Dragon okay Haxorus Haxorus I'll
stay
don't know what that is
whoa
oh
cooler
maybe maybe not cooler but cooler but
here we go
what's cooler than cool I
am
[Applause]
oh man
I heard that this song is actually a sad
song I've never really
like analyzed the lyrics like that why
is it sad what are they singing about
it's about divorce
nothing at all
nothing is forever
I can't remember the lyrics but I guess
she did say a hidden thing nothing stays
forever right that's the only thing I
remember that makes sense with that
I wanna meet your mama just want to make
you oh
oh yeah what does that have to do with
the voice
because
well they're already married but he
doesn't want to meet her
mother
's foreign
[Music]
oh
the song is about the dissolution of a
relationship and coping with its fruit
shallow Hedonism songs self-aware that
is catchy and it goes yeah you're not
even listening really really
what color did it no oh
I'm like 350. I went in with the wrong
Pokemon
[Music]
but like even when I understand the
language
I and even when I sing it myself
I I can just sing it
with a brain empty mind empty kind of
state you know and then
I don't I don't hear
anything
this is just about shaking and pull
around make sure yeah what the hell is
that about what is all the cheering
about
anyway what am I supposed to do with you
little [\h__\h]
thank you
now
you cannot decide for me I will decide
for myself
oh oh my God I have both a syrup that's
so cool
then I didn't ever see that in action
before I think
I avoidant
[Music]
oh
psychic
oh that would be good because it is
special
90.
that's a
H isn't that a better Lumina crash
whatever you like Lumina crash let's do
a side beam makes sense
[Music]
Spanish is guarantees special drop down
okay thank you hey tour you traitor
I like your body give out an opportunity
to give up oh no
you need someone to pick you up maybe
you can teleport to a Poco Center you
can do that right I'm not the only one
in this world who is able to use that
skill hopefully
out but about
it
[Music]
where's the extent here
guys
we have to talk about something
oh the trainer didn't fight
a couple days ago
[Music]
it's recommended on YouTube body
algorithm yo there's an easy path like
that
and music video from a group called Tara
and I was like Cara
that wasn't that the name
wasn't that the name of an old Idol
world
K-pop Idol group that was however mostly
active in Japan
um and a lot of their songs I really
liked back in the day
tell me which one where I continue
talking
um
but you know I I didn't even like watch
the video properly I just let it run in
the preview a little bit to check like
no way they haven't been active for
years
oh one is fine okay
so yeah I don't know it doesn't really
look like the old Tower to me anyway so
I guess well it's been like a lot of
years so maybe some maybe maybe it's
just a similar name and and uh I'm
mixing something up here or
yeah because maybe they just chose the
same name so it's definitely not the
same group right because that song was
new
yeah and it didn't really look like the
old pharaoh
a good old camera
group
no so I ignored it but then
uh yesterday
sent
um a music video camera a new one until
Discord we have like a channel where we
just share whatever
and I'm like
at the same time
I was browsing through Twitter
and I saw a clip
a concert clip of camera really recently
performing all their hit songs
that I loved so much
[Music]
as well
stuff like that that's the group
[Music]
yeah
should I say I forgot what life can work
was
see
ing
okay
um yeah and then I was like wait a
second was that video I saw the other
day on YouTube actually the camera
making a comeback
but then I was I was watching the clip
of them performing all those bangers
one after another
it's a good old bangers
and I was surviving holy [\h__\h] it gave me
goosebumps like insane Goosebumps
the back in the day when they were
really popular was when
a lot of people were I feel like a lot
of people were starting overseas
more and more to do like
Dance videos on YouTube
but people were still doing it in their
own rooms
rather than now I see all these K-pop
dance cover groups all over the world in
groups doing really professional uh
videos right with like moving camera and
they have like 10 people with perfect
uh perfect choreo perfect formation like
holy [\h__\h] it's like improved so much
um
and they do it outside now not inside
but anyway
it reminded me of those days
seeing the Seeing Kara perform their old
songs again
man I don't know their choreos but I
know there are songs
the old songs pretty well such a bob
such a vibe
oh look at that
so that was a big surprise for me I was
going crazy with the um it was actually
a staff member who posted the
Cara video and then we discussed like
holy [\h__\h] that's so nostalgic I can't
believe they're really bad
back we come back
um
the same color that made stuff yeah
I don't understand why there were like
focusing on uh Japan
instead of
uh
Korea because they did make the music in
Korean a lot I guess they also had
Japanese tracks
oh
but they are
kind of a Korean K-pop group
hmm
anyway that was like mind-blowing for me
last night
they were he was in Japan yeah it's so
interesting
they had way more fans in Japan than
in Korea and anyway that come back
holy [\h__\h] that was in Japan I guess
they were saying
I never never thought they would
come back I'm like hype now I need to
look in to the new songs but I don't
think anything will ever be
this is sad but I don't think they can
recreate the same box from back in the
day they probably kind of like
going with a different image different
vibe a little bit
um is that a muscle car
if you watch The Killing voice video
what is that
oh do you mean their new song is that a
new song
yeah that as I said I kind of ignored it
because I thought it was a random group
uh just using the same name
performance I don't know I don't know I
watched the clip on Twitter actually so
it didn't have like
title like that
but they were performing all the
classics man
I think one was also
[Music]
that song is so sick my song is so sick
yeah lupine
I love it
so cool I was watching videos when that
song was out I was watching so many
videos from like girls who covered that
song who did A Dance cover for that song
it was like damn they got moves I can't
stand my dad looks so difficult
man
they got it down they got those K-pop
K-pop moves down
thick
yeah
[Music]
I need to check the Color Fun has the
some songs from Kara well it's literally
in their name so they must
they have to
[Music]
[Applause]
I have no idea what I'm talking about
[Music]
um
all right
[Music]
you will probably feel the same
Goosebumps if you go to my Twitter then
go to my likes
and it's from the top the fifth like
[Music]
it's a it's kind of like a remix
not remix but like a compilation then
performing all of those bangers recently
they don't have any kind of songs oh no
yes right now right now right now me too
me too
as a background music just I'll keep on
playing but
wait
ah I need to listen
oh my God
[Music]
[Laughter]
they're strutting they're strutting oh
wow
and I don't know what that means
[Music]
bring it over
there yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
baby
foreign
[Music]
once your paper plots go
down
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can't only sing English Mr
wow
Mr
[Music]
s
that iconic dance move oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
damn okay that's it sorry for doing that
I had to listen to it
it's just so iconic and legendary and
they're like gods
oh my God
hey she's got the what it takes to be a
ballerina this chick
uh
not a ballerina ice skater it could be
an ice skater oh
wait the vibe in this uh
city is uh
wait with the music and that
architecture I don't want to say
anything wrong so you helped me chat
music
[Music]
oh it's so good
nah this is not a Spanish
Middle Eastern
rabbit yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
what I mean yeah
oh ew that was quite the Oink
[Music]
look at the loss for references to old
games
[Music]
uh which was
that's really old
pixel art huh
you mean those walls
[Music]
as an epic performance from Cara hell
yeah right thank you for agreeing with
me oh I like these little water thing is
again using them here too and oh
Oh I thought she was standing on it like
because I was looking at it like this
looks like she's standing on it in the
water
not quite
quite
um
oh Moroccan yeah yeah I guess could also
kind of beam could be a mix I guess
[Music]
be a mix
I've been to Morocco before so
I guess I could say
I kind of see it
blink
all right so have we officially arrived
we have arrived in alfornados
the end of the world pretty much at
least in that corner
it's Alhambra in Spain oh it's a
reference to a city in space
Spanish Castle from the east of Alhambra
Castle it's amazing this customers
really
Spain there's a place like this
[Music]
I mean
so not so much what confuses me it's the
music because this does not sound like
pain inspired music to me
Morocco very close to spin I that's all
it's the ocean separating it and country
borders but
hold on
South Spain
if you go to South Spain is it more like
Africa
I didn't know that
wow then it has a lot of variation
that's really cool
hey I heard the good news comments on
gym bags number six
not even a tenth of the trainers who
take on the gyms get this far you know
foreign
but I'm not surprised that you made it I
just knew there was a reason you caught
my eye
oh thank you
[Music]
I guess you're really close
it was
uh-huh
[Music]
that's cool I need to check it out in
person
oh please I should be the one thanking
you
anyway I bet you could use a little
warming up before you take on the Gemma
but you know now I'm curious where where
on the map was Valencia
Valencia
[Music]
ah whoa yeah I mean now that I look at
it it's really uh the south of Spain is
really close holy [\h__\h] you could like
if you could
foreign
split the water and walk over
then you could walk over
like a certain someone
[Music]
yeah I guess you could even swim across
can you swim across like it looks really
small on the map but is it is it my
[Music]
mom but um Valencia definitely not in
that region
it you can't swim really
damn if you're a really good swimmer yo
but are there like sharks and [\h__\h] there
I wonder
[Music]
wait let me let me look this up
can you swim from the south of Spain to
oh oh it says Morocco and oh
the shortest distance across the
Gibraltar Strait is from Punta oliveros
to Punta series with a tall distance of
7.8 nautical miles AKA 14 kilometers
that's really tiny because of the
characteristics of Crossing between
those these two points it is not the
most suitable course for the swimmer but
another source says you can certainly
swim from Morocco too
foreign
[Music]
Spain to Morocco swim
it seems like seems like people actually
do it
seems like a thing
some people do it
but maybe not like the best idea
just swim a few laps in the swimming
pool
you can't but why yeah but it's
manageable for a human let's just say
that if you if you can't swim
[Music]
I mean I knew I knew that you know
Geographic geolog
geographically
all of that was close and one another
but I didn't realize it was that close
even though I've been to Morocco
but Morocco me going to Morocco was more
like my mom's saying hey we're going to
Morocco and I was really young you know
when your mom
tells you we're going here for vacation
and you're not really excited about it
anyway because you're
birthday is during that trip and that's
not really where you want it to be then
as a delinquent show
they were like nothing
[\h__\h] this
[Music]
yeah so I did not really care much about
informing myself where we are actually
going
[Music]
just following Mommy
wasn't that delinquent though
[Music]
she tried to sell me four camels
not really but but she definitely
uh
kind of researched how much
I would be worth
which makes you wonder
come on you know the trail by now are we
gonna fight
two
walk out after her we're going together
my dad did that too what
foreign
here's our battle chord for today
at least Suka
I mean a camel honestly very very
valuable but only in certain
environments like oh camel is not very
helpful
if you have it in Austria you have to
get a big yard for it big garden and and
and you know the whole water saving
capabilities might not really help you
unless you're in a desert
how does it how does a camel
save water in its back
does it produce water like others
produce milk
or
what
is that
[Music]
[Laughter]
guys we need to play the game stop stop
trying to have a discussion with me here
[Laughter]
[Music]
when a little fridge I'm warming up
My Humps my arms my homes it's a
conference conception really
what do you mean misconception I I I
knew I knew it was you know anyway
[Music]
well then why did they
always use the camels just for carrying
[\h__\h]
[Music]
and it's a safe water like how would you
make any use of it if it's just in its
body that wouldn't really help you
oh yeah
no I don't know I never really thought
about it
[Music]
uh I guess I guess yeah well I guess the
thing that really was in my mind was
that they say father in their body so
well so that they can go for a long long
time in the desert without water
because you know the fat and the body
whatever I guess in their body helps
them survive longer
rather than a horse which needs or a
donkey which needs more food and water
to go on through those environments yeah
yeah no that is what I was thinking
anyway there you go there we go I just
had to clear my thoughts about it
was right but it wasn't that it was
saving the water for humans it was
saving the water for itself
I think I have redeemed myself
[Music]
Palmer and
I'm switching
[Music]
yeah there's nowhere but they can endure
a lot
and carry or not
[Music]
cute
it's like their brother and sister cute
foreign
[Music]
one right
easy
what you got next you start the rain
sold the snare saw this in there
is that the last one already
oh is that scripted
the Rain Must Be scripted because they
know I bring out my fire Pokemon when
she brings out her stutter
put a diet
[Music]
oh it's already 10 pm
I think after the next gem
I'll end this because I want to make
actually never mind
we're starting a GMT zero so the page
should be obtaining uh in 45 minutes
right
[Music]
so I guess okay I'm just gonna I was I
was hoping to like be like more
available during it in case there's any
last minute problems
or so but also be okay
foreign
[Music]
that would be nice I guess
hey
wait um is this the website we're on
YouTube I mean I've already seen it like
it's it's ready
up like just with the first door closed
still
[Music]
one hour before or so would also be nice
but it was right to believe in you
and before that said crashes
I wonder like I don't think it will
always be like so much traffic at once
and just when I when we launch it but I
don't think it will crash
but I don't really know how much it can
take either
oh okay we can like open it up and like
five minutes or so apparently
[Music]
yay and then I will tell you guys the
URL and you can type it in and try your
best to crash it it's like a stress test
that's an L for me man you've gotten so
good I think that should be enough of a
warm-up
your Pokemon should be all set now here
take these as thanks for the battle
Max potions or nicer you know what I
will show the website on screen then
I think it's to show
ah I think I need to go to another Idol
meeting damn
okay I'll be our Bean
ie
[Music]
foreign
how about we're not doing it in five
minutes but after I'm done with the gym
[Music]
because then we have a nice cut off
good thing is
people in charge on listening into the
Stream
King
[Music]
everybody's listening
all right well this movie almost has 200
hp damn she's got so much more in speed
than like the others wow
really defensive
a lot did I already start the gym test
thingy not yet right that's the
pneumonia lady interrupted me
let me register you as a challenger your
name is kibaba
CCC
and now in order to face generally the
Tulip that's her name it sounds like a
name of a plant gym leader
he'll first need to pass the gym test
here in California gym that means waking
up a sweat with a special kind of
exercise
I'm talking about the emotional
spectrum's practice
created by tulip herself emotional
Spectrum practice
what the woman wearing the black
tracksuit in the practice area will
explain the rules to you just turn left
after the gym and you'll find the
brightest area right next door
what
are we getting
uh evaluated by
a therapist or what
[Music]
Nani
this was a weird one
it's simple
huh
well I don't care as long as I can meet
the pretty lady I don't care
oh
what are you doing here wasn't she a
teacher also
foreign
[Music]
practice but I can't speak why is your
battle studies teacher here yeah that's
exactly what I'm asking
and the Pokemon gym working as an
instructor you ask well I have been
friends with a gym leader here two lips
since we were kids
[Music]
yo she reminds me
she reminds me her looks her design
reminds me of YouTube
we decided to have a Pokemon battle with
a special rule the loser has to do what
the winner says so we battled and well
[Music]
look never mind what happened point is
this is a chance to both get a workout
in and help my
but friends when I don't have classes
yeah the rules of emotional Spectrum
practice or ESP for short are simple
I'll show you a certain movement and all
you have to do is copy it
ready to get this gym test started I
hope your body and mind are ready for
the challenge
she's even got a Harry Potter score
sick
I'm ready is there no fighting involved
I was gonna exercise and show my
eruption of emotions uh-huh
what's up
what's what's going on
how how can I show emotions my
protagonist is emotionless what what
oh should I have done more
there's one okay
I'll just do a couple how many do I need
to do
once okay
just in case oh maybe the first one
really
[Music]
oh yeah
I mean if I press the wrong one do I
have to fight her
because normally there's always one way
to also involve battles
no
really
[Music]
you fight regardless
well I got them all right
easy
that was awesome I can't stop grading
after witnessing such perfect power of
expression that's enough of a warm-up
now let's really put those muscles to
work with a Pokemon battle all right all
right she's cute
oh her not you
letting the children work once again
[Music]
foreign
like it makes sense they're kind of in
terms of like shape and
style
so similar
[Music]
yeah
cute but bears and strong Pokemon
um
[Music]
I love my heart when you move both of
you and your Pokemon don't cry
I'm gonna get complaints if they see
that I made a little child cry great I
can hear your Pokemon and your muscles
screaming with the light I see you're
getting tired but you've got to hang in
there time to start the second hell
oh I can
[Music]
call somebody that made me angry all
those stupid Pokemon I bumped into today
it made me angry
[Music]
all right
all those shinies
is that the problems
how much longer
foreign
[Music]
please don't tell me we're doing it a
third time
y'all know the speed is fine for little
kids that was perfect I almost lost
track of who was teaching who don't give
up yet it's time for another battle hold
out against all that lactic acid
lactic acid what more goal is to grow
strong and build muscle any tips
uh start lifting
[Music]
trying to lift your pink looks very
heavy lift it 10 times in the morning 10
times in the evening
time
[Music]
I mean he looks just from his stance she
looks very healthy it doesn't look like
he has back problems
indeedy what the [\h__\h] is that I'll just
say
[Music]
uh
I just blindly pressed it
[Music]
uh
damn I don't think I have something
effective though I mean like super
effective
I'm 43 well
maybe die job
ah not very digable
you use call mind again
well second time is a big mistake I say
oh but it's making it special the price
while I'm raising my special attack well
that might uh even it fell out
ah
oh
[Music]
wow that was a strong hit
maybe it would have been worth
but I don't know what I would have used
oh well
um please tell me the next one is an
easy anime
[Music]
otherwise it's kind of embarrassing
meditam
and should I switch
[Music]
but what what would be effective
dark
I think supposed to spend with the ghost
okay
oh and yeah I got this special boost
[Music]
oh sick
okay I have enough of that now can we
end the test
am I done
first you passed the test no doubt about
it congratulations but you're not done
yet sprinter with the lobby stuff around
the double you have to report your
passing grade to formally finish the
test okay
thanks to school
she is cool
cool lady
I feel like a lot of girls would have a
girl crush on her
[Music]
crush on her hell yeah
sporks no sparks
[Music]
Peach Sparks snarl
uh oh I mean before I wanted to do that
but then you guys tell you I can just
ghost them
[Music]
foreign
I mean they may have you know a Pokemon
or Shadow Ball will be a problem
but we'll figure it out when the time
comes
[Music]
so here it goes the last
big battle for tonight
the last one that's a great feeling
oh my God she's so cute her dress I
suppose you're right okay I got things
moving here in my end
oh let's keep the tagline simple
naturally beautiful
what color too would you oh come on oh
my God she's such a diva such a
beautiful kid
Ney thanks your dog gotta run now chat
with you later
Mommy
hello there
your dress is flopping
oh my God
my new ocean is right here
I'm chilling at the gym leader here so I
must tell you that being a makeup artist
is my main line of work danger had
nothing but praise for you she said you
tell this late out there like holy girl
I'm absolutely amazed I wanted to meet
you you could be my soulmate I must say
you're a cute Challenger Kiowa but not
as cute and Flawless and gorgeous as me
obviously but you'll get there maybe I'm
sure my ESP exercise maybe all the more
beautiful doesn't that make you happy
because like you really needed it girl
you keep your Pokemon beautiful and
clean as well I see you have quite the
aesthetic sense especially because I see
you're falling over me so that makes a
lot of sense appearance is equally
important for both people and Pokemon
makeup is like magic anyone can use it
to change their appearance
allow me to put my skills to use to make
your cute little Pokemon even more
beautiful
I love you I love you you can do
anything to me
[Music]
I can only look at her oh
you're quite a good face test moment got
magic on what shall I use a new lipstick
lipstick lipstick lipstick put it on
your mouth first and then you know
direct transmission
my love alone
someone said torch songs because that
ride is my special effect I guess
oh what they have something super
effective against me
[Music]
where it doesn't work
you know
but the rest are fun
oh the bird that I have as well
[Music]
said oh wait faito is still in my team
above me
I understand
hello
I still think you're a robot Tony but
even if you tell me the French
it doesn't matter
[Music]
this week this is gone
I will
I wanted to rationalize but can I enter
wrestle as I'm gonna kill myself or is
that two different separate turns
am I faster than Gardevoir
um probably not probably not
[Music]
I'll do a Max potion
don't
spice is motivated the dog
[Music]
whoa
um
should I still do shell ball though
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
you're just as hard to get rid of as
kick a mascara I see I need a good
makeup remover oh I can I can recommend
you something for sure
[Music]
come here my little floor again it's
time for a makeover you'll become a new
you oh yeah right oh
ball
I forgot that she'll change into
something where it's effective than
anyone
oh wow
correct move
do you think so
wow wow
[Music]
maybe we can get enough it's a clumsy
right down to the tops of your floors
oh yeah my boys need some cleaning right
now
some deep cleansing
[Applause]
[Music]
but she has one more right
level up nice some free level ups that
was a lot of
EXP
ERT that was it
Oh I thought she had one more but how
did we kill four Pokemon so fast
discharge
[Music]
no
fake she's so cute I love her design oh
I think she blew me a kiss I think she
did
strength has a magic word that cannot be
washed away
[Music]
my lashes are so on fleek oh my God
of course you didn't hit me with moon
blast because
she didn't even get time for it
I lost the battle and your beauty Rivals
even my own I can't believe it gosh
fabulous you're quite fabulous yes
may I say Divine Exquisite I don't know
where I got that from perhaps I should
take you under my wing before you make a
big break elsewhere
I suppose I need to work on myself a
little more first before I run up and do
such a thing
gorgeous
she's gorgeous
her outfit you know those shoes those
legs
you have earned my gym badge allow me to
strike one of my best
guess let me let me get my camera let me
get my camera I'll
I'll capture it
perfectly it okay
that is not what I expected that is your
best pose
hey guys it's from that Pokemon that
does the same pose right I thought she
would do like a proper model pose hey
why not I wanted to stay or do a proper
model pose
she's so cute though
oh and she's little she's like perfectly
straight look at her how I'm wobbling
and she's perfectly straight is that a
is that gonna be a problem
[Laughter]
no
with seven Gym badges Pokemon of up to
level 55 will be easier to catch and
we'll listen to the commands you give
them
we train hard you'll be able to use this
move in a totally perfect way
like totally
toads
totally you know yeah don't go uploading
a selfie we just took to social media
okay if you wanna then I need to edit my
face first I know I'm Flawless even
without it but I think my makeup has run
a little with all the moving and
sweating I did during our battle
I need to fix it fast before my next
appointment my schedule is absolutely
packed you know I'm going to
um a Louis Vuitton showing next yeah
because they're actually choosing me as
their Ambassador for the next year yeah
I know you're jelly farewell then you
did splendidly today bye bye
oh
I love her
[Music]
why did you leave
hey oh why is the child so cute
sparkly eyes
who's that child is that your child
why is she so sparkly why is she so cute
can I adopt
hey hey Erika here at your service
these gyms really aren't giving you much
trouble aren't they
[Music]
all right you two haven't met happier
she is she one of the four have we
already met all four
who is The Sassy Lost Child
I'm ladies
don't call this
she's good with Pokemon even La Primera
has taken an interest in her but she's
so tiny
tiny dress as well she's kind of cute
but she's so [\h__\h] tiny she's like a
toddler oh wow
[Music]
oh
my I think Pokemon and team poppy a
really strong too
[Music]
which one of you is stronger do you
think
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
I want a belly four so I'm amazing
I hope that makes sense
Elaine baby
huh I mean it's funny
[Music]
now aren't you just adorable well the
other oh
maybe this is the child that I was
talking about from the other Elite Four
and she is the one that they all have to
babysit
but it's mainly that dude's child and
she's the one who made his hair and all
that
[Music]
I know it's hard to believe but this
tiny little one is indeed one of the
Elite Four yeah
I hope I get to show you my Pokemon soon
miss
so hurry up and come to Pokemon League
[Music]
Pokemon
battleing happen weapons
[Music]
and wait up boy
you keep up the good work you heard the
kid she's waiting for you
oh wait no puppy don't leave your power
Rica behind
[Music]
uh
um
she's like five
[Laughter]
interesting she must have already been
doing Pokemon battle battles when she
was still in her mother's womb
foreign
[Music]
probably her twin sister and that's why
she's not here with us
[Music]
oh man
let me visit my website
oh my God I think it's online let's go
all right let me prepare it
um
so before we start
Super Chat reading
let me show you
I mean there's not really anything to
watch yet I guess
[Music]
um I have to wait like two more hours
but no
I guess
um
[Music]
let's see um
how am I gonna show you this
tomato
[Music]
ES
there we go okay perfect perfect
preparing it
[Music]
thank you
I'll get rid of the
oh wait there's like two more Pokemon
just chilling there
we go
and the logo
okay
[Music]
here it is
Hollow Ian Advent calendar tap anywhere
to start you don't have to tap there you
don't have to be part of the system
tippity tap
with music
[Music]
I feel like there's something missing
though oh my God loud
[Music]
ah if it's too loud guys on the top
right here there's something for the
music volume
you can also turn off or turn on the
sound effects for when opening a door
and you can reset the open doors for
whatever reason
and what is this
oh credits and privacy policy wow so
professional
um
when you click there if it's the actual
day then it will open up
and you can then see the video also you
can move the site around like this if
you wanna
um I did just realize like notice that
this is there's something missing here I
think yo the icons
or is this like after I open a door what
my dear developer team
then we have the doors with the cute
icons
after I open oh okay
after you open the door this little
squares will look different apparently
wouldn't they appear after opening yeah
I don't know there's just like random
icons supposed to be everywhere but oh
well okay then I guess you see them
later for now this is what it is it's
snowing and there's music
Isn't it nice
it's simple but this is all all it
needed to be do you guys want to try to
crash it
can you click on yet no um maybe
actually maybe we should add like a
little
um maybe on the a little note maybe
under on the bottom of the house or so
that says uh
it will refresh at GMT according to gmt0
at midnight each day or something like
that we should probably have a sentence
like that here so that people know
or a countdown oh yeah could be even a
countdown because people will probably
be too lazy to look up GMT zero I wonder
can we add a count on you no we perhaps
are able to add a countdown
[Music]
okay okay we'll be doing that we'll be
adding that we can still make
improvements hmm okay by the way I'm
streaming in GM well I live in the GMT
plus one time zone maybe that gives you
a little bit of a reference reference
but in any case in two hours it's where
the first video will be supposedly
available
and even though normally my Advent
calendars only go to 24.
I noticed that American Advent calendars
and so on go to 25 so I figured okay I
guess we'll we'll make it go to 25.
um don't expect anything special on the
last day because I don't really have
a particular plan for the last day yet
as you know things are
kind of last minute
but yeah maybe I can arrange something
but um
definitely something
[Music]
somewhere I mean every day will be
special but maybe around the end there
will be something special
hehehe
but maybe not the 25th necessarily but
anyway you guys want to check it out
the URL
is
so the URL is let me copy paste and put
it in the chat
there it is hello en minus advent.com
check it out check it out I mean now
there's really nothing to see yet
[Laughter]
but you should come every day to see
who is that day's you know person in
charge messages
[Music]
foreign
it should work great everywhere
I'm gonna tweet it out yes I will I will
I will
no no no this is a hollow en only
whole life English only
I wanted something for us
looks great
which time will it change while we're
adding a countdown but it will change in
uh the video will be updated in two
hours
and uh then you know every day at that
time
so two hours from now every day
very simple and adorable yeah I mean
it's basically the best we could do in a
short time
um but I I think it's exactly what it
needs to be
and I wanted it to be this light blue
color because of uh the Holo live logo
yeah yeah yeah
foreign
if you look at the icon of your browser
for this website it's the cover logo
with a Santa hat
I want
when you double click you can
you can you can scroll out how small can
we make it this small how big can we
make it this big okay
[Music]
oh the logo was made in Powerpoint
come
[Music]
tweet about it and I'll maybe even make
a Reddit post after the stream is over
so then everybody knows about it and
checks it out hopefully
yeah so enjoy enjoy enjoy
[Music]
with the support of Kendall the
development
and then we have you know we got the
help from viva la Chiara website people
italics and Dominique
yeah
and I also got right right now illuna
you know the one who always makes my
videos my my song cover videos
to make the house
graphic
yeah because she can deliver fast I was
like who should I ask
um rhino
privacy Paul is very interesting
I need to sneeze kind of
[Music]
hey I hope everything will go smoothly I
hope there will be not too many delayed
videos
[Music]
um yeah right now isn't in the website
credits you have to add that
it's been missed
it's also a quick fix though
yeah all right ah let's move to my
office I feel like I should use the the
snow office soonish
I mean I can already use it
but it's not an updated version or so so
there's like some stuff kind of missing
in terms of singles and Hollow talk tips
and so on
probably get that updated soon also
sorry my throat really hurts so sorry
for
uh yeah talking
and not so energetic manner
it hooks
big Christmas tree but I have the small
Christmas tree it's nice too
foreign
thank you so much Kendall for like last
minute accepting my requests and and
believing in it with me I believed in
you like you know
a lot of people were like thank you mama
don't stress the developers then you
can't do it so fast but hey it was easy
then basically it was done in one day
yeah I believed in it because if you
know how to do it no it should be an
easy thing
I mean I don't understand everything in
terms of website creation and whatever
but I figured that this shouldn't be
like
too crazy quests
then the bigger problem was like really
having everything every everyone
um like deliver in time and everything
like
um how to say
harmonize with each other like the
planning the graphic the coding the
videos everything needed to be done just
so that everyone delivers on time
but
if yeah
just taking care of them
oh sure
oh my last team ah sync up yeah sync up
syncing up the whole team
YouTube notificated you notificated
notified you of this stream now
what the hell way too late
[Music]
oh God
I will read some super Chatters but
where do I need to continue namaste
just in time for the stupid child
reading I guess
stream her
like didn't she like uh say she was
gonna do an announcement did that
already happen what did she announce
was that today or tomorrow oh that was
today what did she announce
special two million celebration stream
oh
3D or what
not sure she just said 2 million
celebration stream
it's on her Twitter huh oh anyway good
for her nicely I was wondering what it
was I mean I had a hunch but it wasn't
that actually
yeah alrighty alrighty all right she
announced okay well it's cute why did
she announce that we already know
let me find some music
actually I could have just continued
playing that music on the website
because that's actually from my audio
stock folder
I was like use this this fits this is
perfect
but no how about some Christmas folk
music
remember this one
ah this could play at a winter village
in Pokemon
[Music]
where do we continue reading guys
I really don't remember
please tell me
[Music]
okay thank you
first should I tweet something out now I
kind of because like I already revealed
it
[Music]
or maybe I wait for the fixes and then I
tweet it out
[Music]
thank you
okay
I'll wait a little bit
[Music]
um
I'm reading these superchatos
money
[Music]
I feel like I haven't read your name in
a while with one two three four five
great super chats
thank you how you doing Felix
I haven't heard from you in a while I
hope you're healthy and happy
and living your best life but hopefully
your best life
um is with kiwawa don't forget to watch
my streams alright
hope you still are watching the streams
thank you so much for the big big red
Super Chat though
[Music]
what was it five that was five now it's
ten
thank you soon
and I see you are really excited about
the pickle talk
me too very much
the thing to be very excited about
[Music]
in a happy life even in smaller doses
well I would hope so always need
chihuahua in your life
oh
[Music]
sweet
so you are her
Grand
fan Grand
supporter grandpan
that is so weird I guess so
that's how you can talk yourself into
having some kind of connection to pecula
Senpai I guess
Grant chat grandless Nissan
that's how it works yeah that's how it
works yeah yeah yeah yeah so it's a real
thing it's legit
it's a thing it's a whole thing
time to thank you for the red super chat
hashtag horror talk thank you thank you
but that's not Twitter
hashtags don't work in the super chats
died so you have to go on Twitter and
write a tweet and then use the hashtag
it doesn't work like that but thank you
for the red super chat
wow
[Music]
foreign
yeah
what what
wait crap
[Music]
all right
so
still the same
you only remember Kiara you only respect
your own that makes sense
now even with the title it makes sense
2000 thank you for the recipe
finally it's happening at Last Rose I
mean cheer her up for us all Kiana good
for you
thank you very much I don't know did I
roast her maybe a little bit about the
monkey
besides that did I roast her
maybe I should have roasted her
oh
[Music]
but when talking directly to her even I
don't have the courage to do it maybe
but I feel like
um
especially before the stream we were
bantering and talking quite well with
one another I enjoyed that well
yeah yeah
I hope it was fun for her
[Music]
I hope that um I did her some just I
mean it's difficult as I said before you
can't really do her justice in a stream
like that
because there's just so much about her
but at least I think everybody who was
watching already knew what a great
Entertainer she is and didn't really
need to be told about it or need to be
convinced about it
we all already were aware of it
[Music]
don't need no one to tell us that
yeah
yes yes
[Music]
already one of my faves freakiana
good taste good taste
thank you very much
[Music]
fidget spinners
foreign
[Music]
although Thanksgiving is next week it's
a bit nostalgic to see this since two
years ago we got hinotori and that
Minecraft collab
when the Minecraft collapsed so close to
Thanksgiving
Minecraft
[Music]
one year ago where is the freaking date
oh there we go ah
it's
uh September middle of September 2021
I'm not so close to Thanksgiving but
[Music]
that's the one where I brought her to
the end server wait where's the one the
other way around
where is that stream
what was it called I can't find it it
doesn't come up
uh
it was cool
[Music]
I'm scrolling I'm scrolling I don't find
it
[Music]
oh
maybe they link the clips because I find
a lot of Clips but maybe they link those
oh there we go
a link to the original stream
two years ago oh November it was like
three days ago two years ago
that really was kind of on Thanksgiving
the 27th of November
oh
it is really like two years ago
[Laughter]
[Music]
I didn't realize wow long time ago
damn long time ago
damn
[Music]
thank you
if you think about it that's really long
two years man
time goes by so fast when you're in home
alive working your butt off every day
but
then you realize every day is a special
day with something special happens
hmm
don't have to cherish those moments
no thanks for reminding me soon
[Music]
I caught the elusive Pokemon
thankfulness if I wasn't elusive though
um
I mean actually I picked the
uh the thing that made it so easy to
catch her was that I told her that the
anniversary of holotalk was on that day
and I wanted her to be on holotalk
before that because I had merchandise
coming up where I needed 25 names on the
T-shirt I mean it could have been less
it could have been more but 25 made it
filled up the the row nicely
and I didn't want to like have a name
missing there
it's self a good balance
who said like in order to have your name
on there and for the merch to look
normal
I would need our whole talk to people
for that place any day is fine any day
doesn't have to be the weekend because
she did say that weekends are
um
not good for that she like has usually
like other plans
like long streams or so so we chose
Friday because of that but yeah the
merch was like I already asked her
before that you know
um but then you know the back and forth
was a bit slow
and we had troubles finding a date I
guess because of the back and forth
feeling so slow and then eventually I
said
[Music]
um
can we do it sometime before this date
please yeah and then easy and she
quickly said all right no problem let's
do it
um let's do it pickle
[Music]
and now her name is safely on my t-shirt
yeah I think it's really cool to have
all the hollow talk participant names on
there
um 25.
if you didn't get it yet the merchandise
is being sold right now
[Music]
um
I should put the link in my description
from my
YouTube videos
also I never tweeted it I never put it
on a community
um post right I should
put a community post up about it can you
guys remind me after the stream
on a tweet
oh yeah because it's not gonna be up for
eternity it's just a month probably I
think
I would have too so I could keep one
shirt smart
very smart like a Metallica tour dates
to your short Metallica that's exactly
it yeah yeah the tour dates that was my
um inspiration from bands and yeah
concert tours
no hey
[Music]
it's a nice memory for me and by the way
like
um I think I said this before like
normally I didn't really want to do mug
merchandise for my birthday or whatever
because I thought like Mug was kind of
like really basic merch that
a lot of other girls do I don't want to
do the same stuff you know so I didn't
want to do it but I felt the mug was
necessary and the reason why I just put
the logo on it and not to try to
recreate the mugs that were on my desk
in the whole talk Studio was not an
issue of like
um saving money or whatever it was just
I just felt like I didn't want to
recreate the mug I wanted the logo to be
on it I thought it would look good and I
do think it looks good
um
yeah I know it's simple but I like that
Simplicity of just the local being on
there yeah
um
[Music]
afraid to order mugs
well I I can't tell you how secure the
shipping is because I don't know and
it's also in the end it's always a RNG
kind of thing but I think they will
would be fine
yeah I think it works for the talk show
nature that's that's uh I agree with
that oh
[Music]
that's my reasoning
uh no no no no
um
on the diorama
I like that one too because normally
normally
um if it's just like
an acrylic figure alone I think that's a
bit boring
but with it being
like on a diorama of a background and
having several layers right
there's the background and there's the
guest and me and then in front there is
a logo and the spotlight
I hope that you guys can fit
um we didn't test it but it was my
desire that we would be able to fit
different
um
you know acrylic stands into the holes
into the gaps instead of chicken the
chicken is just a placeholder basically
but you can keep it there of course
um
let me see if it works and I want you
guys to show me
when the time comes when you get it
[Music]
excuse me I guess no no it doesn't mean
lightly but but you know the job of
holding a place is very very important
too
it's a very important Mission you're
basically the seed warmer for other
whole life members
where you stand later an idol from
hollow life will stand ah think about it
that way think about who you're holding
the place for
yeah and you're making it warm and cozy
for them
[Music]
and where was I I was done with that
um
[Music]
go get that merch please
please
[Music]
next door would be Pokemon Scarlet
episode one
[Music]
Scarlet episode one
oh where's the thumbnail
ah I think I think I kind of
accidentally saved it on a different
folder all right
where is it
I think I accidentally
[Music]
no it's not here
maybe here no where is it
oh yeah
where did I say that
I mean
maybe here
it is
[Music]
thank you guys focus on time thank you
I started playing Slender spy I finished
free characters and met the real boss
yesterday
huh
what do you mean don't I'm supposed to
finish four characters until you meet
the real boss it beat me real hard now
I'm trying struggling with the Watcher
but that knew about this great game from
you always hope you have a wonderful
time with your friend thank you and do
you not have to do all four
you don't need to do the Watcher what
yeah
ah but ah it never like
triggered for me until then because I
may have played them all but until
recently I didn't clear it
with the first character
it can't be anything it has to be the
first three
yeah
why not the Watcher
well Skye you'll figure it out you just
have to watch my stream of playing with
The Watcher and then you can learn from
it
[Music]
but it's also RNG with what cards you
get obviously and what relics you get I
did realize later on when playing
privately again and again that
I was just being very lucky oh it was
added later on oh I didn't know
[Music]
talking on stream and I got backseated
you know so
yeah
uh I wasn't actually that good at the
game
foreign
[Music]
so I told my friend you will probably 70
choose the cat and 30 for the duck today
now I want to go to the YouTube room my
friends will laugh near that well you
know the thing is I didn't even know the
final form from the crocodile would have
that fire verb I mean I did spoil on
myself about the looks of it but I
didn't notice the firebird I just
thought it looked cool and fire the
element itself makes sense for me
well if I would have known about the
firebird I think my choice back then
would have been much easier
and if you would have known that you
probably would have also
guessed that I would choose the
crocodile
but under the Hello song girls what are
you doing here under the assumption
and I also knew what I was doing
[Music]
well what are you doing here even though
I'm streaming you know normally you
don't say hello
what's what's up
see
you
you know
no
oh
who's cute you're cute you're cute cute
wakey wakey from the nap
are you wondering when does Mommy stop
when does mommy give chunky wonky some
people
oh yeah I'm giving you pizza
oh no you can come to me anytime even
when I'm streaming
no oh
barely scratchy and it's good good very
scratch
you know she will start purring even
when I just look at her it's so cute
but the moment I look away
she stops purring
but I'm I'm
scratching her belly she loves it
you know
but the mic won't pick up the purring
unless I
put her snoot literally right in front
of the microphone
[Music]
you
know
I love you I love you Bubble Pop
should I get a cat too bus what kind of
question is that of course
you should it makes you so happy
oh she's so soft
she's such a good baby
it's way more
well-behaved dance movie who is a cheeky
cheeky little [\h__\h]
y'all oh she's letting me scratch her
and pet her a lot
she's not trying to escape just yet
yeah
I don't have room for a cat then you
make room for cat how about you move out
and let the cat live there
and you be the pet
hmm
exactly
thank you
if only it was so easy well I mean
I mean probably still relatively young
so there's still time you can eventually
move somewhere bigger and have a cattle
then cats don't need like
I mean if we're speaking European
um
[Music]
what's the word
European standards
then
even when you live alone in a smaller
apartment for European standards you can
still keep a cat
we want to go
I can let you go I guess
it's not like you're aggressively
fighting for your Escape you're just
chilling but okay I'll let you go here
there you go bye bye
so much hair dear Lord
so much hair
it's like a mommy stump yeah
bye bye
yeah
see you later chunky wonky
um
but yeah
you need to get a cat everybody needs to
get a cat
but you know that
if you want to be happy if you want to
cure your your
um
espresso depresso get a cat
or a dog dog is okay
or any pet really but cat is best
recommendable very much
scored four four zero donations
[Music]
um
oh we typos the calendar
that's oh it's probably because both
Dinah and me are
[Music]
what
why don't say it because now people will
look at it
that is really oh yeah it's related
that's because yeah
um
in in German
[Music]
and Germany's calendar with ER
and I may have asked Lina to write that
maybe
[Music]
and she probably didn't know this
I always misspell calendar really
and that's a little bit embarrassing
thank God I didn't tweet it out that yet
this was a soft launch okay yeah yeah
yeah
soft launch
don't think calendar was oh my God I I
can totally see myself if I would have
gone for long Colo Ian Advent
calendar.com or so
I totally see myself writing a typo and
purchasing that URL
if you purchase a URL you can't change
it anymore can you
I wonder I didn't see an option to
change it but
I wonder
foreign
[Music]
number one oh man oh by the way I bought
it for 12 months because that's the
minimum
but it was pretty cheap
that's my first time I bought a URL I
didn't know it was so easy
stream hard calendar
[Music]
yeah yeah
it will be for next year I don't know um
I was told you know
um if there was more time and so if I
would have come up with the idea earlier
then we could have done it through the
company and have them like organize it
and so on so if anything next year I
will not do it myself anymore I will
have the company take care of it and
then it will also be probably most
likely through their pockets not mine
um but uh yeah I'll take advantage of
that so it's fine within 12 months the
domain doesn't work anymore I mean we're
probably gonna take down the website
anyway even if the domain is still
um working I think once uh December is
over I think we will get rid of the
website
yeah because then it has no use
so the snare
um
makes sense right and a black virgin
Nations
[Music]
and thank you for fighting
all these battles so seriously they're
real help
Tacoma is
MVP
one of my MVPs definitely proud I feel
like I used Tacoma even more than my
starter in the past two streams
because dakuma has like so much
variation man
so many different ways of using dakuma
so useful
oh yeah yeah I'm thinking about changing
the nature I guess
Patrick's Marini dances
[Music]
Frederick's Marini Duncan thank you
Lord
thank you for the pinky your librarian
research mnemonics oh I read this
already a device such as a pattern of
letters ideas or associations that
assist in Remembering something the
alphabet song as an example I remember
the super trap I don't remember how we
got to that uh talk though
hmm
my name is
[Music]
said something oh
black virgin conditions
[Music]
foreign
use my voice anymore
Chihuahua voice dying and we have a
well can we have um
can we bury my voice on in the ground
and then say
thank you for everything on rip
dancer for all you've done
[Music]
yeah goodbye goodbye
a jewelry for my brother
funeral for my boys let's go funeral for
my throat let's go
all right
don't go I heard you
hmm from the distance well
um and hi
and one hour and 20 minutes
and you can check the left side again
some fixes should have been made by then
and
um
some pictures should have been made by
the end and and and and and and then the
video the first one who do you think
will be the first video
[Music]
who will be the person don't tell the
others though because then they won't
even watch it we need to keep it a
mystery
give them give them the hope that it
will be someone else
[Music]
why is she so curious will you miss me I
think she misses me chunky monkey
ah
[Music]
May 2023
yeah probably around that time
no it will not be a Rick Roll with all
that Twitter can't wait out um well yeah
probably they'll they should maybe they
forget to do it right away but I'll tell
them hey
yes yes
all right and I'll see you tomorrow for
Minecraft I will stream too there will
be two povs I'm pretty sure
yeah so um
let's play some Minecraft tomorrow
it's been a while
we play Minecraft with fun
hopefully I can be useful
me
I'm gonna smash some skeletons and take
rip off their heads
and put them somewhere else
[Music]
I will do my best
since you have her mouth
heresy
well you have to have two two windows
open though
soy sauce
it will be probably shitty time for sea
I'm sorry
[Music]
um
see you there okay
[Music]
very much did you see the shorts I made
I thought it was so funny you know I
made it with some stupid fonts and and
then I said there will be square and
when I said Square I made myself into a
square
did you say that did you say that
my short
[Music]
s
I need to make one more short for the
YouTube music weekend thingy one more
and even even afterwards this fine I was
told there's a deadline but I need to
make like a minimum of two shorts
and the trailer and the the video itself
it's quite a lot to make for that I
don't know what to do for another short
I probably will just cut up the singing
I don't know what else I would do and
make it into like an after trailer but
as a short basically
[Music]
I guess like I can't think of anything
else to do
[Music]
so this now I'll eat the remains of the
quick dinner I made last night what
when by the way who um when I was making
hello
meals a while ago that person always had
the same recipes and was like hey I had
to save when I made this and showed me a
picture of what they made
I'll cancel your subscription a lot
what was that was that funk
yo [\h__\h] did you cancel
so you're trying to win
[Music]
huh
I did that sometimes yeah are you still
my eyes still cooking from Hello beef
or have you stopped eating entirely
it was meow
which one of you was it was both of you
well meow canceled it apparently it was
too expensive yeah it's kind of
expensive for free meals a week 45 Euro
I don't know man I feel like I could buy
it cheaper if I buy it fresh but at
least I guess this way I don't have to
think I don't have to use my brain
a fact that you cancel it too I want to
see what you're cooking when you get the
same recipe as me
it was interesting to see like it was
fun because there's so many recipes you
can choose from and I felt you know a
little connection when we chose the same
things
yeah and then I wanted to see how you
did it in comparison to me yeah compare
execution exactly
you pause it this way wow
but you'll resume okay
okay
[Music]
it's like we're eating dinner together
and we're cooking together
[Music]
cute
but honestly I you know I put all the
recipes I get in a drawer they're like
on a really a pretty thick paper A4
um and I put them on in the drawer and
like the other day I took them out and
holy [\h__\h] it's so many by now I can
literally make a cookbook
out of it or I could just cancel it and
like cook those things over and over and
over again but I do like you know the
this like that they just sent the
perfect amount like especially when it
comes to raw meat
when I look at the
um raw meat section in the supermarket
they never sell those amounts they
always sell way more and
you know then I have to make more words
freeze the rest and I just don't kind of
like that
I don't like doing that
if I if I cook more than I have to do
math to
more
of the ingredients actually no never
mind the recipe is actually they always
say for two people for four people and
for six people I think they already
write it down for me but still
but still do you have a butcher no
no
I guess I need to find the butcher who
cuts me exactly what I want but I
haven't when I was a child and I grew up
in a smaller City
I remember going to the butcher a lot
uh
but ever since then I I never see
butcher stores maybe they don't have
many anymore
now that you say it
I don't remember butcher stores Much
Anymore recently
I don't have many left in the U.S yeah
maybe there a lot of them are just like
integrated into the supermarkets now
but back then it was also in the
supermarket as well
oh no
rather expensive but high quality meat
um
they should still be around I'm just I
guess in the wrong place all the time
[Music]
um
maybe you're just lucky I don't know
maybe you were just lucky for having one
close to you
[Music]
but yeah so I guess
I have more than enough recipes
uh yeah maybe sometime next year I
cancel my subscription
and I should probably
um
yeah start doing it
You Know Myself
by the ingredients myself
yeah I guess because it's gonna end up
being cheaper
I think 45 you will quite expensive for
free meals but I mean it's kind of six
meals most of the time it's kind of six
meals because
for six meals yeah
maybe it's not that expensive I don't
know anymore I don't know I don't know
is that
because it's two people always two
portions two servings sometimes
depending on what it is like if it's a
meal with like some like a pork fillet
then the pork fillets are usually pretty
small and unsatisfyingly small and then
yeah just for two people but even for
two people like for me it's okay I don't
need like a huge chunk of meat but I
think a lot of people would be very very
unhappy with the amount of meat they
give you but if it's a non-meat meal
then often I can go for with it for
three days sometimes sometimes
but definitely easily for two days
20 Euro for entire weight that's why I
cut what you spent 20 Euro my minimum is
45 what the [\h__\h]
unfortunately one meal too
yeah meat tomato
or a guy you say six foot six foot
I don't know how much it is a meter but
my brother I told you he ate all of that
in one day but maybe he ate it for lunch
and dinner I wonder that would make
sense
[Music]
ah you mean groceries oh yeah okay yeah
yeah yeah
you can probably get the ingredients
cheaper
um
and 45 Euro yeah
oh for all free recipes yeah yeah
okay anyway I'm gonna go
um one one hour and nine minutes until
the page launches for real those
oh also oh
no Ian
oh update the site guys
if you look at it again the video is not
there yet but there's some icons they
don't tell you what's behind it but
they're just some decoration
foreign
I think everything is better when they
show before you open the door so it
looks not so Bland especially in the
beginning
yeah look look cute symbols apparently
yeah this might make you think that the
first door is Kawaii primary
[Music]
no it's a random
random decoration guys
don't get fooled
thrift stores you know no no no no no
it's random it's random
it's just decoration
yeah yeah
oh it's still calendar yeah well that is
um something that's
will be fixed till soonish
[Music]
see you tomorrow
thank you
[Music]
foreign
yeah
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no one two three
four five
[Music]
hello hello
foreign
[Music]