[Music]
do
so
[Music]
yay
welcome back
once again
to the iron bead stream
[Music]
i have that mat too oh where did you get
it from how come we have matching ones
how does that look
amazing
[Music]
welcome welcome once again i am wearing
beautiful gloves
yeah i don't know why why this finger
is so
chunky
weird it's the the way they
the way they sue it look something's
wrong here
oh well
okay
[Music]
welcome welcome
like i keep on trying to yawn fully but
i always kind of like interrupt myself
it's weird i can't do a full big yawn
you know what i mean
that feels like so
unsatisfying
anyway
you like the music and the pgm i found
it on audio stock and when i when i
heard it i felt like it sounded a little
bit like as if it's out of tales of
symphonia or so like any tales-off game
or the earlier
the earlier tails off games
[Music]
oh yeah like when you're in a village or
something like that
[Music]
it's a bit low okay no problem
i'm raising it a little bit
[Music]
you can't get it right god damn it
yeah it's very chill very calm right
he can't see this net
economy
so today
we'll once again do some stuff with iron
beads but this time
look what i got
i bought some new
um
what would i call them boards or some
new
bases to work with and there they are uh
white they're not see-through anymore
yay so i don't have to worry too much or
stress out too much about reflections
isn't that nice
[Music]
i'm so sorry i had to
fix something okay
okay now now maybe i'm looking
relatively straightforward
because i i you know i'm using my side
table
so i'm looking into a completely
different direction than usual but i
think it works fine
so
uh
what we did last time if you recall
was we made this
little
cute
rain
could think that's good
it turned out
pretty damn good i would say
oh focus perhaps no you don't wanna
really
maybe this focus oh see there's a little
cat's hair on it why is it so bright
what the [\h__\h]
being so bright
hello
okay the webcam is a bit confused
but it's it's got the spirit
i think
does it
maybe not
oh i turned up on the focus last time oh
no but see it is kind of doing autofocus
it resets the settings i guess
it's doing something
anyway
yeah
i think
and this time
what i want to make is let me move this
little bit over here
this time
[Music]
i want to make sure
yay
very colorful
um for this i think my
second
box will come in handy like you know
these ones have pretty normal colors but
then this one has some shiny
um and also super colors i think you
know here we will find some good colors
for the for the t-shirt and for the eyes
and the light blues are also going to be
good for
super duper's outfit
so bright colors bright vibrant colors
for super duper senpai
i have an entire arsenal yeah i have
many many many iron beads
and i i wonder if i'll ever use all of
them up probably not maybe i should like
when i'm done with them when i feel like
i'm not going to use them anymore maybe
i'll donate them to a school or
something
just bring them to my old school
on my old school is far far
far away but yeah
um
they're basically infinite yeah i don't
i don't think ever anyone although maybe
maybe there are people who use up all of
their iron beads
um i got too many meditations
man my mama so
a beautiful dayne
will accompany us
maybe she will bring us some luck
today i'll leave her here so this should
be
enough space if i if i start down here
then i can make sure to stand by
around in around this area should be the
same size
ah so
yeah that's what we're gonna do of
course today also
uh baby run
that was the name i gave it right baby
ron is here too
baby run everyone say hello hi
baby dawn
tiny baby dawn
bubble dog baboon was the name bubble
bubble
bubble bubble iron
japanese bro said
uh the that big slide of super duty
reminded them a little bit of uh ness
from
mother
yeah and i only know them from super
smash brothers but
i agree kind of
[Music]
oh yes
so
um today
i want to finish before
like 9 00 pm if possible
[Music]
because i know my mom's gonna
um come um to visit me
and stay over
uh in the evening so
um i gotta get down before that i don't
know last time what did it take us like
three hours to make uh reyna
but not but i did uh the keyboard
reveal and all that which i'm using
now
nowadays i'm using that keyboard and i
did the snack review and all that so
that took up some time too
so
i'm hoping we can get sobado and the
chicken done that would be amazing
[Music]
oh god
i'm also experienced now
yeah i know a little bit more of what
i'm doing i guess
um
all right shall we get started i guess
hajime
so
the colors we need
whatever i'll figure them out um while
we're doing it we're going to start with
you know
outlines again with the black
oh wait a second do these even fit i
didn't test it out i hope
oh
wow okay they barely
look at this
because i bought them separately what
happens is they
you see this
they they i guess it works because they
don't fall off
if you like
squeeze them onto
the surface but you see how it's barely
on it
[Music]
i thought they were like
i thought iron beads are like kind of
i have to
say
like always like everywhere just about
the same size because like don't you mix
and match and so on you know if you want
to get new colors and so on
you would hope yeah universal that's the
word i was looking for i would hope they
were universal uniforms standard sized
oh well it works it doesn't go as deep
as the other ones but actually it's fine
it doesn't really move
it just doesn't feel like i really
put it
in there properly
oh [\h__\h] there they go where did that one
go i don't know
already lost one of our companions
um
i gotta be a bit careful
because they don't just
plop on there
[Music]
wait they're so far apart
wait a second look they're so far apart
wait why why are they so far apart
oh
[Music]
these are supposed to be used with much
bigger iron beads or what
oh are you [\h__\h] kidding me
could chicano size it
like that's not gonna work
that's not gonna work
oh come on
yeah they're they're completely
different
oh mama mia okay then i guess i'm not
using that today after all oh [\h__\h] i
thought i was prepared
but i guess i wasn't
scouting
[Music]
okay quinoa
help me please
help me
[Music]
oh dear okay
oh why why why why
oh no my social security number is in
the reflection
that's not good
why is it even worse than last time
ah
[Music]
saw my credit card number
okay
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
okay
okay number one
[Music]
the hat
no i tried with
i tried with
putting like white paper black paper all
kinds of papers
underneath but um my result was the best
was if there's something with mixed
colors underneath
um okay you know what
i'm gonna wear
a mask this time i don't know why it's
worse than last time
[Music]
yeah it's the top that's reflective
oh [\h__\h] you know my father had it all
figured out
oh god
the [\h__\h]
okay why did i choose this mask it's
kind of hot but yeah you will not be um
oh
yeah you want it was impressive how my
mouth is still a little bit moving how
is that possible
okay now
whatever you see is not what you think
you see
i don't even know what i'm seeing
oh god it's so oh it's so oh this one
you know this one is out of fabric let
me get my one out of paper
that one
that one came with cat hairs
[Music]
do
okay i'm back i'm back
i was just discussing the best course of
action with
[Music]
did you hear her did you hear our
arguments
[Music]
hi oh no she's entered the room don't
don't come here
don't come here chunky wonky
[Music]
okay
wow
[Music]
last time you were a good girl so this
time you're hopefully gonna be a good
girl too right
you better leave the room
okay
christina
so uh
yeah that's fine
that's fine it's fine it's fine
okay so
also if my hand's gonna be on top of it
most of the time it's gonna be fine um
let's start again
oh all right let me take the ones from
the other porch i got bamboozled there's
bigger
bigger iron beads than that yo
what
i remember there being different sizes
when i was younger also wait my hello oh
it doesn't it doesn't seem
here's my my face is here okay
oh [\h__\h] doesn't even recognize my
my face as a face well that should be a
good disguise
10 to 10 disguise
[Music]
um oh hello my face is here yeah okay
okay good
okay
[Music]
uh
come on mommy i'm just gonna
oh yeah if i hold my hand like
like this in front of it
i'll just eventually get a cramp
oh
it helps it helps okay so how many do we
have at the bottom
um
no no trust me i've tried a lot of
things
um
it's okay
some things
i mean in the end what would you see you
would see someone with orange hair and
purple eyes
[Music]
you know and no nose
so there's nothing new nothing new that
you could see
one two three four five six seven seven
one two three four five six seven you
make me feel like eleven
uh one two three four five
it's all good don't worry
okay so we got the first row hooray
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah that's all you could see wait you
know what if i hold my hand like that
then oh no yeah okay
um much better
uh second row is black white white black
white white black okay
i wanted to tell you guys
about the dream i had last night
don't worry it was not
a
a nightmare
i shouldn't start from the left side
it was not a nightmare this time but it
was very interesting
um
so this was just a small part
of a big dream i guess
but
um this is the thing i remember the most
because i woke up in the middle of the
night and i'm like
what
so
part of my dream was like i was
somewhere in the park or something
and
um
suddenly i see
the actor
of
none other
than mr bean
i don't know his name but i saw the
actor
just
standing there being crowded overcrowded
with people like a lot of people
standing there
um oh rowan atkinson oh cool name he's
got a sick name
yeah people were like standing around
him
trying to get
pictures and autographs and i was like
i was i was like just
i wanted to just mind my own business
because i knew
like hey
i'm i'm kind of famous too if people if
like 50 people ask me for a picture and
like he must be
so used to it
being
like
always
like you know
have always having so many people around
you being like mr b mr b mr b miss me
please please because i have a picture
of you
you know he must be used to paparazzi
and more than me because you know
i don't go outside
so i didn't quite wanna ask for a
picture but
[Music]
this sounds like it could be a real
story
i didn't quite wanna ask for a picture
but um
then
i got closer because i had to walk past
them
and
then i was like okay you know what if i
get a selfie with mr bean
and upload that on twitter
people are gonna freak out you're gonna
love it it's gonna be a good story for
my stream that was literally what i was
thinking inside my dream
[Laughter]
it would be good
for telling it on stream
it's such a dream a streamer youtuber
mindset oh my god
for the tangents yeah
so
i went up to him
and i said
mr b mr bean i'm so so sorry um
would you mind
and then
before i could even finish my sentence
before i could even properly ask him
he
suddenly he was like
yeah give me a second then he walks away
and then he comes back
and
he shows me
a big ass collection
um
[Music]
a certain way let me
let me one second
i need to
check something
[Music]
okay
who is it
i think
gosh now my memories in my brain are
getting
mixed up
so weird
yeah it's
time to be continued no no no no no i'm
gonna continue immediately don't worry
[Music]
okay what's up
he shows me
a big collection of
merchandise of
[Music]
a certain youtuber
but
you know how
sometimes in your dreams
you
like
some things just don't make quite sense
but the the collection no no no it
wasn't even whole live the collection of
youtuber
merchandise that he showed me seems to
be
of a youtuber that's kind of the
combination
of
um
two people from niji sanji yen
no no it was like
milly and anna combined into one person
for some reason
that's that's what my
my
my consciousness was able to
perceive
and yeah he seemed to be like an
insanely big fan of them he had a [\h__\h]
set of merchandise and then there was
there was one one
one piece of merchandise of takanasi
kiara that was more like he only had it
because it was like a set purchase
[Music]
yeah
and that was and i brought it because i
have it because this wasn't my dream it
was this
this acrylic stand
is what
he showed me because he had it as a set
he was like wait so
you know i'm a fan of youtubers
not necessarily of you but i do have
this this you
so when i asked him for selfie he
recognized me and then showed me his
whole collection he's like is this you
this is you right and i'm like oh what
the [\h__\h] mr bean watches youtubers
mr bean
watches youtubers
oh man
i was i was so surprised
but
i don't really
remember what happened after that
i think we took a selfie and then
we went our ways and i continued
dreaming about the weirdest things ever
yeah anyway that merchant as you just
saw is not official
um whole live merchandise but it was
like a couple of artists
getting together like last year
to make um wedding dress versions of
holo myth and i don't know was there
others too
i feel like there might have been others
besides
uh besides the um myth members but yeah
i don't know if it's still on sale
but like each artist was assigned
a different
um
member to draw in a in a like kind of
wedding attire
um
there's nothing wrong with watching
beaches yeah but like out of old people
mr bean
i was shocked
i was absolutely shocked
so confused
but but that just shows you
how popular youtubers are now you never
know who's watching
when you never know who could be
watching the streams
um is that the same
i use a different ramp down there why
did i actually it does look it does look
like a
is it a darker red it somehow looks a
little bit darker to me than the one
above
in the
in the reference
what do you guys think
it is different right are my eyes
teasing me or is it really so it's
really still
[Music]
what science what
sign
sanford probably apologized after msb
movie watch along what when
oh
yeah
is it because the guy from seinfeld um
voices the b movie
[Music]
i understand the connection is that it
they are different okay good
[Music]
oh yeah okay you guys probably told me
that before
[Music]
but i don't think the other thing about
the apology is true
no no
no
[Music]
this
mr bean like even japanese people know
mr bean mr being so famous wow
i met such a famous person
on my in my dream
yeah it was a dream it sounds so it
sounds relatively realistic
like it's not as crazy as other dreams
it sounds surprisingly realistic also
i'm like speeding fruitis i feel like
wow
too bad that was kind of the only
tangent i have for today
oh what other
what other tangents do i have
i can't really think of anything i think
i've used it up on in my coat of the
lamb
and my other streams this week [\h__\h]
but um
i can tell you that today
i slept so much i was gonna wake up
relatively early
to clean my apartment
to get it ready for
um my mom's visit although she doesn't
really care i think but you know just
half half half decent
get it into a half decent state i did
sleep well yeah it was a funny dream
but i did sleep well and like i was i
wanted to wake up at a certain time and
then i woke up and i was like nah you
know what i'm still tired my stream
isn't until later why would i force
myself to
to sleep
uh to no to wake up so
early it's not necessary
so i continue sleeping
and my consciousness woke me up
kindly
like one hour later and then i was i was
gonna wake up but then for some reason i
fell asleep again and continue sleeping
like you know sleeping sleeping beauty
someone has to give me a kiss to wake up
it's going so well
spun so well tangenting while doing this
is really helpful
last time i had to focus more but this
time
it's working out quite well now we go
with the fancy
colors fancy neon colors i'm glad i get
to use them
[Music]
what was i saying oh yeah so i finally
woke up like
i'm not gonna say what exactly because
then the people are to be like thank you
see you sleep healthy i'm an adult
i sleep when i want to
i'm not part of your system
um
but i woke up not as early as i wanted
to and then i i i speed ran i rta'ed
cleaning my apartment and i was
surprised at how fast
i can do it
[Music]
yeah
i found my sleep schedule on the ground
uh
[Music]
now
and i did some
proper cleaning i threw out a lot of
cardboard
and trash and
[\h__\h] in my fridge that shouldn't be in
there anymore
and
i did my laundry
[Music]
my laundry did the dishes
and vacuum cleaned
and
and of course
brushed my cat
yeah i just didn't have much breakfast
but
but when my mom comes later maybe we're
gonna cook together some hello fresh
stuff because i still i have a lot
tomorrow she wants to make
uh tonkatsu for me
hopefully hiragatsu tomorrow she wants
to make that for me because i keep on
keep on talking about it on stream and
she's listening not listening now
probably but she's generally listening a
lot to my streams
no stream tomorrow that's right i have a
feeling although she didn't tell me but
i haven't have a feeling she wants to
sleep over for two nights
tonight and tomorrow
so
um i probably
will put up a schedule monday night
monday evening
um
but yeah
uh tomorrow no stream
and
you will see you'll see oh we'll see
where am i
[Music]
man this this music makes me really want
to play a tesla symphony too
hmm
maybe we should stream it i know you
guys don't necessarily like um like the
ones who did play it say it's not
not as good
as others but
it's a continuation of the first hands
off game i played oh that's the wrong
color oopsie
so kind of
i always wanted to play it
was my first what why would you play
symphonia 2 as your first in the series
this berry is still my favorite this
very is great but i already played that
one so
um i don't know about streaming it you
know i don't want to play i want to
stream games that i've already oh no
more blue right i'm done with blue
i've already played before
yeah knight of ratata or something like
that right that was the name i think
[Music]
my first chance game was tales of
fantasia on the snes wow respect
y'all
a tales of fan friend
welcome welcome
i started out a little bit later than
you
hails of fantasia i still need to check
out that that's obviously a
[Music]
i know people
love tales of fantasia
and
praise it to heavens
oh that color
i don't really have
a color uh i guess this could work this
one could work
that [\h__\h] that's the closest i can
get um
[Music]
i should make a tails off game's
personal tier list
but man
would be hard too
[Music]
they're all so good also it's been a
while since i've played a lot of them
is this one correct
[Music]
i have really bad memory
really bad memory
combat didn't really age well
uh uh really
really
of ambassador yeah remember i'm tales of
ambassador yeah
that's right
that's right baby
[Music]
[\h__\h]
you forgot how could you forget
[Music]
n e s or s n e s game i don't know how
to capture them also
i just got a what was it called again a
wii u
for streaming zelda
wind waker
uh
and it was actually kind of a pain in
the ass to get that one
because that was because you couldn't
buy it so i had to
look
for
um
used ones
[Music]
it was kind of a pain in the ass i don't
know about sc snes are they are they
like um expensive now because they're
kind of like
like so
nostalgic
and rare
are they i wonder
[Music]
not too expensive all retro games are
expensive now
oh they made a ton oh
they're expensive in the us but not in
japan oh
so if i buy one i should probably buy it
in japan i'm sure super saiyan but i
would oopsie
would know where to buy them because
when i visited that super saiyan boy
before
she
she had she had a lot of really old
um
consoles
lined
up i know who to ask
okay
so far so good
how many more rows is this gonna go
three one okay
one on top of three
all right
[Music]
coronet yeah yeah
bye too but i don't really
have
any connection with corona senpai
ah
someone stole my snes like 12 years ago
what the [\h__\h] what 12 years ago
12 years ago
was it so desirable 12 years ago
i feel like now it's more desirable than
like five years ago
people are getting more and more into
gaming
[Music]
that's a tragedy
do
[Music]
is it no fallout boy wait which one was
it
look at the disco fallout boy
they have like
a similar style i guess
i had a similar audience of of edgy
teenage girls like me
uh
ah the good old days
[Music]
one more row
one two three four one okay
one two three four
no i was not seeing things for the
memories i think that's a different song
[Music]
are you really angry well not anymore
i used to be oh so edgy no not really
i mean i i i was
i was dreaming to be edgy
[Music]
oh when my mom comes and she sees my my
balcony plants being so [\h__\h] dead
she's gonna be so sad
she helped me set them up but what can
you do it's not really my fault
i tried my best to keep them alive
i really tried
[Music]
impending judgment from my mom
eh i know i i know what went wrong kind
of
it was not the cat's fault no
of course not
i'm gonna get a lecture about gardening
no no no well at the time when it
happened you know i showed my mom and
i'm like mom this happened and
she wasn't mad or anything she's just oh
man this is too bad
so sad but i wonder if maybe now i can
replace everything with
something
something anything that would grow
um in in winter but uh unlike there is
such a thing
[Music]
balcony plants that
grow in winter
are there any experts in mogu's
nettles oh
[Music]
nothing comes to mind
aloe vera
yeah but cacti is not an outside plant
and i don't think aloe vera is either i
don't think they
that doesn't sound like they want to be
outside in the cold winter in austria
[Music]
we're we're talking about outside plants
guys
[Music]
snake plant
oh well native plants
oh well well well
i'll i'll discuss it with my mommy see
what she has to say because now my
balcony just looks very very
sad
depressing
like a while ago when everything else
was already dying in the balcony and
planned planter
um those disgusting mushrooms came back
again they keep on like
saying hello and then immediately they
say bye bye
they start growing
like three or four
of those mushrooms and then within like
one week they already die and
yeah
fall apart
those mushrooms are really
really short-lived
i wouldn't eat them though they're not
supposed to be in there anyway it's not
like i put them in there they just kind
of came with the soil
no they're not bad for the plasto my mom
said it's fine it's fine they don't take
up much space either they're just
they're just chilling they say hi and
they say bye
that's it it's all good
um
[Music]
okay
yeah
not bad
lower body almost done lower body i say
lower body and like in terms of
if we speak in chibi
chibi proportions
then the head
is the head and the everything below the
head is lower body basically
[Music]
the head is the head
where am i now okay here
[Music]
a white one
oh you know tonight
tonight at like around 4
4 30 or something
austria
or stream time
new episode of house of the dragon is
coming out
no no i'm thinking
[Music]
should i watch it together with mommy
oh no
not not at four in the morning obviously
but
after we wake up
she didn't dislike house of the dragon
so
we could watch it but it might be
awkward
i would feel awkward watching house of
the dragon
with anyone pretty much just just the
last um the
finale of lord and lord of the rings the
finale of
game of thrones
i didn't feel so awkward watching with
my friends because it didn't have any
intercourse
at least not no wait did it
not that i remember
did the last episode have intercourse
i think it was just a war
[Music]
well stop saying intercourse well that's
something i'm supposed to say
i thought that was the most
non-sensitive way of saying it
ah
[Music]
okay
oh
interesting
interesting it's uh
oh
[Music]
woohoo oh like in the sims
was there any woo hoo
the last episode of game of thrones
awesome
something sounds wrong
[Music]
that sounds like i'm like five years old
okay not really i guess five years old
wouldn't say woohoo either
[Music]
huh
okay now i kind of ran out of tangents
you guys helped me what should i talk
about
what do you want me to talk about
have any any questions
[Music]
oh
i'm not going to talk about woohoo
uh horrible cure
what should i say i'm playing hodokyo
early next week earlier than everybody
else
[Music]
oh yes yesterday i watched um
a youtuber's stream
because like somebody sent me a link
in the middle of the night saying and
this feature is currently studying your
voice
and then
i was watching it for a while and then i
made one comment and suddenly
for whatever reason
how
how that is how that is possible
no one will ever know but suddenly you
guys started showing up some of you guys
suddenly
[Music]
yeah
where did you guys come from huh
how'd you find
[Music]
me must have some alert whenever i
comment in
someone's chat
interesting
yeah yeah so um
the youtuber's name was ophelia
and holy moly she was talking so
[Music]
so professionally about
how how
voices work and and all that it was
really interesting
she also tried
studying and and imitating
hecola's empire's voice and coroner's
empire's
and so on she has like several streams
like that
she's so good at all of them which is so
funny because her her normal voice
is pretty low
and suddenly suddenly she brings out an
absolutely perfect pickled allison boy
oh
oh and she also did like a really good
friend rasher and
when i heard her make an imitation of
fran drescher
um it was i said yo that really reminds
me it really sounds a lot like um
what's your name janice from friends you
know the one that always goes after
chandler
and then she i requested her making to
make an imitation of janice and it was
really good
oh my god
she looks kind of like that
isn't she
no it's a [\h__\h]
i don't know
oh my god
[Music]
but yeah that really caught my interest
that was uh
fascinating
[Music]
i'm dolphin
she's a dolphin
she is a dolphin
you know my hands starting to hurt by
holding it like this but it helps
[Music]
yeah you should check her out
really talented
i didn't watch too much of the stream
where she tried to study my voice i i
need to watch like the vods to see to
see how well she ended up doing
she was also kind of like studying the
accent and so on too
my accent
one accent
[Music]
oh yeah okay
if you use an older clip of the
phonetics of your pronunciation it was
pretty cool
[Music]
i was wondering if i ever get sick maybe
i can hire her
to um
speak
or like me i wonder you guys will
probably notice
would you
is this the real kiwa or the fake kiwamo
[Music]
probably if it's just a few words
you wouldn't notice but if it's a whole
stream you would probably notice
[Music]
okay
hydration time
[Music]
oh yeah personality is also a thing
for a whole stream like an hour or so
you'd even have to imitate the
personality
but if something like you know buying
senpai uh you know the situation where
she had canada senpai imitate her voice
and all that if something like that ever
happens to me
oh that could be fun i remember what was
it was it um
what was that stream what were they
doing i remember watching something
money in senpai was
i think she was um playing garcic phone
maybe
with the viewers
and she had kind of the senpai voice
herself but
mindy said i still ended up like talking
a lot even though she shouldn't have
because she was supposed to
she was supposed to like chill her voice
yeah she was resting her voice
mindset by herself is really good at
impressions too though
i'm really fascinated by people who can
do that
because i'm not one of them
[Music]
the skill indeed definitely i wonder if
it's something
that's
easy to pick up i don't i don't think so
i don't think it's easy
you either have a talent word or a skill
for it that you learned
[Music]
or you just suck
and then you have to study it for a long
long long time
voice imitation
i mean there's maybe
maybe
one or two voices out there that i could
imitate too just because they're close
to my voice
[Music]
but yeah not anybody not anybody's voice
being able to imitate literally
anybody's voice who they even the ones
that are so different from your own
that's
that's really impressive
i can imitate animals
a little bit
i can do a really good frog sound that
people always wonder how i'm doing it so
[Music]
that's quite something my frog imitation
people always um leave
uh really impressed and like how how how
does she do it
it's actually really hard to explain to
how i how i do it
i really don't know how to explain it
[Music]
the other day i i did it
i did it for some recording
everyone again was like how the [\h__\h] did
you do that what
yeah i fill my cheeks with air and then
and then
i don't know how to explain what i do
then
hmm
i don't want to tell too many people
though
because i i don't want everybody to be
able to be do to do it and it's not
special anymore it's a secret
it's a secret secret
[Music]
and frog
we're already filling up the hat guys
i'm so fast today
we can definitely make a chicken too
[Music]
it's only been one hour
goddammit come on
here we go
[Music]
getting in the groove we need more
tangents yeah we do
next tangent clap clap
you got anything guys
[Music]
yeah the cute blue iron coming soon
no it didn't play any more overwatch
yeah the local sampler's new song is
really cool
new song
oh oh wow
finally
i can finally see a
finishing line i'll tell you that
um because i decided on a release date
i won't tell you yet though
i'll be announcing it
soon
[Music]
i'm excited because this one was delayed
more than i thought it would be
would was gonna be
[Music]
sadly
but
sometimes it don't be like that
[Music]
this is basically just a chatting stream
with some extra
oh a little extra wait that one's wrong
that one's wrong
i know it's correct
i need another
black one
[Music]
oh i watched like a really shitty movie
last night to fall asleep
[Music]
god what was it called
i was you know i just turned on netflix
and i went with one of the recommended
um
movies
that show up in like the when you open
up netflix sometimes you have these
recommendations that are currently
popular right
it was some comedy movie
there was some comedy movie with um
with
what's his name
i don't i don't remember it was
it was not good
i had a few laughs but it was not good
hi ophelia
[Music]
no there was no adam sandler in it
kevin hart your kevin hart was in it
yeah yeah how do you know how do you
know how do you know
i did not give you any hints
how the [\h__\h] do you know
it was called
was it called what was it
me time yes that's that's the movie
yeah
did i
use the same color yeah okay
[Music]
[Applause]
bad movie on netflix kind of narrows it
down are you saying that are you saying
that um sarcastically
what
i feel like there's probably a lot of
bad movies on netflix
some good ones too me time was bad i
mean
i don't know
i i would i would think you guys would
think it's bad and i didn't think it was
when i don't when i don't think when
even i don't think it's good and my
standards are really low normally then
that means something
right
that that means the movie is
um supposed to land in the trash can
but it's a
um
just a shitty comedy movie
it's not really supposed to be
good i
[Music]
think explain cats that cats
what i don't know what you mean
cats was fun cats was better than me
time
are we having that argument again
this was fun
[Music]
oh
so much hate for netflix sad
sad mind breaking inna was worth it
[Music]
i can show you how i crack my my hands
nice
did you hear it though
[Music]
okay um
where am i where am i where am i i'm
kind of lost track of where the hell i
am ah
okay
because i was mostly working on the left
side on the cap not not row by row
row row row your boat
[Music]
it was pretty loud oh is this
reality it's not that loud don't worry
[Music]
just a normal knuckle crack
oh
you know i'm watching taskmaster
task master season 11 now
and um
there's one lady in there with really
beautiful gorgeous fluffy hair
and she kind of the way she talks and
the sound of her voice reminds me of
cronie
no obviously
you guys don't understand what the hell
i'm talking about unless you watched it
too or gonna look it up now but she
reminds me of cronie
so she's not from the uk i think she
said she's from
australia or new zealand or so
[Music]
but yeah every time she talks
it reminds me of cronies it's nice
[Music]
okay
sugar senpai's eyes are so cool she has
this really bright
lime color
and then that really really saturated
beautiful
blue
it's just so gorgeous i love her eyes
it's so refreshing i look at her eyes
and i feel summer
summer
refreshing
it's like a refreshing
drink on the pool side
a refreshing
lime drink
citrusy drink on the pool side
isn't that a nice nice way of putting it
[Music]
um
ophelia should try to imitate the subway
to senpai recommendation ophelia write
it down
from whole life japan
might be another interesting target for
you
[Music]
i would like to hear you break that one
down
good luck
oh
there have been suggestions before nice
nice
neither did
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
i wish i could do that kind of stuff man
oh my god
[Music]
you know what i'll put i don't have the
same color as in the reference so i'm
gonna put down the dark oops a dark blue
[Music]
was that cute really thank you
i have to channel your inner japanese
goku voice i don't have an inner
japanese goku voice
i can teach you really can you i was
thinking of inviting you maybe to a
collab where you teach me but i don't
know how easy it is to teach because
generally
um
i'm bad at like imitating voices but
if you think you can teach me
then i want to do a stream on that i
think
we can try to
break down and imitate some whole life
member voices
on my channel
[Music]
oh you know what oh
i have an idea we can do prank calls
together
we can call uh whole life members
pre-record it and then edit it
into like a video or showcase it on the
stream we can pre we can prank call them
oh my god
oh my god oh my god
that would be funny but if we prank call
them they see that i'm calling how do i
make them believe with someone else on
on the phone hmm
[Music]
maybe
like they wouldn't believe that we're
doing an off-guard because i i live in
europe no one would
come so far to visit me
i mean
[Music]
it's not very believable to say that i
flew to america or to japan either
change your name on this card change
your name and proof of picture
okay
[Laughter]
all right all right all right all right
all right all right all right all
[Music]
i got too freaking distracted
focus kiwawa focus
[Music]
what if they're off colliding with them
while you prank them well the chances of
that being the situation when i call
them are really low
[Music]
wait oh is that too many yeah it's too
just put many there
okay now we need a lime color
[Music]
oh
oh thank you oh so
so motivating so positive
thank you let's see let's just
i will hit you up
and we can discuss
[Music]
we log into the count oh i guess i i
mean no no no no no i mean
and i don't think
whole life members would want to share
their discord account with me even
though
the idea of it in theory would be genius
but
uh
i don't think that's
now we can do that because then i would
see all their private messages
[Music]
the face is taking shape
i'm actually like all my colors are
still like pretty full
except for black
black is gonna run out
very soon actually like if i do another
one of these streams
it's gonna run out soon
[Music]
i need to need to buy more
black ones but i think i might have to
like look if i find
the right size for this board
but next time i'm gonna do an iron bead
stream i think it will be members only
not so super soon though but at some
point i want to do
[Music]
one for members only
it's
time
[Music]
yeah we're trying to
spray this one but like the
i don't know if it's gonna work out well
oh well we'll see we'll see
it will be a comfy memory stream yeah
you ever doing myth
oh maybe
i i said like last time i said if i
if i meet someone again
in real life like an off guy of collab
then i want to give them
these things as a present so whenever
i know that something like that is
coming up
i'll be iron beading all the way
[Music]
how many have you made it
i only made this one last last week
that's the first time in like a million
years that i tried one but
they're really relaxing it's really
chill
it takes a while but
i feel like they come up so freaking
adorable
so worth it and you can make it into a
keychain
and then gift it to someone so that's my
plan if i meet the myth members again
then i'll i'll make
one of these for each of them
make a
keychain out of them yeah
no this doesn't mean that a horitory of
guy is coming out no no no i just kind
of wanted to start out with them because
i i love them
i love them so much
[Music]
my beloved
birds
[Music]
um
come on come on
[Music]
get
in there
get into the robot
come on come on
[Music]
okay
doing a cover or something
oh we definitely already talked about it
like months ago
a long time ago but
you know
everybody always wants to do so many
things with everybody so
it's like
there always needs to be somebody
really persistent
in a group to make things happen at all
and
oftentimes it's me
but i can't always be the person also
the idea came from mourinho originally
so so she came out with it first so she
she should be following up with it
but i think it was just we were gonna do
a song cover you know we wanted to do a
song cover
um
yeah
it's like it's like like in school when
you have a group project and
yeah
the others are just yeah whatever
so is the the nerd in the group
who has to
get [\h__\h] going
[Music]
oh yeah ophelia if you really want to
start these buy them in a set because
then you have the guarantee that the
beats that you bought actually fit on
the [\h__\h] board that you bought
because
i bought a new one that doesn't reflect
and the
these thingies are way too big for my
beads and my beads are way too small for
them
[Music]
that was you me the nerd
i wouldn't um describe myself as
a nerd in school
because i wasn't even my grades weren't
even good
so like
in terms of
like how well i did in school
i would say i was not a nerd but
if you think about
like my interests and
my hobbies and all that back then and
i was a nerd in that that way maybe but
but but
not in the
common sense i guess
the general meaning
just your average verb i have
i was also
a theater kid for a while
yeah
when we had a
an acting
club or something like that
in junior high school and also before
junior high school
i was part of that but then in high
school
we didn't even
we didn't even have any any clubs like
that at all i think
at all
[Music]
sad
i said this before but my dream when i
was younger was to become an actress
[Music]
and i was a child i wanted to be an
actress
[Music]
and my idol was
[\h__\h] now i forgot her name alexis bledel
bledel
alexis
from gilmore girls
because she made me feel a little bit
better about how i looked like
mukashiva she said
[Music]
because like people sometimes told me i
look a little bit like her but i was
probably like an ugly version
of alexis plateau
but the fact that
people conceived her as pretty
and the way how she was quite popular in
the show as well later on the more time
passed
it made me made me feel like oh maybe i
have a chance to
maybe i can be like her
[Music]
okay here i have to
focus a bit more on what i'm doing
[Music]
there you go
no they didn't call me pretty
if anything was probably family members
i don't even remember anymore about it
anybody who called me
like who said i i looked like a little
bit like her was probably just a family
member i don't remember though
i mean whatever i may look beautiful now
sure sure but trust me as a child
or young young teenager
[Music]
no
i think in starting from first year of
high school
i was i was i had this
definitely
i definitely looked like a weeb
but um
i looked i think i looked like a cute
weeb
[Music]
it was like really long
um
really really long
fringe
people kept on telling me chihuahua your
fridge is so long how do you even see
anything and i'm like it's fine i see
everything shut up
i don't need to cut my fringe
[Music]
yeah it did overlap a little bit maybe a
tiny bit sometimes with my with my eyes
but no i could see perfectly fine
[Music]
um
santa face
i had an emo cut not the best
emo goddamn i wanted to be like that i
wanted a skunk i wanted to have a skunk
in my hair
but
if i think about it i i was i wanted
that because i looked at all i looked at
like seeing kids being really popular
online but
um in austria at that time i lived in a
relatively small city compared to
compared to big cities out there but
i don't really
remember seeing like really hardcore
scene kids
in my
is that correct
what wait [\h__\h] i messed something up
in my area but wait
i messed something up
this this one
[Music]
no one told me are you guys paying
attention
i think it's supposed to look like this
this
is probably it and then
that means that that one is wrong too
oh my god you guys didn't tell me yeah
[Music]
just listening to my tangent i am not
paying attention to this
[Music]
i know it's a little bit hard to see
probably because of i mean the very
exact placement would be hard to see
it's not 100 focused
[Music]
it you're almost blind on you're
too focused on my story
yeah what was i saying that in
in my city actually
they didn't have quite
a big presence those scene kids
if i remember back
maybe some
like low-key scene kids but like earth
skunk tails and all that [\h__\h] and like
zebra zebra colored hair
i don't think
we had
anything like that in my city
but it was definitely a popular
aesthetic
[Music]
thus i wanted to be like that
a city mostly of farm kids don't know
cities so it has city kids but
a lot of like people from the
countryside would come to the city to go
to school there you can dye your hair in
school yeah yeah our school had no
problem with that
that was no problem i think is it maybe
mostly private schools and maybe asian
schools who don't
allow to dye your hair
i would assume
our schools here don't allow that where
where where where
[Music]
all right you weren't allowed to be an
evil kid yeah me neighbor i told my mom
i want fancy hair like that she was like
no
no what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
singapore ah i see i see
yeah i mean i've heard a lot about like
like japanese schools
that are very strict about it like even
even if let's say let's say now this is
events
you know um but i i know of like um
let's say four
not not four kids but like
kids that were even the ones that were
born
in japan but have foreign parents
and let's say they have like blonde hair
or dark brown hair by nature
some schools would force them to dye
their hair black
because like all japanese kids would
have would need black hair because
that's their natural hair color
they like basically the rule is to have
your natural hair color
but then
someone else comes in and their natural
hair color is like something lighter but
they still
have to
um have to dye their hair
black now this is not in every school
but there's definitely schools like that
and that's kind of
weird
um
[Music]
and to say i don't know
foreign
[Music]
and i think nowadays it's not so bad
anymore schools like that should have
been
are probably definitely way less a thing
because they they did
get a lot of criticism for it
like even i just said it in japanese but
even japanese kids sometimes have
a little bit lighter hair than black
and even they would sometimes have to
dye their hair
like a proper
proper black like this
[Music]
foreign
swag
holy [\h__\h] that's that's really rough on
the throat
[Music]
ophelia is gonna suffer
oh it's fascinating
imagine someone talking like this
as
an english-speaking verb it just feels
kind of wrong
but a lot of these voices just feel
right because they speak japanese don't
you think
how why
we're so used to anime voices maybe
oh man
[Music]
sounds like a 4k stuff what's that
like a tv show
american tv show
gilbert
who the [\h__\h] is that gilbert gottfried
what is that sounded like toad it did
sound a little bit like toad
no
that's how i would voice toad sometimes
oh that's a [\h__\h]
a victim who talks like that
now i need to look that up
will i regret it all right
it's not a tuber
that's a normal person
okay let me listen though um let me
you guys you guys you won't hear it
i think
um
gilbert gottfried
reads 50 shades of grey i never watched
that movie
or rent the book
ah
okay okay i mean i guess i guess that's
kind of a
male version
a male and english version
it's it's close
that's not how he normally talks so
right
is that his
ladies and gentlemen
sound of my voice
running on the beach in slow motion
is that arnold schwarzenegger
i haven't been able to open my eyes
since
some kind of common central roast
show
[Music]
interesting interesting interesting
voice
sounds very aggressive
what are you doing just listening to
voices
i'm i'm kind of hooked on this topic now
and where's my music
i have
what about let's switch switch it up a
little bit
[Music]
yeah probably like making his voice a
bit more extreme for the sake of comedy
[Music]
see now i'm not as fast anymore as i
could have been
what happened
what happened to the speed
one two three one two three
i wish i could have somebody sitting
here telling me a story
[Music]
so i i can't i can just listen
listen to some kind of
audiobook
[Music]
now this music right now kind of gives
me
vibes of a mix of
zelda and sims
music
you get what i mean
you get what i'm saying
[Music]
this one doesn't stick properly
are you here to tell them
it's like um
reminds me of
was it ocarina of time
in
in the in the very beginning
very beginning in that um
that city
uttano is also here oh so many youtubers
in my chat meet your bus what's up
which bus
[Music]
youtubers put your hands up in the air
but you probably can't do it because
you're like 2d like me
and you what's up
you end up in the air
you only could
if we only could
unfortunately
most of the time as a veteran putting
your hands up in the air is not an
option so so
so depressing
this depresso espresso
[Music]
where did it go
that's where png's come in handy
yeah
[Music]
i don't know in what role i am but um
i'm just going with the flow i hope i
didn't make like a million mistakes
maybe dakuma
maybe probably takuma is the only one
who's following this properly checking
my homework
wait
what the [\h__\h] am i doing
wait that was completely what the [\h__\h]
wait so the eye is here
oh oh yeah this is this is this is very
wrong
oh
wait what with what
yeah very wrong okay this just goes uh
i want it
this part is wrong
[Music]
one two three four five six seven
one two three four five
six
and seven
and then
and it goes inside here
and one more
i
one more here i'll go go go
now and now and i'll focus focus focus
we need like an orangish color and i'm
not sure should i go with this one
boy where are all the oranges what the
[\h__\h] this is all i have to offer
for the hat
i guess probably this one because this
one's kind of too
too bright
[Music]
this one
it's a bit darker in reality obviously
but
it's also not perfect by the way it's
the closest i can get
[Music]
i need more orange
colors these are not
not ideal but oh well
i'll make it work
[Music]
i thought the hat was red
yeah but i'm just saying orange because
that is kind of an orangish red
if you compare it to the colors i used
down here the red colors
it's uh more bright and a bit more in uh
in the orange it is
kind of red but it's more like a blood
orange hmm
and that's the closest i can get
i mean i guess in
if i if i
try to imagine her her actual design
it might be a bit more let me look it up
[Music]
ah
no generally all the reds in her outfit
are kind of orangish red
um
[Music]
this one's a bit tough though
in her
in her 3d artwork
i would say
i would say even that
these parts should be more orange than
these parts
whatever we probably don't have to be
that exact but
but you know
whatever i'll just i'll just do it this
way
because it's a nice color it's a nice
color
um
i think this goes
here and then
a light blue one
creative freedom
guys
don't hate me
[Music]
maybe
i don't have a good in between color you
know my my reds are too pinkish
they look too pink
so i'm just gonna go with the flow
just do it
just
do it
[Music]
let's look uh what's in this row black
how many one two three
you know what i'll just do
an orange
[Music]
one here
and
[Music]
light blue
oh are you sure the colors that i'm
seeing on the hand camera yeah yeah
that's also a thing
the colors that you guys see seem to be
generally
a bit brighter and less saturated than
what i'm seeing
[Music]
pop up
yeah it will look like her either way it
already looks like her
[Music]
maybe i can
oopsie maybe i can make it like
around the edges to create a little bit
of a gradation of shadow
i could try to use a red one
but as i said i don't really have like
an in-between color so it will look a
little bit
weird i think
[Music]
that would work you think so
um i can try
[Music]
thank you
it's definitely hecking cute okay
finally i have that row finished what do
we do next um
one more
[Music]
here before we go inwards and then
two oranges
yummy oranges
i've been drinking orange juice on this
side yum yum yum also i started taking
starting from today i started taking my
vitamin d again hopefully
that's at least one vitamin
i should probably take all vitamins
[Music]
but let's see if it helps
vitamin d according to what i've read
everyone should be taking vitamin d
anyway if you live in a country like
mine
because our
countries are not blessed with enough
sun even in summer even in oopsie even
if you go outside a lot
during the summer
even in summer you're not getting enough
sun
[Music]
which is weird because it's so [\h__\h]
hot but yeah
yeah vitamin vitamin d vitamin d
will also
make you happier apparently
and less sleepy i think
during the day
so it's like
it's a life hack vitamin d
is a life hack
[Music]
i've noticed before i think last time i
took vitamin d relatively regularly
it did feel like it improved improved my
mood generally a little bit which is
fascinating it's like a
really really weak
anti-depressant
[Music]
recommended those oh i don't remember
i'm gonna google that there there is a
recommended dose which also depends on
where you live like in in central europe
you just don't get enough sun so
your body doesn't pick up enough vitamin
d on its own so you have to help it out
quinoa is my antidepressant
oh i'm sure you're not the only one here
who would say that
cute
okay so
okay we're done with the hair finally
oh
now
one two three four five oranges oranges
but i kind of wanted to mix like some
red right so if i remove
this
put that over here and then
maybe
maybe that red here
[Music]
see that's a that's such a big
difference i mean even even with as
blurry as it is for you guys
that's so
that's so pink
[Music]
that red is so pink
the next
red that's a bit darker and it's this
one but it feels like too too dark
[Music]
that one feels too dark
it's hard to see but the more i will put
all those on here
it will look more
dark
what if i don't see all
what if i do the whole hat and that
[Music]
i don't know
yeah i do i do like the orange look to
be honest oops
even if it's not 100 accurate i do like
it so we'll continue with that
can you paint the beats the beads of
paint or manicure
if only
i don't know nah that's probably not
safe for ironing but like i don't even
have
nail color
i never paint my nails never
never
never sometimes as a child i would put
like glitter
polish on my nails but
my nails are honestly always
just
bland it's so boring
i'm kind of
like sometimes i look at all the girls
pretty super pretty nails
but they're a lot of effort and they
like kind of damage your nails
[Music]
so i don't know
one time when i
put um like
stick on
glue on um
nails
before
last time i did it oh it was such a pain
in the ass to get them off
and then
they looked really damaged once i did
get them off
and it looked like [\h__\h]
[Music]
so
i don't necessarily want to repeat that
the experience
i thought when i tried to get them off i
thought my whole nail would come up it
was terrifying
absolutely terrifying
stickers don't damage your nails yeah
that one but with the sticky ones
they just always fall off don't they
like i have friends who use them and
they constantly lose their nails and
then it looks weird because you have all
these beautiful nails but just like this
one like this one just one one is
missing
it looks weird and then you and you get
really pissed off about losing them
so i would prefer not to deal with that
[\h__\h]
i remember my one of my closest friends
i was hanging out with her and she loses
her [\h__\h] nail and she's like
can you help me find my nail did you see
my nail can you hold my nail for a
second
i'm like what hold your nail okay
don't lose it kiwawa
okay
uh
i would want it i would want those nails
if it was easier to improve my
femininity score but it's too much
effort [\h__\h] that no no no no
oopsie
nami mama had cute nails too
[Music]
that lasts more than a week damn but
like getting used to having
those longer nails was also pain in the
outside i didn't know how to touch
things anymore like my phone
and and my keyboard and everything
and i didn't even know how to open the
[\h__\h] door anymore
because those nails i had on were like
they were like
pretty long like this
but it's not even some people have
longer nails like that my friend has
longer nails than that and then suddenly
i don't know how to function anymore i
don't know how to how to
um
how to carry a fork or
how to open a bag
everything is suddenly so weird
i mean you get used to it but still
man girls
[Music]
suffering beauty is suffering guys
it's just suffering
that in german we say
that schoenstein muslin who wants to be
beautiful has to suffer
we always say that
someone complains about something being
painful in order to be pretty
you prob they probably used it a lot in
germany's next top model even
as an argument well
they're sure sign famous leiden says
heidi klum
honestly germany said tex next top model
i used to watch like early seasons
but
that those shows are so ridiculous
because the situations they create are
actually
low-key or or actually maybe high-key
torture sometimes
some situations they put those girls in
like so unrealistic as if
as if those kind of photo shoots where
it's below 10 degrees celsius or so as
if that's normal you just want to do you
just want them to suffer for the sake of
television entertainment
[Music]
man there's so many youtube videos that
discuss that kind of [\h__\h] like how
how what what's wrong with these tv
shows
it's not only germany's next top model i
think i've heard even voice things about
america next top model
man i'm just so too honest for my own
good am i
[Music]
what says it how it is
not like we were ever gonna collab with
germany's next top model so come on
[Music]
what
what did that just say where the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
even had a girl shave her teeth
in america's next song what
[Music]
did you just d
did you type something wrong did you
mean shave her head
[Music]
what
to give her more of a gap oh
i think i think i've heard of that ah
shape like in the middle
oh
oh oh to make that more of her gimmick
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
i mean i understand
because that that can be like a way of
making your face more memorable
but that's so weird
germany's
america's next top model why why why why
why why why why why
and then there's in these shows there's
always so much drama
between the girls there's so much
bullying and
screaming oh god so much [\h__\h] drama
i'm like i'm i can't
i know there's so many people who enjoy
that kind of television
it's it's just entertaining to see other
people have so much drama not only that
the top model shows but i guess like
shows like whatever
the kardashians or stuff like that
i didn't watch it but i i'm assuming
they have a lot of drama too
[Music]
oh
yeah that's just reality tv shows i
guess your big brother i used to watch
the german version of big brother
because i
but i was really young but i was like
kind of thinking oh i wonder
what if i ever was part of big brother
because it felt like
i don't know somehow it seemed fun but
the more that i think about it now that
i'm adults then that show
that's kind of insane
and cringe
what is it about wanting to see
how other people
live and suffer what what why does it
why does it interest us so much flavor
of love oh
god i think we talked about flavor of
love
before
but
yeah
i watched cause i i watched so much mtv
back in the day and it had all these
american shows
dubbed in german like next
and
one tb
one show was like
um
there was like a dude or girl
who was really into a certain
a specific
celebrity but obviously they can't date
that celebrity for example every levine
so
you they would get like a lineup of i
think three people or in the beginning
five and then they would like get rid of
two and then three three of them would
have to
set up the whole performance and their
whole looks to look and perform like
ever levine or so
um
that i thought was actually
somehow interesting and then the person
would choose one of the contestants
whoever
was the most like the celebrity that
they want to date but if you think about
it
choosing
choosing your partner
by
the
but by seeing whether or not they're
like your celebrity crush it's kind of
creepy
and then
don't you as the contestant wonder if
that person actually loves you for
yourself
or just
loves you if that ever if
any relationships of that show ever
turned out to be something permanent
don't you wonder if like
it
if that's not [\h__\h] weird to date
someone who
who only loves you for
looking and sounding like someone else
[Music]
so weird but
um
i always wondered if those shows are
real at all if the contestants if
anything out of that is ever real or
maybe the contestants are real but they
all know they're just doing it to get
some some screen time
to become famous
through mtv
but they're not really hoping to get a
real relationship out of any of this
definitely flavor of love had a [\h__\h] ton
of girls who just
who just tried to get you know uh
into bed with flavor flav
because it gave them fame
that's why there was a second season
because they immediately broke up
oh my god
i'm done guys
oh
i finished actually while i was extreme
tangenting
oh
flavorflame
flavor
oh my god we're [\h__\h] done
whoa it's time it's time for for bubble
bubble dawn
[Music]
okay
turning babylon on i think is there any
like obvious mistakes
it looks so it looks
finished
looks fine to me
dakuma tell me if you see anything wrong
with it
wait do i see another youtuber in my
chat
today is a hot spot for youtubers
yeah no obvious mistakes it looks fine i
think it looks good
[Music]
it's not mirrored
it's it's not it's it's fine i have to
write the real sweater literally right
in front of me
[Music]
and i'm just waiting for the baboon
to heat up
let me drink a little bit
[Music]
spot on
i wonder if she will if i show her this
she'll probably bring it up in her in
her morning streams
i have to reel somebody right in front
of me
don't you hear her
[Music]
what's up what's up
what is it we're gonna eat dinner soon
don't worry
okay
yeah
i see my mouth didn't move so that was
obviously not me
is it hot yet i wonder
are we ready
[Music]
okay i think i think we're ready but you
know last time i also
i wasn't sure what the right amount of
oh
what was that oh i thought obs died for
a second
this is
the once i iron over her
she will come to life you will see
you know how um
it's like a it's like a voodoo
puppet
it will be her
i'm i'm summoning her to reality okay
i'm going in now i'm going in
work your magic yeah yeah
[\h__\h] i'm nervous
it's okay it's okay there's like there's
really no way of [\h__\h] this up
just iron a million times on top of it
[Music]
see how tiny it is oh my god
no i don't care
oh it smells weird again
plastic smell
is screaming
[Music]
[Applause]
that actually might have sounded a
little bit like her
yakisoba
oh
[Music]
oh it's actually working pretty well
this time
it already looks
oh
it already looks like it's working its
magic
really fast let me get the top part
[Music]
um
[Applause]
i love super the senpai i want to play
worms again with the writer senpai and
arena
that was so funny
it's been too long
[Music]
when did she wanna join oh she's been
here all along
[Music]
circular circular circular structure
circular motion circular motions
i think we're done
this feels like it was very efficient
[Music]
turducken worms was so good right
i'm gonna tell you worms would be great
are you aware that we already did that
though
for anyone who didn't see it you have to
watch the archive it's been a while but
that was so good it's so funny
okay i think we're done it looks
finished oh oops look how nice it looks
it melts to something so
nicely looking
oh my oh my oh my
okay now we have to let it cool down
shhh
[Music]
let me drink some water let me add some
water
to my glass
[Music]
sorry it was on the ground my huge
jug
my jugs
[Music]
blow it
[Applause]
[Music]
that crease fire technique
ah my
my breath can blow out
blow out that's very german it's so
german of me to say
it's such a direct literal translation
uh can
uh kill every fire wait you say that in
english too
extinguish put out put out that's it
[Music]
blow out sounds fine really
i kind of felt so wrong
[Music]
it's still so hot let me i have my fan
on let me hold it towards the fan oh i
should put her in the fridge
[Music]
i don't know if i should make another
one
because i'm actually like
already
um
i feel so accomplished you know
i feel so accomplished just by making
that one i mean another one i kind of
wanted to make is this this baby oh that
one we already have down there
i wonder how long that would take me
a little chicken
[Music]
what's going
on
chicken should be faster
i don't know about that
it will take at least an hour
and now it's been uh two hours for this
one
yeah i think so too it would cut it
close a little bit i don't know when
exactly my mom's arriving either
but i want to be done before she arrives
you know
are there enough beets oh yeah i
shouldn't have enough i should have
enough beets yeah
okay whatever i'm doing it i just don't
really have tangents
anymore i think
i don't know you guys have to help me
out with the tangents
what happened with aoe too sorry i'm
gonna play it next week on sunday i'm so
sorry please forgive me please boogie
boogie
there were some problems
oh i think it's it's relatively fine now
also aoe2 wasn't even supposed to be
today it was supposed to be yesterday
but
yeah yesterday in one week um sata died
this time for real though
it's not gonna be delayed anymore no no
no no
oh
okay i think i'm going to peel it off
oh that was my
it was a million times easier than last
time
[Music]
is it because i ironed it less
wait no yeah huh
anyway now i have to get it off of this
now let's see if that's also easy
[Music]
last time i felt like it was way more
sticky
[Music]
oh
oh yeah okay now this is still tough
i wonder if um i over iron it
[Music]
like i need to
ask like a
like a professional iron bead person
if i did too much but oh oh god oh
i don't want to break it
yeah i think this part i should deal
with my hands again without the
without the
um no the
gloves give me a second
oh [\h__\h]
that looks kind of
broken oh that's fine that's fine it's
fine
flip it like last time what do you mean
flip it i didn't flip anything last time
[Music]
my hands are naked
oh it's tough
to get like into the edges
come on
yeah yeah
yeah baby
[Music]
peel it
yes yes yes
oh yeah
this is you know how people really like
peeling off film off of new like or
whatever like monitors for example
this is kind of like that but more
hardcore
[Music]
oh
oh it's still very hot but
it worked
oh
yeah i'll put on my glove again
[Music]
oh sh
all right
are you ready
before we head
raina
and now
comes the most senpai horritory of them
all
zombie by disco
outfit reveal oh yeah let's see
let's do it like an elephant reveal
again
you didn't see anything
oh no what if i accidentally show the
blue menu on you
[Laughter]
[Music]
a little bit higher
okay
okay outfit reveal
debuting today
[Music]
oh wow the most favorite favorite part
of everybody
everybody loves me to the feet
[Music]
what are those
oh my god look at those beautiful
slender
beautiful feet
nice sock you got there
oh oh i see hands i see bare hands what
who is this who is she she's gorgeous
she's beautiful
wow such a colorful outfit what is that
is that like a sports
soccer jersey what is that it's so shiny
is she a sports famed beach ball
what
so so beautiful kind of tomboy how do
you know how do you know already
we don't know
i don't know yet oh neckline here we go
oh kind of not many bubba not so not so
bubblicious a little bit flat but not
too too flat it's a good in between
[Music]
beautiful v-neckline on that t-shirt
that's definitely a jersey oh
she must be
the what was it the leader of a sports
team or something like that
medium is premium i've never heard of
that before
okay
oh what is that look what is that blue
thing on the side also is that short
hair oh
[Music]
oh we can see a little bit of her face
now oh and her eyes
oh they're so ugh they're so shiny
they're so gorgeous
oh i've fallen in love i think i've
fallen in love do i hear do i hear it
should i smash
your hair a little
[Music]
a little bit um
bent right now but she's gonna be fine
she's gonna be fine look at her
thank you master
well shiny
ooh shiny
[Music]
very flat
the back looks like this
the front is better obviously i wonder
if you can also iron the back to look
more like you know
as smooth as the front
i said something was a little bit broken
i i don't know if you can see it but
yeah
here that you see that
[Music]
it's fine though it doesn't come off but
yeah maybe maybe i'll do something about
that before i send it to her before i
give it to her
i can iron you can iron the back oh
really
[Music]
this is foreign
i think i'll make a kibaba um in the
members only stream
[Music]
ah nice
nice they look so good together
i can i can play puppets now i can be
like i can play
dolls i don't care i can be like
yes
[Music]
and they look so gorgeous so precious
dollhouse building
dollhouse
hand cam street just playing with dolls
kind of cute
[Music]
ah drinking water
okay i'm actually kind of so so
satisfied
i feel so complete
i don't wanna
i don't wanna do another one
this is actually perfect but i do have
some time to read super chats actually i
think i can read some super chats at
least
yeah one is enough one day
one per day a good pace
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
we went we were definitely more faster
and efficient than last time though so
we will get better and better
yeah we saved something for the members
um who's next um
i do have
and do have like
me and energy
that i want to do as well
that's like the ones i definitely want
to make
now let me move my phone back
[Music]
okay
okay well everything went relatively
well except for the fact that in the
beginning
the
the stupid new board that i bought was
too big
yummy
and that kind of sucks but besides that
let me take off my hands
it's a nice hat
and my gloves
adapted and overcame yeah my mask i only
had it halfway on anyway
okay wonderful wonderful fun thank you
guys for joining for another one of
these
um creative hand cam streams i hope you
enjoyed this one as well
now i will continue streaming i will
read super chat so you're welcome
hmm
yeah thank you guys for watching
okay now
don't you like this music i prepared
this one too
[Music]
beautiful
[Laughter]
nice right
it's kind of it gives me a bird bird
feeling
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
okay super tattoo time
and since i caught up yesterday i only
have to read the ones from today
[Music]
let me write something down perhaps
what is this
[Music]
oh that's my
that's my memo
a from
chat time
now we'll put up a photo of the
of the surveillance that i made on
twitter again like last time
as the italy notes
okay starting
and jump around
no i'm not jealous no
yeah i love yakiniku but um
when did i stop moving hello
it's probably because i changed the
connection
oh don't worry about it nothing but the
truth maybe maybe you'll be lucky and
receive a free membership again
eventually
don't worry about it
happy you're here
doc hook thanks for the pinky
like you should lady came up don't sit
on the iron beads throne
the iron beads from iron throne it's not
coffee and leaves little circle imprints
on your royal buns yeah it definitely
would yeah instead sit on the chicken
throne it is made up of jenkins that
bend the knee to the house of the
phoenix very soft very comfy
oh
that does seem like it would be very
soft and comfy
i hope it's some
chickens that still have their feathers
and not just like
chicken breasts
[Music]
i see something let me check something
grilled chicken no no no i wanted to be
i wanted to be with feathers yeah
coming up
oh dear i hope it doesn't
end up like last time actually
ah i found i found an interesting video
the other day and i want to tell um all
the korean bros in seoul about it or
honestly everybody who lives in a city
where
it floods sometimes so i watched the
video that got into my recommended about
just some random dude
who
just
goes up to
a street that's really flooded
and he just unclogs it
and within three minutes
it's
drained
[Music]
and the way he talks about it it's like
he does that a lot and he's really
confident but he just seems like a
normal i don't know dude in his late
teenage years or in his 20s or so but
he's like
you know other people they don't do it
so i sometimes i come up here to unclug
the train here you have to create a
little whirlpool here see now that now
there's a whirlpool and then he walks
around to the other one and he
unclogs that one too yeah after the
storm yeah yeah
so
i i think like a lot of um
a lot of floods are probably that's
that's how they that's how they start
right oh i stopped moving again
[Music]
it was weirdly
weirdly fascinating
[Music]
hello
there we go
something with my internet now
um i missed the stream due to a headache
oh no
you can it's a short stream you can
catch up fast
yeah yeah when something gets stuck in
the drain
you just have to all he did really was
like move his foot a little bit around
the drain and that fixed it what the
hell
so i will remember that
and if you guys ever see
your your street flooding it's really
not that difficult however be careful
i saw that everything written in the
comments
this has happened before so be careful
sometimes you don't even see the drain
so you have to look for it but sometimes
um there is like no like gate on top of
it
and somebody apparently before
like fell into it and died
[Music]
so be careful like make sure there's
actually a drain don't just like
you know
aimlessly
walk around on a flooded street
i don't know how you would fall in there
but yeah apparently that's a thing
but in theory it's so easy to fix
the clogging
no
accidents happen so be careful
careful if you try it
use a rake
but it's like i guess most people just
don't think about or know that it's so
easily fixable like i didn't know i
didn't know that if a street is flooded
like that then it was such an easy fix
so i would have not known what to do
[Music]
i thought it was just too much rain i
didn't know that something probably
clogged up
[Music]
yeah i watched the new london during tv
show i talked about it yesterday in my
cult of the lamb stream
quite a lot i talked about it
yeah
um
patsy thank you thank you oh wait i
don't think i completely uh finished
reading the other one though you bought
it sorry sorry sorry attachment is
coming up so i'm going to sleep at work
oh i can't say lovey-dovey words like i
love you but it's fighting fighting i
kind of said it though you said you
couldn't say it but by saying it you
kind of said it
[Music]
i hope
i hope the typhoon won't be too bad be
careful
yeah
be careful i hope it's comfy to sleep at
work
it's like a like a big sleepover because
i'm assuming there's colleague other
colleagues there too
nice sleepover hope they don't um snore
too loud
[Music]
today's my birthday and the second i'll
be spending with kfb and you my aussie
oh
second birthday already i'm so proud to
be part of this wonderful community
you've fostered over the last two years
watching us grow has been an
irreplaceable joy and honor
thank you for your kind words that's
very sweet
wow your birthday
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear paxy happy birthday to you
yeah congratulations
i i wonder in your time zone is already
the next day i wonder if it's on the
fourth one or fifth but in any case
celebration
treat yourself tweet yourself
and thank you also for treating
other people seems like you gifted some
memberships thank you shane
on to the next birthday
i hope you have a wonderful year ahead
of you
[Music]
oh relationship advice
i don't know if i can help you with that
i have a question about women
how do you keep long distance alive
we've known each other since middle
school and i'm trying to get her to be
my girlfriend please and thank you
um
oh man that's kind of sad um i think
like long distance is really difficult
um
how um how moved to her how about that
is that an option
or stop moving again
some connection problems man
[Music]
i'm gonna try moving
sorry i i think it's really difficult to
give relationship advice especially when
i don't even know you two
council thank you and eric schmidt's
schmitztenkischen
silver's fans thank you soon here's my
long overdue membership in super chat
i've been a bad chick and only joining
streams on and off since last year
ah very aware aren't you but i've just
started internship and your streams have
really been helping me with my sanity oh
much love is always thank you very much
good luck with that i wish you the best
spanking handkerchief and patsy duncan
neko foxton
is that
[Music]
your birthday too
i said it's my birthday i'm watching
kiana stream so kiana's stream seems
like a gift uh
actually i'm a korean kfp tomorrow is
your time fifth of september okay
so not your birthday yet in my country
but over there it's already your
birthday
congratulations
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear my name is
[Music]
please eat
your favorite cake today
and celebrate yourself treat yourself
buy yourself something nice that you
always wanted okay
[Music]
yeah
right hood 777 that kishim black
preaching thanksgiving rental 777
hi hot wings i miss you so much did you
really i don't think i've gotten any
face time with you since you beat wind
waker i'm so happy to be here with you
today well where were you
nice to have you stay
don't leave
thank you
rev navarina thank you soon
[Music]
[Laughter]
gladly in every stream hildegard
[Music]
did you hear that about ui mama's dream
the artist of subaru at the beginning of
the year where she officially declared
somebody was a bird and has always been
a duck interesting
interesting
i've never doubted it
thank you
m
[Music]
it's like when hungry comes from kiana
as a chicken he never
he never confirmed such a thing
no no no and if he ever said that it was
a joke
maybelline 2 501 thank you for the rest
of the chat thank you soon tanja needs
someone to motivate her okay you got the
stencil pencil attention she's our boss
if she can do it nobody can prettiest
bird in the sky as to your idol for all
to see improving everyone's mood in the
flesh tend to you the best hands down
thank you wow
well that's very sweet
so flattering almost embarrassing thank
you so much
[Music]
now
replace all the tantrums with your own
name and say the same thing to yourself
in the mirror
right back at you know you know you
ok
thank you
[Music]
five four out of five doctors agree that
kiara improves your mood the fifth one
changed their mind after chickens took
them out back
[Music]
robert carney thank you for the rest of
the chat thank you soon nice gloves guy
also your stream is fire is always guy
[Music]
what
okay
girl
robert carney
thanks girl
[Music]
you know i say hey guys a lot even to
like when when i'm with the girls but
but saying it directly to me hey guy
just feels kind of wrong
[Music]
can thank you and can you find her
dancing
[Music]
with myself
thank you
good end to end the week get good ends
the week it is indeed patsy duncan
to finally 500k views
thank you guys
thank you very nostalgic
miss princeton thank you for art streams
like this they're creative and we're
kind of finally getting the things we
asked for
can't wait for more you're welcome it's
always nice to have something on the
side to do you know so i don't mind
doing it this way
so thank you guys for the super chats
that's it actually i sped speeded
through them oh no i'm gonna get a
speeding ticket
[Music]
i had fun this time it was a little bit
less exhausting on myself than last time
thankfully last time i felt like so
i don't know out of breath and and my
back hurts and all that
[Music]
now so that's it
natako is a bit more entertaining but in
terms of like human values
so that she
is
a kind of a better person i love them
both they're both my favorite characters
from pacquiao
um
damn i can't choose they have different
different chimes
i feel energetic really
oh
well i wonder i wonder how because the
tangents were fun today
and [\h__\h] it congratulations
yeah i love all the characters from
bakimono katari
i love them
all let's see
downstairs one more super chat here
thank you for the rest of the chat hey
get on my birthday is friday ninth since
i'm in the usual room i was the ninth oh
i was wondering if you can go in the
usual room and sing me happy birthday
for the speakers in the room and i was
wondering if you can release me as a
present
ah no we don't do releases for present
but
i can sing your happy birthday already
if you want to
happy early birthday to you
congratulations to you too
kind of early but okay
thank you so much
what a sweet super chat very generous i
hope you treat yourself too to something
though
then not only me not only treat kiwawa
also treat yourself
oh thank you optimus prime
hearts do i see some hearts
oh my oh my thank you for the hearts
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] now i stopped moving
come on cookie you mad cookie in your
man
reach the [\h__\h] air there we go
and in german we say
[Music]
i'm gonna welcome my mom
and uh yeah
i'm gonna make some dinner hopefully i'm
so lazy maybe maybe mommy can make
dinner please mommy
what the speed run below three hours
what's up
speed run speed run stream but don't
worry
um
next week
on sunday
i will be doing
a 12-hour marathon
yep
guys you don't need you'll be do you
need to come thank you hi since
honestly 12 hours doesn't even sound
like so much anymore
but yeah we're doing it
doing it
um
uh
it will it will end at midnight my time
i think unless i might move it one one
more hour
[Music]
excuse me my what my two year
anniversary
man you've been you've been gone for a
while huh
it's coming up my two-year anniversary
is coming up incredible
incredible it's time
two years oh my god honestly it's crazy
i
i thought of this today but
you know two years in v tuber time
is insanely long because retailers
themselves haven't been around for that
long yet
and the big boom wasn't until
somewhat recently either
so
two years
being a different job for two years may
not be as special
but being a vegetable for two years i
think is
quite special it's an accomplishment
yeah it's only a five-year-old industry
literally
[Music]
are somehow kind of low-key
pioneers as well
in the english-speaking be tubing world
i mean they're they're definitely
were english-speaking youtubers before a
few ones but
i do see us as
um some somewhat of a pioneers and um
you know we go we have to be proud of
ourselves
we obviously got a big push
from home life
from what they built before us
but then
we made whole live english our own thing
and brought in a lot of new fans and we
brought in i think we inspired a lot of
people
to become youtubers themselves
so
i think we should all be proud of
ourselves for
doing what we did
hell yeah
yeah
we kicked down the door kind of yeah
[Music]
so with that being said i thank you guys
for watching today
tomorrow is my day off oh i will be
uploading the animation now before i get
forget it i have the animation for the
monthly
uh members only wallpaper
um
i'm gonna upload the animation i have it
ready now
it's a special
special month you know september
anniversary month so i'm giving you guys
a little bit more of a bigger present
animated wallpaper for members only
don't share
don't share with anybody who's not a
member okay
oh
it's it's actually really fun anyway i
stopped moving again so i'll go now i'll
be the same
thanks guys
[Music]
good night good night
[Applause]
[Music]
you