Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive Genius
Ririka Yo
Kawaii
Positive Genius Kawaii Positive Genius Kawaii Positive Genius
Ichi Ririka
Yoichi Corporation works hand in hand with Rika,
while Genius's homely and pleasant environment
will suit your lifestyle.  We are
waiting for you with a variety of systems that allow you to work in a fulfilling way.
Kawaii Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive
Genius Lyrica
Good Positive
Genius Kawaii Positive Genius
Kawaii Positive
Genius Ichi
Lyrica Yojo Corporation is Lyrica  We
are currently looking for talented people to work with us. We offer a
homely and pleasant environment,
allowing you to work in a way that suits your lifestyle. We have a fulfilling work structure and a variety of
systems.  It
's Genius's first lyrica Yo
cute positive
Genius's cute positive
Genius's first lyrica Yo cute positive Genius's cute positive Genius's cute positive Genius's first lyrica We
are currently recruiting talented people to work with Yo Ka.  In a good environment,
you can work in a way that suits your lifestyle. We are
waiting for you with a fulfilling system similar to Furi-
Kakashi.  I
opened it.
Hello, hello, hello,
hello, hello, hello, hello, hello,
hello, hello,
chaos, everyone.
In other words, yes, there's everyone. I
don't know what's up here, but hello, everyone. It's
begun.
Hello, it's the eve
of the usual live event 2023. So, thank you very much for coming to see us today. It's
amazing, there
are so many people. So, today,
let's enjoy the all-night festival with everyone. Let's
all practice a little.  We are
having a fun time together, so
please take care of us.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.Thank you very much.It's
okay to say hello one by one.Isn't it good
today?  It'll take about a minute, okay? Can I ride the dog
? Yes, it's okay.
There's a lot of people today, so that's it. The
people participating today are Eko. Everyone,
press the tab button and you'll see who's participating.
Masu
Sugo What
is this?
[Music]
112114+14 means 2028 Aja 27
people gathered together Sugo
Pimeni Meni Pipo
So, today I
will play with that new implementation for the first time,
Holmen Hunting.  I'm thinking of
having a little fun with the 27 of us, playing lines and various other
things, but
today I'm going to talk to
all of you, listeners, about home hunting, which I've never seen you play with before.  I'm
thinking, let's do it for a while.Let's do
it.This is the
best.I'm sorry that it took so long to finish.But no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,\hokay, okay, let's\hcome and
follow Jamiko-chan to this place.
Please, today, I
tried to hit back at you, but please stop. Everyone looked at me and I knew what this Subaru
was saying.
That's it. This is what I
said. It can't be helped, Mi-san.
Sakura-san hates the use of having nipples.
What are you making me do with Yaro-chan?
Shame on you.
Stop it, stop it. You're pushing me. You're pushing me. Erase it. Erase it.
Hurry up. It's
amazing, but I can erase it, but Sasu-chan
left it behind. I can't
erase it.  If I deleted this, it would affect the system, so no
matter what I tried, I couldn't delete it.It's
built into the system,
so why don't you put up a button?
Okay, everyone, let's start with the red team this time.Let's
do it between the red teams for once.  Well then, yes,
everyone has their own balance. Well, I
think there are a lot of people gathered together. Yeah, yeah,
generally speaking, there's too little white,
or too little yellow, or too little red. I
don't really see it, so yeah, yeah.
Okay, so I thought, Okay, so I'm going to go home with the red hair. There's
someone out there who's going to go hunting. I
forgot to mention that this is it.
By the way, I don't know if anyone has gotten it yet,
but there's a book on it by the morning assembly table.
Thank you very much.
Let's go back to where we were earlier. Let's get it. This is it
. Everyone is here. Please get out there and head towards the school.
I'm sorry that the en version isn't ready yet because I've been sleeping.  However, I hope the
JP members will support me.
Yes, yes, please. Holmen. The
hunting rules are that each team will select 6 people.
Yes, it's a 2-game
game, so 3 people will be selected, so 6 people will be selected.
Okay, what's this? The red team is playing first, so
let's decide on a few members and get them together.
Okay, okay, what about the boy chat? I
'm thinking that the bubble chits should be divided into red, white, and yellow. I'm
sure.  I think it's going to be crowded, so let's ask the red team to stay here for a
while, and have the yellow and white teams
go to their designated boss chits. It looks
scary. Yes, Mr. Ani.
[Music] It's
yellow over there. It's yellow
.
[Music] [Music]
Yellow, yellow, shiny yellow, shiny yellow
Hey, I'll win, Yellow, I did my best, and who's going to oppose me?
Yo Hanty, first time person, Kakumaki. Sanma
polka. Yes,
yes. All other people,
please enter once. All others,
please wait outside the venue.
Yes, yes.  Is this okay? This is okay,
yes, okay, okay, okay, okay.
These three people who
entered, let's go, let's go, let's
do our best. This is a test of how well you
know the Hololive members. Your heart is pounding,
your head is pounding.
Whether you use your head or not, it's more about passion than your head.It's
true, because you're a hero, so it's passion.But because you're a hero, it's
not passion.It's
mental and physical passion.Is
this mental and physical power,
or mental and physical passion?I've always wanted to ask this.
Last year was Menkarushion,
but it wasn't just that. Kadora is now mentally and physically. He's
here to try to take back his passion. I see. He
made me understand, but it seems like I have to aim.
By the way, do you understand the rules?
Everyone, there are no rules at all.  By the
way, to give you a simple explanation, if you
start the game now, the
person who turned into a demon will be warped to a point in front of the white statue in that bed.You
can't do that.  That
topic will be displayed on top of the screen, so the person who matches that theme will be the
first person to play with yellow (O). Yeah, I'm sorry, I
did yellow, but it's okay
. All right, in order, I
'll do it with yellow (Ha) first.  Yes, sorry, please.
Okay, Yellow. I feel like 6 people have already entered.
Yellow. This is the 31st time, so I'll go with 3. That's fine
. Okay, 3 people have entered. No, I'm just
here to ask where it starts with hunter.  That yellow one has
entered, so I guess I'll make it something like yellow, yellow, then white.Okay,
it's O.I'm a fugitive, so I'm a fugitive.I'm going to
put it in the fugitive, so everyone is going to anasu a little bit.Yes,
a little yellow.  Please wait.
Yes, yes, yellow members are here. We'll
be waiting in the audience seats. The
turtles are here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
[ __ ] Paki-sama-chan, this is exciting. Neither
Polka nor I are here. Which one?  Wata: I'm
also doing a polkaft, so
if I start, I'll do a polka, and if I start, I'll do it myself.
Oh, I understand. Well, there are times when I become a fugitive too.
Well, the other team...
When the other team turns into pigeons,
you end up on the runaway side. Well, this member is on the runaway side. The
members are decided, but everyone participates.
That's right, the participation itself is
on the runaway side.  Hamihameru Volume First
Volume Check Akita
[Music]
First Volume Check Volume First Volume
Check
% Me
200%
[Music]
Well, Subaru and the others are now the first
ones to catch him.
It's okay if you don't enter. Do you understand this?
What is the way of catching it like? If you touch it, you
will be caught. The lead will
be handed over to you, so this person who catches it
will use the lead, for example, by praising the ear.  When it comes out,
go to the person who says this guy has furry ears,
hit this leash, and pull him out.
Friendly pull him to the white statue. If you
press the sign, you can contain him. It's the
same thing as the one on the left.
Good luck!  It's starting, it's starting, it
's starting, it's okay for us to be on the run, we're on the side of running away, we're on
the side of catching the red team, we're going to
catch the red and red.
Well, I guess it's
not red,
but I failed.Where
's the person whose name is red?There's a person whose name is red.There's a person whose name is red.Look at the name.The
person whose name is red is white.  White team, white team, now white team,
white team, white team, white team, white team, white people, white people, there's a cat on top of it, that's it, that
's it.  A
white person, a
white person to catch. There's a white person over there. Do your best, it's falling
. It's falling. It's falling. Something blue
wants me to catch it. It looks
blue. It's a white person, so it's over.
Right now, it's a white person, so it's already white.  Chan, it's
coming, it's here, it's on top, it
's on top of the white pillar, it's on top of the white pillar.  I see
there is a possibility of a chance mistake. I
can't catch a
mistake, but I can't do it properly,
so I probably want to enter. I think it's okay. A lot of people have
been caught, so this is an interesting
story.  It's called a story,
oh,
stop it, it's over, it's over, I
just wanted to try it out.But
this topic is tentative, so I'm going to do it that way.I
caught Nofu,
Nofu, I was watching from above, and I pulled on the leash.  It
looks like it's too much, so run away,
Ririka. Run away with all your might.
If you're caught, you can run away if you use your strength.
Run to the other side. Run to the other side. Hey, let's
start over again. Do we start over? This is practice, so we'll move on to
something like this.  Okay, let's move on to the next one.That's right, the
next one will be the ones that run away.So
please make them the fugitives.But the
white team has not entered this.It's
not all the red ones.It's
all the ones who will catch them.  The team is on the runaway.
I see. I see. They're getting beaten up.
Please stop fighting. If you hold it, it's either right or left. Which way is it? Right, left, right. I wonder if I'll be on the run.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh,
oh, you
can run away too.
[Music]  ]
Yokoko is
strong. He
may be strong at catching. Thank you for your hard work. It's
yellow, but I can do something. But
this is just hypothetically. Tomorrow, I'll probably get more than a few sen,
or I'll debut in 2020. Yeah, I probably
have a lot of studying to do.  But if it's the
wrong person, why can't I get it?If I
catch the wrong person and touch the sign, they'll
charge me even though it's the wrong person.I
can't go inside.  Is it
okay to lie and say that I'm not like that when I'm being chased? I
can't lie. I already have
that data about when I debuted in 2000. I
can't lie to spite myself.  Well, on the contrary, I can't even lie,
but on that day, I probably won't be able to connect to the voice chat.The
enemy probably won't be able to connect, so I won't be able to do it.Good
evening.Well then, it's time to start.Yes, yes, I'm going to
run away.I'll make
sure I don't get caught and survive.
Okay, I pressured Rigros Oh,
no, it's okay, I won't say anything if I'm scared It
's okay, it's not scary at first You're scary at first You're not scared You ca
n't do it anymore Kare-san
's team
[Music]
Hit me
Run!  I got in the way and bumped into him,
so I
went to the window, but Shiro was trying to catch him right now,
right? That's right, he
was caught by that body. It
's my color. Kim, Kim, are you
serious? Yo, Kim.  I
'm so sad,
so I'm caught too. I'm standing up,
and the iris on my legs is sexy. I
can't hear you over there. I'm so sexy, but
wait a minute. I've realized something divine
.  [Laughs]
Narui,
Geroso, you're such a senior, what's going on? You're
here, you're here, you're here
[Music] You're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here, you're here.
Somehow you got away. You
survived and were able to do it, but you weren't caught at all. He was
n't very good, you were Yuu.  I wonder if it's quite
difficult, isn't it? This seems difficult, isn't it? Su-chan
might have been a genius. It's true that it's a continuous hit. It's a continuous hit.
That's why the polka was not good.  I'm
going to keep repeating what I was doing,
but I didn't miss it. I definitely won't miss it. I've
entered the fugitive again one more time.
I understand, but I wonder if I was able to do it. It'll
come out later.  I'm going to push it,
or see it, or it's done. It's done. It's
done. It's done very
boldly.
That's the fashion we have now. It's so
easy and strong.
If you run around, everyone won't think it's yellow.
No, it's probably just the money guys. It's
scary. What's going on here? Seriously?  I'm
in charge of gross idiots, so
please forgive me. I'll do my best next time. I'll do my best next time.
Even if I shift like that, I won't be able to see the colors. I thought I was a
genius, I don't want to be banned. I wo
n't be able to do it tomorrow when I have a chance.  It's gone. Let's
go. It's Iris. It's extremely
safe here. It's red, so let's go.
Turn off the red
and squat down. It looks like you're really crouching down near the operation. It's hard to
understand. It's hard to understand. It's a
mess.
What were you
doing? When I was catching you,
Chiara-
senpai was having a really hard time squatting.  I
'm behind the back, but what's
this white guy?
Or the white one, this white one, this white one, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
that's right, when I was crouching down with a thread of clouds, I
got caught and it was Biji-chan.  Yes, I ca
n't get caught. It's hard to get
caught. I can't stay here. I mean, I can't get caught
if I'm being used. Even if I pull it out, it's
really difficult. I can't crawl. I thought I was being
turned away, so I
thought it would be weird to practice. I
ran away.  Run, run, you got caught.
Stop it.
[Music] Chade-chan, you're running away. I'm so sorry. You
can't
escape. This is dangerous. You have to move. [Music] It's not happening. Run, it looks like you've escaped. I'm
thinking, "I can't win."  I guess I finally found
someone to go in. I crouched down and
waited for the moth
because it would be too much of a hassle,
so it might not be a good idea to wait until someone else gets caught.
Ah, I see. The yellow group.  The strings of all the clouds, it's kind of
embarrassing to feel like I'm conquering, isn't it?
It's a really crazy thing to say, it's a lie, it's a dangerous play, it's
like that. Puki play play. I feel like I'm going to hide and sneak
around. I'm
sorry for tomorrow.  No, no, it's
totally fine. It was fun. It was fun. It was fun. It was fun. It was
okay. Sora and I were
fine. We ran away. Yeah, we got
caught. So-chan was drinking something. So-
chan was eating something from earlier.  They're drinking,
they're enjoying it, they're eating ice, they're eating ice,
and they're eating ice again.Okay, then I'll
have one more time, then I'll head over to Minato.Okay,
next time I'll head over to that.I'm sorry.I'll
ask you to gather in the second room for now.Kaha
Move, move, that's
what's coming,
how's the cross?
Maybe three of us can work together a little and one person can
catch it, but please try it with teamwork.Also,
look at the current balance,
and maybe that tall building
could be cut down a little.  Please
understand, that's
weird. I could have caught it without you
Well, what about people who have a partner
and want to practice with them?
Yes, that's true. Well, if you have a partner, that
's true. Listeners, it seems like you've
already decided on a partner.
That's right.  Yes, I've already decided, so each team
has to decide, so I'd like you to do that with
your partner, so if you're a partner and you're
the fang,
please tap that sign, not just the
person above you.
Ta
hai
White
White Yellow Yellow Yellow I understand.
Eiso-chan polka on the signboard Tachirka.
Well, I'll make an announcement just in case. Yes, our team is starting to hit the ground running. Is the
Bells team ready? Yes,
it's the entry on the left.  Okay, next up,
Kuro. I'm off today, so Ririka and Sui-
chan.
Yes, please, but please come up. The people below also
have to touch the sign. Well, the
people below don't have to touch it.  Yes, only the people on the top are the ones on the top. I
made a mistake. I made a
mistake. I made a mistake. I wonder if I can't undo this?
Wait a minute, I'll ask you. Yes, it's
only the people on the top, like I said.  It's tactile, so
Sora-chan, you can touch it.
Matsuri and Aya-san
are teaming up with Iris, not Iris. He's teaming up with Iris.
Hey, what should I do? If you touch him, he
's teaming up with Iris. Pol, Kagome, and I'm teaming up with Iris.
It's me, but Iris, I'm
sorry, but if Esora-chan
pushes me, I think I can ride on top of the polka.
There's the one with the horse,
Ajasora-chan, let's play this one more time.
Click to play. Who's that?
And Iris, who isn't on the team. I
think it's better for you to experience it. Ahahaha,
General Iris.  Can I have you do it for me?
I-
Iris. Wait a minute. Then you mean Watari-senpai's on
top. That's right. Well, I'll
let you ride on a sheep. Well,
this jigiska is fast.
Who's the jigiska
?  Even if I become meat, I did this.
Yes, Iris
can enter by pressing the book.
Push the book and I have something like a book in my hand. Yes, I
can enter the general. Yes, there
is. Press the yellow block of the yellow general.  I'm sorry, that's the
one with the yellow block, but I'm the
only one left. I'm going to
press this, please.
Wait, can I have you explain the rules
? That's the explanation for the request. I can't see it right now.
Is this a
game where you can kill the enemy how many times you can kill them within this number of seconds?The
person on top of you can attack.  However, the
people at the bottom can only move, so
this is not the number of people killed, but the
team with the most number of kills wins first place.Le
point le point.
In this case, when Ai and
General Kim are defeated, 1
point will be added without a king.Oh, I
see.So, for example, if the red team messes up and
kills, and the 1st place red team gets 10 points,
Iris will be included in that.
If you defeat her once, you'll get 2 points and 12 points,
which is really bad. So whether Iris will
come forward and defeat you or not is a
matter of strategy, and in this game,
even if you die once, you can immediately respawn.
Yes, it's a game where you all go forward and
kill as many people as you can.
Yes, I understand. Leave it to me. Also, there
's this, right? You have three hearts, so if you're on the verge of death,
aim for the person with one heart and kill them.  That means it's more
advantageous to go there, right? That's
true, too. It's better to be protected by everyone. The
general has 5 hearts. That's
right. Since he has 5 hearts, he
can withstand it fairly well.  I think it's better if we're just a good two-person team that protects each other. What's the
strategy?
What should we do? Yes, Rika, let's live. Even if we
attack, it's
okay. It's like this. It's like this. At first, it's like, "That's not right."
Yeah, it's
true that there's a continuation at the beginning asking if I should stay behind,
but the more I see it, the more I see. Haha,
what's up with that? I'll
send you a screenshot. There should
n't be any
hearts. It's too heart-breaking. When I start, when I
start.  It's probably going to be a heart, right now,
yeah, yeah, it's like that. It's
okay to change your perspective, oh,
how are you doing? Let's
go.  It's supposed to be
empty, so let's get started. Please
do your best, everyone. Thank you very much.
Attack attack attack attack attack
[Music] It's
scary to attack. There are three
people. There
's no one around the captain. Oh no.  Oh, it
hurts, it's
scary, it's scary, it's scary, it hurts, it hurts, it's scary, it's scary.
I'm sorry, I was hitting you with my bare hands until the middle of the day.
Is that strong? I was also hitting you with my bare hands. I
should have told you I'm sorry. That's right,
that strong
Nomashine Leach was
definitely the one who hit me, not Mike.
Even though he was so strong, he was this strong. This is Yuu.
Even though he had defeated so many people in the beginning, he was
talking to me. He started speaking Japanese, and he
was definitely talented in Minecraft.
But at first, he was a nuisance.
No, no, I was able to make a sword at first. Sword 6 That element
is my Lyrica. It's amazing how strong the yellow group was.
Yellow, nice,
red, white, etc. At first, it froze
and didn't move at all, but...  Yeah, I'm
going to kill only the yellow team, let's go.
[Music]
Hey, I'm in the Amoto group. I
'm going to support you today. So, come to the red group. You
can get it. Change. Yes,
please. Yes, please.  Well,
if you have a lot of trouble, it's a little different on that day
and another one.If you're going to be lower or higher, I don't
know if you can do it at all.Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
then I
'll go with 3.  I'm going to do the line. I wonder
if I'll do it one more time. Su-chan hasn't done it yet, so I
guess it'll be a while, then we'll say goodbye again. [Music] Let's do it,
oh
[Music] That's the one
in blue. Let's have that one do it.
[Music]  It
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
, it's okay forever,
Zuzu-chan will be on top.
I'm going to do it first.Sorry, I fell a little.I'm
with you now.Alright, let
's go.Ok, oh,
wish will harden, just like before.Here,
this time I'll use a sword.It
's definitely a sword.Everyone is equipped with a sword.Look, it's
there.  It can't be helped because it's the first time I've heard of it. It can't be helped,
right? We're having a practice session today. That's right. Which way are we going to go first? There's no need to say anything. The captain is here.
Please, I've attacked him. Hit him!
[Music]
Hit him! It's dangerous.  It's okay, there's still a lot of
life to be had. You're
behind me again. Don't be afraid to hit me.
[Music]
[Applause]
Hit me, low-key.
Haha, I can't defeat the idiot by walking backwards using my shield. I can't defeat him in one go.
Wow, that's what I realized. It's probably better to keep doing more
complicated things than playing him.
Moreover, there is no cool time for respawn,
so you will be respawned right away, so I
'll leave it there, hahahahaha, I'll
only aim for it when white cuts something, or red-red cuts something like a general, or something like that.
HP may be important for HP,
maybe it's important to catch fish, from behind, it's best to take care of it, or
maybe that carrier senior will be the one to deal with it,
or maybe the real one is Nemiko Michia. I see.
Thank you.
Run away.  The guys who can beat up a lot of people without a hitch are
amazing, that's for sure,
but it's funny
because even if they're from different teams, they can practice with each other
whenever they want.  I'd like to
ask everyone if the
person who plays the knight can press the start button.I don't think so.The person who plays the knight can press the start button,
so I'm not sure.After this,
even if the teams are practicing separately, I'll ask them to do it.Yes, I
quite understand how to do it.  I think so.I just
have one question.What do you mean?I had no idea how
many kills that general would have, or what it would be like to kill someone,
but uh, if the general is defeated that one time, you'll
get 1 point.  Well, it
doesn't matter in the team points from earlier, but the new number for the general
is the
same as the final victory points for the match that will be added to the overall benefits.  I
mean, it doesn't matter how many points
you have, it's the bonus points that will be added.At
the end of the scoring, the
first place team will have 15 points, the second place team will have
10 points, and the third place team will have 5 points.  Points That
's right, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
that's what's added there, so I see. Ah,
I finally understood that.
Even if you get killed, the team that finished in third place will receive an
award of 5
points.  If I was playing the game, I'd be
in 3rd place, but I'd get 10 points. That's
right, that's right. That's right, that's right. That's
right, it's really strong.
This looks like it's going to be a bit of a rhinoceros, so I ca
n't keep up. Then in the remaining time, I'll move on
to Gamla.  General:
That's right, I can't even think of a target. That's right,
General. Please
be careful. Yes, that's correct. If you say
yes, what
should we do next? Isn't it better to check once at Higoetsu?
Well,
let's go to
Himekoshi. Are
you saying you're not good enough? I
got beaten up by a naughty pudding. It
's hard to hold back.
Yeah, yeah
, we're already divided
into teams. I still have the equipment for the bar line.  But,
what's good about having the equipment of the tree line? I wonder
if I'm in the middle of the game, but I
think there's just a lot of leftovers, so
I entered with a lot of fighting, so it's
okay. Goodbye to the team.
Please, that Calliope won't be doing this event,
but what should I do? Just take a look and
leave it for me. I think you can watch it from here.
It's Shion-chan, but I'm not here today,
so anyone is fine.
Then Poiris, okay, this is
my friend. I really wanted to do everything I could to kill him.
But yesterday, when we practiced with Ka-chan and Hame-chan, we
started with this part.
Well, change that camera.
Shift
shiifallBL. Ah, if
I crouch and walk like this, I won't fall. I
won't fall off the screen. Yes,
that's OK. I'll confirm the operation. As
expected, I said yes.  It's okay to change your point of view.
That
's okay too. I've come to terms with it. I
think it's better to change. I think it's better to thank you. I mean, it's better to do your best,
try your best, do your best, princess. It's
better to do your best.  Is it okay, Princess?
Maybe I should change my perspective.
Yeah, I don't know,
but Subaru is easy to do,
so I guess I'll change it. But it depends on the person. I'll
give it a try. It's fun, Subaru.  What should I do with the line equipment? Alright, let's
get Subaru. Middle
of the game. Middle of the game. It probably won't disappear. It'll
disappear. I'll take anything with me, so Subaru,
please keep it with me. I
can't give it to you. I'll tell you after it starts.
So, get
to work.  Hey
guys, do your best, try your best, there's already a block on the book.Shiff,
wait a minute, wait a minute, yes, yes,
shift.Yes, yes, shift.Yes, yes, even if I log out,
it won't go away.This yellow won't go away, right?
Good luck,
get off, get off, get off, oh, here,
one more time, woof, woof, oh, red, pink,
pink, red, red,
pillow,
pink, that's good, hurry, hurry, here, uhm,
knights shouldn't talk, knights can't talk.  No, I
can't
even say I'm already there. No, I'm naked, nodding, doing this,
holding something, but it's fine. I'm
pressing the E button. I see, this is
in creative mode, so this is it.  Is
it a refrigerator? Is that
what I am? Is it a refrigerator?
Click it, click it. I wonder where
it is. Yes, nice, it's nice. Is it the other one? It starts with white again. It's okay. It's good. It's good.  That's good too
Tomato Or this is good Tomato or apple Or
paprika Maybe it's apple or
paprika Ah Matsuri Matsuri senpai is nodding a lot Oadone The
tingling is a little subtle
So I'll leave that book as it is.
Rika
Masu, ah, I'm hungry. I want to eat yakitori and fried sorrel. There
's a recipe for fried chicken made by Yakitori in the Iris book.
Um, yakitori.  It's just regular yakitori.
Well, all you have to do is grill two chickens. You
can do it. Subaru's fried chicken is raw chicken. Kako Subaru-
senpai. And, um, flour,
yes. Also, oil. Oil. Is it really fried chicken? Stop it,
stop it.  I didn't write down how many pieces of meat to eat,
so I ate them one by one,
then cut the flour on the cutting board.After
that, I put the
cut chicken and flour oil in a hot pot.  I put it in there
and I
want to eat it.I want to eat it.I just cut it out.It
doesn't contain oil.It should be sold as oil.Someone who sells it has it.Who has it?There was a
glass.It was there.It
was there.  I've got
some oil. I'll put some oil in it and
put it in a pot. It's okay. I drink some oil in the pot.
[Music]
I drink it and it doesn't come off. It's making me squirm,
but please, make it hot. Maybe I'll
drop it.
Yes, yes, yes, that's it, isn't it? Other than that, I haven't written anything else. Then, Iris gets it and eats it, and her name is Subaru's fried chicken. It's
true, it's true, it's true.  Why are you
eating food? I'm kidding. Oh, please
eat another one. Yes, it's
okay. It's a lot. Okay. Well,
let me tell you the color. The top right is
red. The top left is pink. The bottom left is also pink. I
wonder if it's yellow.  I don't understand the bottom right. Please tell me the bottom right.
I think it's yellow. Is it yellow? Yes, it's yellow.
Yes, it's finally time to kill it. Yes, it's
time to kill it. I'll do it later.
Button.  Yes, okay, I'm blowing a whistle.
Revenge,
oh, it's a
mistake, my side is out. My side is out, it's finally out. Be careful, be careful, hide here. It
's
coming! Hit me, hit me, I'll win. I
can't see where it was.  Okay, upper left. Is
this it?
Oh, yes, next time, oh.
Magic
[Music]
Te
[Laughter]
[Music]
Hey
[Applause]
Well done, I
made a machine. Hime-hime. She's a very well-conceived princess. And she's a
princess, and Iris-hime-hime!  Right now, I
can hear you again. I can hear you, Princess.
What does that mean? The princess is the princess of that warlord who
lived in Japan. She's the Japanese princess. Is she
really here? She's not there. She
's so hot, so hot, so hot.  Does that
mean that ea is a strong princess? That
's true. No. It feels different. That's right.
Princesses are really good. That's
right, princesses. She was a beautiful princess, wasn't she? A strong princess.
That's the kanji for eaa.  Wow, that's different. It's
so fast. Hey, there's
still a lot of room for improvement. The yellow team has room to grow.
So, if we practice, we'll be able to shorten the time even more. It looks like we'll
be able to cook and color.
Hey, yeah, yeah, we're practicing, so it looks like we'll have practice after this.
Ah, server.  Sleep again.
2. Yes, the
voice goes back. Yes, there was a yes.
Yes, the princess was on her way. The
princess's ice cream was a princess
and she was in a good mood. That's why she was called Netsuhime.  I think a new
cooking menu has been added,
but Subaru's difficult Subaru's deep-fried chicken was really
surprising.There was an attribute hamburger
, an ennie, and pancakes.Yes,
that's nice.This is what everyone wants to eat.  It's
okay for me to ask the orchestra to do everything like this for now, but I'm trying to do everything
right now.
[Music]
[Music] I
want
to go.  Yo,
what's
wrong? It's
okay. I was thinking, ``I'm not going to let you go to sleep,'' so I'm
waiting. Then suddenly I say something.
[Laughs] There are
people who practice on the floor, and people who want to do
this and that. That's
right. People who want to practice.  How
should we practice? I do
n't know what to do. Or maybe we should just do it once. Well,
maybe this is it. Right now, you can do it with an unlimited number of people.
Maybe you should try it once. There's already a red
player.  I think it's just the
three of us who can't do it right now, who can't do it today, who can't do it right now. Yeah, there
's three of us. Hey,
Chiara Let's go now, uh, Kia and Su.
Well, this
is the same for the actual performance, right?
Please give it a try. Yes, I
went to that other server where I said "Good luck." I
feel like if I cheer hard, it'll get messy. I'm
sure I'll open up a group and play that game. The
members who will be playing will be number 6
and number 1.  Okay, please move me to number 1. I
can't hear everyone's cheers. I'm
going to do what I want to do while I'm going. It's okay to do what I want to do, so please join the team.
Eeeeeee
[Music]
Do your best, try your best, do your best,
stranger.  I'm staring into space all the time. Is
this okay? I
want to watch it with you, just like Sui-chan from earlier. I want to be infected and climb to the top. Yes, I
can do it. I can become a living person.
If I become an infected person, I'll become a ghost.  I'm going to take it, so I
'll take it. Wow, it's fast. Do your best. Do your best. Do your best. Hurry up. Everyone's good. Hurry up, swimmers. Don't try hard. Do your best. B is really bad, but oh, it's interrupted, oh, it's interrupted.
Well, we can't do it all over again. No, Sui-chan. Let's
do it all over again. We can play one more time. Ahhh, I'm getting warm. My shoulders are starting to grow. After all, I'm going to play first. Nasu-chan. Yes, I've
been using my legs until just now.  I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
what are you talking about? I'm going to use my fingers. I'm going to use my fingers because
someone else pressed the button, so if I press the wrong button, I'm
going to poop all over the place, so I'm going to do it
one more time, okay? Well, let's go, do your best, Ji-
senpai.  Do your best,
do your best, do your best, go up like Mercury, go up
Yes, if
you want to see it, go to the cat's spectator mode.Press
the cat's purple sign.Here it comes.Good
boy, are you okay?Here we go, nice,
nice, here we go, here we go, we're
on track  Come on, come on, hurry up. No, no
, it's okay. It's
still not good. It's not a problem. It's not a problem. It's okay. Yo,
senpai, A has come up. La, senpai. That's
good. But where are you at the end? It's
okay. It's okay.  First thing first, let's
go to the checkpoint. First
thing first, let's all have a chat.
What did I eat today? I'm nervous.
Okay, Han, what did I just eat? What did I eat? My favorite book. I ate mackerel. I
ate mackerel.
Calm down.  Let's go,
senpai,
but we're catching up.
Yeah, there's not that much of a difference. There's not that much of a difference. That's
right. By the way,
let's touch the bed on the right.  Alright, alright, this is it, by the way, we
have about 6 minutes of pre-season time, so don't get
too impatient. Stretching the knot, I'm floating to death, my head is floating, my severed head is floating. It's flying fast, but this is alright. It's a
route that makes a really bold move.  I get it. Just take the route you've given.
All you have to do is imitate
Ruto.  We're
all together, we're all at the
bar, we're here, we're here to
get the bauba, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing
, it's so hot, we're eating UB, it's so hot, we're so
nervous, we're already under pressure, aren't we?
When I reach the goal, I've
done quite a bit of Unchan, but when I reach the goal, it's really
bad. Normally, it's really hard, but it's a little bit of a problem. That's because
there are 6 minutes, so I guess that's because
Trident's cooldown is pretty short right now.  It's
okay to wait for today. Is it okay to do everything today? Yes, it's
okay to do everything today. It's just that there is a possibility that some adjustments will be made, so now is the time to make adjustments.
Yonema, it's 6 minutes long. It's
been 6 minutes long. It's been 6 minutes long. But it's
difficult to understand without doing this. It's quite difficult even if you do it. It's so nice. Thank you. Nice. Thank you.
Nice. Nice.
Nice. Even.  I really like the yellow team,
it's amazing, everyone is not on top, it
's good, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's
amazing, this is the winner, the winner is the winner, we're going to win, there's a lot of
pressure on us,
everyone is at Anya's place.  I have some
left over here, so I
'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I
guess I'll do my best with the equipment. That's right, bring the fang line
equipment. I've got that equipment.
Please do it. Let's
do it like this. Let's do it like
this. Let's do it. Don't do it like this. Do
n't do it. I'm
thinking about doing it. Don't do it. Don't do it right away.
Well then,
there's no tsukkomi.
What's scary
is that there aren't that many members of the Subaru Yellow Team on that day. It's true. It looks
like it's
going to be fun. It seems like Fu is going with the yellow team.
Ruff is good.  I'm sorry, Isuma-chan. The
follow-up person for the yellow one is
still here. She's there. She's already there. She's not there. She's not there.
She's not in the red and white. Do you want to
have someone substitute for her and do it one more time
?
Oh, wait a minute, then I
'll enter. Oh, then I'll enter. There's a
soul here
[music]. People
might say I don't go there. I
can't enter the world like this.  I'm sorry, can't you enter now?
Wait a minute. I can't do this. But even if I
play the game, this item wo
n't disappear. Items that won't disappear. Oh, I
tried re-entering. That's right. I fixed it once. I did it when I got home.  I
wonder if I was able to enter, but I don't have any horses. Tame-san is the only one who is trapped in the world of fangs. Ah, that's right. I can't say it. I can't say it. Please help me. But if I click on the signboard of my well, my entry will be cancelled.  I made it, just
now I touched the signboard on the wooden line.I'm here right now.I can tell you, I tried that.
Even if there are a lot of people, there are
no entries.
Wait, you have to enter 3 teams.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Try Red. Red. Yes. Red.
Maybe Mercury-senpai will enter again. Ah,
horse.  Even
if I interrupt the game and cut it off, it won't go away.I have a
trident.I have a trident.It was the same thing yesterday.  I
still
have a lead in the hunt, and I practiced with Ririka in the morning for the first time, but
this was it, right?
Oh, I saw you right now, so I'm interrupted.
Should I press it? It won't work. I don't know what to do.
The book is still there, but it's turned into a book, so it's okay. It's
okay, it's
okay. That's that, so it's
okay.  I can do it, I can do it, thank you,
thank you. I have a
trident left for some reason, but I
think it's because of this, and it's that usual. It's always
been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
That statue will come to you
in the middle of the night and say, "Let's get along." That
's right, he'll come with his nipples exposed. Hey,
hey, thank you very much. Good morning.
Thank you. That's cool. Good luck.
Thank you.
Oh my god, the ceiling is giving out nettle lights.
Wait a minute. There are too many trytes. There are too many toilets. I wonder if it's too much. I'm
scared of the noise. A friendly white is coming inside. It's
hitting here and there.
Stop,
get angry, game master.  It seems that the game
master is angry. Be angry.
Do your best against that scary thing. If you do your best, you'll be
cute.
Hey, that's no good. It's being played during the game.
That entry. Ah, I haven't entered it.  Daaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh--uh-uh--'' uh-uh--- uh-oh-ah, I'm an ah-san, I'm an ani-san.
There are people, so I didn't
have to say anything to my colleagues in the future. It
's okay. It's okay, it's okay. I'll do my best. Slow down, take
it easy. You're
putting your face on the ice cream. That's nice. I'm glad you
were able to convey the word ice cream.
There's a cookie in this, but it's still a face.
Yes, it's Nico, but no, I'm not going
to poop. I'm trying my best.
[Music]
Do your best to talk dirty, please do your best.
Do your best with a heart that doesn't have a face. This is good.  It's a
completely different layout than when I first started. It
may have changed. It's changed quite a bit. It's
okay to get updates every day. It's okay. I have
n't lost that much. I have a lot of time. It's the
same with this game, right?  I
may or may not have been a strong person when I was there, but I've changed so much that
it's confusing.It
doesn't
really matter who was the first to reach the goal.  That's right, it doesn't really have anything to do with the goal.Yeah, it
doesn't matter.Then I
hit the goal.Well, if I go to the goal, I'll get the points.Yeah, that's right.It's
not that I see, I have a lot of leeway.Don't
rush this game.  It's
okay to go slowly and it's okay. Koani -san at my own pace, I'm really practicing yesterday
.
Really, yes, that's right, Anisan, really,
but you have that bed, bed, bed,
bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed, bed.
Then it becomes slow, right? Yeah, it's
like I'm learning it for the first time. It's
going to be in slow motion. That's right.
There are slow motions. Yes, there are slow motions. The
layout is really weird. I
practiced it. I
practiced it.  It's
okay if you do your best, it's amazing what it's amazing now. It's like a trick right now. It's too early to return. By the way, this time Kiara
is really stable
10m.  That's 1 point, so hmm
. Well, that's how I got it, so I got a lot of points. I
get 20 points.
Yeah, that's right. 20 points, 10m, 1 point.
So yeah, it's 100, so 200m is the top,
so that's a point.  You're so stubborn, stubborn, stubborn, Ani-san, it's
okay.If you'd rather have a chat, just tell me.It's totally fine.You can tell me not to talk.You're totally deceiving me.You're deceiving me.No, not at all, please don't talk anymore.Oh, it's true.  What's
going on?
Miko is just listening to me.
Amiko-senpai, this is so messed up yesterday.
The layout is completely different. It's just my feelings. I'm
making some adjustments, actually.  I'm
surprised that this has changed so much. Even if you're a, you
can do it. Thank you very much. It's already been a long time
since you won. By the way,
Miko, I think it's okay to throw to the top.  There are a
lot of options around here,
right? When you fall, it's like adjusting a little bit.
The goal is about 20 seconds,
so it's probably better to stay at the highest point.
Well, that means the course will be different tomorrow as well.  I'm going to
make some adjustments.This is the
final one, so if you can make this as it is, it'll be the
same as the original.I'm glad.321
So I
was in the middle of falling down.I
feel like it was easier to do yesterday than yesterday.
But it's still a
bit of a challenge. If you'd like, let's practice together after this. Let
's practice. Let's
all get together once, do the next round of relays, and
then we'll be pretty free.  I think I'll give it a
try.Okay, then I'll leave the Boise server as it is.Either
way, I'll go to Relay.I'm
going to go to Ore's Go Lets, Go
Go Relay, this year.The system is
amazing.The system is big on me.Yeah.
When it's that person's turn, it
will automatically warp, so
you have to register, which is a bit
complicated, so let's do it together now.  It's time for
everyone to run in the relay today. Well, not everyone will be there.
Well, wait a minute. I
want to do it. Let's all
run once. That's fine. Okay, okay.
Iris is here. Iris is No. 1.
Enter.  So I'm going to black right now, so I'm going to go
to black, Sui-chan, black is going to save me, so next time,
Sora-chan, sora-chan, please touch me.
Wait from home, just
press Elo and you'll get it. I've made a
book. I'm sorry.
Can I get 8 people to enter? Yes, that's what I'm
doing, so the next one is. Yes,
press Lyrica. I'm here.  I didn't press it, it
's okay, it's okay, this is in that order, it's
always okay That's okay, that's okay Well, I tried Lyrica, yes, I did it,
okay, then wait for the next Polka, and damn it's an even number It's
scary, it's okay, it's difficult because it's practice.
There's no one, so it's okay, you
can come in with Aji-sanra. It's No. 8.
That's right, the first one is the anchor, and they say, ``Do your best, do your best, and you're good at
fitting.'' Hakosu is amazing. He
plays the drum band.
Well, Tahaji-chan definitely has the talent for microphone training.
Yeah, that's right. I keep saying that. No,
the other day, I was actually practicing riding,
and it was really slow. Even
though everyone started, it started last.
For some reason, it became number 1. It's amazing. It's so fast.
It's the food's secret.
Kachan-chan is in the book. Well,
now there are 9 people who are getting the book.
Wait a minute, there are 9 people all of a sudden.  When it comes to people, there are
only nine of us, right?
I mean, if you open the book now, you'll
see the entry list with everyone's faces in the bar, and it's amazing. Yeah, there
's that there.  Yeah, the second runner is
on the yellow block. When I open the book, I see
this is
number 7. I think it's correct, so I'm starting with number 8.
Yes, that's nice. This is what I'm
using for practice.  We've reached the point where we can max out 9 people,
so it's
okay to ignore that last fever.They'll carry us properly at the beginning, so I'd
like the club to carry us.We'll
start when everyone's all together.  You made a mistake, you're a senpai, so
show me how cool you are, Ruka-san.
I'm
sorry, it's me. If you say it the other way around, you're more of a senpai, aren't you? In fact, you're more of a senpai. To senpai 6,
yes, that's right, that's right, that's right. You
can ask Chan 2 to go.
So, after Kaade Polka is Spar? Oh, I
think everyone has entered, so I
think I'll get the baton. The great manipulator
Iris has the baton. I don't have the baton.
All I have is that book.  When you start, the
baton will appear, and you don't have it.
Yes, that's right. When you start, Iris
will have the baton first, so you
can pass the baton by hitting . I see. Yes, that
means you can click that button. Left click. Yes,
left click.  Where is the second person
? Where is the standby?
Well, this is here. I can't see Subaru right now. It's just here, right here.
Here, here, this is the start, and this is the
first half. The first half is ok. Okay, here we come.  I'm here, I
'm here, I'm going to do my best, I'm going to do my best. Hey, second person, let's go over there. Okay, it's probably the
start of the jump. It's
faster to jump and jump, okay, okay.
Nice, nice, nice,
nice. Show your juniors how cool you are, Elia.  The noisy
senior who is working hard The princess who is working hard has arrived There are
so many, I'm
not a princess.Oh, I'm not a princess.Ah,
try your best, you're good, I wonder
if you're not good yet.Wait a minute, the second one is coming.The
second princess, the second princess, is being reborn.The
reborn, reborn princess.  The
part where you can see the princess who is waiting for the second princess star Jump jump
jump Nice final jump, do your best Oh, it's
coming Good
luck,
yes, teacher, it's really fast,
hurry, do your best It's fast, you're a big fan So do your best So-chan Taira-kaa Sui-chan-
bayo  Su-
chan, good-chan, do your best, do your best.
It's difficult here. It's difficult in the second half.
So
star, it's nice star. Wait for the fool.
What's that? That's me, that wave. Keyoi, oi, yoi, yo. Where is that 7?  It
's okay, I'll do my
best,
then I'll
go to Lyrica, then I'll move on to Lyrica, but if it's in this order, then I'll be sorry
to Polka-senpai.  It's
better to eat it. Oh, I see. That's why I
wasn't running. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Eating this bread is
pretty important. Bread is left
click or right click. Left left left
Click right to pick it up and left to eat it.
That's right, it's complicated. Take it on the left. Ah, nice. That's okay. That's right, Senpai.
Hurry, hurry,
fast. Wow,
swiss. I can see it,
but I can see it. I can see it. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Look at your shoulders. Look, it's
Luca.  What
should I do? This is the only way to climb. This is the only way to climb.  It
's a passion color, so it's okay, so I put a lot of
thought into it. Nice,
nice, nice, it's almost
impossible. Good luck, do your best.
Oh, you can win this. You can win this. I
chased you, I fell. It's
okay, do your best.
Husband jumps there. It's really good.
Yeah.  I can't do it here. It's okay. No, I'm
sorry. I'm
going to climb up. I'm going to climb up. And in front of me, I'm nice and nice. I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll go up, I'll
go up, I'll come down, I'll be
stubborn. 1  The
wave of people is amazing, just like Pummel Physical Passion and the times. The
narration of the polka came. Good
luck! It's
One Piece. One Piece. This is One Piece. Ah,
nice, nice, nice, eh,
Nanaipa.
Well, this is okay, okay, okay, well, that's okay, but originally, I have to
eat bread,
but I see, I can do it, but I
can do it.
You're amazing!
[Music]
Do your best, try your
best, you're
good at it. Calm down. You can do it. You can do it. Takumi: You'll be there. Roi, Nemecha, you're good. What's wrong with yellow? There's a possibility of winning.
Yes, you won. No, please
stop flagging. It's
true, it's true
that you've only given out 20%. No matter
what kind of game you play, you're finishing it from now on. Yellow
Chim. That's yellow. Look at me. Teru-a-
senpai. Oh, this was Sora-senpai.
Miko says she's doing it right now.
Look at
me. I
'm listening to a lot of waves. Miko, I
'm listening to a lot of waves.
Gol
Nice. It's going to come out in seconds. That's
right. It's
amazing. Lyrica and that.  They're fighting each other.
What's this? The
space-color chim is so
overflowing with passion. Mental,
physical, physical, physical,
mental,
physical.
Hey,
a monster is coming. A monster, a monster with all of his face exposed. A
monster with all his face exposed. By the way, we're
going to do a relay tomorrow before the actual show.  I think we should go to the studio, right? What
time is it, N? Well,
we'll meet tomorrow. Everyone's going
to be at the studio a little early, at 3 o'clock. Well then,
I'm sorry.
I'm at work, so I'll be joining you around 5:30pm.
I understand, I understand, I understand, I understand. It looks like Ki-chan is
already ready for the follow-up.
Thank you very much. I hope you'll take
care of me tomorrow. I'll leave you some time for that.
Yes, I'll chat with you later.
Yes, I understand. Thank you very much. After
this, I'll practice. Is there anyone who would like to practice something after this? I
wonder if it's a princess voice or something like that. I want to do it. I want to do it.
There's something I want to do.  Let's
get in the way, everyone. Let's try to master the rele. Let's master the rele.
Well then Sui-chan's bad. I
'm not saying that the first half is better or the second half is better, but
this is it.  I've already submitted this.
Ah, I see. I'm sorry. Which one is this
? This is today's one. Yes, it's today's one. It's not today's. Well, it's the one I posted on the cat's chat.
Oh, then it changes. It's an even or an odd number.
[Music]
That's right, 1 is
Kaku-chan, 4, 1 is Iris
, I'm sorry, and 5 is polka, and 6 is, and 7-chan
[Music]
Please, give me a favor. Please
tell me, I want to listen to Ice Speed.  Let's
go check it out. Ice bomb. Here
on the ice.  I
thought I'd run another round, so I was quite
satisfied with the yellow, but
if there was one more race, I'd do it.There are a lot of ice rolls,
but the ice is blue, and the ice is blue.Right
now, I'm hitting the practice ball repeatedly.
Wow, I was just practicing without starting.Oh yeah, but if I had one more time, I'd do it at all, but I guess it's okay.So, for the ride, is it okay to practice without using that system?
I didn't eat bread just now, but
Lua says I have to eat bread.
I didn't eat it either. I don't have to eat either. But if I don't
eat, I won't recover my strength,
so I'll be
late.  It's
fine, but if you're full, I want you to take the bread that you couldn't eat.  I
can reach the goal even if I don't take it, so
yeah, yeah,
yeah, I want that.Okay, it's pretty difficult, so make sure to take it.You don't have to
eat it.You don't have to eat it.But if it's okay if
it's late, then I guess that's what it
feels like.Eat
it.  If they don't have it, it's against the rules,
isn't it? Yes, Japan has to take it.
That's a rule. Well, from here on out, I
want to make it feel like each team is together,
but I guess that's the only way to move in a competition that uses a system.
Well, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I guess I'll just gather all the people who want
to do it. Hey, oh, then when I go out and do some kind of competition, I'll have a chat with you, and then I'll go over there.  I'm going to
do it again, I'm going to
do it again, this is a relay, I'm sorry, I just
took the bread of Lille right now, but I
can't eat it right now, I ca
n't eat that game.  Right-
click and eat by right-clicking as normal.Click to see the
snow after that icy place.It looks like you
can jump over it if you do something like that.You
can jump over it all, no, no, you can jump over it.If the
timing was right when you jumped over it, you'd get to
that last minute.  Press and hold only the line. It's
almost like
this. It's important, it's important. It's
so important.
[Applause] It's an
iris, so just press it repeatedly like I'm told.
It's just the power of flying.  The
power of God is going to make a big difference. I'm
sure all the other teams will
jump out and ask me how they're doing it. It's
amazing. They're going to collide with each other. What's so good about this?
Tell me, tell me, the idiot in the middle.  Well,
I've been to a lot of places, but to be honest, cloud nests
can be found anywhere, but I can't
seem to get caught in them.The trick is to not go diagonally.It's better to go diagonally and straight.It's
really straight.  Even when turning,
something is blocking the far right side. It's
not diagonally, so you
can just push straight on the far right side. The
outside one is better, the inside left side.  But I
feel like it's probably faster.It
's easier to do it on the right side, which doesn't have inside entry or ririn, but it's faster on the left side.Maybe it's
easier to hit on the left side because it's flying.That side is
easier to hit, but it's faster.
Can you please take a look at the
video? I want to make a video.
Seriously, who is the person who shared the last video?
If you turn like this, you'll
be able to pass
it at that diagonal.I
thought, 100% of the time, you can pass this at that diagonal,
and then you can pass it like this.  It's a book that gets stuck when you try to
read it, right? It has
to be done like this. It has to be straight. That's right, if you don't move so that you can see the spider's nest in front of the book, it will
hit you. Ah, I see. It's
true. After all, it's based on squares.
Minecraft doesn't have any diagonals, so
this person came and saved me.If
anyone has recorded it, please record it later and
give it to me.I hope it helps.Actually,
there is a way to almost get there without bumping into anything.Yo,
what's going on?  Is there a way to avoid hitting the pool pool? The
strategy is
too bad. It's too low. I want to go. I want to go.
When I write anything other than the 1st one, I hit those 3 in a row, except for the 1st bottom. I
understand.
There are three lines, but if you
go all the way to the bottom, you'll never hit
anything other than the bottom. That's amazing, but the
top and the middle are easy to hit, so
go down anyway.  If it sinks to the bottom and then
goes up, it doesn't have to be that bad.If it goes up, it doesn't have to be that bad.If it goes up, it doesn't have to be that bad.The
more it goes down, the more it goes up.The analysis team has come to the sky.  Even
if you hit it at the bottom, if you
press space just a little, you can come up, so I
think you can go a little forward without bumping into it.
Yeah, that's great. Well, I'm sure that's true,
based on this once. The bottom one is
stable, stable.  It's true, it's coming, but it
's stable.It's true that it's
faster to jump at the timing instead of running in the cherry blossom area.On the other hand,
that's a stupid character.Yeah,
in the fish area, I don't really care about jumping.
Jump dash is probably the
fastest, but when you jump dash, you
often fail. Yeah, I don't know the timing, so you'll
run out. I think when you get to the stairs, you can
first jump and then press and hold to
go. Yeah, it's a long jump.  Next, I'm
doing something that I think I can fly, oh, I'm the
red team, or I'm playing Kolo Hunteme. I
want to go
hunting. Hunting with other people. Is it okay? I'm like
that too. It's okay. Hunting is going on. But, to be
honest, that's the problem of the day.  It's pretty amazing, I see,
but I'm
a little worried about Luka's character design, which will be removed in Reto, so I'd
like to do it later.Oh yeah, hunting, I understand.I've
never done it, but I'm a member.Um,
yeah, that's right, I, Hattie, are
playing.  I
'll do it at this timing.
I'll do the yellow one, and I'll do the yellow one.
This means you can do both. You
can do the catching one, you can do the catching one. You can do the catching one.
Wait a minute.  I
wanted to learn what to do in order.Once I decide
who I want to do, I enter.Yo, who will do the hunting?
Yellow, it's my first time, and who's going to do the opposite?This is good.Ihiro, I guess it's
hunting.I
want to do it only once.Now, wait a minute.
Yellow asked me if I wanted to go hunting.Yes, I'll
wait for him to come back.Yellow, please let me go
hunting.The
other members of yellow, the red team, were
quick.Okay, I'm sorry.Then,
what am I doing?Okay, I'm a fugitive.  Yes,
yes, this person is okay, yes, yes, let's
run as fast as we can.That's right, but the color of that name
might be quite important.You'll
understand by looking at it.I wonder if you'll understand.It's
true that people who don't wear the top jersey might not understand.  Tomorrow I'll
wear short sleeves, but I'll wear short sleeves and a jersey.I'm so tired of wearing jerseys.I'm
sure it's cute, but it's cute,
but it's easy to understand.That blue color is coming out.The shoulders are really sticking
out.But
that's how it looks.  It's important and appearance is important.It's
definitely fashionable.The
title may have been changed for the second half, but it's
probably a one-shot.I
see, I don't like it, but the people in the red group are the ones who get in the way of red.I'm
not red, so after all, it's the first one.  Red, if you're behind my back, I wo
n't be able to find out. Wow, you're a genius. Go behind my back. It's not like I can't go.
As expected, I could go behind my back.
There was someone hiding there.  It's something, but it's normal,
but I got caught, but it's different. I was
playing polka
earlier, and it was strong. It's here, in the clouds. It's really strong. We're all there. We're all
friends, and we're on the right side from the statue.
Even though this is the base of the clouds,
this is 0 sandpipers, right now, the red group is playing,
but I had to catch the red group, so it's
zero, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, the yellow group is the corner body there.  What's the
point
? She's cute, she's cute, she's got a white body,
and she
's not in the white team. Maybe it's
okay to wear a jersey, lol. I
wonder
how long she's going to be called a princess. I
want her to get caught with the yellow person, so she's here now.  I'd
like to try it out a little bit.This
is a person who is difficult to grasp.I think
if it's in front of the cage, it's in front of the cage.I
don't blame you at all, but I think it's better if it's in the back.If it
's in front of me, it looks like there's someone behind me.
In the end, it's dangerous
in the end, so it's not good because it's close. I'm close, so I purposely did it here in the
back, here in the back, here in the back, uh, in the middle of practicing,
and there. No, I'm
not chased. What's going on?  It's
all going crazy. It's like everyone's in the dark
. It's like they're all
just talking about something. They're all making nonsense. Kagome,
I'm a bit confused. I'm
just going to fall.  Even if it ends like this, I'm
tired, I'm tired, I'm
tired, then I'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you, Passion Power, Baba Passion Power, Mental
Physical,
Passion,
Mental Passion. I guess it's better for Red to do it one more time.
Yellow,
please make an escape entry.Yes, yes, yes.Entry
okay, entry, sorry.That's white,
yellow, white, yellow.That's white, yellow, white,
yellow.That's my red team.They
still haven't figured out the motion of touching with the rope.
No, it's just the first half,
just the first half without interrupting in the middle.Okay, you
can do it for practice.Or
you can catch it by right-clicking, and you can catch it by left-clicking.Yeah,
left-clicking.  All
Rope rope right touch too touch left maybe one
Chan wait touch left ta ah signboard touch left
Kaunta signboard touch left it's
too complicated Okay left click to release the rope Narumenakueah
really a bit then that too
I guess I'm curious about that too, I guess I'll try it out in the order I want to try it.Catch
it with the right hand and write it like that on the rule back.
Well, maybe I'll
try it once. Yeah, good evening. I
think I'll get caught on the right and the left will fold in, but I can't release it. I think
so. Yeah, I don't think I can release it.
No, it's the two of us. It looks like
the two of us are running now. It's already a festival. I
wonder if someone who doesn't have the theme is caught by mistake. That's right. When the person who doesn't have the theme is
caught, a bang is fired.
Is it going to be an auto venue after being played by a pa? Is it going to go to the cage
? I feel like it's different when I try to put it in the cage.
Maybe it's just now.  You're
supposed to catch this red one right now. It's a
little bit of practice, so don't move too much
. Yeah, let's hit the target. We're going to catch
him. Catch me. Catch me.
Catch me. I'm going to make a mess. It's over.
I love you, I
love you, I love you, you stop loving me, you're in trouble, you stop, I
love you, you don't love me, you've
been caught, you've been caught,
you might like me Sora-chan, you're
making some bold moves.The person who ran this game.
I wonder if it's okay to run, but I wonder if it's better to have some
people running and some people who aren't running.It's
true that if we all run together, it'll be too much.It's
better not to stick to one place.  That's serious.
Yes, that's right. It's like a stack kill. Yes, that's right. If I
get chased, someone will definitely
become that person. Even if the festival comes or goes,
this is also practice, so
I'll have to catch it.  It's my first time in a prison. I
want to go into a prison. It's cramped and
painful.
It's the first time I've been in a prison.  I said "I got kicked out, I
got kicked out, I got caught, I got caught," but yeah, it's true.
Maybe there are too many people. They're getting kicked out. I've
been hacked. I've been
hacked. I've been hit. But it
's all added up in the numbers.  I guess I'm here. I've
been hunted. I guess I'm dead
. Now, wait a minute, I'm having trouble
breathing.
This trash is fine. When I put it around my leg, the string
burst. You know, when I run in the opposite direction, it
gives off that nice feeling. I caught it in the blue.
That's right, I didn't. I didn't know what was going on behind me. I was running around to people, and I didn't get into the cage. I don't think I'm going to run. It's the yellow
team. If Sora-chan, the hunter, runs away, it's
okay. I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything I wanted to do.
Okay, sora-chan and ma-chan, right
click, left fan, right click, left pan. Yeah, it
looks delicious. I don't have enough left left. I
want to be the cat's escapee.
Oh, yeah, maybe Kacha would be good, too. That's
right.
That's okay, Pol-chan, let's go.
Pol-chan, you've taken the trouble to enter, so practice. But what's the
trick? He seems
anxious when he dies, so don't cry like that
. Right-click. When you find someone, right-click.
First, right-click. Yellow. From the beginning, right-click.
Yes, even if you are not a hunter on the yellow team, please
enter as a fugitive.
Where is the entry sign? I wonder where the
signboard is. It's here. In front of me. It's here. It's here.
It's here. It's this place.  Please
somehow erase this button by the day of the day.
Don't erase it. It
's too late. Well, it's not too late. I want to
leave it on the internet. No
one's watching it. It's okay, no one's watching it.
Hey.  Well, it's my first time, so it's a bit off,
isn't it? Look at this, it's okay, no, no, I
think it's wonderful
naked art. Wonderful, completely naked. It's wonderful, completely naked art, isn't it? Is it art
? Iris, this isn't art. Art,
art. I think it's art. No, that's
it.  I was kicked out one more time,
one more time, one more time, please. Yes, one more,
okay, okay. I
wonder what you're going to say. Yeah, it
doesn't really matter. I'm a bird, and I'm not a good person, so I don't think it's okay.  Do you have bird nipples? It's
not that I know, it's that I know. It's fine
because it's about me
after all. Really,
anything is possible. It's
scary, but even if it's scary, we still get along. It's
becoming cute.  Naso-chan is friendly and cute.What do you
think about this movement in Hololive
?Isn't it enough?I
thought that's the answer.
But for now, I want to catch it,
so I'm on the right, that's it, it's Subaru.  I
clicked and ran away.
The polka was played because it was different from the current theme.
Maybe it's okay. It's a
festival too. Catch the people from the red group. The people from the red group are like that.
Anya, bridge shift, really.  I'm on the bridge, it
's white right now, oh, this is that, that right click,
no
left click, I don't use it, left click, cut right, only right,
right click even in front of the sign, I'm really
sorry, right  It's like canceling the light, I see. It's
completely removed and you can cancel it.
If you think it's too bad, you can cancel it.
No, it's gone. Everyone is lying. It's
not white. It's cut off in the middle.
In the first place, there aren't any white people here, so I'm
hitting on you. It's amazing here. It's right there. Hey, I
knew I was going to change my mind, so yellow came.
[Music] I was
put in the middle of the day, Awa-chan
ran really hard.  I'm
trying to have some fun, and I'm
crowded in a fun place, and the inside is
getting more and more crowded, and I'm sweating more and more. I'm
sorry, Princess Niohime.
It's a little sweaty.
Yeah, I'm
sorry for the little bit. I
got
it. I got it. I got it. I
got it. I got it. Oh, right click, right click, click right. Click, click, click. Okay, that's good, that's good, that's good.  I don't know if it's
white, so
please enter the fugitive one
more time.Yes, I'll try to run away next time, or I'll try to
run away once, so I'm making some adjustments.It's
true that I haven't shaved off the white of the red.
Yeah, it's a white white
, it's true, it's really
hard, so it's so big that it's so strong that it's so strong
that it doesn't
matter.
That's right,
so maybe we
should just run around in Neso-chan's style. No, it's
definitely here, here, here,
strong, here, too strong. Here, where, where, where, here, let's
take a look inside this yellow building. This is the
mouse.  I'm very
strong. I'm very strong.
Kome. You can call me Me. We're very similar. The
honey ma position is open for one person. By
the way, the two of us who are here will fit in. The two of us who can do it, the
two of us who want to take the entrance exam, right? Kumo, we've
been caught, we've been caught.
What will happen if they get caught?
Kanuo, wow, it looks like these two can go. Two people will fit in. Is it okay? It's okay, the swing is good, bra.
They're stubborn. They're not popular. I can't see anything. It's
dangerous, so it's only Akori's head.  I can't see it, that
hair smells. What are you talking about?
It's
yellow and white, white and white, white and white. It's totally fine. I can
see it. If it's Lyrica that I can see, then I don't like it. I've
had a lot of dicks. It's so bad.  If you don't,
then you really don't want to.If you don't
say no, you won't stop.Even if you say really no, you won't stop.That's it.You
should pull away.It's
embarrassing, Sasa-senpai.Our
turn will come in 1010 seconds.We're the strongest
here.Here.  I
like your face.
Even in the experiment, it didn't matter who you were, you
were captured normally. It's true that everyone is
not hiding, it's dangerous, oh Noel, you're being captured. Stop it, Suke-san. You're the
best, but you're on that path. Suba-
senpai is great. You're really good at
remembering.  Then, suddenly, I
was warped
to a place where someone was strong, or
something, and suddenly I was forced to go to warp.  It seems like it's
all over when they go to the beach, I see.It's just that it's hard to hook them, but it's easy to catch them and take them with them.We can't move, after all.
Even though I said it was fine, I was worried.This
time, I was running around.What was it like?I was running around.I was
getting caught, right?Yeah, I was able to
run away once, but then I got caught.But
somehow I had to go for it myself.
It's okay, I don't know who the demon is, so if I head towards it, I'll get caught.I'm sure I'll turn around and not know who the demon is right now.I don't know at all, so I'll go right sideways.  The
moment I met Noel's eyes, I was ready to die. I
thought it was over, but I was sure it was all over.
Please, I was captured. I was prepared. I guess I
was standing. I guess I
won't be there anymore. Yeah, this is my one hunting
trip. Maybe.  That's right because it's the end. I want to do a Hime voice.
Please, I
want to do it again soon. If you wait a little,
I'll put it in the chat once. The
next voice is good. The next voice is good.
Who is the voice?
Nemi
and I can't
make it stick. I've become a princess. I've become a princess.
Only the characters that match. I'm sure Miko and I have both started from the beginning, so that's the only thing we have in common.
Yomiko came, but something about her disappeared.  Hey, Miko, Chimiko-senpai, I
can't hear you, Miko-senpai, I ca
n't hear you. I can't hear your voice, Michi. Goodbye, Miko-
senpai. I can't see you've gone here. I can
see Miko, but she's still alive. Miko,
Sachi, Ji-a-
but,
wait a minute.  So, Subaru is
over here. Wait a minute. There's nothing below this.
And I'm pretty sure it's just long enough that it won't fall. It's
long, so I pulled out a little at the end. Maybe I
should go to the right at the end. There's no room at all.
But don't run that way, Pol.
Maybe the pool is the easiest. After all, that's
what I came for. I
put it in. I
heard laughter. Subaru Oh, that's
right. Let's go. Aja Polka. It's about
time to stream.  I'm going to practice cutting it, but I was streaming it. I'm
going to stream it too, and then I'll cut it. It's
about time. If you want to practice cutting just that frame, I'll practice it in a different room.
If you're a little worried, come to the darkroom first. Anyone who
wants to do it.  I think it's fine for
people to do it.I think anyone who wants to do it can do it at all.Maybe I'll
just cut it out and bring it over here.I'll
go there for a moment.Oh, yes.Okay, then let's just leave it as it is.
[Music]
Oh, this is that.
That's a lot of stuff with food.I think Minecraft will probably get drunk.That
guy's fang line is pretty good.That's
true.The screen is pretty good.  It's swaying, isn't it? On the
contrary, I'm jumping
up and down, so it's okay. Is
it up? If it's up, it
might be too much. It's my intention, so it's too much. Hahaha, it's okay. Yeah, it doesn't seem to be okay. It doesn't seem like it's going to be much bigger than before.
Now, after this cat.  I do
n't mind practicing at all, but it looks like I'm going to close it once as a whole.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
can I go
please please?I'm sorry aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
with a
That's what I thought, so I
closed it and said yes, it's okay to continue. But I'm thinking of closing it for now.
So, um,
can I ask you to join me in the long arm where everyone is? Yes, I don't know. Yes.
What if I close it when I get home and then let the people who do it as they are do the same thing and then I close it once I feel like it's ok Yes, I'm going to get together Yes, yes, yes Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I'm going to come back, then I
'll close it.  Okay, that's okay.
Thank you very much everyone for today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your dedication, or rather, for practicing so hard. I'm really happy for you. I hope you'll be able to
support the members who weren't able to come.  I
hope we can all have fun together,
so thank you very much for
your help. This call is about team-related things, but I'm
calling out to people who want to play with that call, so please
come at the right time.  Can I get it? It's the
same with the Fang Fang line that starts up,
and the follow-up,
and I can't do it all at once, so I'm
thinking of doing it on my turn, so I'm just gathering only those who want to do it and
having them come.  It's like,
yeah, yeah, I'm going to do it, so I'm going to turn it, and then I'm going to
close the frame after this, or I can
leave that frame, but Okay, I'm going to turn around and
say yes. Thank you for your hard work. See you tomorrow.
Thank you very much for your support. Thank you for your continued support.
Goodbye, see you again Baba.
Excuse me for interrupting. Yellow is number 5.
[Music]
By the way, there are people who are still in the slot.
What should we do if we continue?  It's just my voice,
Koshi, let's go. What should I do? If you want to cut it off, it's
fine.
But don't leave it to me and follow me. Eh, you wo
n't be there tomorrow.
Where's the voice? Here's the voice. Here's the voice.
It's okay. It's not the
school building. It's the gym. It's the gymnasium.
Yes, yellow, I'll participate.
Thank you, Ama-chan. Chat. Oh, that's helpful.
By the way, what's going on in Matsu-machi?  If the princess were to say something about a certain strategy, I
'd probably agree with her quite a bit. She
said something like red, yellow, and pink earlier, and when she was making that road, she said
it to me, so if I say that, I'll probably move.  I
got the impression that it was easy to understand, so it's
better to continue and squat as much as possible.It's better to
plant while crouching so that it will never fall.Wow, that's
great.Now then, please say it in Princess Iris's voice.
I'm looking forward to it. I do
n't think there will be more than one voice,
but I'm definitely looking forward to it. About 50 voices. I'm
probably suffering from screen sickness, though.
Even if it's a little harsh.  Hey, it's
okay if you let me down.Ah, I
don't get that drunk at all, so it's okay.It's okay.It's the
first time I've heard that voice.I wonder if it's okay.It's my
first time.It's okay.It's okay.There are a lot
of people, and Matsui-senpai is the only one who entered the
knight entry.  I guess I have to do it.
Yes, there are 01 gathering, hahahahahahahaha,
please use chat 01. Yes,
yes, yes, please, please,
please, please. In the meantime, Mikochi's
distribution is still ongoing.
Thank you very much for your help.
There are all yellow members, but yeah, yeah, yellow
members are divided by 444.
How many people are there? It's totally fine. How many people are there? There are 12 now.
There are 3456 and 7888. If so, there are
2 teams.  We'll be able to divide it into two
teams.Okay, Subaru, I'm watching what's going on,
so everyone, if anyone wants to team up with you,
please do so.Wait a minute, wait a minute.Please go ahead and do it.I'll
ask you some questions.  Sorry, I
have one more question, but what is that? You
make something and you guess what it is.
Well, the knights are not allowed to talk,
right? Basically, and the
voices like that...  Yeah, that's fine,
but even with words, this is that, this is the
usual thing, I wonder if it will probably
get across. Yeah, yeah, yeah, here, there's
no such thing as putting green or anything like that.In
that case, that princess is talking.
It's okay for the princess to talk, but the princess is the other way around.If that were the case, then the
knight would shake his head
and nod his head up and down while asking if this is a refrigerator.  Do
you feel that way? Yeah, it's true. It's
okay. Is it okay? It's okay if it's not a word. It's okay. It
's like an answer.
By the way, things like that theme in the princess's voice
can change on the day.  As
for Suruhigo's theme, the cooking one
is not exactly the same in the first half, after all, it's random, so if you
do it with the red team, for example, there will
be a lot of paprika, or a lot of refrigerators.
Miko also thinks that there must be something like that,
but yeah, it seems like it's
random, so Radam doesn't
really understand what's going on.It seems like some
random guy is getting angry, so let
's just say that on that day.  The question is, is there a
possibility that the same thing that is appearing now will not change and the same thing will come out again
?
By the way, the person who makes that creative thing.Well, the
first half doesn't change that much, but the second
question is  That special topic for that day will
come out, that's pretty much it.Mope
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to that day I'm
excited about it.  It's not a thing, huh hun hun
huh, okay.
Yes
[Music]
Well, I was able to go with 44. We
still haven't broken up yesterday.
How are you feeling now? It's a
little yellow right now. Yellow is gathering at 44.
Yellow is now coming.  Well then,
should I enter as a white team or something like that?
White looks right.Enter that white team and
make another team with the remaining people.I'm
asking if there's a red team or a white team.Yeah, it's
pretty disbanded.I want to do it.
Even if we end up disbanding, we can still practice even if we don't have all 33 teams, so we can do it.We'll
do it.We'll do it if everyone
just does Etori.
Princess? No, why? I
want to do it. I want to do it.
Hey, I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to see it. I want to see it. Please. I want to see the princess. Then Mio-chan can come as a knight.
That's dead. She's dead. Then that
Miko-chan.  I'd like to be a knight.
Yes, it's okay to protect me. I want to protect you. Then,
start button. Yes, where is the start button? Where is the start button? Should we separate the voice servers?
Oh, then, let's go to the actual show. I'll be the first team
number 2, please.  Yes,
yes,
yes, please wait. Please,
please.
Yes, I think it
depends on the knights. The
call is important. The call is important. The
response is pink.  Yes
pink red red pink yellow red yellow red yes yes pink yes
yellow now yellow pink yes red red yellow
yes red yellow I'm on both yes
yes pink yes yellow red yes yes yes get off
Push it behind Nana Let's do it one more time Ayoare I'll
get caught.  Oh, do your best! Is this one that's going to
get caught?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yellow, red, pink, yellow, oh, yeah, that's what I was squatting down. If the bottom moves, it'll fall, I see. Ok, red, yellow, pink,
red, yellow, moving, yes, pink, moving yellow.
Well, pink is a little far away, yes, pink, red,
yellow, moving, yes, yellow,
pink, red, yellow, pink, yes, nice, nice.
Well, that's over. Maybe, now, now,
now, I'm doing it. I'm doing that voice right now, so I
'm dividing the members.  Hey,
wait a minute, wait a
minute, uh, who's missing red right now?
Look, is this a tomato, an
apple, or a tomato? Is it an apple? Is it a
tomato? I
don't know what the difference is. Is it an apple?  Teri Ringo
How did you do that? Okay
Pro Hmm
cat ah Wow,
what do I want to eat? Yes, I want to eat Subaru's fried chicken again.
Also, um, grilled mutton.
I think fried chicken comes out every time. It's dangerous. I
did it.  But you know, I didn't even get a hamburger.
Well, I guess that's right. And the mutton, just open it normally. Hey, okay, I'll
cook it on a mana board. Yes, please, yes.
Wait for the wheat here.
Grill this.  If I remember correctly, I
didn't say that it was a little different on the day of the event.I guess that's right.Someone
took the fried chicken and cut it up.Well,
let's cut it up.Let's put it in the pot.  I
said ``I'm going to eat the mutton'' and I
put it in a pot and put some
chicken in it.I put some oil in it and it came in.I
guess I'm cooking right now.He's a good cook.Okay, I gave it to him and
asked him to eat it.Then there was a duck on top.
Teruko's plate is cute Yes, the princess
is uh, uh, upper left orange, uh,
orange, uh, upper right, pink, pink, lower left, red,
orange, orange, orange, orange, orange, yes, yes, yes,
fight, fight, press, yes
[Music]
Pa, it hurts, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
when you jump, you get a
lot of damage.  Thank you for coming in. The
timing is perfect. Yes, yes, next.
[Music]
Yes,
the rhythm is so
true. I feel like I've
become stronger.
[Music]
Yes, it's good, it's good, yes, next. It's so
good.
It's really good together.
Okay, there's one more dog. I'm working. The
one on top is that one. Only the person with the bow is the one with the bow. The person with the bow
should just concentrate on the one on top.
Hey, if it's Max, it'll do a lot of damage
Max. This guy, if you
step on a strong nice move, you'll score.
Nice. I
wonder how many minutes it was. It
was 5 minutes and seconds ago.
But I think there was a difference of about 6 minutes or more than 30 seconds, but I think it was 5 minutes and 9 minutes.Yeah, if it was earlier than that, it
wouldn't have come out, but I wonder if it will come out.I'm a
senior, so I'm sorry.
Maybe it was just a delusion. Isn't it better to decide who is going to make what for each dish
? For example, the first one
was random,
right?  The second one
seems a little heavy, and the first one is probably
just regular yakitori or grilled food or something like that,
but the second one is probably fried chicken or
hamburger, or something like that.
Pancakes, yeah, that's right, 4, 4,
4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4, 4?
It's about the timing when it flies and falls a little.Pop
pon pon
pon pon pon pon It's fast.
Please praise me. I'm looking forward to the actual performance. I'm also looking forward to the yellow color
. It's a success when something like a star appears.  That's
right,
when Star Tantan has a brown star on his opponent's body, he becomes critical.I
even learned how to do critical,
but wow, that happened.The one with the bow was
the last one.  Ha, the demon king, yes, Sasu, Sasu
, I wonder if we should make it into a festival? Hey, last year, that
was that. We really needed a critical hit.
Last year's sports day, yeah, we had a really
critical hit. I remember jumping. What
happened? Mob subjugation.  You know, Mobutoba, and there was
also fencing, right?
There was that, Mr. Fencing, who fell down, who fell down, and Mr. Daruma, who fell down. By the way, there are other people who want to practice. It's okay.
Follow-up is okay. Follow-up
participation.  There are people who want to do it, like Mizuo-senpai,
or follow-up-chan, but it's
okay. Wow, the image
is that I've already gotten the hang of it. Yeah, I'm sure there's also anime, senpai. Ah, that's right.
So let's start the follow-up.
Follow-up. After the follow-up, Iro once will be disbanded.
Yes, when was the next practice? The
next practice is at 12 o'clock. The next practice is tomorrow. I
think I can go from 1 o'clock to noon. I think I can go. It's okay. I might
not be able to go for a while at first.  No, it's
okay, it's okay. On the contrary,
if you want to practice something, let's practice a little bit after this. Let's play
together for the first time. We'll have another
hour to go from now on.
But if you keep doing it, let me join in. It's
totally okay.  Alright then, it's a good timing to
start with and it's okay to get out of
here.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank
you very much.
Okay, put it away, you're really hungry. Okay, let's move. We're
not flirting over there.
Please move. We're already there. We're over
there. We've arrived. Don't do that.
Don't look at your stomach.  By the way, this is the only thing that's coming out.
Wait a
minute. I'm so sorry, I just came out.
The moment when everyone's hearts became one.
The moment when everyone became one.
Well then, please touch this.
Oh,
I'm late.
Oh, I'm late. Oh, please
have your entry entered as well. Is it yellow, senpai? It turned out
to be white. If it's yellow, brother, I changed it to red. Ah, I entered in yellow.  I'm
sorry, I changed it to red, I changed it to red, I'm sorry, I changed it
to red, red is open, too.
Do your best, do
your best, aim for it, do your best, I wonder who's going to be faster in this one.It's
true, we can't go, the path has already begun, let's
start.Will Miko, the amazing creator, win?
Also, I'm afraid of the pride of being a creator.  Oh,
there's a battle we can't lose, here's a battle we can't lose. We've
created a new word, ``give it your best!'' Gaba ni gaba ni ga ba ni. Isn't it
cute? It's cute, isn't it? It's cute,
isn't it?  As expected, this is a
person who knows the route.
If you follow this route, you can get there in the shortest time.
No, that's not true. Everyone is really amazing. It looks so
good. You're lying. You're lying. You're lying. You're lying. You're lying.  My
senpai is really good and I heard a great undertone
right now.
Well then, do
n't wait, wait, let's get along,
okay? The speed of revenge is amazing. You're
back in the middle of falling.  I
reached the second checkpoint when I realized that I couldn't
do it anymore, but I'll be back soon. It's amazing. I'll be back soon. It's
okay. This is fine. It's not a competition
. I don't know where I'll go in the end. It
's mental.  This game is
definitely mental, certainly mental
and physical.It's the mental-physical passion that's
important.As a player, it's
different teams, different teams, different sources,
so
[Music]
This is
amazing!  It's super
stable, stable, this didn't work out.
I'm not going to die. I'm not going to die. Stop, stop, stop, but that's it. I
can't do it
because Iros isn't here. Seriously, I won't be there tomorrow. Please don't fly and die. I'm
really begging you, what should I do?  Yes,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, but tomorrow the
voice channels will be separated, so I'm
with you. Who's with me? Yes, I'm with you. Hey,
Lily, please stop. I'll
go instead. I'll stop it.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it, Ririka.  I wonder if I'll be there tomorrow.
Well, don't worry. Seriously, I'll
follow up too, so my passion will be a mess.
Everyone's going to be broken by the follow-up.
Please come back and be nice to me. Chiara.
Do your best, Chiara. I'll stream it here.  There are
still people out there There are a
lot of people out there There are a lot of people out there Tomorrow's Kateru is
currently on the air It seems like it's currently on the air Ah, why
did it fall? Please follow up. We're
all watching it. Last,
last try. Last try on Holo-up tomorrow.  Isn't it the actual performance
? Tomorrow, the
actual performance will be today's practice.If I go up, I'll
have a bad sound.I ca
n't reach it anymore.I made it.There's no
way I can do this.If I can go to the top, it'll
probably be yesterday's layout.  It's almost the same as the one
below, and the bottom has changed quite a bit. It's
great that you've reached the third checkpoint. It's okay, you idiot. Do your best.
No, there's still time. I went slowly. Well done,
I fell.
It's okay, Anya-san. Please leave me the speed of my comeback. Please leave me the speed of my revenge. Please leave me the speed of my revenge. You can rest assured. That's great. What should we do? We
only have 19 seconds left from now.  It's bad, it's bad,
it's bad, it's just 15 seconds left.
You're the one who's going to fall. You're
stupid, you're stupid. I want to die, die. On the contrary, it's amazing. But you won
, you won. You won, you
won.  No, no, it
's over now, so this is it, no, it's over for now. I'm going to practice behind the scenes after this. It hurts. It hurts.
Stop
it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well then, those who close the frame, please close it.
Mone, thank you for staying.
Thank
you very much. Thank you very much. Well then, let's disband for now.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you for waiting. Thank you for watching today.  I
'm lonely, but I don't have any plans to take a slot tomorrow at noon, and
there probably
won't be anyone to take pictures, so I do
n't know,
but it'll be at night.During
various evening performances, I won't be streaming.  I
'm planning on filming, but after that I'll be talking to members only for a
while, so I can't do it at all.After the
actual performance, it's going to be a members-only thank you
party.Rika
just wants to talk, but it's been a
while since I've streamed my butts.  I want to do this, so
please help me.It's not going well.It's not going well.I want to practice as much as possible until the day of the day, so I'm looking forward to your help.I'm going to do
this, this, this, jump, jump
down, jump, jump 2 consecutive times.
From the jump, I
jumped across everything. Is it okay to jump? I
realized that it's easier to go up if you look down. It's the worst. Hey, it's
okay if you fall down there, so go down first.
Finally, do this. Go up.  It's hard to come up with
something. I want to try my best not to lose it, but I always get so nervous that I say things like "no, no, no," and hit them on the head.  It
's important to run without worrying about it, and all the seniors are good at it too, so you
have to be careful when you're at the bottom. At this time, you're at the
bottom, and you're practicing here and there.  Do you
want to do it
? Mental is important many times over and over again.
No,
right now, it's like I'm about to go up from here and there. It's like I'm
being pushed back, right? Right,
right? I feel like that.
Okay, jump, jump, jump, jump
from jump, jump, jump, jump from, jump,
jump.
Shift
from oh, this is what it's like to jump from here on down
Wow, now here and there is no good, it's like a robot,
this is what it's like,
isn't it?
Kaka Ikeru Kaka is in charge of the cherry blossoms over here Yeah, it's an even number [Music] That's right Jump Jump Jump Run without worrying about jumping Run without worrying No that much You won't lose that much time Even if you fall over there Ah, you won't lose any time Even with this  Okay, there's no time
loss. If you can take the best action in everything, it's difficult. The
sea is difficult. The
sea is difficult. I wonder if there's a
trick to this. I wonder if there's a trick to this, like
punching the bubbles to make them
disappear.  It's like I'm praying
[Music] That's
right.
[Music] Hey, let's do our
best. Should we float properly? Well,
even if we dodge diagonally, it won't work, so we won't be able to
go properly. Well, if we try to force ourselves to go to the bottom, then
that's it
[  [Music]
Kahoi, I can't climb up there anymore,
so I'm going to
do this, and I'm going to do this, and I'm going to press the shift button, and I'm going to have to exaggerate it
and go up.
But now it's stable, but the actual
performance is fuwa Pom
Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom
Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Pom Poi Ah, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
So,
thank you everyone for watching today, and thank you so much for that Suppa-chan, too.
After I fail again and again, I would like to read that departure again in a separate frame.
Thank you very much for your
support. I'll do my best tomorrow. I hope you'll support me
a lot. My uncle's dangerous pinky finger has been pushing me so
much that it
hurts.
Thank you. I hope I can talk to my seniors
properly.  I'll do my best. I was able to talk to you
today. I was able to talk to you today. It was
okay. I was wondering if it was okay. Thank you so much,
thank you so much.
[Music]
Yes, I was able to do it. Thank you.  It's
important to be a good girl, so I try to keep quiet and explain things, so I'm going to do
this.
That's great.
Thank you. I promise you'll give me lots of support tomorrow.
Ok,
then why can't I succeed
? I'll
try my best again. I'll
see you on the stream tomorrow night.  Let's
do it Ah, it's
hot, ah, it's no good if you stay down the moment you dive like that, no, no, that's cheating.
]
[Applause]
[Music]
Bye