Wow, my
stomach already hurts! That's
why today's
live show is
on a fishing boat. I
look forward to competing with you. Is the
sound okay? I'm
serious. The level of tension is crazy. There
are members.
3rd place for the taste that matches the week.
Wow, I'm really nervous.
Now I'm going to
go to the tea house and eat some porridge.
Subaru wants to do his best since we've made it through the preliminaries. I
wonder who's going to go to the next section. Block d Block  I have no
choice but to run with all my heart. I can't do anything with tricks anymore.
I'm asking for JR. It's really too strong here. It's
just
serious. No, it's serious. I'm coming to Monolux. I
caught it. I
smoked it. It's seriously 5.
Alright, it's time for the assessment. Alright, let's go with our open eyes and sincere Subaru.
With our sincere Subaru, why are you so
lazy? There's only 2 pens
here. I'm here, saas world.  Please
give me the koragoku. It's like
Article 10. I'm on
tour. I've
been getting a lot of calls like this. Wait a minute.
8. It's
okay. It
seems like you can buy something like this. Ah, I'm nervous. If you want to kill me quickly, please kill me. I'm about to see it for the first time.  It's the hardest time to go right and right to execute it.  I
thought about changing it, but
there's something about it,
because she's a woman who lived with Katarina.
However, I won't change Subaru's name here. I'll call
Katarina Matsubara. I
thought I'd change it to something like "Susu" to deflect some hate.  But
then, if I try really hard, I'll really try to
spell it out in words I already understand.
Ramen,
well,
well. Well, I'm just chilling and sleeping. My hands are so sweaty. My hands are so sweaty.
Ahaha.
Lou is no good, come look at me
Lou is too scary.
Wait a minute.
[Music]
Ah, ya!
Fast game
ana. Please trouble me.
Okay, then seriously. My
heart rate increases the most while I'm waiting. I want to
go home.  I'm not sure, but it's only Subaru. No,
but I have a fever. Yes, I want to go. SS
Yes, I don't know how it will turn out, but
I think it's important not to give up.
No, the sound before the game is really relaxing.  I
keep thinking about Subaru for letting me race so early.Every
time I experience something like this,
[music] It's
too bad.
Well, I don't care. I just want to have fun driving. But if I
make too much noise, things will get really bad.
Why are they
burdened with regulations?  No, I can't carry it on my back.
Subaru is going to share the porridge Dirac,
but I'm going to do my best today. Okay, let
's have a little tea.
Web
Well, the tax is easy and fun.
Seriously, seriously, seriously.  I
want to go to Subaru in the sky.
Yes,yes,
but if you have fun, your
concentration will improve and you can get e12.
There's no choice
but to get into the lead curve lungs because of the runner parts. I want
it to start soon,
but I don't want it to start
ca
Seriously, I want cheese to stop. I
want cheese to stop. Subaru. Oh, maybe Peach.
Peach mute speed.
Solar says mute peach. They're
aiming for color.
You know, I thought Musipah was good too,
but it's
amazing today. He
doesn't run recklessly like that, so
when I thought about it, I saw that the shortcut at the end of Kinpar was
too strong,
so I guess it's around that.
Donut a Yamonee,
that's bad.  I don't think so,
but if I start with honesty, it won't be the same everywhere.
Come
on, come on,
Che-chan, there
are quite a few Nishi-ku patterns in total.
Ah, what?
From the same time.  Up
to 8 times Keech's size, stress caused my eyes to
become swollen.I've noticed that there are a lot of things flying around in my eyes, like some kind of dust.  [
Music]
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
[Applause]
5 items
Put it on the snow - it
won't
turn pink I can't go back
[Music] I'm
here [Music]
From here
5 items
[Music]
Pabu
[Applause] It's
probably Ares Day
[Applause] Ha  I
can't take it off, it hurts
[Applause]
[Music]
It's so bad
[Applause] I
ate it. I don't
have
it. I guess it's fine.
Ah, well, well, well, well, well, the
dog was back at the party.  I
was a trainee from then
on. Phew,
okay, let's go ahead.
Well, the rice is a little sweet. If you want it
pink, go for pink turbo.
OK,
well, for my wife, it's
too much. Papa, Musi bread is good too.
Well, I don't really understand the Nehru at the end.  I
wish they would stop. There's a
sting in the front.
This is luck.
Okay,
8 catfish.
Let's go.
[Music]
No gays.  I ca
n't get the points.
Wow, it's so serious. Front
f You
can hit it, but they'll aim for you from behind.
[Music]
Karate, that's nice.
Keep going home a.
Aim for the hole. It's
dangerous.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music] I do
n't want any points. I
'll add it. No
one will accept this in Japan. I
don't have any coins.
Collect it here.
No, I don't mind leaving it damaged.
[Applause]
Also, Ocher is fast, so the original key is fine.
Yes, I'm lucky, this is
lucky, this is lucky,
I don't need this, I don't
need this, I don't need this, I don't need this, I seriously don't need this
[Music]
Well, I'm not good at it
Bone Body
Double Draw
[Music]
Put herbs in it No,
since I've been frustrated, I can
put together an Abdie at home  I'm
already irritated with Bob and Khan
[Music]
Take the double
Knight's analysis It's been frustrating
since Bob and Ylang Ylang Ylang Ylang
Ca
n't
be irritated anymore Bomb and I can't be irritated
Yo Kuruma Ru
Natsuyo r r Dal Darley
Reka No, I'm sorry for the pest control, but I want to erase the tag cow.I'm
really telling you
this, but I can't throw the tide.I think I'll
go to Artic Tac.Ya compensation, I
can't throw rocks, so I don't know.  That's
it
Bob is irritated and
irritated Don't do it, it's really sweet
[Music]
If you say crawl, it's ok
Good at it Eat
mute Will it bloom at the end? How to use items
At the end, I can sit and check out the first one.
Hey, Hokkeko Chu-chan
[Music] I
wish Abe had a grudge.
[Music]
Taco-chan is bye. There
's no swab.
[Music] It's
strong because the cheese goes against the odds. It's
hard to turbo even the pins.
No, but you can't replace this.
Kids are being targeted.
[Music] I'm
cutting hard for half a shaku.
[Music] Here
[Music] It
's not there.
[Music]
What's in here? I don't have to cheer for you. It's
good
. [Music] Abune, it's a reverse Nan color here.
[Music]
Baba,
boke
[Music]
Aokeru, I'm going to
make a blue note.
I'm not shy.  I have no choice but to live with
insurance.Insert the book.
Oh, I'm seriously a 4th generation. Hey, I ca
n't concentrate anymore after 4 races.
Hey,
my heart is pounding.
Lou, that
's terrible.
That's a terrible turn. I'm a 4th generation. I'm
not good at Marion Bar kits either.  That's it, it's dangerous,
just where should I aim? Well, Mario
Circuit is fine.
[Music] I
don't even remember where we'll meet anymore.
Haa, I want Musipan to be an Animal Crossing running group and
Animal Crossing.Ah
[Music]
big blue Neh fick Blue It's
scary to go without a book or something, so I'm
steady and calm and collecting love and running
Ah, I
'm really concentrating.  Let's
go outside.
[Music]
Alright, I've cut the oily version.
[Music] Be
careful.
Collect the coins.
[Music]
Stop.
What is this?  I'm
in
[Music] I'm in
trouble [Music] It's okay if I fall in one
wf No,
give me
[Music]
Wow, I think this is
it That's right.  It's
Mattel, USA.
[Music] It's
not there.
[Music] I've
already taken this voice. Wow
, ah,
ah, oh,
no, if I do this a little, there will be 5 people.
Well, I don't know what I'm talking about right now.Switch
[Music]
Dobson or something, I'm going to do it anyway.Subaru
's favorite Animal Crossing.Okay, I
want to win here.So,
Barley, good, good, good.Satoshi
Garley, well, I've been practicing.The only thing I can do is
win at the ritual.
Okay
[Music] I do
n't think it's possible
[Music]
There's a good piece of work by American Const.
Well, it's tough not being able to get items. It's
tough not being able to get items here. Yamato
Tsutsu.
[Music]
And it's 3, isn't
it? Well, it's okay
. Ayabe: You've calmed down.
Kaizu.
People are turning around, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  You
had it, right?
Now, please share your love for the rice book rec. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
Turn on the okke here
[Music] I
don’t have any coins
[Music]
I want to go.  The
body curtain is already dangerous
2 days
[Music]
Star from behind,
double!
[Music]
Can,
this isn't a long discussion
[Music] I
don't think I drank it all
[Applause] It's a
big killer
Okay,
Gaskelevan, the
arm is serious.  I thought I couldn't do it,
but now I thought I couldn't
do it anymore I thought I couldn't do it anymore It's
important not to give up
Nice Killer
's Animal Crossing Day
Haa
[Music]
Car
Okay,
the whrar has
arrived, and
it's time! A
magic mirror called Bowser Castle
[Music]
Concentrate on the car
[Music] It's
okay, let
's go.
It's summer time! It's
dangerous here.
Okay, it's only the first week
[Music]
Collect all the love
2  It's too late today to cap it!
Pocket
[Music] You
can just run inside as usual.
[Applause]
This is a dangerous item.
OK
[Music]
Hmm,
you
forget. No, I don't really need you.
Rider
who [ __ ]. Blue.
Replacement scene.
[Music]
Okay
, that's a bit of a turn.
Boo-boo. High pressure game.
Hey, he's an example of someone who has a bomb and is too strong.
[Music]  ]
If you think it's part 8, that's
it.
[Music]
That's all
Yeah,yeah
bpa
[Applause]
Attahaya,
please
p Ah, ah, ah,
re
ran
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you, thank you, parents,
thank you, see you at [ __ ] Easy, I am
amaran.