[Music]
welcome count
to start the streams oh wait wait wait
wait forgetting
straight
up
stream money apparently
don't be right back wait
[Music]
any stream up yet
is everyone
are you ready
[Music]
yes
i have a stream going currently yeah i
can hear you guys all around me
give me a reason why you are not today
starting from
emilia oh why i'm not fresh today um
oh okay
um hello everybody i'm amelia watson
hello live english miss number one
detective and um i'm not wearing pants
that's why you're not sucks good
i can't i can't use a lot of stuff
honestly if i was wearing pants that'd
be more worried you know
i knew it
okay definitely not us so next up bae
your introduction please and why you
know what we're gonna get
is about across our council representing
chaos everybody how you doing
[Laughter]
[Music]
um i got a cute pet look at my pet oh
yeah
you purchased a little hamster i mean
you bought it with real money
real human
i dollars the hamster thing and i was
like i gotta i got it
are you isn't that one of your kind your
hamster yeah
[Music]
wow that's kind of kind of weird
but interesting
all right
all right um so yeah um
death is real sus but guess what
everyone i'm not death i'm the sheriff
around these parts and because i'm the
sheriff the sheriff is never suss the
sheriff obviously didn't do it um
some people may say i i shot the sheriff
but i did not shoot the deputy meaning
uh i don't know what that means it just
has something to do with the sheriff and
i'm not i'm not suspect so there you go
how can you be the real whatever you
can't even spell sheriff right okay now
that was because now that was because
there wasn't enough room for for me to
spell it correctly
all right sorry
listen i'm definitely
i'm the sheriff
that that is very necessary yeah
i don't know
yes it is there because there's only one
all right who's next who's next i'm
going to get kicked who's next
no my name is fauna and i am simply a
potted plant therefore i cannot kill
good plan
that's a
you've already killed enough people for
today so your deed is done
exactly forever
no no no plant has never killed anyone
little shop of horrors does it ring
about ever
never mind i remember that musical
i remember
all right
um
[Music]
is
it's iris live english project hub video
singer
uh
i am very excited i
am a hundred percent say so i would
never lie which is why i would never
recess
sorry
yeah
everything i would never i wouldn't ever
virus don't trust her killer and good
liar
iris yes no trash
iris that's not what happened to my fox
yesterday
[Music]
a very very um
good self-introduction while other
people mostly just say hey my name is
this
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yes
hello my name is cronie oro
from
the council
[Music]
but i'm a more royal color royal gloom
oh it's not looking okay
where's the blue okay don't look at the
color objectively look at the color
that's inside all of us oh
[Music]
wait did cronie say why she's nuts us oh
right i'm not sus because look at this
i'm wearing a mask i'm doing my uh part
in this situation don't get close to me
we must hear you
well i tried to social distance but i'm
not science because i'm doing my part in
the society
and it's pretty funny
i'm an upholding
the first time this happened everyone
was singing really out of sync
this time it was just plain rude
we need a new code
i make sure you oh i gotta hide it from
you folks though
hold on
[Music]
wait a minute it didn't work
do
[Music]
i am the guardian of civilization and i
am an apex predator of the sky and i
could kill you if i wanted to
that's right
that's how you defend yourself that is
that that is the most non-sus
introduction ever yeah
but i don't want to so i won't
okay
but i believe that because you are so
peaceful
mm-hmm
okay i take it back i take it back i
take it back um
i i might not i
no taxi back i take it back i take it
back
[Music]
um
the
priestess of the ancient ones
i think yeah sometimes i forget but um
oh
i am not sauced because i'm already dead
look at the the halo above my hands
that chorus of o's was wonderful
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you lina
next up sanna is not streaming but she's
here so please let us know
[Music]
um hi hi i'm shawna sugama from her life
english council
it's been a while hello guys
[Applause]
i have a big limiter on my head
yeah
that's a flamingo
if anybody thinks i'm sauce i'm going to
take it off and take all of you down
with me
that's a threat
that's really reassuring
back into the space where you belong
right or actually you're a part of
migrants you should be fine you should
be fine if you get kicked out i have no
i have no reason to
oh um well
i'm very happy to have you here
thank you for participating we're really
glad to have you as part of this even if
you're not streaming thank you
of course the facebook will be
back soon so we can all look
[Music]
and
i am the one organizing this
and i'm really happy that we could all
get together 11 people is a lot but
we're going to have a lot of fun today
so let's get right into it are you girls
ready to be
yes
[Music]
all right let's go
the crewmate oh dear what's this
i don't understand this man
hi i think
we just had a lot
hi hi
hi
i don't know i'm not very good at this
game
hey i'm good at this either hi hi wait
you gotta press tab in order to see your
tasks okay
okay tap
tap tap
[Music]
i was just explaining to them uh what
proximity chat was
oh
that's it
what is it that's literally it i'm just
kidding doctor tell me
oh okay i was like oh it's okay it's
okay
i don't know man
[Music]
where do i go don't hurt me
don't hurt me no i'm trying to find the
meaning
i'm trying to find the meeting room
wait we can't move around here
but
i haven't really played among us i don't
know what i'm doing
[Music]
three
absolutely
i think that this might be quick
um
screened again
[Music]
we just got started should we do a new
lobby
i don't know if it's gonna be any better
though
i'll try fixing you but maybe i don't
know maybe reinstall among us or
something like that because you had that
before that's weird yeah
i was by myself it was the room with the
folder on the table oh records okay iris
you spawn
uh where did i spawn let me look at the
map real quick
detective
i don't know
do not have never really played this map
um i think somewhere like in the main
hall
okay well me sana and cronie all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked them
down there and
yeah they were already fauna and cali
were already dead so whoever responded
with them there were two killers with
them and they possibly were at the same
time
i was alone i did not wait hold on a
second all right
[Music]
for throwing
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah what a shame that they that they
killed you when you're so when you're so
innocent
yeah
wow
i haven't completed a single task sorry
that was a lot of fun yeah if we if we
both blamed the girl i think it would
have worked whereas it was just like
she just
makes some volume adjustments
this is why the relationship does not
work
see you have to do tasks in this game
and make her laugh in front of other
people
[Music]
and noise there's noise too this way
this way
[Music]
by the way dear chat i most likely will
not look at you too much because i don't
want you giving away things
uh will this ever come back
oh we don't know the other one
this is why the divorce is happening
it's not my fault i'm wondering if we
should we should close the library so
let's you know
test it out again hi babe
[Music]
i just can't trust you anymore i just
can't trust you
in front of two witnesses just to send a
message
[Laughter]
a message very important stuff yeah
obviously yeah i mean
what else do i have to do
i pointed to that but there's nothing i
can do there
i are they all wires hello
wired
i have a few more things to do no i
don't know how to do this this was my
task in the in the test round i don't
understand
turn it to zero clockwise is this what
it's telling me to do yeah and turn it
to four
counterclockwise right
[Music]
no
okay we'll have to look at chat what
i
what
around once and around oh
okay
no
i'll spin handle ones
once
i don't understand
never use the locker i use lockers but
you didn't have this what is this thingy
what
this one is weird it is weird
below the zero
what
here oh i see you can't let go of it is
that it so
wait what oh i wanna restart restart
restart restart no no
okay
zero
four
seven
what
again
okay
okay okay okay okay
okay okay i have more things to do so
quiet
where where do i go
to sneeze nice thank you okay now i'm
not gonna look at you anymore
[Music]
but i have absolutely no clues because i
was running around a while here and i
met no one close behind
so who's done with their tasks
[Music]
but i think that's something that an
imposter can do like show
[Music]
uh i think cronie can vouch for me that
i'm not cess right crony what do you
think he mustn't look at the chat well i
i know that watson and sana were
definitely safe because the killings
took place when uh all of us were still
around
people who are considered suspicious to
me would be
bae or kiara
[Music]
you know what
no no no watson's definitely in the
clear because
i didn't know
[Music]
this is not great this is not good i
pushed it too far
where are you smalling guys
next time
room
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
i must complete my tasks
shoot
what
[Music]
i haven't really played
i love that that song is stuck in her
head
today we are almost done
to the
pit
that i can't see because people will
clip it out of context
what
[Music]
oh
that's not that's not what i upload
there you go
download
oh wow
what great download speed they have up
here
isn't that nice
yeah they had really good download speed
bay
where am i going i don't know do you
need help
um
[Music]
i saw another task what
one more all right
oh no i thought i had to upload
something
and
not voila i sell more it gives me more
and more oh never mind
huh everyone go i think you can press
tab oh is anyone around me um
[Music]
let's see what's this
okay
now i'm done
where are you
are you gonna uh you guys start with
number one and then go to two and then
three four
boom a deathbed um
yeah i finished my tasks it looked like
santa really for some reason i have a
task in the toilet
oh yeah you have to unclog
i
where have you been just now but no just
now oh my gosh it's yeah
where was i um
voter down butter down
let's make this quick though so that ina
can come back
[Music]
she wasn't really doing her tasks she
was just walking around my tummy is
really rumbling i mean were you doing
tasks
yes
what were you doing what was the last
test i have a good one
uh describing it was kind of overrated
that
is um
i think it's between
storage and like developing room
question question question room
i know oh no no
i had just seen kiara like right next to
me uh we were together
[Music]
as an imposter
was the one who reported the body too
right
this is my second body i'm recording yes
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh we could hear each other during that
under the virus
on my screen though she has i don't know
if it's i don't know iris did kill me
it's just
[Music]
and i'm serious
what i thought we were a team
yeah i mean ever since then i'm in
prophecy
i was so sized
[Music]
what me we leave we leave the room right
yeah
ah bye-bye
you know what that means
hold up how do i leave the room um
um
that's how okay
you see nothing
let's see
oh wait why can't i oh
give me new
oh
okay
let's see if i can properly join oh
will it work
[Music]
yeah me too
i'm also the sheriff
[Music]
why would you put the blame on me
what i think it's from the previous
round i think it's because you're you
are so uh
eager experience to say
it first
and i always think whoever says it first
is suspicious
uh understand i feel like imposters are
usually very quiet like they try not to
talk because they don't wanna unless
they're very experienced in that sense
yeah
people are usually bossed into the room
be like all right so who did it
[Music]
everyone's just like uh you
you
you did it
oh i think it's huge like oh no wait i
think it's cool
[Music]
all right which one of you suckers is
the imposter um probably you callie
oh so it's cali
it's cali
is kelly looking in the future
i'm the imposter
yep what are you doing over here
oh i'm just uh you're welcome vibing in
the corner
i'll join you okay so because i'm
surprised okay but i'm pretty small
right now you come around here
i do now
okay
i
[Laughter]
revenge or anything right yeah
she pushed the fox down the hole
[Music]
and you know it doesn't matter anymore
i'm gonna because i'm getting in i'm
gonna lobby one more time
[Music]
that's silly we could just come over
here let's see
soon we will all be together again
feeling suspicion over each other
wondering who is going to
[Music]
i'm here
we can
we're gonna let ina try
no problem you know i just want you i
just want you to participate this is the
curse the en curse is just kicking in
mm-hmm
oh i am the owner now i think i must i
think we're supposed to leave i think
ina is going to make a room oh yeah okay
yeah yeah ina is going to make it
enough to make a room leave everybody
what's that
i can't keep track
i suppose we will see
i'm over here hello how's it going
sorry i'm not very good at keeping track
of uh
where the stuff thinks
oh sorry
hello
are y'all having fun
i hope we can get
[Music]
i wait i'm simply waiting for a
you code remember the art i made it's
behind me
do you remember
i actually forgot quite a few of these
uh
not sure what my thinking process really
was
[Music]
cannot find the real
game you're looking for
try again
cannot find the game
you're looking for
uh-oh
i must alert them doesn't work for me
i cannot find the game you're looking
for
hmm
oh
i see
i must change some things
what i'm trying to
let's see let's see let's see okay got
it
[Music]
missing
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
where we drop
hey
why are you quiet
she was crying and just i just felt so
bad hello hey i can't keep so bad about
it i can't hear bae
hello i can hear her
hello you can't hear really maybe try
refreshing the bread accruing there's a
refresh button on the top left
hello
hello you can hear me though right i
hear you where bago she messing with me
i should probably do my tasks actually
let's see
where am i
whoa there's a lot of things to do down
there
how do i
[Music]
the only thing i can say about that is
that i heard kelly's voice close by for
a moment but
that was like i didn't even see her
close by i only found the body like a
few moments later
but i wasn't i wasn't doing anything i
was like looking for a task to do well
why were you not doing tasks i don't
think you're done with tasks we just got
started there's a lot of tasks i doubt
it's a bit okay i don't know how to play
the game
it's a really big map
i saw her coming up towards me and i was
in the armory which is on the bottom
left side cali passed by me
that's very funny hahaha time to kill
hahaha please let's find it
me e94 and cali spawn together but kelly
went off pretty
um yeah
i was pretty lost if we did it
i was pretty long
you just said that you did you weren't
doing any tests no you said you weren't
doing the tasks
oh god i don't know how to play the
[\h__\h] game
[Laughter]
if you really don't know how to play the
game i will give you a tip now a serious
tip press tab open the map so you can
run around while seeing the tasks and
that's a very easy tap tap
okay i was like i was like looking back
and forth between the map
[Music]
did you vote yeah
that's enough to throw me out
is it
no
she's safe
okay for now i'll remember this oh where
did i go
i have never been to the bridge the
engine
i
where did i have a bunch of stuff i
think
wow
electric i'm far from that dang it
fana you stay away
i have an uneasy feeling about that that
leaf i tell you
this is where i have things to do but
it's
hard for me to under look at this what
please explain actually i shouldn't
uh oh
i'm gonna try a different one i
understand now i think
do i do i have to just do all these
this is how you do it
maybe not
oh yeah this might not be how
do i have to go in order
yes
i see
see i swear that this one said wait i
haven't done four yet have i i swear
that one said
six
what there's more than six
okay where's the fourth one
okay
that was six uh
i go
okay five
six
seven
okay i was gonna say that better be it
um
what else is there
here too
nothing
oh look i got so much done and then
there
it's a lot harder when you're not dead
this probably isn't the best way to go i
should probably go a different way
howdy partner
what
ma'am
ma'am the sheriff do you understand how
this works how'd you figure it out so
fast huh
hey hey
all right
which one of you just closed the toilet
door
the cockpit
i was about to go uh to the very very
bottom
um
who used the toilet
but it was locked for me
um because when i found iris's body
right as i hit report the door of the
bathroom door closed
someone hid in the bathroom you can do
that it's a ghost
i can't vouch for santa at least
hmm i don't know i'm just lost every
kitchen i was trying to put the egg on
the uh the frying pan
okay
a bit sus i was tracking her she was
muttering to herself
[Music]
no i wasn't looking at chat i was just
talking to them so they didn't have to
listen to nothing to be fair are you
guys just walking around completely
silent
i was trying to talk to you but i was no
i'm just trying to change
i was also in i was in the area below in
the bathroom i was doing the task where
you pick everything up off the floor and
girl i did see me there but i didn't go
up i came from the other side someone's
in the bathroom
someone's in the middle of the bathroom
without your hands
here's a better proposition whoever's in
the bathroom wait
when we spawn back in while i see you
come out no
all right in the very beginning i
spawned with uh inaudible i can vouch
for
i just remembered
yeah just because you spawn with them
you can't vouch for them i mean i was
running around with sana at one point
lost
okay
okay i don't know well fono says for now
if you say so
but are you guys really just not talking
i'm talking
talking a little bit i talk to myself
anyway though as i idly do stuff
why are you calling me out
[Music]
hello i have a weird feeling about ina
she's very persistent on letting us know
she is lost hi
where am i wait i'm worse stop hi
hello partner
hey
barter how you doing porter
i'm also kind of scared of cali um
a bed
this is no minecraft
hi
hello hello
hi hi
hey
hello hello everybody
let's see it's a one-way street
i see this place
it's so sad what is it
i have a weird feeling about you do we
do we look at this oh my gosh
[Laughter]
i was uh in the top right area that's
like uh before the wreck
right yeah around the records area
and um when i was about to enter the
rankings area i saw kelly so i wanted to
say hi so i followed her and uh next
moment she completely disappeared i went
i went into all other like like uh
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared so
you walk down the road man
you can vouch for me i went down to the
bottom and tried to go through the vent
and i couldn't
stop stop stop let me talk let me talk
let me talk let me talk let me talk let
me speak let me speak
okay what i mean is there was a vent
down there and i couldn't get through it
because i'm not the [\h__\h] imposter
that's what i meant why'd you travel
went down to the bottom i was trying to
go to the crying
i was trying to go
she just wants me to get thrown out
has a bandana
why else would you call this [\h__\h]
suspicious emergency meeting kiara
could be a next level imposter tactic is
[Music]
you don't have to vote i just want to
mention it
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
wait never mind don't worry
see
i mean that's cause i was kicking it
it is hard to tell with kiara because
she
immediately accuses people which to me
seems like a very imposter thing to do
but then also her leniency
with you don't have to vote right now
also makes me suspicious because i feel
if she really thought it was callie then
she'd be like well i don't know actually
hello hi
oh i don't have that one i don't have it
either
and i don't i don't know because i
haven't played very
much your next pack my next task is i
have a lot a vault or no wait which is
closer
how do you get around the ladder you use
it
how do you get this thing to come over
you can't you have to go to the other
side what the heck
how do you do that
let's go all the way around go around
i'm gonna go around all around
oh babe
i'm scared i'm scared too that's why i
said that um
well do you guys want to stick together
yes let's stick together okay
keep up
oh there's so many
[Music]
[Laughter]
holy [\h__\h] i missed the part of the body
i was just wearing my
[Music]
i think we can vouch for each other um
at the end right before the body was
reported we saw ina and gura together um
yeah carol's with us too actually
yeah yeah
they're fine they're all fine
which kind of leaves them
[Laughter]
are you kidding me well
she's trying to save her reputation by
reporting the body she killed trying to
look like
we don't literally kill someone and then
report them immediately
we don't know how you can now why
um but we also got to remember we
haven't killed often imposter yet
because all of these have bodies that we
found
[Music]
all right well i don't like you pointing
the finger at me bae and i think that's
suspicious i'm pointed right back at you
on your boy i'm just trying to be a good
[\h__\h] sheriff
okay
sorry are you kidding me
it's it's nothing personal it's just i'm
loving this
this is beautiful you are you're next i
don't know
last time
and it isn't now
son is awfully quiet and so is mermaid
what are you guys been doing yeah
we were with bay time
and i've been loving it
no one's standing up for me when i when
i like literally why would i could have
killed you if you guys were alone i did
[\h__\h] nothing anyone who would vouch
for callie is there anyone listen
i haven't seen
either okay
why are you pointing the finger at me i
don't think i can vote i haven't seen
you you haven't
all right you guys gonna regret this
peace
[Music]
at this point everyone had something
about someone vouching for them except
kelly it's really hard there's just one
task at the record so i don't know what
to do but i can see the task
i'm alone
meeting room
well all right freaking guess
hello okay i'm scared
um
[Music]
but let's keep a distance keep a
distance
[Music]
what do we do about
up and this
right oh wait
where's the
[Music]
uh
this thing wait you have one
i don't have arrows where do i see the
other one
[Music]
but now i'm getting further from my
tasks
[Music]
uh oh i don't know where the other one i
shouldn't go in here
uh oh
oh it fixed itself or someone else
okay let me see i waiting room and i
keep it getting a half tab as an option
um
i think i need to use my mouse actually
hello
hello um
shoot i have things up here i don't want
to be by myself but
okay where's nina
wait
okay i see
wow it worked this time
okay
okay okay okay
what else do i have to do let's start
first i have
let's see there's arrows pointing there
but i don't really get with that
why can't i use it
now the arrows are gone
this way oh you know i'm supposed to go
over there
i was following the arrows
i'm confused
i haven't played on this map
what
huh
oh no
okay
let's see
oh no again
okay
let's see what's this thingy
see these arrows again
huh
what oh oh i didn't even see that
[Music]
okay
i thought that was a okay um
i'm almost done almost
i haven't seen anybody i don't like that
i haven't seen anybody because that
makes me look suspicious
[Laughter]
i understand that i've been on my own
but and i understand i will be voted out
but it was kiara and it was inna
why why was it me and why was it you're
looking yeah what was me and kara
says
why why why theory
do i dare say
what do you mean
well ina kept saying that she was lost
and i thought that it was
suspicious
i mean this is my first time in the
world it's my first time subscribe
please describe with your own words the
uh past tasks that you have been done
doing
what was the last task the last one i
did was the one where i had to dress up
a mannequin
and then i had to use the card
and i kept having to do the guard
for the doors i'm going with my gut
and going with my gut feeling i'm gonna
go my god's too easy he's been awfully
quiet too now i'm suspicious of being
high this is just it has been really
quiet hasn't she i think it's enough
okay i think i know who it is
[Music]
oh it's me
what did i just say before i died
where are we going
oh my god no you guys are so sad
no that's that's that must be bad what
did i say right before i died howdy
partner
howdy howdy who got it got your goat
[Music]
um
everyone
all right we've already
i didn't
oh she can't hear me it's okay
i have an animal
yeah i don't need my mouth why did i
keep using my mouth i don't need it
okay
i am armed
careful now
i can't see chat but i am so convinced
it's inna
i really just thought she could be that
clumsy in the end i guess
why do i not hear
[Music]
i don't
hey yeah so i have a question so when
you're imposter and you're like going
pretending to do tasks etc can others
tell if there isn't really a task there
to do
uh no you know
but
like if you're doing
certain like if you're acting to do
tasks that should be probably longer
because there's really long time
can stand out that you're
done quickly
is someone um
what's codes showing
you sorry that's
[Music]
okay remember when i saw callie uh
remember when i saw callie and i thought
she did the thing really fast it took me
a little bit to figure out and i was
like why did you figure that out so fast
do you remember that i was kind of such
but then i just truly thought she was
that unfortunate with her faces
i
[Music]
even if i could make the kill i i waited
for my chance i was
patiently believable
i still don't know
yeah i got watched the performance was
so genuine you actually heard about my
heart
oh yeah a little bit asking enough to
kill me two times i knew it could you
hear me but kiara you're always
successful yes sorry
i asked you not to kill me and you said
okay
that was those were my last words
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
a lot of stress oh i wish i was an
imposter for once
i'm going to go to the kitchen
someone living in the box
hi
let's see
[Music]
that was so fast
oh my god can you explain what vera did
what did she do excuse me hello can i
have the floor please she was walking
out explain yourself electrical
after excuse me taking off here i was
ahead it's not yours
i have
excuse me i have a question
was the shark near the washroom no
questions at this time okay i saw i was
and then i saw guru was also in the room
that kiara went that was close
i don't know that doesn't mean it wasn't
inna i watched it
for me
she was right behind me
no you was right behind me you were by
yourself in electrical because i was
humming no no no no
i was humming the berries in cream tune
and i was like i know we're electrical
you didn't hear that
[Music]
did i stop by the washroom i spawned and
i spawned in the place with the folder
on the table and i went right down to
electrical i don't remember how what
happened never stopped by the washroom
how was that
i just wanted every time
every time you were in the city you
would do something in the washroom
she wasn't in the washroom
we just spawned in i don't know i'm
pretty i'm pretty convinced can i can i
have already starting to stink because
you didn't shower
can i
can i have a moment please please i have
no enemies
i don't know
the story she's gone from meek and shy
to very suddenly very demanding of the
room's attention i do i don't know which
could
mean on
youtube i don't know
i would love to have fun of course
it's so distant
i mean it's still early in the game i'll
i'll keep it very good
i remember i need to make a burger so
i'm going to go to the kitchen
she's making a burger
oh you're actually making a burger in
the kitchen that's a task i thought you
truly were going oh
i lost how did you make it back i lost
the instructions wait where is mine
electrical
see
where am i we don't have to go this way
no wait there's one over here
[Music]
i saw a girl girl ina the sheriff and a
cranny
in the main hall
this thing
uh
wait main hall wait where is that you
can you can wash them you can watch them
yeah oh
wait i see it wait where am i spicy
okay thank you
she's following are you following me
hi
wait
my footsteps are also loud
[Music]
so
what
are you going i don't know
wait where is the
thing right i don't know it's not this
way i don't know where they are
[Music]
shorter was it
that's not it
i actually lost wait
i can't
i'm lost
wait armory
oh
okay very very right
yes okay i see i see
i see i see
i'm mary armory
armory
kitchen feeling back wait how do you get
this
oh
no that's not
i see ice you know i don't see
that's not it
where's the one that has the kitchen
[Music]
yeah i kept telling her not to follow me
and she just said cronie
[Music]
no i was trying to i was trying to keep
an eye on you just in case you know you
go for that kill you know yeah she was
saying i have been trying to fight ina
how is it okay that ina keeps watch of
you for protection but it's not okay if
i do that i don't know likely it should
when the very first round when i
reported when i reported ina absolutely
flipped her story and went from the
super meek i don't know where i'm going
to suddenly
super loud and embarrassing as if she's
trying to protect herself
to be honest i don't trust either of you
so
okay that's fair
what both y'all were a little suspicious
okay okay um i mean is that you're
suspicious of both of us and not one
versus the other thing i saw you know
she went to go do a task and she ignored
me and i yeah
i kept bumping into her every time
uh it was just three of us in total so
if one person uh left it would just be
two of us
and i kept having that situation
because you were being left alone with
ina and i haven't heard from in a while
and i wanted somebody to be
my watch
mm-hmm
okay so are we still we can try going
together then
are we skipping
are we gonna be paying for now there's
still a reason to i don't know
put my vote on guru i don't really have
a reason so
i don't know both inna and cronie were
listening to us so please be mindful of
inna
imposter too you're really trying to put
it on inaudible
being
i'm just going to keep doing my task
listen
to knowing we're just going to keep
doing my tasks
all right
she forgot to talk um
all right i won't bother anybody this
time i'll buzz off oh
right now
that was two different people that
accused gouda though in two different
instances
what is that is this a shower
no
um
those are showers
oh wait what's this
what
how would you get over there
can you
not oh my finger hurts first my leg
really hurt now my finger really hurts
let's see
meeting room
hello
hey hi
hi distance
oh no i can't get through there
shoot
oh my ear really itches
hi
i'm going to the meeting room wait where
am i can we go together
yeah yeah
oh there's four there's four points
okay okay we're all here okay there's a
lot of people right i just have to
convert electrical power
no it's okay
okay
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
i played
wait
walking around the christmas tree
is this a
there you go
boy's
[Music]
that gurus and the clear have been uh
following her around and
yeah
i think i saw her
before
oh yeah and i saw her doing the carding
and okay
yeah it seems like she's in the clear so
trust me
so i'm pretty sure she's in the club too
yeah santa is also in the clear we saw
each other and didn't kill each other so
i think sean is okay as well
so girl you
[Music]
no it's not let me answer the question
thank you the microphone is in my hand
uh because at the very beginning of the
match i was singing the berries and
cream song and i went into electrical
and right then and there ina
beheaded that person
the story's changed get out okay
nice job detective you can't read your
own handwriting it didn't change i don't
know
i don't know what to do
i don't know either
i just saw me and cronie showers i'm
just yeah yeah iris isn't in the clear
i was just trying to scratch my ears
it's not ina
i don't know i still
i mean
you guys see cronie following gura
um yeah i haven't seen you good at like
a while but last time i saw crony
she wasn't with like nearby guru though
um so that was when the light came out
and i saw cali breaking out
all right well i don't know what to do
so i'm going to skip freaking out wait
you found the body
i found i have no reason to make enemies
you found the body yeah
where did you find it and where the
mannequins are
oh
watson why weren't you there what did
you like so easily
what do you mean
you're pointing a lot of fingers
[Laughter]
[Music]
you didn't accuse her of killing you
just said she was more suspicious but
now you're saying that you saw her cut
down my mind cutting out
[Laughter]
[Music]
let me see how do i get to the lounge
can i get here
no this is not how you get there i'm
trying to get to
the viewing of the viewing deck
um
i was watching the security cameras and
ina and iris iris leading ina behind
went into the room to the left of the
engine room and then only ina came out
and then cronie came in and i said hi
crony and then nina came in and i said
oh crony i'm gonna go see that body that
ena just left in there and lo and behold
there was the body of iris
oh well that's a very convincing you
know what it would say you in your
defense
[Laughter]
wow girl i'm sorry i doubted you holy
[\h__\h]
i feel bad i mean i never i never voted
against you but i'm sorry i doubted you
i'll be honest i thought i was going to
um
not last the very first trial but i
turned it around and i think that was
good enough for this round
it lasted this long
the other
[Music]
neither of them are safe
somebody stay with me next round you'll
see
[Laughter]
why their hairs look like that
i don't like that the hands look like
that
what
i want to spawn in oh
wait you think shoes were to spawn
that's what this is
wait
what
i'm a little slow
just a little bit i'm just a little bit
stuck in the little body
[Music]
what about watson
how do you
do puppy
[Music]
bum bum
i am so scared that i must keep myself
company
who is everybody
walkers
where am i
kitchen
[Music]
what the heck
buh
[Music]
this way
i ran out of time
one last one
[Music]
there's a time limit because of the task
[Laughter]
yeah we can't even if venus is crew i'm
just like maybe we should just vote for
her
[Music]
well hopefully not in the next round
uh can i ask you one
question in the in the better curling
settings does everyone have
impostors here dead uh checked because
it didn't work last round
yeah
i could hear
i'm more curious about the private
talking vents is that working because
i've never like i mean oh yeah i died
too early but that's the same
i think so yeah but only
need to play some classic music while
you're here
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
she's not back yet
[Applause]
[Music]
monomer
[Applause]
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
definitely me all right cool cool cool
that's cool all right all right where
are we spawning boys
you can choose where you spawn uh yeah
you can i just
i just did that for the first time
hello garbage hello
hi
where do i have to go
hi sonia
um
[Music]
what
i got a gun just kidding
[Music]
what kind of stuff what's up
documents
yeah
i only didn't kill you because there's
other people
what is she doing
i don't know how to
she's playing mind games
am i playing mind game not you
where'd she go i wanna i just wanna
watch her
her dialogue intrigues me
how do i get where i need to go though i
should probably look
oh no wait that's not how i get there
you might know my nice
that's not how do you get up there
that's how other stairs
[Music]
now i have more down there
i just want to get it over hey hey
hi my man hi
ask everyone
what their iq is way up here
hi why are you laughing because i
i heard kiana go in the distance i asked
everyone what their iq is
i need to go down here how do i get
there
i heard from bay
i think she has hi money hi the highest
iq in whole live english who do you
think has the highest accurate whole of
english not me
that's true
i was expecting her to kill or i was
expecting a kill after i said that
kia
she heard that she may have mis she
might misinterpret what i just said
i'm only sussed when i'm not
imposter i think
i can't get in there
what am i to do
[Music]
how do i get there huh
hold on
that's how
[Music]
what else showers
it's about time i haven't had to go to
the showers this entire time have i
i love how kiara says that and as soon
as you say that there's a report three
holy
because she's been doing tasks alone and
i keep on running into her and i can
watch for uh
as a detective a beacon of the law i
clear cali and gouda uh from being uh
imposters as i was with them and bang
or actually i don't clear cali
i did see watson at the end i was trying
to open the door i couldn't open it
you're an impossible stupid card no the
card keys
[Music]
uh came in to the middle of a room i
don't remember and uh
together someone saw me challenge
because i wear
talking to you huh because you're not
openly no i was feeling ghost mode
i have nothing to base my conjecture on
is talking to sana and son is
she's talking to you right now huh she's
a ghost and you killed him oh
i see i'm just extra talkative
no oh yeah
i don't know
i'm just gonna escape yeah but why would
watson
out her own teammates or skip yeah i
think i'm gonna skip but i was playing
mind games
or is omni being too painfully obvious
that we would question it is that her
angle
gonna be cautious
oh okay
oh i thought irish would be here because
she said crack it like it's hot
hi eva
hello hello
wouldn't it be weird if you got imposter
three times in a row
what are the chances huh
[Applause]
walk away
let's see okay i'm back in i'm back here
i should i think i need to go up here to
get to
showers
oh this is convenient
oh wait no this is just my task here i
thought that was for the
red light thing oh man
i smell it girl we were alone and she
could have killed me but she just went
off and did her test
he was kindly howdy and i went on my way
i saw kiara and we were on the left side
of the map so this kale couldn't have
been chiara but i think it was the other
imposter who might i didn't even see him
he already passed it
where did he see me i don't know i was
trying to get to the whatever it was
sabotage i forgot what was crash course
or whatever
i was in records but i didn't see
anything you were in records
does it have the
table with the folder on it that's the
wrecking room
yeah like i walked in from
wait i'm not so sure anymore um
[Laughter]
[Music]
it might not be records if you didn't
see me but i'm pretty i thought it was
records it's like
describe it
i don't remember anymore it was but i'm
pretty sure it was records uh like are
you sure i've been there so iris no it's
not since i take my vote back i don't
even know where are you where are the
you haven't heard a lot from mume or ina
yeah
isn't it
oh i was all the way okay i spawned in
kitchen with mummy and then i went to do
my task in the uh the bottom left thing
of course called uh so our suspects are
iris and kiara got it
[Music]
for me right
i mean you didn't kill me
yeah we were up there at the top
room where it's really easy to kill
people blood didn't
and
lie though i'm sorry we have 10 seconds
left
i don't know
seriously
um i'm just gonna i didn't i wasn't very
convinced by iris i was not convinced
what's your problem
i don't know
[Music]
anna's giving me a funny vibe either i
made it
usually
when you're crew man you have like a
whole bunch of like uh deductions in a
row what is closest to showers
i think this was it yeah
i didn't realize i also found the last
time and i didn't kill her last time i
didn't kill her this is done but how
does this work
[Music]
and then she got bonked that's sad
poor bae
oh that's not where it is first
spoiler room
wires
wire
there
okay cargo
um i really don't know who could be
hey
oh hi everyone oh hi
hello
keep a distance please please
[Music]
uh i have to go into the cargo room if
anyone wants to go there with me
[Music]
[Applause]
why are you thanking ina why were you
thanking enoch wait no it is all of
council this is
okay
[Music]
is
and i saw callie and then now
that will tell you
uh
[Music]
i don't know i'm trying to think
it
[Music]
was something seconds afterwards
i'm confused
yeah definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who we vote off
it's good are you i might have one for
each of us brain right
[Music]
they both killed me
right oh my god maybe her game is [\h__\h]
emergency meeting
i mean
[Music]
let me do this let me do this let me let
me just do this real quick let me just
do this real quick
[Music]
okay let me do one more
left side not at guys
call
what other side hold it off
[Music]
another side killed she's gonna kill me
i'll protect you
somebody calling me
isn't even calling
how do you fix it i don't know
this
oh there she goes there she goes
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
you cannot
she made it
[Applause]
[Music]
uh
that was pretty funny though i got this
[Laughter]
i can fly
[Music]
[Laughter]
well you know what um
regardless of where you fly after this i
hope you learned your lesson
so not to not kill people that's my job
i feel bad i feel bad
wow
she's like the sheriff
such a good i'll be a good girl the rest
of us
[Music]
any time
[Laughter]
see my theories have been really
accurate
and
the washroom
and girlfriend i'm not going anywhere
[Music]
oh
good fun
[Music]
it kind of gets questionable when you
get it three times people don't even
trust you off the bats
it's harder as the game's going along
yeah
it keeps giving him positive to like the
same people yeah yeah i was really
surprised that like you would assume
that you would assume that the reaper
would be like the number one killer of
everyone but i'm actually just a task
master like that basically
i do like the task
oh yeah when i saw you callie you were
so scared of death i know right because
i don't like yeah exactly well see
that's the thing is death can't die so
the prospect of death dying becomes a
thing it's quite frightening oh
super scary
um i think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream i'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of views wouldn't happen yes
everyone's point of views yeah
[Music]
yeah i was like i was like okay if we
get a double kill like like this is good
but i couldn't say anything so i was
just trailing you around
yeah
yeah if you were on cooldown or not so
no no
that's why i like i i thought we were
going to do a double kill too that's how
i was like around and then i killed
someone and then i see you went
somewhere else it's like oh no no the
double kill and then i think yeah
because all right someone tell us
that right so yeah
thank you
only only
we would have wonderful
but you know at the same time like you
know the senpai's i i can't i can't go
and kill my senpai's right away
you can savor the kill huh
right here i like that i like that way
of life good good one
well okay girls i'm gonna go through
everyone from top to bottom again to
give a goodbye one by one and maybe tell
me your favorite moment from today or
your favorite kill or whatever so let's
start with amelia watson
oh uh wait what are we doing oh goodbye
and your favorite moment what's your
favorite kill from today okay uh thank
you guys for watching and thank you
kiara for uh setting it up again and
organizing everything and my favorite
moment
uh i really liked messing with cali that
was fun yeah it was pretty funny
i gotta admit that was pretty cool
you mean i mean uh saying that she's the
imposter what happened no she would just
outright say things like like i'd be
like are you gonna kill me she'd be like
yeah you're lucky my cooldown is off and
like run away
that's another one for the archives for
me okay well thank you amelia next up
bails
um
thanks for coming guys i hope everyone
had fun thank you kiara for organizing
again so powerful
um my favorite moment um wasn't actually
in game um it was when i went to have an
idol meeting and uh
everything wasn't mayhem
how do i like it what was going on
someone please explain okay
[Music]
it's even more chaotic when chaos is not
there that's that's the sad thing
we're gonna have a poke iris very soon
just wait
how what freaking what
oh i'm not wait i i don't need to wait
right i mean you can oh and yeah
right here everybody really guys
[Music]
all right ladies
now let's dial it back just a little bit
give me your goodbyes
me oh let's see my favorite moment has
to be um when i was trying to hold up
the the cell phone to get the cell
service on the deck where anyone could
have killed me and i saw sana come up
behind me and i was like holy [\h__\h] this
is where i
and then she was like hey callie and she
just walked away and she's like no i
have to do my task here and i was like
okay so we just switched spaces and we
like watched out for each other it was
kind of cool it's the bonding moment i
was like
oh my favorite
i'm just excited to explore yeah yeah
yeah
it was really fun
thank you next up fauna
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work and i
really appreciate it
um my favorite moment was not being the
imposter
yeah i don't know i i think i prefer
natural indian pasta too
[Music]
[Laughter]
i wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun i'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
how salty are you
i'm fine i'm fine i'm saying i was
talking to my chat though about like how
i don't usually i don't know have
conversations i don't talk like this
usually like accusatory whether it's in
a game or not it's kind of like feels
very draining uh mentally i guess
i don't like yelling at my friends
we all know it's just a game no i'm not
talking at all i had a lot of fun um my
favorite moments were
uh and i'm asking clippers please uh the
various perfectly cut screams with the
proximity chat
tally specifically
where everybody was terrified of me and
every time somebody would walk by me it
would just be blood curdling screams
i'd like to see a perfectly cut screams
uh compilation of some sort if there are
enough yeah
you had a good one too yeah for putting
this together thank you
it was
my honor my pleasure my pleasure
i was very terrified
i thought it was hera
[Music]
oh okay yeah thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful collab camera
i love among us to bits
i'm so glad i was able to do this and i
i i would go for among us like off
stream anytime if we had enough people
oh my god i like it yeah but
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
impostor was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
and also like wow well personally for a
moment that really didn't have much to
do with me um i really liked how cali
you know when she found fauna's body was
like it was pretty boring
you're kind of out of yourself yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh god i need to be careful with how i
say words from time
yeah that was my personal favorite
genuine very fun game
i was like okay if i get all the hair
girls and maybe the other imposter can
go on a killing spree oh yeah that's
right i was assuming when i was imposter
too i was like oh you know's probably
i'm probably gonna have to be aggressive
so that's why i'm waiting on killing and
killing yeah
aggression is the way to go but i was
trying to clear my name and that was how
i got out trying too hard to clear my
name
i was yelling in her ear the whole time
yeah i'm really just laughing a ghost in
my ear
okay crony next doll
oh
sorry um
what was i was i gonna say oh yeah thank
you
no no no thank you so much for arranging
this
oh
[Music]
thank you so much to kiara
uh for arranging this i really love this
game and
it's been fun i think my favorite moment
was
uh
well every moment was pretty funny but
whatever the
the proximity chat exploded whenever a
meeting happened
[Laughter]
the first time when the meeting happened
everybody was screaming and i didn't
even know what was going on but that was
funny so
thank you for that
that was more fun thank you cronie
next time
hello
thank you kiara for organizing
everything everyone says that
we're doing a hard time
[Music]
i'm i'm blushing thank you please
continue
uh i think one of my favorite parts that
i experienced was i spawned where ena
were with ina
and i turned her and i said wouldn't it
be something if you're the imposter
three times in a row and she's like yeah
that really would be she just walked
away
[Laughter]
it's absolutely drenched in sweat
oh my god
you know has so much blood on her hands
today
yeah i don't know i think it's killed on
many in the last two games
um very good at
you know your innocence and your your
favorite moment
who was your favorite kill maybe
oh who felt the best putting a knife
through there
jeez
well
um
it's gonna be half
there's there's been a lot of good kills
but i think it's gonna have to go with
the
uh cronie in the it wasn't the first
game or something where she was like
please don't kill me i was like okay
you just said sure but only that's easy
to make a good impostor
[Laughter]
yeah it would be very scary and
intimidating though because callie was
every time when i was sussing callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
i was so scared who's yelling at me but
i'm sorry it's you huh
no it's you know you reverse
okay santa give us your your goodbye and
your favorite moment please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab cara um i'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too i missed your vlog
my favorite moment is like
[Music]
we're so happy you are here today sanam
we're waiting
[Music]
waiting for you tonight
about my favorite moment as uh
pretty much every time i heard kelly
scream but now my favorite moment is
spending time with all of you guys
[Music]
i'm sorry i killed you i
[Laughter]
you should next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because i i believe everything you guys
say i did video live twice at the very
end
all right well um uh for me my favorite
moment one i had so many but i guess the
one that uh stayed in my head now is um
i think it was in this in the
round before the last round where uh
everyone was sussing
gouda and she was just trying to speak
but then like i was really
mad and then ahmed was like well i'm
gonna follow you to see if you're really
innocent and i was like chilling with
inna as ghosts and we were just talking
about the better curling uh just we're
standing there together as ghosts and
then ahmed and guna ran into the room
having a huge fight like disgusting
[Music]
[Laughter]
kindergarten fights
they were running in circles yelling at
each other
oh man um but yeah uh um it was it was a
i'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh you know i had some
troubles in the beginning but i'm so
relieved
i'm sorry about that no no no no no no
no no no
yeah it worked out for sure yeah as the
organizer i'm just happy as to that
everyone had fun and and no hold on
scuff was that present today
no problem
thank you for participating i'm sure
there's some some among us who are a
little bit tired of this among us game
but uh i think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes
yeah it was a blast i'll kill you do
sometime again in the future yeah
hell yeah
yeah do it now with everybody
yeah among us
really
one more thing i kind of want to do is
like because i organized the en id mario
kart tournament now that we are 11 ends
we could do a full en my tournament as
well
11 people like not 12 by 11. is it just
one of the one of the people are gonna
be bots is that what it is
is it time for another training arc yeah
[Music]
well it is uh past 5 a.m for me so i
hope we can and we'll get ourselves oh
yeah
oh sorry an announcement for
oh do you want to announce something oh
yeah yeah yeah
um i have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
uh collab
another one yeah
and mark it on the calendar
yeah big halloween collab details are
secret for now but uh yeah now you guys
mark it down lock it down
your calendars both girls and friends
yes
yeah this one is organized by ahmed so
you know it's gonna be amazing
amazing amazing
organizing amazing not even trying to do
the pun i'm just really saying it's
genuinely gonna be amazing
perhaps amazing
[Music]
i mean outsi myth oats council to hope
and oats english it's ian
korean
okay
ready
free two
one
[Music]
i love that thank you
oh yes i can hear
not really anymore
muted are we muted right we're muted
right