[Music]
me
tan me
[music]
me
me me tan me
me me me me
me
[music]
nao
me me
goo
cabin in the form  Hongo 4th place
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, I
went in.
[Music] I'm good.
[Music]
I'm
good.
Uuuuuuuuuui
blue wear species Stone is
a little
different.
A
Everyone, Mayumi, the
bugs are here! I tried to play Japanese, but today
Japan is limited, well, it's a little okay, but I ended up having a
live show.  english There might be a little bit of English in
there, but in 9 minutes, it's
so energetic that it
's going to be abolished. I've always wanted to do it, but I've always
wanted to do it too soon. Why,
training today?  I decided to do it.There are a lot of people in Japan
.
Unfortunately, there are a lot of
people out there at this time of day, so I end up meeting a lot of people
.
The era is not the next one, Span Jobs Burn. I say
so. A
girl who looks like a schoolgirl is a helper.
A pia buh Adu surfing & Star Hara Taboru blowing a ball 4
Star
Nice to meet you. After all, it's rare to feel safe in that Japanese shadow.  I think it's a first for me too, so I
think I'd be happy if people saw it.a I'm
worried about people coming to the store.The
scene where I'm using the room.Ah, I wonder
if it's okay.Ah.
[Music]
Hey.
Yesterday, I said that the rain would become the Meiji Restoration. Some
people may not have noticed, but yesterday I
went to Marshmadovo.
So, I'm
planning to share that with the general public, but I'm
planning on answering everything about Kitamajiba yesterday.  Um, it was because of that,
but
most of the tea is probably 50%.My
question is
about Pekkura-senpai.In addition to being
exclusive to Deppuri, Ikura-senpai, who is the core material, is too much of an island.
I think there are probably a lot of Japanese listeners who like Tekura Raw Pies
,
but when other people ask Baek and other seniors' questions, they
just don't get it.
However, the next
question was about 40% ingredients,
and before that, I
had to finish the tape with a question about the mutual amount, but I
kept ordering,
and I
thought, ``This is crazy.''  I mean, it's
cheap if you keep having nosebleeds on paper Well, maybe everyone is expecting it,
but it's really good. It's
funny when my senior talks about it, so that's what my dad said, but from that chat, it
feels even more original.  I wonder if I'll get to the question one day.
Hey,
quality too.
Who would you like to collaborate with if the ban on collaborations is lifted?
What kind of conversation would you like to have with your senior? What do you like
about your senior? How did you find out about him? I like his sandbag broadcasts. It's
always been the same. I don't
know.  I'm a liar, Ivan, chocolate fashion, my
family, please post it as a sponsor. Bye Oe Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Jack
to Jack as pink revise? Oh
no aa It's quiet, then go to the Philly team  I'd
like to see something like Pekarsepa 3D or blow 4 or something like that from a house where it's warm but not amazing, but now I'll have to stream it myself.  I do
n't mean that. I think there are many different kinds of jokes and turns, but that's right. I'm often told that I'm a living person. I do
n't think I'll be able to read the following tags: What should I do?  I'm
not trying to do it though
After all, Baek has seen almost all of Senpai's archives, so I
wonder if that's an influence. I don't want Specra-senpai to think that he's trying to imitate me.
How should I pay him? Ah, ha.
Aaah,
that's what I was told. Why are you trying to make Baek look like your senior? How can I
get rid of that? I'm
not, but yeah, I'm saying
a lot. Well, today, most of those serious broadcasts.  I
think it's going to be a story of complete defeat, but
thank you for your support.  There
were a lot of questions about Mani.
[Music]
I'm sorry for the people who haven't slept in that square, but I'm sorry. I read everything properly.
I've read it all. Let's go see that first viewing at the Wood Fest Fashion Park. Let's
go see some kind of horror right away. Pecora. I saw the name in the front. That's all there is to it, and it's just a spa.
Ahaha. I
'm in. Woopapa.
Mathematics energetic nx 3.  a
I'm not feeling well, but with your brightness, my heart is also energized. Thank you very much. I'm
rooting for you so that I can collaborate with my seniors from the beginning.  Is
n't that a question?
Thank you. Well, I'm not overdoing it. I'm also looking forward to it. I don't know. I
often hear that people get energized by my broadcasts, but I
can't really imagine if that's true.
Well, anyway.  A
certain senior of mine, Susumu Nagai, is giving me energy, so I think it's better to think of him that way.Okay,
this
is a question that doesn't include the senior's name.I have no choice
but to use it.There aren't many of
them.Ah.
ana
Hello,
Kyara-chan's Kamishima Japanese is mixed in so it's easy to understand and her
reactions are cute, so I'm watching this.Thank you Coop.Does Cha-
chan ever eat Japanese food?I'd like to know what kind of Japanese food you like from eating investments.Streaming  I
'm always looking forward to seeing Chara-chan's energetic side, and I'll continue to support her.Lure,
uh, hey, horsey, oh my, my favorite is,
for example, Tontaccha Travel.  Douyakidori
Tsuma Yakitori Yakitori Hani I wonder if they eat Japanese food. But Yakitori
may be called barbecue when you think of it as barbecue, but it is completely different from the foreign version of Bahiko, so
I think that Yakiniku is Japanese food. Well, it's Japanese food.  When it comes to Japanese food, I like grilled meat and grilled
meat, but I prefer yakiniku (grilled meat).I like yakitori, but it's yakiniku.That's
Japan.
In English, it's called barbecue, but it tastes different.Well,
if you've ever been invited to a barbeque in Japan, you'll probably have
enjoyed it because you've never eaten barbecue in Japan.  I thought it was a grill and
was expecting a proper bar, but instead it
turned out to be yakiniku.I love yakiniku, so it's nice, but I
thought it was barbecue sade.  I
thought it was barbecue char, so I used the normal yakiniku sauce,
and I used meat from a yakiniku restaurant.It's
not barbecue.This is yakiniku outside in Kansai.It's yakiniku
done outside.
Are you Japanese? I
wonder if you think all Valkyu is yakiniku, but the
barbecue is different. I
think both are kind of attractive.
Well, I love muscles, but I was expecting something different.
Wow, you should really check out the two pillars. Big
Rea.
This is how
many Japanese viewers will do this.
ni charmy nice kamen yay
push up barbeque
ender jab soon come
on sister tonkatsu daisukin
but what i like is fillet cutlet
dan i
used to see that tonkatsu  I
stole it because I liked it 2
Hmm, well, I didn't know that it had a fillet cutlet back in the day,
but what should I say? If I
called it an old man, it would be stupid.
To 33, I
asked 33, ``Ah, isn't there someone who is kind enough to give birth?'' 33 said, ``There's something in that fillet cutlet.''
Now I only eat Harizuki Hirekatsu,
so I'm 33 years old and I'm so
grateful for the greatness of this old man.Well, I
have the impression that the old man is much older.No, I'm
playing with the old man.watch The old man is much older.  I
have an image of Naru, but that's not the case. I
think it's acceptable to say that I'm an old man who wears udara.
Well, that's what I mean. I love ramen, but
I can't really drink it.
That's why
[Music]
Um, I'm really embarrassed to go into a normal ramen shop.
Well, how long does it take for everyone to eat ramen?
Everyone can eat it in like 5 minutes, right? You
can finish it in an instant.
5 minutes, 3 minutes, 3 minutes.
Well, it's only 3 hours, but the
earliest I can eat is 30 minutes,
so it
's safe to eat that way.Well, it's not a fork and spoon, but it
's still as it is.
People say that farmers grow very slowly, but I
don't have any sense of it that day.I
noticed something when I grew.  Well, if
I grow longer, on the contrary, I'll have
more sides, so I'll have more food to eat. That
's a good thing. It's a good thing that I'll grow longer. 1 house, 5 pieces, and that kind of thing.
Oh
ios re dinger noodles.  Ingredients Can Parks Wessai author
Prada is not good all over the house y Special collection wooden chair How to live 5 quickly Rose arch is 5 and
Daichi Prefecture Soi 11 ast Farm
Well, that's what it is. Well, let
's
go.
Next time, I'll definitely lick the pekrasen tube again.
Hmm.  8 is a different size that can't be placed.Okay,
what was your impression when you first talked to Nominu from the Fallive family?  If there is
anything you would like to do in the future or anyone you would like to collaborate with, please let me know.
Mun's original home port I remember the first time we talked, Ando. I
roughly remember that cat. First of all,
that hunting and hunting
turn money.
Kari-chan, who I thought was an interesting person at first,
said that the words she used were really funny, and the first thing she said was that she really
wanted to get along with this person.The first thing she said was that she really liked this person.  I
talked to Kare-chan when we were alone, and I fell in love with Kare-chan's appearance at first sight.I
thought she was the type of person, and I really loved Kare-chan.From
the beginning, even when I heard it for the first time, I
thought I'd like it from the beginning.  I thought that I
couldn't help it,
but I was really naughty and the powder was really helpful.Who is it?Well, if it's a
serious story, I'm
busy.  He's always very helpful. Even
though he's
always busy, he always
creates a sense of reality for me. c This nude statue is a
good thing. For example, that first loading screen in my house. Well, the illustrations are from the
old days when I was there.  The animation Hakari-chan made the
video for her debut book, which I also drew, and she
added the animation to the roof, but the
actual one is on the floor.
I said, ``It's okay to do something simple,'' and I said, ``It's okay to be simple.'' I said, ``It's okay, it's okay to be simple.'' It's
no good. It's really just the finishing touches, and I can't
make a firm promise. When I was told that I'd make it, I was already
4 years old, 5 years old.  When I got it, I was so happy because I realized that even though it was out of stock, I was able to do a lot more than I imagined. I
really love Kari-chan. Even though I'm so
busy, I still try to sleep and help her out.
Well, I'll leave that aside for now.  Maybe
Oh, the other flowers were wonderful from the beginning, too.
But Gura-chan's beginning, I always thought that I was quiet like this.
That's right,
even when I did 2 wows, I didn't have a crown. I
guess I didn't understand all this time. Oops, you're cute, but I thought you were a bit outspoken. Eh,
continue.  At first, I didn't understand
Ina-chan, and
Itoi-chan was also very calm and kind.From the
beginning, I thought that this girl was going to be saved.Ame-
chan, from the beginning.  I
guess it's called a stump. It's reliable. I wonder if we can get along. I thought it would be fun. Well, I thought it would be easy. Hmm, I'll have to look at it. It's so cool. Hmmm,
hmmm.  That's right, I'm
counting on you. I was definitely thinking of going amelia. Amelia-chan is amazing and reliable. She
might really be the best person to help you.
Amelia-chan, yeah.  I
always thought that Ame-chan was great.For
example, when I made the layout for her hanshi paper, I was really
bad at it, so I didn't know what to do.I was
really worried about the management,
Amelia.  At first, she
asked me if I could make it for her, but when I told her that I had to make it myself, she
gave me all the different materials.
That's the problem.It's called "vector gy" in Japanese, but they
gave me a lot of non-vector side dishes.Eh,
4# r releaser e 4 a japanese Soap Yun Soi.They
gave me vector material, so I was able to make this.Hmm, it
worked out well.  I
wonder if this is what I want to do from now on or who wants to play 4-on-3.  I have
n't collaborated with Anna-chan and Kari-chan yet, so I'd
like to do a collaboration with the other three, Ano-Usa, and both of them,
but it's hard to come up with the content yet.  Puff has added one more person, I've
added my own, and I'm
sorry.
Well, Mabe Salmon, A-chan, Sweet Hosting's arm,
Check Thaler, a
full of hot top bars, and a, a
[ __ ] mhr, aaaaaah, so much power, b younger.
Well then, the web is all stagnant. Haaaaa
Besides the question of whether I would like to collaborate with Amano or anyone else, I saved it so that's another story.
Thank you very much for the three people. Next time...
]
Two Moon
[Music]
Yeah Boo
Boo
Data
is out
Eh, this is my senior's name
Guts
Uh Aati key
Good
My Japanese: Ah, isn't this Japanese? My Japanese doesn't have music yet, so please forgive me.
Question: Suka-chan always refuses Kina-chan's affection, and in response to this,
Beko's senior always refuses.  He's kind, and lately he's been
using English to draw pictures of machines and brains.That's true, but even so,
Chara is always telling Kai-chan that she's married.What does
that mean, Carr-senpai wonders?
What's the description?Funfun's fans have certainly been saying this
recently.It's been said recently, so I
'll explain it to you.I
want to marry Haru-
chan.Peck is my senior and I love her so much, but I want to get married.  I don't have any feelings like that.
Ah, I
just
want to be friends.
And
yeah,
from now on, I have a
hammer friend who wants my seniors to think that he likes me
. Ah,
that's the pattern.  Now that I've
been fishing with that dream, I
have a slightly different way of thinking
about hunting and Aqua Super.
By the way, I read that it's already morning, and I
understand now that I'm a parent and child, but that's
true.  I feel like my senpai is really kind to me.Hmm, I was
really worried at first, but I was wondering how I should approach him,
but I
thought it would be dangerous if I pulled him out, but he
drew my vowels during the stream.  It's about  Thank
you very much, I
thought that you were standing there.
Success, success,
next.
It happened, but he did it all the time. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I
really want to watch
3D together at home  Ah, wait a minute, I went to see it.
Sound
is the basics. I just want to see it for just a moment. I want to see what's going on.
Just for a moment.
What are you doing? I'm not good at
hora hora.  Ah, the theme 3 d Okay, I
wonder how they're doing it
a
[Music]
Yeah,
ah, a, yeah, yeah, that's cute
. I wonder if they'll do a lot of them from now on. Huh, yeah, a [Music] a They have all kinds of faces, right?
Hey, let's focus on the de facto abolition of
sutras.I
think I'll have a chance to do something with 5 Japan, but if Chara collaborates with Baek.
Why do you want to have fun collaborating with your husband? Hayao
Down Collaboration Minecraft Hut I'd like to ask you many more questions.
Yes,
I got a check.That's right, I've never played Minecraft.Um,
but I wasn't really interested in Micro to begin with, but I've been
watching a lot of my seniors' streams, and I find it soothing to watch them do it, and I
can watch it for hours.
Kara Day 5 I want my senior to introduce me to the hood server, and I want him to
take me through the experience of using it, like ta, which I'm always looking forward to doing in Minecraft.  I'm
looking forward to catching that trident at sea.
Ah, there's just one thing. Well, I know everything about Sepa, so
please don't make me explode. Please don't make me explode again.  I
saw it too, and I
'd like to do a lot of collaborations, but I'd like to do something together.What I
want to do the most is
Maikura, but I
want to compete.
Well, I bought it when I saw that it was abolished in the letters on the Pekar line bar.Well,
if I could wait and live, I wouldn't be the director in the mountains, so I thought maybe I would have bought this too.Well, I'm
practicing.  But it's hard to breathe out. When it comes to it, I
can't find the words.
Hmm, it's a little difficult, but if I do my best, I'm not sure if I'm buying it or not. I do
n't know what I said.  I
wonder what's going to happen, let's compete next time Appa: I'm
going to practice
Eh yeah
[Music]
Kutcha-
chan Thank you for always having fun broadcasting
As for the question, I'm at home, so I can understand. Pei-yana-chan is writing about how annoying she is, but
Cha-chan is drawing illustrations.  I used to really like drawing illustrations.I
used to draw a lot.I
worked at a lot of companies.I actually want to become an illustrator.  I
had a dream about ``Hello,'' long ago. I was
always told that I was very good at my age, but
now that I've started doing other things, I no longer draw illustrations.  When I open my eyes, I think I'm normal for someone my age,
so I'm no longer special. I used to be called special, but now I'm special. Now I'm no good.
Well, someday I'll get
some illustration data again.  I'd be
really happy if I could get a job, but
I'd like to see if it's Kilo.  Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu value form nature- nature-
nature glory form nature form colors  It might be a little further away if I put it out.
After Ai hurried back to the countryside, I drew it for the first time in
a while, so if I study and practice a little more, I might become a town or village.  It's
increasing It's
a bit small English translation cats
Oh, you're good at it, Parry, I'd
be happy if my dad told me, but I won't do it
Flattery 4 cars
I Well, from Sony it doesn't feel that way Hahaha
yeah SD Characters Wow Noah no no Jingu screen  There was August, but
next time, it's been a
long time since I've been serious, and I've been thinking that I want to have something other than a proper person, but I always have backgrounds
and English studies.  I did
n't like Niigata because I didn't like my dad's medical background,
hey,
hey, he's cool, so I like him.
Hmm,
for my dad,
as expected, papuwa for him, it's too amazing, and
when he told me it was a movie bird, I
believed him. [Music]  I can't do it, I'm not good at it,
but I'm happy, but it's
seriously wrong.
Even Mario was fooled. I'm
sure I'm praising the buses in that direction.
Tannuna -Camera Net Ah Ah, Ah, ah, ah, ah, Ah, Ah, is the most praise.  I
want to draw myself,
and I also want to draw my senior, Doigaki, and
various inons. I want to draw male seniors,
but I guess I
have to practice.
This is what I want to do in the morning.
Which do you speak better, Japanese or English?
Yeah, neither do I. I was
thinking about it, but I thought
Japanese would
be better. Maybe I'm better at it.
I said pronunciation bar.
Arashi. Hey, special price aircraft carriers don't speak English. It's my native language.  Well, it's
German, so I guess English is closer to German than Japanese, so it should be easier for me,
but for some reason,
Japanese is a little different and
difficult.
My pronunciation is better in Japanese than I am in English.
Sometimes English gets weird like that.
There are words that I don't know how to pronounce and where to pronounce them. Even
Japanese words are better in English. [Music] I can understand a lot of words.
Yes, that's right. I guess it's
about the same. In the end, I guess the balance is about the same.
Torii Trilingual Bird has a similar feeling to Parilinger.
But it's about the same.
Pima Ingusuma Chap new sparks in
Ba
finger charm nice  The players from the Plantation team, supported by pitters, are
harmful Spain
aturn
Hmm, I
guess I'll answer the checker,
please give me a service shot.
Kitani is stuck. He's
in. Ah, I'm
flooded with service. Let's
give him a good one.
Service shot.
Ugo.  Ah 4 shares
Ah, this is
a little neat,
Dam
Service Shot
Umm Turtle,
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah, this is the difference, please,
please,
please RAN
Ugh ok Please take it Kyuppa I
thought it was a waste because I don't see much of this place I thought it was a waste No no
no Okay, this is
good, isn't it?  Right,
this fishing season is definitely good, and the way her socks are a little tight is a good girl. A good
girl and a miniskirt.
Hey, hey, I like the miniskirt on the right, and the
rap that prohibits the use of belts. It's
so ec, up,
tape tape. That pink color on Kako's nails is so nice.
This room is so nice, too. What do you say?
What should I say? Um, what should I
say about this part?
Hmm, what is that next to the word "I'm trying hard" and "I'm eating"? Do you know that next to that belly button?
I wonder if it's the wings of the navel. I wonder if that's what it is. I
sent a copy of Somai Vogue.
Why are so many weird images coming out of the navel? Hahaha.
But maybe that's it? 6 and the images.  Come on,
no, the camera is shaking because of the guard.Oh
yeah, it's here.Well, you
see, there's no sound at all.It's all
amazing.It
's possible.  The
perfect feeling is good. The hips of amazing and the waist are that tale
-very good
BOOK Papa
-donomon Ah, oh,
paparo, and papa,
Daddy made by Daddy to Hiratsuka.  The
firewood is surprisingly good too. I
like it, but it's not just about the naughty part.
Actually, it contains what I like the most.
How do I do this? Now, when my
father comes, I'm going to turn the cloth off. I wonder if it's my
favorite pink tone. It
hits the universe, ah,
this isn't it. It's
like a reflection of the universe.
It's a beautiful sound.  It's
beautiful,
oh, oh, oh, it
moves so much before it moves so much.
[Music] I'm so happy
that I'm going to be able to play this game.
While I'm going back, I'm going to be
in 22nd place.
Was it a good service shot?
Was it a good feeling? I wonder if
I fell in love with it again.
Hmm,
ok, ok,
I love you even more. Let's
go to pets.
I can't make any progress at all because I'm such a talkative egg. I wonder if I'll knead.
Hello Cake Taker and No Fraud and No
Match Machine are a little different, right? I'm Ah-chan without Chicken, but that's how I got interested in Japan.
Ie-chan's Japanese is really good, so I'll try my best to study English as well.  That's
what I thought.Ah, I often get questions like this.There were quite a few people who said they were working hard to study English.As
a Japanese member of the group, I
wonder what sparked their interest.There were so many different influences at the same time, haha.
that  I don't know
what it was, but I was showered with it.
[Music]
That's right. My
mother gave me a game that inhibits the right brain. She's been working on it. She's
doing a shared video. What is this about this girl and
her style?  The style and atmosphere
of this RPG game was the first I'd seen, so I thought it was really to my liking, so when I looked into it, I
found out that there were a lot of things like that
.  When I found out that there was a game called RPG, I got really
into Decherzu, so ever since then I've loved Thes, and I've
played almost all of them besides the version,
but I'm pretty sure there's one that I've played before.  I
think it was pretty much the same timing now, but
later on
in the library, there was that
German train in the library.  I
found this one and thought it was a really cute drawing, and at
that time, I thought that I like illustrations like this, along with the one from Colored Tales, and
from there I
started drawing more and more illustrations myself, and I started drawing illustrations about Japan.  I
wanted to know more about it, so I did a lot of research.After that, I started to get really into Japanese idol culture and
idol music Hello Project,
and I was so hooked on
it that to put it in English, I was like, "Wow!"  I
have
That's how it goes, but it's so long ago that I don't even remember whether that game came first or that manga came first.That
kind of thing. Um, 7. Good luck studying English.
[Music]
1st place Germany Which one?  I think
I'll save 71 out of 7 right now, but I
haven't progressed to 10.
[Music]
Pooh
[Music] I
think this is a problem that Japanese people have.
Result History Kama Chara-chan has been showing up a lot lately, probably because she doesn't go out much due to telework.So, if
there is a way to relieve stress in Kya-chan's own way, could you please
let me know?Please continue to stream, thank you 2
I think the main problem with the Japanese people is that they work too much,
which causes them too much stress.I
basically live my life at my own pace.
I only do things that I absolutely need to do,
and I've lived a pretty good life, but in recent years,
I'm also an amazing person.I've accumulated a lot of that,
especially a week before and a week after the fire.  Ah, I've
been under a lot of stress and have to do a lot of work for various reasons, and then all of a sudden, to be
able to be seen by so many people, well, I'm also curious about the prefecture, which is
amazing.  I'm the
type of person who researches a lot of things and chooses a lot of things, so the
number of replies keeps increasing.To be
honest, I don't know how to relieve stress.On the
other hand, I would like to know about it.Um, I
have a pet.
If it were true that I'm not around right now, I could let that pet heal me and relieve my stress,
but it's
not there right now, hmm, it's a bit difficult, isn't
it?  What am I?  I'm depressed because of that
stress level, and
it's hard because I don't have Neko Neko, but that's why I have
other ways to relieve stress.I
guess it's about the dullness of Annette Hari, minus Netflix.  It's
interesting to watch the time, but I'm the one who's watching it. I've
watched it many times, but I'm rewatching it now. I guess I'm
getting energized by watching it.
But I really want Lean Nico to heal me. It's
not Lens Beast Veil, it's my older friends. Ah,
everyone knows it.
Ah, if you haven't seen it, I recommend it. It's a cat. Thank you. Bach. Is
it a cat?
Ah, I want to meet a cat.
Actually, I took a nap today, but when I saw this dream again, we were happy together. I
thought he was skipping the course, but he was just playing MacArthur.  I
love taking questions from Yasuji Eighter.
[Music]
How many people are you
trying to make? Here are 5 examples of
this ne-yo.
Me 4 challenge clearly stated.
Also, I really like the board.
What kind of cutter should
I use? Don't use me. I'm using this.  I'm the last phoenix left in the world. If you
use me for cooking, there
will be no more phoenixes. Is that okay? Is
that okay? Do
n't you think it's a waste?
Is that what you're talking about? Please stop using the chicken-up recipe from the Pattern Japan interview. Dad is the one who
knows best that it's not chicken. I asked him to
respond, and he said that
to me a lot. He said that to me in Endless.  You might
think that if you eat it once, you'll be able to respawn, so no matter how many times you eat it, it's okay, but that's not the case. Is
that
just psychology? But no, I've
been living for hundreds of years, and at the end of my life, that girl is already
a.
Day rises again from his own lungs,
but if it's assembled, it's 4-4,
so it won't try to eat me. It's a waste, a
virgin. Hey, it's a phoenix. It's a waste, isn't it? It's
not delicious, and the
person who burps and pats too much.  Enter
Hmmmm
Pooh part
[Music] I
guess it was because of my connections.
Oh yeah, I
got asked a lot of expensive questions.  Good
evening, I'm always looking at the abolition.I'm currently living in Canada and studying English.  I've
been asked to teach tips on how to use English well, but I don't
know why there are no dental clinics, but on the other hand, I want to improve my Japanese skills.
Can you use things like Chaa-chan? I really enjoyed reading it.
Eta
A That's right, I went
there.
Japanese people can use English well. I
have no choice but to learn how to use it. That's different. I have no choice but to get used to it. That's how
I am in Japan.  Words
How I Learned Bar There's
only one way
I learned Japanese. I didn't use honu. I didn't have any teachers. The only way I learned Japanese was
through conversation, or just communication. If you do that every day, you'll
definitely become fluent in English.
But you really have to use water every day.  I
think it's okay if you just talk to yourself c Or English conversation I think it's okay if you do it every day, you can do it on Skype, you can have chocolates.If
you do something like that on YouTube or something like that, if it
becomes a town or village, if you
buy it anyway, it's nursing care
communication
If you do this, you'll be better at pronunciation.When you come
across a word you don't know, take note of it immediately.When
I memorized that Japanese, Volume 1 a  I didn't take any notes. I
thought it would be a hassle because I was
lazy, but I looked up the meaning of
that word and tried to use it right away.
Then I couldn't get it out of my head. Well, I'm special.
Yes, I don't think there are many people who learn that quickly,
but I think it's better to write down blank notes, and if you
think about using them next time, it will
be easier.
Yeah, even with those kind of bones, it's still difficult to get into the 5th frame.It's
especially difficult.For example, I
tried to memorize other words like Italian, but the pain just didn't enter my head at all.Why?
And I
wonder why.One
more thing, I
didn't have a conversation.Two things, I wasn't interested.So
unless you're really interested in fashion, you won't be able to remember it.And you
have to have a conversation, too.I'm
collecting as many people as I can.  Is
this
3?  Did
you all
learn a little bit from what I said? Well,
interest comes first.
Interest and motivation.
Chaa-chan1 I think Chara-chan's Japanese is really good, but sometimes she speaks Kansai dialect.
Have you ever been there before? It's
different now, but I've lived in Kansai before.
Hmm, it
wasn't that long, but I've lived there before. I
wonder if that's the influence of that.  I only speak Kansai dialect.  I was
told that 5 was a great patient, Bendel.I
didn't even notice it myself, but now it doesn't appear much anymore, but I
think it pops up occasionally, but with you.  When I introduce myself to him, I often say ``Ie'', but we don't
agree.That's
typical of the Kansai region.
For some reason, I was ranked 3rd in the museum. I love Osaka. I used to go there a lot when I visited Kosaka after the earthquake. It
feels like that. I want to go to Misaka again. It's
like Osaka. Oh yeah. Something happened. I also had questions like
this.  If I'm going to continue talking, there are so many colors for that question. I
looked for a bit and found 8.
This is it. Hmm.
Throw.
[Music]
Hmm. I
shouldn't have saved 71 questions.
[Music]  It's
not white, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh,
babaa 1
[Music]
ANA eh, is
good,
and I'm waiting a little,
and I can't find it
someday.  I can't find it either, but I have one question to sew:
Where do I want to go in Japan? A
mud bath question. There was that machine, but I really like it.
After I changed my clothes, where have I been? Where do I want to go?  I
want to go to Hokkaido, which is equivalent to collapse.I
want to go to Okinawa.The things I've
loved so far are
Arashiyama and
Kyoto, which was quite a while ago,
and Hakone and Enoshima.A
no, my mother's clothes.  I've
been to many places like Itoshima and Sawyer, but I've
never been to Hokkaido, so I
want to go there.  My
brother wants to go on tour in Hokkaido, right?
There's a snowy festival there, right
? I want to go
there. Also, Fukuoka-san is my favorite ramen. Unfortunately, I'm
from Fukuoka.  I ate it, but I do
n't like going to Ramen girls, so I
went to Ichiran.
I like tonkatsu tonkatsu the most.
[Music]
Then 333  It
took me 30 minutes to sort out the list, but no one else would see me, so I do
n't think they'd say I'm an idiot for eating this person.
But I was able to answer that, so that's what I said. Yeah, I was
asked this too, but I'm
tired. I'm Usagi and I love the songs of caregivers.
Eh, no. There's a lot of fraud. It's a lie. My senior is lamenting about the sitter.
Expenses adk Did you know about that statue? I
want to know. In the future, a Kei Ginpei. Do you
want to do a collaboration in the future? I'm rooting for
you, Mom. Well, maybe I don't remember either.  Maybe
it's Kirino, after all, I found out about
Kirino, and as soon as I found out,
this kid was funny, celebrating the 5th ball and holding it for a long time. Um, I'm already
standing up and looking at Senpai Pakal.
Ah.
Oh,
and I think the future cards are going to be something like that, and I
think I'd definitely like to stream 3D if it's possible someday.I
want to do it together.I'm
in.
- There are so many questions that I haven't answered yet, but I've included about 32 questions and 3 questions. Um, I
'd like to answer
[Music]
Answer 4 a
This is
it, Nee-chan, this is already in the past. It's
a bit long, though.
1 head
Dandandandandandan
[Music]
tan
Heheta I
'm Itai-chan It's lame
e 1 series Kiha is the latest version of Mechamecha Chara-chan Thank you I
will join when membership is available Membership Nu  It
might be done soon. Tomorrow's streamer might
have something to announce.
I'm a big fan of Fukupa-sensei, Cannon-chan's father. He said that Inn's food is
delicious, isn't it? He's the father.
With Black Rock Shooter, I fell in love with blow-sensei butts.If you don't
mind, please tell Kiha-chan who is the catcher with the pitching sense that you like.Thanks
to Kiara-chan, who speaks English and Japanese, I want to study English.  I think so. There
were a lot of people like that. Good luck. I would
be very happy if Chaa-chan transformed into 8. Thank you. I'm
happy.
You know, when the song Black Rock Shooter first came out, I was also in love with it.
Takaya
When I heard about it, I really liked the blackness of the air raids and the design, and
then I watched that animated movie.I
guess that's what impressed me the most,
but there was also the design of FJO's Altena.  I really like the
Chitto Seiryo 6 design that I've been working on lately,
but I do
n't think it's my favorite because it
comes from my dad's favorite exercise
.  It's
someone's name, but when I
saw a cute scene, the glasses moved a lot. I felt uneasy about it.
My
mom thought that personality was interesting, haha. He's
really cute. He has a really nice body.  The
scene where the feathers are smooth and beautiful, the universe is reflected in the eyes, the two hats are cute, and the smile is really wonderful.  He's
wearing a Fallen God version belt, but for some reason it says not to use it, so I don't
know why.I
feel like he has all kinds of secrets.It has duct tape attached to it, but it would be amazing if it had been there.Haha  The
scene with the duct tape makes me wonder why it's not allowed to be used.
Wow, that's such a strange collage. I'm holding on to the data from the Marinu area. It looks
really delicious, so I
wanted to eat it, so I honestly stopped by.  I wish I
could go eat, but when I look at it, I
like it.It's interesting, and the weapon looks strong.No, it's
not that toy.I heard that it was Hongo, who seemed moderate but was definitely strong.That
time.
Well then, the
nest of a transforming angel shouldn't be changed, but
if you reply, you'll turn into a real phoenix.Do you
know that I'm going to go up in sadness?I didn't want to go to
Udaka.
[Music]
Ah, haha, thank you for the question. See
you
then.
I just wanted to compliment you because I like the open-faced design,
but I'm not talking about myself.  It's like I'm in love with myself,
but don't
chase me, I'm really in love with Chopsticks Digging, but it's different for everyone.My
dad did a good job, so this is what I'm talking about.  It
's just that I think I'm being arrogant, but that's what I
want people to understand. It's wonderful, isn't it? It's because of this body. Oh, it's wonderful. I have no choice
but to say nice things. If I
look this cute, I'm already 4 years old.  I have no choice but to
press on,
thank you. A
pattern key.
Let's go after that. Please take
good care of Kara-chan. There's one more thing.
Typhoon: I'm
a little worried. Houou: Hmm. Shall I
answer this?
Hey, this is it! Ah,
yes, I haven't had a good appetite lately so I can't eat breakfast, but
what do I always eat for breakfast? Well, this changes quite a bit. I
wonder if I usually eat that sweet thing again today.  However, I said on Twitter that I should
put it on my skin in the morning and roast Rakshasa.I
don't think there are many people in Japan who sell Nutella, but there aren't that many people who eat it.  I'd
definitely prefer that chocolate spread, which
tastes completely different from the other non-Nutella chocolate spreads sold at Japanese supermarkets,
so why not just
coat it with poison and eat it?  Oh, yeah, and
that
gravure doll in Japan is a little different, but
have you ever heard of ``muse ri'' in German?I
eat it a lot in Meiji 22, and it's
hard.  I
like the scrambled egg knee-high dough, it's amazing.I like to eat Kuro-chan, too.Basically, there's no
bread left, but I highly recommend it if you spread it on it.Nutella
Pop.Oh, recently.I
make it a lot, but it's French.  Here you go,
just the French toast. Well, I think it's already sweet, but I'm going to
put some extra tuna on top of the French toast, and I'm going to put some fruits like bananas and strawberries on it, and then I'm going to add sugar at the end.  I
can get a book, but I
can't do very two wheels, but it's really easy to learn French toast,
but it's a
terrar poison that is not in French toast,
but if you eat this, it's
too happy to eat this.  That French toast was a bit of a
hassle because it took so much time,
but making it yourself is way
more delicious than that French toast face.  If you
all like it, try making it.It's really easy.What is
it?Here's some white bread.First
of all, here's a hint.First of all, let
's toast the bread.Let it
cool down. That village is doing that.It's that
one egg.3rd grade new.How
much was it?  Kenena 15020250450That's about it, but I
also mix it up with eggs, Sato, and my little brother, and that's what I personally like to include.
Add a little bit of the cinnamon book, mix it, mix it, mix it,
mix it, mix it, a 8, and
put that egg thing on top of that, and then put that egg thing on top of that, and then
put that egg thing on top of that, and all that, all that.  Ah, I
saw the sponge cake. You took it all.
About 8. Now,
miscellaneous. Did I
forget something? I
feel like it's there. I said, "Let's do it
with ummm." I asked the customer to bake more and
eat with umm.
Hey, I saw this in a YouTube tutorial, and it said that the secret thing
was the toast toso role first.The
final result seemed to be
even better.I don't know if I was relieved or not, but that's all I did.  Lily,
I do
n't like maple syrup, so I don't use it.Even if I have it, there are ways
to improve it even more.There's
nutella on it, there's fruit on it, and there
's even more bunny ice cream.  Let's
have ice cream with bunny.
1 minute for breakfast. Ah,
this is the best.
Oh, I like sweet things quite a lot. I
also often eat this with Yuro rice, and it's Ryoko's thing.
b I also eat Tappa March machines, but I also love sweet things.
From the morning.  Kids, what should I say? It's
4 times as much.
Strong people
eat French toast with ice cream and Nutella on top for breakfast. I
highly recommend it.  I
wonder if there's just one more thing. I'll endure the doubts and say if it fits the question I definitely want to answer. [Music] Non-tan-tan-tan-tan-tan-tan Okay, everyone, let's have French toast tomorrow. No, you won't regret it, and it's super healthy.
Super healthy.
This is this, this is what I wanted to respond to.
A Happy
birthday to you. I
don't know your name, but I wish you a happy birthday.
Cheonggep Atsuta p Air Lee Seong-gye Bassi j
song  Come here in the Potter car.
Sanzefu. The
house and feature snow were also in German. Yeah,
okay. It was in German. It's the same melody as Happy Bus Stop, but the lyrics are a bit weird. Please help me with the
rain letter. Way
.  Well then, I'm
really enjoying Yaroka's departure chat, but talking to everyone,
but uh, if possible, I'd like to
finish it by Daisy, Japan time,
so I'll read the Shupa chat.  I'm a
kid who can talk a little more, so everyone, I really want to do that distribution of the Japanese original,
but I don't know how fast I
can do it from now on, but I'm free to do it as I like, but I've been told to do it as I like.
But I still have to read a little copy, so I wanted to
do it more once a week, but I
guess it's about once a month.  I
thought I'd put it all together, but once we're able to have a collaborative meal, I
think we'll have a lot of Japanese spoken in collaboration with all the seniors.I'm
sorry Anno, but I want to do more, so I want to at least open the clinic in January.
Okay,
just once,
I think it's a bit of an unusual pig.I really want the viewers of that Japanese dental survey 6 lives to enjoy it, and I
want them to know about ``AnoKore Live English'' and to support me.  I
wish I could connect Yokoichi Daishin, 5 English, and Japan Live Japan all year round with everyone,
by all means, too.I've been told a lot of things, but in the end, I have no choice but to do what I want to do.  I
can't be happy if I don't do something
like that, and there are a lot of people who support me, and the people who said things like that to me were
actually moon-well,
that's the way it is.  It's
okay, thank you for all the questions. I don't know how to talk so much, so I
couldn't answer that many questions, but I
think I'll be doing a Japanese-only stream again next time, so I'll take a
moment to say hello to you. Well,
where are you going tomorrow?
[Music]
That Suan ship's biggest cherry
blossoms will be broadcast tomorrow.
Wait a minute, where are you? Hey, are you wearing this?
Help me! It
hurts, it hurts,
eh?
Chat
Eh, what and what did I drop?
Morning time: Tomorrow, 6:22 AM Japan time Building A. I'm
sure there's insurance for announcements and stuff. Tomorrow, I received a new microphone, so I'll use it tomorrow for that new microphone.
Mr. Mickey. I'll
also get the mixer audio interface tomorrow.  It's supposed to arrive, so I should be able to start using it tomorrow
. My microphone is being called [ __ ].
Actually, this is supposed to be Sora Imai's suffering right now, but people are calling me [ __ ].  I
got a microphone from Kari-chan at Minecraft, which cost a lot of money,
but maybe I'm doing something wrong, or the settings for how to use the rear are wrong, so I
can't really use it properly, but I bought a new one anyway, and I
should be able to start using it tomorrow.  Eto:
If I can use it, I'll make an important announcement tomorrow at 9 o'clock.
Okay. I
think it's 4 at the same time. Well done, ok.
Everyone was really excited, but I thought it was a waste of Abe at the microphone. Oh
yeah, everyone listened to the karaoke last time. That's
amazing. I can only sing Japanese songs, so I can't sing well, but I can't sing English songs very well.
There's the issue of investigation rights, but Japanese songs are easier to sing, and
that's why a lot of things have come up.
5 seconds before I fall seriously in love with a pink unrequited love, I'd love to
8 Even if I become a mother or a grandmother, I've sung many songs, such as Bluebird,
but tomorrow I'll sing all kinds of old songs.  There
's also a song called ``I want to re-sing it''
Hey, it's starting
now, so please listen to it if you'd like.There's also an announcement from our own company.That's
the kind of girl I am.
There's also a collaboration with a left-wing monkey artist who has a pretty thin movie at an amusement park.Well
, there's a collaboration on that dog's channel and Ina-chan's channel at 1 o'clock Japan time.Oh,
Venture Kensocho is really talkative.  This guy,
uhm, I speak German when I chat with Carspa. Is it
okay? back They
always say it's only Danke employees, but I
hope everyone is okay with it.
Hiragana and katakana are fine, but if you can
type them, I'd
be happy. I'm
desperate. I
wonder if there's a lot of departure chat in Japanese today. I can't think of anything right now. I'm looking forward to seeing how your child moves. I'll have another cup of Ness
antibacterial.  Yo, that iced tea chest,
Adan, it's okay to have just the house, but I'm glad it's a men's season.Today, I'm
going to cover a wider range of
things.Ah, but I'm sure some people will go home as they are, but I'll open it.
Well, thank you very much to everyone who planted it. I
watched this for a long time. All my seniors in Japan are broadcasting interesting videos.
Thank you very much for watching. In addition, I will be broadcasting the second part of that from now on.  It's been a long time, but I would be
happy if you could see that.Also, I would like to take
everyone's opportunity to say, ``Maido'', ``
Papa'', which is
pronounced red and brown.As
always, Mr. Azuma, the first one is...
Usually, I don't use 3 because there are so many English names. I don't know
what to do because they get mixed up. I'm
not used to seeing them. I'm not used to adding san in Zuppa Chat, so it's strange.  I feel
really uncomfortable if I don't help you. You
didn't call me.
Just try it. I'm already used to that routine, so it's difficult.
Eh, maybe it
's the fever or something strange. I feel like it's rude to be in a situation like this.  If I do
n't use it, I'll end up contributing a lot. But the English names keep coming up. It's
really difficult and difficult. Ah, it's sweets. I
just come
up with an idea. It doesn't look good. I'll try it naturally.  It's a 3-tiered family car that I'll use.Ahaha, it's
weird to have an arm that says thank you in German.This is
Shun-san with a magnetic 810 sire shaku.
Warm up Airo Fappe 13 Cushion Me Game Figure Division machine moment of soulfulness Fu
Char is in the nuclear power plant house Mr. Pinsprose I
thought this person told the Japanese people how to do it
Outside the rank
Chana is Pekorin  Tomochi Takahisa who endured the Tan family week
danke gathering Sonobe Clin Danke repair day game winter is not a thing
Danke gathering
Ethos Sakagawa san danke car
Snowbell's acid residue Junsu went bankrupt,
Danke, Kuruma-san's handshake meeting day,
8 years ago, short-term end, it's old, it's really Japanese, epima. I
called the Prin participants and Hornisse officials. I
threw away the names.  Yoshika is in 7 specs. I'm
so confused. Kotoha-san shakes my hand. Mr. Udo
raises the ventilation fan. Mr. Orange joins the participants. Mr. Shall, Tankishu Mach. Mr.
Tony God short-term season.
Volume 152, Volume 3, Erasable
8. There was a collective army of insurance heroines. Thank you for infiltrating this the other day. I really
want to retweet this because I can't pay my respects to it, but this might be a bad idea.
Said Ise: I
really liked that Sorry Big, and my older sister was like, oh, I'm sorry, my sister is like that.  It was a really
good illustration of all the girls that I drew, and I was really happy.I guess
I'm one of them.The
complaining countries were really happy.It
was really good.It seems like they saw the puppy.Aaaah
[music]
Just a car
c d e a Just  3 Kesha Carrot Flavored Yatsuhashi Bullet Singer Absolutely the person who is in the middle of the day Nepeku Oh, I
raised my senior's name
When I opened Ageage that thin one time, this name  I
saw you. What are you doing now
? Yes, uc. You're
definitely wearing a window. Ah, what are you doing now? Everyone is wearing a window after all.
Everyone's like that. I wonder
if that window is over already?
Sunbird.
Hey, I'll never be able to do that.
Thank you for the 1 window. Ah, it's
over. A. Why don't you prepare?
a. It would have been better if it started at 11:00 Japan time, but they decided on the function.
10:00
Mom, it's a
waste to just be here now
maika
Ichi-
san, it's only been an hour a day -
Seriously,
timing 8 It's
seriously starting again, it's happening again
Wow, Dad is in a hurry
Mike Ra, it's like a garden, but I piled up about 100 sheets at my own pace  I'm watching it in the archives,
so 22
Yoshihide, the third generation with a gentle taste,
Onya, one-step slope, weak, Yuda decay, Patch App Takanobu Frau-chan Peace
Pal Sore Dou Ball Eyes Pippi Bara Character
Study
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaamamiyamuramachi
It's Jimmy Choo Rain wig can't be done
english and japanese team election
3rd tank employee Cancer's Japanese is very good and wonderful.I will continue to be
wonderful.  Thank you for letting me hear your Japanese.
danke I'm going to send a message to Shunmanya-san about the flag and the poi search.
Thank you for coming. danke  I wonder if it's going to be a match, I think there's only about 2 I've seen.
Come join today's 3rd Keiharu.
Mr. Kazumaki Rio and those involved say 8,000 steps. Don't go to Wide Share Prince Plaza.
Compensation starters check the air. Regular
version fluff.  w What kind of track record is it going to take for 22 minutes to have fun?
Danke Shuu-
san voice actor Sanpei hehehe
Danke Shen Zombie Sausage 3-Dan House Haruhi Station Service Came, Shuka is Seiko-
san Danke Shun I
feel like I answered my favorite works of Papa's work and even if I want to go to Yu Yun
If you're talking about the anime, I wonder if it's blue.  After all,
if it's not enough, I
really like the skis.The
designs are all great.I
thought the chain was perfect for them.Second
place, Rank 5, Ah, there are 3 types of beach models. Hiroshi Asaya
Festival bot 3 bullets wipe out 3 cotton pads 3 strokes of carbonated reporters are conveniently available in 3 places Gyaaa
Yuasabune mother-in-law special wifi promotion explanation next time mint plus top garden
chirp Nissho penkifa Bingo Monsa even short
cherry blossoms  Let's say, the
watch central Ping Eyes Python Man is attached to the electric pen from the pen Q 3 is titanium,
isn't it?  A collection of
Muse Boy subcontractors killing Muse Boy around the earth-melting machine on Tankishu,
compiled by Soup Tama-san p Just showing the mashimaru makes the customers smile, so
it's amazing.  The
end of the san landlord
Cap dad is weak Last spring Yamayo got a tank car
Yes, that
's my sister, yes, I understand. Is it okay to be that old man or old man? Even if it's the old
man, the old man is better, and the same state is not. I
wonder if it was. Danke, I'm going to erase the car cap'n papé costume. I'll
pass it through to the medium-term budget Danke collection.  For those who don't know about it, I recommend a Japanese food called Abura Soba.I've
never eaten it.It looks oily.There's
oil on the side, so it's cheap to slurp.I wonder
what it's about, Pack.
Warm-up employee cap, eat Chiaki-san,
maniac 3rd tier, Isha-kun, Akashi, 3rd tier cosmetics,
4-1 Miyamaki Line,
Atarano, I
want the name of the white master, 6 Rama Toki, I
want Zutto, Aingyu Shudomo.  There's no point in saying that.If you don't
know it, it won't
taste good.It's a
change of pace.It's
been a long time since I've been supporting the grappler's 3rd incarnation.We
are having dinner.ios  Erase it, see it, it's delicious today.
Shop Tsubaki Ponzu tells Xu Ning Rinki to the door 1. Don't touch it. The
child of the epi-gu also has a good time. It's the bus stand of the Kesha family.
Only the horse's body is lined up.  ga ski danke shen ji danke car
just looks like a hairpin
Thank you for the total action in 8th episode 2 I
was able to make Roman Grandpa before too.
Mr. Exploration 1009 is really good at the way it is between Chonma. It's really good to be in the middle of the day.
Mr.
Bankisha Anywhere, Mr. Sero, the
flag bearer.
How many articles
does His Majesty Echo think?
This is
ke. I'm
interested in the number of books, but I can't read the end of Takeuchi.
Takeo Titanium.  Around empty titanic acid residue
Favorite 043 Tank Failover Tasan Minami Kyushu Sasan is Shu Yong About
8 cats What a week Distributed learning
Hmm, only sedans have car-type hexane,
health improvement
photos, only bankruptcies, and space cats.Three
black spots are boots.That or that is a difficult spot,
isn't it?
Every day, the toe cap is good, it's
good.March is the only car with a science
mountain.Printer.  Dankeshen is definitely the oldest in the realm.If it
was a pamphlet that said that the red bean paste was born around the spawning period, it would have been a big hit, so don't tell me.Author:
Tankishu's beloved mom Takshu before dating in the morning  The
end of the 13th edition of the book that combines sugar deficiency syndrome.
Everyone is so grateful for that service time.
After all, the woman has blue hair. She loves it. She can do it here, but it's a bad car. It's not a
reporter for the 3rd edition. It's
just a week of mania, 3rd tier family, and carbonated luck.  Niniku M-san Danke collection
Denki off-leak increasing Mitanya Shun
Kohei Kaga-san Genki starring will die or become a 3rd-dan family  I fell in
love with Mr. Ishikawa all over again. I love Kariya and Sesha.
Thank you for giving birth to me as a receiving father. I'm really grateful as well.
Bankisha
Kura pura I've read up to Mr. Bakkiba's caterpillar, so who is he? Did I choose him?
That's great! Thank you very much Bullet Standard Acetic Acid I
thought the name was beautiful even before the first transformation.This machine with the Japanese name of the wooden shape also came out.  So
did you notice it without going to the mountains
? Okay, that tweet was a big success. I uploaded my name. I
tweeted it, and it even included the line that I did before my debut, ``I want to do it in the first place.'' It's a
line from Steins;Gate.  I didn't get everyone to notice that I added it. I
wonder if they noticed the round-trip putter. I retweeted the couple's father, but
I wonder if they noticed that in that tweet, I added the message of peace and harmony with Inzuge that I wanted to pass on.  It wasn't easy for people to
notice me, so I was told that this guy was saying something terrible,
but I guess I didn't say it.I'm just
looking forward to it.I just added the leader's line from that day.I
can see it in the makeup of the 3rd episode.  There are a lot of people, after all. Mr.
Ayumu, a reporter from Orantan during his warm-up period.
Only Mr. Taiyo supports Mr. Totan, Mr. Minami Kishu
Shirochi spawning steamer,
only assets, only cars, and
only photos of hydrogen.
Hototogisu dandan reporter,
this kind of ally like long-term fee h or 8
Furya usage fee
Lou embezzlement Miya-san, employee Fenis mountain only employee, sister-in-law Sesa-ani-only car,
pudding 3rd edition, make-up Sash-san, Dankeshen swing 3rd edition, Kyosen junior  Kaga-san is difficult,
so I'm going to update the short-term spring airport 6 and Ross-san, because
someone might come by.
Please update.  It's a
good time to bake it. It's
from me. It's from me.
Yes, Suzuki, and well, the
only person who can't stop paying for one book is San Kishu Zu 2, it's the state's birthday. There are also people who sent it individually.  It was
Zhu Shan.
Oh, oh, congratulations
again.
It's just the carbonated carbonate that
disappeared. The clever bread is the master who is the master. Gu Yamabata will never erase Yume Santan.
Good luck and bad luck, 3rd tier family, Shun
a  Kayako-san, Danke-
shun's cool, Aisu-chan, Takenyo, and Ai-san, who are so bad at pizza, I guess.Yuta-san is the
only one who wants to play mo 3. But
when is Shifu-san, Tankishu, especially the chicken residue makeup,
fluffy?  Landlady-san station new contact two-sansan incarnation
tail still Anko-san Danke car
Our car Cheek sheep only support a 8 ah
Darja, I can't breathe, hehehe,
stuttering, Takuhide Kagoyama, come on Ramen Man 3, take it.
Street C Yu
Thank you very much for your support. I will continue to do my best.
Nyankoromochi-san, make-up, chatboy-san, how many models did you steal? Santan family, Shun, potato, three
big decisive battles. It's an
adventure. The rabbit is losing a series of battles. Yupopo Tsuki is being raped.
Danke Employee
Japanese. It's a way to meditate with Hanshin. Good luck.  I
wanted to study English after watching Please Horo Ianu. Everyone says so.
Mr. Alvin has 3 types of coffee, 3 turns, 3 turns, and Mr. Yamagami River.
And 3-dan Ieshun
Origami 3 laps Edo Daisan Kishu Mechaka Power generation
3-dan Ieshun Japanese distribution a
Even if I don't care, Lotte is the one who is studying English, so I am learning English there too.I
think it is difficult to speak politely, but the
people involved in the distribution are
3rd generation hereditary Meisen, and
only 10 days off a week.
[Music] Single
item uk Danke Shane Hatsuka Arigatou Nubai Mitan Iya
Shun
Nef Cry 3 Dan Ie Week Returned to Birth Major 6 Thank You
Nihongi I can read it.
Ami Mami Japan has been abolished What happened? From now on, I'm going to be able to act freely and be myself as a key person. Please
wait for a year.
Tojun
Scene Thanks to Sakemi-san, I can
move energetically in my own way. I'm
really grateful. Thank you! Festival Battle  Thanks
to Sesame Tofu's landlord Shuntai and Sansan Sanke Haruki Ah-chan's move, it gave me an
opportunity to continue watching Horo Comfort, and it motivates me to study English.
Please take on the challenge of what you want to do. Thank you, Danke.  I
'm so happy. That's my purpose.
I brought the Japanese person
here so that everyone could see that horse that was ranked 5th place.  Thank you everyone for watching the upcoming implementation date.  I
wonder what it feels like to be like Sebashi,
looking at the sunset with warm feet I want to
be like this If
you love me so much,
there's something I love about you
Erika-san's Spring Respite
A Singularity-san Short Season
Leatherlight 3-Dan House Collection
Kushozan  Only Jen,
Rep. Nonta is here for the Passion Act, Killer-chan, I'm
rooting for you one step too far, so do your best, Grameenphone will be abolished, and thank you to that person.
Mr. Booley Ann-chan, Mr. Yamayoshi Toshi, I'm going to do a surprise attack on the 3rd stage when I dig it up.It's a 3rd model.If you
mix it with the professional ship, the 3rd stage standard tree is only Eru-san.
I think it's the roots of Mobis that can be enjoyed to the fullest with the burgers that can be clearly separated from the nutrition store in the Japanese-speaking world.
3 models
a
I want to read
ah,
what should I say?
Yeah, yeah,
just this one is fine.
9 Kazuya-san, Naginagi-san, Ka-shun, there's
no longer a 3-key car, ah, let go of the
blue one, throw away the handshake touch.  I'll get it, so I'll
erase the flames, Aoi Tachibana, Takashi
Hayato, is that okay? This is Aoi-san, and only the aberration and the main character
follow Kiyo-san's danke season  I
want to understand the truth of the universe, but I want to understand the truth of the universe, but in commemoration of the spawning season anniversary, I support the 3-dan family.Please
call my name.I chose it.Today's abolishment in the week of the three major families was really fun.  I want a
separate version that includes paintings, money, tomorrow's cocosis, Mike's lines, etc. I'm sure Ayu-chan has told me a lot of things.
Once 3rd Kesha Unu Pudding 3rd standard 4th time 3rd Kishu Choi John's Enan 3rd Dan
Keishun 23 Dan Keshen is a sleeper, Mr. Price is a mess, he
has a really big face, he's really cool By the way, it's
only Denken Shanghai Prefecture is Jisan Lottery Pearl  Bread is easy. It's like a book.
3 minutes in, Stars Sky Poipu 4. If you turn it into a private property right away, you can become a super immigrant.
There's a battle bar jump. Enjoy.  It's easy to get a door hatch cabaret flying in the air and
mix it up.Theo who suits me is an
office worker.There's a
buzz, but there's a little water.Imimi p, come on, Friday, Saturday, and Saturday.  I'm
looking for a
good Tachibana production.I don't
know if it's okay or not.Thank
you for the fun half-body before going to rescue work.  I'm
full of hope and motivation. I don't think I'll be able to see you next time because I'm working on a junk job. But I'll be
back again.
Andy
Ato is a hard-working sensor.
Pekoland is an exclusive sheet metal worker.
Pinter, an employee of the landlord, is helpful. He's a new face in March.  Thank you for the first time Spa Chao Can-chan
Thank you for Doctor Powder I have to buy it again and open it again Oh
yeah, this is that update again I was listening
to the sound and was playing it.  I
think this is the last one.Customers
here
A 4th place Peso-san danke A lively character with perfect service I want to support you more and
more Thank you
Touko Risu It's hard to entertain the power even after 2 minutes  If I have to think that way, I'm sure I
can do it.I'll do my best and walk.Hmm, I've
been thinking a lot about that, but from now on, I
think I'll go about it this way.Thank you very much.
Ram's steal Tsuda Eh
Tanya Shun le Then steal 2 I wonder
if there's a half-delicious ramen Harukana
After all, it's more delicious if you eat it for 2000 yen
Thank you for bringing it to me I
want to eat ramen
39 Sena Ah My
dad is kind
Photo: I'm
fine with this daddy, I
'm just kind,
a  I love Cure-chan's bright smile and movement.I
know she's worried about some difficult things, but I want
Cure-chan to be able to carry out her Oni Day activities as she pleases.  I
'm writing a book.I'm also a fellow fraudster, so I
can't help but look forward
to the ban being lifted.I'm
worried about whether or not I'll be able to go to a conversation cafe once the ban is lifted.  Shall we
go from there?
But I don't want him to
do this, so I
thought it would be better to wait for him to invite me, but it's
difficult,
but my senior doesn't often invite me to collaborate with him transitive
But I don't want him to force me to collaborate with him.  Yes, my
seniors won't give up on me.
[Laughs] Do
n't worry about it a bit.
danke Peripheral pricing Southern Kishu supporting gold 3rd singer who loves the Japanese language and rides the class
Thank you very much
Fashion show A band Curve owner ran Chapsal ah
1 IPO Toyama Kinji day
danke Is this the last of Shu Phoenix Rakushun
?  I wonder
if it's okay. I'm a
bit huuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
today was everyone today was the surprise of the eastern army 1 kikoden king general election ti 1 Josenow young  The
star is correct, and the submerged statistics are also
there.Thank you very much everyone, except for the pig who anchored, the steam meeting will be gathered tomorrow.
bar Cebu Good Big Sam Carry Menu Front Fund Purse Book EP There's no
filming location to buy Wish-san Tarkin sheet music shorts
n Spent and tee Tomorrow we'll have karaoke
at the farmhouse  I
think the big announcement is on the horizon, but I
have an announcement to make.
Everyone is waiting for you.
But I wonder if there's anyone who remembers
[Music]
n o
Ao Fielder dee
Inua
[Music]
c Yotsubanyaan There
's someone who remembers Oh well
r 4 meu  Riser Member Windage Otsu Zapa Grass Powder Zoom web
e 280 Biter Cody Successful Guitar Amazing Hori Mizu I
told everyone whether I typed it myself or copied and pasted it and shot it.Everyone wrote it very well.You're very
good at German.On youtube  It's right away
can you do Life Tuber House YouTuber Burn
Ah Order Complete
[Music]
Oh
by aaah
me
Thank you for your hard work
[Music]
N
ni
Oh tan  The
person who just started up the time is the one who said that.
My Poupeko's Speed ​​6 is
safe. I
had it for
4 days.
ND That's it. I had it
made for me. This is what I was doing.
By the way, there are some people who were able to play the game on this screen, too. They
made it that way,
and they were like, ``I'm coming,''
but I've
seen a few of them.  I
tweeted it, but I
got
it.
[Music]
Walker, let's mix it up and get it right.
ni
me It's
not a station building. d 3
[Music]
One
bl
me