[Applause]
[Music]
T
[
Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music]
De
[Music] A [Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
DET
[Music]
A
Chaos Chaos
Hello, everyone. I
mean, I don't know how many people are there right now,
but I can't tell from above, but hello to everyone. It's
begun, and it's
been a long time since I've been in the middle of a
long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.
Since it's the eve of the festival, I'm going to eat it today.
[Music] There
's a huge number of people, so we
decided to enjoy all the vegetables together. We
all decided to play together and practice a little.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank
you. I say hello. I say
hello to everyone one by one.
No, it's okay. Isn't it
okay? Is it okay to have a dog today?
Okay, let's move on. There are a lot of people today,
so those who are participating today
are these people. If you press the tab key, you can
see who is participating, which is
really amazing.
1234 How many people are
this?
11123114?  14+14
means 2087 people. That's amazing.
It's Meni Meni Pi Meni Meni Pipo. Yes, that's
why today we're talking about that new implementation.  I
'm thinking of playing with everyone for the first time, Holmen, hunting, playing with the 27 of us, and playing around with various hooks and hooks.Here, let's do a little bit.Today,
listeners are still asleep in their sleep.  I've
never seen this before. I'm thinking of
starting with hunting a little bit,
but let's
do it. Let's do it. Well, this is the best.
Sorry for the slow completion.  I
feel like it was, but no,
no, yes, then. Now, let's go to the place.
Now, please follow Jamiko-chan. Today, I'm the teacher. Sui-chan is here. Cat, I
'm here. Stop hitting me,
stop fighting. Hey, everyone, look at this Subaru.  You know what I'm
saying? We should all get
along, right?
[Laughs]
These are Subarzos. These are
not the Barzos we made.
What are you talking about?  You
can't do that, Susu
said she
has two nipples, so I can't help it, Mio-san. This is the
most unpleasant way to use Sumaru. I can press it properly. I can
press it properly. I can press it properly.
What are you making me do? I'm
embarrassed to say that I'm being pushed. I'm being pushed. I'm not being pushed.
Erase it. Erase it. It's
okay. I could erase it at any time, but Su-
chan left it for me.  If something
were to affect the system, what would we do
? We couldn't erase it. It was incorporated into the system.
Hey, something happened. Yes, what are you doing
? Miko-san, why don't you bring out the button? Well,
everyone. This time, it's the red team.
Okay, let's have a look at the red team once again. I think we've
got a good balance of everyone, but I think they're too excited,
or there's too little yellow, or there's too little red.
Well, I don't think I've seen it at all, so I'm like, ok, then there's the red-haired one. There's someone who's going to be hunting. Yes, it's going to be there. Yes, it's going to be here. It's not that one, it's this one. I forgot to say that, but by the way, everyone is already here.  I do
n't know if anyone got it, but there
is a book on the morning stand,
and please go back to where you were earlier and
get it.Here it is, everyone.
This is it. Please head over there and head towards the school. This is it. I
have created a rulebook, so I'm
sorry that the en version is not ready yet,
but I hope that the JP members will support you.
Yes, yes, here.  Well, the
Holme hunting rules
are such that each team selects 6 people.Yes,
3 people, 3 people, and now 6 people.Okay,
then the red team will be the first to be selected, so the hunters will be selected.  I think I'll
decide on 6 people and get them together.
Ah, yes, what about voice chat? I'm
thinking, let's just leave voice chat as it is. Let's split it up into red, white, and yellow. I'm sure it'll
be crowded. So, the red group
will stay as it is.  Yes, yellow and white go to the designated place
and understand.
That's right. Yes, please.
Okay, let's stop. I
wonder how many people are in the O-red group now.
1234567 Asoma-san is here.
Wait a minute. There are too many servers right now. I'm
losing track of where 6 times the servers are. I'm sorry, I
'm moving.
Thank you very much.  I'll do
my best, please. I'll
do my best.
There are only 6 of us now, including Ekoe Zeta.
1234567 That's 8 people, right?
8 or 8 or 9 people in total. Hello
men hunting. Yes, yes, it's me. Kade will appear. Kade and Niseo
. Ah, blue and gold. Oh, then Miko
should join in too.  Okay, Miko too, I want to
try it out, so I'm participating.Okay,
okay, let's go.I
might explain that,
so I'm just going to participate.
If there's just one more person, Kali, Biji, or Fuwamoko,
someone can join in. Ah, what's this, rice hunting
? Ah, I see. There's no one left. I
thought of the crab's voice. Help me.
Calliope.
Here's the
entry sign.The first three players are there.Is there
already a yellow player?Is it
okay to have three players?It might be okay to have three players each.  I'll
do it once, so I'll ask you to watch it.
Oh, I see. I
don't think there's any hunting going on. I see. The
yellow team that can't enter has already
entered through hunting. That's
what I mean. Ah, that's what I mean.  I'm going to
go to gold, please wait a moment.
This is the first game that yellow will play. Ah, I'm sorry. I
did yellow, but it's okay. It's okay. There's no
order at all. First of all, yellow to yellow.
I'm sorry, but I'm
sorry, I'm going to start with ``Hunter''.Okay, I think 6 people have entered yellow, so 3 people are yellow.This is the 31st time, so 3 is fine.Okay, so 3 people have entered.Where does it start from hunter?  I
just came to ask about that yellow one.Since you have
entered it, I think I'll make it yellow, yellow,
red and white.Okay then,
O.Yes, sir.Yes, that's the fugitive.Everyone will
put it in the fugitive category, so it's a little bit.  Aus
Yes, yellow, please wait for a moment.
Yes, yes, yellow member. Please
wait in the audience seats. Yes, then,
all the fugitives of the white team. Yes, this purple one, the
fugitive.
]
Cook, okay, please wait for a moment.
I'm not doing anything. I'm not doing anything. Everyone,
touch me.
Sorry, that's the order. From yellow to yellow.
Now that the order is yellow, red, white, red team,
please touch the signboard of this fugitive.Yes,
thank you very much.
And that's what I did, I
can do it, but I've never done it before. I've never done it before. I
can click on the fusitive light. I can
click on it. I can click on it. I can click on it. I can click on it. I can click on
it.
Sorry for the inconvenience, I see. I was
clicking and watching Wasp, and Zoro and I were falling in love with each other,
so I'm remembering a little bit. I'm
confused about what it means. I'm confused. Zoro and Zoro
look alike. Oh, that's what it is.  Okay,
then,
um, oh, that's a great sound. Okay, then let
's start. Okay, you can run away from this. Right, you can
run away. You can run away.
La, the three people in yellow are running away.The people in the red team are
in danger, run away, run
away, run away, run away, run away, run away, run away,
run away, run away, help me, demon.I do
n't know who the demon is, but I'm sure it's a demon.Yellow  The
team is a demon, the yellow team, the yellow
team is a demon, so it was easy because I'm the yellow one. What's wrong? I'm sorry for
catching you. I'm
so confused. I'm slow. I'm slow.  I
see,
run away for a moment, run away, oh okay,
let's go, haha, do your best and play chess.The theme has become a white stop, right
?The person in the white group.The person in the white group.The person in white.Now the person in white has
become a hunter.There is still more to that written at the top.  I can't believe
they're still running away. The
white
team is running away, isn't it? It's impossible to get caught. Yes, I
have a tete team. I'm a
member, so please eat,
Polka Senpai. Ah, I've been ignored, Polka Senpai.  You
can't catch it, no matter how much you do that to get in the way.Get in
the way.It's definitely a nuisance.Good,
good, catch it.Perhaps that's
not it.  There's
nothing wrong with that, so you shouldn't get in the way. Ah, yeah. Ah, yeah.
If you get in the way, the yellow team will get points,
so you're right, so now you have no choice but to
support the people on your own team. I
see, the people on the yellow team.  become
For now, I'll just have to get caught by yellow. That's it. Yellow doesn't have yellow in it. Ah, it's definitely the end. What do you mean? Sorry, what do you mean? Right now, yellow is the topic for today.  The
topic is tentative
[Music]
Yes. Wow, it's going to be like this.The venue on the day is,
for example, how tall are the people over,
how old are the people who made their debut, etc.It's
pretty difficult, isn't it?  Difficult  There
are also some simple and difficult ones.It's a little bit like "Unshi" and "Kuwa".It's
true that I got it from the 6 people's
DMs.For now, I've
summarized only the cats,
so Mito.
Okay, so I'm
going to read a little bit. I'm going to read a little bit. I'm going
to read the other beauty and the bottom of the page.
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Yes, please
take advantage of that person.Since
this is a tentative title, there are some people who call people from the yellow group and
try to catch people from their own group,
but I don't care.  On the day of the show, there
will be questions about people who are taller than Hamana, Holomen who debuted in 2000, something a little simpler, and people who are Holomen in their entirety.
Thank you for your enjoyment. This might be strong. Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry, but that topic is a bit tentative. So
for now, I don't have my own yellow team,
but I can do something about it.  Let's
say that there will be a review of how many centimeters it will be tomorrow, or a
review of Yui 2000 and what year,
etc. Yes, that's true, I've learned a lot,
but I guess I picked the wrong person.
If I catch the wrong person and touch the signboard,
I won't be able to get into the car.  Is it
okay to lie and say it's not true?
Well, I can't lie. The
data about my debut in 2000 is
still there.  Well,
maybe the voice chat isn't connected,
right? I'm no
match for that. Good
evening. Well then, it's about time to
start. Yes, that's it. I think I'll get started.
Yes, please. I made a mistake and ended up being a fugitive. I
clicked.  But this time, it's
okay to be brief,
so you don't have to worry about everything.If
you're worried about that, then that one.
Click again and touch the sign again to fix it. It
'll start even if you touch the sign again. Yes,
okay, let's go from here. We'll
catch it. We'll have to go. Let's
go. Right click.
[Laughs] Let's
catch the red.  I'll
try to practice catching them,
and if I try to narrow it down to yellow or white right now,
if I put the wrong person in there, the
hunt will fail.
Is the score there
going to decrease? No, it won't go down, it
won't go
down, it won't go down.
Catch the people from the white group.The people from the white and white group are the people from the white and white group.The people from the white and white group are
Kia-senpai.White, white, white, I
know you climbed the bumpy stairs.He
's here, rain, and rain.Ra is here.Ra is here.Did you find rain?
[Music]
Yes, where are you? Do your best, do your best, 15 seconds. You're
running away. You're running away. Where
are you? You're in that place.
Da cooperation. No, no, no. If you're okay, do your best.  It's
yellow, it's
on top, it's on top, it's on top, it's
falling, it's definitely falling, I'll pick up the people who are falling, it
's falling, wait, wait, it's yellow, wait, it's yellow, it's all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all
right.
Eh,
it's so far away that I'm trying to push my way, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, I want to, it's nice, it's a nice fight, it's a game like this, I might not be good at running.  That's difficult.Next,
we have an infected person and a non-infected
escapee.He's also jumping, but
maybe he's just slow.Yeah, he's also pushing when he runs.Yes
, he's pushing.  Is this
the control? Yes, this is running.
Which one is this? Where is this? Which one
is at the entrance? Try running. It's running right now. It's running. It's
running. It's
okay. Oh, are you okay? Yes, press and hold jump to speed up. So, yeah,
that's okay. Long press.  It's okay, it's
okay, so I learned a lesson by pressing and holding it. I
can do it, thank you. Next time, I
'll catch everyone. It was fun, everyone.
[ __ ] Mia Fujitive.  It's
going to be a board fugitive Fugitive I
touch the board and now I'm always
fast I'm also popular and I'm pushing the ribs
Okay, I made it to the ribs
Oko-chan
Kihanta is fun The one below I
haven't said anything yet.  I'm looking forward to seeing what the topic will be. I
think it's going to be quite difficult to find someone to help, but I think we'll
need some cooperation. I
'd like to narrow it down to one person, like 3 people can use this person.
Oh yeah, that's right,
does that mean we have to decide on this person?
Well, let's start.
Yes, I'm really fast right now. I'm really fast right now. Looks like it's
okay. It's important to hide.
First, it's the red group. Oh, no, no, no, no.  No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.  I
don't know if it's possible, but it
does look like white.I feel like it's not white because white is going to go and catch it.The red team is also at a loss.Can't we
help now?I
want to
help.Help me, I want to help you.Help me,
help me.  Help me,
yellow, please. I wonder if I can help.
Help, help, help the yellow people. The number of yellow people is
increasing, and the good news is that I'm getting caught
.
Yeah, in the end, the yellow one was more successful. No, it's true. Yeah, it's true. It's true. It's
true. It's
true. I'm being caught. I don't think it's okay. If I feel like it, I should be able to escape.
Next time, I think it's definitely not possible.
Wow, you got a 6, you're so good, you're terrible. I
don't understand it, so I don't understand the title below either. It's true that
this time we lost because of the speed of our feet, but we won with our brains.
That's right, with our brains, we secured the red-red team. We
had 3 people.
But no, no, but it's still this, it's that, it's
got brains and high claws, but it's hidden.
That's right, if you dare to get serious now, you'll be found out. It's true that you do
n't want to alarm someone who is strong,
right? It's like you didn't catch them.  It
's painful, it's painful, I'm
going to call Mio-chan for a second.Okay, okay,
let's do our best.
Chansou Nan Mio-chan This is the middle part of the game You can
ask me to do it Miko I can't do it right now It's okay.  That's what I'm
thinking, so please come to channel 4.
Ah, hi, 4 is here. No, it's no, it's channel 2.
[Music]
Sorry, please come to channel 2.  Can I
have it
? Yes, yes, please. There are
so many. How do I kill him? How do I kill him? When I tell my friends, it's really
reassuring. Thank you for keeping me waiting. Is there any help on the second floor?
So, this time, the
topic is the same.  Even so, in the actual performance, it
feels like we're going to go through this one more time,
but tomorrow the topic will be completely different,
so we'll think about it a little bit, and the three of us will
work together a little to catch one person.
Please try to do it with teamwork.
Yes, yes, after that, look at the current balance.
Please be aware that there is a possibility that that tall building may be cut down a little. I see. It's
really hard. Mon-
a is terrible, anti.  It's gone, it's gone,
there's no anti, so I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
'm going to move to the next Kiba Line, Seoke Kisekimase, everyone.  Let's make
it warp, okay? Let's go up
and float up. Wow, magic,
magic. Okay, let's do this for now, everyone.
Okay, those who have a partner are probably going to want to practice with that partner. Yeah, that's true. So, if
you have a partner, that's actually it
. Listener.  It seems like you've already
decided on your partner, right? Yes, it's been
decided, so each team has to decide.  I
want you to do that, so if you're a fan and you're a
fan, please stand up on that sign.Yes,
only those who are older than you, who aren't fangs, made a mistake.If you make a mistake, if you make a mistake,
just one click.  Let's put it together,
please separate it into red, white, and yellow for once.
[Music]
Please 4 White
4 He's
not there Hey, he's not
here either Let's put it together Where is that? No,
wait a second, that's the operator who got off.
Well, I haven't decided who will be at the top and who will be
at the bottom, especially since I'll be at the bottom. Of course I'm
going to be the one at the bottom, but it's a big deal, but it's an aura.
Thank you very much, Miko-senpai.  I'm going
to write a book, Kasua Aristo, knead it a little, start, press the button, and the start sign is fine.Yes, thank you very much.
Right now, Kaka is out as a general. This is it. Right now, the
person below is under that, under
that position,
yes under position, that F. It's better to press F5. If you press F5, you can
see everything, so you can protect and win.
Yes, yes Yes, why is this the
need for that boosting person? It's okay,
so it's okay.
It would be better to focus on it. Maybe we should all move together, holding it, etc. The brain seems to be good. For example, the chocolate line and the leader are approaching like this, and everyone should do it like this. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.  I don't know if it's fine.The
strategy is to take one person at a time and stay close to the general, then run away.Suma-chan.You
can run away by yourself, or you
can fight together.It's the same.  I'm
going to give a quick message to Ochosu-chan.
[Applause]
[Music] I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry. I'll
press Rukore. Please, please. Can you please explain to me next
? Let's explain the rules.  Well, I can't see it right now,
so please explain it
to me. I'll go and do this. Well,
how many times have I defeated the enemy in this few seconds?
Excuse me, Jami-chan, to each of those teams.  I
can't look at the rulebook right now, so
could you please give me a quick explanation? Understood.
Yes, I have a spreadsheet posted at each team that summarizes the rules,
so if you could take a look at it, it
's the same content as the rulebook.  I'll explain it
to you.Yes, yes, I'm
sorry to have kept you waiting.Hey, Red Team.Red Team.No rule.Are you okay?Red Team.Ah, wait, I
had that translated for you.What
should we do?Wait a minute, what should we do?It's
okay for the good guys to fight.  Hey, filing
O-chan will lead me and I will
start, so it's okay. I'll
kill you, I'll kill you. You're as light as a feather. By the
way, it's that general Calliope, so I'm Mamoru Leader.
We have to protect the point.We
can focus on the same person while protecting the point general.For example,
Toa.Then that person who came is a little far away and I
can't see it, but say Iris.  Let's
all hit the one on Iris
. We'll make sure to beat
him up. We'll move around him like this with Style O.
When I say let's move, we'll all
move like this. It's good for me, a strong OK. Now,
let's move as a group.  Neung group
Oh,
so I can feel that even if I respawn, I'll do it there. It's
true, teamwork Teamwork, I'll
do it to you until I push myself.  It's
better to do it right.
Hey, what about the 5 yellow teams?
Hey, it would be cool if we could kill this. I'm sure.
What should I do? I'll definitely kill this. I'll definitely
kill this. Who was there just now?  I'm
so far away. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  It
's good, it's a good jump, it's a
good jump, it's a
good jump, it's a good jump, it's very protective, Mamoru, Mamoru Oh, that's a
shame, that
's the kill leader.Yes, yes, this is the one that came out just now.It's
not Chiara, it
's Chiara.Watson got 8 kills.  I
think it's not bad that Ka and Ka's team won too, but it
's not bad. It's not bad, but it's a little more beat up.  I
really want to beat him up a little bit more.
Even if I beat him up a little more, I
got 3 kills from Senpai. It's
because Senpai was so
good at it. I'm sorry to see that now,
but it's just a little bit,
Mikoji.  I wonder if I should use him as a starting role.Okay, okay,
let's look at someone else, but then I'll just gather everyone together for now.The
other person can't come in.Ah, he can't come in.
Okay, then our team 3
will be the only team, or something like that,
or maybe that's it, then maybe that Suma-chan
should come in. I'm sure that's it, or
something like that. I'll do it in a mix.  The management didn't say
that it would be okay if the person on the line touched it,
but right now, out of the number of people,
one person is grilling it, and the yellow person is probably grilling one person.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, but I'm going to support you today,
so I'm going to support you today, so even if the red team comes, you can change it,
yes, please, yes, please, well, I'm
going to do it on another day.  If you want to be a lower level
or a higher level, you can ask me to do it at all.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, then once you
decide, okay, one more time.  I'll do it. I wonder
if I'll do it again. I haven't done it yet and I want to try it again. I think I'll start. Let's break
up again, please.  Subaru, I
understand that you did it with me. It's okay,
it's okay, it's floating all the time
, it's
always on top, but it's on top.
Subaru-chan will be on top.
Yes, thank you very much. I understand.  I'll
protect
you, definitely jump, Mamoru-senpai, I'll do it. Thank you,
Masu-chan, yes,
gore, oh, Kiara. It
was an operation, but Kiara, please kill me. Please, really,
senpai. It's not easy, no, no, it's not true, it
was heavy.  My
senpai was also as light as a feather.He was
as light as a feather.He was like gold.He's a
mess.He
's just like my stinky girlfriend.
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, the
injuries were terrible, that's what I meant, right? But no, that's not what I meant. That's not the case today. That's why I came to get Kari's Ne Kill Power. I'll
give it to you, Kari. Please be
kind. Go ahead.
[Music] Let's go, let's go, let's do our best Let's go ahead and do our best Let's get in the way of everyone's channel Let's protect everyone Hello everyone It's a group of people It's a little yellow [Music]
Nikkeru
[Music] I
might die, I might die. I'm in danger of defeating someone. They're
coming from behind. They
're aiming for me. On the contrary, it's nice, nice, nice, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's the
enemy team, the enemy team, the yellow team.
Maybe it's the enemy team.  Hit us, hit us! We're
getting screwed.
Yellow is so brutal.
I don't know what's wrong with that guy. Let's
hang in there.
[Applause]
[Music] It's
a bit
amazing.
[Music]
Ekaowa, you were really strong. It's
great that you ran away with Wako-chan. So nice.
Nice. But the enemy is a little complicated.
Come on,
everyone, please gather at number 02.
Everyone, please gather at number 02. Are you
going to have that career senior take care of things
now? The actual show is near.  We can fill it
up with a lot of things we can do to get away with it.
[Music]
That's
interesting. We'll do it again after this. If you
want to practice with different teams, we'll
practice with you whenever you want.  I'm
sorry to hear that people can do that kind of start, but that cavalry person
can press the start button, so it's not at all true.
Even if we were on different teams practicing after this, I
'd appreciate it if you could do it.  I
think I have a pretty good idea of how to do it.I just
have one question.What?I had no idea
how many times that general would kill, or whether there would be
any benefit if I killed him.
If you do that, you'll get 1 point.
This
doesn't matter in the team points you mentioned earlier, but the number of dead generals will
be added to the final total.  It's the
same as the winning points for a match.It
's a bonus point that is
added regardless of the points from the previous match.I see, the points are tallied at the final stage,
right?The person in first place gets 15 points2.  The team in 3rd place gets
10 points, and the team in 3rd place
gets 5 points.That's right, that's what's
added to that, so I understand that power.That's right,
even if you get that kill from earlier, it will
be added to that place.  He says he's not there.  The
feeling is the same as everyone else, but I see.
For example, if the team in 3rd place kills the general
5 times, they
will get 10 points.  It's
interesting, but no, this is a little
too close to turning into a rhinoceros, so
if you have the time left, you can aim at the target.I
thought that's a good idea, but I can't aim at it.Oh
yeah, that's right, so be careful General.
Please, yes, I understand. So what do we
do next? The next step is to check once with the princess, right? Is
n't that the
voice of Deba Deba? Let's go.
[Music] Are you
saying that?  It's
amazing. There are a lot of bugs.
Everyone got hit. It's
hard to go outside. Ok.
Alright, let's split up into teams.  I
still have the fire line equipment,
but I don't know what to do, but it's been discontinued,
so I thought it was okay,
but I just left it behind.  That's
fine, then, split up into teams.
That Calliope isn't doing this event,
but what should I do? Just
look at it, and I think you can watch it from here.
too
Okay, that's actually Shion-chan,
but since she's not here today, I guess Shion-chan, Gold Hand,
Blue, and Door will be fine. Yes, yes, yes. I
learned a
new recipe. Well, let's take a look. I might
want to take a look at it.
Can I do it instead? Yes,
yes, it's okay. There's
something I want to check. Yes, I'm sorry. No, it's
okay, please. Is
this game different? Yes, I'm going to become a princess.
Well, even if you're not a princess, you'll
get lag even if you're a knight.Let's
try it today.If it gets lag, then
think about it for a while.I wonder
if that's the case.  That's
right, yeah, I can't believe it. When so many enemies
appear, yesterday
was the only time I've ever been lucky.
Ah, I was fighting an enemy from the past.
Thank you for being so cute.
Hey, you're all so cute, you're such a cute princess. You're so
cute. You can get married
. What should I do? There's
going to be a lot of husbands, so who will they be?
Well, I guess I can't be a candidate either. Sorry, that's impossible.
So why, why are you so cute,
Princess Towa?  It
's the Princess Store. Okay, yellow is
ok
. Yes, it looks naked. Princess, let's start.
Yes, yes, yes, there are a few things that have changed.  I do
n't know if it's true, okay, let's
go, let's go, do your best, do your best, do
your best, do your best, pink, red, pink, white, yes, red, yes,
pink.  Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, it
's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
not chill, it's not chill, it's chill, I'm sorry,
pink, yes, red, yellow, white, pink, white, pink, red, white, red and white.
Okay, okay, chill, chill, chill, chill, chill, red, white, pink.  The
knight
says, ``Don't talk, please, go ahead.''
[Music]
Hmm, you can't talk at all. That's
right. Yes, please. Yes, you
got it right. Next time, please. Yes, it
's paprika.
Yes, it looks like paprika orange.
[Music]
Oh, this is dangerous. No, what was that
?
[Music]
Oh, wait, I get it, wait a minute,
this is it, yes, it's nice, it's
here, it's here.  Awesome.
Well, grilled mutton and elite pancakes.
I see. Elite
pancakes. I had the mutton refined on the stove.
Yes, the elite pancakes were made on a chopping board.  I'm going to make some wheat
sweet berries, so I'm going to
make some elite pancakes. Please
make some wheat. I've
made some flour. I'm going to make some sweet berries. I'm going to cut the sweet berries, and then I'm going to bake them on a griddle with flour and eggs.
Now I'm going to bake them
on the serving table.  I cut the pancakes and
served them with sweet berries. Blue is excellent
. Wait a minute, isn't blue too good?
As expected, I'm good at it. I looked at pancakes. It
looks like pancakes. I'll try this tomorrow.  I was
thinking, but this, this, this, this is
amazing, this is so cute, this is really cute, this is so nice, let's
go, there's one for each of them, it's amazing, oh no, upper
left orange, lower left pink, upper right yellow,
lower right I want you to tell me orange pink
orange upper left  It's orange on the upper left, pink on
the lower left. Yellow on the upper right. It's pink. It's pink.
Isn't it too early? It's
not too early now. I went from the left and started from the left.
Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, beat me up,
kill me, kill me, kill me,
push me to the limit, where is the last one, the last
one?
Naa, the potato man is out. Potato man, do your best, Maga.
If your physical strength is low, come back. Hey, do your best,
do your best.  Who's the pig that you're aiming for? Pig Now,
the pig is
going, the pig at the trot
might be strong, so I'll go last. Yes,
this is the only one going to the left. Ah, this is it.
Write something like that again. I wonder
if you're aiming really hard. You're aiming for the same person you're aiming for.
It's cool that you're coming in.
That's fine. You
might not have revived. Do your best, do your
best. It's okay, ah,
just a little.  Ku's cooking was too good.
As expected,
everyone was strong. I do
n't think I could use the arrows that I didn't hit. I can't use the arrows by pressing and holding them.
Hmm, I see. This is the worst case scenario. I guess it's
like having to pinch-hit for someone else. I'll
have to take that into consideration, too. I
see. I
see. The poor Internet of money. That's so
fluffy.  It's not bad if it's only once, but
I have about 2 practice sessions and 2 practice sessions.But the ones that
come out are 2, oh, and the ones that
come out are individual, race, and um, Kiba line.
Well, that's right. Maybe it's better if the person doesn't get two.
No, it's not because one sticks out. Yeah, that's true. Then, I
guess it's best to ask Fuwamoko-chan.
Japanese: I've been doing this for quite a while now.
Yes, I'm weak, I'm weak,
please, okay. Thank you very much. Please take care of me. I'll do my best. I'll
do my best. Every team is the same. Yeah,
yeah,
yes. Yes, I'll make you feel good. I'll do a
lot of work, and I'll do it. Thank you.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
Please, where is that cat now?
[Music] The girl's
eye riff was so determined that she was in a good mood, which is why
she was called the Heat Princess.Every princess
thinks about that new cooking menu.
However, did you see Subaru's Subaru's
fried chicken and fried chicken?I was surprised.There was a
hamburger steak, an
ennie, and pancakes.Yes, it's
nice.I want to eat this.I want to eat this.
No, I'm sorry.
I was a little surprised. I was like, Okay, so I'll leave it like this for now. I'm
fine with asking them to do it, but the follow-up stuff is super busy right now.
Oh, I want to take a
look. There was someone I wanted to see. I want to see. I want to see. I don't want to look at it. I'm sorry. Someone's wobbly. Just ah-chan. That's really cool. It's so nice. Let's go. Let's go.
What's wrong, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, you
suddenly asked me to see what I was thinking, so I thought it was
something, but then I realized it was someone else.
That was me, I'm sorry,
but I want to
do the follow-up practice, and the relay, too.  Is
n't that okay? Well then, I
guess this is possible now with unlimited numbers of people.
Maybe I don't know, but you can
try it for a moment. There are already red players. Oh, I
can't do it now.
If we can't do it today, there will be three of us. Yes, there will be three of us. Let's
go now. Well, Chiara and Su-chan. This will be the same for the actual performance. Maybe, but just for a moment, everyone, please take a look. Yes, we'll do our best.
Yojashin-chan and Chiara.  Do you want to
go to that other server for business? I
think it's okay to split up into groups. I
feel like it's going to be a mess if we cheer, right? Let's
open a group and have members play for that game.
If you're a member of the team that's going to play, I'd like you to move me to number 6, number 1,
or number 1.I ca
n't hear everyone's cheers, but I
want to play while listening to what I want to do.So,
Chim, each team is
scared.  Um,
[music] I'm
going,
oh, do your best, do your best, please do your best. The infected
people are banging on the infection sign. Where are they?
This happened. It's true.
Awesome. Specter touch. Ahh. So many decapitated heads.  It
's flying, yeah, it's true, wow,
where is this? It's the same feeling,
wow, it's on top.
[Music]
Yeah, it's not like someone
pushed me. Or maybe something is wrong with me
. I
don't know yet. Good luck, good luck.
There's no training here.
It's a spa.
Complete o I'll do it another time Yes, do your best Fatoh How are you
doing now
But no, it's cool See this entry Twaa this
Everyone please use the signboard tag
Yes
o [
Music] Oh, I'm about
to read it, Good luck Po
Good luck
[Music]
Other people  I
want to eat
hamburger hamburger is
good.Hamba-senpai is also good.Is it
okay?Yes, it's okay.Yes, yes, it may be okay.Yes, it's okay.Okay,
okay.Do your
best.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.
That's right, it's serious
[Music]
It's good, it's good, it's good, it
's good, it's steady Namada will lose, it's good, it's
good, Sui-chan is coming It's so close It's so
close
Nini, they're lined up Nice, that's
amazing  Mineko went there too.
Hey, Wow, Kia has fallen. Okay, okay. Calm
down.
Calm down. Wait. Wait. Wait.  It
's a good fight Aaoi, it's
beautiful It's too good to be true It's too
good, it's okay, it's okay I
have a bed, so it's okay
[Music]
Ii-chan is approaching
Sui-chan is approaching Baba-baiba,
Yosui-chan  Bye bye Su-chan Bye bye There
's also a pet. It's true that there's a pink beet here. No, it's just a matter of
reaching the goal in the remaining time,
so it's certainly not about speed.
So, ok, wow, it's really fast.
The switch is going there, do your best, do your
best. Moe. Even the color is that book. I do
n't know how to calm down. The
stage is completed and it's calm
and cute and colorful. Yeah, that's how it
turned out to be colorful.
There was a big jump here.
Nice, nice.
Even if I stopped, I didn't come back.
Nice,
nice, pounding
Ropa
[Music]
Yeah, it's good too, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice,
it's good, it's just power, it's
good, it's nice, it's nice, it's good, thank you for being a genius, it's
been more than a minute since I played the toy, I can do it, I can do it, I
can do it, I can
do it, I can do it, but it's nice, it's nice, it's good, it's
falling here  It's the worst. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay. Checkpoint.
It's okay. Just a little bit more
[Music]
6 meters left to go. We
all made it to the goal. We
ate a plain hamburger steak.  I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm so nervous. I'm so nervous. I'm
nervous, but it's a lie.
Yes, I'm back. Let's go home. I don't know what to do. Hey, try
again.  Did someone want to do it? I probably have
n't done the relay yet. I
practiced it. Yeah, I haven't done the relay yet.
Yeah, I feel like I want to do it. Well, I've done the relay too, so I want to try it again.
Yeah, I want to do it.
[Music]
Well, I guess there's one more person.
Actually, I could go around without doing it. That's
right. My team is Chloe,
so I
guess I'll just ask the other teams.  Okay,
wait a minute, then I'll do Zeta, and
Zeta will say sorry,
but the point is different when you reach that point.Yes, okay, okay,
Mio-chan is there.  Is there
another member of the team who is home? He's
not here today. Okay, I'll
ask the yellow one as well. Please wait a moment. If I
come in, I'm sorry, but there
's the yellow one over there.  There's still a follow-up
person, there's one, there's one more person,
there's one, there's one, there's one in red, there's one in white,
so I'm going to put in a substitute person and we'll
do it one more time. Ah, oh, oh, wait.
Well then, I'll enter. Oh, then,
can I ask one more person as the second person?
There are some members who would like to try it, but that's
okay. I'd
be happy if you could enter.  The
white team is going to do it one more time, and everyone is going to try it.The white team
is going to wait and go.How do you fly?It
hurts a little,
but this is
right.  Click and hold yes
Yeah,
yeah, you can't leave it, no, that's not true. I got hit a while ago, so I
just got hit back because I got dropped twice. I was
n't messing around, that's wrong. I
thought I was going to drop that thing.  That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine.
That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine. You
can practice one more time. Oh, it
's okay. Is this complete?
Yes, wait a minute. Look at the list.  Is
this yellow? Right now,
Anya wants to enter, but
somehow, Anya is trapped in a world of instant battles, and
even though she's trapped in this world line, she's trapped in this world line.
That's right, Anya, she's supposed to have
entered the country, so I'm not happy about it.  It's
true, I can't wait a little longer,
so I keep writing that I haven't returned the game.
I'm captured. Anya -san is a little bit in the world of the Kiva line,
and I wonder
if I can touch it again. I'm going to go to the entry.
Come on, let's do a tree,
now I'll try to cut it off, or
maybe I'll try pooing. I still have the book left, but it's now a book, so I guess I
can't do it. Yeah, it's okay, it's okay.  It's
okay because it's the Ludo Box guy,
it's okay,
thank you very much I can go to me I have
somehow, but that's why
it's always the usual that's always
they.  Subaru also has 41, so I
have 41 right now. Don't give up.
41. 41. That statue will come in the middle of the night.  Let's
get along. That's right. Let's get along. It looks like we're going to come
out. We're going to come out with our nipples exposed.
Now that we're Mikoshine, we're going to have a pink poop. It's
beautiful. Thank you. Good
morning. Thank you. Good. Thank you.
Thank you. We
did it again.  I can do it.
Oh sorry, can the white person
enter again?
Yes, I'm aiming for my life, and it looks
like I'm okay. I'm falling. I'm
being targeted. You're doing an amazing job.  I'm
throwing a trident with the power of an angry god
. I'm
starting a game that can do such a thing. I've started such a game.
Yes, I'm going to become a dyer, I'm going to be
infected.
[Music] I'll
reverse this. It would be amazing if I could do it from the beginning.
[Music]
Nere
Okay,
cuckoo, sorry.
ONE Just wait a minute.
Ah, nice, nice, I understand. Maybe it's a little late. It's
okay. It's okay. I'm just strong.
Beginner,
Beginner
O. Okiara wants to practice one more time,
so he's doing one mo, right. White team,
oh, do your best, try your best. I wonder if Ande will show up.  I guess it's
going to come out.
There's a lot of yellow today. Red, red,
yellow. Let's take a look. It's
difficult to actually do it.
There are two difficult ones.
Trident pieces
[Music]
Nehaa
[Music] It's
going to be a difficult game, but it's going to be the second round. That
's right, it's just the actual performance. That's right, it's just the guys who are doing it, but pretty much everyone is
feeling it. That's why it's actually very difficult.  The
first three were
amazing. They were so amazing, but they were practicing so much in the middle of the night.Yesterday, I was
working while watching One Piece, and
when I came in, Chiara was doing it forever.  It's all right, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right, all right, all
right.  If you think you've gone too far,
there's no place for you to adjust.  I can
understand why you couldn't click it.I
know, you've never climbed it before.It's
faster than last time, it's really
fast, it's really fast, it's really early.Just in case, we've
won in a row.And Chiara has been climbing all night.
Oh, it's so bad, why, why
, oh, wow, if you fall here, you'll lose quite a bit. It's
difficult. Oh
yeah, it's amazing. There's a checkpoint at the end, so it's
true. It's true, but it's not okay at all.  You
can say it, no, no, no, no at all,
shut up, no, no, no, no at all, don't talk anymore.
Oh, really, what's
going on? Taaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, miko is
just listening to me. ah, ahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
The layout is completely
different.It's actually different.I've made some adjustments to make it look simple.In
fact, it's stuck in.I
was surprised to see how completely different it was.I'm sorry, but Ani-san could do it.
Thank you very much,
you've already won, so I
think it's okay to throw it to the top, but it's a lot of odds, so it's going up, but there are a lot of options around here.  It's
like adjusting the
goal. It's nice, so it's the
highest.
That means the course will be different tomorrow as well.
This is the final one, so I
see. If you practice, it'll be as good as the actual one.
I'm glad, I'm glad. 321  So
there
[Laughter]
[Applause] I feel
like it was easier to do things yesterday than yesterday,
but
maybe it's just my imagination. It's a bit of a misunderstanding. If you'd
like, let's practice together.
Okay, let's practice. Let's get everyone
together. Next, we'll do the test once. After
that, we'll be able to do it pretty freely. I
think we should leave the voice server as it is.
I'm going to Ri.  The
surgery where I have to poop has Yes, I
think I decided the order of Katsumi on my own. It's okay,
thank you, it's okay. Thank you, I came to Kiba Sedaki. It's this way, it's this
way, it's this way, it's this way, it's this way
.  Kome Kokois
Everyone has already decided their turn, so
there probably aren't enough people, but
if there are too many, I think I'll include Mikola.
You can enter and watch it.Okay, okay,
can we
all just enter? There are 8 of us, so maybe we can all make it.Okay,
everyone.Okay, everyone, let's keep our
spirits up and everyone.  Is it
okay if I have 8 people enter? Yes, I'll
do it. Yes, I'm still pushing number 5, Mel,
and number 6. If
Amiko also joins, I'll be in the red group.
Eh No. 7 Ina and the last one is Shion so Eh Mito
Yes, Ao, Kanate and Zeta can go in wherever they
like, okay, yes, they
can go wherever they like.
Okay, wait, that's the last one. I
wanted to see everyone, so I ended it.
It's definitely the last one. It's
good. Do you like it? Yeah, I like it.
By the way, yeah, number 2, number 4,
number 6, number e
[Music]
diff
Well, they're gone, aren't they? So, I
'm wondering if Jita, Ao, or Kim can go to the second stage. There are 1,234,5678 people, Miko Sakura, and what are they? Well, on that day, too. I think it's probably 8 people.  But yes, there are even entries
for the Grand Nine runners, so
wait.  I do
n't have any, so I guess 8 is fine.Yes, yes, it's okay.No
one has entered yellow, so I'm
going to take care of number 2.I'm thinking of number
2.I can now max out 9 people, including those for practice.  Oh, I see,
that's right, so you
can ignore that last line. The two of you will enter and carry properly, so I
want you to give me a hug. Once everyone is here, we'll start.
Yes, it's a senior, so it's cool.
Show me that number, that's
5, it's really easy to understand, isn't it? Yes,
this is the closest book, right here.
In front of Fubla, in front of Fubla, plastic number 2,
number 4, number 6, number, uh,
this one, oh, ice, in front of ice cream, ice cream.
Previously, when it comes to the next operation,
it will automatically warp.
Yes, that's great. That
means you can keep looking at it.  You can
automatically see it in the center here, which is
amazing, but I haven't tried it yet, so I thought I'd give it a
try.The
baton was probably a left
click, so let's try it out and
have some fun.  Yes,
yes, yes, infected people will automatically come here.Okay,
fight, fight properly, baton.I have a baton.I have a baton.It's really true.It's a good fight.It's a good
fight.It's a good fight.It's a good fight.  It's
a touch, everyone, punch punch baton. It's a touch, yes, it's a punch.
[Music] It's
fast.
Ah, number 2. Number 2
is no, that's right. Number is number 2. Ah, I haven't gotten it, so I want to take it. Ah,
yeah, that's right. I can't go with a punch. Okay,
ah.  It's true that I can eat now.
No, I can't fly. I can't fly. It's
okay. I need to eat bread. Energy.  Do your best,
do your best, do your best, do your best, punch,
punch, punch, oh, nice, practice, do your
best, seta, do your best, yo, ignore me, ignore me, no jump, oh no jump, oh, it's
okay, oh, it's okay, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh  It's good, it's good, it's good, it's
falling, it's falling, it's straight here, it's
here, it's this leaf, it's fine
if you say leaf,
Lilia, you're
doing well, you're doing well, you're doing your best, you're doing your best.  Good
luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, jump, good luck, good luck, good luck, good luck, jump, good luck, good luck, control control control,
cheeks, dashes, and gs are control keys.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'll
do my best. Yes, it's okay. Even if the money has to give it its all, it's okay. Left click Raku Raku Raku Raku Raku Raku Ruo Oo
Nice O  Do your
best, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up! Wow, today's practice, so next time, practice. So it's okay. Next, what should I do? Just walkin' this workin' up, go ahead, go ahead, go ahead, go ahead, early one, do your best, I'm going to fall.
Oh, do your best. [Music] Yo, where's the battle now? It's okay, nice,
nice, you're early, you're early. If you don't rush there, you'll be
fine, okay
?
Do your best, ride the wave,
do your best,
do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best
Nice
bib, good, what number is it?
[ __ ], no, it's a punk place. If it's punk and boring, I
might be able to do it. Yeah, it's true
.
[Music]
If you don't go here, the
snow is right. It
moved. It's okay, nice leader, it's falling. It's okay, it's falling. It's
okay. It's okay. It's falling. It's okay. It's falling. It's okay. It's
falling. It's falling.
It's okay if you don't like it. It's okay because it's cold. I'll
try my best to make sure my friends don't give in.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, he might be lined up with white hair, and there might
be some woof-woof-chan in there.  There's
something creepy about the clouds. It's
okay, it's okay. Go, do your best. Go, do your best. You
can do it. You can do it.
Okay, now I'm waiting for you The thick voice has
become gone I'm waiting for you I don't know, I do
n't know, I don't know, I don't know, my seniors are here I think I'll
reach the finish line now Miko Seriously, come around once again Seriously, really quickly, please
[Music]  ] It
's early, it's okay, so hello everyone. I wo
n't forget the wonderful things. I won't forget the things.
Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Thank you, do your best, do your
best
. It's amazing. You'll be fine if you practice. I
think you'll be fine. Yeah, it's fine. Practice a lot.
Masuko-san is someone who
can mix things up and have fun, so
why not try mixing things up? What's the team-related thing?
So,
Yoshimiko-san, this is the system. It's pretty
easy to mix up and play, so
regardless of the team, I'm going to try it out.
For example, it seems like you can play Hunter while doing the fang line,
but it's also possible to do it by mixing up members from different relays.So,
for example, everyone
touches the signboard for entry and it's fast at first.  If you touch your favorite white,
yellow, or red, you
can enter
and up
to 32,739 people can run.That's right,
if you limit the number of people to 9, the anchor person
will run one lap.
If you're someone who wants to do it the next time because you can do it with a bang, then if you
can't do it right now, why don't you just participate the second time and
do whatever you want?
Or maybe the other teams aren't ready.There
are some people who are acting violently, so we're not going to do it again
with the full members.That's
right, so if it's confusing, it's
okay to have a mess of teams.So
how do we decide?  I see the team  I
think it's okay if we just give them some support after it's too early and we're done.I think it's okay if we just give them some support.I guess
all you have to do is enter it one more time.That's
just the entry button.  Hold it down,
get it, yeah, right there, the white and
white team, the white team of the white team, or the white team, which doesn't matter,
wait a minute, ah, I have to interrupt the game, wait
a moment, okay, yes,
this,
and then, only the red one can do this.  It's about to
turn into a red team and then a white team.Yeah yeah yeah yeah but
maybe there are some people who can't run.If
everyone on this team doesn't run, they'll ask me a little.The
yellow one.Yes,
don't go.  This is it for
those who haven't run just now, just hit the space with all your might.Wow,
yes, yes, what's going on?I thought I was going to run one more time, but the yellow was pretty good.I
was satisfied, but if there's one more race, I'll do it.Yellow
Yellow.  The largest number of people
But it's okay if you're blue, but right now I'm
hitting the drill repeatedly, I'm hitting it so
hard, I'm practicing right now without even starting. I
don't know, but
if there's one more, then it's totally fine.  I'll do it, but I'll just walk normally.
Is that okay? Well then,
Lillee, is it
okay to practice without using that system?
Yeah, yeah, I didn't eat the bread. You
know, I don't have to eat, but if I don't eat,
my physical strength won't recover, so I won't be slow, and I won't be able to
run anymore. I don't need to eat it,
but if I'm full, I can eat it.
I wish I could get the bread I want, but I don't think it would be better if I got the bread I want, but yeah,
no, it seems like I just want you to get this, because
even if I don't get that, I can reach the goal, so yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Well, it's quite difficult, so you don't have to take it and
eat it.Yes, you don't have to eat it,
but the part where it's late is a bit
strange, and
if you don't eat it, it's against the rules.Isn't it?  Well,
that's against Lulu, so I
'd like to make it feel like each team has their own team, but I guess we'll use a system.
In the competition, only one of them can move, so we'll
gather people who want to do it.  I
guess I'll make it look like that.Oh, then that Yellow.When I
have a competition over here, I'll ask you
to chat and then I'll go over there.Yes,
please.Yes, please.I'll
communicate that way.
[Music]
What's up with Moshi-moshi? This is the one where you
can practice without using the system.
So, without using the system, you
can practice freely without starting or anything.  I've already
received it, so those who use the system
have to do it one by one, so I
guess I'll give them a command. Those who want to do it, oh, I see. Well
then, yeah. For example, I'm going
to do Holomen Hunter one more time, so if you want to do it, please come.  It's
like, ``I want to sleep,'' and I say, ``If anyone wants to play, please come.''
I give the command, ``Hello, take the bread.'' I
had a question about this, so I'm going to share it.  You
can also do a dash without taking the bread,
but if you
can do that, it will be quite slow, and it will be even slower.However, if you don't
take the action of taking the bread, it will be faster.  It's
also a matter of gender, but that's what I do.I
dash without taking the bread, so
taking the bread is a must, and as a rule, I have to make sure I
don't take it at all.However, it's
okay to eat or not eat.  I
thought I'd share the rules,
but when I do that competition, I
'll give a shout out to them, so I'll let them know.I'm
sorry, but for the relay, let's
just do that practice without using the system.Okay, that
bread.  There was a question about bread, and yes, it was
okay to just eat the dash without taking the bread.There
was a question about whether it was okay to just eat the dash without taking the bread, but I
wanted them to do the same thing when taking the bread.  It's
better to eat because my legs
won't get faster.Tomiko
thinks, ``I'm so hungry, it's going to
happen quickly.'' That's right, I'm going to get hungry
here.  That's right, that's right. I'm
hungry. I can't run when I'm hungry
. I'll have to walk, so oh yeah,
that's right. It's going to be dangerous if I don't eat.
Honestly, I don't think there's any benefit to not eating. Yes, I think it's okay. I'm
thinking of gathering people who want to do something, just people who want to play, and having them participate in each competition.
From now on, it's free, and it's not the competition that I want to participate in.
But if you feel like having some fun with everyone, please come
and hang out with us.If you want to play with us, you'll be able to pat us, so that's okay.Then we
all practiced on our own and came out to play.Please
come and have fun.  Yes, thank you,
thank you,
thank you, thank you,
thank you.  I
feel like we've just made the final adjustments for the
tournament, but everyone has been practicing quite a bit, and I want to do it at my own home, so I'm not feeling like this right now, so I'm
thinking about collecting the competitions, but which ones.  Good
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you. I guess I was at
full speed right now.
Okay, I may have neglected everyone. I'm sorry. You all will be guardians tomorrow, so
please support us as much as possible.
Holomen
Hunting Holo  As for men hunting, the
topic this time is Holo men hunting.Let's look
forward to tomorrow's Holo
men.Should we do something other than hunting
?  I
think it's good, everyone, it's
better to try this one. It's
hard to go and get it for the people who go above this one, so it's
better to give it a try tomorrow as the cheat stick might run out.
On the other hand, it might be better.
No, it would be quite easy to do it with people from the red team and the white team,
but you have to choose people.
This might be a little too high.
Neona is coming
[Music]  I feel
like I want to play home hunting for the red team.I
wanted to do that.I couldn't do it a while ago, so I'm
going to play it on the day as well.But
since I couldn't, I haven't played it even once.Well, I
don't know how to play.So, let's talk
to everyone about Holomen.  I'm
recruiting for hunting Ah,
thank you. Thank you very much.
Yay, yeah, yeah, yeah,
okay. I did it. Yay, I feel like the broadcast was over by now. I
didn't do it at all.
It's okay if it's over. Miko is
streaming, so why don't you chime in?
Yes, I'll close it for now.
Yes, I believe in you. You can also stream freely.
Okay, how are we going to do this?
[Music]
Yes, yes, yes, but I'm still streaming. Still streaming.
OhoH, let's do Nico too.
Yes, the red team has entered.
Just yes, the red team has entered. The
yellow hunting red team that entered was
quick.
[Music]
Let's use this as a platform for the second half of the
game. Let's go back. Is red okay for fugitives? Let's
start.
Hey, I'm doing my best. I'm
alone,
but how can I survive? Left click. Left click. Left
click to catch me. It's the red team, so
please catch me. You can catch me.
Now it's fun.
No, I've
been caught, I've been caught, I'm on
top of you, who's on top of me, who's on
top of me, who
's doing this?  It's over, it's over
Next Next A
White
Kya I wonder if
there's anyone white I'm not there
I'm here I'm white I'm on top I
'm here I'm here I'm on top I'm
hiding Mecha
Oru Wow, come on, come on, oh, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. Maybe we should increase the quantum. Match [Music] Time, yeah, we should increase the match time. We should increase it. Hey, Zeta, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on. Yellow, light click.
Then, click on that Lyrica light, Rika
Gomea, anyone can do it, just click on the light, and then
press Hunting here. If you don't, you won't be able to go in. Ah, that's what it means. If you
don't touch the board, you won't be able to go inside.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, touch this board. I don't know how to do
this, so
maybe once. I
can't attach the rope.
First of all, I feel like I was catching it. I think I was catching it.
But I guess I left-clicked on that book one more
time.Oh, I'll
try it one more time.I
wanted to practice catching the red team one more time.Oh, I'll
stop right now, but here's the first one.  I'll do it  I'll
contact everyone once in a while.
Yes, I'm sorry, but there's no one here right now. I'm sorry,
but the members of the red group
still don't quite understand how to do it.
Only in the first half of part 1, when it comes to the red group's theme, is it a little bit?
Can we practice one more time?
Yes, I'm
sorry. Yes, I'm sorry. Everyone from the white team. That's the white team. The
yellow team. I'm sorry. The red
team. They're still touching the rope. Yes, it's
already the first half.  Somewhere along the way  Is
it okay if I just practice the first half with an interruption? Oh,
then I
wonder if I can have you
enter one more time as that hunter.
chan Hey, there's one more person, right? He
came out. He didn't come out. He didn't come out because it's a flow up.
That's right. Who
came out? He came out. He
entered. He entered. He entered. He
didn't enter.
Maybe we should try it one more time. Go back.
[Music]
Okay, let's try it.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hey,
red and red
people. I want you to practice this and that.  Is it the
wrong person? The red
boss is stirring things up
[Music]
Kurute
Terue Ne Click
Click Knikku I'm talking about it
So I'm already here I've just been arrested I'm sorry tomorrow I've been
arrested I'm sorry I've been arrested I'll
do the next one One click and that  Click again  I
wonder if I'm going to talk about it? Yeah, yeah, that's right, I'm making a face that I caught it. Where is this bib? Left click to let go. Right click to capture it, and it's already raining down. Oh, I
can go a little further. I caught it, oh
my gosh.  More than more, more and more, look,
please, please, please, please, if you
let go, it's no good, right? It's no good, right? If you let go, it'll go back to normal.
Oh, just touch the signboard, touch the signboard, touch the strange board.
[Music] There was
another person who looked like he was there. There was another person who tried
[Music] I'm sorry I
got it so quickly.
Oh no,
no.  I'm
really into it. I was able to get Subaru in
this time. I
haven't put in Subaru here and now. I
caught it. I
think I understand how nice it is. Thank you for your hard work. You're doing well.
Okay, nice,
nice.
Okay, thank you, Okay,
this is how I learned how to run, so now I can
do it. Yeah, yeah, Okay, then the yellow
person, the yellow person, then the
runaway person, who runs away. Let's
go, everyone, we're all runaways.  That's
okay even if you're the one doing the relay.
Oh, right click and left pan. That's the
yellow one on the left. The other yellow members can also
become fugitives, so write that.  It's okay, all you have to do is
catch the yellow one
. That's right, that's right. The
white team is also going to do the hunt. Do you
want to do it? Oh, let's do it next to the yellow one.
Oh, yes, yes, okay. Okay, then
that white team is that white team.  Even when I'm on the team,
I'm a runaway, and I can be another member of the white team,
so yeah, yeah, please give it a try.Yes, that's
not the next one.Thank
you for taking the day off.Alright, I wonder
if it's bright now.  It's
about time,
thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work. I look forward to seeing you again tomorrow.  Noko
Asodafu was doing it
[Music] I
see.
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you. I'm still streaming.
Yes, Amiko is also still streaming.
Oh, are you okay
? Let's start.
Hey, let's go
. Good night, everyone.
Bim,
good night, everyone. Let's take a break and try it out.
What should we do next for the white team? We've been caught.
No one's been here, and it hurts. The
first thing that everyone notices is  No, it doesn't really feel like it. It's the
first time I've been caught. I'm so
happy. But I must
have made a mistake. I've made a mistake. I don't know
why, but now I'm being targeted again.  Why don't you just
run away?
Wow, you're
from the
White Team. It's the White Team
. You're
right, Kao-senpai has been here for a long time. It
's a really nice place. No
one has noticed. Really, no one has noticed.  I think
it would be better if we stayed away from each other. We're far away. They're fighting. People think we're the white team. We're the red team. We're the red team.  Haku was
captured, but he did
n't realize it.
Hey, Polka-senpai didn't just want to use it.
Ah, that's the theory. Masu-un keeps getting
captured.
Maybe he likes it, or maybe he'll have it if it's already Pokkatepa.  I wonder if
there's such a thing as Nebo, when the person in question isn't there,
but the person in question isn't there.Why do I get caught?My senior thinks I'm yellow because of my hair,
or do I like it when I stop again?  It's a
problem, I'm catching it for the time being. It's a problem. It's a problem. It's a
good job. That's a
white one. It's white. Let's correct Miko. Let's get in there,
listeners. That
big one was destroyed.
There were people who had been there for a long time wondering if it was going to happen.
Yes, it's a great entry and entry. It's
not a drop, it
's a drop, everyone's entry is being cut. I wonder if the
people who gathered there are saying that their entries are being cut are true.  I
'm sorry, everyone, I'm sorry, I
was trying to hide here,
but it's true, I'm starting to feel sorry. I'm sorry,
everyone. I
can't help it, I'm just pretending to
be a listener. Yeah, that's right, it's okay, it's about me, a listener.
That's what I thought. I
thought it was going to be scratched off.
Okay,
hey, let's
try this, but it won't fit.  I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I can't go in, I ca
n't go in, I ca
n't go out.  I can't appear, but I'm
still entering. I can participate, but I can't appear.
[Music] I
'm the first person to participate, but
everyone is helping me out.
If I don't rescue you, I'll need a teammate next time. I
miss my friends. Mia, Ueo-senpai, Miya,
Aotsu, Oke-senpai, Senpai. I'm
getting really beaten up. There's
only one person in the red group, so it's Miko-senpai. Oh
my
, it's tough, it's okay.  The white team is in a mess. They've
been captured. Hey, red and red are trying to run away.
Was only the senior who got captured? Hey, hey, come on,
tell me what's wrong. You shouldn't say things like that.  It's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's
amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, isn't it? It's amazing, isn't it?
Yomiko-senpai's special makes me angry,
Somiko-senpai's special is special,
so it's special, so yeah,
yeah, there's a lot of yellow.
Red isn't there, but wow, what are you doing
? I'm stuck in a spider's nest. Ah, I'm stuck in a spider's nest. I was trying to escape,
but I couldn't escape.
Even though it was too good, it's really possible to do something like that.I was
caught by a person with a cloud who hasn't changed,
but Ririka suddenly disappeared.Reset the game.Please
interrupt.Please
put a sign in the middle of the middle row.
Where is this board? That's what it means. It
was a nest of ku. I don't like Senkyu, but in
the end it disappeared when I was thrown into the cage. Yeah,
well, maybe it's just a waste of time.
No, Ririka-chan suddenly disappeared, so she
was probably taken away.
Well, everyone, please practice. Miko.
Tachimiko. I'll call out to you again. Okay, what should I do?
Nahi, is your voice good?
[Music] Nah, good,
Aki  Did you do it? Yes, I
think it will take a lot of time if we are going to play all the rounds today,
but there is probably a team that I want to practice with.
I was thinking, ``I'm going to pass it around to people who want to do a floor-up,'' and I'm like, ``It's okay if I get removed,''
so I'm free to do it, and then I'll close it once, and say, ``Yeah, that's right, let's
gather everyone together.'' I
'll do that.  Well then, can I ask you to gather the whites? Oh, I
'll let 2 gather. Yes,
please. I'm sorry.
I'll close it once, and after I close it, I think it's
okay to have people take pictures.  I was
thinking about doing it.
Hello, hello, hello.
[Music] What's
that?
[Music] Everyone can talk. [Music]
No, wait a minute. The voice on the call
died.
Members whose participating clips are enabled
are [Music] [Applause
] [
Music] [Music]
What
[Music]
This
Desumo-
chan
That's not finished
[Music]
Why is everyone connected to RTC? Hey, who knows?
Reboot, wait a minute
.
[Music]
Okay,
reboot. Nico's disco that everyone is playing is
coming.
Hello,
hello, I heard this. Hello, hello.  Hello, hello, I'm
sorry, but for
those of you who are thinking of closing that whole thing and then closing it and continuing, it's okay to just leave the
frame as is, but I'm thinking of closing it for now, so...
Can I have you join me in the room where everyone is? Oh yes,
yes, Rolo was there.  I wonder
if Ospor is missing.
Hey, it's okay for the first time since I'm back.
Okay, yes.
Thank you everyone for today.  I'm
really happy that you've been practicing so hard. I'm
looking forward to supporting the members who weren't able to come and having fun together.
Thank you very much.
After this, it's Miko's call.It's okay
even if it's not related to the team.I'll
call out like someone who wants to play with this call, so please come at that timing.Can I ask you to come?The
same goes for that fang line that starts up a little bit.Follow up.
Well, I
can't do everything at the same time with the princess, so I'm
thinking of doing it in order, so I'll
gather only the people who want to do it and have them come, so I'll
pass it around and then close the frame.
It's okay if I leave that slot, but
thank you very much.Yes, I'd like to do it at once.Thank you for your
hard work, everyone.I'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you very much. It's 6:00 p.m.
Hey, thank you very much. See you
again. Please
excuse me.
Sanro will be in number 5 for now.
Where should I go?
Let's collect the voices.
Who is it? It's Mio. It's Mio. I'm sorry for that. But Umiko, who did that, is still everyone's favorite.  I
thought I was going to watch the practice, but I
didn't close the door, so I
thought, "
Okay, okay, it's already tomorrow, Miko-chan. It's early. Okay,
no, it's been so long."
Yeah, but this time, the quality has
improved a lot compared to before, and I've been able to incorporate a lot of things into the system,
so I think that's a good
thing, but
still, I still have to make adjustments.
Yes, that's true. It was really amazing, but it worked out somehow.
Yeah, yeah, tomorrow, I'm
going to buy cookies for the three of us to eat, so I'll
bring Ei, so Mio Sama.  Kakashi-chan will be carrying me,
and I'll be
bringing snacks with me, so it looks like it's going to be a while.
We'll be doing the commentary in another studio,
but tomorrow we'll be in that studio. The
three of us will get together for a bit, so let's do it.
Yes, last year too, Nemi-o-chan
brought me an assortment of sweets.  Hey, you
brought it for me,
Mio. No, that's right. It's like a gift. I
love Mio-chan's gifts, so Miyoko.
No, thank you very much.
Let's get together at number 01.
Voice: That's right, once we get together,
yeah, I see, that's it, right, Higo. It's just a
little
bit of a start. Yes, it's like dividing the members, etc.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. It's like practicing your voice. Yeah, um,
maybe,
please, please, please,
please.  Masua Mikochi's distribution is
still ongoing, so
please take care of it. All the
members of Masu are there, but how about the
yellow members being divided into 444?
How many people do you
have? 1234567888 right now. 8
If so, we can divide them into teams. We
can do it. We'll see how things go.
If anyone wants to team up with us, we can.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Please proceed.  Please say that. I'm
going to ask you something. Oh, sorry. I have one more question.
What is that? The
part where you make a figurine and guess what it is.
Yeah, uh, the knights can't talk, they can't talk,
right? Basically, the
voices and things like that are good, but with words,
this is that, that's the usual thing, and the
words like ``dawa'' will probably get the message across.  ``
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, put green here'' and other words like that.Then,
that princess is allowed to speak, and the
princess speaks.  I
'm wondering if this or that thing is a refrigerator when I'm talking, and the way the knight shakes his head up and down while listening, or nods like that, does that feel like a no-no? Yes, it's a hit or a no. It's okay if it's not a y-no-no. It's
okay.  Oh no, that's like an answer.But yeah,
things like that topic in Koshi, and things
like that change on the day.In
terms of topics, the one about cooking
is not exactly the same in the first half.  After all  It's
random, so in reality, if you make red hair,
for example, there will be a lot of paprika,
or there will be a lot of refrigerators, etc.,
but I think that's true, but it's
still random.  I do
n't really get it, it seems like some
random guy is getting angry, and the
topic for the day is random, but the
one that's appearing now doesn't change, and there's a possibility that the same one will come out again.
And by the way, that creative
person. The first half of the questions are not that different,
but the second question is about that day
's special question. Yes,
that might be quite difficult. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes.  I
feel like there are some changes to the orchestra,
but nothing that would interfere with that.
Yes, it's okay.
[Music]
Etc.
Yesterday I was able to go with 44. No, I'm
not sure how it feels now. It's
probably yellow right now. It looks like yellow is going to gather around. Should I
do yellow now? Then I
should enter red and white.  That's right,
that's right. I'll enter the white team and
do it on the day. I'll make another team with people who are just like that. I
wonder if there's a red team and a white team. Yeah, yeah, they've
disbanded quite a bit. I guess they've
disbanded quite a bit.  Those three teams together  I
can practice without it,
but I'm like, Okay, let's do it. Well, if
everyone just does the entry, then we
can do it. Well then, we'll
do Princess Watame, and then we'll do the night. Well then, we'll do Princess Anya. Why
don't we do it?  I want to do this.I want to play an ancient soldier.Okay
, I want to see the princess.Please, I want to see the princess.Then,
Mio-chan, you can come as a knight.That's
dead.She's dead.Then, I'll
ask you to be that knight.
Oh, you're cute, Suma-chan,
isn't it? Cute,
start button, okay, where's the
start button? Where's the start button? Do you want to separate the voice servers?
Oh, okay, then let's go to the actual show. I'd
like to be number 2 on the first team. Yes,
yes, ma-chan, number 2.  Oh yeah, okay,
let's go. Oster, can I have you protect me?
Imiko-senpai, Wata Anya's turn. Bro Misa,
Olets go, Shiro Nemiko.  The
white orchestra is a little short, shut up,
Higata,
hurry up, white, pink, pink, strong. Hey, it's a princess, stop it, stop there. I'm in
danger with the blocking movement. Okay, hey, I'm back.
There's more.
Later, from white,
later.  Back, back, slow, pink, pink,
pink, pink, pink, which way, which way are you
going, which one is
white, pink, red, yes, yes, yes
Yes, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, princess. Hey, the
princess is already in such tatters. I've come to the red.
White, pink, white, pink. Oh, white, white, pink, red, red, red. Yes, yes, yes.
Pink, red. Don't move. Don't move. Oh, okay, okay. Okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
what's this?
Yeah, what's this
? What's this? Oh, oh, that's weird. Yeah, what's
this? Why can't I cut it like that? But wait, what's that? Oh, I
can't tell from the white lump.
Great grilled rabbit meat and viewer's characteristic hamburger There
is rabbit. Masudote grilled rabbit meat is raw rabbit meat.
Beef, please, potatoes, rainbow, okay, raw
garlic, raw beef, beef,
beef, garlic, that's it, miko's favorite,
grilled garlic, love, love, my favorite meat,
what to do with carrots, on a cutting board, on a chopping board.
What should I do with the potatoes? I'd
like to serve them with potatoes, rainbow potatoes, carrots, and minced beef on a griddle.  It's minced
meat, it's minced meat, it's
just what I want to say, please.  I
smoked it. I'm
sorry about the grilled rabbit meat. I'm sorry,
Miko. Isn't this charred, too
? It's okay, it's okay, it's good, it's
good, it's good, Oona, yes, next, next, nice.
Next, oh my gosh, I'm doing a monster.
Yes, it's red. Red, upper left is orange, orange, and upper right is yellow. Orange,
red, orange. Yellow, yeah, red, orange, yellow, red, orange,
yellow.  Orange,
red, right, orange, yellow, red on the bottom, red on the top, orange on the right, yellow,
orange on the right, orange, yellow, okay, nice, I didn't understand that at all, nice.  It
's slipping through, it's slipping through.
Mikochi, run, run, protect it yourself.
Okay, okay, nice, nice, nice. I'm not coming. I'm doing my best, I'm doing my best, okay. It's
hot. It's hot. Protect it. It's hot.
Everyone.  It's burning, everyone's burning, it's
burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's
burning, it's burning, it's dead, it's so nice  I'm exhausted, I'm exhausted, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's no one's
fault
, it's a mistake, I didn't do it, I
didn't do it at all By the way, I
didn't do it at all, look at me now  I'm so
irritated that I'm really stabbing you.
Don't give me a weapon. It's the worst. I'll give it to you
for a while. Do you want to share the server with me? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes.
Please give me a compliment. That's right. I'm
looking forward to the actual performance. I'm also looking forward to the yellow one. It's a
success when something like a star appears,
right? That's easy. The
star is that. When the other person's body has a brown star,
that's it.  It's
amazing that you even learned how to do a critical hit,
but it's amazing.If you have a bow, the last thing you
should do is go to the Demon King Nesa Suyana Sasu Matsuriko.Wait
a minute, that one from last year.  in  There
was a huge need for critical hits last year.It was a
sports day.If you want to be sure, it was better than critical.Do you
remember what was going on with jumping?There
was mob subjugation, there was mob subjugation, there was mob subjugation, there
was fencing, there was Thing, there was
Shidama.  Mr. Daruma fell down.
By the way, there
's something else you'd like to practice. It's okay. It's
okay to
follow up. There will be people participating in the follow-up, Mr. Suisei.  I guess I'll
just follow up with my husband. Wow, I've got the impression that he's already got the hang of it. Yeah, it's true that Anya is too, isn't he? Anya-senpai. Yeah, that's right. Let's collect the follow-up. Let's follow-up. Okay, if we follow
up, we'll get one yellow. Shall we
break up?  Yeah,
yeah, when was the next practice?
12The next practice is tomorrow, uh,
tomorrow, yellow, 1 o'clock to noon, I
think I can go.
Maybe, it's okay, it's okay.First of all, on the other hand, if
there's something you want to practice, let's
practice a little bit after this.Let's go and practice together over there.We'll
be out for about an hour from now, but if you're doing it, please join us.It's
totally fine.  Well then, it's a good time to start. You can do
whatever you want. It's okay.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you for your
hard work.
[Music]
Thank you. There's still one more person to do the floor-up,
but Anya. Who's going to do it?
That's why your stomach is protruding.
Put it away. It's cute. Yeah, put it away. I'm really
moving. Don't mess around there.
Please move. They're already here.
We're over here.
Don't say we're petting each other.  Look at her, her stomach is protruding.
By the way, how cute is her belly protruding?
Chao-chan's stomach is protruding normally.
[Laughs] The
moment when Tamin's hearts became one Ya
Shunya
Hey, that's it, please touch this.
Okay, I'm late. Oh, I'm late, too.
Sensei-senpai's entry is yellow. I
changed it to white, but what
should I change to red? Oh, you can change it to yellow. Sorry.  I made it red,
oh, I made it red, I'm sorry, red
is also open, it's really open, I can go to that, red, I can
go, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, you can enter. If the yellow
player turns red to red, you'll be
able to do it. Go for it, do your best.  It's too
early to know who's in the middle
of this. It's already begun. I
wonder if Miko, the amazing creator, will win.
I'm the creator's slide cancer.
Here's a battle that can't be defeated. A battle that can't be defeated.  We've
created a new word, ``Ganba nya'', ``Gamba nya''. Today, ``
Gamba nyabanya'' is cute, isn't it? ``Gamba nya'' is cute, isn't it?
Well, now that we know the route,
if we just follow the route, we can get there in the shortest possible
time. That's not
true. Everyone is amazing. That's why everyone is so good at it. That's
what we're doing.  Oh no, Aji
Nemiko-senpai is really good, you've surpassed me
. Now you're
amazing. I'm waiting for you to die. Sorry, I
'm not waiting. Let's be friends.
Okay, let's just get along. That's a bit tricky. You
come back while you're falling. Ah, the second checkpoint. As soon as you realize you can't do this anymore, you come back. That's amazing. You come back right away. That's great.
Okay, so this is still not a competition.In the end, why
can't I go there?Yeah, it's mental.That
's why this game is mental gel,
mental physical, so mental
physical passion is what's important.
Well, as expected, I'll get it quickly as a person. It's
another team, another team, this is another source.
So, do your best with this, oh,
that's it. Good luck,
you're amazing. There's so much left. Stable, stable. I didn't do well last time. Let's
die.  But Suba isn't here so I can't stop her.
Seriously, she won't be there tomorrow, so please die.
Who is Sui-chan?
I'm with you. Hey, Ririka, please stop. If something happens, I'll go instead. I'll stop it, stop it, stop it. Ririka, stop it. Ririka, stop it. I wonder if I'll be there too.
So don't worry, seriously, I'll be following
up too, so my passion
will be a little messed up.
Everyone's going to break down with the follow-up.
Come back, Miko, onee.  Eh, there are
still people streaming here. There are
a lot of people who are doing
it. There are people who are doing it. It's currently on the air. It's on the air right now.
Why did it fall? We're
all watching the flow-up
at the end.  The last try flow up is the
last one, and the real race is tomorrow, isn't it? It's tomorrow. The
real race is today. If you ask me for practice, the
layout
won't be that different from today's, so I won't be able to reach it.
Good luck with this!
Good luck! I can't reach the top. If the water goes to the top, it's
probably the same layout as yesterday.  It's great that you've
reached the checkpoint.
Idiot, are you okay? It's
not okay. Do your best. There's still time. Let's
go slowly. Let's do it. Ah, I fell. It's okay, Ani.
Just leave the speed of recovery up to me.
Just the speed.  Please leave it to me
Just leave the speed up to me, I can do it. That's
great. What should I do? There's
only 19 seconds left from here. Okay, okay, 15
seconds left. Fall, you're serious. I can't see you, but fall. You're an idiot. You're
an idiot. I want to die. I want to die. Idiot bye. Bye.
On the contrary, it was amazing, but on the other hand, it was
amazing.
Nemashi
[Music]
[Laughter] Well, it's
over, so this is the end.
After this, Neja will turn
yellow and it'll end.  No,
no, no, that's okay. I'm the one who closes the frame. Good luck. Thank you for staying. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. Well
then, let's disband for now. Mr. Ba. Oh, that was
interesting. This is so difficult, isn't it? Everyone. I don't like this,
though.  In the first half, there were quite a few
instances where I would get hit if I jumped, so I'd wait and try.
Yoshimi is doing it again, I'm watching you do it one more time, and I'm going to
reach the
goal, but I really tried my best, but I'm really trying to do it.  I'm going to go with the goal, goal,
goal.
[Music] I
'm so proud
[Music] It's so
good
[Music]
Okay
[Music] I'm
going to put a little emphasis on the
opposite side of things.
[Music]
Okay,
hey,
hey
[Music]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, 144 seconds left.
We won with 144 seconds left.
Oh wow, Miko is
amazing, this is seriously, she loves competitions. Na-chan, you're late. I'm not here yet. It's a good thing. It's the creator's pride. Yeah, it's nice. Ka-chan,
Miko's Yellow Miko is in first place. By the way,
here's the thing.  You can't go home after you finish the race,
after all.If you finish early, you'll be here for
those who have more time.I was
thinking of making something like a bonus bonus place.  The
smoother it is, the faster it goes, but if I make a mistake during the actual
race, I'm probably not going to be able to reach the goal like I did earlier.I wonder if
this is a good thing.That's a bonus.When the
stages didn't go well, I
thought it was pretty bad and stopped.  In the end, it
seems like the end of the competition is a bit complicated [Music
]
Yeah, there's a big difference, so yeah, yeah, that's it.
Okay, seriously, this is amazing.
[Music]
Okay, so how was everyone today?
Tomorrow, it's the real show. Win
or lose, it's the real show, so please
come and see us tomorrow from 6pm.  Thank you very much
for your support.
Thank you very much for your support. I look forward to seeing you all tomorrow. I really hope that
everyone will practice harder than ever before.
Everyone is
really working behind the scenes, especially the newcomers, and
everyone at enid gets together every time and
gives support, so I couldn't come back later.  I think it's amazing that everyone is
taking the initiative and working with their seniors.I'd
like to
thank everyone for their support.
So, let's meet again tomorrow at 6pm. Well then, it's Otsumi. See you
soon. Let's head to the ending, no, let's go to the shrine maiden's room. Ok, let's have a little sleep. Oishokochichi Otsumi. Thank you very much. Tokowa. Things will stay
like this.  I think I'm
going to be a little nervous since it's going out tomorrow, so I thought we'd just have a chat,
but it's already my 4th time
.  It's
good. The girls who are showing up have already
gotten used to it and are getting everyone's support.
As long as it's really a big help, it's good. It's the
only day a year where you can see cool faces. Why? Yo Why? You're
always cool. You're always
cool.
Doroisho topics too.  Yes, it's a mess.
Even though it's the end of the show, you're still supporting me a lot. Behind the scenes, I've already set up a slot for tomorrow. You
're really supporting me.
Minnazu-chan
and others have been particularly involved this year, making
things easier to understand, and
each group has someone
acting as their middle child and explaining
things that I don't understand.  She's doing things like, "Please come and listen to me.
" Nesou Towa-sama is a really good senior
[Music] Nanesou
Towa-chan is always running around to everyone every year, and
even today she didn't understand before the broadcast started.  of  They
support me in detail, like
massaging and not so much,
so they support me in that aspect.I see,
as a shrine maiden, I do it once a year,
even once a year.  I don't think so, but I especially feel the warmth of the seniors and juniors
at the athletic meet.It really feels amazing.
No, but I'm really busy as usual, so
there were some members who weren't able to participate,
but I'm glad that I was able to do it despite my busy schedule.It's
not over yet, but I'm sure there are members of Rigolo
and others who couldn't participate.  I
think we had a lot of interaction with the members of ``
The Sports Day'' and the
practice session just before the event, which
was an opportunity for collaboration.  I
wonder if it'll turn out that way. I think that makes me happy as a shrine maiden
.
Hey, good job. Thank you for the performance. I'll do my best.
Everyone, but I
think I'll be fine without that expensive thing from Holomen Hunting.
Hey, everyone
.
[Music]
Yes, that's right
.  No, everyone, see you tomorrow. There
are 6 types of topics,
6 types,
3 lots of red bean paste,
18 lots of red bean paste,
etc. It's really hard to think about it.
Even though it was difficult, I thought it was impossible for Nemiko and the others to do it alone, so I
asked the management about things like ``Uh-huh'' and ``I did it.''
But the comments stopped, so it
was really difficult.
What really makes it difficult is that there is a question that is asked,
right?This time, it
's about catching the red group, catching the white group, catching the yellow group, but to put it simply, it's
limited to people with animal ears from Holo Live.  Why?
That's right,
so if you
pick out the people with ears from the red group and the yellow group, then it's
Maruto, so if that's the case, then there are four people, and
so on.  For the second question, I
looked at the balance and
made a lot of adjustments, such as making it the one that had the most answers, so in the end, I
ended up making some adjustments to the question that would be asked today, such as red, white, and yellow.  I have to challenge the number of faces.
No
, that's why it was so hard, the balance,
that's it, it's so amazing. It's so
hard to think about it, it's so hard, you
know, it's hard to think about problems, right
?  [Music]
Yes, time is going to stretch a little bit more. I
want to stretch it out.
But I don't know if I can do it now. I do
n't know, but I
'll contact you right now.  A lot of people
come out every year, right?
[Music]
But
Yeah [Music]
Okay
[Music]
Hey, it's hard to decide where to put in the effort. That's
right. It's
just cats.  It's not like I'm doing it by myself,
so when I make adjustments to the individual commands, I
have to ask the support staff to help me out a bit.It's
really difficult.
[Music]
Nesui-chan has mastered the flow-up.
To be honest, I thought it was a bit difficult. It's
amazing. There are so many people who do it while leaving 100 seconds in.
Everyone is amazing.
[Music]
It's good.  I wonder if there will be any
additional elements or not from now on. Well, let's just
say, there's a lot of pressure during the actual performance,
so I think it'd be amazing if he showed up during the actual performance. Yes, it's
at that level, I get impatient.
Yes, that's right, it's usually my first
game.In the games where I start, I often don't score a goal.It's the
same thing even when I'm out of practice.No
, I'm going to sleep properly this year too.This year, it
's in the evening.  Yeah,
yeah, there's a lot of things like that, but Miko and the others are
really excited for the first time. I'm really
going to take a good rest.
Thank you, everyone. Please look forward to it.
What will happen tomorrow?
[Music]  It was a lot of
fun, but I
managed to reach my goal. It
's a little early,
but I think it'll end like this.
Tomorrow, I'll see if something goes wrong, or someone
crashes the game, or something like that.  If something
happens, we have decided how to respond. There
are games where the game is interrupted, and there
are matches, for example, in the second year.
Everyone is on the verge of reaching the goal, but one of them falls.
In order to deal with things going awry, we've put in some kind
of gimmick where everyone goes into a stay state, but
even so, we still
have to get the listeners' consent because it
's still a game after all.  Minecraft: No matter
how long you've retired, there will still be times
when a bug or some kind of trouble will occur.It's the
same with any tournament,
but at those times, you'll be so warm and supportive without blaming anyone.  I
hope you can encourage me with your comments.
Yes, it's shopping after all, so I guess it's the person's
fault. I'm sure some people
tend to be a bit like that,
but please feel free to give me a warm comment.  I
think it would be really warm if you could stream it.Well, I
'd like to end it with the members who participated saying that it was fun,
so please listeners for your cooperation.Thank you
very much.I'll cut out this part.  That's
fine, that's fine.As a note of caution, I
hope that the listeners can watch it from the perspective of real parents with a warm heart.I hope everyone enjoys saying this in a friendly manner.
As a campaign organizer, that's what I think is the most important thing.As
expected, all the members are practicing and
working hard,
so please give us your support.Let's get
along, listeners.
Even if we get
along well, for example, even if there are comments like "Good luck," it's
like, "Good luck, it's okay, it's okay.
" I hope you can spread the word in the comments. I
don't think you'll see it, or rather, I'll always make comments that support you.
After all, there are many places where everyone can
do their best, so listeners, please leave a comment. [Music] Let's have a Masui Akaikai. Well, we get along well, but it's still the listeners.  I do
n't know,
but the number has increased.
When did it increase? Who increased it? Is this your
father? There's a flying colone.
There's a flying colone. The
quality is good.  That's expensive.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your support tomorrow.
Well then, see you next time. Thank you, Hesta.
Hey, everyone, check out the Super Chat again.
I'll let you read it, so I'm going to close it here today.
See you tomorrow. Let's
do our best on the sports day. Well then,
I'd appreciate your help from the management perspective. See you
soon. Bye [
Music]
Bye
[Music]
[  [Applause]
Oh