[Music]
do
hello
hi
hello there
are you here to
to join my party
as you can see i i reserved the party
room uh
wow i don't think so many people would
show up oh gosh i might not i have
enough berries for everybody hello
hi
how's everybody doing thank you thank
you for all the happy birthday wishes
and art and super chats
being around hello hi
sorry i'm really nervous i'm very very
very very very nervous um
also my voice is really tired i probably
overdid it
yesterday so sorry sorry if i sound a
little wet
welcome welcome to uh what's this place
called
welcome welcome we have it all we have
the ticket blaster over there we have
the holocure game over there
we have the oh i love korean games we
have the crane game
we have the bay animatronics
oh boy
anyway yeah uh what are we gonna do for
my birthday uh well i just had a
premiere for a video
done by tana uru
uh
i
i i told i told him to just go crazy go
for it
i don't think he disappointed at all i
didn't see that video until i think it
was maybe
20 minutes before i saw the premiere
i hope you guys
hope you guys liked it
it was a little crazy
oh boy oh boy what else do we have to do
drink water one second
oh goodness
what else are we going to do we're going
to have some uh call-ins we're gonna
have some members of ian and id and jp
say hello
um i'm gonna tell you now it's not
organized at all i put my focus in the
wrong places i am so sorry to everybody
who is
going to be here today um it's it's a
free-for-all just you show up you you
hop on usually we give a designated time
for these things but i did not do that
um
and i also asked extremely last minute
very last minute so some people just
cannot make it
and that's okay i asked i i think i
asked less than 24 hours ago
um but yeah we'll be doing that
in a little bit i don't even know what
the order is i have no idea who's going
to show up
um
but i have
two questions prepared am i trying to
think of more
um
you guys have any uh good ideas for
questions i wanted to do questions we
don't usually ask
for jp members i want to be simple i
have those questions
who are you that's a good question to
ask
who are
you please describe yourself oh that's
real that's really putting people on the
spot there
that you're kind of funny
favorite type of berry
that's a good one then i can ask i can
follow that up with why
i think it's important for the question
to be not you know just a yes or no
receive a yes or no answer
tell me about yourself why are you oh
excellent yes it's going to be like an
interview for them i don't want them to
talk about
me
i want to know more about them yes
oh excellent oh these oh these poor
these poor these poor girls
anyway
[Applause]
i suppose i should step
wait before i step in um
did i finish the flow oh yeah we'll do
that i will also announce merch but i
will actually continue having call-ins
even when i'm done announcing merch just
for those who
needed a little more time
um they'll also go over some fan-made
things
hold up
sorry guys i'm gonna be clearing my
throat a little bit i overdid it with
the karaoke yesterday
i also didn't sleep very much that kind
of affects it too um but real quick real
quick yeah so um i'll announce merch
we'll do a few more call-ins and i and i
want to go over some fan-made things
you're going to hear a lot of clicking
around i'm very nervous it's probably
going to be some scuff
uh please bear with me
but yeah i'm going to insert myself
into
the call into the arena let's go oh wait
where is it
um
i go
oh gosh i hope this oh
sorry
just unbox the volume okay by the way
we'll see when the discord happens or no
they're actually here it's not discord
um
but we'll see we'll see you when they
show up if the volume is all right
okay for now the music's okay okay cool
cool cool
all right and i should probably okay i
will do this
this okay i think i have this figured
out
all right all right i think i think i'm
good to go i am good to go
universe spring bring me
that
hello
happy birthday
to
you
happy birthday
to
you
all right
[Music]
but it didn't work
wait it's not my birthday today
now you're getting me yeah it is
it's not my birthday why are you calling
why are you singing happy birthday
i don't know it's just you seem to be in
the potty room i mean we seem to be in a
party room and this happy birthday movie
on the on the walls and stuff i don't
know you tell me
oh maybe you're right sorry
it's likely i forgot
oh
oh thank you
needle what a seal impression
um what does the seal sound like um
that's the sea lion can you see lion
impression
why
i don't know
all right
yeah happy birthday
how are you happy you do great don't
worry
thank you
you're welcome i also do this
don't question it okay i i
oh gosh how do i speak how do i do this
quickly
it's okay your real gift you already got
last time don't worry about it
yeah she knows you guys don't know suck
it you never know what it is
that oh this is the present
oh how do i do this oh no
hello or you can put it along hello
you can put it alone at the table
that'll be cool yeah i'll go on the
table can you guys see what it is what
is it
i
i tried
shut up i tried
i tried i think it's cute we're in a
heart together
yeah it's very wonky huh because i
didn't anticipate the hair and you
needed to make space for your face
[Laughter]
yeah thank you
oh my goodness
oh awesome
thank you they held me properly last
minute with some stuff thank you bae
nice okay birthday you know there's
always the thing about birthday parties
when you plan a birthday party you're
always very stressed it's okay i'm glad
i could help
thank you thank you
oh my god i feel like i've overstayed
already oh my god no you're fine you
have another minute
i have another minute oh my god the
things we can accomplish in a minute oh
we should tease them
oh
we know something you don't
[Music]
haha you never know what it is you never
ever ever know never ever ever we will
never ever tell or show never ever never
ever it's just between us
yeah
you excited
i'm so excited to see your merch bro oh
my merch oh i'm excited to show it that
is it did i
no i feel a little bit but also like i'd
like to say that my guess was pretty
accurate because she like mimei showed
me a sneak peek of the birthday room
yesterday and she just showed me the
animatronic and i'm like why is the
first thing i thought about snap i don't
understand and then i see it now it
looks great
yeah it does it's over it's very clean
it's very nice
amazing
well i'll be watching while eating my
breakfast and
it's not the time for breakfast but it's
okay i'm gonna be enjoying my i mean my
party food in the corner of the room
um just keep an eye on the animatronic
um
you know yeah
if it moves and eats something oh yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
i let's see if i can do this
i hope i can do this why is it like this
oh i see it
okay i want to put every where should i
do this i'll put people
over here i guess
how i should do it does that make sense
i might get oh maybe i should i don't
know how small to make it how many
people are gonna be here
we'll do that well that that should that
should be enough that's not speaking out
maybe i can put it oh i see how i can do
it all right
wait i can't wait to drew me something
that's so cute
uh
birthday
to you
happy birthday
love you
happy
okay
[Laughter]
happy birthday
thank you you know
how are you
i'm okay i'm nervous oh it's okay it's
okay i come to calm things down before
everything
everything goes into chaos i mean she's
already here but i mean yeah hi
even more hi
how are you
good
i just woke up
good morning
good morning i passed out yeah
[Music]
actually i don't really decide to do it
actually i did that one time i i sent
you like uh
that's the thing yeah so oh exactly so
happy when you send that to me i get
really happy
yeah like that
i saw it and i was like oh my god i need
to show mommy yeah she needs to know
this
yes
do you want me to ask you a question oh
sure
what's your favorite animal
i think chad already knows this answer
but it's uh it's a cafe bar i had a
feeling it was a candy bar
i had a feeling you would say cat before
can i ask you why
they're so like chill
and they're like so cool with all the
animals like even if like a bird
sits on its head or like a cat like uses
it uses as a bed like anything else like
they're just so chill you know and they
get along with everyone
i think like that's something something
people should you know aim towards be
chill with everyone
made it even more beautiful i know you
mean i see so many pictures of cappy
bars with different animals
yeah and you see the pictures of them
it's just like them just chilling in the
in the hot tub with the
little beacon on their head with the
waterfall falling on though it's like
man
i wish i could be like that
yeah
okay
interesting interesting
thank you for coming by did you
did you know this that before hollow
live i watched you the most never heard
that
i think i heard you mention it before
yeah maybe yeah
we should we should we should play more
games together down here
yes please
it was so fun playing fortnite with you
yesterday
the two games we got together yeah
it was worth it
yeah you're you were in ash because i
was watching you right
oh no no no
i still got a long way to go
i think by this point you played more
than i
oh that's good yeah i would love to play
more games yes yeah let's do it
okay
anyways i want you happy happy happy
birthday
yes i hope you have a wonderful day
thank you you too okay i can see you two
to that okay
you have to think about it a little bit
i feel you
okay
yes i wanted the wah
by the way is the volume okay guys is
are they too quiet am i
you quiet is it equal
do not be shy please let me know
oh i'll let you know
oh
will you let me know
yes you sound just fine
thank
yeah of you
happy birthday
thank you cronie
and i like your cover
it's like one of my favorite songs
[Music]
why
i don't know i didn't expect it to be
one of your favorite songs
it is actually do you like the dandan
songs yeah the dondan songs like
but like that one you chose specifically
yeah oh yeah it's a good one
yeah i
i love them too
i love them too oh my gosh she's
listening to danda dieha
all the time yeah
yeah that that was like my favorite
ah interesting i didn't i didn't
know i didn't know this
yeah but good job
thank you it shows
thank you
yeah you treating yourself for a
birthday
ah
not yet maybe later maybe later i'll get
a snack
what kind of snack i don't know i don't
know what will be open um
subway
you know some ways that was really good
i think i might have some subway oh what
did you get from subway again
uh meatball oh yeah yeah right
and and chicken
meatball and chip oh you mean like those
are the two or you get them together
i get like
two foot longs so that i can have them
for later oh i remember this yeah
yeah yeah i remember this
because you've done that before oh
not smart that's really smart
i get a phone too we're like yeah i save
it
yeah hey smart
it's your mm-hmm flavors flavor of
sandwich two flavors yeah
i see i see what do you get
i usually get the veggie
oh the veggie oh healthy nice no it's
not even healthy it's just cheaper
i'm used to getting the cheapest thing i
can get
uh
it's good yeah it's like a salad between
bread
yeah i mean it's it's healthy it's good
for you
unfortunately i don't like good things
for me oh
oh yeah
i don't like healthy things right you
don't eat your veggies i'll eat your
veggies for you
yeah thank you mm-hmm i'll take good
asparagus
can i do that
all right maybe i think i took your
asparagus you didn't want it
oh yeah i remember
yeah it's like your asparagus
good times
good times good times
yeah
and
yeah i just uh wanted to tell you happy
birthday and
please be sure to enjoy yourself with
your whole mans thank you
thank you for coming by
of course and
hmm
i just wanted to say that
your voice
so cute
stop
sorry girl i just wanted to say that
girl you're gonna make me fuss
i mean
that's that's the plan okay
[Music]
okay bye girl bye girl bye
bye girl bye
bye
akudo yes to me don't sleep yet okay bye
what the heck
that made me fuzzer i wasn't i didn't
know what she i didn't know what she was
gonna say
hi
hello
birthday
[Music]
thank you
where's your picture
your your video was so cute
this year cute owl can do no wrong
cute owl can do whatever she wants to do
well i don't really do anything i
watched
exactly see see you did nothing wrong
exactly i just watched can't get in
trouble just for watching and doing
nothing and not helping and just
observing and staring while everything
burns that's fine to do i mean uh it's
not like that's what you do i'm just
taking off after you when did i do that
when did you make things burn and
destroy things did i i when did i just
watch
i i tried forever
what fire are you talking about there's
been many fires fauna which fire
figurative fire or literal fire oh i'm
thinking just about the history of earth
oh you know
when it used to be on fire sometimes
fire is necessary for new trees to grow
exactly
exactly as soon as fire is necessary
even for civilization to grow
oh
that's an interesting way of thinking
about it and i have something for you
yeah
oh i do
i wanna people
oh no it's so cute
i wanted to perfectly capture your
cuteness
i got it oh i'm so slow at setting these
up oh hold on hold on do i make this an
image or
that medium image will work i think
this file format is supported okay
i think
yes i think
yes it's you it's mermaids her it's me
it is real
nice looking observing
i do i do that
you know it took a second for it to load
so i was just thinking okay
and then i think oh that's so cute and
then and then you know
it loaded
and i thought oh that's so cute
i wanted to make it uh more subtle it's
a little bit blinking i wanted it to
wait like a whole a whole minute before
it flashed but i couldn't
do it i mean i don't know how to make
gifts
technically it did that for me
yeah
thank you discord yeah thank you discord
for being slow
thank you discord
it's really cute i like how you did the
eyelashes too
yeah don't you have luscious lashes
beautiful
oh thank you
what a cute owl oh what a cute
[Music]
oh nice nice and obedient
good owl good owl i'm a good good owl
yeah happy birthday i like your the
place you got here i know bae mentioned
five nights at freddy's he really does
really does contour
the image of five nights at freddy's
yeah i don't even play that game
maybe you should i don't know
maybe i should
you should i think i'll get a scary vr
version too okay maybe i don't do that
but
it's one of the scariest games for me
personally i don't know why though it's
kind of silly it feels like it shouldn't
be scary but then it is i know it does
have its fair share of like really
sudden jump scares yeah that's the thing
like loud music yeah that that it gets
you it gets you i'm expecting that bay
animatronic back there to come to life
at any moment
stuff somebody's lifeless corpse inside
is that lore
really
yes okay you're not just making it okay
you didn't just think of that okay
it could be your lore too oh well not
maybe not you
in the suit but you know
maybe
oh wait maybe it's my demise
oh that would be too sad though
that's pretty bad way to go i guess so i
guess you have unlimited imagination for
that sort of thing
worse
happy birthday movie thank you you are
allowed to observe as many atrocities as
you want thank you
thank you i'll try to create a natural
disaster just for you oh wonderful thank
you oh god
that's a joke that's a joke it's a joke
if anything happens it wasn't hurt it
wasn't me
thank you
[Music]
otherwise you can't see anything you
can't tell what it is
hello
oh on the birthday oh thank you
wait you're not funny hold on oh sorry
[Music]
happy birthday to my guardian of
civilization because
i'm a human too oh are you now
are you really
i believe it thank you
yeah
thank you
oh can i ask you a question
yes please what is your favorite animal
oh
i like mud skippers have you heard of
them before mud skippers i mean the
pokemon pokemon hold on
oh yeah they're kind of like a pokemon
oh i've seen these before
yeah they like they go out of water and
they they like fight by opening their
mouth really wide
and they're really dumb looking and cute
you answered my next question which was
why are they your favorite animals
is that yeah they're really bad looking
well and it's kind of cool because
they're i think they're classified as
amphibians but they're pretty similar to
fish oh isn't that they look like fish
out of water like they look like gobies
which are
a cute type of fish but they can go on
land
it's really cute
and cute and
stupid those go together
quite often yeah
elsa i made this for you speaking of
animals
[Laughter]
yeah one of my skills is also uh balloon
animals so uh
oh wait i'm so slow i'm gonna share it
so
hold on i got it i'm just gonna name
them random things now i was actually
naming everything thank you oh properly
you're welcome yay
it's uh
well actually it's a net it's just an
animal yeah we'll just leave it at that
animal
yeah yeah okay
thank you wow you're full of
so many unknown talents your skills
thank you actually a loot animal is kind
of scary because if you i feel like i
always pop it every time i try
like actually i don't think that often
yeah
you never tried
i haven't tried before no i used to be
really scared of the sound of balloons
popping so it sounds cool yeah it sounds
horrible to me
right yeah that's why it's kind of scary
yeah then they pop in your hands oh
no no no no no no no
i heard i heard you ask bae if she could
do like an animal impression but he said
can i ask you to do one that you're the
birthday girl right
okay i'll try
uh okay how about frog
yeah that's good i was gonna ask for a
giraffe then i realized that
did your abs make sounds um they must
you know what i do i probably just slap
my hand because the sound of them you
know fighting
other necklaces
i feel like they make noises like
something like that
i don't know let's do something with
that tongue
yeah
do something
besides
plants
i bet
okay
i googled it
i haven't had a chat you guys know i
haven't even heard it but i'm i feel
like that was actually super accurate
it's pretty scary holy it's like
really deep grumble isn't it i'm gonna
have to look it up later
curious i don't think i've heard a
giraffe before
spooky
interesting all right well i'll jump out
now but uh happy birthday good luck on
the rest of the stream i'm looking
forward to your announcement oh and your
song earlier was so cute thank you thank
you so
[Laughter]
[Music]
much she actually makes balloon animals
what a skill to have
that doesn't require that many
you could probably just carry the stuff
you need in a backpack and pull it out
whenever that's such a good skill to
have
happy birthday
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay
uh
[Music]
um
i love cats the most
rarely but sometimes they are very sweet
to me
yes i see
[Music]
favorite cat
my favorite your favorite animal
my favorite animal um
[Music]
freeze my
promise so
hi
i want to clap
come on
do you like
game
um
[Music]
oh
bye
[Music]
i didn't think she'd ask me
i didn't think she would ask me what my
favorite animal was i wasn't ready for
that
cute
[Music]
oops
oh my gosh i'm shaking i
didn't expect her to come so early oh
i think it's early for her
who's there
hello
hi
wait
i don't have it i do have to be sorry i
need to find you
guess who this is
wait who is this
who is this
who could this possibly be
[Laughter]
i don't know who you are either
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah what i was concerned i was like oh
no is it really did she just wake up is
it too early for her oh no
yeah i mean that is part of it that is
part of it no it's not it's not a
cronium pressure or anything like that
no no no
i was just i was gonna say i was trying
to say something funny and then nothing
came up so i was just so i'm just like
okay deep voice videos but yeah i
thought that was pretty funny
that's good to hear
hi
hi ross
[Music]
why are you in a why why are you having
like a chuck e cheese party
[Music]
is that is that
animatronic doll what is that that is
yes that is
oh man does that mean that if she opens
her mouth she can like literally eat
children
i have not played
that game
whatever
that's what you were going for right
that's sort of that's sort of vibe right
no but i guess well i guess it works out
yeah it totally fits i just learned i've
just been learning the lore so can you
imagine say goes to someone who doesn't
know that apparently children were
stuffed into the mouths of animatronics
yeah
i can't i can't watch the gameplay i
can't i can never play anything like
that but
yeah but yeah i do know the lore the
lord is interesting oh i see i see yeah
it was really scary is it because it's
scary or like the visuals just jump
scary like that's the main thing about
it
everything is jump scare from left to
right yeah i'm not a fan of those either
yeah it's just it just makes you scream
24 7 so i
that's the whole point of jump scares
right so yeah
uh
i see i see
ah should i should i ask you a question
i'm sure
that works
let me should i ask you the same
question or should i ask a new question
uh i have no idea just what comes it's
okay um
what were the questions
um i'll ask you i'll ask you this i'm
curious what is your favorite animal
oh animals
turtles
turtles why are turtles your favorite
animal
because they're so slow and cute
because they're slow
i don't know they're they're cute i
don't know whenever like i see them like
in pet stores eating like um
you know like uh cabbage or lettuce it
looks so cute like munching on it like
taking forever doing anything
this is adorable i don't know
have you i've seen them eat fruit like
uh strawberries
uh-huh and they get so messy they're so
slow but then their little mouths get
yeah like i i've seen like um videos of
them eating like strawberries and it
looks like a murder scene yeah it
doesn't look like guts around their
mouths like spilling out strawberries
what is your favorite animal
i didn't expect people to ask him
like i feel like i'm supposed to know
this but i actually don't like it if
it's not dogs what is it why would it be
dogs i know because you have animals
you have animal you think that oh that's
probably your favorite animal or is that
just because you can keep it as a pet
i do like those animals
those animals yeah dogs are pretty i do
like dogs a lot
i'm a dog person over a cat person i
like cats too
yeah i know and i feel like i'm i'm more
of like a cat person but that's mainly
because i'm i'm just not used to being
like licked
oh my dogs
i see
like i just had to say by dogs because i
mean it's just it just sounded awkward
the whole way
i only noticed how awkward that sounded
and then that's why i decided to add my
dogs but then i noticed that my actually
that actually sounds horrible never mind
but i noticed it until you said that
but yeah i'm not used to it i'm not used
to it i hate i i kind of don't like it
like in general i mean i can't like it
either
yeah i know that it's like a way of them
like um
i don't know showing affection but like
ever since i was a kid
like whenever some other like
like elementary school classmates would
like bring their dogs to school
i would just freak out and like run away
from the dog which is like the dog yes
which would make the dog chase me and
and yeah
okay they're like oh you're playing
you're running away yeah they think that
i'm playing with them but no i'm
actually screaming in terror like please
don't lick me
oh that's interesting that's you're not
scared i mean it is gross you get i
guess you get used to it when it's like
i don't know your hand or
your face but i always hate when it's
the nostril or the ear i hate that oh
that's it
my grandparents had a dog
back in the day
and um i still remember like visiting my
grandparents house as a kid and like
there it was a poodle the poodle's
really cute but i remember like it would
greet
like my mom with like a really really
sloppy kiss like all over her mouth like
they would try to get in like you know
into the mouth so i'm just like that's
that's kind of like
yeah so traumatized maybe like
i had a friend who had a lab a labrador
that was so slobbery and
when i was small it would like knock me
over to lick my face
uh yeah i think you'd be drenched out
it's disgusting but it's that one i know
it's like you know i know it's supposed
to be affectionate and it's it's
supposed to be cute and
yeah but i i just i i don't know maybe i
have i have a small
i don't know no it's okay i don't think
most people like that i would i would
assume most people do not actually enjoy
that part
okay i feel like i feel like i would i
would be able to handle it now i still
find them really cute and all like i
still find really cute dogs adorable but
yeah that's the only part i just can't
get used to as well
[Music]
oh yeah sorry i think i've been keeping
you for a while
i'm sorry
okay i asked the question and you you
gave me you gave me answers thank you
yes yes i gave you an a plus answer all
right thank you
all right the next person's waiting so
i'm gonna head out then happy birthday
mummy your dawn dawn cover was adorable
thank you thank you
thank you for coming bye too bye
bye bye happy birthday
hello
literally wake up i'm late no no no it's
okay it's okay this is good time it's
okay
thank you thank you for coming i know
you've been busy
yeah thank you thank you for the
invitation
[Music]
how are you doing
uh
well overall it's been good last night i
i slept late because uh i was like doing
the minecraft thingy for the next
project oh okay okay i haven't fixed the
bunker honey don't worry i will fix that
later once never miss all the things
okay i was i was worried you were up
late fixing it
would i would i destroy it i was
ah
well you're so good at minecraft i can't
i wish i wish to learn a bit more i'm
really bad at it
you want to learn with me yes please
character
i don't know just tell me what you
wanted me and
i will figure around and teach you a
little bit if you if you have the time i
would love to learn more i know nothing
about building
well i think uh
start from the next week i'm pretty sure
oh okay yeah okay i can ask i'll uh i'll
i'll message you i'd love to learn more
like useful
yeah or if you ever want to play other
games too let me know i don't think
we've talked much
have we talked before
no
we haven't talked much we're just like
doing our own things busy with our own
things and so yeah oh well i'd love to
talk more if you have time
or if you want to do stuff
okay i will i'll
i will try to talk
it's just like
i just like i i i don't know like
whenever i want to talk with someone i
just like get anxiety over you will is
it is this good is it not just like that
oh don't you don't have to worry with me
because i get the same with new people
don't worry i'm always happy
to talk you don't have to worry
i feel you
that's why i don't message you
okay
happy birthday i
i don't know uh probably i had to go
because i'm i'm literally late i need to
go too it's okay
thank you thank you for coming bye bye
bye
i don't think i have spoken to her
in a call before
i've only messaged her ah i knew she was
busy i'm i feel bad i'm happy she came
by oh thank you
[Music]
mommy
oh
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
hmm
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
i
it's the first time we are talking along
like
yeah i came here to sleep late because i
wanted to talk to you
later
[Music]
english
yeah i drive i'd love to club late with
you on the song someday
yes i want to
[Music]
and your
artistic sense of
drawing
when i see her drawings on a new product
[Music]
favorite manga to
wiki
with information
favorite manga
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe we have the same taste i think
it gets along well to me
hi i'm looking forward to working with
you ah thank you
me too
good night
thank you thank you
hi
hi hi
[Music]
i'm so bad i'm sorry
i'm sorry i didn't
hello
happy birthday to you
mom i just woke up so my voice is a
little crackly happy birthday to him
good morning
thank you
thank you thank you for waking up by the
way
oh yeah it's really not that early it's
just you know how i do oh yeah i know i
can be the same i take my midday naps
yeah i wonder if those make it any worse
but i can't help absolutely
gosh darn it i had a special drawing i
wanted to give you but it's not quite
done it's it's a little
it's a little special but i'm going to
post it on twitter so just keep your
keep your eyes peeled for it because i
want to make sure that it really like
gets across like how i how i feel about
about you
and what i see when i look at you i
think feel like oh yeah i'm so excited
it's special
yeah okay i'll be out
i'll be on the lookout
guys like a hawk
i got them i my poor allies but i got
them
yeah you've been getting a lot of gifts
today huh
should i ask you a question
sure i'm an open book fireman monster
what's your favorite animal
a cat
it's kind of boring but cat people are
gonna say lemur they're gonna say no
you're lying callie
it was a lemur shout out to cat
cat did you say lemur because someone
said cat wasn't a good enough answer
you're like fine i'll be exotic
well you know what yes and no basically
i want it to be special
but
you know
cats are special enough
lemur would maybe be number two and then
fox
wait a minute informing me
do you have a persona
no they made that up for me i made a
mistake a long time ago on twitter
somebody asked me if i had a for sale or
something like that
i responded
yes that i would be a lemur but that was
because i was thinking about what kind
of ears would i have if i was to become
a holo men with ears and i was like well
everyone's a cat so i'd be a lemur
because i wanted to be special
and then i didn't realize for whatever
reason i had responded to a tweet asking
about a fursona situation
and i was like wait
no i don't actually have one of those
and thus began the long chain of
furry art that is this come it's fine
it's fine i did lose like 5 000
followers from that but it was super
funny so i didn't really care it was uh
it was some interesting
and interesting part in my lore
so
yeah
i i i guess i missed this arc of
kevin yeah
finding your persona
no it's better that you missed it so to
be honest ringtail lemurs do have really
nice ringtail tails that are like very
special you know cattails are cool and
whatever but if i had a tail like
attached to me as well as like lemur
ears i definitely want like a lemur tail
with rings on it well what about you
oh yeah oh you mean like the the ring
markings or actual rings on it oh no
bling the bling would be kind of neat i
guess kind of interesting quirky
what about you mame what would you be
would i be it
yeah wait what's the question
what would i be for ears what ears would
i want oh yeah i'll state it i'll state
it very clearly so that you don't get in
the same trouble that i did yes if you
could have ears on uh on your model what
would you choose
ah what would i choose
no idea
kind of hard huh i feel like cat here
i'll probably probably if i i mean
probably dog ears
that would be so cute i like dogs
i feel like we don't have enough dog
here i mean we have of course our our
god
senpai
but i feel like there are there just
aren't enough like dog ears you know i'd
love to see that at least floppy dog
ears
yeah oh that would be cute
i'm imagining it
cute
i love that
well mummy you have a wonderful birthday
okay i've got my my trigger finger over
whatever you may have
for in store for us not to say that you
will have anything because it's
never a required thing but if you do i
buy
oh
oh i still yeah
so i'm excited also i loved your i loved
your uh song
thank you
[Music]
it made me laugh super hard at the end
when you pulled out the knife i like
that
that's good thank you tell me your true
colors
yeah
of course yeah never stop being yourself
that's because
we know what you're we know we know how
you are
so sweet so adorable so secretly
sadistic i mean oh no
just kidding
so so sweet and full of adorable just
don't worry about it it's cute i like
gap so you're fine thank you thank you
yeah never stop being yourself mommy
have a have a fantastic birthday i'm
gonna
i'm gonna go die i'll see you later good
night good good rest callie thank you
for coming will do
of course enjoy the rest of your
birthday bye bye
bye bye bye
you never know what conversations you'll
have i guess during these
birthday collins my goodness
sure
hello
hello can you hear me i can hear you
hi movie happy birthday
thank you good morning
good morning
yeah what a nice place
where is this where is this place
it is that's nice i want to go
to movies and book my birthday party
there
have a special we have a really nice
berry buffet
let's go that's so nice that's so good
that you have a fairy buffet i hope
you're having
lots of fun eating berries on your
on your special day
i just
i just woke up and then i saw i heard
the conversation after this it was
really really interesting i thought like
oh my gosh that's not interesting but
what yeah
what do we talk about are we really
gonna talk about
ears or lemurs no i don't think we're
gonna do that
i could ask you a different question
oh you could you could
what should i ask you
you should
ask me
yes
no nothing
nothing
i want you to dare
okay um i'll ask you what do you like to
do when you aren't streaming i feel like
i know some of the answers but
when i'm not streaming i like to
um
craft thumbnails alone unleash my
creativity
be alone and
reply my manager and discard i don't
know yeah that's the i i love doing the
same things too i
am so good at those things
oh so relatable also i like um playing
with my cat that's it oh yeah i have a
pet cow kitty cat i am yeah i've seen a
picture or two i remember
hey
you did
yeah super cute
oh that's so soft
did you did you own a pet i forgot i
have an animal
oh animal i know i know i know i have
heard about the legendary animal yes yes
yes
so cute
i was gonna say but you are the cutest
animal but you are not really an animal
right are you an animal i sometimes i
take the form of an owl and i guess i'm
as a human i'm an animal but no matter
what what what you are saying is not
true they're there's far cuter
nah
you know as a part of a fellow holotori
i am obligated to you know
to you know represent like come on you
are you are the cute the cute bird even
though you're not a bird but when you're
with us you are a bird so
everybody's a cute bird though
everybody's a cute bird
is shot a cute bird
not oh not them i meant
oh wow wow wow that shift of tone right
there not them no no not then no oh not
them all right all right then all right
but you you okay you are a cute bird is
what i'm trying oh
oh okay okay thank you thank you thank
you thank you you are too you are too
so
[Music]
i
i have a question what for you
i have a question for you
if you
were to
well what would be
your favorite thing
to do
if
you
were an animal you're not an animal
right i don't know sorry i'm just so
sleep deprived it's okay this is no this
is a great question what would be my
favorite thing to do if i was an animal
um exactly i'd like to be an animal that
sleeps like 18 to 20 hours out of the
day
no
so i probably sleep a lot oh i'd like to
be a bear and hibernate
a bear but does a bear eat berries bears
bears eat berries
or something bears
i guess so
bear eating
the berry eating bear yes that sounds
nice thank you for answering my question
on your happy happy happy birthday i
hope you have a
wonderful one
thank you for letting me call you
yes we're waking up just to call thank
you
[Music]
um the recipes
okay bye bye
bye bye
i did not expect to be asked i'm not
supposed to ask no i'm supposed to be
the one asking the questions they're not
supposed to
they're not supposed to ask me questions
i'm not prepared i'm supposed to make
them get all flustered
who
thank you hi
so before before i say anything y'all i
want to say to the viewers that movie
actually got me a birthday present
oh
yeah actually you got me a birthday
present right
so cute thank goodness
you're welcome i felt i didn't know
where when to show us i was like you
know i'll just send it to you
i'm glad oh liked it
i really like it thank you
[Music]
so did you have a good birthday today
it's been good it's been a little
stressful but now it's pretty it's
pretty chill right now
oh really it's pretty chill right now
okay you're okay yeah yeah it's good
it's good how's your day oh
normal it was it was normal but
today i met you i met you
oh it's okay
it is good i see i see oh you're welcome
thank you you made my day literally
literally if you make my day how are you
i'm so i'm so glad you can make it thank
you thank you for coming i have a
question for you if that's okay
yeah
yeah sure oh a quiz okay let's go what
is your favorite animal
ah
you don't want to ask that
is it is it
gonna have some kind of
anything's okay yes anything
anything
uh it's um it's
actually cockroach yes roach cockroach
yep how come why
i
i i don't know that i mean they they are
hated by a lot of a lot of people so i
just kind of like
i i don't know
they're cute so there's there's an
outgoing
um like a big cockroach is i i forgot
what's the species name but it was so
big it's so
it doesn't look like coke brush but it
is a cockroach i forgot what's the
species name but it's really cute
yes i've noticed when bugs are over a
certain size they become a bit cuter
yeah it is that's why it's really good i
noticed that
[Music]
they interesting interesting themselves
like
that's right they're interesting
see
yeah they're really good
you can have a favorite animal for any
reason doesn't have to be it doesn't
even have to be oh it's cute oh it's
it's soft it can it could be that is
just an interesting animal but you think
they're cute yeah
the bigger one um
[Music]
thank you you should really touch it
sometimes the big one i forgot what's
the name oh my god so yeah
it's not bitter like it's it's a
cockroach but actually like in the size
of a beetle
i've touched that before um why is it
called again oh my god i forgot
i'm weird
freaking american
or something
like maybe you can go big booker or
something there's a few species that are
big
maybe
they're actually don't don't move a lot
oh they don't move a lot
oh they didn't move too much
they don't grow too much so they get
this kind of like stays in burger but
it's still like a crock but
yeah it's really good
that's not
interesting yeah
yep yep yep and they don't cry too
and they don't fight them
new thing for you guys and new memes so
thank you so much for having me yeah
thank you for coming thank you thank you
you happy birthday and i love you bye
love you bye bye
cockroach that's a cool answer actually
look where would she go
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
no
okay
[Music]
thank you
uh
[Music]
is
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
drop you want me to draw you
hi
[Music]
i
hello
[Music]
um
wait
[Music]
[Laughter]
i love you
[Music]
hmm
oh
[Music]
what is your favorite game
my favorite hmm
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
foreign
oh my gosh
wait wait hold on one second i
i made a mistake i don't have her
drawing or her icon
oh no photocap but of course it was
porka of course
you didn't even need to have her on
screen but i'm going to get her real
quick let's see let's see let's see ah
i am so slow i'm sorry i thought i got
everybody but i mean
i haven't oh no
i'm doubting myself
i'm absolutely doubting myself one
second
let me get
here
everything is unorganized there we go oh
there she is oh
man
[Music]
i haven't thought of you wait where are
you all right yo disappeared i actually
don't she was there
but she disappeared uh hold on
where did she go i actually don't know
what happened to eop
it says she's
i tried resetting it but that
did not seem to work
what the oh there she hello
i really don't know what happened to her
but she's here now she's here now okay
i'll put her
wait when i was not in order oh gosh
hold on i'm gonna start putting
everybody here
this is my
break right now organizing the icons
but i have people waiting so i want to
be fast okay hold on
it's out of order again i know i see it
i see it i i understand i see it i don't
i don't know how to think okay and then
there we go
okay
okay there we go
oh yeah i don't have everything outside
inside
i hope i have everybody
it's not enough
hello
hi
hi how are you
i'm
quite greedy yeah sleep deprived a
little bit
better
oh thank you for coming i hope you can
sleep more
yeah it's okay obviously i saw some of
your tweets why why aren't you sleeping
oh yeah last night um i was rushing for
the minecraft thingy
yeah
and yeah i woke up to finish it actually
today yeah
goodness do you sleep enough usually
yeah yeah sleep enough yeah i mean
i'm the amount of sleep that everybody
has like
kind of different right like someone
probably can sleep like for eight hours
and still feel tired but
there is
uh people that
just need to sleep like six hours and
they got very refreshed i think
which one you're right
i don't know i feel like if i sleep like
eight hours i got very dizzy
so you need less than eight
yeah
less than yeah probably five or six yeah
yeah i i can't tell how much i need to
sleep because i'm always tired when i
wake up
whether i sleep three hours six hours
eight hours or four days oh
oh really yeah okay 14 yeah i see those
eyes as long as you get enough for
yourself
yeah
thank you for coming even though you're
tired
it's okay thank you for inviting me too
yeah i have a i have a question for you
oh yeah a question yeah what is it
what's your favorite animal
oh animal um
dolphin dolphin interesting
why
ah i don't think why um
the reason is probably because
dolphin has a very big brain
big brain yeah
big brain
yeah
that's a good reason
yeah i i i just i just find it very cool
to have like animals with big brains
i want to have big brains though your
brain seems pretty big
not because like your head is big i i
was saying you you're smart
oh okay
thank you then yeah you seem smart yeah
i seem smart yeah yeah thank you
[Laughter]
oh pretty cool that's really cool oh
interesting interesting
everyone's giving me really interesting
answers
oh yeah yeah i i heard that previously
too so have you decided what's your
favorite animal now
well mine is
yeah let's play i actually told sort of
senpai that they said something similar
to you i said whales and i said because
they have a good head like because
they're smart ah
oh
i see
similar okay you have similar tastes
nice nice nice
thank you thank you for coming hey
okay thank you enjoy your birthday
thank you i hope you get a little more
sleep maybe or
[Music]
very interesting answers here a lot of
donut i don't know what i expect from
people actually that's what i'm asking i
have no idea
[Music]
hello
hello happy birthday
[Music]
hello
oh
[Music]
um
more cake
[Music]
sauce
i'm a quilter
[Music]
oh
the freedom of being a cat because dogs
are canines are too loyal
yes yes yes ah
[Music]
see you
it's
[Music]
come on
oh
oh thank you for showing it
[Music]
i
[Laughter]
okay
i will
i will draw you
yeah i want to draw you okay okay
thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
okay
oh my goodness
she's so
cute
she's so cute
i tried to
in dm's it was kind of sad because
she said she wants to speak more and i
said i want to speak more but we don't
speak
the same language
translate oh she wants a drawing
she said anything's okay oh no
oh careful careful
let me put this in the
spot here
there you go there we go okay
all right
ready for whoever is next
hello
happy birthday
to
you
happy birthday
to you
[Music]
hello
i know
we played we played ark together yes
so
hmm
i have
been practicing
my
english
sorry i'm not good at speaking
angry
no i you i like you
you are good you are good at english
well thank you so happy i remember
i got those thank you spread
so the game with me so before us thank
will you
my best to study english so that
i
can
communicate with
her ian senpai so
i'm amazing
[Music]
oh i want to learn japanese
uh
to talk
to
you all to talk to you more too
oh thank you
okay i told
japanese
for
you
[Laughter]
thank you yes
thank you
you know
more english than i know japanese
[Music]
yes
year your birthday so pink and white so
use something present for you
oh i see
i remember oh yeah okay okay oh thank
you
thank you
[Music]
happy birthday have a nice day thank you
have a nice day too
arigatou thank you
bye bye
oh no she was so cute i forgot to ask
her a question
oh no
she asked me a question
oh hello
hello
hi
is this
brown hair brown gang don't care
[Music]
let's go
oh yeah
yeah but still
that's a big it's a big group so hard to
talk yeah
yeah we didn't talk much on that collab
hello how is the birthday party it's
good it's going good how are you doing
i'm good i'm i'm kind of lacking sleep
but this is fine
this is fun life is fine that's what
happens every day oh it happens
yeah
i have something for you oh wait let me
let me
let me send the thing
can you can you see it i see it
cute
look at me
oh it's so cute
right here hope you like it i love this
facial but
no i hope you like it
i want it oh there we go now i save it
oh there it is
oh it's so big
oh my goodness thank you
yeah happy birthday
thank you happy birthday we should
definitely play something together again
oh yes please yes please um
what game have you been playing these
days
i don't i've been playing that much
i'll play anything i like to play games
with other people anything we can play
anything
yeah i i saw you playing russ i was just
about to say
once you get the hang of the game i
think you'll have fun with it
i think so too i've been seeing a uh
seamlessly uh jp play
i've seen you play a little bit but
usually oh you usually stream when i
sleep but
yeah oh isn't that
okay real quick i have a question for
you oh
sure what is your favorite animal
my favorite animal
these days
i have been into flamingos lately
flamingos oh that's cool yeah
wow yeah i've been into flamingos lately
i think more people need to perceive
flamingos they're kind of underrated
yeah i don't know they they have they
have an interesting anatomy i love i
love the long legs and i love the neck
it kind of kind of it's like shaped like
ass like an s you know the long neck
yeah yeah yeah i think it's pretty
interesting i think it's interesting too
when you really think about it
they are
very bizarre very bizarre yeah that's
that's that's why i like them that's why
i like them they have the mysterious
like feeling to them you know
mm-hmm well that's a that's a good
answer for me yeah
what about yours
when i asked this question i didn't
expect people to
ask me well doesn't have to be your
favorite maybe can
can be like something like an animal you
have been interested
in lately you know oh actually yeah so
i've been watching some videos about
eagles
oh
eagles yeah i love them they're watching
them i love them
videos of eagles hunting
oh fishing when they fish
oh
it's really cool it's kind of crazy it's
really cool eagles are really cool
i like a bunch of birds i love birds
i like birds too
yeah
same let's go
i'd love to play i'd love to play rest
with you
i should have more free time hopefully
soon now that this is the birthday so
yeah we need more free time
it's okay after after your birthday
yeah it's gonna be well for me for me
after my birthday like
i i got like some free time before that
it's like packed my schedule is like
packed and everything but
after after the birthday
yeah if you don't have like any free day
or like free schedule let's definitely
do it
okay okay i'll i'll check in with you
yeah
okay
thank you for coming
thank you for having me and hopefully
you're gonna have a blast today have fun
thank you
[Music]
brown bye-bye
hair don't care
short brown hair do not care sister
okay let's see i think we can um
i think
oh wait
let me see what's the time
i have to check
i don't care okay um
i think we're going to take a little
break
oh i'm sorry to the person waiting i'm
sorry for the person waiting oh
we're gonna take a little break um so i
cannot show you guys merch that's not
supposed to do now right
am i supposed to show the merch now
oh there's gonna be there's gonna be
more calls after this by the way
it's not is now the time
oh let's see
what this is this is a mixed answer hold
on yes okay
okay okay
all right i have
not done something like this before
please bear with me
okay
why am i so nervous about this
would you guys
would you guys happen to be
interested in uh
some
merchandise
or maybe you don't know you don't maybe
you don't know yet would you like to at
least
at least to see what what would be
offered
first i'm going to procrastinate and
drink water hold on
suspense okay suspend i need water
hold on
okay there's a layout issue
let me figure this out
oh no well there it is i guess um i've
i've messed up i have made a few
mistakes here hold on a second hold on a
second
there we go that looks better i i messed
that up you see what the problem is
though you can't see it oh gosh of
course it's scuffed anyway
merchandise merchandise in a second let
me you know what i do this
aha oh my gosh the answer was so simple
it was so simple okay
here we go here we go pretty good
[Music]
there we go
i'm ready
polka's just the polka can stay
polka can stay there okay
i have merchandise it is not going on
sale tomorrow it is currently the fifth
in japan
that's why it says on sale august 5th it
is not the fifth though
in
other parts of the world so it is going
on sale in approximately eight minutes
maybe
maybe seven minutes if the latest
because of latency uh
it'll be going on sale in eight minutes
so i have eight minutes to talk about
this merchandise with you but as you can
see
we have beautiful beautiful beautiful
art by azu papa
all right i also want you to scoot over
hold on honey
yeah
i'm
any more suspenseful all right here we
go
[Music]
this is the merchandise
this is the complete set of the
merchandise we have a journal
journal actually
let me see how can i
how do i sell this do you often forget
things
do things often slip your mind
are you one of those people that no i
should do this actually i'll do this
later anyway this is the merchandise so
we have a we have my journal we have
we have a hootsie plushie coming out a
houthi plushie we have a friend pencil
pouch which goes with the journal
so you can put all your pencils and pens
have them nearby and there
and then we have this feather bookmark
um i'll i guess i'll go into more detail
when we get to get to the slides and
i'll try to sell it to all of you that's
right
and also a bonus postcard i'm gonna post
card with illustration by azure zoo papa
by papa
oh hi am i so nervous okay
let's see let's see it
so this is the bonus for
uh the complete set if you decide to buy
the assistant order
if you decide to buy the complete set
you get a postcard
with the visuals just so pretty look at
all the flowers and the windmills oh
it's so pretty
um
let me see yeah so first gamers i have
to read it the birthday image completes
that limited edition this is for the
limited edition um
yeah of the complete set as i just as i
just read out um what makes it limited
is that it comes with a handwritten
autograph
from me
so i will be handwriting
autographs
onto these postcards
for you
that's what makes it limited
that i don't get carpal tunnel yes
[Music]
um it comes with a duplicated foil
stamped autograph
so it's not a real audit
it's my autograph but it wasn't
handwritten by me i didn't uh
you know use my cave woman grip to write
well i guess i used it to write that one
but
i didn't
do it
just for yours like i don't know how to
explain it
yeah
so
what is that
yep did i explain that correctly let's
win it correctly a limited edition is a
real autograph
and then
uh not limit unlimited is coil stamped
autograph i didn't write that one that
is my autograph anyway uh next thing we
don't have much time oh no
let's see let's see
there we go now i'm gonna try to sell
this journal to all of you are you
forgetful are you forgetful like a
certain owl a certain alley you may be
watching right now do you perhaps have
to write your thoughts down so that you
don't lose them completely
well well well what do we have here the
perfect thing for you a journal a
journal to keep track of all those
hideous horrendous
dark thoughts that you may have for you
to write down
or just you know if you have groceries
or errands you need to run or maybe you
have something you need to do and you
need to write a little reminder for
yourself or maybe you want to write some
stories
or maybe you want to keep a journal of i
don't know my streams if you so please i
don't you could use it for anything yeah
me i wonder if i can make it a little
bigger can you see
it's a bit hard to see here i'll
probably be able to see it better
on the website oh gosh um
i'm sorry this is so scuffed uh so you
can see it has a little we have a little
friend drawing i actually made the
drawing on the front a friend
and then it says
on the back and inside is the visual the
illustration that azu papa did
and then we have on this
uh one of the first pages you can write
your little names that i don't know if
you want to do that if you write your
dark thoughts but you can write your
name there in case you lose it all your
personal information so it can be a
return look at the little framing around
the journal too
it's really really cute
yeah yeah yeah yeah
sorry let's see if i can readjust it i'm
sure you'll be able to see it much
better on the website if you wish to
look at it
okay and then next thing
set up the journal
and then we have a little hootsie plush
do you just know after having him sit on
my sit on my desk for so long and on my
lap that
he had to be made into a plush
he had to be made and so on look how
cute he is this is who'd see the little
owl i have who
fluttered into fluttered into my home
into my basket and i let him live here
he's a bit more i like i like him uh
look at a little hoopsie plush
i really i'm excited for this one i
don't really i used to collect plushies
a lot but i don't really collect
plushies anymore
this may start up my interest again
though
it's the buffer oh okay
okay it's taxidermy no no no no no no
not this one no no we don't have no
don't worry we don't have the the budget
for the for taxidermy owls no no no
no no it's just it's caught it's cotton
polyester it's polyester polyester oh
don't worry about it don't worry about
it
and now you guys you guys can match me
if you have a you can have a little
hootsie sitting on your lap while i read
super chat while i talk or something
oh so cute
let's see oh gosh you're not much time
and here is here is the friend of pencil
pouch
yes we have friend on the pencil pouch
and inside of the pencil pouch you will
not be able to escape him he is on both
sides and inside
yes i thought this would go pretty well
with the journal so you can keep
your pens and pencils all together
whatever else you may need to keep in
that pouch maybe some little snacks
maybe a sharpener maybe some erasers
unless you put in pencil pouches i also
have scissors in mine
i used to have a little hole puncher too
yeah little little pencil pouch just
yeah i thought it'd go i thought it
would go well
with the
journal
and then we have
the bookmark this bookmarks
actually made of a metal
it's a it's a metallic book more antique
finish metallic
antique metallic fit finish there you go
so yeah you know it won't bend and break
like a certain paper bag um
and
i don't know i can't imagine it being
cold i don't know why that excites me
if you leave it outside overnight
i don't know why that's so exciting to
me
you could also heat it up maybe don't do
that you might damage it um
yeah a metal a metal bookmark a hard
bookmark i don't know if you would would
you wanna you could i guess use that for
the journal that would make sense
that would make sense also by the way
apparently it's live now uh sorry it's
live now it's been so if you want i i i
if you want to get stuff but i'm still
all done uh but if you've made up your
mind go ahead but if you're sony
convincing all right
convincing that sounds bad if you're
unsure if you're unsure um yeah this is
that's actually about it
that's about it so yes the the bundled
sales the birthday merch completes that
limited edition
um and the birthday merch complete set
uh if you're i would assume if you're
unsure about
or i don't know you probably want to
i don't know i don't know how quickly it
will sell out good good luck i hope i
hope everyone who wants one can get one
uh
um and then
so okay if you don't want to buy them i
think your nose ready if you don't want
to buy them all together if you don't
want to get um the bundle you can get
individual items which are the journal
the plushie the pencil pouch and the
bookmark you can only get the uh the
postcard
either the one that's
autographed or has the stamped autograph
you can only get those
uh
in the bundles in the bundles
yeah yeah yeah
did i do
it here we go
smaller
oh so pretty so pretty so pretty so
pretty
that's it
don't be mistaken
okay if you are if you are
on the other side of the world it's
august 5th um it's it's don't be
mistaken it's on sale right now even if
you are
even if you are in um
wait what i can't if you say it's
not i don't know it's sold out already
it's been two minutes are you sure
oh would you look at that i told i'm
totally the one that pinned the comment
there
i'm totally the one that pinned that
comment for sure ah there's the link no
way it's sold out
all right that's weird okay
what sorry that's blowing my mind okay
um
okay
i have my doubts but at least the
unlimited stuff is there if you
if you still want it if you still want
it um yeah sorry i will i still have
callings to do maybe we could i don't
know you guys that's the merch
that's that's the merch i hope you guys
like it i hope it's useful for you guys
i'm really excited to see it when you
guys get it uh once you get it take
photos and stuff uh
i'm really excited to get it too
sorry um we have uh i rushed that and
now i'm rushing again because we have
more people more people uh to join
and for calls and stuff oh gosh bless
this person for waiting so long oh bo
bless plus i'm sorry
all right let me
rearrange everything
let me rearrange everything here
yeah i think uh we can maybe come back
to talking about it after i just feel
bad she's been waiting she's been
waiting 15 minutes no okay let's see we
got the icons back
there we go i think i'll i think i'll
chill here i'll show to the side then we
get we get a good look at a baby there
okie dokie i'm a am i ready wait uh-huh
i'm ready okay
she's ready too
hello
[Music]
hi i'm so sorry thank you for waiting
no it's okay i'll wait forever for you
oh
cute oh thank you thank you i'll eat
your picture i have it
it's okay i can't believe it's sold out
damn it you guys are not leaving some
for me
it must i think it's an error or
something that's really weird it's like
two minutes
thank you thank you santa
oh my goodness hi how are you
hello oh first before i forgot i i
uploaded on
okay uploaded it oh oh
i made a little something
that's cute oh no it's cute oh no
[Music]
hold on
you like it let me i take so long to do
this like i i gotta show you it's okay
it's okay it's big
oh my gosh that's really cute thank you
no problem i'm gonna make it bigger for
a bit i'll put it here for now that's
a good use of the space
that is so cute i love the colors
it's so warm
yeah it is so warm
[Music]
no problem have you been
how how are you
i've been great i'm a little bit uh
sleep deprived but then all
but then from what i've noticed from
this colon all of id is sleep deprived
so yeah
you guys just don't sleep i see yeah
we're just really bad with
schedule sleeping schedule management i
am i am the exact same i think i went to
bed at 5 00 am
wait really me too
oh my goodness owned what are we doing
no way
oh no no
ah as long as we get enough sleep i hope
i hope you guys are all sleeping enough
that's probably what's most important
i think that goes to you too mrs sleep
at 5 00 am
fine that's all good
oh i have a question for you zetta
okay
what's your favorite animal
uh you
what's your second favorite animal
no but but i'm being real i do like i do
like owls they're really soft
but
they're from owls
i like blobfish and hammer headshots
oh wow
very nice why do you like those
um
they're like stupid but cute
this is getting a pattern
i feel like i feel like i can relate
people call me stupid but cute so like i
feel like i can relate to bluffish
that's silly i feel like you're very
smart
no
am i not i think maybe we're similar
where we're told we are totally very
smart people we're just bad at showing
it sometimes maybe but we're we're so
smart
oh we're so smart
we're so smart sometimes you know
sometimes people just comprehend
can be contained in one single stream
exactly exactly they just they don't
even know what hits them they're so
they're so little might i don't know
there's so much of imbeciles
thank you for erasing my confidence
of course you should be confident you're
great
you do
oh thank you so much for coming and
thank you for making me a gift it's so
cute
no problem thank you so much for having
me i'm so nervous like i know we talked
a lot already but i'm still nervous okay
you are wasting your nerves on me
there's no reason to be nervous around
me
i promise no no
no you you activate my neurons
i see it
look make sure you get i hope you rest
enough today
and thank you for waiting thank you you
waited like 20
[Music]
what is it
brain can't compute okay
don't worry we are like i said we're
very smart we don't need to use the
words i knew what you meant
exactly we can communicate without words
exactly
all right i will say goodbye now to my
favorite favorite animal bye bye bye
bye thank you happy birthday happy
birthday thank you bye bye
oh goodness gracious
openness gracious
let's see
i'm not sure
i want also
okay i don't really know what the
schedule is i'm being totally honest i
don't know what this schedule is
i also want to say it again i asked
extremely last minute
for people to come here so not
everyone's able to make it those who
can't make it message me
and i i know and i
don't don't
i need i just really want to make it
clear it's my fault it's my fault
i mean it
super
super last minute i should have focused
on this a bit more but i
did not so i think what
we can do now is watch videos because
some people that couldn't make it were
able to send videos
so i think oh
[Music]
here
wait why is it no it's not good enough
hold on i'll fix it
there you go all right what was this
oh you remembered what the what the
cockroach it was the madagascar
cockroach that's one of the ones that
came up in in google when i hooked up
big cockroaches so
i see i see
somebody that's what
she
said okay
so let me uh i'm sorry i'm not prepared
i have to pull up the videos now
of those who were not able to make it
and also keep in mind
everyone who made a video made it within
less than 24 hours like i asked really
really last minute so
thank you to those who could make a
video and to those who weren't able to
it's okay
i'm sorry it's my fault i'm sorry
let's see uh how do i set this up
probably just do one here
one here
all right
i haven't shaved
i'm pretty sure i saved them but where
did
uh first first i gotta do this okay
sorry we gotta do some clicking i don't
know oh gosh wait i can't hear it
hold on hold on
let's begin
me a video let's see what she
has to say
let me um
make it i have to make it so i can hear
it
oh gosh how do i do that
this one
something is blocking my way hold on a
second
sorry
okay
i don't know how loud this will be i'm
gonna go ahead and pause the music
just in case
but
let's see
[Music]
can you recognize me no no i look a
little bit
less like a phoenix
and more like a
owl
one of you one of you i thought maybe
on your birthday
you might be a little bit more
comfortable being surrounded oh you know
animals more like you always and to
become
one of you
i
practiced
an owl
impersonation ml here we go
[Music]
how is it do you feel more at home now i
feel i feel very happy i know you're
feeling hopefully hopefully my face i'm
happy i hope even if there's not too
many owls around usually that you feel
comfortable and happy
in all life
english or your whole life in general
thank you for being part of it and and
yeah enjoy your birthday finally
birthday oh my god
took you long enough i hope you're
enjoying it and enjoy all the all the
presents and the sweet words from
everybody
yeah wish you all the best
and maybe teach me how to be an owl
sometime because
they're cute just like you mommy
happy birthday
okay i'll i'll practice some more
kutut
that was so cute i like both i like both
of those the last one and then the
that is so cute
thank you kiara
oh
she's such a nice
she says nice things
maybe foster i was like i don't know
maybe like
thank you thank you
oh thank you chiara thank you thank you
oh
oh goodness i think she i think she it
might have been really late when she
made that too thank you i'm sorry i'm
sorry everyone for
having me do last minute videos
thank you thank you thank you
let's see let's see
um my mom i think we have
did i save this one i think i saved them
hold on wait the music's gone maybe i'll
believe the music i just wasn't sure if
they added music or not probably not one
second i also have to adjust myself
i have to go out this morning so
i can't go your birthday party i'm so
sorry
i have a message collaborating with you
lately
i miss you very much
it's you
i like that illustration you do
for me
louie baby is
so cute
i have it as my iphone wallpaper
and i love your singing voice your cover
dilemma is my favorite cover
i want to collaborate with you
about single song
in the future
shall we sing
i hope your happiness have a fun
birthday today
bye-bye
[Music]
i want to sing with you
thank you oh my gosh she made it her
phone background that's so cute
oh my goodness
oh
so cute
i have to chill i have to calm down calm
down
oh my goodness thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
let's sing it together let's do more
stuff together please please please
[Music]
download it one second
download
oh gosh i have to close my tabs here
hold on
there's so much jumping
what are mud skippers
mud skippers have cockroaches
[Music]
oh
sorry i couldn't make it to your lovely
birthday party today okay
so
i said i'm sending you a video message
swag lovers moments cute boys and your
crime atmosphere and your illustrations
recently had a chance to draw
an illustration
but
drawing is very very difficult for me
so if you don't mind
please give me some advice for drawing
and also
let's collaboration with horatari again
i'm looking forward to
next quarterly collaboration
happy birthday mummy chung
have a good day and have a delicious
cake
see you soon
bye
thank you
why she wants me to she wants me to help
her draw
oh so he has some nice english she had
there
she said atmosphere took me back she
said she's the atmosphere i have nice
atmosphere did she say
i was surprised
no solo senpai has very nice english ah
thank you so much i'd love to
collaborate again
i know it gets very busy but i'd love to
let you collaborate again when
everybody's free
and available i'll wake up for it i'll
get up don't worry
depends on the day maybe ah
i'll do my vest
i'll do my best
thank you thank you
all right and then
okay here we go
oh gosh this is cute
oh my goodness okay this is just a
message just a written message hold on
let me
let me set it up
how do i do this
here did i save it oh maybe i didn't
save it i opened it but i didn't save it
i guess hold on
hmm
[Music]
her handwriting is cute
what'd she say a moo may that's me
happy birthday
glad to play a lot these days let's play
it together again
sorry it's messy i wrote it with a mouse
that's i think i want to see what her
handwriting is normally i thought this
was that was pretty good
looking forward to talking to you again
i love you daisuki
thank you for playing games with me i
want us to do more collabs too
i think we are we're ready we already
want to do more
yeah we just have to
plan yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah thank you thought thank you
i'll put it where should i put
maybe it
here
yeah
right here oh it's so small you guys
can't read it that's what's sad about it
um
let's put it there
okay
okay all right you think of what to do
[Music]
so how long let me double check
let me double check something i
might have given
quite a large window for if
anybody else was
available i don't remember how big that
window
was
though was it another hour
i think
so
i'm not sure
i'm not i'm not sure
[Music]
the direction is to talk about
my merch more
was it not enough
was it not enough um
maybe
maybe i'll do that a little later i
wanted to look at some fan-made things
so let me see if i that's gonna take me
a little bit to pull up too
let me see if i can
do that hold on a second
um
how do i set this up
[Music]
sorry
we're going to sit awkwardly together
for a second while i try to figure all
of this out these were the things i
saved
until
now
what does this play this on stream what
is it
what
it's a
game oh i gotta set this up wait hold on
how should i set this up um
hold on
i i
my manager arranged some stuff for me
there's a game a game for me to play
hold on
i wasn't prepared for a game
um
wait one second it's gonna take me a
little bit sorry
type time is it a game
no spoilers it says
sorry i have to set it up now okay
[Music]
um
like this i guess
[Music]
i hope this
is big enough
sorry this is gonna be kind of awkward
i can just go to my
no i'll stick here i'll stick here okay
i have to move it how do people
work through birthdays so quickly
how on earth i'm so slow
okay let's go here
okay
okay sorry i think i got it set up
there we go the chat disappeared hold on
there you go there you go
tada
i just like to watch well that's good
it's good or similar you guys like to
watch okay
let's see let's see yeah we have a game
what is that that's a little quilt or is
it a cooler i guess it's just a feather
oh touch to start check requests at the
bottom left icon
moomin no spoilers until your birthday
okay i didn't even know this was i
didn't even know about this so i have
not spoiled it for myself
wait there's audio hold on
wait what
hold on a second
do i use my own audio
there was audio here hold on
is there
there is
it's a little loud
wait a second hold on a second
what the oh wait wait
what is it
oh my gosh custom music oh you guys
can't even see that look in the corner
there what is that
little human in the tank what on earth
is audio okay
what
quests
it's a game birthday gifts
birthday messages
we don't question unlock the scene it is
a game completely quest to unlock the
secret
check the painting go outside and meet
humans around the world go outside i
have to go on a world tour
maybe i should do what's in here for
help
oh my gosh
sorry this is there's a lot here where
do i
where where do i start
i'm not no i'm not ready to go outside
yet
the outside is a big scary place i want
to stay in here
for now right right oh my microwave look
at all the rice
the microwave
cute
you guys see okay
what oh the spider
can i squash it
i guess not
all my stuff
my drawing board oh
cute how do i zoom in oh
did i leave the game oh i see i see
oh my goodness
oh my gosh there's a lot of stuff
artists
hi hello there's no music anymore look
hold on i guess i guess i'll look at
this real quick
i'll play my music because there's no
music
look at this
hi hi
happy birthday
thank you
thank you look at this heart
thank you look at all this oh my god
i wish i could can i zoom in more
a little bit
what is this
what happened to friend that's great oh
my gosh friend what happened to you is
this friend these are all friends
either
or maybe
maybe these are fake friends just to uh
just to remind friend of what could be
it
you guys setting an example for him
after he sold you all those fake tickets
i see i see
this is his final warning
his final warning stop selling fake
tickets
friend
i see look at that it's so cute
it's so cute
a little friend with the oh does he just
you
you know he looks the other way he
doesn't want to know
okay thank you these are all so cute
oh my goodness happy birthday thank you
thank you look
that looks like a pet rock thank you i
always wanted a owl pet rock
oh my god
this is all so cute
are you helping me beat friend up oh my
gosh
oh hi
oh my goodness
oh what's the heck that's is that the
jealousy is that
is that friend gelatin
what is he just a blob monster
it could either be a meal or
a monstrosity
it could be both
a slime friend
it could be yeah it could be both
i mean we have to eat all the everybody
else too
oh my goodness cute cute cute cute
[Music]
what
oh i took a slice out of frendy
oh goodness ever seen him with so much
so much fear in his eyes before
happy birthday
thank you
happy birthday happy birthday thank you
don't you notice me okay
thank you okay oh what are all these
friends my goodness
so many different types look at this guy
thank you
happy birthday pat thank you
oh my goodness look at that yeah all the
letters thank you
i love that face
this is so cute
happy birthday thank you
thank you i like the lighting used for
this
thank you look at the berries and a
banana
thank you thank you
thank you everybody for all the art
that's a lot
thank you guys
oh my gosh oh my stomach grumble i just
remembered i just remember there's a
that is whatever this is this came from
a game there's an entire game oh gosh
oh gosh should i complete a quest though
by looking at that
let's see i think i have to turn the
music off
what put chat back
woman's doodled their birthday greetings
on the shared drawing board click on the
image to open i did that
didn't have to tell me oop or i check
some things friend has a few outfits he
wants to show
and then
kept letters scattered on the floor
these letters
wow that's a lot oh dear
this is probably something to do
either
off stream or for different that's a lot
and you'll keep track for me
this may have to okay
it doesn't check this off right yeah to
save this
no no don't check it off i have to save
oh
yeah that's it
that's not lucky that's for that's for
off stream that's for off stream only
153.
thank you thank you oh my
thank you everybody uh who wrote a
message
that's so hot
spoiler oh i see there's spoilers
spoiler for the stream i see they're
they're just for me i see i see
i see perhaps they're not meant to be on
stream since there's a spoiler over them
i see
what else can we say more animal
that's actually animal isn't it
i'm actually not sure
that's animal
has animal vocalized enough that you
could collect those
feel like when i first started around
debut she definitely did
oh my god cute
yes
[Music]
oh my goodness
okay
oh cute
see
listen i'll show you for you to listen
to oh my
god
what
oh shoot
[Music]
oh my goodness
i have party music
[Music]
wait i'd like to use that
where where'd you get that
who made that i'd like to can i have
that
oh my goodness what would you call that
that was party music party music
mute dancing music head popping music
headphone
[Music]
birthday gifts did i open that
what
has prepared various gifts for mommy's
birthday
oh we can we look at these
wait they're downloads
oh they're it's an asset
spoiler
[Music]
oh my gosh
can be upgraded
that's so cool
[Applause]
happy birthday thank you thank you
oh thank you
oh my stomach grumble i'm hungry stop
because my is because i'm getting
butterflies
i'm freaking out my stomach has to
grumble i'm freaking out
[Music]
very nice anatomy
that's such a different type of anatomy
what i don't really understand well
i don't know
it's interesting i don't know like the
sharp lines i actually really like the
sharp lines
used in muscular artwork
very cool
oh it has nice lighting
cute cute cute cute
is this a poem wait hold on i need water
i need water
that was a lot of water sorry
let's see it
weeks before a stream every human had
hands on deck lovingly and carefully
planning on what mummy might want to
peck
very early we settled on some berries
everyone was ready and willing to go
yet we had a few who still feel bore
or at least they told us so
under threat of project failure
many of us prayed for days
understanding that our efforts could
maybe
make our elsies day
everyone is happy
everyone is here
it is our best wishes to you on the
celebration of the year
very cute
thank you it took me a second to get the
flow huh
thank you thank you
what's this
i'm
oh
you have oh you what is this this is fan
fiction
fan fiction you think you are worthy of
being knighted already
well it's not texas
it doesn't hurt
entertainer and my inspiration to pick
up the drawing pen
happy birthday moment i hope you approve
my first ever genuine drawing me is this
your first drawing what
all right you're right this is right
okay i say it is fan fiction
it is a fan fiction
no one gets knighted by me
unless they fulfill a lot of stuff that
i won't say otherwise it's spoiling it
thank you
oh that's cute
oh my
i would i would like i would like to use
that please
that's so cute
oh my goodness
oh i love the colors on this one oh the
pink is so nice thank you look at
everybody
super cute thank you guys thank you
everyone who made art here
thank you
let's see
do you have any more quests there's a
time to oh read it afterward on credits
top left oh secret request secret final
quest top left credits
let's see
afterward happy birthday i want to see
it this time a lot of humans work
together to prepare a gift for you we
put together
a birthday party with many gifts for you
to open
maybe i should have wrote this for you
sorry
as you can see
council and humans are in attendance but
now that everyone celebrates this day
with you a special day with you
including myth all hallow life
production talent staff and seven
hundred thousand humans who truly like
you
the first and foremost thank you is for
nanashimumi why
you are the one who brought us together
oh okay you're welcome for that i guess
you're the one making a smile laugh and
inspired regularly
the human community was built around you
and the amazing things you show us in a
special day let us be the one giving
back to you
this is the day when we appreciate that
nanashi mummy graced our world
this day may have added one to your age
but isn't it a small price to pay for
the next whole year of fun moments we'll
have we'll enjoy it together
oh
look at all this
oh my goodness everybody thank you
there's a small price to pay
aging a year
that's okay
okay i'm not a human or yeah i'm not a
human so i don't i don't care i don't
care about aging i don't i don't care
about that
look at all this thank you everybody
oh thank you thank you everybody
[Music]
thank
you there's a lot of people coming
together to work on stuff
thank you
let's see
oh
[Music]
wait i haven't gone outside though wait
i didn't go outside well i didn't go
outside
i don't need to go inside everything
everything i love everything everything
i need is in here
[Music]
i don't have to go outside it's okay
i can make a wish
by blowing out the candle
[Music]
oh
oh my
goodness
[Music]
cute cute cute cute
derek outside
oopsie
wait what
oops sorry
now you all know you all know i had to
should i should i go outside
oh i see okay that's for later i think
that's for later i don't want to show
that on stream i see good good you have
spoilers
i'll look at that i'll look at that
later
all right i'll go outside later i'm
gonna i'm in the middle of a stream i
can't i can't do that right now
[Music]
i can't do that right
now ah
thank you thank you everybody
that worked on this
[Music]
why is this background music making me
kind of sad not sad i don't
know ah
thank you
i don't know how to leave it
thank you thank you
[Music]
there we go
there we go there we go
i see
thank you guys
oh my i hope you guys can see that okay
not so small
wait what is this where is this window
oh here it is okay
ah
thank you everybody who was a part of
that
it was hard to
rub my head around
wow people took the time to do that
i don't know six times to do that for me
thank you
thank you for for doing that organizing
it and everybody who participated
see
there's a few more of these i wanted to
look at
um
oh
yeah sorry i have to save the files now
[Music]
do this how do people keep track of
everything there must be a better way to
organize
organize everything when it's your
birthday
um let's see let's see
okay
there
i wanted to look at this looks yummy
look at that i really wish i could have
that
look up there's just so many cute things
about it the little feathers the leaf
feathers on it the berries
the berries on it and then the little
look at the little the little
oh it's so cute i love the chocolate
drip i love when chocolate meets vanilla
i love chocolate vanilla swirl ice cream
and i love
like if i love it with cupcakes
when when it's chocolate icing on
vanilla cupcakes
really oh it's just really yummy it
makes me want a cake it makes me wish i
had gotten a cake for myself but
i did not maybe i can uh get one
tomorrow
yummy yummy yummy yummy
you
thank you for
uh
a paleo a paleo thank you for making me
a cake oh wait the inside i want to show
you guys the inside of it too
oh no no no no i wasn't sure what's on
the inside is it hold on
i'll show you guys
look at that
oh the chocolate
what is it is it
at first i thought it was banana but i'm
actually not sure what it is you can you
guys tell what it is
yeah that is a clean slice
that is a clean and clean slice it does
look like banana right
oh you know what you know why i'm
questioning it i think it's because my
other monitor the colors are a little
messed up so it makes it look a little
green it kind of looks like
it kind of looks like it's honeydew
melon colored i don't think that
wouldn't be enough that wouldn't be in a
cake
but now i see on my other monitor
definitely it looks like banana oh that
looks so good
that looks delicious
oh thank you for making a cake i hope
you eat it and enjoy it
oh so it looks so good i want i should
have gotten cake
that looks delicious
[Music]
oh this was interesting too sorry i have
to save
you guys to barely have to save
everything
let's see
this here
i think i'll have to open
i have to open a clip studio i think for
it
now i'll just do
window
this is the first page
let's see
let me get oh sorry i have to move it or
should i move it
[Music]
all right sorry
there you go we have a newspaper
the weekly owl
newspaper
move this over here
don't worry i'll make it bigger and we
can read it together
where'd it go
okay
let's see let's see we got the weekly
owl for thursday 4th of august 2022
that's international holiday um
the hooch birthday edition
oh it's also my birthday uh for for
moomies for mummy's birthday let's see
let's see
happy birthday mummy someone paid to say
happy birth like they paid for us um an
ad
a section in the newspaper to wish me
happy birthday
happy birthday mummy congratulations and
best wishes on your birthday in almost a
year we could share with you many of us
here learned to love and appreciate you
for who you are and greatly enjoyed
seeing you grow from the bundle of
nerves right after debut to the capable
and confident owl you have become now
to celebrate your great day with you we
from the weekly owl prepared a special
birthday edition just for you
while there are many gifted talents that
don't mind standing in the spotlight
there are also those of us that shy away
from receiving too much attention
this does not however in any way mean
that we are any less thankful for what
you are
doing and we still want to show our
appreciation for having prepared a
little something in order to create this
special edition we have collected
submissions from those that just like
nanashimumi do not have a name and nls
wanted to contribute
even if we might lack some professional
polish we hope that you can enjoy
this special birthday edition from the
weekly owl happy birthday moment
it's a weekly thing
or is that just the name
is that just the name
once we got origins wait what is that
who's that
origins
a long time ago there was a small oh you
can't see them anymore i'm here hello
a long time ago
oh hi girl
thank you
thank you girl
hello
i hope i hope everything is going okay
grub a very busy shark after like i
wasn't even 24 hours ago
girl girl busy busy shark thank you girl
i hope everything is going okay
[Music]
i need to i want to show you if you
haven't seen the video the video
the dawn dawn video okay did you look at
the end of it
you should look at it
thank you thank you
ah
what this
wait i made it too small and i can't
i can't read it
who is that like
oh wait now let's go okay okay here we
go hello
let's see
a long time ago there was a small town
in slow decay succumbing to council's
forces of entropy and i've never said
this don't don't look at me uh
uh old men were dying and young men fled
to better lives in bigger cities people
tried everything to save that town but
nothing could be done
no force could stop
stop giving me a word i don't know how
to actually pronounce i've only seen it
written before stop
it in trophy
sorry i don't listen to people sorry i'm
sorry
my back
members decided on
a
certain project the project was to
create their own
savior
that is it
no their own
guardian
soon enough that guardia in it that
humans today know as
many
was
born
well kyle her goal was to save the town
from natural
okay
a fatal
flaw occurred during her
creation
making her unable to remember her
purpose
that town wilted at eons ago i'm sorry
eons ago
yet it's guardian it roams this world to
this
day
those are my origins
right because i wasn't born i was right
i wasn't burped i wasn't a bird that's
how i came to be
that's how i came to be
thank you thank you for documents thank
you for documenting it now i have proof
here i have proof
let's see what's this
your haven zoo
reopens after three months why what
happened
fans have been waiting with baited
breath
for the planned reopening of the beloved
am i saying that right you'll haven
ben
after they announced they would be
closing doors briefly to remodel and
upgrade some of their enclosures and
other facilities
last week's reopening ceremony clearly
couldn't contain the excitement felt by
both avid fans and regular citizens
myself scrambling citizens alike when
more than 500 visitors lined up in front
of the zoo a day before the reopening
ceremony and the zoological park
recorded a record breeding twelve
thousand of park goers for that day
the stars and mascots of the park a pair
of great horned owl twins that received
many visitors in addition this is new
tropical themed enclosure introduced
lemurs make
what's the flavors
right the zoo sorry that was really loud
i just
looked
it clicked for me
i think
look for me
okay
where was i
the travel enclosure introduced lemurs
making it the country's first zoo to do
so it was also packed so much
so that the staff had to limit the
number of visits
within
a whole
ticket system
also new to the zoo are two bears that
replace the old ones that sadly passed
away shortly before the planned
closure
are you claiming that cali and kiara the
bears are no longer with us
zoo
no no i should check on this
in addition to exciting exotic animals
or predators a new petting zoo was built
which lets children pet different farm
animals and deepen their knowledge of
how these creatures coexist with our
society
the big the big pig john was quite well
liked by the visiting kids
interesting
like uh
wow
what do we have in this
horrific bank robbery in humansville
weekly recipe
a crossword puzzle
oh
i want to see the crossword puzzle
let me see if they say the other
let's see what's this
horrific bank robbery in humansville
suspects still at large
disaster is this big enough can i read
it
might can i see okay
let's see
disaster struck the quiet town of
humansville last wednesday when a group
of four armed gum and held the staff and
clients a small local bank hostage the
suspects demanded staff hand over all
cash for this by the bank fortunately
one of the staff members was able to
sneak away and trigger the alarm without
the suspects noticing
in ensuing chaos a brave client
reportedly drew a toothbrush
one of the suspects responded in kind
and the two engaged in a fight with the
toothbrushes that only ended with the
local police arriving
during the subsequent two of the
suspects were shot dead by officer oh my
god one officer suffered an arm injury
and another's face was glanced by a
bullet luckily no officers or hostages
sustain any life-threatening injuries if
you have any information please contact
your nearest police station
are you are you claiming that fun and i
killed people my gosh
i have no complaints this isn't this is
who i need to speak to your publisher
manager person
they're telling the story incorrectly
what is this journalism
what is this
wait the suspects were shot are you
saying sorry my i didn't read that
correctly are you okay i'm sorry again
again i think there was an error here i
think there was an error i don't believe
that
yes they're dead they're dead you don't
have to look for them anymore they're
dead
that's right yeah
they're gone
long gone are those animal books
is are is that an ad for
animal books
oh gosh you can't read it
animal books look at that
oh no it's too small i can't read it
animal books i want the animal books who
do i call
how do i order them how much are they
how much how much are they
oh man i can't even see what the
auditions are interesting
let's see what is
this
purchasing of tickets will come to it
well comes to an end as a money
pocketing ticket selling scoundrel known
only as friend has finally been
apprehended by the beloved ninashimame
that's right
the trial date is still being set for
the evidence is damning
and he will surely be locked away in his
carver box cell until he is
rehabilitated he will never be
rehabilitated he's a hopeless cause
but sure
that's right that's right
a missing person's report
oh no
missing unknown okay wait missing since
august 27th 2021 what could have what
oh no
age unknown sex female descent unknown
height five one wait a hundred pounds
approximately hair brown eyes brown
missing from construction at sight in a
wolf shot how do you see that whoa whoa
my stomach rebel
walsh climb
high is it
a young woman has gone missing from a
construction site in the
wool
where she was last seen on august 27
no one in the area seen or heard
anything about her since her
disappearance last year was more her
employer pete tried to get in touch with
her family
only come to the conclusion that she
does not seem to have any family contact
any family to contact
according to pete the number she gave as
contact for her mother seemed to be a
fake
while the call did connect all that
could be heard on the other side were
hooting noises as if you'd be trying to
talk to an owl or something
furthermore her sudden departure put the
project on hold in his business in
jeopardy
at first his primary concern was to get
her back to work to finish digging that
hole
over time that eventually gave way to
concern about the whereabouts
of this missing worker
that sucks for him
oh weekly recipe
one second i need more water and i also
have to check
messages
blah
hello
let's see what
a weekly recipe and this watering summer
heat one might often feel a loss of
appetite or indigestion in such
conditions and from the dietary habits
which result under them it can be
difficult to obtain the vital nutrients
your body needs coincidentally soups are
not only good on a cold winter's day but
can be a light meal during the scorching
midday
just for the benefit of our readers at
the weekly owl recommends this recipe
it actually gives instructions
already have a couple cooked white beans
nice three ribs of celery
a medium i yeah
two small
cats
heat a pot over medium flame and chopped
half of that bell pepper
into the appropriate size
pour in one tablespoon of olive
olive oil
i use olive oil you should be using
sunflower oil or canola oil
vegetable oil
uh
i don't know how to say that i know what
it is it's like the
cube right
oh that's what it is
sorry i don't read cookbooks
mirepoix
it's an aromic a
a role or a
aromatic flavor based made by lightly
cooking onions color oh
i'm not that gonna have a cook sorry
i'm sorry
i thought it was i thought it was like
the broth the little broth cube what is
that called what is the broth cube
called
i don't know
anyway
let's
see that's it
it is nothing it is nothing and nothing
like nothing
it's not even close
beyond sorry
anyway but
really cookbooks used to not have
pictures in them you just have to know
what things are and what they look like
crazy
let's see
when the other onions turn translucent
certain chopped bell bell peppers and
continue cooking until fragrant add half
a can of wholesome
tomato disgusting and chop roughly with
a spatula put it in a bake why would you
use a bay leaf ruins everything bay
leave and a teaspoon each of both dried
based dried basil and a rake oregano
after adding the beans
turn oh yeah oh i skipped an instruction
oh wait
okay pour enough water to cover over the
vegetables by one-fourth
water watch it a lot of water in a soup
that's disgusting
turn it to a simmer and cover
turn to a simmer
and cover when the soup starts to boil
clean one cup of green beans and one and
a half cup of spinach cut green beans
and spinach into several sizes skip the
step if you're using your spinach if
wait oh young spinach your spinach
your young spinach
and three cloves of garlic after the
soup starts to smell fragrant and the
white bean turns soft add green beans
and continue simmering until tender
green beans okay those are pretty good
uh stirring garlic and spinach season
with salt and pepper and some drops of
vinegar to taste transport
should i actually try to make this
interesting this is too small for me
here wait what oh serve it with a slice
of bread mmm oh and garnish with parsley
sounds horrendous i'll try to make it
though
i gotta make it i can't read that very
well but it looks like it's
and
the georgia brand canned nightmare is
the perfect addition to your pantry
on a quick and simple
meal for your dinner
just warm up the can of student
nightmare with tomato
i didn't know you could buy that in
store
you just sell that
over the counter
or on the shelf
i don't know that
it's wild
i shouldn't be allowed
interesting interesting
i think it was uh there was a crossword
but i think i have to set it up
set up the crossword in a
clip studio i guess so i can ride on it
let me see if i can do that quickly
um
[Music]
i'll probably have to crop it and then
you guys will have to read or i'll read
it to you guys do you guys want to help
me
you're actually curious about it
actually wait i might have time for this
hold on i mean we don't have time for
this maybe we can do this we can do this
another time we won't have time for this
really no
maybe not
i don't know
next time
i don't know and let's do
yeah see you next time
i'm gonna take like five minutes to set
it up anyway
that's exciting because i've been
wanting to do i wanted to do crossword
puzzles but we don't have permissions to
do any crossword puzzles
so
yeah we'll do it you know another time
oh let me check with
manager
if there's anything else otherwise
oh you hear windows
i have windows activated at closed clip
studio
activate what do you mean activate
windows
what are you talking about
what
activity
what did you hear you heard me close a
program and thought that it meant my
windows was not activated
you sillies
you silly you're silly willies
silly willy willis
um
let's see
okay i think what i'll do now
is
i will show
i want to show
a sneak
peek
of something
a very very very very very very small
sneak peek
i was supposed to have another thing
come out either today or tomorrow
but
i decided to redo it
at the last minute
i wasn't satisfied i wasn't satisfied
with it so
i redid it it's not coming out tomorrow
it's
hopefully hopefully within the next week
hopefully within the next week
it will be
all good and already
i redid my part so now
i wait a little longer you all wait
just a little longer
i don't know should i i don't know if i
should tell you guys what this song i'll
just say is i'm i'm doing a i have a
song cover
that'll be coming out very very soon
it's a little delayed but yeah song
cover
hopefully within the next week it has
beautiful
art
beautiful art and i want to give you
guys a little sneak peek
maybe see if you can make any guesses at
all
as to what what it could be
uh i don't think anyone will guess it
though
let's see
there's your sneak peek
what is that
what is it
i bet nobody i bet nobody will guess it
um
whatever it is it looks really pretty
ah this is this is a cover it'll be a
cover within
the next weekend i um i've said this
before
i still don't have a
i don't have a schedule for it yet but i
also have
a new original song
that i'll be working on
i don't know that's coming out but
yeah this thing you know this thing this
is a cover this is a cover of a song i
really really like and i've liked for
a really long time and i'm really happy
i got to uh
i got to do a cover for it
why are you all going why y'all i said
this before
i i mentioned this didn't i didn't i
mention it
i have an original in the works
in the works but i kind of put it to the
side to focus on
other stuff
i focus on some stuff at the end of last
month
and then my birthday and now i focus on
other things for this month such as
council anniversary maybe
maybe another really cool thing is
happening this month who knows it is but
you don't know that uh but now you do
another really cool thing
this month um so hopefully it learns all
that's out of the way i can
put more
towards it let me get it out get it out
when i
when i can
it looks like
we may have another person who wishes
to say hello
i give a pretty big i give a pretty big
window
uh
yeah i give him
one because i didn't like i said i
didn't assign anybody
any times and i spent the really i asked
at the last minute
yeah yeah
okay
but apparently i have like three minutes
okay uh what should we do for three
minutes uh put this away there's your
sneak peek
next time you see that you'll see it for
the entire thing
let's see i think someone will join and
i have i believe one more video
yeah
one more video i'll show
closer to the end
yeah
let's see anything else
what can i do for 10 minutes
what do i do for two minutes
show my merch again for two minutes
two minutes uh okay
where is it it's gonna take me one whole
minute to set it up again and then
okay
and then okay it's ready okay now one
minute one minute to show the merch
hold on
wow look at that oh the merch wow look
at that if you want some oh
yeah if you want some you can get at the
store the link's there wow look at the
merch wow wow
first official mummy merch wow wow for
my birthday my birthday is today holy
moly look at all that wow
oh you gotta get the bundle you could
get the individual items you get the
four individual items there what are
they again they're the journal they're
the plushie they're the pencil pouch and
it's the feather book we want the
feather bookmark
wow
incredible
incredible merchandise holy moly yeah
you could also get it in the bundle if
you decide to get the bundle you can get
the bonus postcard wow
incredible
wow
why is there a mosquito in here not on
my birthday get out of here
i didn't invite mosquitoes to my
birthday
[Music]
hello
oh that's me
oh
hello
mommy
[Applause]
yes it
matches your voice perfectly
yes
all the best in your the birth of your
birth
you're welcome
how are you
oh i'm i'm i'm great um you know i
actually asked for five minutes because
i i drew a quick sketch
oh let me see let me see oh it's cute
wait
i've said this again i've said this so
many times i asked super last minute
i forgot that you're supposed to oh wait
i switched it wait i was there before oh
shoot wait what was there before
oh gosh i messed up here but i'll
replace it in a second look at that yes
thank you
thank you thank you oh ollie
yes i have a question for you
oh i like questions
what is your favorite animal
maybe i like elephants
why do you like elephants
i don't really know it's a childhood
thing i just think they're really big
and cute
that's a huge cute is a common reason
for an animal do your favorites i think
that's acceptable
they are cute
what's your favorite why is everyone
asking
because he asked first but i'm supposed
to ask the question here everybody keeps
that whatever i ask people what's yours
and i'm like what
you can't do that
it is the rules it is the law of nature
you cannot escape from it
i can't give
that's true i've given like three
different answers to different people
what else i'm trying to give you um
what else do i
like do i
[Music]
why am i blanking on what i like
i think
is it because you like a lot i do like a
lot
i do like orangutans
orangutans
they're cute i do like all animals
i know all the animals are cute in their
own way
yes
thank you for it thank you for stopping
by i'm sorry it was really last minute
no no no no it's okay it's my pleasure i
actually forgot it was your birthday i
usually
i usually have like this this monitor
where i look at the hololens birthdays
and see who's coming up that's i forgot
it was yours it gets kind of confusing
because technically it was yesterday for
you
i'm celebrating in a weird time zone but
it's okay to forget the forgetful one's
birthday because i ever get birthdays
too
you're looking in the past
anyways
yeah
since it's your birthday do you have
like any wishes
wishes
have you been asked this before
um
no
i wish
yeah birthday wishes what do you hope
for the upcoming year oh for the entire
year
yeah
i don't know
i don't know i don't know what i want
you don't know well i don't know maybe
like world domination or i think
i want to get more like okay usually
when i get baked goods like cakes or
cookies and stuff i just get them from
the grocery store but i want to go to
actual bakeries to get them so maybe
i'll do that more
oh
so you want to shop
sweet for yourself a lot more yes
that's a cute wish
what the heck
you could have wished for anything else
in the world but you decided to wish for
a cake that's what i'm thinking of right
now
i like that oh you get your cake and you
have a lovely birthday okay thank you
thank you ali
all right i'm gonna chow myself out you
have a lovely time with uh your humans
yeah yeah
[Music]
who was there before
oh no
let's see um
[Music]
that's too small i thought it was bigger
than that
there we go
should i
what should i do
um
what to do
perhaps
perhaps i'll give oh shoot i didn't
usually wait first of all who is it
who had art there i have to replace it
right there
anna's drawing thank you
there it is yes there it is
big again
all right
here we go there we go there we go
[Music]
i'm not sure what to do okay
should i
wonder if i should go up until the hour
because that's the time i gave but
i think some i think people just might
not be available that's okay
this is also i think a really awkward
time for
quite a few people
so
hmm
what did i do for three minutes
because the last video i have isn't that
long
[Music]
yes maybe oh maybe i'll talk a little
bit about
the people that came together so that i
could
on my birthday
so as you can see we're in the moment
ease right now
and this this um
this establishment was made by
do i usually prepare i usually prepare
slides uh for credits but i'm sorry i
didn't think about it this time i'm
sorry but please please uh please check
out azure it should be in the
description thank you for making me
making me my birthday party i love it
i think it's great thank you thank you
and of course i had my little
dawn dawn video
uh go up before the stream started
uh and that was
uh we had quick case uh mixed it for me
super quickly thank you and then we had
kind of dude basically
yeah did everything
actually i didn't see the video until
like
it was like 30 minutes before i set the
premiere
i think within a
he came up with everything i was just
like yeah you do whatever you want
you know you're you're pretty you're
pretty funny you're pretty
pretty funny funny content creator
never whatever you so please and i got
it back and i was like oh my god
oh my goodness
thank goodness yeah kano
does so much work for ian
there's so much of work
constantly working so thank you thank
you for for making it something for me
for accepting accepting my request thank
you thank you
actually insane
let's see i think i would also like
i should do this now i don't know what i
don't know how to look with the flow of
things it should be
um
why not when do i think everybody who
came to my birthday when when do i thank
all of you
when should i do that
um i do it now
should i do it should i do later
what should i do
tomorrow should i do it tomorrow
should i do it maybe next week
maybe maybe next month
maybe maybe i'll say thank you on my
next birthday
that'd be the appropriate time to thank
thank you guys
am i on my second
birthday that make sense
about
i don't know
i think that
i think that everybody who was available
uh
has already
made an
appearance i'm pretty sure
that's okay
next year next year i'll be a bit more
prepared i'm surprised so many people
came honestly i wasn't really i was
really expecting i wasn't really
expecting
many people to be able to
just kind of asking people just suddenly
drop everything
especially if they already have plans
made that's why you were supposed to ask
probably at least a week in advance
at least a week but i
did not do that that's right i gained i
gained experience
get experience from it
that's okay
um
yes i can play
the last
video i have
am i ready for it though
i want to
i want to procrastinate
am i ready
watch it
i wanted to save it for last because i
don't feel like i'm ready for it
i haven't seen it yet
um
yeah okay i'll have to set it up one
second
where
you guys couldn't hear that windows
thing could you
um
because it didn't happen
let's see
that up here
[Music]
okay
okay i'm ready i think i hope let's go
i'm not ready
[Music]
hold on
it was too big
hold on hold on
put it here
i think she put her
own music
did she i think she might have i
probably should have checked before i
didn't want to watch it before
okey-dokey
let's see
[Music]
is
one year older
[Music]
congratulations
happy birthday my favorite cutest
sweetest elf
i'm sorry that i couldn't be there
on your birthday
i'll be watching i just have to send you
this video in advance yeah yeah yeah
you know the circumstances counselors
knows the circumstances um more than
anyone and thank you for
just always
being
the most considerate and sweetest owl
[Music]
sorry let's see
um what do i know about your birthday
oh i saw a
little bit of the art
you look so adorable and i saw
um you're also planning some really cute
merch i'm excited for that
i'm sure everybody is going to be blown
away
and you also talked about um some other
things
i don't know if you announced it or not
already uh
but today is a special day where
you have to be spoiled rotten with
affection you cannot run
did you have something nice to eat
oh
um
drink some coffee or maybe coffee cake
[Music]
i hope that you treat yourself to
something really nice
and get everything that you want
and also
from now on and
in the future i'll be cheering for you
[Music]
one day a civilization will evolve
into um something amazing and then
you know maybe i can give you a tour of
the universe or something do you want to
go to the potato planet
[Music]
well take it day by day um have a lot of
fun
always be watching
happy birthday again
[Music]
i love you mummy
i can't say too many words because my
nose is stuffy
[Music]
so i can't just message you
thank you for leaving me a video
it's okay
it's okay i'm
really happy
you left the video i probably should
have watched it before so it didn't it
wouldn't hit so hard but
thank you i love
you oh thank you oh
goodness wow
that's why that's why that's why i
receive it for last
[Music]
i don't like that
yes
yes yes
call it a day for the birthday party am
i missing anything
am i
i don't think i am but i can't remember
yeah
sorry can you imagine if i show the
merch after
the timing of the merch i have to get
that figured out
no you saw the merch you know what it
looks like
oh my goodness oh my goodness how about
how about we space this out a little bit
that's why i do need a laugh of it oh my
gosh my
ow
i like my
face on this friend real quick hold on
look
i guess i guess i'll thank you guys
today
i guess i'll say thank you
thank you
for everything
i'm really bad at this stuff
i'm very i have a hard time being
sentimental all right i have a hard time
expressing i don't know i get all oh
i don't want to be corny oh gosh i can't
be too corny oh gosh i can't be i can't
be too dramatic here oh i have to reel
it in i have to play it cool
i have to play it's not it's not guys
it's not like i'm really grateful for
everybody
and that every day i
think to myself how crazy it is that so
many people
like to watch me
come by
watch my streams and
talk in my chat
draw from me
and support me
is that yeah
[Music]
oh now there's a lot of phlegm nice
oh yeah like
look you sniffle
wait hold on i need to sniff a bit more
should probably keep tissues nearby
i don't have any
anyway
uh
yeah just
thank you
everybody hey
i know that
one of the messages
i read today said
this is the day that we celebrate
lumay
but
for me i don't know i don't really feel
like
celebrating myself
i just like to celebrate
that all of you are here with me
so it's a i guess it's a celebration
for all of us
does that make sense i'm really bad at
expressing my feelings
right
so
thank you guys
this is
i want to do more for you guys
i hope i can do a lot
more in the future
i'll do my best
i'll try to balance everything
a bit better i think i'm
i think i am learning and getting better
at it so
i really hope i can do
a lot more for you guys
oh look at that
i think i'll call it a birthday
stream
okay
who
participated
said hi today here come by you all get
done stun done
um
there you go okay
okay
bye guys i
don't know i i might see you tomorrow it
depends how exhausted i am i don't know
if this dress will hit me like the you
know exhaustion after a stressful course
of events will hit me
probably after this maybe a bit tomorrow
but
if not if i don't see you guys tomorrow
i probably will i'm not sure don't don't
take my word for it um if not tomorrow
um
probably next day
yeah see you soon
i hope you guys have a good
rest of
your day
or
evening
night
or
go to bed
bye
bye bye bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you