foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello hello
[Applause]
everyone looks different who are these
people
oh no um yeah when we entered the VR
Universe our bodies uh they warped and
something happened these special forms
yeah something happened and we were
swarmed into these forms okay just
crying and they're staring right
straight in my eyes
what I'm perfect
every way you are perfect
though
you're missing about this world couldn't
contain me
in my corner okay look at my corner okay
hi who starts
you
me
oh okay
um
Iris it's Iris I don't think you guys
can see how I look in my perspective so
yeah check out the other perspectives to
see what I'm what I have turned into uh
thank you Star World
um yes everyone's just so cute and just
sad of being aware of McAllen and
grody's just like I want to disappear
from this world sort of post except
never mind no she's looking at us now
excuse me
scary when she floats across the floor
as a floating head
I have the kind of effect on people
yeah
it's fun and the council's keeper of
nature I came to this costume party I
got all dressed up you can't see if
you're watching my stream but
um the elevator broke and we're stuck
here so
all you can do is stare into the Vortex
of time endlessly I suppose
it has a long neck
I'm Kieran
giraffe yeah looks like yeah with the
horns
put some leaf on her horn yeah
eyes are still shining brightly
laughs
ah
a bit guilty wait wait why are you guys
looking at me
oh my god oh wait oh okay okay
um I feel put on Spotlight hi I'm an
oral crony I'm the woman of time and
right now I don't have my body because
this world couldn't contain me yeah and
the only part of it arrived but you know
what that's okay because that means I
I'm ahead of this game
hahaha
um
on top of some broken clocks what's
happening wait oh is this
the reason the elevator is broken
is it yep yeah is it something you'd
like to tell us crony is it
uh I mean explain yourself it wasn't
really my fault that the elevator
attendant was rushing us all in and
I did get a little annoyed
so you annoyed it back
I
hold a Karen I pulled a bit of a Karen
oh no
oh
wait what's a Karen
don't worry about it seriously yeah
don't worry about it don't worry you
don't know is that someone's name yeah I
really don't know wait wait oh was that
as someone's name like what
um Karen is like uh you know I would
like to speak to a manager
come here
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
um who's next
moving
I was mummy
guardian of civilization but I died and
everybody screwed now
no no
what about the elevator this is part of
civilization too there are a lot of
screws in here but um
because we're screwed good luck yeah
we're screwed yeah good luck everybody
I'm in my retirement
oh you look very cute as a ghost thank
you how's it treating you I'm glad
you're not part of a
h
oh the ghost died
[Music]
wow
what do you mean
[Laughter]
yeah
cute cute worm cute
cute
[Music]
a wormhole
uh oh you were Ground pounded
I'm standing
merch I think I did
wow look like a delicious gummy worm
you look like
a turtle
[Laughter]
oh no oh no
[Music]
okay
a giant gummy worm delicious
[Laughter]
yeah that means you're sweet you're so
nice I hope you're she's not the sweet
and sour gummy worm I know those exist
oh I love this song those are yummy
Chinese
look like I'm dying
pickles
[Laughter]
you got really loud
arms they're my faces
I'm winking why
are you looking I'm leaking
in the r menu emojis
[Music]
you've got the long
um
I've been trying to offer a present oh
wait oh what's going on oh yes oh okay
we're seeing things
no I'm just thinking
bae
oh no hey guys it's a mistletoe van
needs to introduce herself I guess
Merry Christmas
introduce yourself
originally
[Music]
what happens to my model
I was reduced to primitive form well I'm
inside your head this is crazy this
actually looks oh my gosh that was that
was a wild ride I'll never forget you
look amazing
Minds when you go inside of us oh let me
see oh what what sort of mine do I have
why are your hands inside of your body
oh there's a rat to your brain oh I see
your tongue that's crazy
no that's probably my nose
[Music]
okay I don't know what's happening
anymore
we are combining into one
one extreme existence elevator
it looks like Connie would know
yeah
really
I literally got
wake up
my stream on look at this
[Music]
I want to do that
oh
Iris your modesty your modesty
the whole world can see
my mind down I don't really know what
I'm doing
ah
because I know wait how did you guys lie
down the floor slide uh you have to die
you you you press R and then you die you
expression
we are all dead yes
[Applause]
we've been in the elevator too long and
now we've hoped to come to death
[Music]
the mermaid's just crawling on the
ground oh
I can see my body a little bit please is
this a spoiler
for how I really look you can still see
what's going on oh no
[Music]
are you t-posing are you t-posing right
now
[Applause]
flashing
[Music]
he's definitely still flashing
how am I still flashing I can't see
what's going on
you're a very very obviously
why are you in that position
this is not proper Idol Behavior
[Laughter]
oh no
we've been rescued
[Music]
oh
geez I destroyed these monsters
[Music]
oh my God
it's just like dead by a daylight all
over again make sure the head of the
branch that makes sense
[Music]
don't grab them
okay
[Music]
I'm giraffe Karen means giraffe
beautiful neck
[Music]
don't look don't peek
I'm just getting a nice angle here
I swear I wasn't doing anything okay
okay I know you like moms on me
oh that's true
[Music]
[Laughter]
it looks a little familiar like I've
seen it before
um
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm sorry
I wanted to get a good shot hold on I
gotta watch something really quick uh I
just gotta check something you guys do
it okay
um
[Music]
why are you so old already
is your mouth Moving On Your Side
[Music]
I haven't seen myself for the first time
what do you think
I think
I'm pretty cute not as cute as you
though
we're both green though
right you're cute
wait I can look even more like a bobble
head
oh
put me on the Shelf
collectible figure
hold on if I do that too much
I don't think she wants me near her
anymore
[Music]
I'm relaxing
maybe there's a portal under him
[Music]
parkour
all right guys
[Music]
I'm listening
it's like we have
a picture
thank you Mommy
[Music]
um
oh do I have a tube
why do you react like that
When I Look From a Certain angle I see
it too oh
do you see it down here
um
[Music]
pretty much like our terminal here at
the time headquarters as you guys know
over there is the head of the branch as
you can tell
um so these are time terminals which uh
um is the whole bunch of armies run them
and recently we did have a zombie
outbreak a zombie army outbreak so we
had to close off this section here but
I'm hoping we can uh unclog that soon
yeah
and uh we also have a few different uh
reception desks here we do have a small
one like usually I would be here and uh
I would help you guys uh you know if you
had like some issues you know if you
guys wanted to know what timeline to go
to I could help you with that uh today
we will be traveling to another timeline
and as you guys know Council came from
another timeline which was in another
dimension and you guys got all messed up
in the elevator somehow um it has been
having some issues so yeah
just currently closed as uh it is a
holiday but we also have the elevator
which you guys have seen awesome don't
make me go back in there
um
sing it today do not press the second
button we'll be using that later oh and
over here okay the car which you guys
are welcome to help yourselves
[Music]
crying over here his Fountain of Tears
they are salt water we were thinking
about adding some fish but uh yeah some
salt water uh Fountain here he's got a
lollipop sweet delicious oh
[Music]
I stole it now he's going to cry more oh
no
[Music]
perfect perfect this Lobby uh has a lot
of timelines attached but we do have
portals specifically for all of the
small myth members here I'd like to add
some more uh areas for you guys too in
the future
the first step we're gonna go into Cali
[Music]
how do I sit how do I say oh there we go
Iris
hello hello
so very close to you right now
so large and it's beautiful like the
Moon yes yeah your eyes shine like the
stars
bright eyes it's like icing heaven when
I look into your eyes in hell at the
same time
oh oh is that a good experience
um you fell I fell I fell from this
world
if you guys go too far from here you uh
fall out from this world
did it
hurts okay follow me
I'll give you candy
dangerous
[Music]
oh we're here oh we have okay
in the desert oh
we died
[Music]
yeah
use it well
this is my third actually oh yeah you
died once already
next area now let's go over to the next
portal to the next time
[Music]
we will be going into the small Kiara
timeline let's go check out Tiara's
portal
I think everybody was on board with us
because we're leaving some people
oh my gosh Chef's number uh parasol
[Music]
oh it is
so cute
[Music]
beautiful
eyes
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah it's really pretty around this time
of year as you can see the trees have
the trees we have some pumpkins for
decoration and this is like the main
Town Plaza it's really nice kind of
reminds me of like Animal Crossing if
something's really cute yeah
[Music]
I feel like we could play hide and seek
in this map
[Music]
no one will know I'm here
they will never know
oh I better not get left behind
[Music]
us
out of business
team ruins of Atlantis
[Music]
is there
pretty cute
oh it's for United oh no I have bad
memories of that trident wait
oh yeah let's have bad memories
it's really pointy object from the
different dimension
[Music]
oh man
dick
enters
right in the belly button
[Music]
give me the house
thank you all right so a little bit
about this uh I believe in the ancient
ruins of Atlantis which we could go back
in time and bring Atlantis back in its
full Glory if you guys would like to see
that add another time but today this is
the timeline that we are in um beautiful
here under the water yeah
yeah
uh like meters are we down below the
surface
oh no
Connie was stabbed
it doesn't look like she's running away
from it it looks like she was stabbed in
the face
[Music]
come on everybody
let's see wait for everybody all right
into Eno's portal
feeling a little intimidated right now
they're coming they're coming all right
let's go and see this portal
oh my God
oh
so cute
[Music]
there's a paintbrush
Iris hey Irish
I do not need any medical assistance
I drink the potion it was no good
oh I was trying to
see the hell under
but
can I help you out yes please help me um
it seems like your enthusiasm was enough
to revive me
[Music]
don't drink this
really
don't drink what this is crazy
don't drink it
okay
she drank the potion I told her not to
wow
[Music]
you know would know
is
okay I'll take that
oh
it made a new flip oh yeah
[Music]
oh no oh no
um
drink this one maybe it will help
just open your mouth I'll pour it in
yeah in the left
[Music]
oh
it must have been the answer
[Music]
it's for you
thanks bro
[Music]
also here nice relaxing tea area as well
as some nice open windows with a
bookshelf and of course some paintings
and as you guys can see up here these uh
canvases are actually from her first um
[Music]
oh
cute all right everybody we're now gonna
go over to the last portal which is the
small Ahmed portal
where'd she go she goes through the wall
[Music]
oh no
we do have to go through the reception
area to get there
the pumpkin
[Music]
sorry uh-oh you take a seat
everybody ready here we are
oh
[Music]
oh there's a blue there's a blue oh this
is a pop down
oh she's over there she's trying to fix
it oh yeah so uh this
[Music]
is
small almonds
maybe some crimes what
[Music]
I can't do nothing without the juice for
it
she's immune
[Laughter]
I saw her do it
I didn't know that this is a deadly
concoction it was an accident
she looks so she looks happy
yeah
I love her
[Laughter]
oh yeah
concoction of life oh I'm sorry
just relax
to be dead sit down in a little bit when
we go to the next area oh yeah oh that's
exciting okay yeah just to tell you guys
a little bit about this area this is
where some small Amish come to rest
whether it's due to time or crimes uh
it's a bit of a prison it's a bit of a
resting place
yes
[Music]
okay okay
don't come at me with that thing
don't run when with syringe in your hand
[Music]
oh no you totally can't reach it
portion
of the trip today is Halloween so we
have some spooky activities planned and
we are now going down to the spooky
Halloween timeline
all right so if you guys would please
press the second button here the instant
teleport
buttons oh
or
[Music]
is it right now
oh
no so I'm actually dead yes
[Applause]
I couldn't make it I couldn't make it
even yeah
everybody's in here
okay
I'm good
now
yes yes
I'm not done
sometimes
[Music]
but the saplings are alive and well
oh no
um yeah
I spoke to him no
because I died and so I can't guard them
anymore so oh this is bound to happen
they just returned to Nature became
compost
now the saplings there's no excuse
adorable
that's good
yeah good all right so um we're gonna do
a little tour of this area let's start
over here first
um
[Music]
deformities of sorts I think there's
been some messing around going on here
but as you can see there's this looks
like an evil ritual each council member
[Music]
maybe
excuse me
the trees are dead though that's true
the trees are dead no and they're just
just sleeping
oh is it is
hibernating for the winter
yeah they will revive in the spring
I think her vampires
I can't get rid of the
camera's taking pictures
maybe we can get some screenshots like
Cali like a chainsaw maybe yeah for
something I don't know that's a great
idea
all right let's make some screenshots
[Music]
I gotta do my own sound effects
can I see this
[Music]
sure you betcha here we go all right ice
cream here we go um
[Music]
I should
be so dark
people that have ice cream or sweets
[Music]
hahaha
well guys
to the other side over here
[Applause]
let's go yeah
this spooky ambience
[Music]
oh Luigi
welcome to take a seat
scattered all around this area if you'd
like to sit I'll take a look though
and we also have this meme
[Music]
Luigi has nothing to do with this
spirits of your hair
[Music]
from the Mario franchise huh who's your
favorite
it's not a sign
wait can you shut up
guys are way too shy for my kids I think
the ghost whispered in my ears
death
destruction despair
I'm gonna cover my ears no no no no no
no if you guys wanted I'll take a seat
everybody take a seat uh in the chairs
in the couch
right here hello
my favorite sandwich yes the best uh in
between in a sandwich you're like a
marshmallow
marshmallow sandwich
we gotta put ourselves under a fire then
to make it
[Applause]
um is that a good idea yeah we'll
survive right I mean look at our forms
right now yeah
I'm dead so
oh
are you bowing down to me finally
learned your position in our
relationships oh thank you I appreciate
the respect I feel utterly respected
right now
oh
okay I like your flower I like you
there's a lot of other chairs
I like that there's a leaf stuck in your
ah just noticed oh thank you and I like
that the branch is a part of you yes it
grew right out of my skull hi and I like
you oh
we're watching we're watching crony is
watching is there a problem
[Applause]
I like your hat
it's a helicopter
I like yeah
I like it
some cheeks yeah
why are you suddenly complimenting me
huh I like you too
could you guys see it I mean
who wouldn't like do it ghost stories
[Music]
I was so safe
do you need someone to sit with you
I wish there were two seats here
[Music]
in the chair
um
scarecrow now I am alone on the chair
am I allowed to stand will I get in
trouble for standing
[Music]
here
um
all right I'm in the middle of your
relationships too yeah
so wide that it's just like cutting in
between everyone why and if I'm not
happy
wide fauna
do you fight with your neck like other
giraffes
in this form yes
yeah when I need to assert my my
dominance I'll give them a neck grab
oh no a neck grab
crony you wouldn't understand because
you have no neck
yes
well at least I don't have
crony's clock is is like grinding into
me I don't know by the way
I'm being sliced into pieces right now
I'm not gonna sit
oh all right
um okay everybody Welcome to the spooky
spooky timeline as you can see we have a
big Yago here and we could uh actually
let's Ouija board of juice to talk to
the three Spirit of Yago but
unfortunately it seems like we've
misplaced a little plan check I believe
it's called Uh so it's not here but I
thought instead of talking to the
spirits we could tell some ghost stories
do you guys know any ghost stories
have you ever seen a ghost before
yeah do you want to hear the story
yeah I want to hear
okay once I was driving down a winding
dark Road and I saw a lady and she had
no face
so I hit her and she turned into a ghost
um
are you are you sure she had no face
it wasn't just a trick of the light
dark like faces disappear
yeah no I I took I saw the body and
there's no face
My Stream though I want to hear it
car I wasn't driving because I can't
uh I think it was with my mom we're
coming home from somewhere it was really
really dark and then all of a sudden
across the road there was this like mist
of some sort that had no beginning and
end it was just in the center of the
road and we drove right through it and
we tried really hard will you ever see
some something and it it takes you by
such surprise that it leaves you
speechless for a little while
yes yeah that's what happened it was it
was it was kind of genuine fear for a
second uh but we're trying to think of
what it could have been and there's no
way it could have been smoke right
because smoke doesn't you would have
seen it fizzle or how would it have
traveled out into the road like that
without any
well how would it have lived that long
you know I was really scary and I don't
know how to explain it or I don't have
anything I'll explain what it could have
been
um
yeah at least you guys were in the car
so you guys were in the safety of your
car
yeah
oh my gosh like a kind of spooky story
but it's like from a thing it's like a
book I'm not gonna read it but like I
can recount it to you
yeah
you get in trouble
I just uh change the details
here's how are you okay Kiara
I I looked at the chat for one second I
just had to laugh
all right
so there's this girl right
and she's at a gas station
it's filling up the gas in her car it's
just a normal day getting off of work
you know the usual and then she decides
it's time to go home as any other sane
human would you go to work you go to
home just a typical day right so she
finishes getting the gas in her car
settles down in her little seat
gets ready to drive away yeah I hear it
too gets ready to drive away
ghost I hear it coming from your area
it's a ghost
drive away
and uh heads off down
excuse me
I'm sorry
gas station story
[Music]
down the dark and musty and spooky Road
and she's on like a Countryside roads
there's no one around until she realizes
that she's being followed stop oh my God
no way someone is falling no one is
following her yeah that's right there's
a car that's hot on her tail and it's
been following her in fact for a while
she realizes that it's been following
her again ever since the gas station is
this just actual cannibal Shia LaBeouf
[Music]
yeah that's right if you remember the
gas station there was a dude and he
followed he followed the car
there's one car here there's a car here
and they're going down the road and it's
dark outside and then the car behind her
this innocent victim starts flashing his
lights flash flash flash over and over
over and over again oh man body motion
Surplus what could it mean what could it
mean
she doesn't know but she's starting to
get real scared because she's got
another 30 minutes left to drive all the
way home so she keeps driving and the
the girls keeps flashing the lights
flash flash flash what does it mean you
don't know she gets very scared and
decides I need to call the police I need
to call them so they'll be ready when I
get to my house this dude to kill me
he's gonna jump out of his car and then
and then hold on I got I got my effect
my special effect he's gonna come out of
the car and and stabby stab
yeah so so she decides she didn't just
beep at him with the car like you know
beep beep beep
oh no she did she gets pretty mad at him
but he like doesn't care and so and so
she keeps going and he keeps flashing
eventually if she gets home she runs out
of her car the police are there they all
pull up and she runs out of her car and
the guy pulls up in his car
and he comes out and he's just a normal
dude and he says ma'am are you okay she
says what are you talking about my man
says
there was a dude in the back seat of
your car getting ready to stab you and
every time he was about to stab you I
flashed the light and then they caught
the guy in the back of the car
[Music]
that is a scary story
did they kill him and turn him into a
ghost
thank you
has thank you anybody else
does anybody else knows I have a scary
story
[Music]
oh I guess I guess it's a tree story
it's about living in space Australia or
Australia Bank you have any do you have
any sort of scary book stories
oh okay I mean that counts I'm scared
yeah okay
dance
foreign
[Music]
to Revenge you
no this is my own doing
I I can thank you I can threaten some
people if you need me to wait anyone saw
it I can make sure they forget it oh
no because I want to do it again to them
that's okay oh I see okay
well wouldn't it be better if they
forgot
so they could remember again
I want them to remember
okay
out of nowhere a huge like black light
up it crawled under my bed and then
I didn't do anything
they disappeared outside of you now
they crawl into your mouth
[Music]
that like
oh yeah
since we thought throughout our lives so
yeah oh yeah perfect definitely truly
perfect
I know this form is immaculate
yeah I'm only showing five percent is
anybody else I just noticed that crony
has fangs yeah I do
I bet you can Munch into some juicy meat
um
already know about this thing
sorry sorry
chicken at the wrong one oh okay I was
um I was living in Japan until a while
ago and um I I moved after after joining
whole life uh uh I moved into a big big
house
but the house was very very uh old it
was that when you walked on the wood it
would make sounds like what
right oh yeah so it was really really
old and it had a lot of it had a lot of
issues to it but well it was a big
two-story house all to myself so I was
like I'm just gonna try my best to
ignore that it's uh looking really old
so the first night arrives and
I'm I'm like yeah I got this whole house
to myself and I was trying to chill but
I was hearing noises
from ceiling it was like
[Laughter]
wow
it was very scary but I was I
immediately contacted my my landlord and
he was like yeah they're there there
might be some history of ghosts in this
house but please don't worry about it
we'll send you some ghost exterminators
so a few days later and the the
Ghostbusters came by and all those days
I I heard the ghost was like
continuously not only in the night but
also during the day it was kind of
freaking me out because I was also
trying to swim but it was I was hearing
it on the first floor and on the second
floor and on the in the side of the
walls on the bottom and on the top
everyone so uh the ghost exterminators
they came and they looked into the
ceiling and they they saw the ghosts
they saw the ghosts really and they said
that it's like they sound like about
freaks free ghosting no no no no
and they actually have ghosts poison
with them
and they put that yes that's right girl
they got the ghost toys in it they put
that the they put the ghost poison in
the ceiling and then they close it and
they they were like okay Kiana you call
us and tell us Call the Ghostbusters and
tell us how the poison worked and then a
few days later I did start hearing less
but it was still a little bit a little
bit so I called again and I was like yo
Ghostbusters I'm calling you because who
I who else would I call Right girls so
they say all right
who are you gonna call
Ghostbusters
and they say they were they said they
were gonna come back and they opened the
ceiling again and they looked inside and
they found the ghost of two ghosts the
Box
apparently those two ghosts of the
ghosts were
um the parent ghost of the ghosts that
survived and it was red because they
added they kept on trying to add poison
for the last surviving ghost but it
seems like that ghost has started to
form some kind of immunity and we tried
many times but it didn't it didn't
really work and then one time for
example I was sick but I
with the door open because I had it's
just it was like such a tiny idle
meeting room that it's like almost
impossible to close the door and I
started myself with my eyes
like ate your food once
yes
that's that's horrific I don't know if
you've heard of it but ghosts are
apparently
um uh uh not they don't like eating
chocolate because it will kill them
[Music]
so they're both survived chocolate and
and poison and all that so in the end I
started to accept the fact that I'm
living with a ghost and actually we're
best friends now and the ghost's name is
Casper yay
[Music]
I don't really remember Casper really
haven't watched yesterday once yeah no
Casper's cute
she's levitating
herself possessed
okay
[Music]
get the salt
I know
if you can hear me
good if you can hear me decide
don't start in too much control right
now okay only a little bit it might help
um Purge the ghost if you want to play
on desktop that's okay too because I
know you're feeling a little sick so if
you want I will reinvite you okay if
you're feeling too sick okay okay all
right
so this should be really easy just get
comfy yeah
comfy
sit down relax
she can't move her hands there she goes
yeah
the demon is banished demon is gone
the demon will come back right
the shark will come back
[Music]
pretending to be like an owl what why
are you pretending because there's
something wrong with many different
animals
[Music]
can you wake up
yeah she can totally hear us
[Music]
what
what what what Golem
hi princess
what
uh
May
oh yes I'm here okay okay yes I just got
worried because we were sinking into the
floor a little bit
about me oh yes I'm I'm kneeling at the
moment okay I just wanted to make sure
that you're not
also possessed by a ghost
why is everyone getting ready
[Music]
oh yeah it's a fun time
you know yeah I play dead you guys want
to hear another story
yeah
we do I can tell you guys it's not a
spooky story but it's terrifying in its
own way
all right cool thank you yeah um all
right so here's the story have you guys
heard the story yeah the crunch bird
s
told me the story of the French bird
long ago yeah I remember my grandfather
told me I know it sounds like that right
like KFC right exactly like you can
imagine a big scary Phoenix Yeah so
basically crunch bird my grandfather
told me this story it's been passed down
in Reaper Legends for Generations so
basically there's this couple and they
decide that they want to have a pet
right they decide it's finally time to
get themselves
um ahead of their own because you know
they've been living alone can't have
kids that kind of thing so uh so they've
decided okay we're gonna go you know off
to the Pet Shop so the husband's really
busy he's working and so he tells his
wife go ahead and get us a pet he
doesn't care what it is he says whatever
is fine right so the wife goes to the
pet store and uh is kind of talking with
the pet Clerk and she's like I wonder
what would be good you know a dog a cat
hamster all very cute but hear me out
how about a bird and so the shop clerk
has alright I got some birds I'll show
you some birds takes her to the back
starts showing her the birds and she's
like oh these are all very find Birds
but what's that one in the back there's
this big cage in the back it's got this
huge foul Beast of a creature inside of
it he says oh that's the crunchy machine
that thing's way too dangerous yeah
crunch bird is what it's called you can
call it whatever you want but I call it
the crunch bird and she says well why do
you call it the crunch bird he's like do
you really want to know she says yeah I
really want to know he's like do you
really want to know she's like yeah I
really want to know show me the bird
really really no exactly
and so so he takes he takes the bird
from the cage all right and and he says
crunch bird table
and the crunch bird goes and it destroys
the table goes to that table just messes
and destroys it the crunches the table I
see exactly that's why it's called a
crunch bird Iris I can see your pants
too all right now just be careful
um so next he says next he says crunch
bird
Crush bird chair the crunch bird goes
and it destroys the chair all right so
now the chair is destroyed and so the
wife says you know what this is a
dangerous animal but I think it's got I
think it's got potential you know it's
got like it's different you know it's
not just like your run-of-the-mill usual
uh pet and I think my husband might like
potential exactly it's got that
potential real special pet potential try
saying that 10 times fast real special
pet potential special Pepsi it's
probably not that hard so so she says
you know what fine I'll take the crunch
bird and um and he he they do the
exchange she gives them the money he
gives the bird right she takes the bird
back home sets up the cage gets it all
nice for her husband to come back home
now husband walks through the door and
he sees this foul beast in the corner
and he says what the f word is that
can't say the f word we have children
watching possibly so she says let me
show you she opens the door lets the
crunch bird out
and she and he says what can you tell me
what on Earth is this thing she says who
puts a crunch bird he says crunch bird
my ass
[Music]
I think you know what happens after that
just in time he's telling him about the
crunchy sense
[Music]
any word was important to the plot
development of the story okay
[Music]
I look like I'm about to unleash stuff
Ninjutsu like a fish okay
I thought Connie had a spooky story do
you have one protein
all right when you tell us
yeah yeah yeah sit in the rocking chair
I am athletic
one yeah
this is something that I experienced
oh no
So a family member and I were just you
know chilling out in our room and at
exactly 12 a.m uh the phone started
ringing so I said oh wow
why would friends call you at this hour
that's really disrespectful
and then
and then she looked at me and said that
that's not my ringtone
and
the the song that was playing uh was
pretty much all about
I've Been Everywhere searching for you
where have you been because I see you
like are you hiding somewhere in the
crowd and
and then we got kind of creeped out we
uh picked up the phone and
it stopped playing
and then suddenly at every night
exactly at 12. that same ringtone was
happening
and that was that was not the ringtone
that she said and later on she decided
to delete the song from her phone
and it still kept playing
and
and then we had some interesting events
taking place such as how when I was all
alone in the house I would hear
a piano key a single
piano key just going ding ding and I
would go and check it out nobody's there
or
I'd be all alone in my room and my dog
uh who's in the same room would
look at whatever's at the end of the
hallway
and I keep trying to call their call
Thai mutt's name and
they won't
they won't turn their head it's fixated
at whatever's at the end of the hallway
everything was Pitch Black
uh yeah
um
that that phone kept ringing and maybe
something about that house was weird
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
and that same family member had some
other experience where
they would have nightmares
about how they can't move but they would
be in a fire where they would get shot
so a lot of nightmares every single day
and
sometimes a woman like crawling over the
ceiling really fast just to look at her
in the face
and everything that's on the ceiling is
haunted no yeah like a ceiling fan yeah
and then later on that was when she was
living alone and when she decided to
live with her family again
this time she couldn't move again in the
dream
but
uh at her bedside she saw
a woman with all her face covered
and
and you know with the hair and
everything and she said oh you know what
I see that you're with your family now
and
because of that I won't bother you again
oh
yeah yeah and after that it was kind of
nice
after that she never had those dreams
where she's paralyzed in her sleep
ing yeah
those do exist yeah
it sucks
I don't really remember any experience
of being in sleep paralysis
does anybody else have
else but
yeah
right now
[Music]
thank you
yeah scary stories
[Applause]
you guys listen up I'm gonna tell you
about the next activity
awesome
the next activity is Amaze so
um into groups and the senpais will be
scaring the core highs
group a and Group B so if group a is
going to be Council you guys just step
on over here for a moment all the way
over here to the left or to your right
thank you and we have Miss and Iris over
here
[Music]
senpai
yes
[Music]
over here
okay I'm ready I want to be scared
the way this is gonna work is um I'm
gonna send you guys counsel don't go
into the maze yet but I want you guys to
go all the way over there to the other
side
um where the summoning circle is and if
you guys could wait over there uh that'd
be great thank you guys okay I will come
get that back to you in a little bit
[Music]
off on your hand
come here
I came out with like 10 bruises oh no
hey hey hey did you fart
[Music]
what'd you do did the ghost beat you up
or something oh you know you know last
time I went into a like a in a haunted
house thingy
um there was one part I got so scared I
just ran over the door but I didn't
realize there were like obstacles in
between and I like catapulted over them
and it was a seal bar no
I don't like haunted houses I've been
two on one candy and people were just
screaming
forget all your problems
I don't recommend it why
yeah because it's fun have you been
I'd have to really good I've been to
really really good ones and I've been to
ones where
um they act so sort of awkwardly jumps
out and then backs away when nobody gets
scared
um
oh you know what's really funny though
that was like um when I when I
catapulted over the steel bar I remember
the person who was meant to be scary
like runs up to me and he's like oh my
God are you okay
I like his costume on and everything and
I was like oh yeah
oh my gosh when you talk your eyeballs
move your eyeballs get off
wow
perfect
hello everybody again
the uh gravestone over there face the
gravestone and uh do not look it's not
it's to not spoil you guys okay it's
creamy I'm feeling scared now I wasn't
scared before
a little worried
oh do you want to go right now you can
probably run away yes I can
should I it'll probably be fine
okay okay we'll we'll wait for you
I'll meet you okay
okay
what do you think are we scared of you
it doesn't make you sad but here lies
crony Maybe ripperonis
it kind of Rhymes I like it do they
taste like pepperoni oh I'm sorry do you
like pepperoni do you write this right
out of ten
all right
you know what
it's a referoni out of 10.
as to whether that's a good score or not
I leave it up to you guys to decide
I really want to look around like other
people's I know
but I'm just looking at everyone's back
hey what's that supposed to mean
hey hey where are you looking back don't
look back
[Music]
okay it's all right
I'm gonna scare them back I'm gonna be
like
oh 29 30. all right you guys the maze is
now ready for you to explore you guys
can turn around and uh we can get going
yeah
she'll be back soon okay okay we'll wait
I still can't say anything you're so big
I'm gonna
um I'll tell you guys in Discord when to
go okay just give me one moment okay
um
she's back
let me just wait uh I will tell you guys
in Discord when to go to the maze okay
okay
[Music]
let's discard
oh it's like chaos
can we turn around
yes wait I think we can oh yeah look
inside craining his head
like if you clip it just right it's like
super nice to see you in here
oh my goodness why what
my head yeah your head is crazy gosh
your neck is shorter now I don't know if
that's it
I'm in my mouth
that's amazing Council uh you guys can
go ahead okay
was this here before
wait it's kind of scary
come on guys are we going together I can
lead the way don't worry be the Supreme
Courtney
you hear your fan tells us which
direction to go oh
[Music]
thank you
yeah have you been going to the gym
s oh
[Laughter]
of course I work out
six packs
it's the kind of it's winter time we put
a stop over there I'm hibernating don't
touch my eyes there's someone scared
it does not feel right now
hey
it's a substitute oh my god did you go
to the nail salon
oh
[Music]
get out of here
oh
my God
oh my god oh that's so scary
scary
what is this
I am dead hey wait a minute is this
mermaids no no no no no no no no
I can't tell if you're naked
[Music]
deep voice
I guess you can just go past that's fine
[Applause]
I'm scared
[Music]
I don't even know who this is
this Iris
[Laughter]
[Music]
I got it
all right
all right oh yeah I never know about
this view
I feel uncomfortable
laughs
oh my goodness
oh yeah I just saw some shark buns
that's so cute
it's so cute
[Music]
it's good
how do you turn off your name
yeah how do you turn off names yeah
oh yeah yeah
I think that's three okay
oh my God look at that you know we're
looking at it oh no the worm is between
them too no Ophelia
[Music]
um
are you guys
over here
who is this
oh you're not supposed to say who you
are you're supposed to say ah
um there you go there you go so scary ah
I'm so scared
are you scared of these rock hard yeah
[Music]
yeah
sharking shark games
what do we do
let's go
okay Mommy
okay I think it's the other way we go
this way and take a left
Mommy
this is how we exit found Kiara
oh
the secrets of the maze have not been
revealed
mermaid you have to see something follow
me
there's something for you
uh which way was it again
this way this way this way this way this
way
[Music]
oh my goodness oh my God
this looks like something that moving
true yeah that's my creation is right it
is
I like how the kohai's drawing is
scaring senpirus
go back to the beginning
[Music]
what are you
uh I'm a Frog oh I can only see your
silhouette
wait this isn't even scarier
come on
[Music]
this ain't nothing compared to old
phasmophobia
oh Cody's already in
oh
come here oh come here
pretty good
that is pretty good because I'm scared
oh my gosh
I suddenly want to sacrifice my whole
heart and soul
wholeheartedly
cold-heartedly oh my goodness
please
take my heart
and my eyes
Courtney you're missing a heart you
might as well take it all
I bow down wait
wait
oh
[Music]
take me
please
oh wait what is this what it's heart the
heart oh there's more there's more red
hawk sacrification which way do you guys
want to go this way or oh
this way oh
maybe there's a dead end
what do you see
[Music]
what
oh
is that what you saw
what what is this one just like cute
little frog
oh hi okay
it will go this way
wait wait wait we didn't see everything
wait is it just a dead end no no this
one's a dead end over here
wait is this the dead end oh what
no no there's more where
fauna how would you get in there
how'd you get in there
should I clip oh
I see
oh
the sounds of the others are fading away
oh okay so this is the exit oh
did you see any more
no
um
well it's spooky I like the atmosphere
me too ambiance
oh wait where this way
wait I thought this was oh okay there it
is
I hear screams in the distance
oh shortcut to beginning there was this
where we go
yeah yeah uh
I hear screams in the distance
why are they screaming I don't know
wow
oh my God what is happening oh you guys
are back
he's back okay
this time opposite so uh if council
could go to the mirror area and uh she
almost died what she was doing did we
get too scared now worth it
we scare not I think we get too scared
now I'm ready
[Music]
trained for this my whole life
to be able to I Got the Feeling we won't
I don't know Iris was already scream
screams the one
being scary
but cold
oh
it's The Wizard of Oz
Moving Castle
oh
sorry
because because
wow
oh I've gone
too too far
I've gone too far okay okay I didn't I
didn't go anywhere I didn't go anywhere
okay
well
what was that sound what was that
I'm scared already
here I left her umbrella her parasol
hello
but if you make it what
how'd you do that that's good
that one was scary
whatever that was that was good
okay we'll do that we should do that
yeah that's so good
sounds more like a small dog
oh I like The Grudge that's pretty good
you brunch South
hey you sillies
my animal wait you're not supposed to be
here
you're not supposed to be
big
[Applause]
[Music]
all right you guys can now change into
the avatars that you guys have the
monsters oh okay oh that's scary awesome
yeah and you guys now it's your turn to
turn to try to Spook the spook yeah you
guys have monsters too
oh okay I don't know if I'm supposed to
show it on stream
I'll show it now it's okay oh
well I'll hide it
I don't see myself
yeah that was pretty dike
yes
oh I like this one no it's really dark
here
oh
face me and then we all pick this one
cute nice
[Music]
images
oh my goodness
mushrooms
all right just wait one second um okay
let me make sure that there I will be
right back do you guys wait here
a chew
s
oh my gosh
where's my chew
s
okay come on you guys we can go into the
maze now just you know hide whatever you
like okay okay foreign
to my left
I feel too crazy when I do that
whatever that mushroom was heard me do
the crazy laugh
terrible laughs oh
that's pretty scary
wow
[Music]
oh there's a mushroom
it didn't work at all
you're still part of nature boo
they weren't scared at all
I was too shy to do the laugh
s
should I do the laughs
bears
I I'm trying
I'm too shy I have a crazy laugh but I'm
just too shy to do it
you can do it it's okay okay sounds
awesome I bet okay I'll do it
will they come back this way
I have to sneak up on them
[Music]
oh my God I'm too shy
whatever
I'll do it
inspired by said pies I cannot be so
embarrassing in front of them they're
gonna think I'm weird
[Music]
thank you
wow yeah it's very different
the machine and so cute and I got really
flustered and was trying to draw her but
do you think that was scary and then I
made that instead do you think that was
scary
do you think they heard it I'm scared my
microphone's not even picking it up
[Music]
oh
I want to say thank you for the guide
[Music]
stuff here
you go inside here
[Music]
you guys have to go in and pay we go
inside the price
[Music]
noises there's noises
oh
nice try though
not even a little
bit
[Music]
by that
is my camera
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my God
hello Mike
my brethren
have you ever tried cutting them
[Music]
I don't eat mushrooms
that's why I don't eat them yeah
[Music]
just creeping on them
releasing some bats
oh my God you're bad not the mushroom
bro
we shouldn't eat the mushroom it's
poisonous
oh my God is becoming a predator oh my
God
oh
[Music]
all right
came right up to my face with the
mushroom
okay
your face oh very cute
oh it's very soft and smooth
[Music]
you guys would like to exit
over here
[Music]
is it getting louder is it just me
good it's dark in here
today very dark
out of everything
who is that
to the exit you guys can follow the
blood steps to the eggs
[Music]
it was the cute little boo
no there we go oh my God
oh my God who's not waiting at then
did you chew again
it's probably two again oh
hi
oh never mind
come here harmless come here Iris the
harmless oh wait what are you guys
planning on doing come here
oh thank you thank you please don't take
my buttons my buttons are important to
me
oh no not another two monster
mushroom no no no two wait mushroom
mushroom
appearances
I think we made it
looks like yours are Gary
Gary
okay guys
oh there's only one round here
I don't know I'm kind of getting like a
Marv did I hear stuff Marv
Marve yeah
I guess Gary who probably works a little
better but one is
[Music]
you're under the mistletoe together
oh yes we have a special Premiere that
we are going to be watching in the
auditorium and we're gonna go back there
now
so if you guys if you guys could follow
me and switch back
let's go
okay everybody's here everybody's going
sorry all right we're cute again oh
come here
[Music]
oh there we go
so cute everyone
here
okay I think we're all here if you guys
can follow me into the auditorium do not
press any buttons
green
[Music]
tomatoes
red
um actually
no idea how this looks like it's cute
it's floating
all right
now I think originally I'll wait till
everybody's here I'll get up on this now
make a quick announcement
[Music]
no that's it oh you guys are welcome to
take a seat you can stand if you like
um okay so originally we're gonna have
some performances but uh it looks like
it didn't work out in time if anybody
does want to perform now's your chance
you could do show and tell you maybe you
want to show us you can juggle or maybe
one
does anybody want to come up anybody any
volunteers no I've seen so I'm okay
okay well we do have uh for chat and for
you guys
are special
yeah is the original video
no way
in uh here and uh so if you guys want to
get a good view a good seat now's a good
time I'm gonna turn I got front row
seats
and I haven't seen this either
what I didn't know this was happening
oh
grit oh my God
Irish hasn't seen it either I don't
think yeah no I haven't seen it you guys
is this screen it's black
[Music]
I see a black screen I only see a black
screen you guys are all ready
[Music]
here we go
hold on any second sorry my light stick
is the sideways don't mind me
ah
[Music]
reactions
oh my gosh
she's waiting in the closet tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
we're about
oh my gosh
[Music]
so good
trick or treats
it will premiere on my channel so you
guys after the stream if you want to
re-watch it you can go there and we
watch it as many times as you'd like and
I'm going to
[Music]
and also Twilight 3D it's so awesome so
many people worked on it so thank you
everybody that worked on it thank you so
much and thank you guys for watching
experience
thank you
for this that was so good good yeah
thanks for organization
yes Encore Encore
um
[Music]
the camera
down in front
oh
wait a bit that was bad this star too
[Music]
your oh she's waiting in the closet
tonight
I just noticed the graffiti yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
it's so radiant
this is
[Music]
Empire
[Applause]
[Music]
singing songs
good job everyone
it's so good
[Music]
amazing lyrics
um if you guys want to follow me to the
reception area
[Applause]
oh I just noticed their mic stands too
okay
here yeah
all right
help me good job a lot of bikes
[Music]
I'm here perfect hi um
is this like a real party we're gonna
jam out a little bit and then we'll say
goodbye to everybody you guys I thought
you did some cool screenshots so dance
together Waltz together hold each
other's hands hug each other whatever
you want to do dance on the tables dance
on the chairs
please
yeah we're both kind of long we can wrap
around each other
oh yes
wait this is a breadstick I just
realized yeah
[Music]
what a spooky scary song
Bad Girls
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
I'm trying to fix it
um
massage
[Music]
oh it works okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you guys for watching the
Halloween stream I hope you guys have a
safe fun Halloween happy Halloween
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]