[Music]
[Applause]
oh e
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
n e
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
pap
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n e
[Applause]
[Music]
KY okay okay okay okay okay
okay
K actually I should be here
howdy truckers
howdy are you ready to truck some
more cluck cluck clucking Trucking
there's no difference it is all the same
cluck truck all the same if you know
play the
game
he uh y truck
simulator is on on
again let me put it on oh yeah how did I
start the game before oh yeah wait that
was like a pain in the ass
previously oh starting the
game I think I'll just start it
[Music]
normally what the what the [\h__\h] what
what's happening is that the game where
is it I
[Music]
here wait my mouse is not moving it is
Task Manager time once
again oh my
[Music]
god oh oh my God when I'm the mouse
doesn't
move oh it's already annoying the [\h__\h]
out of me
why why is why is a game that could
potentially be so good it's such a pain
in the ass
oh okay every time I need to move
something task manager here we
go there we
go new update is that why is that why
it's a pain in the ass right now that
the mouse is like wiggling in the middle
wearly anyway I think I think we're we
got it we got it I don't know I still
have to figure out what was the best
position for me to be in uh but right
now I I'm I'm here because of my
walkie-talkie
thingy my shirt is bugged what yeah uh
Germany rework in the Rin region not
that I really know that place much at
all or care about
it uh but hey Germany let's
go go away go away go away go away steam
why won't you close the window can I
close steam okay good I forced it to
close all right uh today is not Koke uh
your truck just so you know just so you
know just so that we're understanding
each
other oh was that where Doom me was
oh I didn't real realize that doesn't
matter but maybe oh maybe we
can maybe we could go ah we'll see we'll
go here and
therey I still want to adjust it I still
want to adjust it why does I why why
does it have to be like that want to
adjust window have to go into task
manager all
right okay we're back in this game but
but uh last
time last time we played this
I I was um [\h__\h] around a
lot uh okay it's kind of [\h__\h] loud
too why is it so loud please be quiet
actually let me just turn it down over
here is it too loud for you guys I think
it's fine right for you guys uh we were
messing around a lot we trucked around
and found out uh I I feel like that you
know caused me to maybe not get as much
exp as I could have possibly
gotten it's kind of
loud uh so today we'll we'll play
properly we'll play prop oh wait that's
not the music oh ah that's a different
music what's this music called then if
that music that's playing right now is
not music then it's uh UI Music Volume
oh
yeah okay shut up get
away uh
sign [\h__\h] I was
like before my stream I was like making
and eating a salad and like GH I ran out
of time I was like eating it a little
bit in the loading screen too and I was
rushing to get all these assets going
and stuff and yeah yeah something has
been forgotten and that was the starting
tweet starting no tracking
now come here everybody truck with
me together we're Trucking and together
we're
clucking oh tweet should be out now I
hope
so okay I I don't remember how to play
this game how how
how not even point tonight I don't
remember you guys have to help me uh uh
uh uh uh and you'll have to help me
figure out how to not get [\h__\h] fined
for every little [\h__\h] Game Change
detected to avoid game save compability
problems due to changes in the game
World any unfinished deliveries were
canceled with no penalty I don't think I
had anything
unfinished welcome to the new desktop
from here you can interface with all
functionality within the game I'm I
don't
know from from now on you can purchase
your own
trailers but but that doesn't that's not
part of the upgrade that's just part of
the normal game progress right an
upgrade or paint them to match your
truck your trailers can be stored in
your chosen garages they can be used by
your drivers to increase profits to I
just I don't care I just want a simple
truck I just simply want the truck in a
very simple
way switch off fines if you want nah
it's not that bad B that I'm like like
oh the fines are like ruining everything
no it's it's fine it's
fine uh
so how's this how's this go again uh the
jobs quick jobs it's the only thing I
can do still
anyway okay oo there are some well paid
ones that are starting from
salsburg h
although might want to check like this
is this is uh yeah important this is
standard and
fragile standard and high value okay
M wait
how what does it say how far it
is I guess well this one's really well
paid though sheesh
[Music]
oh my
God task
manager oh
okay H the best is to switch to sword uh
price per Kil oh okay oh yeah oh there's
a price per distance I don't see price
per
kilometer just price and price per
distance
are you sure that that's a
thing oh
[Laughter]
oh
hold
[Music]
oh oh 26 EUR per
kilometer yeah I guess I'll do that
we're going to Bruno we don't talk about
Brun
no we don't talk about brw no no no no
okay how [\h__\h] it's night it's night
time man I don't think I ever started at
night
before okay oh a nice I can't even see
how do I turn on the lights again uh L
for lights probably we want
the is there a
difference is that the the lights didn't
change but I clicked
twice
oh good start Good
Start feels wobbly actually I kind of
want to do full
screen this is can I do full screen
please actually unless you got to force
me to use it to do it on my on my right
screen uh
[Music]
options uh uh full screen
yeah no I went to the righted
screen no [\h__\h] you no why do you suck so
much no why do you move over there I
hate you just going to make you bigger
than
um this one
maybe now it went to the other screen
again but it's okay I can move
it is it bigger now yes it's bigger it
fills up pretty much the whole screen
pretty much it might be missing
something somewhere
though okay oh okay okay we're good
let's
go no it doesn't I can't select the
screen yeah yeah I manually dragged it
but then it returned to Window
mode it's whatever this is [\h__\h] up
everything's [\h__\h]
up oh God this feels so weird
a aren't we carrying aren we carrying
fragile
stuff okay it's
okay how are we already at 8% guys makes
no sense to
me go go go how much time do we have 2
hours
h i I don't understand so the top right
is the time it is now right right and
the the bottom left time like under the
kilometers per hour is the time the
deadline and the kilometers that are
left and and and the hours that the GPS
thinks I'm going to take or that I have
left as oh it's estimated so it's not
the
deadline
okay what's your ET what's your
EA what's your EA what's your
EA what's your ETA what's your
[Music]
ETA your
arms
apparently there was a
comet to be
seen uh last night or
so what's up with that is that
common in Portugal yeah I just saw some
ducks seeing reacting to the
comet in Portugal where did it land do
we
know do we know where where it went did
it land on Earth or did it go somewhere
else I guess we would probably have it
in the news if it landed right because
that would probably be we may have a lot
of
passing comments but uh rarely Landing
comments right that would probably be
news right bigger news possibly bad news
right they oh comments don't hit Earth
me oh so wait just because it hits it
changes the definition
oh I didn't know
that
metor most of them burn up in a not at
all ah when's the last time a meteor
landed on Earth Google now tell me
entertain me guys entertain me
uh
tunguska no not 65 million no
way surely there's been recent
ones not that long ago small ones land
all the time but they're tiny by the
time they do
oh they land every day
wow wow so busy this
traffic why do we allow these Outsiders
onto our planet
huh without we have to stop them we
don't have space for so
many
meteors I
am I I vouch I pledge I pledge to be to
take care of okay cool I see what's
happening already they're already
manipulating
me yes I must I must protect the Earth
from outside influences like meteors
it's too much we cannot take anymore
we've taking that big one 60 million
years ago
apparently and look what it has done to
us
what crash vehicle offense who the [\h__\h]
did I crash now
ah [\h__\h] manipulation
again I do not stand for that
I didn't do [\h__\h] check your mirror
there's nothing
there there's nothing there so
ridiculous it was so upsetting it made
me miss my exit and now I'm super slow
because I stopped [\h__\h]
ah wait I like this scenery
though
a I don't think
I've did I drive to Vienna before yet
last time
because I don't remember seeing this so
properly maybe we just left Vienna or I
don't
know previous but we're we're leaving it
now
too yeah yeah yeah yeah I did really
this feels like
new no no no no [\h__\h] you crashed into
me no for real though like what what
what what what am I getting charged
[Music]
for
guys where where's my
lawyer
help I was I I why would I stay in my
Lane when I want to switch
SL
huh that was that was that's what you do
sometimes when you drive and that's what
I was trying to
do how do I see the mirror camera can I
add one to the
screen turn how the [\h__\h] do I do turn
signals
huh there's no way I need to do that in
the game
oh the sun is the sun is rising
[Music]
wow
F2 nice okay but different
uh M okay okay yeah that one's fine I'll
put it there
yeah brackets for indicators nah no way
I have to do that
[Music]
ising
myself like that
in guess what that meant also this is uh
the I think
yeah
the don't now in German we say don't now
not
[Music]
not Australia
Austria is my hood is my hood Austria is
mAh
Hood welcome to Mahood welcome again but
we're leaving
Austria and we're going to where are we
going check where were we
going point out the landmarks uh
[Music]
yeah this very Tree on the right
side this tree uh that's the tree that
uh Mozart used oh [\h__\h]
you [\h__\h] nasty
bastards Mo used to pee
on uh when he was uh 20 6 years
old yeah
that tree is a holy
tree and thanks to his pee whenever you
touch the tree it will automatically
play some beautiful classic music from
Mozart it's a great tree one of the
greatest trees of all
trees
yeah we have been already met by these
like well I have mirror NE next to
mirror here is mirror setion actually
we've met by these like police uh path
changing police people like three times
already now what the [\h__\h] I've been fin
for crashing into nothing two times
already what the [\h__\h] genuinely what the
[\h__\h] change to the right rear view
mirror you
mean what what button was that again oh
y y sorry sorry sorry s oh okay see like
now I was going to say okay now we're
crashing for real for real but I
actually
didn't for
once when I was actually about to see it
happening instead of being gaset into
crashing into supposed cars can you not
stop there please I don't have time for
this
[Music]
thanks by wait what button did you guys
say did you say
something isn't this where I came from
well we've had some some manipulation so
far by the game
yeah
F2 so you want you want this
one not that it's going to help me much
let's be real
cow
cute H are they real yeah they're real
they be moving
they be move move
moving stepped off of my gas for that
one well it feels like I'm still
stepping off of my gas with how slow
we're
going
thanks
thanks uh I've been watching a bit more
Shogun don't worry I want spoil you or
will
I no I won't I won't I've been wanting a
bit more shun I think I'm at episode
four now
maybe yeah it's good it's good that you
guys recommended it to me I recommended
back uh Uno reverse card he's
good finally also see some good
violence glad you like it so far it's so
good yeah it's a shame it's so short but
how many episodes does it have when when
do
I when am I when am I going to be doomed
10 oh okay that's fine Fallout had less
I
think kept on telling my mom to to go
watch Fallout and she's like yeah yeah
yeah like she likes Fallout the games
but couldn't motivate her to immediately
watch it even though she believes that
it's
good what's with these
paths why is there what's going on
there I guess they like Circle back and
then I'm going that I will be going down
that road for
Real uh I'm not yes oh yeah mhm I
remember you guys were here before
you're still not done with your [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you well I'm just going in
circles I'm just going in
circles it's like M penguin drum all
over
again no it's not no just because just
because it has circling or turning in
its title does not mean that it's a good
reference for this
occasion okay we're going
there looking an endless loot man don't
ah oh my God I was about to miss it
thank
you what do I do what do I how do I get
back up oh no a oh no no no no no no I
can get out of this situation how why is
my why is my truck so so freaking
fragile like I mean no what what sorry
don't go away what's the
button
no how do I how do
I how
I have seven
what and then
enter [\h__\h] hell
man 1,000 the trip will take 2 hours
48 but I need to that's I need to [\h__\h] I
need to get
somewhere no n this your customer
expects deler very soon um show me the
[\h__\h] map there
show me the [\h__\h] map show me the map
how how
how uh soon what do you mean with
soon can you please I don't think I'm
understanding the language English right
now please uh support me with your
translation services
guys what is soon TM
uh hello hello hello
hello thank
you well
whatever better late than never
right I've been here before
right I feel like I toed myself to this
place
before oh come on [\h__\h] the red
lights I don't have time for it
oh Bruno is right over
there
Bruno it's right around the
corner let's go see I looked I looked I
actually looked I may have not stopped
but I
looked you saw it you saw I looked over
there 2.5 hours away from me or or I
don't understand that
[\h__\h] is Friday
12:46 n it just changed so it should be
the the estimated time of my arrival but
when is when do they want me to
deliver
F6 uh expected oh in 20 minutes I
suppose
uh yeah
wow
uh yeah that's not going to work out
unless I suddenly find out how to make a
do demo
door we were totally unfairly
manipulated right off the GetGo what the
[\h__\h] where's my where's my neide luck
huh maybe we should put some never ride
armor on this truck
so
that all the fragile cargo will be
safe gas gas I'm trying to go fast and
70 kilm per hour sounds fast but it
feels like like I'm a
shne a
shne
Uhn snail yeah oh okay this is
interesting in German
if you want to be like like he hot babe
oh that's a hot babe or like a cute cute
girl so you can say
sneer it's actually a common flattery to
call someone like a cute snail or so but
in English I've never heard that before
but in German it's like super I don't
know
why like what's cute about the snail
okay no let's be real uh as long as it's
not one of those naked snails that have
no house and are just Brown like poop
then they can be perceived as cute but
not like you would like use that as I'm
not gas Ling you for real where are my
Germans
at we say that for real for
real ah no crash baby I slid through
that like a
snail like a that one too beautiful
Wawa is
rushing yes I'm speaking the truth it is
true this is true it is the truth and
still yeah so you could say wa is such a
cute snail but in English that sounds
pretty cute but in German it doesn't
sound that cute it sounds a little bit
more like
babe what what what what happened what
happened suddenly my head was in my
pants I don't
know what the [\h__\h] was
that what
happened what happened I don't know why
I was suddenly looking down I can't even
replicate that what what happened is
that a bug
it's like I fell out of my truck or I
thought it I thought it fell down
again I didn't click anything either
it's so
Random did your mouse malfunction maybe
I don't know could be but that's so
Random I didn't even move
anything and the heist sake oh yeah yeah
yeah you can say hi SN that's a hot babe
yeah people say that it's not even that
outdated feel like people still say that
today hot
[Music]
snail now the other way
around hot chick does not work in German
see that's a good example I'm teaching
in German you can say hot snail in
German but you can't say it in in
English but in hot chick you can say
that in English but you can't really it
doesn't work like that in German you
can't
say that's a an heis
cin especially cuz a chck is a
small oh this way ah I'm sorry I know
I'm sorry okay this time I'll admit it
cuz I even heard it normally you should
hear and feel the crashes this time I
did that
oopsie
close yeah
yeah
so yeah Uh something's um genuinely
wrong with you guys too in the English
language calling someone a hot chick
when what shouldn't it be chicken if
anything cuz chick is the baby what's
wrong with you
guys
H are you really qualified for this
job uh I'm doing it so I'm I'm I'm
qualified
automatically chicks be
H yeah when they're on the
grill on my grill about to be
fried 10 10 they do be
hot thank you oh [\h__\h] I turned my off by
accident yeah
B yeah B
who yeah yeah it's more like an insult
but I mean same way in English you can
use you are chicken as an insult too
so it goes both ways in English you guys
I guess you are a little bit versatile
isn't this the guy I crashed into the
yellow
one like it is
chicks are cute chicks are cute aren't
they are they hot though
no but it's
okay I'll I'll forgive oh I'm yawning oh
I'm that tired oh
[\h__\h] well yawning doesn't necessarily
have to mean I'm really tired right I'm
fine I only need to stay awake for 35
more minutes surely surely this is not
going to be a stardo valley
situation
right
right I hope so cuz then I'm going to
cancel this game I'm not going to play
it anymore
either oh kind of hot 40 C
approximately of a newborn chick the
body
temperature that's that's pretty hot
that is pretty hot I
mean hot it's it's
warm not hot would say it's
warm is M to sad no we talked about it
we talked it
out no she's uh she was like yeah no
problem you should play Terraria then
I'm like no thank
you no thank you
okay are we going that way yeah all
right all right all right what if I just
um go this way sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry Sor
please move please
move thank
you
probably did not really work like a
shortcut how I ended it
to cuz I had to stop my [\h__\h] engine
because that bastard slowed me down that
is probably my
competitor that's why he did that
[Music]
man uhoh it's red now burn burn burn the
Ring of Fire the Ring of
Fire are you shifting what does that
mean I have arriv arriv
[Music]
yippe
yippee I'm so late I'm so late I'm like
3 hours late or so
[Music]
okay
Enter uh sorry I'm already
late time taking 10
hours no wonder I was tired man Trucking
is hard life yo but I still got a a good
amount of XP let's
go
y next
oh that's the best paying job right now
H going back from where I am right now
sure why not it doesn't even have frag
fragile
stuff okay here we
[Music]
go leaving right
away did not even get time to look at
stuff H okay to calm
down not that
much good kitty good kitty who's a good
kitty yeah good job oh I'm
transporting
tractors oh it's green okay this is a
more friendly kind of beginning I feel
like green light
good
exit oh green lights again over there
beautiful sunny day no
rain y it only 3% let's
go good good good good good this truck
accelerates faster oh yeah I feel it I
feel it oh good
truck wow it's a machine
drive on the left side of the road or
you think I'm you think I'm going to
England or what I don't this game does
not take you to England does
it oh what's
this
River they have like sandbanks there no
I just look the reflection look like
it is this also the the newed
oh that little island is nice how do you
get
there I want to look at that that island
in the middle of the river looks
interesting tell me about holy [\h__\h] I'm
[Music]
speed we got to slow down a little bit
this truck is
fast
hyena hyenas
hos if you s say you should say that
animal's name hyena hyena just say it a
little bit more like
hyena then you're like saying in the
Japanese like slangy accent you're
saying oh [\h__\h] that's
Speedy cuz normally it's
ha ha and then maybe a n or
so like it's fast isn't it but if you
say
hyena then it's like speed
H hia that works too n not Qui
hia hi no cuz
haa haa
hia new greeting not not hi no no no
hi oh well okay understandable the
police was right
there but why are you not focusing on
whatever you're doing there with that
other car HH why you looking at me focus
on what you're doing right
now that was
$500
she it adds up
H all that money but I do I have to pay
the fines cuz I don't have to pay the
pay the repairs so probably don't have
to pay the fines either
right lucky I like this l
lifestyle nobody's firing me
either
called yo your name is
like
pretty oh my oh my God you must have
felt something when I was saying all
these
things you must have been like hey yo yo
she keeps on saying my name and like
H yo she loves
me all right right
side oh I think we're like almost there
no we are like there
yeah let's go
what I was chilling I was appreciating
where where am I ah I was appreciating
the
scenery okay okay okay it was that way
huh no no not vehicle malfunction come
on you can do it I'm almost there she I
didn't think they would like
that's how it went when I met that that
invisible wall it was not clearly
indicated other people can drive through
too like that other truck over
there they should [\h__\h] invisible walls
just like put a proper wall
there invisible walls are just [\h__\h]
lazy it's just because developers are
[\h__\h]
lazy man
then they blame me for it it was no it
wasn't those little those little yellow
arrows are not a clear
indicator because how can you expect me
to not be looking at the beautiful
scenery
yeah in a country like
this true see as a developer
true see
they're admitting to it can we go to the
airport can we free
Drive can we just like not take a job
and just drive
around can I explore
City you need your own
truck but they're so
expensive hey guys if you play the game
like how early did you just buy your own
truck am I playing it the wrong way by
always doing the the rented
trucks I just took a load after 4 hours
go in depth take a
loan but then once I have my own Tru
then I have to pay for all of the things
that just doesn't sound like a good
idea doesn't sound very
smart where are we going where are
we I have we going to
cats did we pass through
Vienna to go to grats cuz it felt like
it that looked like it was Vienna and
then I got Bamboozled and I thought oh
we're going to Vienna
yeah we did
huh today today today I looked
up uh prices and places to do my diving
license not my driving license listen
clearly clean your ears take a shower
and clean your ears I said diving
license [\h__\h]
thank God I'm still
swooshing looked up some stuff I don't
know I'm probably going to do it alone
there's some places that offer like
oneon-one it's just more expensive or I
join like a group of strangers not sure
what to
do not sure but yeah saw some saw some
prices and places I don't know I don't
know when to do it m
and then I felt like going to the Mal
Dives had this urge so I looked up some
prices but immediately scratched the
idea cuz I realized I'm
crazy but man the urge is
there I do want to go on a
vacation oh man maybe just like not even
males but like a
e danger danger danger really really
Slim
diet is paying off right
now uh what was I saying oh yeah maybe
just like a
small uh vacation within Europe and I'm
even thinking maybe I should go
alone isn't the mivs like sinking uh I
mean I wouldn't say
it's
sinking but I guess in a way is it
sinking it it feels more like the ocean
is rising
not like the males are sinking but I
guess relatively they are stinking at
the same time as as it's
rising if you see it that way I
guess
but but uh yeah you can still go there
but yeah we talked about this before
that in a 100 years the males will not
exist anymore which is terrifying and
fast inting at the same time but at the
moment it's a very popular Resort
destination for expensive vacations
especially
honeymoons so scary yeah and the males
isn't the only place where that's
happening too but the thing is the
males are uh will be gone as a whole for
other places it's like okay maybe a
little bit of their beaches are going to
be Tak over year by year but the whole
country is not disappearing for the
males it's like the whole place will be
gone cuz they're only small really low
Islands they'll be gone while other
countries maybe they only you know have
a certain percentage of its land being
taken over by the
ocean it's not it's not that
crazy but the males is [\h__\h]
up so that's a good reason to go while
you still can
huh can't stop me I have a really really
fast come
on
speed
[Music]
engine C
you wrote that
wrong they took the dive out of M wait I
didn't realized dive was in that
yeah more reason for me to go diving in
the M Dives and make a get a diving
license
first um but yeah I didn't I wasn't
really trying to go there I was trying
to talk about me considering maybe going
on a
solo
vacation May when could I go maybe end
of July
maybe cuz
uh-oh cuz um I think right after that
I'll probably be going to
Japan I
mean you would think I could take a
vacation in Japan but no I think I'll be
I'll have to be around on standby for
like dance lessons and stuff
go for it why not yeah uh you know cuz
Europe you know they have some decent
places I guess not as amazing as the
males but
yeah and it's been a while since I've
done a
solo vacation like
that so it's a bit in it's still always
a bit intimidating but at the same
time today when I thought about it I
felt like yeah [\h__\h] it I'm I'm going to
do it I kind of I mean I wouldn't mind
somebody joining me but I don't
think I don't think
anybody like you know everybody's so far
from me right hey yo I didn't crash
anyone map please thank you uh
everybody's so far from me so like you
know let's think somebody would go on a
vacation with me from America or from ID
I'm just choosing Europe because it's so
close to me but I wouldn't Rec I
wouldn't necessarily recommend it and
suggested if it's about
going
uh open open
open thank you if it's about going to a
vacation together then then I would say
you know let's go let's go meet
somewhere in the middle or go to
somewhere more interesting Europe has
some cool places too but then I I I
probably wouldn't choose Europe if it's
somebody coming from a different
continent like that un actually no
though I guess Americans and ID people
too like maybe they do kind of feel like
oh I would like to go to Greece someday
and see that
famous uh you know white and blue
scenery
sometime I guess I guess that's
something these non-european
might be interested in huh but I just I
I I have seen a bunch of places in in
Greece and Spain and Croatia and Italy
and I would still choose males over it
even though it's so [\h__\h] expensive so
at least it could be much cheaper that's
that's the good thing about it and it's
faster for me to go
[Music]
there but
yeah but I don't know if I can really
squeeze it in I'm kind of busy I'm going
here I'm going there and then I feel
bad like not being able to
stream I don't
know I'm thinking about it though maybe
you know even just like if I go alone I
feel like I might just go for like 4
days or
so it's not a waste of time not that
much time it doesn't take up that much
time
especially cuz it's
close well SCA beaches I want to yeah
yeah yeah I will go to Sea beaches
eventually Thailand and Bali to Greece
gree or Italy or Spain or France the
south of France man I kind of want to
check it out but the south of
France I think I wouldn't want to go
alone to anywhere in France because
I don't speak
French
and it's a bit difficult without French
knowledge over there I
think thank you welcome to the
stream is that a
coconut yeah yeah yeah
yeah
pre-recorded yeah I could do that at
least for like one or two days but you
know I always prepare some kind of
content when I can so it would it'll be
all
[Music]
right all right let's [\h__\h] go from
the land of
the uh
90 turned
money to Germany
stardard Shar was so far down there huh
[Music]
H reworked content that ah I guess that
part is reworked okay well not not like
we'll see the difference I I won't
notice the
difference all right here we go we
sorted price uh best price by
distance should be should be the best
thing we could do right
now I'm from that region let's go
what a shitty path this is but actually
kind of
cute very very
secretive oh a good news I think o nice
River I H what the [\h__\h] are you doing
here look at that dead pan face you
don't give a [\h__\h] you don't give a sh
you're not even real you're just a
[\h__\h] robot huh are you you have no
feelings and dust you do not care about
the damage you do to me you're just here
to destroy me make me
feel
worse all right all
right he's dead
inside yeah just like me I can't I can't
I'm pressing forward and it's still like
sometimes just does not go
man why did you have the have to be
there at that moment huh it's like you
planned
it all
along okay I was going to say I
think I uh I'm just missing one more
reply but I'm pretty sure that reply
will be a positive one uh so it's so on
guys Yoo even even the truck is getting
excited and bouncy it's so on the the
the Minecraft one block with myth
project is so
on and June looks also very possible
right
now like starting from middle of
June around
there yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay so I'll have to look into how
to make that cuz I think think I have to
make a server right I have to buy a
server and host
it um I know for like big big big
projects I can get the company to buy
and you know like do
it but I don't know it's a smaller kind
of project I don't know if they would do
it for this thank
[Music]
you well this is kind of kind of kind of
going into the direction of the car that
I I I'm considering getting kind of
lowkey not really though not
really yeah I mentioned this uh when did
I mention this yesterday actually just
yesterday and I quickly
gathered some hell yeah let's
goes
yeah yesterday I I I you know I I
somehow I don't know how I remembered it
but I said oh yeah I wanted to do one
block ages ago with
Ena but then I realized I kind of want
to do it with
myth yeah it will be a fun
project where we focus on playing
Minecraft for like a couple
days maybe two weeks or so even I don't
know I don't know how long it's going to
take but I did mention that I would
ideally ask everybody to like don't
really stream much else just focus on
Minecraft for one or two weeks so that
we can really get it
done and yeah seemed like everybody is
cool with
it I think this will be a really really
nice project for myth oh [\h__\h]
you where's the
police yay I'm
excited I'm excited for it yeah I like
smoke basically they they kind of
inspired me to think of it as a a bigger
project as well rather than just one
oneon-one
so excited me
too ah wait wasn't it something like the
person who hosts it has to be online
or is that not true for the others to
play I
mean not if you buy a dedicated
server okay I wonder how smoke did it
because I I from the compilation I
didn't see a single moment where they
they were completely
alone if it's locally hosted yeah you'd
be making a server to avoid that is okay
yeah I I probably have to do that how
much does the server cost
guys how much is
it it's a bit of a pain oh
really 15 year old oh okay oh easy
easy easy easy easy all right 10 101 15
nice okay now maybe I'll just ask the
company to do that for me and then take
it off of my my
pay cuz
like you
know
bureaucracy although that might make it
slower the
progress I'll see what I can do I'll
I'll ask like hey can you guys do this
for
me
please please dock my p i
yep well I can't stop the truck is so
fast okay
shortcuts what is this Customs oh I'm
being asked to go for
Customs oh what's the custom in this
country in Austria we uh say ala
Zen okay I'm starting the
process how did you not crash that SW
everything is in order let's
go wow wow wow wowow wow
W that was incredible right I I I I just
I was so scared but I couldn't even stop
the truck I wanted to I I backpedal so
hard oh
man
yeah yeah s found it oh thank you Daisy
how you you doing Daisy how you doing
how you doing another idea uh I had like
you know recently Minecraft is all up in
my
brain with Hardcore Minecraft and the
one block and stuff and I was
thinking what
if in like combination with like
maybe the book club Hobbit reading if
that ever happens so this could be like
this could be half a year in the future
or so but in combination with that with
all the members who participated in the
book reading what if we like find one of
those like uh Lord of the Rings servers
in Minecraft that are like that you can
visit like the Disney
one and you know go with that group and
make it like an a tourist to Minecraft
Minecraft tourism tourism stream in yeah
Lord of the Rings
world I'm sure there are
some no I'm not baiting them into what
what what what I'm not baiting anyone
into
anything I I'm so good at baiting people
don't even notice when and I'm baiting
them thus I am the master
baiter yeah yeah
yeah it's tough man it's tough this
audience is
tough It's A Hard audience
wow are we in do L uh since a while ago
right wow this is like kind of like
cinematic this bridge and then the tall
trees all over all I can see ah is tall
trees I don't even see my lights are
they on now
ah yes okay a [\h__\h] sorry I didn't crash
into anybody though you're
wrong smoothie eat the cable please you
have what
why
what dead corner now he's
dead well he deserved
it he [\h__\h] deserved it for making me
pay so much money funding for the server
anything for me thank
you yeah I'm already excited I uh I'll
start planning it maybe I'll even
commission a logo for it for us to
use
yeah I'm happy we can do this
together
yeah I think though probably our format
will be a bit different from smoke like
from how from what I can tell from the
streams it was usually just one person
streaming and they had
like or or was it because like they had
like all four of their life tods lined
up but there at the on the side I don't
know was what was it mostly just one
person streaming because I was going to
say um I'll probably just like say do
whatever you
want uh stream if you want do your own
POV if you
want yeah they had like a
unique thing going
on yeah my lights are
on because I was fine for it stream
POV not going to be much difference in
the beginning exactly yeah maybe the
first stream the beginning can can be on
my channel only and then from there on
out as we are building more and more and
uh everybody's a bit more scattered we
can have everybody do their own
povs sounds good sounds good I
think they're on they're
on I mean I don't know I don't really
see a difference for
you sounds
nice w
Germany let's go is it are we getting
there wait it's still 50 minutes away
and the sun has been setting behind us
beautifully gorgeous the lights aren't
actually okay these ones then because I
can do like this this is also apparently
on this is off and this is on but then I
can click again it's like still on but I
guess it's the the different kind of
Lights I don't know
Divine even hell yeah yeah I'm a little
bit motivated right now
to organize some of these things
huh
bird horor
[Music]
collab Minecraft
stuff who knows what else the W is
cooking who
knows but I think uh there's nothing
else I think but there could be any
moment now I could be cooking up
something
else o o o it's raining ah wipes how do
I wipe my shield again my shield my
glass
front W no idea yo I'm I'm I I know
about these things when you know about
it pretty
much windshield is how to
pee oh right oh it's pretty strong oh I
saw fer oh that reminds me I wanted to
talk about this I um I've flown so many
times now that I'm I used to be the type
of person
who uh takes out their phone and like
takes pictures or like uh time lapses
and [\h__\h] from the departure and like
nice pictures of the clouds and
everything I used to be that but I've
flown so many times and I don't really
care anymore and it's
pretty much like there there's some it
is beautiful uh often oh
Thunder and we're taking a look outside
every once in a while but um I've just
seen it all so I stopped doing it but on
my flight
bag got discovered I'm the first I'm the
first it shall be my
city y'all shall be my
subjects I don't think I've ever been to
stard
what's this what the [\h__\h] is
that that down
there what uh what was I saying oh yeah
so on my way back from where was I ah
silent uh in oh in the plane it was a a
Night Flight it was really dark and all
that and but I had a window seat and
Y I was like sleeping and then somewhere
at some point I woke up because the
[\h__\h] cabin is so [\h__\h] hot cabins
are either very uncomfortably hot or
very uncomfortably cold and when you ask
like some sometimes there's individual
events and sometimes there's not I
cannot believe that there are still
planes that don't have individual vents
for certain
seats because even when you ask like hey
can we do something about this
temperature wait where am I supposed to
go
they usually can't where do I go oh
there there is there an entrance there
doesn't really look like it on the map
man look like I stop here no it was
business class but I there was still no
it was generally regulated uh in the
whole cabin there was no individual
vents that was
crazy crazy I'm telling
you it's so hot that I couldn't sleep so
I I wake up and I I'm just
like and I look out the window no it
wasn't thae Airways uh it was uh the
other
one Turkish Turkish
Airlines and it was the older one I
think yeah the older cabin of Turkish
Airlines they have some new ones too of
course but this was an old one I'm level
eight now let's go or level
seven I know don't care
here don't know what it does but
yeah it was so uncomfortable but I I get
up and I look out the window and I see
stars and I
see I see I thought it was funer I'm
pretty sure it was funder pretty far
away this is something I have never seen
before uh on my million flights through
the world I like I tried to capture it
on my phone but but it was just not
showing on my
phone like for one second I was able to
capture like one Thunder but in IRL it
was much brighter and it was much more
frequent and all that a lightning yeah
yeah yeah yeah lightning duh um yeah and
it was so interesting to
see cuz I could see it like at like
around the same level of height and I
saw the wrath of God
but I was like shocked because within
this like area where it was
happening it it was like going down so
hard like there was so much lightning
everywhere like I felt like this this
must be a [\h__\h] thunderstorm over
there or
so
crazy but then IRL if you're in that
location it
probably doesn't feel like there's that
much I wonder like is it does it always
look like it's that much and then when
you're actually there it's it's not like
that but I don't know it was it was
crazy I got to use low ISO set I tried
like doing something like that with my
phone but nothing was really
working but it was so cool to see I've
never seen something like that before
and funs are kind of crazy Micro
Burst I've flown a ton and I've never
seen anything like that maybe you got to
look out the window more
ha no but you got to be lucky to see
something like
that 1 second exposure time usually good
for Thunder uhuh but I was trying to
take a video and it didn't have ISO
settings on the video I think I think I
don't know it was just so nothing was
working but I captured it with my eyes
and that's what's most
important they will try to avoid getting
close yeah it was very far anyway it was
very
far red
Sprites I'm such a huge fan M thank you
thank you thank
you
yeah k k come
Sita come Sita if the lights are on
inside it's no it was dark inside
actually it was
dark but still my phone didn't even know
what to focus
on my phone saw way less than me even
though my phone supposedly has a really
good
[Music]
camera okay ah we just chilling while
driving isn't this wonderful what a
wonderful time yo this one pays way
better than the others
oh found her
again what was the W talking about huh
what could it
be she's speaking Euro she's speaking
German why should I
[Music]
say I tried so hard to go slow
or should I say Australian is what I was
going going to
say
chill oh thanks
man thanks
man I was talking about uh Austrian
trains getting way too
expensive like there's the in in Austria
you know in Germany there's the Doan and
in Austria there's the
UB what does it stand for
B Bund ban bundan maybe yeah okay that's
what it
is so that's the Austrian train and then
many years
ago it gained a competitor that
immediately got really uh popular called
bestest ban which
means
uh West uh for a I had to think really
hard what what West was in English it's
just west
yum no Crush
please uh West rail yeah
and and that was million years ago and
people really liked it because it was so
cheap
and it didn't go throughout the whole
country but it made some important
Connections in Austria like the most uh
like well traveled ones I
suppose and
um and the cool thing was also just
simple things like I really liked that
you can buy the ticket in the
[Music]
train because if you go into the UB
train without the ticket he's going to
be like what the [\h__\h] I will find you a
million euros no um but yeah they were
so cheap back then they were like half
the price of or even less than almost
almost even less than half the price and
especially there were like even cheaper
tickets too sometimes like special
tickets but generally even their main
prices were half half as uh expensive as
what the main
Austrian oh
KY thank you Kyla for the raid we're
talking about trains while
Trucking yeah Austrian
trains so yeah I liked using that
train and then I moved to Japan and this
and that and many many many years later
I come back and I I check out
the the vest B again and it's it has
caught up in pricing
it has realized that they have
sucked
H or kissed the Austrian asses
enough and has gained enough popularity
and enough Fame that now they can just
increase the prices like crazy and are
basically same price as the ubb so
now there's like no I don't I I'm not
going to use trains anymore because they
suck no sometimes you have to but so
expensive everything's so
expensive yeah I talked about this
before but I still kind of like it more
because I like the design of the trains
more from zest ban it's like green and
modern all the trains are so modern
while the UB they have some Modern
trains but then some dump trains are old
H nothing nothing there have you guys
seen
something yeah old trains and and the
colors are just
like boring color
scheme and
vban it's just cooler it's just cooler
because it was the the contrarian option
to I
yeah I like the second flooor they have
a second floor yeah they have some cool
seats I mean UB I think also H has does
it
no actually no I guess it doesn't have a
second
floor maybe on some
trains but not not really though but the
vest bu has second
floor so
cool there are time yeah pretty
much
usually I guess they have some double
decker but I guess they're mostly I
would think they're mostly um used for
different
routes UB really is better if you have
like one of these like whole country
tickets or one of those summer tickets
or whatever but I'm never I never get
those or the inter Rail ticket that's
like for all of Europe I think if you
want to travel for Europe my friends
have used this ticket before it's
amazing you can travel through all of
Europe for so cheap with the inter Rail
ticket I think that's the one right if
you ever think about doing like a Europe
trip and you want to you like
trains then I really recommend this from
the experience of my
friends m
but uh this one's like kind of I think
wait can you have it anytime throughout
the here cuz like from what I heard it's
like a Summer ticket or is that a
different one from what I heard you have
to use it in summer oh wait this is a oh
we're in V oh the o the O right oh God
yeah B I got
distracted
oh oh I don't think we've been so deep
into Vienna
before
Oh
SC oh
good ah for inter rail there's an AG
restriction as well ah yeah yeah oh
isn't this uh oh my God wait this
is wait no oh wait what is this is yeah
this oh my God this is some shampon
Palace right over there and then behind
it isn't isn't that trampol Palace over
there yeah y you can see look at that
lit up in in the back the lit up thing
building in the back the beautiful one
it's a big beautiful big big big
historical Palace it's beautiful do I
get I this is so worth it getting find
if I do but I don't okay cool look oh
weting
[Music]
cool
wow and then behind that Palace there's
actually you can't see it now I guess I
didn't even model it I think but there's
a big hill and a big garden and there's
the zoo the the oldest zoo in all of the
world was it the world or was it Europe
I think the oldest zoo in the world
right is over there and um and then if
you go up there's a a a nice another
what do you call it again uh gloriette
which is like a style of
building uh in E European
architecture uh it's also you know very
historical stuff really
cool uh and it's there it's up there if
you go up the hill yeah cool stuff cool
stuff I'm so excited that I got to see
that within the
game better than geoguesser at showing
you guys around this game is doing a
better job at that so far at least
although ah I want to play tesser again
because I've heard that after I played
it actually quite a long time ago
already
uh they updated the Austria Maps so that
you don't always end up in the same two
cities so we could play it again because
it's not as [\h__\h]
boring and repetitive as it was
before Germany too I
guess they must have heard my complaints
yeah
yeah so maybe maybe it's time for the
first time in a million years to bring
out the geoguesser subscription again
did I cancel it or do I still have it I
think this one I
cancelled ah oh Google Maps yeah I guess
it has to do with Google Maps
M I can see the beautiful stary sky in
in my
mirror wow
good am I late by the way what is it
F6 uh remains 4 hours 30 oh but I 40
I'll be there in 1 hour and
wow
speed empty roads and stary nights
yeah I can imagine if you
drive through that it's really beautiful
as long as you're not tired then it's
amazing making good time when you don't
crash mhm and good
money more upbeat music start oh wait
did you guys I don't remember was the
music in this game copyrighted did you
guys say it
was probably
is and I could turn on my own music but
I'm really just just like last time I'm
just enjoying the silence and just
yapping over the
silence it
is normal radio oh I wonder if it's oh
it would be so cool if they just oh it
would be so cool it would be so cool if
they played local radio
maybe even
live or recorded uh
sessions like austan radio and like yeah
they do like
real real
ones
what oh
[\h__\h]
sorry you need to put the URL in the r
oh you can a you can make your own radio
I see I
see
cool oh I would totally do that if I was
playing this game just for fun
privately I'd probably totally do
that
lo real most likely you can't play yeah
yeah yeah I'm not going to do
it obviously
uh they have some already loaded
ahuh and are those live too or are those
uh just record it and maybe edit it to
fit the time or the place through
in you should be live for real speeding
again I don't know I don't know why my I
don't know why my truck is so
fast is there a um I guess this is maybe
a thing with like modern cars is there a
feature where you can like cap your
speed probably right like modern
electric cars you can probably do that
like
uh there is right picture what what
cruise
control is that only on like electric
cool new cards or also an older ones
press C
what's what does it
do no all oh really oh it's on every car
oh
really
[\h__\h] no I am not accepting this I'm
going back come
on perfect that's good
enough go
what we are doing so well in
time calibration engine w w w whoa W
interesting Temple mod
aha
interesting real trucker of that move is
that what real truckers
do OH police in front of me polia
oh no polia I'm so fast Slow Down slow
down yeah there we go
POA
okay
okay that is the
[Music]
fire well if uh my truck started burning
from that I would immediately uh
have no issues because there there is a
fire
there can I fit through what the [\h__\h] do
I
do that turn is too tight
though uh do I have space
there where do
I well we just got to commit some crimes
maybe for now
oh I can't oh no I can let's
go perfect perfect I thought I had to
turn the other way but no this way works
too
yay I made it I made it with a lot of
extra time on my hands
[Music]
yay y
I'm I'm here I've arrived thank
you
thanks yay
satisfactory hell yeah baby that's
that's what they say about me that's
exactly what they say about
me extra time but destroy right no no no
I did not no no no no you are you are
talking nonsense oh this is not good
money compared to what we just had but
we can go to
Italia so far okay it's time it's time
we go to Italia because I was just
speaking
Italiano where is that cute Italian
YouTuber who likes me where is she the
one with the eyebrows that's her right
she's Italian right maybe I can go visit
her maybe I can go visit her pun yeah P
where the [\h__\h] are
you now that I'm talking about
youh where's she
at
ech lights to thank
you before I get before I get
fined well let her know that she has
been
summoned she is
sick sick as hell no not good not funny
not
interesting way way
overdone she seems to be intimidated by
you that's
probably a lot of people intimidated by
me
but actually no like if anything within
the Indies I think Wawa is the most uh
out of Holo within Holo W is the most o
[\h__\h] off going to get find because you
bastard W is the
most one of the most ah open and
inviting and welcoming and talkative to
Indies I would
say approachable yes approachable is
probably the best word
but I mean I will admit maybe I was a
bit more
approachable like until like a year ago
or
so I've become a little bit less
approachable perhaps maybe in terms of
collabs um but I still like to be
friendly with them and
yeah I've watched some sometimes I peek
into some uh
indie or small
Coro debut streams
too and I'm like damn these girls are so
cute they're so
cute a [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] it's not fair I'm [\h__\h]
cursed I'm so
cursed yeah yeah sorry like in my
brain it's
uh it's like yeah sometime somehow it
feels like anything that's not like Holo
or nii or visho or even visho feels
because they are so free visho feels
more Indy to
me they just like they seem like they're
free to do whatever the [\h__\h] they want
so it feels very Indy to me um but like
anything that's not Holo or nii just
feel like Indie to me just from the like
atmosphere and
Vibe yeah yeah
yeah we sure just the wild
west yeah I mean it's good for them they
have uh a good relationship with their
company and stuff and like get so much
help and freedom and but you know just
just saying not not saying that any of
these things are not available to me but
like they can play whatever [\h__\h] game
they want they can play whatever music
they
want uh you
know but not saying that one's better
than the other
because uh my lack of so to say freedom
it sounds really it's a really strong
way uh strong word to use in this kind
of topic but my lack of that
uh is basically repaid in other
opportunities that I get thanks to being
in Hollow so One hand washes the other
yeah there's tradeoffs and for
me I think uh if that's what you want
and that is what I want then it's worth
it like being able to perform at such
huge
venues is probably the biggest
plus and
yeah
actually can't
compare with any any other place the
way we even in I and
ID the way we get to do all these big
things there's some more things that I'd
like to do that I'm also not able to
sure
but we still get to do a lot of cool
things that others don't get to do and
I'm grateful for that for those
opportunities and want to make the most
out of
it you know Advent having
they're in Japan together for a a good
amount of time Arc right
now reminds me of myth myths in Japan
Arc like it's it's like almost like I'm
looking at like I'm back in the past and
I'm
looking at the whole myth in Japan Arc
from an outside of
POV it's really interesting and it has
just
begun myth house it's not like it feels
like it's a long time ago but if you
think about it it was just like like one
year and a couple of months ago cuz it
was last year in January
February we just like had to wait a long
ass time to get to this
point to get into Japan and do all of
that took a long ass
time but it's kind of nostalgic looking
at Advent um chilling in Japan now
together as a whole
gen it feels nostalgic to
me
not oh [\h__\h]
get to 80 and press C aha okay I guess
you can't press C when you're in red
okay
see aha so I can't go over it now oh
seems like it nice thank you for that
man I'm going over the I'm going over
though what it wait I'm totally going
over what I'm totally going
over it's not
working press C and let's go oh oh it
will just stay around this without me
pressing W that's how it works
ah oh chill autopilot basic
Bally nice
thanks finally o I'm on autopilot be
careful yeah that's right you have to be
careful not
me everybody around me in traffic has to
be careful when I'm an autopilot not me
I'm chilling it's your fault
H nope nope I'm speaking sarcastically
guys
I guess this is not quite autopilot it's
just cruise control
hold
no this sounds like
my the and then the stop the
stops I've noticed recently
my stove does this
too uh when it's like not on 10 when
it's or or or 9 or 8 when it's like
seven or six freaks me out why is it not
just making a constant noise is it
malfunctioning oh my God I'll never be
fine for being too fast ever
again oh
no no we good we're good
sick oh yeah cuz somebody asked in the
chat a moment ago I saw
that the scenery is great um if I made
the pizza I didn't make it yet I'm
making it today stay
today and I bought the ingredients which
wasn't much not much necessary I'm
making a 300 calorie pizza today
which after doing research and realizing
how many calories an actual Pizza has
it's kind of insane 300
man it better be good
yeah I did not find the fancy starch so
I'm just going to go with my corn starch
Mya and I'm going to top it with turkey
peoni the
peoni and and maybe add some actual
pepperonis
the the sour a little bit
sour
and ones from
the uh yeah ah yes the peon yes yes yes
yes oh I don't know why oh okay I have
to go down okay it doesn't adjust to
that okay okay okay
okay start on it oh my God we're in
Italia where are my Italians Italians in
the chat Show Yourself wa it's 80 again
show
yourself step into
Italia oh oh please help me remember how
to speak Italian
wait I want to read comments
[\h__\h] does that say me it is
me the
Italian
[Music]
Salo let's go
I here ah
e
person oh wait how do you say again some
like Italian or Austrian or
so
noo Bavarian yeah because I I mean I
could probably because it's very similar
to just Austrian
dialect uh Italiano Italian
Austria Austria I I remember that from
my lessons but it was just Italiano for
Italians just like the
langage yeah we already mentioned
P were you did you just come into the
stream ah hey
sori I'm thinking of doing a Korean
dualingo stream next week hope I don't
forget about this thought because for
dualingo streams I have to uh I have to
like sign up for like permissions
basically very much in advance and give
them the stream reservation very much in
advance
too so if I want to do it next week I
kind of have to plan ahead very early
shall we remind you yeah maybe after the
stream yeah would be
nice yeah dualingo is kind of pain in
the ass to schedule pain in the
Brazilian buttlift ass of
dualingo nice ass man nice
ass
hey h
sorry that super that chat went away so
fast I couldn't read more than
allora that's what my teacher always
said Alora she thought she was very
Italian what the [\h__\h] is that bomb up
there so yeah I want to do Korean
dingo uh because I'm I'm I
smell I smell a ghost group collab
coming soon soon soon
soon we haven't said anything any dates
yet but we're getting closer now that I
can use my accents
properly
I I ended up or I am ending up as we
speak uh asking them to convert my model
in the end should have done that from
the
beginning um
I'm I it's such a face palm situation
man it's such a face palm situ I I can't
even if I talk about
the behind the scenes of this one very
simple
task cuz originally I I was waiting for
holo to do it for me then I gave up on
that after waiting for a
while oh
man and I'm only doing the conversion to
do a collab of kosu in the first
place and now I'm circling back to
asking them for their help after
all feel bad like relying so much on
them but they are
op they're so
good yeah but then thinking about how
I'm in the end going to ask them for
help I could have done that from the
beginning and we could have had a gole
collab maybe two months
ago
so
yeah is that your mom does have skin
under the clubs often this is well why
why why you looking at that eh why you
looking at
that perfect
H almost
crashed oh well my suit no my suit I've
had it since no maybe I mean I'm better
at using it now but I already had it two
months ago I think
I know I almost rammed it is this
Italia doesn't look so different so
far oh oh we're going to go for
Venice what Venice is so close doesn't
look like Venice at all in this
neighborhood she and going to go through
Verona not my shirona no we're going
through Verona I didn't sing that song
in my last K my EUR truck K remind me to
sing that song in the next one then
what's it called I didn't sing it did I
or did I did
I
shirona
shirona did
I what's that song is it called M
shirona oh okay I I think I sang
it but that's one of those rock songs
that I know for very interesting funny
reasons that I have explained to you
guys
[Music]
before can't remember any other part of
that song There's hot air balloons up
there cool
wait wait
what Okay C C
see okay this is looking a bit more a
bit more no not particularly Italian but
a bit more
Italian nice air
balloons and
[Music]
easy
easy he said e and I was on my way this
what does that even mean I'm for some
reason I'm just assuming
it's like whatever whatever that
was I had to go out and get that little
kitten INX just to play it oh nice did
you have
fun it was a really nice game I can
imagine even if you watch the stream you
might have fun with it on your
own oh okay that's what I thought mhm
mhm that's what I
thought oh [\h__\h] why am I pressing W I'm
so used to pressing W just leave it
leave it to the speed oh it's going down
though wait I have to press C again
wait
okay all right how do I cancel that how
did how did I cancel
it what are we past
vsia didn't look like vsia at all
V
Venice why say ven
breaks uh okay so where uh I'm Panos
Uber where is she I'm supposed to pick
her up somewhere
here panco where you at you little
sussy raccoon she's a raccoon right was
she a raccoon
no no P red Pond something what
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] red
Ponda Reda is probably more of an
insult red panda hey yeah did I tell you
my connection with red pandas hm did I
ever tell you think I
did did
I did I
hi I'll tell it again
okay so I love red pandas okay who
doesn't they're so cute
right um I am obviously a phoenix no
matter just to make it clear no matter
if I would have joined whole life or not
I've always been a
phoenix um but when auditioning for H
life
I uh you know made a little audition
tape and I uh thought oh I should role
play as something make myself like a
character to act
out and because I loved red pandas and
because I had a a great
name uh to like add to that
I made myself a red
panda in the
audition
yeah you didn't notice huh great all
right let me pay let me get a
through
okay yeah cute ride man the the thought
that I maybe could have been a red panda
but I'm a phoenix so so it was you know
just uh for the sake of auditioning
we're in Verona let's
[Music]
go Verona uh how do I say ah Ben V Ben
venuti was that good travel or was that
welcome I think it was
welome oh [\h__\h] Ben
venuti welcome right y I
remembered Verona ver
Verona ver Veron I've never been
here
before but yet it speaks to
me or maybe I have like with my mom when
I was a child and I just don't remember
may maybe I changed trains or something
in Verona before
because as a child I've definitely been
to Venice I
think pretty
sure I've done it once again that was a
good drive I mean some red lights and
stuff
but oh that's a lot of
exp
y one of the fast songs about Al of man
wanting oh [\h__\h] oh really
oh well it was uh different times I
suppose in terms of
Music should visit again yeah I
should yeah I should I want to go to
Italia okay let's do another one then
we'll get another level up where do we
want to go I want to do something that's
like somewhere else but they're giving
me so many Austrian jobs how come
but they're getting cheaper and
cheaper because my base is
there
milk if I don't deliver the
milk then all the wives in the world
will be forever
waiting for the milk I cannot let this
happen the
milk let me help out those dads really
quickly I must
help so that everybody can come back
because there's already milk at home
milk at
home K funny
so we're going from Switzerland to
Italia almost same thing ha just kidding
but I mean you got a bunch of languages
over there
[Music]
Switzerland it's like the Canadian
Canadia Canada of
Europe
maybe so confusing a country of so many
different languages main languages so
confusing man make your mind
yeah
nice nice Dodge we have like two well
well no wait okay so you have the sweet
Chad the sweet
sad do sweet do and then maybe I think
uh some of you speak a more normal
Deutch too it's pretty common too right
and then there's the Italian and then
what about wasn't it French too a a more
French uh French part of Switzerland
right are those the
four I think I nailed it my Switzer
knowledge is
impeccable
uh H this way okay now there were like
three paths okay okay this this is the
one oh I thought I missed
it no what
[Music]
come here come
here he missed exit TW what no I didn't
huh what what what
would it help if I turn around
here I'll just go
straight please show us the map what
you're seeing it bottom right not my
fault that your eyes are so focused on
the bottom left
V and this latine oh
[\h__\h] only spoken in Switzerland ranish
is it
ranish much is different
huh some some people in the chat were
saying that it's
confusing hm
wait I didn't know that was one of but I
guess that's very very unique
to uh
Switzerland uh which way am I go this
way
right oh okay well that was not the
worst
crash so we're good we're
good ALK
yes yes yes yes
yes that looks like a butt ah now it
looks like a ball
sack I'm sorry it is what it
is looks like a
very I'm sorry all right
well yeah well I'm yep moving
on yeah I'm not wrong thank you thank
you what do you mean you only see two
maps what are you talking about what
what are you guys talking
about I did not have a Red Bull
no just war
w w one of the cleanest tap Waters in
all of the world Austrian tap water
Switzerland is probably also up there I
think European countries in
general we
have very very good not not all European
countries though very good
how Japan tap water depends on the
region but I don't know how it is in
comparison
to other places but I think yeah our is
better that's for
sure I almost exclusively drink tap
water yeah like sometimes I drink
bottled water but I sometimes even think
the tap water tastes
better depending on the brand of the
bottled
water but if you can
get such clean and nice tasting water
out of your TAP why would you buy it
seriously I don't understand people I
don't get it it's cheaper I
think out of the tap obviously
right all day everyday
noise I use a
filter yeah yeah that's also a way of
making your tap water better but we
don't have to do that in Austria it's
just that
good I don't buy bother me
me me neither it's a waste of money
thank God I am privileged h
privileged I'm going back I don't
care they can't stop
me okay going to crash into
myself reversing on the [\h__\h]
autoban
unbelievable who the [\h__\h] is this this
driver [\h__\h] stupid
[\h__\h] is what they're
thinking understandable
understandable no I mean let's be real
that is even the road range that you
could uh
meet on the autoban or on anywhere on
the road
actually this was tame compared to what
you could be called IRL without knowing
because usually you don't hear it and
people are just cursing to themselves
thank
God Mama Mia Mama Mia Road R really
scares
me people who get too angry on the
road too scary chill the [\h__\h] out
please especially if you have other
people in your
car or truck in that
case I hear Vienna is the rudest city in
the world uh I don't I didn't hear about
that I can say Vienna's waiters are well
known in the C coffee
cafes to be rude but that's just the
culture but I mean
then again they say Vienna is the the
world or
Europe yeah
like bet what what is the best place to
live in easiest place what friend no not
friendly but like what was
it bad
tempered I wouldn't say so though I
wouldn't say so what the [\h__\h]
yeah what what what about
France just kidding yeah like Paris just
Paris in
particular I'm sure there's worst places
out
there yeah quality of life I think that
was the thing that Vienna capital of
Austria
is being told that they are go hard
interlockin wow I like this this I like
this this kind of tunnel where I can see
the mountains
beautiful now I cannot see anymore damn
it guess we're going through the
mountain
now people can be rude as
[\h__\h] how is that even measured
though if you one might say if you were
experiencing this root Behavior maybe
you were root in the first place wow
are we in Switzerland right now or
Italy because this is amazing it would
be very much what I expect of
Switzerland let me see
uh I think that's still Switzerland cuz
Baron is
close yeah we're in switzland yeah yeah
yeah yeah she she so beautiful man
Austria is like Austria is really
beautiful
too but
like I feel like Switzerland is
more what's the word like wherever you
are and wherever you look it's like that
while in Austria it's like there's some
extremely beautiful places but it's not
like everywhere some places are more mid
but then twitch is more uh like
everywhere everywhere like
that uh this way
yeah con con con consistently that's the
word I was looking
for
consistent consist
consistently the godart tunnel oh this
one's famous this is the godart
tunnel oh never heard about it because I
I never drove or was part of a
driving
Squad in this area in Switzerland at all
I've barely been to
Switzerland just one
time didn't see much oh wait why am I at
70 what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
nice
she said
f that's just the word
for like the
drive in
German you little
shits ah wait I have to go here a little
bit lower there we
go uh straight
I get faster
why 6,000 chickens in
cargo to I have some chickens to
transport I thought it was milk when did
it change to chickens
eh what happened did you guys evaporate
or
liquefied it's so beautiful oh my God
Milano
Milo let's
go chicken milk can you make milk out of
chickens cuz I feel like you can make
milk out of
anything so maybe you can make mil out
of
chickets I mean there's there's nuts
that you can make milk out
of and you
know can you milk chicken
what if I take your blood and then
bleach
it that is basically milk
guys what did I say something
[Laughter]
weird oh by the way while I'm in Italy
and Switzerland you have to write my
name with ch
K with
ch and in Switzerland when we're in
Switzerland you have to pronounce
[Laughter]
it sorry sorry Switzerland people for
catching
Strays the Swiss
hey
yo hey yo where the [\h__\h] are
we uh nothing written here what the [\h__\h]
no idea where we
are where are my swits
people Swit Switzerland people
whoa whoa that looks like if I if I go
over there I feel like I will go into to
the elfish neverland and
die if I go there on the ship and go
through these
mountains I'm not a Chihuahua
I'ma nice
one nice oh bacon lettuce tomato
sandwich in that in there oh I think we
need to blow that truck up
I'm getting hungry even though I just
had a salad before the
stream what
l l
l as they say in
German l l l
l if you guys remember I sang that in
fully German in A Kar unarchived before
if you're curious you can look it up on
YouTube Ki Lo l l and you can probably
find a clip of
it h
VI
sh I don't want to stop the engine was I
supposed to stop the
engine one of your best kokas yeah
besides my EUR truck K excuse me no but
my my
some of my favorites that I can remember
uh one of them would be the the like 70s
80s one I
did but actually I feel like my just
chill non-ed ones are also my favorites
because I don't like try so hard to
force into a theme and I just sing
whatever the [\h__\h] I want in those
without feeling pressured to confine
myself and like make you guys so
like as happy as can be just sing
whatever I want to
sing but when we talk themed ones I did
really like the
theme and the songs of my like 80s
K has been 82 years don't you mean 84
years or has it been two years since
that Koka is that what you
mean how long has it been has it been
that long no way it's been two years no
way think that was like last
year 1.5 million one what happened
there that was uh endurance right I sang
a lot on that one a long one I was
suffering no pretty sure I was suffering
in that one
tequila
tequila My Savior I am straight edged as
can be and don't drink alcohol hate
alcohol but tequila saved my life
once Sparks only K not really something
I would put up there with my favorites
no interesting car over
there what the [\h__\h] is
that speed slow slow please
slow have we arrived at our
destination are we in Verona now that
was our goal right Verona was
it Alpha Romeo ahuh heard about it I've
heard
Legends oh wow there so good at this
game they're actually slowing down in
the curve down to 40 when they're
supposed to how do they do that
amazing amazing
[Music]
fascinating I still have three hours in
game damn I'm so fast wa I'm doing so
well see when I'm not singing and trying
to gesture for the sake of entertainment
and switching songs and reading lyricss
and everything at the same time I am not
that bad at this
game there were so many debuffs on
me during that K Euro Truck stream but I
still want to do it
again I still want to do it again got to
give it another try sometime when I got
time but time time is of the essence and
it's a limited resource yes yes yes
yes I like this this
pretty pretty it's so fitting because
today I'm making the pizza with the
peoni but without proper I wonder what
Italians would say to it but I mean they
must have respect for someone being able
to make a pizza out of egg
whites that deserves some respect
especially if it turns out tasting good
h
the pineapple no maybe next time first
I'm just going to go simple simply thank
you what's kiss in Italian again I feel
like I knew that word
before but yeah if it's if it's good
then I'm going to try a different kind
of BB beat uh maybe a Duna with corn
Pizza
AO but you oh I actually did not know
that
one right not
not
right I'm picking up Samurai
speak thanks to Shogun
I mean I've heard of certain words
before like saying instead of vat or so
saying sesha for
example I knew a bunch of these before
but the the Shogun show is like bonking
it into my brain it's pretty cool pretty
nice like if you cannot speak any
Japanese and you watch that
show I don't think you'll learn anything
from it it's like really difficult
but if you already have some basic
knowledge
then it's quite interesting to pick up
some
words no I don't think Ida uses S no no
no no no especially because that's I
think that's a samurai word and ID has
not a
samurai pretty sure sesha was a samurai
word an actor said it was complicated
for them too a I can imagine yeah
like there's really polite Japanese but
then like several levels of politeness
in
Japanese she what
no she's she's not a
samurai yeah so there
n but even yeah ninja yeah what the [\h__\h]
man what the [\h__\h] man don't Gass at
me H don't gas at
me let get my
phone have I been
gaslin I'm I'm on my phone with one hand
oh oh oh hope the police does not come
by wait Auto auto please
UHA
life
uh what is
she wait wait wait
[\h__\h] it doesn't say here what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] this Wiki is not
explaining to me clearly what she
is she's just a bodyguard now it says
[Music]
Japanese Bros I only trust
you I'm driving with one hand by the way
guys let's
go really what yeah and I do kind of
like remember
her being like you know to her being
called ninja is
like being like how when Kyla gets
called
penguin but I wasn't sure just now if I
gaslit myself into that because the chat
is giving me
confusing
feelings she Samurai uh
oh Samurai
[Laughter]
she should she should use more samai
words
then it's confusing if she she doesn't
talk in the proper
manner oh my God there's this tiny like
fly flying around it's annoying me it
almost flew into my mouth while I was
driving with one hand
danger yeah I I do remember being like
but it could have been the other way
around just like you know with Momo suu
and suzu Momo like you just get confused
about it at some point because
they you
[Laughter]
know and then because of other people
outside of her absence being like ha
she's a
ninja but also she's not even wearing
proper Samurai
attire like I mean where's the helmet
and all that where's the proper armor
huh looks different than Shogun if you
ask me wait why are we so slow I thought
I
captain yes Suz Momo no Momo
suzu I there was a time where I wasn't
sure
either if it was Su Momo or Mumu I got
gaset as well
[Laughter]
and that was when we were like more
actively speaking than we are
now I'm
ashamed m
t so many of these borders [\h__\h] off fly
this one's a tiny
one ah
touched my
forehead Fuki I would never say such a
slanderous thing about Fuki
stpy no no no no no I know the
boundaries
okay we have arrived once again
in my
Verona it's a red
light go
away it's like ticklish stupid stupid
tiny baby
fly come on come on
I I I closed my eyes for a moment and it
went from red to Green where was the
yellow the [\h__\h] did I just teleport did
I travel in
time was there never a yellow to begin
with Chen
bro Chen the bro
what I'm driving so much around in Italy
and you know you know there's a certain
Italian kfp is
missing I'm missing their
input where the [\h__\h] is
froo yeah half the milk has been
delivered
yay oh there you
are all the
husband can go back home from their milk
buying
Journey because there is no more milk
necessary to be bought smooth R too yeah
you think
so yay the return of all the DS oh and I
got a level up yeah what should I get
what did I get here anyway delivers
up to ah okay maybe I should get another
one of these so I can go further away
even
[Music]
further mergent deliveries unlocked
higher
reward fuel safe ah this one's good too
I guess but so far during my rides I I
haven't really recently I haven't really
had a need of you know loading up my
fuel
but what what's ADR oh wait somehow this
didn't look
like anything I could invest in it's
good for money long distance more fun
because the the things they look
different somehow I didn't think this
was anything at all what is this
explosives I don't want to transport
that
flim flammable
gases nonflammable flim flammable
nonflammable but does this bring more
money I guess wait I can't how do I
there's no plus
here how do
I do I have to sign
something I don't see a A plus sign
click on one oh I can choose
I don't know which one should I choose
does it
matter maybe just like No undo undo how
do I
undo oh there we go like just maybe the
basic flammable
one maybe
radioactive is there radioactive there's
toxic and infectious
corrosive don't think there's
radioactive that would be uh kind of
[\h__\h] I don't think
we do that in actually well in Austria
we don't have um like nuclear plants but
probably other
countries we
do in Europe so I don't know I don't
know how this kind of stuff works
because we don't have that in Austria so
I don't know how I can't
relate yeah we don't Isn't that
cool and I don't think people are ever
going to build one here because we're
used to
this
greatness so everybody would Riot if
they wanted to build something like that
kind of a shame
actually I'm
proud what the [\h__\h] you guys are
crazy what power is Austria power is
power we are fueled by power power is
made by
power he's dead easy
I power the
country yeah I I I powered them yes
fueled by
schnitzel it is a good
fuel I was thinking of
uh maybe buying a a truck and then yeah
how do I buy a
truck how do how to
how to buy
truck first I go to bank maybe but let
me see used
trucks Oh I can afford this without a
loan should I buy a used one or a new
one with a
[Music]
Alan Scania
new one tantu only deserves the best but
then I'm going to go in
dep look at condition okay so the more
stars the better the condition I suppose
this one's in a really good
condition this one's in full oh all all
of these are Volvo Scania
man
manuh
Reen I don't know anything about cars
but one of you guys said Scania and this
one has full condition W but it's so
expensive I cannot afford this one
huh those are way too
expensive why
that's brand
new is 70,000 not
7K oh this one you
mean oh it's not even that much more
expensive 10K loan a bit more oh no
actually wait wait uh I need like 12
12K but then don't I need a trailer too
then
oh
shees getting a moved around in the
process of getting it to where it's
being
sold pretty much probably could
be you get the trailer for The c ah okay
okay okay okay wait
so
bank I think I've proved myself to be a
worthy truck driver
so I think I deserve a
loan how much should I say 12,000 can I
these are
like can I do something more uh
exact should I go for the 50k
one
1,400 a
day a day a
day 1,
a oh that's a lot why don't want this
big
loan maybe how much do I make from one
drive approximately what if I just get
the 10 one and then get a bit more
money it's too late I got it
yeah I can just what this pain is so
good what the
[\h__\h] wait this is really good 33 per
kilometer that pays so well let's go
let's go let's go let's go oh waa whoa
whoa whoa whoa
whoa what's art why does it talk so
nicely it's an articulated
trailer high value fragile okay okay I'm
going going to show my best side
now it's so well articulated unlike me
okay how do I even start where do I the
map is misleading
me this
way oh yeah maybe this way and then
through
here got to be really careful of this
one Hit the Road Jack dble
I have extended my length y I don't know
if I can do this it is the first time
we're this long I'm
snck okay oh man okay I got to keep that
in mind I'm so long and I
gu
wait
what where's my whatever
okay long long
W I feel like I'm playing sliver do iio
right now with this long of a
truck come
on is that's what articulated means in
truck language truck
lingo mely pay off loan to save
money no but this was just supposed to
help with the last 2K that I'm
missing but yeah if this one brings me
13k then the loan is
[Laughter]
useless immediately pays off loan who
the [\h__\h] are you why did you get a loan
to begin with
lady I can't
see
o sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry I'll fix
it all right
done nope no no damage I
think wow w w o wait we are we're in
where we're in
stard they got a nice looking Arena oh
what is that no that's a train station
or Park house that's a [\h__\h] Park
House you know what that means right put
one and one together this is a PK house
house what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] kind of Park house is
that it's famous that's so cool it's
like a bridge and like a stadium and a
train station that's what it looks
like yeah it's a house for no it's a
what it's a house for
parking you park
houses I mean you could park
uh what do you call call it again the
ones that the cars where you live
in you could park that there then you
kind of Park in your house if you live
in
one okay I was not thinking
RV yeah like a camper Caravan yeah I
guess it's called
RV that's Ah that's kind of like I don't
really feel like this nowadays but when
I was younger I thought that would be
the best car to have
for road
trips I kind of wish that my family had
one
but my mom doesn't even have a license
so owning a car was never really a
thing it would be so nice you is anybody
in the chat who has
one like a car that is like a
home it would be so nice ni to travel
with that I could become an RV
influencer show people my life in
the in the wait I still feel like that's
not the right word what do these
influences say what do they call
it van yeah van life there we go that's
what I was thinking about oh wait I
should slow down probably
the W were
gone oh that's right that's what they
call it that's what they all call
it I almost H the car well almost skill
issue should have hit it should have hit
it too bad I
didn't to rent one instead of buying
yeah but now that I'm thinking about it
should I get
one
no I don't know if I would make really
good use of it if I had one probably
not oh my God the the
wheel and the circle thingies behind it
ah looking like a face to me the middle
part of the wheel looks like a nose or
like it looks like a Mario Super Mario
face oh my
God look at that
does that not look like a Super Mario
face to
you yeah I feel like I'm seeing a
mustach
too M M
[Music]
M today or yesterday today today uh that
Mario RPG remake came out Paper
Mario I'm thinking maybe I should play
it I don't know
should I give it a try next week or
so tomorrow oh okay don't tendo was
playing it
today play it it
rules if it's not too long maybe maybe
we skipped Princess Peach sadly but I
watched a full playthrough of
it
instead but maybe this one maybe I'll
play
alongside Fallout of course oh by the
way Amy told me I'll be fine without
mods Just Save A Lot she
said that's what she
said 25 to 30 hours I don't
know not too bad not too short not too
long
good advise probably
true I'll be fine I'll save a lot
okay F5 button is that the safe button
okay okay okay okay I'm getting very
accustomed
to the safe uh to the F5 button right
now thanks
to Manheim oh oh D KS D Manheim the land
of the men oh only men live in
Manheim the country of the land of mans
oopsie I [\h__\h] up again see there you
go passing
through this is better but where are we
going
Manheim to AO
ah it's still Bri
outside do I have my lights on now I
can't tell I pressed
L how do I did
I you guys should have told me
[Music]
earlier oh
let's go a little faster and then chop
it there we
go they have to be on always no not
during the day but it's not working
again why is not working see
see oh it's not
working
see
oh oh
oh it's working I think now it's working
it's just going between 78 and
79 when I make a curve or
so other the drivers of flash light yeah
that's so sweet that's actually besides
all the road rage on the road that is
Road
T that's
sweet sometimes people be looking out
for each other huh or maybe it's not so
much looking out for each other more
like
[Music]
like like when you're you try to point
out to someone like in a way that's like
like a know it all is that how you guys
are pointing it out when you see that
rather than
TI it's more like you [\h__\h] idiot turn
your [\h__\h] lights
on so like that
no it's actually nice okay that's that's
a relief that's sweet good to know okay
I have to go there but I'm too long
how can't believe that worked
out can't believe that I I could not
have really gone there earlier and
yeah I don't know it didn't look like I
would fit because he was not slowing
down
obviously I guess I could have slowed
down and like waited for him but I would
have like almost had to put an almost
full stop I
think good one my lights are my lights
are on it just doesn't look like it
don't don't stress me
out uh where where
are oh no idea somewhere close to
Frankfurt and
Manheim looks nice any Germans who
recognize this place should be
recognizable where is this frankf foot
is it like the airport or so oh it was
it looked familiar kind of
ha was it ah it looked like an airport
yeah these buildings are very
airporty
yeah and that's why Frankfurt is closed
I so
empty
wow
wow speaking of German airports recently
I was at cologne
airport and I've been to a few airports
in Germany but damn I did not expect
cologne airport to be so [\h__\h]
dead both on my arrival and my
departure it was so empty so ghosty
both in the like arrival Lobby like
after you get off or like also
inside like everywhere it was so empty
even though the cologne airport kind of
is like a shared airport between two
cities I was
surprised was so empty couldn't even
find
our checking counter because it was uh
just one
table just one you know normally there's
like several next to each other it was
just one that's why it was like so easy
to pass
by
weird and then the the dude at at the
counter was kind of
like well my friend said is this cuz my
friend did not have much experience of
flying and thought that the counter dude
was like really rude and was like asking
me is this
normal are is this is this whole
interaction normal I'm like yeah I mean
you are being kind of dorky so the
counter dude was probably losing his
patience a little bit
and was a bit possibly a bit rude but I
don't
know I despise the dorf airport dor how
was that one
again I don't remember if it was a bad
or a good
experience new ETS update you can turn
lane assist system oh but what is there
a button for
that not that I really needed I like
being in between these
Lanes I like balancing on the White
markings and then jumping from one to
another it's just what I like to
do laugh is a h
away I want to ride it all night
[Music]
long if yeah if you want to hear that I
sang it in the last herot truck
simulator stream but that is on archived
so I guess you can't see it
anymore
no there it
is I think we're doing pretty
good think we didn't even get damaged
yet and I don't think I got fin except
for the
lights I
think w w
wow and we're there in 1 hour 30 while
we have how much
time six no 14 14 hours
remain
what so
generous how come I was
always oh man the difference it makes
when you're not singing while driving I
was always like so close or late in my K
her truck
stream
damn the sky right now looks like
DreamWorks OMG OMG are you seeing that
that looks like DreamWorks no doesn't
not makes me think of it same colors and
the Stars
wow
right thanks for
confirming this part a little bit less
that part over there looked like
it yeah the the the the not just the
logo but like the the whole scene the
logo
scenes oops I'm too
fast it farted the truck
farted truck farting sounds
you know when truck
goes
funny well it's always farting yeah in
German it's always farting because it is
driving oh are you going there too buddy
looks like
it nice a my chat broke to
no no don't break I will never give up
don't
break okay okay I'm back I'm back in the
game it already showed that I had 98,000
EO how did I wasn't I at 80 did they
already add the money to my account
before I finished the drive
oh oh because they added the loan to
it I don't know why what it is about
that makes me want
to recreate
it Shi this little song
[Music]
too
fast don't even have to zoom that much
y oopsie how do
I oopsie pressed it by accident thank
God the roads are not
busy I'm
shoting hamburger bun spilled on the
road no
way no you made that up right col
discovered what I already discovered it
a couple weeks
ago
lies oh do we get to see the
[Music]
C I want to see
it oh I want to see it I'm
excited where is it where is
it oh oh there's that like a TV Tower or
something like
that I I feel like I I came from this
street also oh there it is uh when I
came from the airport it might be the
same
direction let's go the the two the two
spiky ones are the cologne cathedal Kad
very famous I saw it but I I didn't look
much I just saw one side of it close up
and then I was like okay I'm good
uh uh oh wa this
one hard to say but yeah this one I
think
okay
colog oh [\h__\h] yeah okay so me my sorry
forgive me I'm so excited to be here oh
I do I feel like just from being here
one time arriving one time with a
taxi it already feels familiar maybe
because it was fairly recent now how am
I going to
see please let me know when it's green
there we
go
INF egg thank you welcome
welcome to the
kfp is that is that Burger King
advertisement what it felt like it I'm
sure surely they're not going to put the
logo on it but it felt like Burger King
advertisement very nice
looks very familiar col was pretty like
not
just not just the Dome Dome the
cathedral just
overall it felt pretty clean and big and
calm didn't see many
people I kind of wanted to eat Curry
worst but then didn't have the chance to
because it was really short day but I
know it's very
cliche but I do like C it's really yummy
man can make it easily at home too I
think but best to get it on the
street yeah was from the
street never had it is so
good first had it when I was in Berlin
that was my first time many years ago
and then I was like he yo he yo that's
so
[Music]
good you guys don't even know the extent
and variety of sausages that we in
Germany and Austria have to offer yeah
but I'm generally like kind of annoyed
when
people and I think Germans would
probably agree with that when people
like when they think of German aan food
and all mostly German though but and all
I can think of is oh sausages sausages
there's way more than just sausages Okay
and like we don't even eat that many
sausages but we do have good sausages
that is true one of my favorites is vice
wor with uh mustard like the vice wor
you have to peel the skin off which is
really weird you don't normally do that
with other sausages but with Vice wish
it's like a white fat sausage you boil
it and you serve it just with like maybe
a a pretzel pritzel or so some bread and
and you eat it with a sweet
mustard it's so good sometimes I just
have this this desire for it and then I
go and buy a full package of
white Vice W and then eat it 3 days in a
row um exy thank you
yum
yum I have arrived where do I go
straight
forward
really the video of the dck watching the
metor yeah yeah yeah yeah you probably
found it because I liked it Twitter
algorithm recommended it to
you y big money
okay okay safe safe
saay nice I did so well did I get extra
if I'm
early urgent delivery
bonus y I got 13,000 almost 14,000 no
minus at
all that might have been almost my best
drive today
actually it might be okay how do I pay
my loan
back uh immediately pays back loan
unbelievable shouldn't have had these
intrusive
thoughts
repay then
finally we can buy the truck if it's
still there
uh the one I wanted is this one wait did
the price go
up no I'm missing
2,000 did the price go up or is this a
different one it looks like the same
one what the [\h__\h] was it always like
this
no no I'm just going to buy a different
one I don't care what about this one
it's more expensive
[Music]
no was it on sale before I don't know
man I can't afford
these oh they just got more expensive
steering left hand a yo how do they
know 22 35 what's this Gap
68 and that's
suddenly is it okay to take this one
maybe buy a new Fresh truck but then I
need a huge
loan get new
truck okay let's see the prices
uh truck
dealers I know
four man which one out of these
ones or is this oh it's just free I
think man
EO not a bad choice eer how do
you where do you have this
knowledge
man man are you guys just saying it
because I'm saying
it man
[Music]
evle but
man okay
can I can I buy online please thank you
trust it I need to own at least five
trucks you [\h__\h] kidding
me do I have to drive there on the
autoban oh no okay I'm
there okay where's the difference
between doing it online I'm here
now
uh2 wait that's my money oh they're not
that much more expensive
good feel orange it looks like red but
it says good feel orange I like that
night name oh there's just these
two I would go for the Good Feeling
orange it is me when I feel good I turn
a bit more red I
guess I can custom the color but that's
probably going to cost even
more no particularly bad truck okay
level 16 for different color is that
what you're saying but okay I want
this but oh wait oh no I can't buy it oh
this this one I could
buy what just because it's orange what
the [\h__\h] I'll make it orange myself then
eventually
uh nobody likes to have Guild exactly
thanks for membership renewal so I need
a little bit of money if I get 158
158,000
158,000 I need a bit more than that
pisses me off
man that pisses me off what why can I
not choose the
amount I guess like a 50 and a 10 would
be okay
oh my
God is this really worth
it
uh I hear B
book it sounds like B book when I click
things okay customize configuration
color is there no
color oh it's not that CR
oh
what you're a truck
simulator oh that's
cool bubbles
wow
well okay custom color is a bit more
expensive I don't know if I can four can
I can I still change the color
afterwards although wait
this
uh addition wait additional price 100 oh
wait it's not that bad because the 2000
is already like in the price I
guess wait so 160 ah y I can afford the
good feel orange very close but yeah
really close this one oh I can afford
this one too it's beit more expensive
but I can get like a more of a waa
orange like
these like
maybe or
maybe like
these what or is am I going by the hair
or what am I going by I don't know this
is good this this is the real the real
good feel
orange light
okay like the this like
this using all my money for this I track
so hard for
this let's
go
y I bought my first car it's a truck
oh I have my own truck
house
wow this is mine it's all mine it's my
[Music]
hood thank you look how cute he is okay
that actually looks kind of cute that
looks kind of cute without the the back
thing on the trailer you're looking kind
of adorable
now wh what what what happens if I drive
into
that wow
automatic manage this garage
notel no I'm so
happy Kiana's fast
parking has done so well today has made
so much money and has gotten this
beautiful own truck
finally yeah did it safe like after
after I got the truck well I'll let me
save again here good
a first
oh first truck let's
go okay I
saved goodbye you track simulator
my first track my first
track
yeah close game go bye-bye now go byebye
go bye-bye hello I think it like kind of
crashed I must force
it to
die yeah okay it's gone
okay are you guys ready for some Super
Chat reading we're caught up since
yesterday I'm going to read Super
Chat this time I'll go where should I
[Music]
go don't know where to go I guess I'll
go to my office but then let me take off
uh because it will look
weird I have to put something on so let
me put this
on very helpful why it looks so good it
looks
good to the office we
go speaking of the office maybe you guys
you stalk my Twitter so maybe you saw it
in my likes but I found this video first
I thought it was like an IRL
surveillance cam video turns out it was
real
um my
D it was a the office video uh like an
uncut version of a scene that I don't
remember at all where
uh what's his name
again yeah where he falls into the water
and he acts like he's
drowning the COI Pond yeah and then in
the replies to that I saw another
video that was uh the office clip I
don't I don't know why these are in my
recommendations in the first place but I
love the office so I'm fine with it um
and I saw uh this is the one that I
liked so maybe you saw it in my likes I
saw the scene this one I remembered
where um I guess this is like when when
uh the [\h__\h] what's his name again what's
the what's the boss's name again I'm I'm
blanking out right now um it's like his
last day or so I suppose Michael thanks
and uh the everybody's gathered in this
one room and they're singing for him
[Music]
10,000 you know they sing and H the the
lore to the scene was written there in
the tweet and I did not know no I've
seen the scene but I did not know the
lore behind it that
Michael did not no this was unscripted
he do Michael Scott or his actor did not
know that they were going to sing
that and so his reaction is legit and I
didn't know that and then I watched the
scene with that knowledge and I was like
this hits so much harder
now that I know that he didn't
know that this was going to happen and
it made me teary ey as well it's so
emotional wow oh man they nailed it
too you guys got to watch it especially
with this knowledge
now that's so
sweet they sang all together and they
harmonized so well and Michael was
getting teary eyed too
and like smiling and like hey yo hey
yo so
good I
heard I heard that Iris has been
watching clips of the office but not the
actual show I would like to tell her
please watch the show it's so worth it
the clips are great but like she was uh
question
if the whole show is always as good and
as funny as the clips and I would say oh
oh hell yeah like it's a
constant a
constant
clip it's all just a big clip it's all
so funny it's all
clippable man you could clip every
[\h__\h] scene it's like all that good
there's no bad moments really
H in my
opinion I'm hungry so I'm going to read
these super chats and I'm going to try
to make this
pizza I got to hurry I'm hung goody so
next to my m k today's superjets I am
caught up let's
go yeah like there's you know when
Michael is not in the show anymore it
definitely drops in quality but besides
that it's still it's still decent un
watchable after
that all righty unnown D take 47 danan
Psy danan green wer thank you for the
pinky I just caught up on the Minecraft
streams and I thought you deserved some
PR it was very admirable how you and
Anna pretended to get along with each
other no that's not ruin the mood for
others despite wait where's bgm despite
hating each other right I know it was so
hard to
pretend cuz I hate her so much oh my
God she's so
annoying she's just so
[Music]
annoying do you hear
those all righty thank you that's funny
grin
Wilder I appreciate it thanks for the
support yay
Jeff star thanks for the pinky too hey T
there's a YouTube viewership bug
happening right now that's affecting
viewership sadly there's not much anyone
can do about it for the time being
besides reporting it to YouTube oh I
guess I kind of slept through that
because I don't think I was affected by
it huh W just sleeps through all the
problems that are being
caused sleeping through the
[Music]
storm well how bad was it what was it
showing
like zero or
[Music]
what 100 to 200
oh that's
weird
well made me remember how I discovered
whole life because of you and myth after
a break up a so thank you for making me
smile when it was difficult no problem
I'm glad that we could help you in such
tough times to get your mind off of it
or
so that's
nice circus music
[Music]
stops matild Hecker
d downar
d oh yeah also I guess welcome back
Matilda oh you're always
welcome looking for the top danion
what
em than
pinky one of my most embarrassing moment
as a
[Music]
trucker trucker I was driving in La
delivering Lumber wa H and then you
dropped it and all the lumber all the
trees rolled away no I entered the store
entrance but the back of my trailer ran
over the edge of AATA
stand the T spilled Aller drinks I ended
up paying $200 that's not even that bad
butata what is that sounds Mexican
orata oh and or or is a name given to
various beverages which are generally
plant-based but sometimes contain animal
milk in Spain it is made with soaked
ground and sweetened tiger nuts
nuts in some parts of the Americas the
base is cha
melon or sesame seeds like it looks like
a like a I don't
know milk tea but it has cinnamon on it
looks nice looks kind of
aesthetic it's
delicious I've never heard of it
before a iced rice milk beverage from
Mexico that's a simple blend of rice
cinnamon
almond uh it cuts off there ah and
sweetener huh
rice but like you can't feel the rice
right is like Blended or
so looks it looks good I I like the idea
of it I
think it's like a Mexican version of a
chai
tea Blended hey I want to try
it you can probably get it in America
too right next time in America I'll try
to find
it what the [\h__\h] is this really how you
make it there's this
picture you got to have a strong blender
for this to
work is this how you make
it I don't know that's like I feel like
my blender would not do a good job at
[Music]
this what the
[\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
damn uh maybe I can make it
myself looks easy enough
actually H I like
cinnamon probably ground yeah I would
hope you don't put that stick in there
would be easier to just put already
ground cinnamon in
there chai tea is TI h TI titty TI T So
chai te is titty
T just adding more and more
teas chai tea is titty tea good to know
good to
know anyway that's interesting damn The
Edge wait the edge of a horata stand
what what Edge like damn I hope they
weren't too angry at you
[Music]
but you paid 200 and hopefully ran away
with AATA anyway in your hand it was a
tent a did you damage so much just from
going over the edge of a
[Music]
tent I guess so they were pissed off oh
come on drink a little Chata and then
you chill the [\h__\h] out come on it
happens
but who the [\h__\h] delivers Lumber in La
man it sounds crazy sounds crazy I can't
imagine a big Lumber truck driving
through La hard to imagine they called
the
cops oh
man too
bad now maybe you decided on that day to
never drink orchata ever again am I
saying it nicely by the way
is this how it sounds
like yeah woohoo let's
go the H is quiet I
suppose
[Music]
water my neck oh wait it was at the
moment where my neck was like in my ass
and my my hat was is that what you
referencing To Hai hyena let's go thank
you D oh wait your profile picture a
you're you're um I see I
understand space
waterful what did I just hear wait
what were you guys not watching the
stream
hello SP waterful D mp53 GX D for the
pinking
there's not much to be done about it the
Earth is constantly shifting and
changing ah we're talking about like the
moldes disappearing the Sahara desert
desert used to be an ocean land masses
will sink and rise and temperatures will
jump and fall oh okay yeah you bring
something up that I can counter with
attention of a video that I watched the
other day
um so apparently in
Africa this was interesting to know uh
was it the Sahara Desert or a different
desert I don't know but one of those big
deserts that they have is like sending
lots of sand downwards into the South
more and more and they try to prevent it
by making a big strip of green
stuff uh like planting all kinds of
greeneries uh from uh the left side of
Africa to the right side of Africa
somewhere in the
middle uh to just act as a barrier the
green barrier of
Africa it's really interesting cuz all
of that was like sand and looked like
you could not make anything green there
ever again um cuz it was like really
hardened rock hard
sand um but yeah they made it all green
like they added so much Greenery and
it's so beautiful because it's also like
nicely designed in like half moons and
so on maybe look it up if you're curious
on YouTube the
green barrier project of Africa you'll
find it I
think and that way they're stopping the
uh how to say
extension the not this extension because
the the over the years the desert just
kept on growing and growing and
expansion that's it yeah the expansion
of the desert and with this they can
stop it kind of
M and it looks so beautiful really
cool there we go nice tangent
educational tangent mental Jetty
D oo sounds like fun enjoy eat all the
sausages you want
I'll what I get another free shorts
coupon how do I deserve that what did I
do La was suddenly raining shorts
coupons from the
sky yo this time this time hopefully it
won't be so outdated by the time I get
it wink
won yeah for my Japan trip you say
specifically for my Japan trip has to be
something that happens in Japan then
okay okay
why I see I see I'll keep it in mind
thank you LC la
la mp53
G there the
pinky let's go server funded thank you
oh yeah oh I'll try to um after I get
the one last reply I'll start thinking
about how to set this up I'm excited
[Music]
space wful with the lore with the
history the lore of
Earth and
Sushi D thank you as well Julian B
Dan a troll for fun
[Laughter]
dun nice mud arcade
d m we just got away you know that's
like it's kind of up to them I suppose I
don't know what schedules what's the
reason for their schedules and like who
they do first no idea about the nendos
like it's it's up to their whm I suppose
chicken Cruz
Mr
happy but good to Bo
St you wanted it in wom apparently there
you
[Music]
go I did that I love back Del but I
Jones D thank you for the red CH thank
you D no words with it why why are you
so quiet have you lost your words
because you were stunned by my beauty in
this outfit or in the previous one both
were stunning let's be real
understandable have a nice
day np1 free GX
[Music]
D liar you are a liar youf mod D for the
pinky the a free is literally my home
street drive it every day a short part
between diets and montab between frankot
and K hearing that you lit passed where
I live it's kind of funny so close but
still so far ah well I mean you say it
as if I passed through where you live
IRL but it was just in a game UF
mod but I'm sure that these roads look
very familiar to you that's really cool
cuz I I can't really relate to that that
much in Germany but a little bit a
little bit here and there around the
airport felt very
familiar must feel exciting it wasn't
real no I was not actually IRL streaming
my drive through
Europe I don't even have a license guys
can you imagine if I did that duh of
course it's
fake I played a Simulator
game I can't play anything besides a
Simulator game if I don't have a real
license yeah that would be insane that
would be
[Music]
illegal the truck the truck that I own
is real it's
real that's real I I
believe eight J D yeah I don't know I
don't know if you're asking seriously
but no I don't know how to drive you m d
thank
you oh love driving in
Japan wait is there a Japan P truck
[Music]
simulator
unharmed almost H thank you I am getting
better yet it's kind of chill I'm just
chilling do you like
visb I follow it's just okay I like
green one I don't actually remember what
white one tastes like to be
honest I don't remember I maybe had it
once in my life or maybe zero
I can't remember I generally try to
avoid it also because everybody else
also generally prefers the green one
[Music]
asparagus so if that's how people prefer
it then it's probably the better one
never had greenb for
real hey y' it's so
good you're eating BL
I have to admit uh these past 3 days my
lunch
was a
brst I don't know I just saw it in the
supermarket I just felt like
it um but it was just one brw and
mustard I did not have anything extra
with the brw it was a pretty thick one
but just a single
one I don't know how many calories it
had but I think if that was the only
thing I had for lunch then I think it's
not so bad after no maybe it has a
different name in Austria I don't
know girl
dinner it was so [\h__\h] good though
because the mustard that I had is so
good it's like a kind of a Swedish
mustard Swedish not sweetish not
Swedish uh cuz it has like honey it's a
honey mustard mustard with honey so good
oh I love mustards in
general so
[Music]
good Swedish
mustard SP water for D and chocolate
andic F the right Super Chat hey B just
letting you know that I love hearing you
yapping and tracking you mean clucking
and trucking you totally missed out
there
yapping and clucking is the same so you
could have just said clucking and
tracking it would have sounded way
better it's been a great podcast and me
occasionally being in chat to comment
about something funny that happened
thank you for watching and listening I'm
happy to be your truck cast
hey hope you had a good time was a
little bit short but you know we need
some shter streams here and
there and I'm hungry if I I don't feed
my tummy soon I will have to end up
eating you guys and that's not good
that's not good no no no thank you so
much M I'm also a chocolate Insomniac
man also are you going to be part of the
B Mona Daddy watch along you better be
we're starting this week we're going to
watch one full season and one go you got
to be there you are yeah let's go ooh
I'm going to sing along to the opening
[Music]
what was the opening of the first
season I'm just never sure which one's
the opening and which one's the
[Music]
ending ah stap
stap let's
go okay I'm excited
wow we getting excited for watching
anime who is
she but you know how much I love Bako
katani so you mean all 15 yeah we're
watching the full thing it's going to
take like 6 hours
apparently five or six
[Music]
hours yeah if I ever gotten I wouldn't
call it fairly recently yeah
but wasn't that even already 2023 at
this point like last year you could
say might take the day off it's on
Saturday
so maybe you don't even have to take a
day
off yeah last year has it arrived yet no
it hasn't but I it should actually I
don't know why it didn't arrive maybe
they did not even attempt to deliver and
sent it straight to the straight to the
post office so I'll have to check my my
my thingy if I got any
notices I'll check should be okay
[Music]
though okay so that's it for today if
you guys for watching tomorrow we play I
think which spring R I think
if I remember
correctly yes tomorrow a little bit
early in the day
oh because it's uh an RPG it's I don't
know if I'll make a full series out of
it but I think it's relatively short so
I could I could we'll see if I like it
then we'll finish it eventually but yeah
oh dingo primps oh my
God good Lu making the pizza try my
best okay it it looked pretty easy in
the
recipe the only thing is really getting
the con
texture and like yeah texture of the
white the egg whites
right no remind me remind me elsewhere
remind me on
Twitter not here
[Music]
can say no to cute girls
exactly they look really
cute you Chef wa that that I
am so with that being
said thank you for watching today dang
in Germany we
[Music]
say I'm going to cook the cook the pizza
and the pasta no just the pizza and the
[Music]
baboni bye-bye
leave a
comment and a like And
subscribe I'm reading your comments on
YouTube I like them all yesterday
[Music]