Cinderella,
a fairy tale by the Brothers Grimm, a rich
man, his wife became ill and when
the filter that we came to the end called
her only daughter to the
bed and said every child stay happy
and that's good, the good Lord will always be at
play and I want from heaven  looking down on you
and wanting to be around you
then she closed her eyes and
said goodbye. The girl went out every day
to her mother's house and
cried and remained pious and well
winter came  The snow put a
white table on the bike and when the
sun came out again in the spring,
the man
had another woman. The woman brought two daughters
into the house who were beautiful and white
in the face but spiritually and
black in the heart
On the other hand, it's a bad time for the poor
stepchild, the stupid one is supposed to
sit in the room with us. They said they
have to eat bread and earn money from the
Mitterkirchen market. They took his from him
beautiful little path, they dressed him in a
gray old smock and gave him
holding his shoes
whoever the proud princess like the one
she is cleaning they shouted they laughed and
led her to the church
there she had to do hard work from morning to evening
full get
up the day before carrying water fire  Turn on,
cook and wash on top of that,
I know everything, then I
gave him similar heartbreak, mocked him and
poured the peas and lentils into
the ashes so that he could sit and  She
had to read them out again in the evenings when she was
tired of working. She did
n't go to bed but had to
lie down in the ashes next to the stove because that's why
she always came out strong and dirty. She became Cinderella and it
meant that her father had to go to the
mess hall  wanted to
then he asked the two stepdaughters what
he should bring them beautiful little
fine pearls and gemstones the second
but Cinderella he said what do
you want father the first live that
looked at you on your way home
Brecht took off his hat for me. He bought
beautiful dresses for his two step-sisters,
pearls and precious stones, and on
the way back he picked up a green book.
He brushed a piece of hazel rice against him
and kicked off his hat. Then he broke the
rise up and warmed up  When he
came home, he even gave the donors what they
had wanted and
Cinderella forked the raise from the
Haselbach Cinderella thanked him and went
to his  Mother went to the grave and planted
the raise on it and cried so much that
the tears fell on it. Many universities
watered it, but it grew and was a beautiful
branch remedy against all days.
Wept and prayed three times under it and always
a white field came along the tree
and when it  He made a wish out of language
and deduced what he
had wished for.
But it came to pass that the king
arranged a festival that was to last three days
and to which all the beautiful young
women in the country were invited  to
be and a woman out of
hunger we meet two stepsisters
when they heard that they
should also appear there were in good spirits
Cinderella and spoke can do
the hair for us
he is the shoes for us and
fix the edges for us
we are going to the wedding  The
royal
castle said Cinderella rumors but because
she would have liked to go to the dance
and party stepmother she would like to allow him
Cinderella said she is full of dust
and dirt and wants to go  wedding you
have no clothes or shoes and want to
dance
when it stopped with requests
she finally spoke through the clean key
lenses poured into the when you have read the
springs out again in two hours
you should go with me
the girl went through the back door
to the garden and called you farm
doves, you turtledoves, all the birds
under the sky, come and help me
read
the good ones in the potty, the bad ones
in the potty  Kröpfchen then
two white tarts came in through the kitchen window and then
the lovebirds and finally
all the birds
under the sky buzzed and swarmed in and surrounded
the US fans and the great mickey with her
head and started with a picnic
and that's where we think it's time  and
let all the good guys into the
shots. It was barely an hour around 20
and they were all ready and flew out again.
He brought the girl the bowl
Stepmother was happy, she thought it
would now get on her skin,
but she said a Cinderella,
you have no clothes and you ca
n't dance, you will only be laughed at, she was
now crying, she spoke at the end with two
keys of lentils in an hour
from the ashes you can read in like that  Should
you go with me and thought it could
never be more than Siege
had poured two bowls of people into the ashes
against the girl through the back door
to the garden and we called out numbers
fooling the turtledoves, everyone here, little
birds under the sky, come and help
me read,
the good ones in the potty, the bad ones
in the little bird, then
two white little potties came in through the kitchen window and then
the turtledoves and finally
all the birds under the
sky evaluated and swarmed in and let themselves be looked after
Alchemy there and the pigeons nodded
their heads and started
and then the rest of them also started and
left  All the good ones weren't in the
bowls and he had been around for half an hour,
they were already ready and flew
all sorts of ways. The girl took the
bowls to her stepmother, was happy
and thought she could now go to the
wedding, but she said it does
n't help, nothing
you can do  Don't go with me if you don't have any
clothes and you can't dance,
we would have to look at your beautiful ones,
then she turned her back on him, the old one
with her two proud tech land,
when there was no one left at home against
Cinderella to his mother's grave under
the  Haselbauer and called little tree shakes
and shakes you like gold and silver
over me then the bird brought
down a gold and silver dress and
with pointed and silver embroidered
slippers in the hall he put on the dress
and went to the wedding but his sisters
and the stepmother could
They didn't think so and thought it had to be a foreign king's daughter. They didn't think that she was so beautiful in Cinderella's golden dress and thought so at
home  in the dirt and looked for the lentils
from the ashes, the king's son could
take it by the hand and
defy him.
He didn't want to dance with anyone else,
so he didn't let go of his hand
and when someone else came to
ask him to speak,
that's my dancer  It's you,
it was the evening, he wanted to go home,
the king's son, but he said, I'll go with you
and accompany you because he wanted to see
who the beautiful girl belonged to,
judges him but and  jumped into the
pigeon house now the king's son waited until
the father came and told him that the strange
girl had jumped into the pigeon house
the intended was already Cinderella
and she had to bring him soldiers
so that he could break the pigeon house in two
but there was no one
in it
and she  When we came into the house,
Cinderella was lying in her dirty
clothes in the ashes and a dim
oil lamp was burning in the chimney
Cinderella quickly jumped out of the
pigeon house behind Mr. and
also ran to the hazel tree.
He
took off her beautiful clothes and laid the grave and the
bird took it away again and
then she rushed
to the kitchen, standing in her gray smock
set on the other day when the festival started
again ohb and the parents and
stepsisters were gone again in
cinderella also hazel tree and said
shaking little tree and  shake you like
gold and silver over me then the
bird threw down a lot of proud year's clothes
the day before and when it was with
this little one at the wedding
you were amazed at its beauty the
colexon but did he wait until it was there
you could have it right away  the hand and you can
only be alone with them when the others
came and asked, he said, "This
is my fighter".
When it was now evening, Ford and
the king's son wanted to go after him and
she wanted him in which house did she go  It
jumped away from him and in the garden behind
the house a beautiful large
tree arose on which the most beautiful pear
lines climbed like a
squirrel between the first and the
king's son knew not only that he had gotten there,
but waited until his father came and
said yes  The strange girl came
to my attention
and I think it was spoken to the pear tree.
The father thought it should
be Cinderella, had the ax brought and knocked
down the tree
But there was no one on it and
just then the kitchen came. Cinderella was lying there
in the ass, like the other one that had been spun
down from the tree on the other side.
The bird on the hazel tree had
brought the beautiful clothes back and put on her gray ones like a child
on the third  The day when her parents and
sisters were gone, Cinderella went
back to her mother's grave and said
to the little trees, little trees, shake you
and send you joys of silver
over me now  The bird threw him a
dress that was as splendid and
shiny as any he had ever had
and the slippers were completely golden. When
the dress came to the deed,
they all didn't know what to say because of their amazement,
the king's son could do it all alone
him and when he was asked
he said, "That's my fighter". Now in the evening it
was Walter Cinderella Ford's and the
king's son who accompanied Wolter,
but he jumped so quickly that he
couldn't follow  But the king's son had
used a cunning and had the
whole staircase painted with bad luck.
When the credits came up, the
girl's left part was left open.
The king's son had ruby ​​on it and he was
small and delicate and very cold the
next morning he left with it  to the
man and said to him no other should
mine be ground than the one that
fits this golden shoe on the foot.
The two sisters were happy
that they had a puddle for themselves, the
eldest went to school with him  the room
and continued to try things on and the mother
stood there but she could
n't get in with her big toe and the
slipcase was too small for her so the mother handed her
a knife and roughly said the cer
off. When you're queen you do
n't have to walk anymore
The girl ran the therapy with one foot
in the shoe doggedly in pain and went
out to the king's son then he took her
on the horse as his wife and rode
away with her but they had to pass the one just
there  They sat on the hazelbuck for two days
and called him and called good team
stuck, the right breast was too small,
three more public on her foot
and saw how the blood came out, he used
his horse to kill, brought the wrong bride
home to them and said that would
n't happen  the right hand the other sister
should put on the shoe then they went
into the chambers and came with the ten
lucky ones the shoe but the verse was
too big so he handed the mother a
knife and addressed a piece of it  heel
off when you are queen you do
n't have to walk anymore
the girl wrote a piece of the
heel turn off the foot into the shoe
doggedly in pain and went out to the
king's son my name is she got
on the horse as his bride and rode with her ford
as  When they passed the hazel tree,
the two pigeons sat
on it and called out rookie the cuckoo
is stupid because of the shock the shock is too
small on the right  The bride, now still at home,
looked down at her foot and saw
how the blood was pouring out of her shoe and how
red had appeared on her white stockings.
Then he turned his horse and brought the
wrong bride back home.
That's not the right thing to say either  There is
no other daughter for her,
the man said no, only
a little one from my late wife is suspected to be
Cinderella because that can't possibly
be the bride of the king and said
send it out, the mother answered
Oh no, that's far too dirty, it
shouldn't be seen,
but he wanted you out and
Cinderella had to be called because
it will first get his hands and face
in, then he went and showed himself in front of
the war, who then handed him the golden
shoe  He first sat down with
his skull and pulled his foot out of his
heavy neck and put it in his
slippers.
He was like a glove and everything was
safe
had danced with him
and shouted that's the right bride, the
stepmother, the two of them had fun and were
frightened and were immediately in front of him.
But he took the Cinderella unlocked it
and cracked it with the Ford. As they
passed the hazel tree, the
two white bags shouted rocket ebook
Bürgenstock  The shock is not too
small, the right bride, the publishers and
when they had called that, they
both flew away and Tim sat down
Cinderella on the shoulders one on the
right and others on the left and remained
sitting there when the wedding with the
king's son was held on the side,
the false sisters wanted to
ingratiate themselves and share and take his club
when she stepped people now went to church
the eldest was to be calculated as the
youngest  On the left side the
pigeons each grabbed one eye, then
when they went out the
first one had to be guided and the youngest one had to be
raised. The dreams of
each one grabbed the other  eyes out and were they
punished with blindness for the rest of their lives for wickedness and falsehood
why
[Music]