[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
the
[Music]
K ke
K oh okay that's probably too
loud ah oh oh is that is that is that is
that too
loud that's probably fine it's still in
the red turn it down a little Ki but
it's just like it's it's you know it's
not it's not you know equalized the ups
and the Downs are strong but if we talk
normally then it's too low oh you okay k
kik you guys are not saying if it's okay
sounds
okay loud and clear yeah
why do I look down so much
wa welcome to the
males there go okay welcome to the mes
say welcome to the
males it's your favorite pairing
Kisa your new favorite pairing one of
many
pairings no there doesn't have to be a
favorite there's many new pairings to
appreciate in different ways yes yeah
yeah
did you guys enjoy that old intro I just
randomly found it it was already in my
OBS I don't know why it's there but it's
there and it had to be used the OG the
OG chicken chicken chasing video that I
drew and C animated did you get the rose
P again no here it costs
money right how much was it to way too
much way too I think my models for some
reason I think I'm lagging look look at
this oh what's happening you are lagging
were you always lagging no maybe it's
once I started the stream the internet
is like
over
overheated we we we'll see we'll see
we'll see yeah I mean at least you're
moving yeah just just keep on talking
and then it won't be noticeable that you
okay it's fixed oh really okay nice
yeah yay it's overheated well why
wouldn't it be overheated with these two
cute burp ladies with our matching uh
Hawaiian shirt which is actually not
what we're wearing cuz you changed into
pajamas they don't no what do you mean
we're wearing it on this what do you
mean um I think I talked about this on
stream that I was planning to do this
and while I'm confirming Nissa and I did
wear the orange
and all right we have switch sides the
orange and the blue uh Hawaii shirts I
got that's some real tacki haai Shir I'm
still wearing it it has pineapples on
and flamingos M and watermelon
watermelon and some flowers and flowers
and mine's orange and hers
blue yeah it's so cute you like it yes I
like it because we match and that makes
me feel special yay yeah we're matching
and I thought I I I thought up until
today cuz today was the first time we
wor up until today maybe they wouldn't
have thought that we are romantically
involved but today we're in partner
outfits I think it may have done it may
have given us an image change yes I hope
so you hope so yes you hope they think
we are romantically involved of
course uh can I do my intro to yeah of
course hi Darlings this is H life
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only Nissa Raven craft
hello first time in the mold first time
I didn't drown so that's good you didn't
drown yeah of course you didn't drown
how can you drown the water is so
shallow and calm mhm it's so beautiful
very beautiful we're going to talk uh
since this is the first stream that
we're doing in the males we're going to
talk about uh our experience so far
and yeah if you guys didn't see I did
make a schedule for this week can you
believe it a schedule on vacation in the
Maldives unbelievable what yeah I just I
I wanted to use the art again and I
wanted to feel like you know we have a
plan and then we will follow it because
we have a plan makes it easier yeah yeah
so I don't know where we should even
start though like there's so much to
talk about m
is is there where somewhere where you
want to start I mean I do have like some
pictures here that we can maybe take as
guide we rode a sea plane a sea plane
you guys remember when uh that was
really popular in um Animal Crossing
yeah Animal
Crossing everyone was obsessed with the
sea planes I I was on one of those and
Ki was so nice she let me sit in the
window seat yeah cuz I sat in the window
seat before
yeah yeah when we we uh had a little a
little flight in a really loud these are
really loud they're so loud they go like
really loud sea plane and we flew over a
couple of islands until we landed on
ours but it's really small there's not
many seats in here um you can perhaps
see a little bit W Sugo you can
literally see the cuz the door is always
open you can literally see like the
pilot the pilot Pilots mhm uh doing
their thing to go very fascinating did
you ever look at them yeah I did I
couldn't see them very well though
because there's lots of people and we're
kind of like near the
backc but it was very fun D that's not a
lot of room yeah it was like five rows
maybe uh it's pretty small on the right
side there were two seeders left side
one seat honestly it's like pretty much
the same as my my previous SE plane
flight M yeah I imagine they kind of
have to be pretty small yeah they're all
so small they're all like this but it
was nice and actually uh was nice you
saw some islands right and you got
excited they we got excited tell me
about it well I've never quite seen
islands like that down in hell so I was
not sure what to expect you know cuz you
know you know when you're traveling
somewhere the first for the first time
and you see a lot of like the travel
pictures first right so you're like well
I don't really know what it's actually
going to look like and these you know
the saturation could be turned off there
could be some editing you think so yeah
so I was like I was like I I knew I was
going to have fun but I was ready to be
a little disappointed with the water I
was not I looked down and even from the
SE plane I was like oh my God it is
pretty much exactly as blue as all of
pictures tur very tur it was crazy
yeah it was so nice I was so happy to be
able to go back here it's a paradise
we're not in the same place as where I
went before cuz I thought first of all I
don't want to like there's so many
islands in the males there's hundreds uh
and I thought I I shouldn't go to the
same place I should try to experience
something else and also because the
other ones prices were kind of
crazy yeah yeah birds in Paradise
paradise birds isn't a bird yeah right
yeah we're paradise
birds you should get sponsored by the
mald tourism board I think so too if
only you'd be perfect at least the
tourism board doesn't have to sponsor me
but maybe like it would be nice to get
like a oh what's going on oh am I
lagging
now oh I well oh it's just not maybe
it's tracking like both of us
yeah H what it was like confused oh my
eyes are still shaking
okay okay okay okay and what was I
saying I yeah it would be nice if at
least like we could get um oh my oh now
the tracking is weird cuz I moved it if
we could at least get the hotel for free
mhm but
no I can't even I wouldn't even have
like
the I don't know like the confidence or
audacity to even be like M hi I'm an
influencer I have 1.5 million
subscribers
can I get the room for free like I
wouldn't I feel like we can't really do
that yeah it's a little
difficult but I still I don't think it
would be
impossible so you but I don't I don't
know I don't really like that I don't
really like doing that in the first
place like from my side saying do it for
me if they are like hey we want you to
stay at our place so you promote us a
little bit then cool but like from my
side I don't want to do it if you're if
you're reaching yeah I totally
understand that in that
situation cuz I also had that like I was
working in a hotel and checking emails
and people just yeah constantly asking
you for I have this platform and they
don't even have that many people
following them they like 100 they're
like I have 15 so if you give me a it
was a bit more than that but yeah I just
put the email in the um trash in the
spam in you are not getting a free room
no you will pay or go
away yeah please contact me males I
would like this to be a yearly
thing you're baely talking Nisa I'm
sorry please talk please interrupt me
and talk I I don't like to interrupt you
though I like you're barely talking okay
it's hard because I I obviously watch
your stream so I'm used to just
listening to you talk and I usually
chill out so the the moment I hear you
talking I just kind of I start zoning
out in a good way because I'm like ah
she's speaking my queen but you better
talk yeah yeah yeah okay well what nice
so we got off the sea plane and we got
on our Island and immediately we were
greeted by
uh yeah
these
coconuts surprising to see uh holiday
decorations in the most summery place
I've ever been everything was Christmas
decorated it was very hilarious but we
were we were greeted by people drumming
and then we got these like woven
necklaces Oh Yeah from like palm tree
leaves I think yeah they cute necklace
they they had this whole like welcome
ceremony they do it every time when
someone's arriving we can always tell
when a plane's coming cuz we hear the
plane but then we hear the drumming m a
little bit of drumming in the distance
yeah but it's it's nice like it got me
like a little bit excited I'm like oh
wow this is so welcoming and the
necklace is cute and yeah then we then
we got like a little tour yeah oh yeah
after the coconut how did you like the
coconut thing I my first time I tried
coconut juice out of a coconut but I
never had coconut juice to begin with
mine was like leaking on the table botom
like it was definitely not condensation
so I slurped mine up really quickly cuz
I didn't want it to make a mess there
wasn't as much juice as you would have
thought in it really I had a lot inside
it kind of tasted
like I've never had just coconut water
so I don't know tastes like but so it
was it was like it was not too sweet but
it tasted also like there was some like
uh orange juice mixed into it yeah it's
just I I thought so too I thought maybe
coconut juice has like a hint of orange
but no it's probably like literally just
because the straw was like pushed for
the orange and then there's like a tiny
Mount of orange on the straw but that's
enough to give it like a hint of orange
crazy it's pretty good and then we got a
tour of the island yeah in a cart yes it
was um tennis cart a little
nerve-wracking but it was fun
nerve-wracking yeah cuz I'm not used to
being in new
places I'm like oh oh it's all new it's
so scary it's so new there was it was
pretty interesting to me to see like a
different layout of like these islands
cuz like they all like it's like a
resort per Island basically but you know
all the islands are different shapes and
different like uh arrangements and like
the one I went to before it was like if
felt like it was like a forest that
where all the paths were like
intertwined and Tangled like one big
Forest I don't know and you could you
could really get lost but it was kind of
nice and then here it feels like it's
just like M mainly One path that goes
straight in a line so you can't really
get lost which I'm very happy
for yeah so that's pretty cool and yeah
we got a tour they showed us our room
which it's beautiful and big yes it's so
big it's fantastic bed is comfortable
mhm we are sleeping together of course
we we're not over the water this
time for financial reasons
mostly um but yeah cuz we have a nice
like we're in directly in front of the
ocean we can walk right over into it and
we can even see like from here if it
wasn't dark as hell now uh I could see
the ocean
if I look straight ahead I know I there
the ocean is right there I can see it I
can see it when I lie lay in bed so so
beautiful like waking up in the morning
and looking straight outside and just
the water is so blue and the path is so
nice too like with the the trees like
giving us a little bit of an arch yeah
it's this very gorgeous like exit like
you feel like you're coming out of the
trees and suddenly finding a beach for
the first time in a world that's
Untouched by human it's not the case
obviously but that's like the weird
feeling that I get just because it's so
the water looks so untouched I know
people are swimming in it all the time
but oh my
God it's so pretty gor yeahum uh and
also yeah there's a lot of a lot of
restaurants again and they have like I
think they even have more activities in
terms of like water sports to offer than
the previous one I have to compare
everything but but there's oh they made
us okay this I thought this kind of
interesting they made us download two
apps there's one like hotel app where
you can like book everything that you
want like restaurants Etc uh and then
you can see your itiner itinerary yeah
itinerary
itinerary and then there's another app
which is it shows you where the shuttle
currently is at there's like little golf
cart shuttle going around the island so
that if you don't want to walk or if you
don't want to use your bike because we
get bicycles you can use a shuttle
um we we have barely used the shuttle
because we failed at it several times
yeah well it was so weird because
actually yesterday so when we first got
here we decided we wanted to go eat and
it's it's about lunchtime right so we
decided we were like oh it's not that
long of a walk we'll just go so as soon
as we get settled in we go and uh my
issue was my bag actually got stuck yeah
and so I couldn't change so I was still
in the winter clothes I had from flying
to Austria now in like 80 degree
Fahrenheit
weather this it's basically from okay in
Celsius I can only say it in Celsius but
it's like from from 5 C to 30 C mhm
wow it's super duper freaking warm so um
hia lends me very kindly some flipflops
but I think they were too big for
because no because the room had
flip-flops like they were really really
B really big so I was like you want to
use mine and they they fit in size but
like I feel like no matter how they fit
like they're going to first time you
wear them they're going to tear you
apart so uh now I have the issue of uh
we we tried to go into the ocean after
sorry for skipping around to bit and um
I realized wow my toes really burned
like the the inner area between like my
my big toe and the one after it and then
I look later and it's because the skin
got completely scraped off just that
area from the middle part of the sand it
happens but it's because we walked so
long because we missed the shuttle right
in front of our nose then we waited
nothing came eventually we're like I
guess we'll start
walking you said we'll start walking it
was all my fault on if I would have
known cuz I was like oh we'll probably
just pass a shuttle we can flag it and
have it pick us up but every time the
shuttle did pass us which was rarely by
the way it was
full today we went on a short walk again
or no we're we're riding bikes right
today it was bikes mostly and every like
I felt like every few minutes a shuttle
pass us it was way more common yeah and
they were like empty and I was like are
you kidding me yesterday when we needed
it desperately yeah we started walking
and we were hoping that a car would pass
by and
for us but yeah and we kept on walking
and walking it was hot that was one of
the most exhausting walks of my life
because I was really hungry really
hungry still and the the heat the Heat
and the sun was killing me at the same
time and lack of sleep so free uh
debuffs from life but the food was
pretty good I got what did what did you
wait the first first lunch yeah the
first lunch you got the steak and the
mashed potatoes and I got a tuna ramp
the steak was so or the steak was good
but the the potatoes it was like they
put it in a Piping Bag and then swirled
it into circles cuz they were so nicely
placed it was so cute you know I I
wanted to say I wanted to complain oh
yes it's so expensive everything is so
expensive mhm oh my God okay okay so
there's like you know there's free
restaurants and then there's stuff we
have to pay for uh for food but then
also massages of course are expensive
but like one 1990 minute massage will go
from
like 210 to
us okay okay and then what about water
sports huh want to want to check out
some water sports well uh tough luck
because it's going to be expensive the
non Mo Motorsports are like yeah free
pretty much um I think most of all of
them maybe
but wait where is it exper is it under
experiences water sports does that
include tips I do think all of it does
include the A C it's de so yeah
10% at least there's that yeah so if you
want to do jet ski for 15 minutes it's
68 bucks for 15 minutes of jet
[Music]
ski yeah there's other stuff like yeah
but I don't I don't even want to try
that if anything I would have tried the
jet ski
M wind surfing paddle Bo paddle board is
free no know it's it's it's okay and
then there's like excursions
mhm most of them are cost money yeah
there's like one free like snorkeling
trip they can take us to but then
there's a special one that costs
money a special one where we can see
special uh
animals and 80 person 80 80 USD per
person 80 Plus+ plus it actually says
what does it mean 80 plus plus what does
that mean what's it say 80 plus plus per
person I don't know more why more why
double
pluses yeah so like everything's really
expensive and which like is to be
expected when you want I feel
likeing take me for free I mean yeah it
still sucks it's like you think about it
when you go on vacation especially when
you're paying for like an allinclusive
Resort you know it's nice because like
for example we got our first massage
today that one was actually
free 45 minutes for free mhm and then
anything after that you have to pay for
and then I mean really a lot of the
restaurants are free the issue is just
some of them are reservation only and
for some reason like we went to one that
was reservation only today it was like
completely empty inside but when we went
because we had accidentally only booked
for one and we're like they'll probably
let us in but let's try to edit it and
it literally for whatever reason
wouldn't let us it was like this is
completely booked we get there we I I'm
expecting this place to be full cuz
apparently it's fully booked right
literally only one other table had
people at it and I was just like huh
yeah I don't know what that was that was
very weird hey honeymoon bath with rose
petals 150 bucks me and way it got that
for free before for not even asking they
just like imagine they just did it you
know I thought about it I wonder if what
happened with that is they accidentally
did it at the wrong room yeah and then
they're just like oh maybe yeah and then
they're like oops and they're like well
I'm not going to drain it now
maybe it could be or they were just
better and
nice special bath decoration 150 that's
unbelievable yeah and this one doesn't
even have as many roast petals as the
one that you had no no yeah yeah true
but oh oh oh there's oh there's
variations
oh oh I could just buy some roses and
make my own Rose
bath yeah that is true or like the
random tropical flowers that are like
lying outside randomly on the floor yeah
just collect those oh that'd be so Prett
I was even thinking of bring bringing a
a a a bath bumb I was thinking about it
bringing my bath bombs cuz I have so
many he was like maybe I'll bring him
along take a nice bath I want bathroom
though was amazing oh yeah it's incred
it's outdoor yeah and that's
crazy bathtub and shower outdoor mhm
yo it we took a shower together with our
swimsuits on of course like normal
people and like I was so crazy I was
like I'm outside right now with my ooshi
taking a shower oh yeah
yeah oh
it's funny because I said as a joke
let's shower together to Safe Water and
then it actually happened today no my
she said that to me and I was like what
did you just say like it was obviously a
joke in the moment I know but like oh my
God you're just like she's I I have to
be honest can I can I drag you that yeah
she's so cute and I I can't help every
time I look at her I just have the
uncontrollable urge tell her how cute
she is to the point where she has said
please stop calling me cute yeah because
first of all it will not be special
anymore she will call me like cute so
many times a day you're just so cute I
can't help it especially in moments
where I'm not cute like like all moments
but like when I'm not wearing makeup and
like Missy why do you have to have
makeup to be cute you don't that it's
just a fact like what the hell excuse me
you just and it's so Random it's like
out of nowhere always I just look it's
like it's like it's like you know that
anime meme where you're like watching
the sunset and like the girl's looking
she's like wow it's beautiful and then
the guy's looking he's like at the girl
and he's like yeah that's me with you
except I say it to your face instead of
like waiting for a weird
moment thank you she hasn't called me
cute once though e you are cute I've
told you like you say you say like I
don't know you you're like I'll also
tell you you're like you know Finn cuz
you're
like yeah but I'm just I just don't know
a do it so it doesn't get overused MH
mhm I see I see we come from different
places I do like your hair very much and
I I I wish you wouldn't braid it all the
time oh yeah no
she she braids it all the time it's
pretty but it looks even prettier when
it's open it does but then it gets
Tangled do you want to detangle my hair
for me at the end of the day no that's
what I thought then I'm going to keep
wearing it in a
braid well you're like Rapunzel I am
like Rapunzel
Rapunzel that's what the prince says in
German to Rapunzel Rapunzel letel let
down your hair let your hair down please
oh I should show them my pictures so
yeah wait we what's next in the timeline
yeah well I don't know there's not
there's nothing day one basically ended
by we went and we got dinner at the
buffet it was very nice and then we came
back and K up preparing for today no
wait wait wait wait you completely
missed one important part I we ate lunch
we came
back we took a nap at 5:00 p.m. and I a
good nap I made an alarm for us really
soon after after okay soon after an hour
or or an hour and a half or something
like that I would have had us wake up
then my alarm goes off but I wanted to
sleep a little bit more so I extended it
and then I couldn't fall asleep in that
extended time so I was like I'll
extend it again didn't work again
extended it again didn't work again and
that in the end it was 3 hours that we
had napped and I was like okay it's
8:00 p.m. now I'm going to wake up
narissa because I mean she's sleeping so
comfortably but we should probably get
up to get dinner this is really bad so
yeah so she woke me up we went and got
dinner but you you said why why can't we
just sleep until morning why why do we
have to go God okay keep in mind you
guys got to remember that I'm in
extremely jet legged cuz not only did I
fly from a place from Hell a CST time
zone to Austria so I was already not
like kind of starting to adjust a little
bit and then we got here which is like
what 4 hours time difference so then
we're here and I I'm still not caught up
and so I was tired I think you just you
know you know I think the heat can make
you tired and cuddling in the bed we
were not cuddling with the bed yeah just
being in the bed makes you automatically
tired mhm it's just so warm like even
right now just thinking about it it's
making me tired stop talking about the
bed or I'm going to fall asleep no at
least today we didn't do the the second
we all we did have a nap and we were
going to take a second nap I was like n
said this is really bad we cannot take a
second nap thankfully stayed up while
talking because well so we took the nap
yesterday right that was too long we had
a dinner and then uh we came back so we
we went to dinner at 8:00 p.m. right we
came back maybe 1 and a half hours later
and at 1:00 p.m. I was I was like making
my schedule and then at 10: p.m. Thea
goes to sleep I was so tired you were so
you fell asleep again and I was like how
can she sleep already again I'm wide
awake I'm making my schedule I'm not
cleaning out my suitcase I'm doing this
and that I'm making thumbnail for
tomorrow I already had it yesterday yeah
guys I'm doing all the things passed out
I'm so sorry I'm trying to find the
lights because we couldn't find the
lights so I'm like going around the I
knew where they were but she didn't want
to wake me up to ask if you would have
woke me up I would have told you I'm so
sorry oh let see how it is oh what would
you mean you see how it is yeah and then
uh I was like I probobly should go
to sleep finally at midnight because you
were if if I go too late and you go too
early it's not going to match up mhm
finally I go to sleep at midnight and
then we both wake up at 5:00 a.m. yeah
yeah I I don't want to blame you it's
not my fault I will blame you only 10%
why because you woke up and that woke me
up but then I tried to sleep again and
it I couldn't no I woke up and I was
trying to fall back asleep cuz I think I
got up to go to the bathroom I think
like you like you being on your phone at
5:00 a.m. made me mentally feel like I
have to get up I was I on my yeah yeah
you were well she woke up to go to the
bathroom and then I and then you were on
the phone but I had like my I had my
screen brightness all the way down yeah
how did you even see cuz I turned around
why were you doing were you trying to
get close to me no I just turned around
because I wanted I was wondering hm is
she using I had this feeling even though
I didn't see it I felt like I think
she's on her phone so I turned around
and you were on your phone
why do you need to confirm it you're so
crazy I wanted to make sure that you
properly going back to sleep because 500
a.m. is not a good time to wake up I
mean I slept an appropriate amount of
time you're the one who needed more
sleep no the problem is that you it's
it's totally understandable that you
were awake at 5:00 a.m. because you
slept you had the nap that was 3 hours
and then you fell asleep again at 10
p.m. of course you're going to be awake
at 5 a.m. yeah but it's okay it all
worked out in yet CU we got up well no
first we talked for an hour then we went
to the beach in the morning we were
trying to see the sunrise yeah but it
wasn't in a good spot we saw like some
of it yeah then we were stalking the
hermit crabs again yeah there were so
many we accidentally turned down the
wrong way to get back or remember and
like our neighbors had like an army of
hermit crabs they were like passing the
road basically trying to get to us yeah
cuz it's not like we don't have many not
so any hermit crabs either like I mean
look there's so many these are this is
just like 5% of what we have in our so
to say Garden or whatever I don't know
they're so
cute there's so many yeah they're like
there's some really big ones and we keep
on stalking them you keep on like
presenting them as a sacrifice to me I
feel like yeah well you know sometimes
when when the person you're with gets
excited when they see a Hermit Crown you
have kfp you understand but it's a bit
terrifying cuz you pick them up I I'm
just like looking at the ocean and I
come back and then I look and and I see
you put like five hermit grabs on the
table and they're not able to get down
to the sand they're like oh my God and
they're looking at me and then I come
closer and then they they like hide in
their shell it's so cute but it's so sad
though like we're going to eat them I
would I would agree if we they're so
scared yeah but then they forget about
it like I'm sure they don't even
remember and even if they do what they
get imagined you get picked up by a
giant human you go back to your family
live to tell the tale you're going be
like oh my God what a hero you live you
live I live yeah well I'm also
sure humans touch him all the time so
even though they still hide I'm pretty
sure they're also kind of like used to
it you know they're like oh most of the
time they're just looking and they're
not going to hurt you but you know it's
your instinct to hide just for the
people who don't have Twitter let me
show you this terrifying
monster oh
that's so fake so fake narissa that
scream is so fake no not a
lizard yeah that was the fancy lizard
that we saw yesterday but besides that I
only saw like normal colored like gray
brown colored geckos this is the only
cool one that I saw yeah and it started
doing push-ups mhm mm it's like crazy so
cute the
push-ups even though you call them
sit-ups cuz I would had to think first p
so cute it was getting buffed and then
and then this is from today as well but
um I've noticed there were like holes in
the beach not only out of the water but
also inside of the water these
relatively big holes I almost wondered
if they were for snakes yeah I thought
so too you know um that animal that's
like an eel that goes like upward it's
not an eel though what what is that
called I don't know you know what I mean
though right it's so funny
say Clans no wait wait wait I I want see
see
no what am I thinking of uh I don't know
I like a Wiglet do crabs build holes
that low wait don't guys don't say the
correct answer
yet see no Mor yeah I think
I'm I don't know it is not a Mor yeah
it's not but I I thought it would be
cute if it
was you don't want to see aore popping
out in the ocean let alone the sand it
would be cute but then eventually uh
today I found the culprit and even saw
it making a hole in action yeah this is
not the video but I've been seeing some
big ass craps here look at that oh okay
wait wait I don't know why the video is
so
small wait Play It
Again
you see this
crap it's so big his eyes were so big
and it was like fighting against the
water the wobbly
water cute very cute and I saw it like
running away from me and then quickly
making a hole like this it's so big it
was such a big boy especially when we
were mostly just catching like hermit
crabs and stuff yeah there's these big
boys though mm the masters of the hermit
crabs the ones who
probably I wonder what they taste
like have you ever had crab yeah I love
crab you love
crab I
don't I don't why not oh what did I just
oh uh well I don't why not I don't what
do you not like about it I don't like it
I don't like a lot of seafood well
that's perfect because then when we go
together I can eat the crab and I
thought you don't like seafood much
either I don't but I like
cations not a whole do the only thing I
don't like about crab is how difficult
it is to eat M cuz that I love crap
but when you're breaking open the legs
it's so tedious and just shitty I hate
it yeah I can understand here's a nice
picture oh yes yes this was our
breakfast view cuz we went to breakfast
so early today the first thing in the
morning 700 a.m. after was a lot of time
in the morning on the beach it was so
nice nice breakfast it was beautiful and
then after what did you take me to do
for the first time
sing cuz like yeah yesterday you didn't
really join me swimming around so I
didn't stay in long cuz I was it was
lonely oh I'm sry no but today I to you
snowling we got a snowling equipment and
you were so nervous you were so
terrified I'm so scared I'm so scared
but it was not something to be scared of
right right yeah I mean uh it took me a
little bit because I I couldn't figure
out obviously I know how to breathe
through my mouth but so for some reason
I just could not stop breathing through
my nose so like obviously there's no air
in the mask for me to breathe in so I'm
breathing through both my mouth and my
nose simultaneously so I'm like not
getting enough air so yeah you have to
focus on your breathing you really have
to it's just like singing so I was like
uh I I started to feel really
claustrophobic and I started panicking
for a little bit but obviously we're in
a really small space so it was really
easy to just get back Catch My Breath re
rethink what I'm doing try to remember
and think of how to breathe before I'm
in the water and then get back in and
try again so kiata was a very good
teacher I mean I didn't do much I said
it's just it comes really naturally and
it's easy you just you don't even have
to like be a good swimmer cuz you wear
so like yeah they give you worried about
the little mermaid fins yeah the fins
like you don't have to be a good swimmer
you're basically you're just let the
waves or the water carry you because
you're not here to swim you're here to
just chill and look at the fish yeah so
just fly just float you know how to
float mhm no so it was so nice I
actually cuz you guys have been asking I
didn't eat sea water at all this time I
know I got a lot better at this thing we
were successful I had much more control
over it um but like I I did get a little
bit like sick after everything no I
didn't throw up but like I felt like
dizzy and sickick mhm mhm which is fine
it got it eventually was gone but okay
so I have to say like this coral reef
that they have with the fishies there
that the closest one that we can
basically reach um from like our room
easily is yeah it's fine to look at it
once but we want to go out a little bit
somewhere with the boat to check out a
coola coral reef because the only really
cool fish that I saw that we saw I saw I
saw a a rainbow fish did you guys know
the rainbow fish from the children's
book yeah I look sad it looked exactly
like that I I looked up pictures of uh
rainbow fish and some of them look
different than the others but what I saw
was exactly like the one from the
children's book and I was like holy
I need to show narissa and you were
taking a break at the moment so I
quickly swam I was like holy this
is beautiful it was one single rainbow
fish who was like like being a loner
right he was being a loner he was
tackling he was really low to the ground
he was tackling the the sand on the
ground probably looking for like shells
or whatever or little fish to eat I
don't know what they eat but he was like
swirling whirling the the the sand it
was seemed like some technique yeah uh
like how I I was saying how cats um rub
against like the edges of tables or so
that's what he was doing with the floor
of the water so I swam over to you was
likea come quick I saw I saw rainbow
fish H sh please follow me and you were
like oh but then we couldn't find it
yeah but then we randomly saw the
coolest thing a nose fish yeah a unicorn
unicorn fish yeah nose I just call it
nose fish yeah unicorn fish he had a a
horn as as his nose kind of yeah it was
like really cool what did you think I
was kind of frightened um frightened did
you think he would attack you no but you
know what I I got really nervous when I
swam out to the boundary for some reason
I was like I've never even seen Jaws to
be scared of it but I was like what if
what if it starts swimming towards me
what if there's a shark out there and it
just comes towards me I'll never be able
to make it
back I was like no there's no fish no no
no no no shark there no goo I'm so
scared G Can't Swim anyway G leave me
alone please I don't taste but you were
it's kind of cute you were like even
scared of like there's so like all the
fish are normal and you were like yeah I
I might have forgotten myself so for to
mention I'm a little scared of fish
actually and like uh it's because when I
was really young I was swimming in a
lake and you know Lake water not all
lakes but some Lakes are really murky
and you can't really see more than like
a few inches deep it was one of those
lakes and I was tubing fell off the tube
tubing it's like where you're on a tube
and you're holding on and a boat is
driving around so I fell off the tube
because the boat was going too fast so
they were coming back around to get me
in that time I'm sure it was just a
normal siiz fish and it just felt giant
to my little baby brain okay but I felt
a fish touch you a little bit yeah no go
across my thigh and I screamed and I was
like I'm about to die well I would
probably be freaked out a little bit uh
if a fish touched me like that too but
when I was swimming around like that
didn't happen a single time they they
definitely easily always keep like a
distance even even when you think you're
close they still like swoosh around you
so no need to worry I think they don't
want to touch you they are terrified of
you that's what they always say about
animals that yeah you're scared of like
spiders yeah they're actually more
scared of you I mean they're more scared
of you I would be too scared of the
giant like I'd be scared of a human
giant even if like we could speak the
same language so the fish I mean they
were pretty chill like they they just
kind of gave us space but I don't think
they were like scared I think they're
probably used to seeing people M you
know you know what fascinates me there
were a couple of these fish um that are
like not so spectacular they're just
like pretty much transparent white fish
they were really pretty though pretty
transparent they're pretty not as
spectacular as the other tropical fish
but the thing is with those fish you can
literally
see like their poop
inside their
body because like normal I saw them
without it and I saw them with it you
see just like one string of black
surrounded by like a little bit of like
a a yellow aura why are you talking
about something in the middle of their
body you can see it that that's how
transparent that fish is
e
disgusting imagine girl we were swimming
in the ocean's toilet
basically I don't want to think about
okay so we stopped
snorkeling but this is the cleanest
ocean toilet anyway like it's so clear
the water is really beautiful really
clear that's true I got better at
snorkeling so now I'm excited to go out
with a boat tomorrow we're going out on
a little snorkeling trip I'm taking you
with me what time is it I won't tell you
now tell me later yeah but it will be
fun it will be special hopefully more
like this I wanted to say like this
Coral R was like me maybe I haven't
Haven seen so many yet right but this
was like it was like a 4 out of 10 so
I'm hoping for at least a seven out of
tomorrow but for you how was it seeing
all the colorful fish was there one that
stood out to you besides the the the
unicorn fish um I mean I really like the
transparent white ones actually I just
thought they were so cute like I was
looking at them and I was like those
ones yeah I mean the other ones I've
like seen before not like or like in
like aquariums and stuff like now in
person yeah I mean in aquariums is it
still in
person what do you mean I would not
count that it's not comparable to seeing
them with your can almost I mean there
was you're in the same water in the same
contain I kep screaming though and the
last time I screamed I think too much
like air came out of my nose that I
created a gap and then suddenly I had
the sensation of drowning even though I
could yeah yeah yeah even though I could
still breathe from my mouth because
suddenly my nose was covered in water
and I was like
I I'm so scared I mean I I don't know
what it is this time I just everything
set on my head perfectly but before I
also had like a lot of like
leaks both in my inside my snel and in
my goggles so maybe for the for the
goggles maybe you just got to make them
tighter yeah and then for the S as long
as you like keep it properly like as
long as you bite into it and don't like
I don't know dive under then there
shouldn't really be any water in there
yeah no the snor was completely fine the
whole time so that was safe but yeah the
goggles I was like oh no I'm so excited
you did it though because as I said I
think once you try it once it'll be like
your favorite thing to do on vacations
you you'll always be on the lookout to
like go snowling if there's like a coral
re around you got to go
snowling yeah
so I'll do it if it's with and even
though it costs a lot of money I want to
go to the special animal snorkeling
there's special I don't want to mention
it now I want to do it to yeah H and I
want to bring you guys I brought my
camera I uh my special that's not a
GoPro but it's like kind of like a GoPro
the the insta 360 or so I think that's
what it's was called yeah and I brought
it and I looked up I'm still like kind
of nervous about it but it does say you
guys can come confirm it for me if you
want to I need a second opinion it does
say that it's
waterproof uh as long as I take it off
of the the base like there's a I don't
know you guys going to look it up but
it's like you can take off like a
clip that part is waterproof so I'll I'm
also just scared to like Drop it because
with my snorkel I'm not going to be able
to like pick it up from the bottom of
the O but I have this like magnetic
necklace okay here's the question guys a
magnetic necklace where the camera
sticks onto it's like an accessory that
came with it will it still be magnetic
on the water why wouldn't it be I would
I hope I hope I don't know I think I
think it would be but just making sure
I'm pretty positive the answer is yes I
would think so to yes
okay okay yes it will L shut up don't
laugh at me just making sure it's it's
important magnetism isn't affected by
water okay then I'm so scared I'm still
so scared I don't want to break the
camera I really hope it's really
waterproof yeah I hope so too I'm always
really nervous cuz some stuff is
waterproof only for like a certain
amount of like death mhh exactly but
like for that I'm like M I don't trust
that it's really waterproof yeah when it
says that but it didn't say anything
like that about my camera and also like
I'm not going to go deep anyway I'll
stay like at the top um can I say
something
yes wait can I say
this
what oh yeah yeah one Miracle That's So
Random we have the same phone same exact
phone same
smartphone Samsung uh Ultra uh s22 s22
we have the same I was looking and I was
cuz you were connecting me I think to
your to your Wi-Fi hotspot and I was
like oh wait a minute we have the same
one we both wear cases so we didn't
notice right away well I feel like I
wouldn't have Noti Andro chats team
Android you don't like iPhone let you
right no I don't like iPhone at all
actually sorry iPhone I never know like
I I struggled so much cuz we use iPhone
for work right we have a work iPhone and
like when I try to like turn it off or
like go to the settings menu or whatever
it's so confusing like where do I swipe
I never understand I never get it I
don't like it I'll use it though Android
gang raise your hands let's go Android
what's up Android
gang I'm so happy to know you're also an
Android lover it makes me feel like I'm
winning I mean I have to say I've always
been an Android User I have to say like
I like the the portrait camera of the
s22 a lot but for the uh Zoom the mega
mega mega Zoom I have to say my previous
uh hu would had a better Zoom m than my
updated then newer uh Samsung the zoom
the zoom it's only the zoom but the I
really love the portrait mode of the
Samsung so it's gorgeous I've been using
it by the way speaking of the portrait
Zoom uh let me show you some yummy food
pictures this was noa's uh green curry
green curry which he warned us so
strongly it's so spicy it really was not
that spicy at all yeah it was there was
one pepper in there that looked like a
bell pepper and was wasn't it's the red
one and that was spicy but like the
curry itself was like really not spicy
at all oh do yeah but then like I tried
it too even for me it was so funny
because kiata was looking at stuff and
she was like oh is it spicy I don't
really like just spicy yes just spicy
yes and this guy was super recom like he
was very much like insistent on the
things he'd recommend yeah once I said
that I can't eat spicy food he was like
uh all of this is spicy you should try
this you should try this you wanted to
bring us four different dishes and we're
like no we don't need that many and then
even for the desserts we already knew
what we wanted and he was very insistent
he was like no trust me get this one DT
too he's like you can still get those
ones and we're just like dude please I
already know what I want thank you
though I appreciate it but I didn't ask
for your dessert recommendations like he
recommended this once is like um he said
it wasn't spicy canop yeah yeah it
wasn't SP like he he recommends it first
for me and then I say okay I guess I'll
take it and then later he says oh no
don't take it it's spicy like I'm like
what why you recommend it then when
that's the whole purpose of now you
don't want me to take it but it was fine
the the planting was really beautiful
like I mean look at this this is what I
really wanted and I did get it brusa but
it looks like kza is on top but it's
actually rot cheese that looks like kza
though it kind of does look like kza in
this picture and yummy good good B that
a lot of Olives but I I'll take it I'll
eat it as long as there's tomatoes in
there
mhm yeah so that's some food and oh yeah
just a random picture that I also
already had up on
Twitter now one of our views the the
sand is so white it is it's so we were
when we were biking today we stopped and
checked out one of the beaches oh my God
yeah I want to go there maybe tomorrow I
don't know if we get up uh like snor we
go snorkling but maybe before snorkling
I don't know warming up for the
snorkling so we'll find time we'll find
time oh she's leaning on to me we're
just like looking opposite directions on
the screen
guys how's your sunburn we're not
sunburn yeah actually fascinating you're
welcome it's cuz of the big American
sunscreen yeah I beged you to bring
American
sunscreen maybe Austrian one would have
done the job but I don't know it's okay
you brought sunscreen I brought the
Hawaii shirts for us yeah they're so
cute we're
matching American sunscreen yeah America
let's go oh also I've been actively bird
watching as you guys know yeah I we
couldn't find this one again it was so
we keep on I keep on looking for it well
it was so interesting because just as
okay okay that story is so good you want
to tell it then yeah cuz okay you go
you you you you are the the our Butler
okay I am me okay we drive he's showing
things look at
this I'm sorry do you actually do you
perhaps have um like any kind of like
interesting tropical birds are still on
the island I slam on the brakes and look
over to the
left look this this one right here is
nesting currently she recently moved in
oh like he was in the middle of driving
fast and then I asked the question and
we are immediately right there it's like
oh good that you're asking yeah good
timing and that's when I took that
picture she was nesting we were like
pretty much like right next to her but
she didn't fly away I'm guessing it's a
her cuz she's nesting right
apparently apparently she's nesting but
then at the same time when we looked it
up this bird was like potentially a
juvenile yeah or it's a a a gender thing
I don't know cuz it's called red build
red build Tropic bird and the pictures
that I found they had all much more red
beaks and a really long beautiful tail
did you see no you have to look it up
like oh my God the the fulfilled version
of this bird the extreme version of this
bird the tail no I'll show you now it's
not like a normal uh tail of a bird it's
crazy okay let me show you red built
Tropic
bird you guys look it up too
look oh wow what do you call this
gorgeous yeah jeez it's like w wo look
at the
dynamic and that's what we saw that's
what we saw it's such a special bird I
think are you guys looking it up it's
pretty right yeah okay so it is a a gen
I thought yeah cuz uh first I thought it
was jinile but then thinking about it a
lot of birds are like not only Birds but
like um like a pea fouls peacocks pea
fows the males are like fantabulous what
the what what why let the let the
girls look pretty too man the girls are
still pretty they just don't look as
flashy yeah s this now it's to attract
the ladies yeah I guess so makes a
little sense so need something to
attract the ladies and then I I saw a
bird right after that was so cute I I
wish I would have taken a picture I
can't I don't know what it is I wish I
hope I see it again do you remember that
tiny tiny I think it was a pretty dark
black bird I do I remember tiny bird
that was like moving its butt a little
bit when walking M and it it was moving
kind of funnily yeah was cute though was
that I have no idea it was like dancing
when it was taking a step I think not
wiggling like yeah but like kind of up
and down dancing I think but with its
butt and pretty small it was pretty
small small mating dance it was just
like walking across the street you think
it was
mating For Me Maybe internet a little
bit mad yeah I'm completely broken
oh open your
mouth oh I I've been broken oh okay it's
it's it's having a a hard time it's okay
yeah it's Okay Internet G it has like
it's up ups and downs yeah it's okay
so I'll try to find that bird still but
we also saw several
herin gra ha yeah they've been
everywhere they're so beautiful it makes
me think of the new hayami aaki movie oh
apparently they're really common though
generally even in America right yeah but
for me I don't know he he looks so cool
they look so cool cuz they're like so
long-legged and long long necked they're
very
beautiful oh you're getting one guy
Google says there is no difference Al so
maybe it is juile thing what but who
knows doesn't matter cuz we're never
finding that bird again it gave up its
nest once we have made it public maybe
maybe that's why maybe cuz I uploaded it
on Twitter it said I'm not I'm going to
change my Nest don't do that they're
going to steal my eggs so I'm going to
move saf me I can't believe you kicked
that bird out of its nesting spot I
didn't kick it out but like you
personally I I that I doxed it yeah so
now it's like for safety I'm going to go
oh man that's I feel
bad bir Sama I was considering you for
whole to position oh excuse
me excuse I'm right here but don't know
you're constantly under
consideration you're currently being
tested I'm intern Shan it's okay this
trip is a test n what I didn't know this
was a test excuse me oh I'll do anything
you want Teno H wait I feel like there
was another thing I want to
say there's so many things that I'm
writing down in my journal as well we
are keeping those journals there will be
a stream after our vacation when we read
out the journals I want to note real
quick too our limit is one to two pages
no no no I mean that's not really
official I was just saying that I just
want to say that is what kiata told me
so I just want to say that the limit
that I was given
was one hard liit I said you were like
how much should we write I was like oh
no one one to two
pages it's a hard limit well first she
said one page per each entry okay and
then she said I need two pages actually
we'll do two I like okay and then she
wrote like what four five maybe so I
stopped at two cuz I was like one day
one day you only had so little things to
say about the ins
am I not interesting enough I wrote five
pages about you and honestly I could
write even more about you I could have
written more too then tomorrow for or
today cuz today you have to write the
journal again oh yeah then we better do
that now before I pass out yeah after
the stream just so you guys know I think
I had this cute idea I hope you guys
think it's cute I think it's really cute
um so we're going to we bought we bought
like two little A5 journals and that
have like a even a fitting Tropical
Pattern on the cover and yeah we're
writing observations of each other in
there mhm per once per day and then in
the end we'll like review it either you
will read your own or you will read the
one that I wrote about you well if you
have to read mine good luck trying to
read my handwriting I don't know which
one is which one is funnier reading the
one that I wrote about you or reading
the one you wrote about me which one's
funnier I I don't know we should ask
them M what do you guys think cuz like I
think the way I'm writing
it it's really funny maybe I should read
it myself cuz I know what I I want I
want to hear you read it in your voice
you know if you find a stay cat there's
no cats here no cats or dogs it's all
like it's Islands there there's no cats
there's only birds and geckos and fish
and maybe maybe there's some bats out
there I I don't
know each others read each others H well
I mean I can read it and she can like
still like be like interjecting like hey
what does this mean what do you mean oh
no I'm not excited I know the kind of
you wrote down what do you what do
you think I wrote down you're going to
write down the weird thing I said
there's many there's many no I didn't
write that down but I can certainly I
can tell it on stream now no cuz I
didn't write it down I have to say it at
some
point
stop laughing at me I was waiting to
tell this please forgive narissa okay I
I will say uh oopsie oh ah oh my God I
deleted that okay I will say this
forgive her for her sins it's not a sin
I did nothing
wrong so um I picked her up from the
airport right and I get us an Uber we're
driving and
then
there's this one moment where we're like
we're on a oneway we're on a oneway road
and she's like what did you say huh okay
so we're on we're on the left side of
the road and as you know in America you
drive on the right so I didn't realize
we were down a Runway or oneway and this
was the only time I was paying attention
while we were driving because we were
stopped so I sat there and I was like oh
my God I'm on the left side of the road
I really am in in Europe and I'm like no
wait no what no I was so confused myself
cuz like okay yeah we were on a laptop
and I'm like in my defense in my defense
I thought because you know America
sometimes we are a little stupid like
when we use you know like inches and
like you know all our weird measurements
and stuff like feet you know like we
have all this weird right so I
assumed because Japan and the UK are I I
don't know why I assumed that everywhere
else was left side and that we were just
like we are we have to be interesting
you know America is so interesting so
we're going to drive on the right
instead I didn't realize that it was the
UK and Jaan extremely rare yeah I told
her I said narissa most of the world
drives on the right side and this is
actually just a oneway street and you're
like you turn around and you're like are
you sure is this really like yeah like
wait wait until we go around the corner
he will be on the right side and also
look where the driver is sitting Nissa
he's sitting maybe in the same position
as they sit in America right and I was
like oh my God you're right and the Uber
driver is probably sitting there like
this stupid
American oh my God and and I explain to
you is as from my maybe there's more
there's probably another few countries
but from my knowledge I only know of UK
and Japan well then we had the even
worse one when we were sitting on your
bed talking Australia too and New
Zealand and India okay five
places out of a million I'm sorry and I
I kind of makes sense New Zealand
Australia I see a connection there um
yeah do you want to tell them about the
currency one yes I want to tell them
about that there was another funny thing
on the same day
um how did this even happen I I I don't
we were talking about money yeah and uh
conver verion and I forgot you were like
thinking that we have Franks no yeah in
Austria I'm like no no no I think you
fought cuz I see a note here that says
uh oh no no no okay never mind okay okay
yeah I think you yeah you were thinking
it was Franks in austr like uh I no I
thought no Germany you thought it was
from Germany yeah because blank for or
so maybe I don't know I don't know I got
I got very confused cuz obviously it's
euros right pretty much everywhere in
Europe and except in the UK where I
thought that they used Franks but
they're not what do they use what do
they use what do what do they use
narissa what do they use in the UK I
taught you I taught
you I'm hiding the
chest why don't they use Euros they
pounds girl pounds I don't know pounds
pounds is
like how I don't understand there is a
whole shelter I I've never been to the
UK still you just hear about don't see
like Americans I'm sorry I feel like
even most Americans I mean no they
definitely do I just I don't know I I
think it's because Sweeney Todd tricked
me into thinking that it was an old
currency because it's like old you know
it's like I think placed in the
1700s something like that and he's like
I weage a 5 lb but you never beat me and
shav in the face so I was like oh yeah
the sealed currency they use Euros or
Franks now I don't
know but I don't even know what Franks
are is that like old French I don't even
know like why would I say that
what's wrong with but also keep in mind
I was extremely jet legged and very
tired and laying on my oshi's bed for
the first time
so I require just imagine if you were in
my
situation okay
kfp excuse
me it's so embarrassing I I know I don't
know if you can really defend these
statements you have made to me um most
of you have uses
zero uh I can't help it okay we used to
in Austria many years ago we used to use
a different currency that was called
shilling but then they switched
eventually a shilling please won't you
give me a
shilling please I just need one shilling
for some Shilling sticking out your gu
for some chilling I have a head head H
you're so Europe no you're so Austria
tax oh my God Austria Texas please stop
texting
me ah yeah those were some funny
comments um made by you are there any
funny comments that I
made bring it on no you can't think of
anything off that's because you're too
smart you're just like I've been
following her around like a puppy cuz
I'm like I'm so scared I'm in new places
please save me I almost had a really
embarrassing moment today though where I
really thought you were going to be
pissed at me why cuz we were um going
from one end of the island to the other
end of the island to get lunch on our
bicycle I felt really bad actually so I
felt bad Kata was going the right
direction but um someone passed by and I
it was cuz it was hot I wasn't even mad
at you but like like I was like I think
we definitely went the wrong way and we
were cycling for 10 minutes already
already I used such WR strong wording
and I was like oh no kiata is going to
think that I think bad no no I was
doubting myself to like after 10 minutes
of cycling we were almost there but like
I was I was also like starting to
question myself was it really there I'm
pretty sure it was there
go yeah I was like maybe we should check
just to be sure but I didn't have a map
on my phone so I couldn't check but yeah
so then but then he's like no you guys
are going the right way so then we kept
going but I was like oh no K I feel so
bad she probably thinks I I don't trust
her yeah she was she was saying maybe
maybe it was on the other side of
the I just didn't remember being so far
away yeah it was really far yeah but it
was worth it it had a nice be they're
like this is the worst honeymoon ever
excuse me we're having a very fun time
it's not even a
honeymoon honey what okay here is the
best story of the day okay the craziest
mindblowing even it's not even related
to Nissa but she was mind blown too yes
yes oh okay oh my god listen in the
airplane to the
males we were sitting we were so lucky
we were uh on one of the side RADS with
the window right yeah and it's a it's a
trip Cedar so next to us there could
have been a person but thankfully there
was no one there so we had quite a lot
of space yeah yeah and then next to us
was a row that was actually empty but
because it was a four row seat in the
middle people eventually took advantage
and I think two people sat there and
made it their space a couple moved there
but yeah know we didn't pay attention to
them until the end of the flight it was
really like after like a million hours I
was like yeah they turned on the lights
in the cabin yeah we were we were done
you know dozing and sleeping we we were
having a pretty I think we were talking
pretty loudly us
too and so I guess some people around us
may have heard our voices mhm don't
worry this is not like what you think it
is
maybe suddenly like this this road that
is like next to us with the aisle in
between that row a lady she turns over
to us while we're met in a conversation
and she's like saying something to me
and I don't hear it clearly cuz she's
like relatively far away cuz I'm on the
window I'm like what what what and she
says it again I still get it cuz she's
also talking in German by the way so
narissa wouldn't have heard it yeah I
was just like he again I'm like what
what and I go nearer and nearer and then
I I don't I don't I didn't recognize her
but she says to
me I am this person person from this is
is a woman that I have recently met a
few times for some business basically
Private Business M and she says she's
that person and I'm like even then it
took me like a moment to realize what
cuz she wasn't wearing makeup she was
always wearing makeup and she was like
dressed more fancy here she was in
pajamas no makeup hair up she looked
like kind of different and I'm like what
the say how can you on the same day
mhm fly with the same flight to the
males and be seated move to a seat that
was open right next to us and she wasn't
even originally in that seat she moved
herself voluntarily so and I'm like w
see a few days ago I met this lady and I
told her you know I'm going on a
vacation and she somehow also said she
will be unavailable in the next couple
of weeks I'm like Okay cool so I thought
I wouldn't see her like for a while and
then something I didn't tell her I'm
going to the males I just told her I'm
going on a vacation and she didn't
mention she was going to
the always see her in there and
I'm like what the I lost my mind this is
insane and I I we had some chitchat we
talked a little bit yeah yeah they're
like what a coincidence oh my God it was
so cute told me it's her like second
time like oh my God me too like oh
talking a little bit crazy I I am was it
my tax lady let's say yeah it was my tax
lady oh my God I I I and I so excitedly
told my mom who's probably watching this
right now Mommy I told you this story
which is so mind-blowing so excitedly
and she gave me no reaction she just
changed the
topic mommy how could you no
reaction what this is like the most
incredible Story of My
Life it's like it's like it's like it's
like as if I went to the got on the
plane and then randomly I don't know cie
was in it yeah like what the are
you doing
here what are you doing here but
unfortunately we're not flying back with
the same flight yeah that's
okay um dude the people I obviously I
won't say who it's not like we know them
anyway though once we actually got to
the Mal Dives we were stuck following
like the whole way the most
insufferable
people they like our bags were getting
moved to get checked in together and uh
the people checking their bags went in
front of us so we were kind of like
separated right so there were two the
guy carrying our bags and the guy
carrying the guys in back of us bags and
then he stopped he's like um excuse me
those are our bags and I was like okay
well ours are right in head he's like
okay well then you should move up to
them which I was just like dude it was
kind of like he said it were really rude
Manner and to the point where I didn't
even realize he definitely had a British
accent but I was sitting there and I was
like I think this guy may not be English
because his English was so rude that I
was giving the benefit of the doubt and
I was like you know I think this guy
maybe English isn't his first language
he sounds kind of maybe like he has a
French ey I don't know but I was it was
really really rude the inflection and
everything so we kind of awkwardly moved
up but then he went and he pulled up
anyway and then like even though we were
getting helped first he then took over
because he wanted to be helped first and
then they had to you know take pictures
and everything cuz they're like oh so
the resort knows who to look for and so
they went to do that to him and he's
like no we already took them we don't
need to take anymore you know like
really like
rudely like I was like dude you're going
on a vacation chill out kind of weird I
mean I don't I I mostly like I feel like
you uh how to
say you
you you w you experienc it like more
consciously than me I was like mostly
like just zoning out but he was he was
seeming people people don't act like
that in public where I'm from like you
yeah like obviously there's a Ken every
now and again you know where like you'll
see someone being like my Taco Bell
order is not correct and I need you to
correct it but usually especially if
you're in like a nice place like no one
really acts like that I'm sure there are
people who do but I've just never
experienced it but like
usually you you like experience carens
and like cheaper like not really that
high again I'm sure it happens but not
that I've ever seen like super duper
publicly right um so it's just weird to
be on this like fancy expensive vacation
where you assume everyone is probably
pretty well off and then you're just
seeing them being like and they were
being really rude to staff too like when
we're up in like the waiting room like
cuz we were waiting I didn't witness
that at all I did we we were waiting for
the the SE plane and it was it was quite
a bit longer than they they had
anticipated and they kept like every
time the the people would come over cuz
you know we're getting like drinks and
stuff um they'd be like oh we what is
the cause of this delay this has been
way too long it was a delay yeah and I'm
like a schedule yeah exactly and I was
like Bros why are you even yelling at
these people the the guy the staff he
told us pretty accurately right in the
beginning how long it's going to take 1
hour 30 minutes or so of waiting time
and that's pretty much how long it took
yeah but super entitled uh and I I think
we actually passed them again today when
we were on our bikes yeah right when we
turned around you you're like I don't
know you have some kind of like mental
connection with them that I don't I
don't realize that they exist when I
when I meet rude people I purposely go
out of my way to avoid them just cuz it
I just don't like it you know yeah yeah
no generally I totally agree it just
kills My
Vibe My Vibe oh know hope I hope they're
not on our flight back or anything crazy
like that I don't want to see them ever
again yeah m n rage story yes but
besides that I mean everybody we didn't
talk to any MH people here besides the
staff chilling and like laying bed
together our massage today was amazing
oh my God yeah it felt so good I gave
you a massage ear you gave me also
massage yeah yeah you were saying you
can give me massage I'm like really and
she doubted me and then she was like
you're actually pretty good she's good
she got so into it I thought she would
only massage me for like 2 minutes
because I was always cracking my neck
and she got so concerned she's like stop
I can't I'm in pain I know I get you
yeah but like you massaged me I thought
it would only take 2 minutes you
massaged me for quite some time you even
got some lotion yeah make it easier so I
didn't hurt her
skin yeah thank you so much of
course yeah but the massage was really
good we both I think almost fell asleep
yeah I'm already I'm falling asleep
right now e really I'm so tired
no no no yes no I'm sweepy sweep you
always sleepy so far always kiaha let's
go lay down it's so weird cuz I feel
like when we were in Austra it wasn't
quite like that we slept properly for
the night I didn't I was I what the the
night before we flew out I was up until
7:00 a.m. Austrian time and then you
woke me up when you got out of bed mhm
and I just got up with you so I didn't
sleep very long at all
all but I just went to bed at the same
time as you but that doesn't mean I
slept seemed to me like you slept
comfortably I I did go not your bed the
bed you gave me was comfortable though I
just couldn't sleep cuz it was like my
body was like it's
only it's only 4:00 p.m. or something
and I'm like no please let me sleep and
my body was like no yeah I want let no
it's not mean not letting her sleep
either got up because of my cat uh I
think they're I think they're making an
implication no no oh
no I just I just she slept in a
different bed yeah I have a guest bed in
a different room in a guest room she's
like ew you want to sleep in my bed
absolutely
not but now we're sleeping in the same
bed yeah cuz you decided you liked me no
it's fine I mean if I have a guest bed
I'm going to let use the guest bed we
don't have the gas we sleep in the same
bed but I wanted to sleep with your
pants as they only have double beds here
mhm there's no no twin beds in this
destination but there's more than enough
room that tiata doesn't touch me when
I'm sleeping which is very important
it's good it's
comfortable H I'm tired too though well
why don't we end it for today and write
our journals MH and then go to bed
m let me just okay let me check okay
there was
a and if there was something I want then
I no that that's going in my journal
that's going in my
journal is so cute taking NES throughout
notes throughout the day I'm a
professional streamer after three years
you know I've been doing this for a
while though but you I don't want to run
out of tangent so I have to write down
everything you're smart I should do that
okay I think I think yeah um besides the
fact that I rolled in the sand yesterday
I think I have everything covered mhm it
was so cute Watching You the sand is so
soft So Soft if only my feet didn't
hurt is it better now you had Band-Aids
on all day uh I washed it just now but
it was still burning quite other just
put another one on yeah tomorrow when we
get up um before we leave I'm going to
put new Band-Aids on very fine sand
there very fun sand I mean I did it's
like generally really clean cuz there's
like constantly people they have like a
team who constantly cleans everything
like in the paths they just get rid of
the leaves and on the beach they got get
rid of whatever stuff there is to get
rid of um but like when we got up so
early in the morning there was pollution
yeah there was pollution there was stuff
from the ocean that shouldn't be there
like I saw a I don't know gas
tank or something swept from the ocean
onto the beach I took an artistic
picture
mhm that's like it was like so nice
looking I was like why did you take such
a nice looking picture of trash excuse
me it's art it was send a
message even in the malds yeah yeah but
they get rid of all that like but it's
just in the morning you know all this
that comes from the ocean gets
swept so you guys don't thr out your gas
tanks into the ocean what the
man holy man W can make trash look
like art it's narissa you can do that
too you have the same phone I don't I
need to ask you to help me with my
camera settings because your your
pictures look so ni mine I realized that
you know this uh this wide angle is all
cool and all that but you know where the
real is at portrait mode not I know
I know free time zoom is so close but
you just got to go back free time zoom
makes all my food pictures so pretty one
time zoom cannot do that the fre time
zoom is where it's at I'm going to have
to try it yeah that's what the the food
pictures uh were made with mhm yeah I'm
a good photo photographer no it's really
not that difficult you just you know
okay be modest keep your
secrets it's not difficult just like
snorkling it's not difficult you don't
need to be so worried so concerned you
can do everything that you set your mind
into on to I don't know how to say
and I'm going just say set your mind too
yes M
yeah okay guys tomorrow let me show you
the schedule in in case you haven't seen
it guys cuz I am proud that I made a
schedule uh do schedule I think here
yeah wow wow wow
wow H today Beach Tatsu tomorrow we're
smashing on nissa's channel yeah because
she made the effort not for this purpose
why did you even do that why did you
like get all all the Smash characters
why wouldn't you why was what is the
motivation behind that why wouldn't you
but wait world of light is like the most
fun part of Smash when you have no
friends to smash with I just realized
you must have played so much you must be
really good at smash now no I
played it on the easiest mode and I
basically was just trying to unlock
everyone guys can you confirm that she's
still at smashing oh they know I
literally just button Button Mash the
same button over and over
again I have to get confirmation for
that is that true yes
yes she's only down B okay hey don't
don't tell her my no she isn't she just
uses be moves okay n is basically a
champion no okay girl came ready to
smash can confirm better than Mama yeah
probably she's bad possibly Ro after
playing easy mode what the
okay that's good that's good cuz
like otherwise you would be too good to
blame me no no I'm not I'm not too good
at all all right awesome do you have a a
tog go
character
um sa for all oh okay why why you so
like nervous about saying that I I would
I had to think about it cuz I was going
to say peach I was like I didn't really
play Peach and I was going to say Kirby
and I was like I didn't really play
Kirby but I think I played seph Ro and
and you want to say random things that
you didn't really play well because uh
I've been a peach man since I added
Peach into that's a long time ago yeah
but um I'm just I've never been good at
her I also like to play uh link a lot
too oh link is always interesting H so
then we're going to do K on n's Channel
as well that's on archived s it will be
with this shitty microphone I hope that
will work out yeah I even I I brought my
I brought two headphones I brought the
mic splitter so it's going to be fine I
think mhm I'll be having a solo member
stream I don't know what I'll be doing
maybe just chitchatting who knows but
this is probably the last member stream
it is going to be the last member stream
before my break um so I'll see you there
and satday we're just taking it easy and
uh Sunday is's another stream together
yeah together together we got to figure
out what we're doing though yeah no I
know what we're going to do but I just I
keep it a secret you look forward to the
surprise I know everything I have
everything planned out in my head n I'm
a planner I'm a planner together no Go
Wrap that lotion um
no there's no lotion that needs to be
rubbed we're going to go to bed
time thank you guys for watching hope
you enjoyed the updates and our stories
about the mold yes yeah it has only you
enjoyed our matching shirts yeah but the
sunburn there's no sunburn yeah no
sunburn yet surprisingly they're
probably will be by the end but yeah for
now we're
good already buttered up up and ready
huh no I mean we're I guess we're still
oily cuz we didn't take
a that's fine my Skin's absorbed if I
not definitely not like oily absorbed
we're not oily as you would like to
think we are
weirdos picturing us covered in
[Music]
oil yeah yeah go ahead guys think think
what you want think whatever you like
it's fine whatever helps you sleep at
night yeah okay thank you guys for
watching thank you we
say good job there is uh my almost
German sister friend wife yes wife
goodbye guys bye bye have a nice uh day
night bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye and make sure to use #t
Kia not # KP I mean you can still use #
I'm still checking it out but you
know Kissa is where it's at it's going
down
ATA I'll feed this okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
byebye