[Music]
aah
yeah the ptm is from the game
[Music]
oh
wow
[Music]
hey
here we go
[Music]
oh
go get em piano go get em
[Music]
okay here we go
can you hear me welcome
to the stream which is sponsored by
alice fiction yes
thanks hello welcome
hey i will today tell you about
a new i'm allowed to say this right it's
not condescending i mean they say it
themselves a new gacha game
rpg a puzzle rpg
for your
mobile devices or tablets or so
yeah
yeah yeah it's called alice fiction and
it comes straight out of japan
so we'll also hear some japanese voices
but also maybe some english voices yeah
uh
yeah but not only waifus i also saw
husbandos
so something for everybody's taste
um oh [\h__\h] the bjm is too loud i think
sorry but the pgm is so good yeah they
sent me like a whole folder of bgm i can
use
and this is like the nichijou all day
bgm it's so good although the the
loading bgm was really good too that was
a different one yeah
really chill i want to use them in my
normal streams
can i can i um take them home with me
please can i use the bgm in my normal
streams please
[Music]
yeah so i'll tell you uh about this game
and this background by the way is also
from the game looks so cool
yeah there's a burger burger place right
behind me here yeah
yeah it looks nice so so futuristic and
kind of like a
i have to say
cyber space world i don't know
is it kfb that's not kfp but maybe we
need to take over
uh
so before we um you know chit chat i
will go to the side uh actually no first
i will show you
i will show you um something that you
can watch on your own and then we'll
watch some more things and then we'll
play the game and so let's first i will
start here i want you guys to get in the
mood a little bit okay
i want you guys to feel
feel the hmm what's the icon in english
the world world aesthetic vibes i don't
know just just look at it and then
you'll understand
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
the song is so catchy like i heard it a
few times and like actually like i
already had it in my head after the
first time but the the chorus is so i
can't hear the toy
it's so catchy like you immediately
remember the song oh my god i really
like it it's so so good
yeah that was kind of you know um
something that gives you an overview of
you know some characters and that was
the theme song that if i understand
correctly gouda is going to sing or
cover
so
now now i kind of i kind of thought you
know you might enjoy it more if you
watch this on your own but you did
definitely uh
hear me humming in the background that
was on purpose
yeah
yes so
uh now
i have some more for you to show for me
to show it to you
and next i am going to show you
um
i think this one
watch this
[Music]
who's logging in for the first time let
me introduce
[Music]
you have to get as many as possible and
then you get a special attack unleash
[Music]
we have to save the pretty girls
and yeah japanese voice acting
oh there's different game modes
and fight against the battle
no i know i know it's like maybe that
sounds good not the way i want to say it
but it looks so like typical anime that
you would see on the tv
created by a group of famous creators
would you also like to live in alice
fiction
i'm translating here live translation
yeah the art style is like very very
very typical
what
some some mysterious ending yeah uh live
translation from takana
yeah yeah yeah there is actually like
this was just partially english but in
the actual game of course everything is
properly english it's even available in
german if you wanna i actually first
downloaded it accidentally in german so
yeah available in many many languages
check it out at least you know not voice
acting in german but like the game
system language yeah okay and then
before we go into the game i have a
bit more to show do you guys want to
look at some characters yeah then we can
already make up our mind who do we want
to get for
the gotcha
[Music]
i don't know what that weapon is
she's cute though
[Music]
is
excuse me and glasses
alice fiction these are just some of the
characters
um
so many girls but also some boys i only
saw one for them but my eyes immediately
go to the girls hello
like a scene straight out of an anime
okay okay okay okay
so that was that
uh
now i think i showed you three videos
right
was that three videos
i think it was free videos yeah yeah
okay then i'm done with the videos
okay
so one more thing before i go into the
game i i feel like you know i have i'm
like doing a powerpoint presentation is
fun okay here's some info bam
okay
if you
join alice fiction now wait let me turn
on the bgm
i'm a sales woman okay listen to me this
stream is sponsored but this is the good
stuff listen up listen up everybody oh
sh okay bgm should be back on it's kind
of starts kind of quiet
okay
so so
between the 26th of july which is like
two days ago so it already started oh my
god fomo volvo
alert alert alert fomo fear of missing
out no
you cannot let it win over you
or maybe you can you should i guess
because yeah you should fear of missing
out
oh jokes on you i pre-registered oh yeah
there's a link in my description
um
that is kind of like a tracking link so
if you click that link then they will
know that you found the game for me
so please do that um
okay so 26 until the 16th of august is
the duration if you log in for 10 days
during that
time period then you will receive up to
3 000 quarts and now we don't know like
we don't have a feeling yet for how much
that is
but it's probably a lot um
and we have
daily free gata of course of course of
course generous generous gacha yeah if
you you can draw once for free every day
between the 26th until the 9th of august
so this has also
wait
the dates here don't align in the bottom
oh wait that's maybe a different one
no that should be the same i think the
dates are
kind of um
wrong here one says ninth one says
second i'm not sure which one it is it
probably says it also when you download
the game
but
what was i going to say yeah this also
already has started so fomo alert and we
have this daily free gotcha see this one
aha
this is a world memory gotcha it's not
the same as the other one this one gives
you something called world memories
maybe we'll find out what that is and
yeah once free every day between 26th
and 9th of august
the dates confused me but there you go
then we have a release guaranteed
catcher
so this is another different one where
you are guaranteed to get a free star
or a freestyle character or a five-star
world memory
this is from the 26th until the 16th
of august now this one actually makes
sense okay
gotcha may only be drawn with paid and
or bonus quartz okay
yeah and oh then we have a release
commemoration training bonus oh yeah if
you go into the game now you will get
double ooh baby a double
exp basically yeah no drop amount of
battle rewards and other rewards yeah
esp oh my god above
thank you thank you the grind begins
sounds good to me so they give you a
good starter boost
yeah i think that's it for that slide
okay
okay then uh
oh i guess this did not say that i'm not
sure but
uh the
pre-registrations reached over one
million
i know what
so that means that they're giving out
twelve thousand quarts
four
forty gacha draws
is what my my note says
twelve thousand that sounds like a lot
yeah so we have the daily free kata to
release guaranteed gaja and the training
bonus www
now we can play the game
yeah
finally
my hands are sweaty spaghetti but
the game doesn't mind
for sure i think this is okay to show
now
oh my gosh double i know i know
holy [\h__\h] okay
we're jumping right into the game
a trailer so i literally started off
from like after you first entered the
game
[Applause]
oh something's going on it's like we're
hacking or whipping heck there's a virus
or something
optimization failed seems to be a
hostile virus freezing you can't
no hey i'm here for sponsorship don't
freeze my account i'm here on official
turns
protect that
[Laughter]
should i read it out loud
who's this pretty girl oh hello
activating garden mode i'm your garden
now
sorry i like him
[Music]
take back your for yourself your my what
my what
she's pretty yeah
oh no [\h__\h] not a blue screen no
my nightmare
uh blue screen is really really really a
bad sign i haven't had one in a long
long time thankfully this messed up
program has been normalized oh really
what does this mean
welcome to the mental verse of alice
thank you so kind i forgot everything
that just happened is only happy nothing
weird going on oh it's the same world
world ception
welcome to the metaverse of alice
it's a nice voice acting so i'm not sure
every single time it's the same boring
old greeting all logic and no
personality
when it comes to counseling and caring
for people so why are their greetings
always so cold
they have no no heart no soul
yeah there's a translation but i know
some of you guys are too lazy to read
well now you look a little stunned yeah
i'm talking to you me me stunned
i'm i'm i'm less stunned than you are
look at yourself you're not you're only
blinking i'm moving
[Music]
yeah uh you know no no no it's a trick
question i i know
i know your name uh
but
um
testing if you know your name myself
it's so embarrassing when you don't
remember someone who obviously remembers
you and
judges you for not remembering them i'm
sorry i have a birth brain i'm a phoenix
would you mind handing it to me with
that thing
was a thing some fried chicken from kfp
you hungry
i'm not i'm not confused
hang on a second why do you look so
confused
yeah yeah yeah he's uh he's a scientist
or something like that
he looks familiar
chronograph
don't tell me i didn't tell you anything
about the chronograph music
my brain is empty well please explain i
am empty soulless i'm a robot
of all the things we've really got a
problem now
today is my first time logging in
i'll head back for today sorry for all
the confusion i'll be seeing you again
soon i'm sure
cool i want to do
oh that reminds me i know you said that
was your first login
but just so you know you've been here
before
here
really maybe i'm one of the characters
in the gacha i don't even know about it
why'd you not tell me about this fiction
dainty girl
hello
who was that was your princess
am i your sister
good silver white hair always winning
[Music]
really we don't look alike at all
your avatar's memories were erased
hire me for voice acting please alice
pictured
you look confused
let me help
guys close your eyes
and just don't look at the orange girl
on the screen just look at her and don't
you think that you know that that
totally fits
your body in this virtual world is
called an
avatar whoa
whoa
did the white girl just speak the
white-haired girl to speak english what
actually so the the battle
has english voices but the story doesn't
have english voices so
[Music]
i'm just saying i'm i'm free
i'm waiting for her to stop talking so
that i can i don't overlap with her
it stores your personal data it holds
information about your body and memories
in the real world
alice gets rid of any viruses you pick
up and optimizes everything
but sometimes your data can get lost and
your avatar will temporarily revert to
its initial settings i think that's what
happened to me
i love the ellis references like in the
logo you see in the background there's
the the the grinny cat on the moon and
all that yeah yeah yeah so there's a
queen
ooh i wonder how many like references
there will be
to alice wonderland
what was that creepy smile just now
the girl the guy early also mentioned
something
do you remember what happened when you
walked in
if it was the first time you'd have seen
this
thank you for logging into the metaverse
of alice alice is an other live service
that provides each user with a
personalized advertisement this avatar
is created with registered data and can
assist the lifestyle improvements in the
real world this is a space for both
business and pleasure
where unique experiences await you to
find them
we hope you enjoy your life beyond
[Laughter]
[Music]
this isn't your first login until your
data has been restored
no need to [\h__\h]
what
look
like this he's such a flake
hey stop right there
[Music]
well she's your sister too
why is everybody your sister i'm
starting to think that we're not really
related
by blood
wait wait why did people still here
hey you too hurry up and get out of here
me but i'm a part-time warrior i think
this will be no problem for me
oh she was asking me oh okay i thought
she was you know
she's calling everybody says okay
she's protecting me
she jumped in front of oh
how sweet
maybe we are blood related
um god
kelly am i too late
look out his face what do you mean log
out his fail
does it kill her
it ate and
it ate my little sister
you for real sauce that's not cool
you can't show her show
confirming connector acts as secret mode
unlocked secret mode
can we fight now
oh my god what is that
wow
[Music]
prioritizing master protection commands
that's good that's good right
that's the chronograph that's the thing
that they were asking for
oh
what
oh is that me
i guess i dyed my hair to brown
it's crowning time
no way a folklore
but i guess it's like the the clock from
alice in wonderland that
from the bunny but i don't know is that
a reference too i wonder
don't tell me she just summoned a
folklore from outside of alice
whatever's happening it's awesome now we
can fight back
hell yeah
now let's fight yeah yeah yeah
she's a summon uh-huh
[Music]
okay
we will fight now
this is the battle system i already you
know played a little bit yesterday just
to test the game if it's working i know
a lot is happening at all at all at once
and you're probably pretty confused but
for now let's work together and focus on
this guy i'm going to explain how
battles work so listen closely first up
is how to attack
try tapping a panel adjust scent panels
of the same color can be broken together
yeah for example the blue one
good no problem with breaking panels
just like that try breaking other panels
yeah the red ones and these ones and
we can get rid of this one and then get
the yellow one time is up okay
see it's really simple
but there's some things that you can
activate
that's the basics for attacking for
newbie you catch on fast hey
all right let's try connecting and
breaking three or more patents if you do
something good will happen also guys
you're welcome to play along the game is
already released so
play along and learn the game with me
shall we
ah there are different color panels in
the way um can you break those first
easy
get this one get this one now get the
green one yeah
and then
now we have a skill that we can use
if you break a skill panel it will
activate a crash scale let's break it
cool crusher
she's cute the blue haired girl
and now you hear this english voices in
the background
[Music]
ponytail girl
success
crash skills are strong attacks i hope
it won't take long until using them
feels like nature already it's pretty
easy to get used to it
when the signs done it's the opponent's
turn
oh
for two turns oh it boosted its attack
it's not attacking oh it is attacking
that's a lot of damage aoe damage
eventually
i took a bit of a hit there you okay
allies whose hp falls to zero will
retreat so be careful
yeah in any case why don't we try using
a skill panel again do you remember what
i told you before brake panels are in
the way first uh yeah sure sure you get
the triple oh baby and then we get this
one we can get this one in here you can
do it right ah hell yeah okay okay okay
so we can even we don't have to activate
the skill alone we can get all these
together
oh wait a sec look over here
see this skill panel is leveled up oh it
says level 2 skill yeah
if you break this it'll make for a real
powerful crash spill go ahead and break
it
yeah
breaking it
there
nice ax oh i like how the weapon is cool
[Applause]
[Music]
holy
two of us are almost dead
this enemy is strong
now now it's not but he only has 10 hp
left so we're fine now's not the time to
be holding anything back use my active
skill excuse me
okay you're uh competitive in the
inhibit inhibition conceal convert up to
one
own panels into own level one skill
patterns four turns
two turns boost physical attack of one
self and hide physical attack allies by
one okay that sounds confusing but let's
just do it
new skill
oh she got the gun
cute okay we're buffed now
but we didn't do any damage
what do you think it made a skill panel
for you now make that skill panel level
two
okay
there you go using active skills like
that can turn the battle in your favor
ah that's right i forgot there's one
thing you gotta watch out for there's a
time limit to the panel yeah yeah yeah
the color behind the panels tells you
how much time is left yeah guys look if
you look behind the
[Music]
if you look behind
the
jewels thingies now you will see that
yeah it turns red
once the time limit for panel breaking
faces up your party will start their
attacks try to make and break as many
skills panel
skills panels as possible within the
time limit yeah so
yeah yeah okay let's do it
yeah let's do it this one
this one this one this one this one this
one this one
too far apart too many different colored
ones in between
oh
you're
thanks
seriously it's just the same reaction
girl
give me a break magic
i'm just about to drop over here
drop over here hey do you think
you can summon that vocal yeah i think
so
i think we can do it again again uh-huh
oh now we ran away
it's scared
but if i remember wait can we give her a
name already she's still called strong
girl
but if i remember correctly momochi and
the others are over there so there's no
need to chase after it
we're safe for now
uh
what happened to mina to my sister
though
i get it you're worried about that girl
but you need to calm down
that thing is heading towards my friends
and even if we went after to help them
we'd just get in the way
but
she's telling me to calm down but in my
eyes my little sister just died in front
of me
how can i calm down
not calm panic panic
we're both so exhausted we wouldn't be
of much use no i'm fine i'm fine
anyway i know i said we're safe but if
we stick around we'll find ourselves in
other kinds of dangers
we should get moving i'm sure you're
bursting with questions so follow me if
you want some answers
not to mention i have a couple questions
of my own okay you'll have to tell me
about yourself and what's up with that
watch
well i know nothing
i know absolutely nothing yeah that
emote
chicken on fiery mouth is probably the
best way to describe it
[Music]
i think we can skip it because we're
already watching it even though the song
is fire
[Music]
welcome to the main screen welcome to
alice or should i say welcome back
i'll explain a little more along the way
so listen up first we need to increase
our party power
[Music]
so that watch of yours lets you summon
folklore with quartz
we can try other methods later let's use
this one for now
no way looks like you don't need cords
to try this time
not only that you can retry as many
times as you'd like
don't need to delete the game and
install again to get your favorite
character in the first try
what
seems like this time special so let's
give it a shot
okay tutorial gotcha this nah
use quartz to make 10 galaxy rose okay
let's do it
so many messages
it's my my discord like every day
top screen
[Music]
what did i get what did i get what do i
get
two golden ones and one rainbow one
i understand
[Music]
cute she has a huge book looks cool i
like her style too with the big big big
scarf and the oversized parker in the
high-waisted skirt love it love it love
it cute
next though
oh dear
shoes
where's jack the ripper
originally from would you have a fairy
tale or something
i guess like it's a fairy tale
except heard it from the literature ah
books
london england that didn't mean it like
that
wait it was a real person
oh anyway uh so she's cute
she has oh some big ass weapons i like
her style but judging by her eye bags
she needs a little bit more
she has sleep big
uh weapons
yes a big weapon
ah she was fighting with us already so
it seems like when you get a double you
get these kind of medals okay
cute i like her ponytail girl cute
oh we got her too binky one more time
oh so this is our first second star oh
19 years cute
[Music]
um a big a big coat a big coat
some fancy pants
yeah cool okay
one star i don't know
gregor
it will be really interesting to like
look up
what all these characters reference to
i mean
you know cleopatra is obvious but who's
that
she's good at math oh
oh
but i'm not i don't know if we'll get
along well
i like
her reminds me of someone
oh
i actually i feel like i could wear
something like this to myself yeah i
love the the pattern of the scarf and
then you know that that
neck
what's turtleneck trouble next sweater
um high-waisted paint yes yes yes yes it
was a great magician
here's our finger
someone cool
[Music]
cool
okay very cool oh oh you like her
oh people actually know her what the
[\h__\h] you guys played the game
[Laughter]
why you oh
let's go
you guys are excited so i guess i should
be excited too let's go
did you find a good character if you
aren't happy with who you found you can
ah i want it but i think we can do a
couple more normal gachas as well so
we'll just keep this one
and then um
we can do different gachas later on i
think we're still receiving uh
some of those crystal thingies looks
like you found a good character now
let's add them to the party so they can
join the battles with us
okay
her hair is really cool
and i like her stance it's a really
confident pose okay so here here we go
to our party
this is the party menu here you can
build your party to take with you
uh into the battle select the character
to go in this slot oh you're kicking her
out
sad
okay then we can add her the folklore
you just summoned okay so they ah they
call the characters folklore
ah
[Music]
won't be able to help unless you include
them in your party
you can check your party's total battle
power right here but party power is a
value that shows how strong your party
is okay currently is seventh is about
seven thousand six hundred
[Music]
while you're still unsure about a lot of
things just try getting your party power
as high as you can okay and that's
helpful actually that's like a good guy
like when you don't know yet
which characters are good just look at
the numbers
what do the numbers mean mason it means
you know the higher the better the
higher the stronger
anyway now we don't have to worry uh if
we went into pawns again all right let's
get a move on okay we're doing another
battle
and then we probably can go back to
gacha a little bit
quests okay
so here's like
the storyline that they want to go
through
chapter one
okay i think
what did it say
[Music]
i definitely should do this okay
attempt
uh-huh
should be easy how much
eat cooks up
[Music]
the fight is on
while we're at it i'll give you some
tips to get the upper hand in battle
first let me tell you about elements
all allies and enemies have elements
that each have a counterpart to break it
down
wood is weak to fire
earth to wood
water to earth
water is weaker
and fire to water
light and dark steel equal damage okay
okay okay okay okay
i think today i might not need to worry
too much about that right
if you want to check these during that
look up here aha
ah there's a little cheat sheet on the
top left
okay
as they say seeing is believing attack
that earth type enemy i'll have to i
i'll have the advantage because i'm a
woodturner
okay if you want to target a specific
enemy tap directly on an enemy before
you start breaking panels
okay or we can just not do that but we
can also do that
now the target attacks and crash skills
will focus on hitting a targeted enemy
first however you have to consider when
it's best to target because enemy
related active skills will also focus on
them
[Music]
okay i think i got at least like i don't
know two combos
[Music]
i think they're going down yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
wants to die next here we are again so
that's basically it for battles but
there's one last thing i should mention
there's a set number of turns to a
battle you've got to defeat the enemies
before this turns left reaches zero
ah
seven turns okay that's easy
you lose if you're careless so keep an
eye on it
okay
um
[Music]
the puzzle the puzzle system i
very strong too fast 300 damage even
more than in the first round okay
maximum energy increased and fully
recovered noise thank you
i'm getting some level ups and bonds in
his bonds too
so i guess there's some maybe some
stories
one-on-one stories
yeah it keeps you involved in the combat
yeah
yeah yeah you gotta pay attention
by clearing main class it looks like
you've unlocked missions let's go check
them out
okay
receive oh okay so here we can get a lot
of stuff this is where you can accept
missions
if you clear them you can get rewards
you've already got something go ahead
and take it it's yours
you can receive rewards all at once try
the button on the bottom right that says
receive all
oh
50 50 50 50 100.
okay okay okay
what are missions there are three
different types of missions the usual
normal missions daily missions you can
take on each day and newbie missions
that are helpful when you're new oh
you can receive ports and other items by
clearing the missions
that's about all i can tell you for now
keep progressing for requests and
complete missions
okay raja
do i get something uh ah do you want me
to go back i want to check the missions
but okay oh we get some more stuff
some keys
can we like
what can we do with that i wonder
and then
a thousand quarts
okay
and
another thousand quarts here are the
promised three thousand i guess
oh what is this
newbie premium logging pass log in for
seven days to get a total of four
thousand two hundred sixty quarts oh wow
wow
login past 1027 days
[Music]
yeah okay so these are some campaigns
that might be helpful if you want to get
deep into it
oh emergency oh yeah see they apologize
for some kind of problem and give you
more money nice
also i think i think if you scroll down
here
there's me and kuda
here we're doing this right now
takanashikiya and the whole live ian
this is happening right now oh my god
they're talking about me
and yeah here since it's written here i
guess
i'll let you guys know got good as
english version of unreality escape
which is the the song that you heard
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah but she's doing an english version
that incorporation with fantastic youth
will be performed for the first time in
a live broadcast enjoy this cup song by
goguna time
okay
oh wait we have now
wait shouldn't we have more
let me have more
points
[Music]
we can do a free gacha so let's do it
uh
um
daily free gotcha
draw one for free
use course to make one gadget drop
i thought it was free we're doing it
free right yeah i think so
present box okay
but this one is free i think
get my 12k okay okay okay
captain drake who is captain
who is captain drake like i want to look
up every character like what their
background is
ah wait okay that was just one okay i'll
give you
again now let's go back there's a gift
just is it just uh she got something
i don't know who that is why do you guys
know what it is
gift box i'm here
oh 1000
[Music]
feels good so we're gonna do more of
that now
[Music]
a private year
okay so
more gotcha then um they told me to do
more gotcha so i will do more gacha
gladly
uh which one should we do
though release freeze
should we
take only
this one is
was this one
only
[Music]
yeah yeah this one has to be paid gotcha
we can do the no no i wanna do ah world
memories we can do featured gotcha this
one okay oh
right up green up is musashi who we
already have
we'll get something good anyway
eh
goddammit what about this one by the way
okay uh
what is this one p-shirt world memory
uh-huh royal gotcha
at least one two okay
should we do the rare gotcha or the
featured gotcha guess we'll do the
features gotcha
again we can get the dude i guess is he
the only dude in the game
okay well we have a lot of gotcha so
that's a currency and then let's do it
ah
go go go go
i don't need the raiders i don't need it
give me something else please
okay we only got golden ones anyway
[Music]
oh i love that that's cool
actually someone i know from history
cool
she's cute
[Music]
i love her style not really not not
really like the real marie antoinette uh
the real marie antoinette was more
elegant but okay
i was seeing her before andrew middle
we've seen her before
i saw you already in my team
thank you
oh see the blue ones that's the second
one that already turned into a golden
one
what's what's shiny soul
supposed to be
cute
she's like that
ah
what do they call it again
so yankee
oh
surprised i don't have a bow i guess but
um
that's a cool weapon too
cute
i don't know
first name is tia you can call me one so
you basically have three names
very confusing
looks like attack because of the the
shield perseus
what's perseus
where's percio's from
she's op she's nice oh nice and she
looks good
wait for ah cool
i like greek mythology
why do you all know that what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
that's so cool
shall we try again because i want a free
star
does this already mean that i'm only
getting golden ones i guess so
damn it
what
oh
three golden ones though
maybe some blue ones will turn into
morgan okay hello first year
[Music]
oh
white hair once again i love white hair
um
antonio
what mozart's rival
what couldn't have been a big rival
though because i never heard of them and
mozart was my best friend back in the
day so
ah no challenge from mozart
oh antonio sonia is it oh wait is that
italian
what's that's rival what
i've never heard of that dude
i love that
oh man okay
okay okay i understood ryokai this
[Music]
this is so fun like i can learn so much
about real people that existed or maybe
not real people maybe wait is it all
real people
because jack the ripper was real
but great mythology those weren't
necessarily real
but it's like i mean things that people
know about
robin hood was robin hood real
guillen
[Music]
yeah okay i'll put so greek my fault
roman general
oh
it's so interesting what i'm i'm like
legit fascinated
mickey absolutely
[Music]
he's sculpting sculpting sculpt
sculpting that's so cool holy [\h__\h] he
looks like so special
wow
i know him i know him
i know him
wow wow more more i want to see what
else they have
i'm going to try again
they're using them so much wait is there
something cheaper
draw ten for three thousand
ten we haven't done this one yet
should we try this one at least once get
characters where i gotcha
10 draws guarantees at least one two
star
two star what
what about this one
[Music]
at least one two star
um i don't know so it's basically the
same as in terms of
how much
yeah
how much uh i can get
uh
i'll try it at once maybe we're lucky
please let me be lucky
please
[Music]
where's my stream i look come on
come on
where's my streamer look what's this
hi
um
i need to show off some cool freestyle
characters okay okay we all have these
already
we got all those okay
hey
at least in german we call the the back
of the you know your foot there we call
it the achilles cena what do you call it
oh i feel it's healed in english
[Music]
because of some dude i guess he cut that
part or so
in greece yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah cool
cool cool
i'm so fascinated holy [\h__\h] more
no i'm running out of it
and then i need like 500 more to do
another one
should i do the other one one more time
[Music]
hello
i'll do this one one more time maybe
do one more and then earn some
rare featured
the rare again
is this no this is featured or anything
and then i'm doing rare again okay let's
go rare again
oh come on come on come
on again
i turned into a golden one again
michelangelo
nice to see you again
[Music]
cp or cpo
this cutie patootie and this beautiful
beauty and this cutie rooney and this
cutie patootie
okay we cannot try anymore
i want some more
how do i quickly get more
i guess we'll just do another battle
we'll probably get something right
chapter one
story
with voices
okay
then at least i can show you some more
stories
we'll play a little bit longer because
i'm having fun and i want a free start
[Music]
him again
yeah yeah she's okay what about middle
hello
stop hugging her don't touch her
[Music]
he's in charge of this institute and
finally we know his name
oh it is i just read in the chat
probably her dad oh
it is her dad
[Music]
papa
yeah yeah noi is new in german yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
poor girl got adopted by this dude why
why did you not is there even a mom
is there even a mom
where is the mom
i want to meet the mom
so
but i'd like to hear more details from
you let's head over here so you can tell
me about it
yeah yeah yeah yeah
you're saying you don't know what that
girl was
i mean she said she was your sister
you'll remember me not when your memory
has been restored now where is this
pocket towards your viewers
[Music]
and dancer there it is don't steal it
please it's really cool
[Music]
yeah it looks pretty cool i know i know
it looks like something crony or ame
would be carrying
you're talking
in all likelihood her memories were
deleted by the queen the queen the queen
i want to be the queen wait is it the
mom is the mom the queen
is it all just the whole thing to play
with their daughter to keep her
entertained
i heard that
if one were to unknowingly view or
download the virus a lot of data can be
deleted if the infection is great
you should send a support call to the
queen for her
already done once everything's been
confirmed i'm sure the queen will
restore her memory from a background
i suppose we should explain the queen to
while we're at it let's see there we go
queen controls manages and runs alice
kind of like the boss
is on the top of her mind right now
you're probably wondering what happened
to her after the pawn ate her and
whether or not she can be saved
i'm curious too but i've only heard
rumors
you must be pretty
the real world that's fine so there's
nothing to worry about but how how are
they in this world by the way do they
put on like vr goggles or what
so
as for that monster the thing we've been
calling upon it was randomly born from a
combination of programs and data
discarded by the queen and users of
values
you probably wouldn't be too far off if
you thought of it as a sort of chimera
or frankenstein's monster
it's like a composite computer bug
that makes sense yeah yeah i can see
that
there's pawn forms in the waist area a
realm that's also called deep space
spice
this realm is similar to the recycle bin
on new computers
transferring vast amounts of data in and
out of the waste area takes a special
door access grant by the queen which
leads to specialized businesses or
research organizations
gets out that means it had to have
changed upon one of these special
two-way
[Music]
time there's been a lot more important
sightings
in general area recently
could there be a door we don't know
about
it in any case we all all we can do for
now is wait to hear back from support
about tk's memory
about to stay here until your memory has
been restored all right i guess i'm
stuck okay
with some cute girls
did the lights in his eyes suddenly
disappear that's creeping me out it's
scary
all you have to do is pop into the waist
area and sweep up some pawns for me
using the chronograph of course
i'm getting you involved in something
shady don't worry everyone's above bored
and approved
that's right
and while we're out fighting we can pick
up anything that looks useful you can
even get some pretty cool items for
folklore sometimes
just don't overdo it in case something
does happen there i'll contact those in
the waste area now and make sure they're
on standby
no need to look so worried i can handle
any kind of area i would have been
offering
things covered
she makes me feel safe
yes mommy sorry mommy
all right i'm going to open the gate to
the waistband
this here is the gate we use to enter
the waste area it's the only one the
queen has authorized for the institute
so make sure that when you're heading in
there are usually only weak ones around
gates but just in case okay let's get
going shall we let's go
[Applause]
hacking into the gate
oh not found
it
[Music]
that's not something you want to see
ah but i got 15 quarts that's not quite
enough
but maybe from the battle we get more
yeah let's go
uh wait no i don't want to i want to
change the group uh it's forcing me to
play with the same group okay
[Music]
tired of the back to back fighting yet
you know there's actually a convenient
alt oh there is an auto mode oh
no
this button here lets you increase your
speed in battle only movement speed is
doubled or tripled
so even though it's faster it doesn't
shorten the time you have for breaking
panels so don't worry aha okay oh let's
do that then
okay trying
this is my chest
three
i don't know i don't know that one
should
[Music]
okay
okay in the beginning apparently you can
like think about it it doesn't start it
immediately that's cool
three
two
one [\h__\h]
it's all right
try to break free i know i know i know
yummy
okay okay uh three panels doesn't it hmm
you can try the blue ones for so maybe i
don't know
i'm gonna try
this is my chance
three
two i did it
i did it
[Music]
okay strong
play a wreck
okay we got 50 courts but maybe maybe we
get some rewards
[Music]
resource questions unlocked let's go
check them out now
okay i guess we're doing that
oh no
oh no return to the title screen
by the way i'm i'm playing uh with uh
uh a special testing version
so maybe that's why that happened
maybe it's not the version from the
store
shouldn't happen to you guys
[Laughter]
yeah it's like a beta version or
something like that
from the developers
hello yeah thank you
thanks
now it's not forcing me to do the thing
give me more presents
[Music]
yo what is this
oh yeah this is like uh received items
up okay okay well she got something
stupid
[Music]
yeah okay i know about that
release login book i know about that
okay yeah yeah
release yeah okay i know about all that
i guess
[Music]
party switching time
so disney
party
so we could no she's two stars she's a
or she no she's not twister she's level
two we can switch her out remove
and then add
a
a two star oh they're at the top oh yeah
it is
i wanna add her
and
wanna add
michelangelo
i'm gonna add
so much to choose from she's cute
she's cute
eight thousand four hundred right now we
have two fire though that's maybe not
the best choice huh okay we had her in
the party for a while so how about we
add instead
this girl she does deep up but she's
also the green one
how about
her we're now lower than before but at
least we have several different elements
two fire is fine i guess it's fine yeah
but you know
what i have some variation
how about this though seven thousand
nine hundred
how about this eight thousand two
hundred okay let's go with this
let's go with this
by the way what are world memories no
correspondence
oh
we cannot even learn about this yet
maybe i should have done gotcha for
world memory
here we can look at the characters
there you go antoinette cleopatra
and we can enhance them later on
okay we're not far enough to use the
other thing is here but we'll we'll get
there
another time
okay i'm gonna do
the thing is we would have to go for
some more story right
[Music]
although the next one is
wait did it not say is this someone
[Music]
ever a town
did we do that one
a tutorial is not over yeah yeah wait
i'm welcome to two channel reviews yeah
okay
we have to do this one again
okay no problem we have a different team
now so i want to see i want to see what
they do
[Music]
wow
how much
[Music]
i like the animation there oh what does
michelangelo do he sprays
sculpture with him
4 600 damage
for 60 no scope where are the injuries
[Music]
oh
not bad not so bad oh i see it i see a
quadruple
holy [\h__\h] never had that before
[\h__\h] okay now messing up
but we have a quadruple
[Music]
what's your name again
oh yeah we gotta oh no they're gonna
buff they're gonna buff
okay how are you still alive excuse me
we have to do something about that um
opportunity not
oh [\h__\h]
oh
they're ganging up on him even though he
has barely any hp left
[Music]
don't you want to be whipped by her huh
what's your whip what's your name
absolutely cool
wait at least this one we got to see
some more
characters in action not bad
nice
nice so
i like the items they also are alice
references like the teacups and the
cards
uh
what like i get i guess what
okay
resource quest just unlock yeah okay
yeah let's go check them out hopefully
it doesn't crash again
okay
oh there we go i unlocked the resource
quests
resource quests give you credits and
battle records that are handy when
you're leveling up your characters
first off let's try the xp quest level
one okay we can do this and then i think
we're gonna end it for today
it was only supposed to be an hour but
we're going a bit longer
attempt
so yeah we can get some resources from
that if you want to level up a character
make them stronger make them buff
[Music]
like the stage
i'm gonna aim for the green
and then we'll see
oh
oh oh yeah baby oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh i don't know i don't know
[Music]
also like the bgm with the violin in the
background
don't bleed
what giant flashing button
i already got the gift is there more is
there more for me to get i'll take a
look
sometimes you know the most obvious
things
are just you know
in a screen where so much is going on
even the most obvious things you just
you just can't see them
[Music]
how exciting
we have
nice nice nice
[Music]
yeah especially if you see the screen
like for the first time you know you're
not used to it yet
[Music]
you're already inspected anyway
i don't think we ever had that much
damage before
[Music]
okay
pro gamer jaw
yeah yeah okay
credit question hp quest can only be
attempted three times per day so don't
miss a day taking on these quests
hey the battle record let's go ahead and
use it to enhance the character oh okay
teach me teach me
here
character
you're forcing me to enhance you
what if i don't wanna
you can level up your characters by
using battle records however your
character's level is limited by your
player level oh sorry well let's try
actually using a battle record shall we
use this
and press the enhance button this will
raise your character's
level okay i'm giving it to you this
time but don't get used to it
enhancement complete okay
nice why don't i explain about expansion
too
okay
let's see now we can look at this you
can upgrade your character stats with
expansion items let's try expanding some
[Music]
i almost forgot you need credits in
order to expand the institute will pay
for this one so don't worry it's our
treat
i'm getting sponsored by the institute
this time we'll expand hp oh oh you're
forcing my hand again okay
it's the following items for expansion
yes yes
well hp is always good go for a little
stamina
yeah yeah yeah
player rank equals your character's max
level by increasing your player rank the
max level of your characters also
increases you can officially level up
characters by using battle records
another way to level characters is by
gaining experience for completing quests
expansion items can be collected
primarily through completing main quests
if you don't have enough items you can
read your main quests you've already
cleared
[Music]
some expansion slots are affected by the
character's max level after you play a
rank increases level of characters first
before expanding them this way your
party will get even stronger
see how you improve let's continue
onwards
are you letting me do my thing again
uh so where is that is it this one
is flashing no wait what's flashing what
what do you mean it's flashing
i don't see something specifically
really big
center bottom
this but that's just
oh i can still receive something there
that that's that's just because i'm
meeting
because i cleared some quests yeah yeah
yeah yeah
that's literally
only available now because i just did
that
receive
[Music]
some energy
ah this is just the newbie missions
okay okay that should be enough to do at
least one more gacha
oh yeah yeah yeah and if we complete all
missions we just we just need one more
then we get another three thousand we
need to draw normal gacha
okay
and that was free
[Music]
wait did i get it
and i get it did i get it
[Music]
did i get it
three hundred again nice
okay okay okay
let's do this one
let's go
maybe we got the boy the pretty boy
no no
rainbow
[Music]
but gold can probably also turn into a
rainbow
right like
wouldn't that
i think that would be nice because blue
can turn into gold and why can it not be
you know gold's turning into crazy
captain drake
[Music]
okay she's new that's nice
the maiden of the lake who is she who is
she she looks like senpai
yummy mama
maybe in my love
is rival that's cool that's fun
but who's vivian
yo his sword is all covered up like is
she giving it to someone as a present
r for a legend king arthur
[Music]
oh i don't remember that
now the whole door
it's like casual casual yummy mama
sorry mommy
okay at least we got some new characters
there i like them okay
now um i'm gonna go back to this one
what do you think guys rare or should we
do a world memory because
wait i can't because i guess
ah we have to clear something first
i don't don't
i see
uh-huh
let's go for blue haired girl add that
one in the on the top row okay okay okay
let's see if we're lucky
i want to be lucky
i'm gonna morph and move and mag and
everything together
[Music]
are you for real come on come on come on
come on come on
wayland who is wayland anyway
uh-huh
wait no i guess it's not i guess some
somebody the ship was named after
somebody okay
right i suppose
where he's a dude
a dude
oh
why are you
i'm not german
i'm not german i'm austrian
no idea about this dude
[Music]
shut up you little [\h__\h] i'm gonna put
you into the usual room
[Laughter]
whatever whatever whatever you do
whatever
[Laughter]
[Music]
a lot of gotcha
well thank you everybody um i think i
have um let me let me see
let me see
[Music]
yeah i think uh my my job here is done
basically
let me just
i shall
oh
okay
it was fun but stream of luck was not
there
please use the link in the description
or in the tweet uh if you want to get
the game because then people will know
that you got it because of you watched
my stream
and downloaded
yeah
i could do single poles oh well it's all
right it's already
already playing it nice
nice nice i wonder what other characters
are hidden in the game
what lore there is and all that and
where if i'm ever gonna find my sister
again you maybe you guys can help me
find out
and uh uh yeah uh check alice fiction
twitter for most up-to-date news on the
event dates because there were some uh
dates wrong on the slides sorry about
that
uh
ayah wait there's one more thing that i
should show though
[Music]
release commemoration promotion
hi
a social media play for a post campaign
this should be okay a social media play
through post campaign will be held
worldwide how to participate hashtag
ellis fiction challenge
and upload a playful video of you
getting wonderful on twitter
yeah winners will be chosen randomly
five participants get a quartz hundred
no quartz that's worth a hundred gotcha
oh [\h__\h]
thirty thousand quarts and then twenty
percent participants will get three
thousand coins okay
let's go
sounds good
and then we have this one that you
already know about it's me uh my turn
was today and the sixth i guess that's
next that should be next week on
saturday yeah saturday saturday
uh
yeah so check out kuda's stream of view
curious streaming in in gurishu
and then we have yeah her singing live
on stream the unreality escape english
version covered by gar gura
yeah i wonder what her
her version will sound like because i
don't think uh
there is an english version so far
okay i guess hers is the first time
because i didn't hear an english version
so far i might be wrong but i only heard
the japanese version hmm
will be interesting
and then a worldwide collaboration with
rey arks scientist situs
sorry don't know how to pronounce that
starting expecting from august 10th jst
the worldwide collaboration with the
super popular random game
scientists will begin
yeah unreality escape and renew remix
version will be playable for free with
scientist status
oh a rhythm game maybe gouda will check
that one out too
yeah that's it
thanks everybody for watching thank you
for sponsoring the stream alice fiction
it was fun i like it i like the
aesthetics and the soundtrack the
characters the lure
that you know thinking about what this
character originates from
is really really fun so thank you so
much for the opportunity
i hope you guys enjoyed the stream and
the game
[Music]
tomorrow
i think tomorrow is on archived kana
okay so see you there bye bye
thank you
[Music]
oopsie
no i was just i was just closing my ipad
[Music]
bye-bye
you're closing because i finally have
like one of those covers i didn't have
for a long time and then i was starting
to get some scratches so
i got a cover
one of those
like the ones that are like a book but
also like the
like a stand like a tripod for your ipad
basically
yeah yeah yeah
the magnet one yeah the magnet one that
when you open it
it's it realizes oh you just opened your
ipad
[Music]
okay bye