[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
um
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody and welcome to Among Us with
whole life English and Indonesia
[Music]
well we have Grabbers here today to
present to you a new feature that just
was updated in Among Us the whole life
Cosmic kills
wow
everyone is super hyped okay let's go
it is if you get the whole life Cosmic
Cube then uh you can like get outfits
from selected members from Whole Life
Enid and Japan this these streams are
not sponsored but we just really want to
show you so good look at everything so
[Music]
introduce themselves and they can also
show off their sexy outfit while they're
introducing themselves all right let's
go
I might get kicked out of the room
eventually but let's just start oh let's
start with Ahmed hello everybody
uh number one detective I'm naked
um
she's only wearing a head
by the end of the collapse you will have
some sick outfits some sick trip right
yeah yeah
[Music]
okay below um we have Anya at least in
the Discord so anyone produce yourself
please hello everyone I'm shirakamian
today nice to meet you guys
second in the nation hello
hi
okay next we have kaleido primary
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not streaming but guess what
also my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which
means I'll be streaming in 480p which to
be honest why even why even [\h__\h]
bother why even bother yay mommy swag As
a sheriff let's party let's party
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi gouda hello
yes we're officially in the Among Us
lore now yes
[Music]
welcome how does it feel that now you
can have so many imposters of yourself
to even know who who is you anymore
I love it there are many sharklings
around
this one's right here right next to you
is cool please introduce yourself or are
you Gouda
who is you who is him
ah quiz
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my God
[Music]
it's a crazy music
yeah
[Music]
right now
I don't know it seems like an imposter
she's wearing the whole outfit
it's suspicious
suspicious
changed all right whatever
and then we have Muna who is also part
of the people whose outfit you can get
in the game hi Muna
hi everyone
my life Indonesia generation one nice to
meet you you're wearing your own hair oh
yes
I feel like right now I'm wearing a
scientist outfit right now I feel like
I'm I'm doing a touring love in the
Among Us
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
ice cream we're working on it
delicious
[Music]
what are you going for what outfit do
you want
uh whichever is the closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right
yeah
hi
Raymond from whole life ID today I'm
cosplaying as sexy naked money in your
area
[Applause]
was so good what the heck that was
really good I thought she was here
wow yeah hello
[Music]
actually unlocked a bunch of other
people as well but oh my God yeah
oh it sounds fun not at least the
organizer of today's events are of
today's event
let's go
[Music]
yeah
okay
of course of course that happened one
second now we'll open a new room that
timing was amazing
it happened on your turn yeah yeah yeah
okay a new code is in the Discord chat
please please go get it and don't make
it scene to the to you
um
one second
[Music]
ah hello oh that was funny comedy gold
yeah perfect timing okay okay
let's let's re introduce
[Music]
wow
a really sexy combination of Marin and
pecora you look at that that's so cool
oh my God
looking good I can also do like a
millionaire I can do so much I can do
this and
[Music]
um I will now change the world settings
we will have everything included we'll
have scientists whoa in case you don't
know the scientists can see the vitals
at any time no not any time well there's
a countdown but you can see if someone's
dead before finding the body and then we
have the engineer engineer can is a
crewmate who can jump into the vents so
you can maybe with that
yeah or you can maybe find some other
imposters because of that might be
healthy
yeah
very spicy and now we have the guardian
angel which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from death
and I only have last but not least the
shape shifter this one is oof that that
calls for a lot of
fights
I knew it was you I knew it was you
shave shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people wow it was Anya
[Laughter]
but just so you know all of these rolls
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know it's not happen to you now
oh
yeah
come on
it's starting
to see me
[Music]
[Laughter]
I love this game so much
all right
stop stop it stop it stop it why are you
here stop stop following me
[Music]
quite a horror
we had a talk like we were testing the
waters out during the hey what up
we were testing the waters out on like
EO trust you guys
oh lights out
so yeah
there's so many voices here what the
heck
how many people are here uh you can't go
through here we gotta go through nope
not here
hey
ah this is a maze
yes
that was quick
that was fast wait where was it the the
um where was the body yeah Armory Armory
um
I think or was it Ollie
[Music]
in the armor right oh yeah because like
uh
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the armory
but
that was the beginning I was in the back
room when it was for now well she got
killed fast
you know anybody want to step up and be
like yo I'm something I have no idea
though I didn't you can uh if if you are
you were telling me that um I was in a
Armory you can ask a gura because I saw
Guru also in a nearby there in the
kitchen
um
[Music]
huh
I love this game I I like making them
confused
it really do
like I feel like this is like personal
hey
what up somehow
what up
I'm gonna be a fashion designer what
should I do oh I couldn't Jam
[Music]
okay how's Japan senpai
okay
so yeah we were like testing out the
voice uh proximity right and apparently
like um
um if someone were to like to
shape-shift we'd be able to tell if it
was them if they were talking
and so we were like yo how do we tell
people apart if someone did shapeshift
and oh hello sorry
hello
and then I said well you guys would know
it's me if I suddenly scream titties all
the time
it's not Ollie if she does not scream to
this
[Music]
oh that's a little fire
yeah so during that one run while we
were practicing I kept on screaming
titties
yeah but there's a test
oh oh wait did girls invite your dad
over here
yeah but
oh
I'm sorry
what
okay
I'm so sorry
ah it's so far
and this isn't this is really fun
well she is
so funny I love this so much
and then we go to the showers again
or cargo me we can just oh come on man
oh my God
kitchen
a kitchen kitchen
um me and Maury Senpai we were nearby
electrical I was going to the music I
was with a roommate and Kelly Senpai I
mean I went to the Armory and put guns
away I passed by I passed by I think it
was Watson or and
and gura in records yeah I can I say
that last time I saw zado they were in
the main hall with Cobo
[Music]
I was listening about global because uh
she she telling me on the previous one
it was me well I definitely like far
away from the kitchen and now
um
but then she left do you have anything
that you want to defend Cobble yeah
so any last words
what Fork was like in the in front of
the fan yeah sure just uh see herself I
like just what she said and then after
that I go up
right near the lounge that was beginning
though that was the very beginning no no
I I after that I go up
after killing her you mean
um
we have like we have little shorts on uh
choose uh who's you're gonna know
I don't have enough information yeah I
have no idea
I haven't heard
uh there there she goes
poor child what if she's not the one
though
[Music]
who's gone people
well it was this what do I do here
what
what do I do
huh
I wonder who to kill next killing people
is so fun
who to kill who to kill hello
I mean maybe we can kill some people
after pretending like I'm doing my task
maybe we should shape-shift after this
don't you think so Chad
yeah we don't want to be found out
hopefully no one
um
no one would suss us
hi who killed her who killed her
okay that's insane Watson is dead uh I
found the body
oh is that it was like the previous that
was dead last time yeah oh
um okay so I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks
while I was figuring out how to do the
mini game I was like how do you do this
then mume ran in and was like hey he
hates he and doing things and then I
walk out and watched his dead body is
there
Watson if you were entering the front of
the ship you would have passed Watson
how did you not see her well I don't
know but I did pass I want to say I
passed Guru and I wouldn't be about
we people people didn't yeah
I was asking that
Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about I didn't know you remember
so much Kelly I'm I'm just surprised to
say I don't all right now listen here's
the deal so the amount of time that
passed in between me entering the room
seeing Watson leave and mume entering
and me going outside was so short
it was like no time at all you would
have passed her I just I just want to
remind you that we have 10 seconds left
so I think if you don't have followed by
I'm gonna choose your moment I'm sorry I
have to vote for a roommate I just don't
believe it
and there goes mum
she was a good last I think maybe unless
she's the Imposter that would make her a
murderer
yo what yo
[Music]
wait it was actually mummy
and come on
[Music]
cool down yeah
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately in a month
[Laughter]
he's shooting Sheriff thanks I think I
think Kelly you should go for it Amelia
wants some detective outfits
[Music]
yeah
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yeah
[Music]
oh
let's see
wow
oh my god oh that was funny hey I'm
Gonna Get You nope you wanna see it you
wanna see a magic trick
why is it that I always clean the towels
you guys nasty you guys dirty
well lights it should be not it's not
nearby never mind
I'm gonna just clean up I'm gonna be the
best waifu ever where's the last one you
yeah
that's what I thought it's kind of magic
trick
uh
best waifu
award goes to me I am good waifu
all right uh
[Laughter]
she scared me hello nicer location than
a toilet hi I'm going to clean the third
stall unless you want to do something
with me in the third stall
okay
sorry drained your lunch
Amelia goodbye
goodbye you Amelia how could you how
could you hey
can you hear me I bet you can are you a
little sneaky you're so
happy
YouTube
this whole wide world
oh wait I should protect Muna Senpai
but as in by now
thank you
[Music]
tell it to me now found Ollie dead where
um that was crazy so I don't know the
map super well but I left the shower so
I put away all of the washcloths from
the shower and then I walked off and I
turned right and I went down that long
hallway and found Ollie's body right in
the middle of there but I didn't see
anyone coming down from there so I'm
kind of thing
so like above the shower house above the
shower knives to the right yeah on the
way to the archives the sheriff is
amazing there that you that you're that
you remember well let's see
um Renee was busy doing things around
the shower
um also rained could have killed me and
she didn't close I think girl was in the
shower as well but she like went down to
the left no I was up in the meeting
of the kill because because if if it's
really if it's raining if she already
killed right but I mean Renee could have
killed me several times and she didn't
so I I feel like yeah I can vouch for me
she was trying to tell me a joke and
then I ran away from her oh yeah also
could have killed me but didn't so
yeah I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
realized why
[Music]
wait that is so scary what
um can you hear me are you an imposter
Spiderman actors rotoscoped into Mario
Kart oh it's the moon
wait
Watson senpai
what
it's them
well I can do my task a lot easier since
I can just fly
I gotta protect people I feel bad if I
don't protect anyone at all
and
and and uh and uh who is it Emilia
Senpai was it
okay
[Laughter]
you guys can't do anything even if it's
double killing him leave it to me
oh but there's a
delayed no no no no no no no the dog
excuse me protect the sheriff new
weapons
don't worry Murray Senpai I've got your
back and oh oh oh nice invites here get
away okay okay
is coming see
it
oh it's okay I appreciate that you
helped me I gotta go finish my tasks
Ollie but you're doing good work you can
save someone else I'm sure oh I'm so
smart foreign
always
someone who would accidentally show it
remember and then randomly don't worry
Harrison pie I got to it protected you
hopefully
hopefully I don't know
after I'm done with all my tasks I swear
to diddly darn I will hunt both Amelia
Senpai and Luna Senpai on the 96.
they're there oh my God where's the
chair we found it
Armory
anybody else
and we confirmed each other as Alibi
yeah
below the main hall
I was on the way actually I was on the
way to the kitchen so any any sooner I
would have found the body but I'm from
the engine room like from the main hall
I saw you I saw you at the right side of
the map
yeah sure because I was doing tests at
the cargo bay you know
[Laughter]
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in the kitchen and viewing
day
what
[Music]
hey yo you guys can hear me I bet you
guys can uh-huh right here right now no
one was addicted you guys are lucky you
guys are super lucky
save them
[Music]
a big boobs
big bottom still big Bottoms in bye
not letting you have this one
not letting you have this one no
no me
oh
okay look at this point come here come
here look at this my child
because
amika's possibility
right now
what you came from this side because
like explain yourself
[Music]
hey
saved rainy on that one
wait can you only like save one person
at a time or can we give it to like
multiple people
do your task
96 57 too bomb
let's go
[Music]
they are gone but be careful they might
be watching movie
they might be
those tiki Tiki
little
oh where is this
understand
oh wait not this this
remember you gotta download your stuffs
yeah
and upload them
we upload them here
let's go EMF level five uh oh
I feel like someone's going to die again
uh oh
no
they're smooth me a little mummy but I
gotta I gotta keep an eye on
it
what language are they speak this is not
me haul
oh so where are they
oh my kid my child mommy mioli are you
actually are you
Mama meal is sad
Mama Dad I'm sorry child I can't take
care of you anymore
where are they
don't see anyone
hey yo time to haunt some people Cali
where are you at uh there you are hey
I'm right here
to respond yeah make them talk
where was I
[Music]
[Applause]
and I
um
there goes
uh
you've been a good sport movie
don't worry
oh no I mean she could have killed me
some more
all right time to hunt some people
apparently I don't even know like don't
worry you're not at all in a year
wonderful you're fabulous you're six
you're hot
right
now
I gotta haunt the [\h__\h] out of it I do my
test yeah where are they
I'm so sorry woman you're wonderful
where are they
are they venting um no I'm not dirty no
I'm not dirty that I said until they say
something
where are they ha ha you're really doing
their job diligently that's for sure
you're really into their murder job yeah
for sure for real for you hey how's it
going what up
Killers
all these ghosts are gonna haunt you
forever yeah
until you say something when you're
alone and someone's gonna be like oh man
why is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
of me
so yeah
she was I was I was in before that I was
in a cupcake with with gura and then and
then rainy come and say she got she's so
doppelganger of me
so I don't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see Randy
yeah
it was so very clever blame it on the
doppelganger
I was like for a while together she
could have killed me for them so I think
she's fine okay
I think we already voted one out so
there should only be one imposter left
there is a couple of times
but but she didn't kill me neither
[Music]
maybe you were on cooldown
well hopefully we don't die
no one was ejected no one was ejected no
one was ejected
she wasn't like talking as if she like I
would protect you cursed by she was like
aware of that that she's being heard and
then purposefully tried to create an
image of herself being you know don't
worry I got your backyard I will protect
you
angel
like actresses oh no one hears me anyway
so we're playing with moon I was real
weird yeah
I gotta go here
um
[Laughter]
hahaha
you guys you guys didn't know this is a
contradiction
we're still there
yeah but very quiet
oh you wow
wow
[Music]
I wonder why people kept aggressively
trying to frame me yeah that was pretty
hard to watch yeah it was really hard to
watch I was barely doing nothing easy to
do
quick I'm gonna I'm gonna actually a
little bit hold on wait okay
nice if I buy some clothes
but I had no evidence
maybe if I wear clothes people will be
alive yeah maybe it's not her you know
maybe it's not it is
nice I have a question on there because
I heard you in the in the selection
screen where you choose where to go next
I heard you say something that sounded
like something
I felt like you might have been acting
was that what you were doing
um
so you were like aware that we would
hear you and you were on purpose saying
something that only a crewmate would say
yeah
[Music]
my God
are we waiting for Muna right now yeah
I'm back okay
[Music]
let's go
awesome
all right back to business
nope nope nope nope away from me you the
little devil
ding ding
big big titty milky but Jiggies
um we go here
and a cockpit cockpit
all right
you guys usually like um download your
stuffs
like your um your off-stream materials
because I do
they're awesome you get to watch them
even with no internet not watch I read
[Music]
some flyers
some sick
sick shall we
and make sure that no one uh
notices are killing it
oh hello hello I'm gonna I'm gonna um oh
no
oh no
goddesses
then you will know um
so rainy I saw rainy uh yeah uh going to
the Armory and the kitchen when when I
want to go to engine room so I didn't
know I thought you were she from cockpit
or main hall yeah so uh each other in
the kitchen and I'm from the
communications Armory kitchen I saw
viewing that oh alien girl it was short
yeah yeah
we kind of passed by each other it's
always me what yeah what you guys have
yeah I'm saying that we were in the
group
yeah and Calvin was in the shower I I
saw her I saw her in the shower but then
I saw a Callie on the left side I think
she went to the left side so she was
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi maybe I
was going out to get service I did pass
you Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't uh you
probably weren't that worried since
you're outside Yes
actually right by the body because uh I
was the one who reported it was coming
up the ladder yeah I couldn't see
because it was really dark
yeah you went on I went up
[Music]
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't yeah I don't want anyone
dying yet first I don't think I think ah
okay I'm just gonna like skip skip
I have no idea
don't kill me YouTube don't do it I
won't
let's see hi
[Music]
wait where where ah I go here
all right reveal code it's red diamond
uh
Mario coins and uh
Ruby Mario and diamonds okay
awesome Ruby do we have anything here we
just need to go to the launch and pick
up some more towels
this is dirty you're calling that hi
hello just cleaning towels here don't
mind me
[Music]
oh
spicy
spicy what the heck
hello please please don't do anything
I'm just I'm just a little guy
if I killed Humana assembly would be
right here and shoot no right yeah
please don't kill me it's my birthday
let me kill you guys instead hey
stop don't kill me no not in the
bathroom it will hurt
oh no don't watch you pervert you're
absolutely perfect I'm showering can't
you see what are you doing anyway
well I'll look here isn't fine
hello this place is like a maze
happy birthday thank you everybody
[Music]
it's my birthday so don't kill me
wait what
I would know that right oh my God
Anya's dead
What the freaking
I just found Anya's body in the bathroom
and I'm pretty sure Zeta and somebody
else versus us here okay
where's that where's the body uh anybody
else in bath or showers oh no wait what
the [\h__\h] Lounge Lounge showers Lounge
Lounge yes
we're out though let's we're out a day
where
um the last time well last time I went
near the shower and main hall is I saw
only
amen and I think I think did anybody see
Anya with anyone
no
I know I didn't see I just did yeah I
think I think is she alone in the
huh we're outside then
I think it's uh probably Kiara and Zetta
what
she's innocent
yeah listen to me I am always us when
I'm a crewmate and when I'm not a
crewmate I'm uh nuts us so keep that in
mind now you're sassing me which means
I'm a crewmate it's always like this
it's not gonna work I didn't
why the [\h__\h] why aren't you providing an
alibi instead of Defending yourself huh
what is this
why did Thomas found the Buddy twice
included room where like she would have
killed me
[Music]
I'm gonna skip I don't know I'm gonna
skip because I don't know that's
unbelievable
oh wait what others call us who's
willing for me that's cool
hi
[Music]
don't worry don't worry we can be
together
only I'm gonna go through the cockpit
let's play together let's play together
okay all right let's keep an eye on each
other
so we're here
I'm scared I don't want to be close
stem and then gonna go to the viewing
deck oh is your yes I have something
there too yeah okay
yes yes oh thank you always thank you
for standing up for me yeah because it's
just um I don't know you're being like
I
was just not your birthday it's not it's
not
wasn't it your birthday like a like
recently oh no my birthday is actually
uh next month like in two weeks yeah
yeah
um yeah
go away
all right where else do you still have
more I I already have a lot oh okay it's
Zetta for sure I'm voting no no really
no really why why exactly okay okay why
are you the one you you said you you
found a buddy three times in a row now
yeah because I just happened to be a
detective who's really good at spotting
bodies
could I have killed you or would I have
uh killed that body if I was with you
and in that room for like over 30
seconds
yeah I don't know uh you want me to be
honest um what you said was oh just
kidding I was just waiting for my cool
down yeah but I was already in the room
doing the task before you got there
hey I don't know
um
it's like three times
can anyone uh give an alibi to Jetta
no no no I mean nobody can guess like
instead of running away from the body
because Rayna and I were both up in the
room like in the meeting room and then
eating as I went down I was with Rena
the whole time and then we saw Zayna
pass Us in that hallway
foreign
[Music]
but maybe it's wrong I went for Jenna
too but hmm
ah
a couple went full Emma instead of me
interesting
hope I wanna stick together the three of
us gonna have like a yeah family meeting
the two sisters we can go to main hall
records right oh records are okay
she's not here uh-oh harrisoned bye
I'm gonna just do my task then
elephant it's just a little bit cute
because you know she's constantly
yapping but when it comes to Big collabs
like this she gets very shy and it's
just super cute
oh you gotta go there I hate this
it was the Mario thing right that the
Ruby Mario and Diamond diamonds I'm so
happy
so happy what other hair tasks do you
have one more over here okay
[Music]
and then I'm done what about you you
have some left yep I have two more
okay I'll follow you in one two three go
yay let's go field trip
if you want to open the door uh lucky
well I'll do it let's see who's faster
oh no
let's go
I hope someone is going to the other
side
oh okay wait you can go you can go on
this side okay
[Music]
[Applause]
good luck okay oh no oh I'm I'm
separated from here
yay only one person can go there Emma
was gonna kill me I swear also I'm done
with my tasks let's go oh let's go to
the emergency meeting and talk about who
couldn't finish that dress huh okay
sounds good
oh yeah you done oh I have I have uh
this one and then another one
okay six five three Five Guys
come on
it must be over here
[Music]
okay okay a club was going so we can do
this one and nine three oh three five
minutes
[Music]
oh sorry sorry sorry sorry I keep
pressing the wrong buttons
[Music]
probably
I know she's still alive she's alive
[Music]
trust me bro trust me bro it's almond
Prospect row okay it's Kiara
[Laughter]
I'm not even near you I'm scared I know
it looks like you oh you just didn't
have an opportunity to kill anybody did
you what what I always have an
opportunity to kill but I was constantly
with her
um I'm telling you it's on the DraStic
probably Kobo to be honest because she
was white rain and I were together and
Kobo was not doing any tasks and she was
just following us trying to wait until
one of us was like separated
what were you doing recently
I was just following them
why are you done with your task or
no my last stars is in an electrical
then why did you go up to where we were
Ollie Ollie yeah I'm just scared I'm
just you're usually so good with numbers
but why did you mess up why did you keep
messing up that number thing I had to do
the keypad thing for you oh true
with the dead side but Tommy was on that
side too right now I was just being
stupid
I'm sorry
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place all right
because we want to develop you off
I'm gonna vote for Ollie because I kind
of feel bad for her because nobody ever
cusses her
what
yay
that's so nice of you raymie thank you
for assessing me finally
one day I will get that imposter oh
[Music]
uh oh
because what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
Elena is just [\h__\h] around man
this is getting pretty scary
[Music]
don't worry just finished my task and I
will be okay it's a ruby a diamond
diamond
Senpai are you here
we just gotta wait it out until one of
them kills each other okay okay okay but
we have to find the body or we go ready
for the Emergency meeting we go up there
again
that's also a plan only as long as I can
count on you yeah I went over to go
start tearing and uh cheering us on
they're like ah oh you guys don't know
it's them it's actually them
oh no the lights are off again ah do you
wanna
understand call it
a bit wait can we
read it
why did you run the boat
where are you here
okay I'm gonna go up back to the
emergency meeting okay
because I only have one emergency
meeting and I already used it so it has
to be someone else monkey
pushing hard on this oh okay someone
come on Fair someone's there
[Laughter]
[Music]
by I have an idea I have an idea how bad
I go with cobot I go with what I go with
Kobo and if I die that's probably her
how does that sound
but no
but it's the only way to make sure which
one we need to win
we need to win but like if you go then
you'll die and then if I find your body
and then there's an
hello
[Laughter]
what about your what about the task huh
what do you have left
I already beat my electrical task oh
you're dead so you're done but that
would mean because we're all done if
we're really all um uh normal and we're
all done then we should have won by now
so it's cool come come on what
programming
why but but what if it's not it's not
common what if it's actually a remission
she'll chase us down
though
[Music]
it was Kobo and it was global
um
nice Ollie good job team nice Hustle
[Music]
the gas lighting was so intense
was so spot on
but she was
she was scared
catches her personality it's not that
she's the Imposter it's just her
personality
saying hi to her and I was like doubting
myself you believe me because I thought
you would believe me
um
[Music]
crewmate every freaking time yeah me too
yeah
for sure
hello there's a lot of people here whoa
that's not stack each other hello oh
you're gonna have to stop an electrical
task
s
why is everybody screaming
I'm I'm gonna just
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
hahaha
[Music]
I mean that that was pretty accurate
right I think it's pretty accurate heck
hi hello hi
I'm on the right
when they go together again I still have
no idea where's the lock
right
several ones though there's more than
one
there's more than one I'm gonna go with
you because I trust you a lot
and press YouTube
[Music]
oh wait I need to fill uh this one
actually
what should we do okay all right Emma
wait is there any oh
are we kind of separate it's fine
oh my God
whoa
okay you watched her die
where oh ah maybe we should vote Monday
out she really wants to die oh okay
no okay okay
though I want to be killed though um
killed please well she said please
you want to be killed all right we'll
give you some more time to get some
kills
me you want to be killed or or Kiara
Kira just uh go to Mommy so if she was
the first one or maybe we can just start
the game what uh what yeah
you're killed I mean you know what oh I
want to watch me get like you know
beheaded okay then I'll I'll Grant your
wish you have my belt with me all right
we'll give you until the next meeting
and then okay all right okay
wanna talk about it because she reported
so yeah okay
oh yeah yeah when was the body where did
you find the body Cobble I found the
body in front of
Communications between Communications
and Communications and I was I was uh
I don't think um
the last time I saw Cali was somewhere
we'll give you until the next meeting
because many people as you can wow
[Music]
sounds nervous
bubble fighter maybe she's sleeping
oh yeah because it's like bedtime it's
at 1am Mommy will bring you to bed right
now
or go to the [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
the cockpit
why is it called the cockpit why can't
it be called
something else
I thought over here right okay oh here
what up yeah
hello hi
you are
I can't build a burger
yeah yo
you guys like your Tomatoes I'm I'm a
palazzo tomatoes
nice
and then
I'm gonna go to electrical
I just got an outfit by the way it looks
good on you
locker room
hey
all right
no one has killed me yet
you want you want to get her with me
yeah sure
who was that that was alien and Luna
said bye
electrical
[Music]
yeah
he was pretty quick to get an alibi
there huh
wait who found which body though there's
three bodies right I found zeta's body
in cargo bay and it wasn't there a
moment ago I think but the lights were
off
[Music]
at the very top
I have an alibi for for only and gura
because I saw them and we were we were
near the kitchen first and then go to
security and electrical we haven't go to
medical and cargo bay yet
I've been there
for a while so
what is what's uh what is
is not screaming at all yeah originally
usually when when she was the crew man
she almost she always screamed whatever
she met someone wanted to cut me off and
did scream are you sure about that yeah
what the [\h__\h]
I know I've I've been I've been I've
been uh watching all of you guys
um you know
Sound by on the previous uh previous
games
Kiera really loves to scream when I ever
met anyone that's when she was a
Christian that's because
that's because you're scared and now you
didn't you're not so far you didn't show
that you are scared do you have an alibi
no it's because I didn't see anyone
probably that's because
last minute I don't know you found the
last minute okay yeah I don't know
tiara
[Music]
now I'm scared for my life I don't know
how to trust anymore
garrisoned by my beloved
so if if Kira's Empire really was a
imposter I would really hate it
foreign
because who goes to the meeting room
uh see why is it I keep getting the
numbers wrong it's five six I'll five
nine
I'm just maybe it's because it's the
middle of the night maybe I'm not
focusing anymore
oh now the ladder shoot up hello oh hi
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
wait what
and then the other side
haven't I done oh okay cool
[Laughter]
[Music]
the money
I still
please don't kill me nothing bye please
don't kill munas and but if she if she's
dead I don't know who to trust anymore
I don't know if it's
I don't I really don't know
um
you go to Armory
oh there you
I'll just accept this first
and I'll go fix the lights so they're
here
exciting
was that oh hello
um gotta go away now
hey hey
let's just upload them here
maybe maybe we can do like an emergency
me ah no please please I don't want any
[\h__\h] thank you I'm good
well who's that did Amelia's invite just
say do you want to get [\h__\h] because I
don't want to get [\h__\h]
laughs
all right so what do we do now
what if I hold like an emergency meeting
[Music]
don't follow anyone yet I'll just do
emergency meeting
just oh
these damn doors oh it's getting jammed
who designed this airship
come on
then I'm just going to check if
everyone's alive
as if someone's dead I'll be very
disappointed
oh
see as I thought Ollie it wasn't
a city yeah I saw I saw Muna Senpai
going towards where Ollie was and that
was the last time I saw her the reason
why I press this is because I wanted to
check if everyone's still alive
oh really did you see my Senpai on your
way there or over there we actually saw
that ways no I didn't see the body I
pressed the emergency button
oh okay wait I didn't see the party
no I didn't see the body it really went
to check if anyone's bed by pressing
them you're the last one left and you
want to try to vote people out
I ran into combo but she didn't say
anything
we're in the same room shark yeah I want
to know if you were
called what are they called oh well it's
skin consumer skin wearing shape shape
shifter because you didn't say anything
but I guess it's fine oh
yeah why'd you call a meeting what the
egg no why did you calling me stop the
tasks is that it okay fine well you know
what I'm done with my task anyways so
like maybe I can just go chat with the
girls you guys can vote me off if that's
what you guys want
I might just talk with the ghost there
I bet you could already hear them yeah
they're like no
Wally no don't true
all I wanted to be is uh Soul Time it
did so maybe it's a good idea if you
guys vote me maybe it's you you're very
loud usually
what I mean I'm allowed now whoever what
is it that said the rhyme did that I
have no idea I've been stuck in
electrical doing this stupid
what I thought
that's what I thought so you're not a
world imma be one with Lego Steve
I'm done with my task anyways it's just
up to them
[Music]
she has to play it right Ollie I'm sorry
that that happened to you it's okay my
kid isn't is an orphan yet again
it's just you know she's just trying to
be a detective you know yeah
I
[Music]
believe you you did the right thing
wait who did you got killed by
oh wait he got voted off I'm the
Imposter you what
yeah
and there's another one who's still
alive
the way she said it without face I can't
I can't I think girls if I went to the
electrical
and
yep
ah it was a mother and daughter
[Music]
foreign
it's incredibly difficult that should
tell you whenever people are dying
really fast it's definitely Kobo I just
love how old
she saw the crime scene when goes to the
emergency meeting and then Ahmed Changes
Everything by something the innocent
ones yeah
[Music]
he's right with you Kiara salty
I take it out too early oh boy like one
last round yeah
[Music]
definitely win yes
[Applause]
I'm so done I'm so upset
what do I do
hi
all right
dang it
oh oh okay
so we go here we can uh we can uh
hey
no last one oh I'm so hungry too what
wait
what
once again
[Music]
so here's what I found I was picking up
all of the towels and [\h__\h] in the shower
and I said I hope gura doesn't kill me a
girl is fine I don't think that she did
it but I went to the left and like Kelly
sent by um we were in the same room and
um the people I saw were you gura Senpai
and Zeta okay well let me tell you where
I found the body first before you start
pointing fingers okay listen to me
because I didn't even tell you where I
found the body you just immediately
jumped on me
from the left from the left of the
shower walked up and in that photo room
we're all like it's like the dark room I
guess that's where I found the body I
didn't see that there was a dead body in
there because the lights were out until
it said report I clicked report and I
guess Renee was killed in the dark room
so that's all I have to say about that I
literally was just cleaning up the
shower was anybody down there electrical
S I was at electrical I'm using showers
okay I was at electrical and I saw no
one yeah I saw that but I was there
where where I was at electrical I was at
the bottom right of electrical I just
came under at the bottom well I mean
tomato I like yeah so Kelly
the towel no I didn't finish picking
them up I thought I did but it wouldn't
let me put them inside of the hamper
thing so I still have to grab a couple
towels I I whatever I am snuffling with
only because I was in the electrical I
saw I was in the electrical I was in the
middle I was in the middle bottom and
see that he was in the bottom because I
didn't see anyone
[Music]
fans nearby
well I guess you could say that rainy's
body tasted delicious hey turkeys am I
right
oh guys
too much
okay from here I wanna go to let's fix
the lights real quick shall we
fixing though hello
all right uh electrical electrical
Aussie
I wanted to do my task
let's see uh
I'm so scared let's stay let's see it
together
[Music]
this is so scary man
well I mean I've always wanted to be
such so being sis is good I hope no one
finds out about me killing other people
I hope no one finds out about me killing
other people how high it might hurt
and then after that she's going up and
then I fall I saw
his body in the electrical when I'm
doing this I ran into Ollie after that
and she was saying and I quote sure hope
nobody sees that I know
[Applause]
[Music]
the first time the first time only said
that she was an electrical but I didn't
see it and then the second time you know
we we had to teleport first right and
then after that he said you know I'm an
electrical I find you and after that
um I'm still fixing my electrical and
then uh Ollie passed by going up uh and
then I was on my my end task uh doing
the electricity uh and then I saw
colleague died well I mean Cali said by
his body I just couldn't resist
[Music]
[Laughter]
I wish your partner good luck Ollie
whoever was with you
hopefully can do this alone
got it gotta be careful the next one
might think same gen Bond
the next one might actually be what if
we got this one wrong though I'm 14 but
what if we got it wrong is it actually
Ollie well I mean only because sister
sucks well then you guys can vote me off
there she would defend herself more if
it wasn't her
though
[Music]
sorry Ollie that's okay well I've always
wanted to recess anyways
[Music]
that's that that's that Emma just keep
sabotaging and then
um
let's see
don't worry he said I got this I'll help
you
[Music]
or maybe I mean the Buddha Senpai was
also there
[Music]
oh wow
I'ma just keep spamming then
make sure that no one's here for the
benefit of the doubts yeah do that I'm
gonna just I'm just
of you
don't go away
oh yeah that's right
this time so that's nice
from the alarm like she finished the
alarm and then she walked to the right
side towards to finish my tasks
Etc I'm almost done
and then I will protect the body
[Music]
here
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
Duo
[Music]
everyone
yeah I didn't even have like 10 seconds
of gameplay
you guys figured it out heck yeah
[Music]
good job everyone
that was a great job
[Music]
no no no I'm sorry that that was my
alarm sorry
[Laughter]
is there anyone who didn't get imposter
every single time maybe
yeah yeah it's always
Predators
we're like too strong so the game I
don't want to get imposter anymore
no this game is like never end I feel
like I want to play it until I got a
major imposter it yeah
I wouldn't mind playing more but I'm
just worried about the ID members
because it's like you know two ways oh
yeah it's fine because I usually
[Music]
I can keep going I'm sorry yeah
oh my God
thank you so much Gabe
uh do you look at it
super fat
stop it
seeming me senpai
let's take out the trash
me
out with you wow Kelly Son by Israel
this is stupid Fab
and then the showers
[Music]
there we go
and then we go to electrical
I sir if I go to electrical one more
time
Callison by really planning her tactics
right now hmm we wouldn't be able to
confuse people she said and what's this
about big fat
that stuck to me the most
um
[Laughter]
let's go
guys guys
oh come on give her a chance come on
I don't want to talk anymore
it was in the hallways it was in the
main hall actually yeah okay yeah so uh
I was I was I actually uh saw her
through the showers I went to electrical
a little bit then I went back to the
main hall and guess this I actually met
another Ollie so if you guys said
anything like oh my God I saw the kill
no there was actually a doppelganger and
I actually met her she was chasing me
down
no no listen she was teasing me down and
you know what even if you guys couldn't
no I don't mind because I still have to
pass them even if I fly
here
okay
I think I think I'm gonna skip because I
don't know yeah I don't know I don't
know either she's desperate whenever
she's just like this
and whenever she tries to defend herself
always just like very very desperate
yeah
off and vote me off because I'll do the
task easier that way anyways I can just
fly
let's stay here
I riffed my case it was freaking Olivia
[Music]
man
Callie Senpai who was it are you
listening
are you with me right now give me a sign
EMF level five
oh
I'm gonna just go alone I would be alone
full
[Music]
Empire you're not going to kill me are
you
no no no no see I'll leave I'll leave
I'll leave you alone thank you
once all the lights are up
girl this is going ugly following me I'm
nice I'm just saying my test
why do we have to say
the same yeah I'll let you do yours and
then you can go there you go okay I did
mine do you need to go to a records next
okay have fun
bye bye I'm going to the engine room
so curious invite She Believes In Me So
I believe in her hi Grace and Pie is
that a girl Senpai Gerson by can you
talk Gerson bye she disappeared hi Ollie
hey did you pass my Harrison boy
huh did she talk because she was really
silent she didn't say anything it's
probably a doppelganger
or was that actually her
I don't know
eh
a little bit over here
[Music]
what did you find it wasn't good
yeah hold all together pretty name plate
I want it I I mean I have I have an
alibi yeah you know so I was I was on
the first I wasn't security we drain it
if if I was simple sir I've been I've
been with Renee uh for like a couple of
seconds I'm not killing her at all so if
and then I got to the main town
like was heading towards the showers I
think or the main hall I don't really
remember to the right and then I think
Ollie was asking like have you seen gura
or something okay
and then there was also Zetta or
something but there was like a bunch of
people there there's a lot of the
imagination I feel like Yeah I wanted to
show a magic trick I was like I'm not
accusing anybody I'm just telling what I
saw okay
I mean um yeah I mean uh
okay I don't know yeah um
[Music]
I was around Muna a lot but she never
killed me but okay
[Music]
for like a long time you want to save
her yeah but the thing is I don't know
Anya Anya was also there but Anya is
also dead but girls also dead
[Music]
I don't know because everything will be
used against me so I'll just shut up
because because I was I wasn't on the
main home before I wasn't available
uh-huh
I want to go to the right cards to do
another thought
it was a tie actually
[Music]
because I don't know how to vote for
uh
it's pretty much like meta it's a lot of
meta gaming but
Iranian wanted to see me clean the vents
so I'm just like saying it that way
wanna see me clean the vents because I
actually have an event cleaning
sure
wait did you see it
only want to hear something crazy no so
if somebody says uh if you saw somebody
and they say I got the Vent cleaning
they're lying
hi
there hi and that actually makes sense
you're right
yeah like if somebody ever says that you
know they're lying obviously
all right I was downloading this gotta
download our stuffs
time to upload the data well to be
honest
I feel like being outside is the safest
that was a doppelganger I gotta follow
who was that
that could not be rainy
because Serenity already left and they
were super quiet too ain't it rainy is
the type of person that would talk a lot
during these types of stuffs
why do I keep
is that a doppelganger I saw a person by
his doppelganger girls invites did but
did I see it hello
hi erini I think I saw your doppelganger
it's I know what I need to do tasks yes
you know who it is like
oh what is it what's the answer
because she wasn't
one second and she's just
she wasn't okay
I trust my wife it's just my wife
please talk I need to know that you're
not a doppelganger
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
no I don't know I'm pretty I'm very
scared
I'm pretty I'm pretty source of Cobble I
don't know are you
I'm super scared are you done with your
task because I am Karen pie no I have a
feeling
wow
how many people died actually
now that's a good question we need to
find
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] now Let's Stay Together yeah
I'm so I'm actually an engineer want to
see a magic trick I want to see a magic
trick here here over here there's a
prince over here ready fast pickup line
okay okay okay okay okay okay cool
okay cool
but they're not anywhere by the way
every time I vent oh they're not there
but I need to like
[Music]
uh
where are my tasks anyway
for a task I'm gonna go there now I'm
gonna okay
moana's alone upstairs by the way she's
no longer alone
what uh oh lights
turn on the lights please
I'm very scared I will jump
that was just my imagination didn't
really jump
hello what happened what whenever
I want to say
it's cool
because I like previously when I was the
Imposter with Kobo
um and I died before her I was like
following her to try to cheer her on and
I saw her she would go to that you know
that place uh the Electrical uh where
there's like one task but it takes
literally one second to do it and when
she was the Imposter she would stand
there for ages thinking about what to do
next and I literally caught her doing
that thing now but like she was there I
said hi I ran away because I was
wondering well she's always there when
she's planning something I know no one
died but that's because she's a very
hesitant killer she did that before too
I was watching her and she passed gura
alone a million times and she just would
not kill gouda for whatever reason she's
very hesitant and she goes always always
sort of electrical to
as if she's doing that task but it takes
one second and she waited one minute
there believe me trust me bro I don't
have any proof of her I will I will
vouch because the only thing the only
thing that's like for me suspicious is
that uh she's she's being like awfully
quiet yeah she hasn't really said
anything up until like in the discussion
at all do you have a defense for
yourself yeah do you have a defense for
yourself like why are you so quiet or
you know
quiet from the beginning
I I don't know yeah
what if I really do my task in
electrical I mean why mommy I'm gonna be
so that aggressive
okay
I did it right after you too and I know
it takes one second I'm just I'm just
gonna say Ali and Watson are always
together
yeah yes okay I'm gonna vote sorry is
yeah
I'll skip
I don't know
I don't have any evidence
you don't have any evidence but you're
really like pointing to people what do
you mean I didn't Point anybody I don't
think yeah
I was getting interested hello
[Music]
I'm done with my tasks so if anyone
wants to come oh
Great Brain if that was right
Olly Olly
hey I found the perfect signal whoa
yeah I am yes oh
my God
for people
okay let's look for dead bodies
no no not what I had in mind but okay
yeah aren't you used to dead bodies and
you're looking yourself in the mirror
every morning must you remind me
oh there's nothing here okay okay
where should we go we want to take
electrical
yeah yeah no no Cobra won't be there
anymore
[Music]
where is the next one also we have to
fix the lights
[Music]
those aren't lights
oh nothing bye
oh okay that's really easy
hey
hi
that means there's still one more
impostered
what happened to Chiara shinpai
again
okay wait wait we got luck
[Music]
and
I'm done
bye
take care of my good child
[Music]
foreign
yeah go to the other side please thank
you
I am show you
[Music]
it's not Watson bite
no no no no no no no no no no
your big big size
that's great that's right yeah keep
getting scared I see through your ax hi
um
[Music]
I'm here
where was it um
okay I just saw Moonah it must be Muna
definitely don't you say that um I was
from the Gap room and I passed by when
you are fixing the electricity and I go
to the shower and then I go to records
again okay I was in shower it was
earlier why don't you see you I I saw I
saw I saw I think it was Kiara and then
Zeta is from the shower too and we
passed one right okay
[Music]
where is the location of the body
I don't know what do you think it's
um in the cargo bay between the door of
medical toy Reyna and Zeta which way
were you guys going through the showers
like to the left
I was with you oh sorry
was with me we came from the top to the
bottom from like we saw I'm gonna go in
the other way or you saw her going with
you in that direction
I didn't see her at all which is the
problem what
[Music]
I think there goes some of them going to
the up to go into the record and then
after so after that I said I bet she
failed in public speaks in class this is
actually intimidating
yeah
I don't know he's pretty good ideas
bloodthirsty I'm telling you kind of
except for maybe you and Rene
most of us is it because yeah
haven't seen their potential yet Watson
can vouch for me let's go and nice job
guys let's go good win
s
it's pulling you in like gravity gravity
[Music]
nice job guys good win nice
this is
fun guys
you guys you guys like playing girls
like you guys going to two two groups so
it's like which one should I follow yeah
I think that made it difficult for you
yeah yeah
your speech during the meeting was
actually really scary I wouldn't be able
to fight you if I were the crewmate
yeah yeah yeah you were just like that
it was pretty good sorry I had to that's
pretty good I'm so proud oh my God okay
that was something nice
[Music]
a great a great round
excellent I think
so as much as I want to continue playing
I don't wanna you know force me yeah
yeah maybe another time we don't even
need to play on stream to be honest just
together yeah
whatever toys
all right
[Music]
let's start from the top again I'm there
how was it today oh yeah it was pretty
fun I won an imposter round and then won
all the crewmate rounds or pretty much
all of them so it's you know a pretty
good day pretty good game thank you for
inviting me Kiara thank you for setting
it up uh yeah thank you guys for playing
thank you for always sussing me even
doing me almost never with me
it's like your reflex now but okay I
just want to see your reaction that's
how I kissed you okay
yeah it was so much fun
um I didn't get impulsive but it's fine
thank you so much as long as you have
fun right yeah
together thank you
it was fun yeah
okay next we have Queen cocky
oh yeah that's me whoopsies
um yeah so I think I was born to be
crewmate I don't like playing imposter
anyway so I had a good round
um really only one super good play in
the beginning and then everyone gangs up
on your boy
it was really easy to listen to you and
like yeah it's so convincing and you are
not lying I'm glad to us
I just gotta work on my longevity in the
game
but I got to do tasks and I love doing
tasks so it was fun thanks for the
invite
I do
right I didn't but I made sure to be the
damn this best teammate that I possibly
could
gets like especially like shape-shift
there impossible
oh my God that's terrifying
I want to thank God she didn't I really
want to be a safe shifter I haven't got
that yeah
pretty rare God damn it um well well if
you guys want to look like good on go
get the Cosmic Cube
we'll take over the world yeah yeah
it was a statement about your actions
today how many
three times four
couldn't you share those with the rest
of us huh it's like something in these
collabs there's always like one person
who gets it all the time he only got it
quite a bit too right like right yeah
honestly sorry for uh this who are being
posted together with me because I cannot
um I don't know why but applying on
stream like uh there's
maybe pretty sure
yeah yeah
so I'm not that like I felt that you you
seem very important I'm sorry
if I if I silent for a long time because
uh first I I don't really uh can make a
good excuse yeah I will buy maybe in
Bahasa Indonesia it's so easy but
um I don't know that's fine you can
always use that as the excuse me I use
that with the JP no English please
you did a good job being imposter Kobo
you're really good yeah a lot of kills
yeah yeah
you were scary yeah yeah and then we
have only who gets just so many times
it was it was actually pretty funny
because I thought the reverse psychology
would work it did not
like I like if I actually reverse
psychology guys like twice which means
if I actually access and say oh I'm
actually says that would make you guys
ah Ali's just messing around but nah you
guys thought you was thinking like I
pray I feel like you oh oh
no
it's pulling me
it's pulling her in maybe maybe release
itself
and uh I actually want to thank yours
and fight especially because uh
organizing these sorts of collabs is
like a big castle been there it is and
well all the most utmost respect thank
you for accommodating all of us in this
collab
hey Kiara thank you
[Music]
I'm happy man we had a good reason to
play along with a friend after a long
long time
for a second and go to oh mommy's not
here anymore
oh hello yeah I started the stream naked
in the end the stream naked even though
I unlocked the outfit
inviting me to the collab it was really
fun playing with you guys was fun also
to all the crewmates and also the
Imposter you guys were great
[Music]
it was so much fun I got a few imposters
free
uh two or three I don't remember yeah
it was fun thank you for those who
teamed up with me and thank you bye for
hosting it and I want to apologize
because my stream died six times
how did you survive
oh no I just told him oh God
[Music]
oh no
she can't talk well with that being said
I'm sure she had fun too yeah and uh
hi
[Applause]
[Music]
are you able to talk
Netflix
[Music]
[Applause]
so I cannot hear anyone no wait we're
here now we're here now okay
okay
it's okay uh your full outfit now Muna
you did it
yay congrats
thank you congratulations
I
have fun uh actually uh the first time
I'm doing uh the to become an imposter
with I mean it's really fun
is the one that I'm I'm usually afraid
of whenever
you feel extra safe if I make it a list
it's probably
Amaze is the one who can like talk a lot
that make me you know
so that's usually the person aggressive
detective Sheriff
um
[Music]
I think I got to hear from everybody I'm
glad that we all came together for
another big en ID collab I think the
last one was Mario Parks
a year ago that's a long time ago but
maybe since there's a lot of music we
can try it again sometime soon
[Music]
coming to watch our streams today
thank you yeah and I really don't have
anything else to say besides good job
everybody hope you had fun and yeah see
you again soon sometime
everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
haters
[Music]