[Music]
a
oh
[Music]
W source for animation is in the
description if if you've been here since
the beginning refresh your
video and check the GU
gang which is the the description read
it read it check it out video game
grunts uh
baby sorry if you hear things in the
background that left on the TV for my
cats you know I don't want them to be
lonely I love those
cats my babies
anyway I'm about to start playing
Minecraft please wait just a moment
longer there's another story waiting
this world and beyond our distant dreams
have brought us here a strong unyielding
Bond something something
memories they are watching Jo
oh maybe that's a good guess that's a
good guess I did put on some anime for
them my cats love anime have some Faith
all right let me turn this music down a
little bit hold on a
sec enough reunion we've had enough of
you we've had
enough um now that we're not in America
land anymore
um we're going to need to not
scream connecting to server encrypting
joining
world I can't wait to see what they
did well that doesn't sound promising
right off the bat we're off to a very
frightening
start what's that noise that
goes
Satan we no it's coming from
system hey what is someone in the
voice no why is it rooted through there
that's very
strange the Minecraft audio
is it's going through the same channel
that the Discord channel is going
through that's very
strange I'm going to turn this down a
little
bit I don't understand
why so what is everyone been I'm
doing is that the screams the Damned I
hear well that is my favorite
sound shall we take a
look they got Statue of Liberty horses
now and a sings in One hey debut what's
going
on Y what happened to hey where my boys
go hey why' they clog up the holes
there's supposed to be
Windows oh my goodness it's a lawless
land I found myself in now is this what
the JP underworld sounds like pretty
close there are animals okay that's bad
hey you how dare you do that to me I
just got you back off I monster you
don't belong in this world where's my
sword oh
it's I can beat him up with my
be just like I did the r scallions in
Red Dead Redemption there we
go check the daily for oh the diary fix
it mechanic
I don't think that's meant for me I'm no
mechanic bu basement get sheep diamond
tools o I can do diamond tools diamond
armor okay Stone generator mob farm food
farm maybe iron farm well these are easy
things for dumb people like me so I
think that should be fine is the game
still loud
okay shut your mouth
game master
volume this is probably fine
they' shut their
mouth little too loud for my
taste little too
loud let's see well hostile creatures at
like 25% you can turn down hosle
specifically yeah shut them
up shut your
mouth I love to Yap but I'm I'm not here
to hear you're yapping
cows really need
water I don't even know where our cows
are I mean what happened to the
oh our animals are freaking dead except
this guy this mushroom cow now looks a
little
different where is the
Phantom as a matter of fact where is my
diamond sword I know I had
one well I guess I didn't that's okay
we'll make a stone one
let's
see I'll kill him I don't know where he
is though is the
problem so this is supposed to be the
dirt where my stone
at I'm living in a lawless land void of
organization that's
okay leave it to me your boys can
organize everything once again you'll
see and where's the
wood it left me a lot of stuff to sort
oh boy that's what I love to hear I love
sorting
things fav thing to
do but
first going to need to do a couple
things now you guys may have guessed
this already but I'm no Minecraft expert
like the others so the things that I do
are going to have to
be can we not do whatever it was you
just did
please you're right above me good thing
I'm going to kill them right
now oh they're burning death I mean
that's good right I wish they'd seen me
so that I could kill
them come down
here at least they're dying
right oh yeah now he sees me excuse me
sir would you like to
die they have fire
resistance you're getting hiss that
hardcore by my kitty cat good winess
dummies what a tower
going that's do be keeping them away I
think it's
glitch the game is still out oh my
Lord okay hyle creatures at shut up
there we go that should do the
trick I'm concerned as to why the game
is still so loud hold on a
sec I'm going to figure out what's going
on with my audio AIO settings cuz
there's something wrong with them I
think hold on a
second is the game is being rooted not
to music but to system and that's not
correct why is it doing that can use it
output
music yep that's it
mhm all
right
disable and then it's not going to music
why how very strange might be the game
being scuffed you guys get to watch this
again uh disconnect I'm going to reopen
Minecraft because this is strange this
is a really strange thing I don't know
what's going on I wish it would stop
doing that to me just trying to play
some Minecraft please I mean I know I'm
not great at it but just give me a
chance here to prove myself right just a
little chance is all I'm asking for
for
Man
Minecraft open
sesame I can sleep finally no you can't
wake up we got things to do we got a
very busy schedule here in one block
Minecraft I need to make myself useful
to the
team Ali flopping like a
fish
yeah yeah ready to go in
coach wake
up right play
play game open game open
sesame
Mojang intro animation
goed okay I fixed it it's done now let's
see all right it's rooted to music now
so that's good dunzo
multiplayer one block I should have
fixed
it oh kitties let's calm down
all right and then I'm going to lower
this VA okay that should do the trick I
think we shall see sorry if I'm a little
sleepy sounding too by the way I feel
like always end up playing these games
at please don't
please these group games they end up
being at a time that's not the time when
Mor is full Ganky
right oh well
maybe I should make a room collaboration
room where we can all get in together
okay I'm going to make
one password is a secret that no one
will ever
yes and now I alert the
others room pass is a secret none of you
can get stopped that's
wrong well never mind it it doesn't
matter it doesn't
matter and those cats are popping off on
those
Phantoms I can't blame
them I wish they'd go
away we definitely need some bows and
arrows well
everyone I've got some tools with me
but maybe I want to make a bunch of
tools that will be very useful to the
team today we got stuff to organize
everyone
they haven't died yet I know let's see
so this is NE obsidian NE bricks I know
that all of these go I know exactly
where all of them go check it out okay
so here's another thing we got to do
guys as you all know I am chief
organizer we're going to read The Diary
in a second but let me find another
chest okay end chest end chest
benevolent gift ocean super chest desert
jungle w
hello H behind
me
huh
what I'm being tricked I'm being
Bamboozled where'd she go huh someone's
behind
me but
where is that whistle
noise oh my God Andy just don't look at
him is that who's behind
me all right I don't like I don't feel
so good there are ghosts following me
around Dad I'm scared you and me both
son but that's okay let's just focus on
the
mission this is a wooden anything not
made of wood here nope that looks fine
snow no not snow chest uh
ocean okay
wor behind me I don't see anything
behind me stop lying to
me GRE terracotta we need to make a
terracotta
chest all right I'm going to put this
stuff in the ne
chest I love organizing it's my favorite
thing he doesn't know all right well I'm
just going to ignore you guys I feel
like you're purposefully leaving me out
so
that's fine whatever do do what you have
to
do it makes you feel
better potion of invisibility who would
use a potion of invisibility there's no
need for that maybe we make this the
Terracotta chest no this is still a
sorting chest right all this is sorting
they got one of these the Sher box that
can be pretty
useful H I don't see anything behind me
why is everyone playing tricks on me I
don't understand I appreciate all these
tricks being played on me we need to
make a trash can or something like that
because I feel like can you calm
down watch closely I'm watching closely
nothing is
happening all right
well what
let's
see what am I oh Soul Sand that's right
Soul Sand comes from the nether
chest oh wait I see a ghost behind me
come back no don't you hey hey
hey
fiend Show
Yourself Show Yourself demon
demon show yourself
yeah that's right I thought that I saw a
demon there
boy boy make your presence
known Undertaker
gaha what's she
doing
ywa there she is this going to be dead
dead stuff hey
gaha and then this is going to be
terracotta
there she
is looking cute nice
ponytail what's she doing she's getting
down yeah myth silent
dancing look we're synced
up stop
that's five
in yeah I'm tired from dancing though
I'm tired that was fun though that was a
that was some good
dancing wow was W what do you mean wow
was wahas I'm confused I don't
understand the lingo only 480p or is
your phone being wet your phone's being
whack I'd never stream in 40p what are
you talking what do you take me
for that be what do you take me
for
here y will be joining us oh y this is
going to go in the Terracotta chest
brand new one that I made these are
pretty
though oh and then nether hope you guys
like organizing cuz there's going to be
a lot of organizing going
on only the best
144p did they update the game I think
they
did I saw that Peck Senai was
playing oh y w join the
game y she shows herself she finally
makes herself
known dang it you getting
here question yeah
oh yeah what it do
ye mind if we separate in the Liv we do
oh okay that's fine it's a good idea
honest in all honestly that's a good
idea I'm going to do the
same all right it's time to say bye to
Wawa for a
minute just going to move over to the
side think oh I got to move though there
you go yeah that Works
swag bye bye Gua she'll be back don't
worry no Kiara come back
hey
hey she'll come she'll be back just
chill calm yourselves it's fine it's
fine just coming back don't get
separation anxiety okay fine oh there's
two of
me
wow W pretty
big there she
is yeah two Callie it's more common than
you
think I think maybe a little smaller
Kara's just she's so bouncy
right she's very
bouncy I want to put her over
here
oh it's okay we can be next to you come
over here come over yeah there we
go approach the screen a little bit more
there we
go now we're
chilling bouncy she do bounce all over
the place there we go much better um now
then what's your boy going to do oh yeah
we were organizing it's the only thing
I'm good at so what is this I spy with
my little eye glow stone that doesn't
belong there
belongs here and what's going on in here
terra cotta
uh-uh no freaking way I'm going to throw
up if I keep looking at this hold
on going to throw up
everywhere you have so much stuff to
sort for
you for me to sort hey I made a new
stone only chest good oh good oh goody
that's
good thank you ladies this one at the
bottom next to the Shuler thank you oh
thank goodness for that cuz we are
getting too many items Lads there's too
much probably even have too much
terracotta to be real with you all to be
completely 100% real with you there
might be too much
terracotta another
nice those Phantoms though yeah we we
need to do something about him we can
make bow and arrows maybe we could kill
him but I don't know anyway oh black
terra cotta I spy some terra cotta with
my little eye absolutely unfreaking
acceptable I don't want to live in a
world where there's terra cotta in the
wooden chest I'm sorry is this freaking
terra cotta no it's
not wow a muted no it's okay she's just
setting up they'll join in when she is
ready
more freaking terracotta I
guess guess I'll
die cool sounds Terra cot
toying
silly it's a silly thing to say
d why am I wearing my default today I
wonder I didn't need to do that I could
have dressed up in something else but
oh a voice from Beyond your your Discord
mic is like uh does it sound
crunchy it's like
it's your phone or so I don't know let
me see let me fix it input device okay
how about now oh so beautiful crisp okay
sick very very podcasty I like it okay
cool yeah cuz I was watching I viewed a
couple clips from our first stream our
first the one block stre and I was like
wow why is my mic the only crunchy
one yeah I thought my mic sounded
crunchy and weird yeah crun on that day
on that that to me you sounded not like
just now just now it was very very weird
real real toasty huh M okay like a fire
away microphone oh very odd well that's
okay we're fine now so that's all that
matters yo I spy some wood in here I
hate that I hate that so much I hate it
go I'll be like exp explaining to you
like thing that we um have changed and
gained in a moment I just need to I need
a one one more moment or so take your
time take your time I'll just be sorting
terra cotta like I usually do I sound
angry about it I'm not I'm not angry I
love doing this it's just you know it's
just it hurts me is beautiful it's so
smooth mhm yeah so clay like roll it
around in your hands like Play-Doh
wonderful it's just you know there a we
have to sort that's okay I love sorting
I just I sound angry about it I'm not
okay no ball no these are items they go
in the item box item
box it feels so nice I think you should
maybe you're already starting to do it
but you should like use those other
chests in the in the corner the ones you
prepared oh yes cuz like this is already
like not enough chests and we already
added some to them very true it's okay
definitely do that don't even worry okay
here's the stone I
see smooth
quartz there's all this stuff though
okay I'mma start my stream too go for it
wao that was a nice Western accent you
had there that really took me by
surprise than that was good thank you
that was very I think I can only do it
in like small bits and then if I try to
do two sentences is already going down
the drain oh yeah you can only keep it
up for a little bit huh oh stob doing
that Statue of Liberty I think Fallout
is helping me become better in that
accent well vered in speaking American I
see yeah Vegas is teaching me yeah nice
your studies are paying off in
game nice I will do us all a favor in a
moment and try to kill the Phantoms in
the sky they somehow just don't die yeah
it does really hurt uh the ears what's
going on in here this supposed to be
where the ore is oh my God we got bone
meal in
there
sorry God the chest you angry about the
bone meal no no it's just these AR some
of these aren't or you see
yeah no it's okay man I really missed
you yesterday I really needed you
well I'm here now to save the day thank
God that's so it was such chaos I can
what what happened what was chaotic
about it just a lot of disorganization
you weren't there made everything
chaotic oh really do I really keep
things that in
line
insanely oh my god I didn't even realize
that I feel like I have a purpose now
nice you
doo you doo no matter what I will find
my purpose in this
world quartz I'll put the quartz in here
she has a
little and maybe put the lava bucket in
the nether
one let's see yeah that'll be fine there
Happy Father's Day oh it is Father's
Day people are already saying that
yesterday I mean well you know how time
zones go right yeah maybe it was
Father's Day in Japan now it's now it's
not I wonder where the Red Sand oh red
Sand's probably desert so I'll put it in
the desert
chest
H chest okay okay desert chest so like
sand stuff yeah yeah sand thing Sandy
Shores yeah Sandy
red you you watched Fallout so now you
should uh get the reference when I say
Sandy Shores Sandy Shores yeah did you
did you watch it till the end I did of
course oh my god let's go yeah I also
finished Shogun as well oh damn I've
been kind of like I I'm like three
episodes before the end I think I'm just
kind of waiting right now because I'm
not feeling uh like a serious Vibe right
now when I'm going to bed and want to
watch something you know sometimes you
want to watch some brain empty stuff and
sometimes you want to watch some cool
stuff I get
you I get you no it's it's definitely
get it's serious like it's a freaking
serious oh I'm going to die of hunger
it's a oh no there's a lot going on that
series is great though I watch it just
en raptured cuz it's so
cool
yeah I was I was so shocked
when okay I'm not going to say anything
that's like spoilerish really right but
you remember that moment in shun where
um they uh what was it a pheasant or so
that he had hanging outside his door and
it was like stinky and then somebody
took it down and they were you know yeah
punished for that that was like what the
[\h__\h] is happening yeah I don't think
that it I mean I guess that's just how
it was
though mean they were so serious about
everything they take it so serious like
don't touch it or you you know yeah
don't take it so serious he he couldn't
speak the nongo he wasn't nongo Jes so
he's just trying to speak in simple
words he didn't really know what he was
saying yeah I mean they kind of should
have realized but I think I understand
why they had that part in there you know
to kind of be like yo serious [\h__\h] being
in Japan at that time right like people
weren't messing around you know that's
the vibe that I got wait sorry I think I
need to do a quick intro cuz I just
switched to the gaming
screen you guys may have already been
seeing me on on kaop stream I was just
you know chilling and uh preparing the
stream excuse
me but we are so back aren't we CI oh
yeah but we're back big time and today I
got shaders oh my God it looks so pretty
nice W you're glowing Callie you're
glowing and shiny do I look radiant
right now amazingly even though you
don't look at me pretty yeah so if you
want I can go right away uh give you a
tour sure let me drop this away let me
drop this in the end Drop it like it's
hot Drop it like it's hot boys and then
we'll go ahead and take a look at what
you guys did cuz I have no clue what
anyone did at all
yeah I know it all I know everything ye
all right show me what you guys got down
to business with cuz I want to know okay
so yesterday I started alone for 30
minutes and that created some chaos I
unfortunately had to explode some things
because creepers were everywhere in the
beginning um and that resulted in some
issues here you may have noticed the
merchants and so on are gone yeah
they're all super dead yeah they were
eaten by zombies and this is a big
problem because we need
Merchants villagers again villagers true
so but the thing is like they spawned
only in specific phases so our job
yesterday was we were in Phase seven and
there were 10 so we were mining for
hours those last three phases took a
while um so that we can Circle back but
turns out it doesn't Circle back it's
just like after 10 phases it gives you
all phases at once so the pool of blocks
and things you can get from mining now
is way bigger than in a single phase you
know what I mean cuz it's All Phases
combined yeah so the chances of us
getting what we really want is lower now
but at the same time we can get
everything okay at once yeah that's
chaotic as hell yeah and then uh we
noticed
um
some uh things uh that could be improved
here this is still the mining area this
this block here in between the chocolate
blocks is the one you mine uh I'm going
to build like something where uh it goes
immediately into a chest here through
the water so our what was the actual
purpose I think
because our inventories were always full
I don't know I don't know anymore but
yeah now it's looking really chocolatey
and nice and then you can like click on
the chest here on the side and like
there's more to sort For You O exciting
so the there's a lot in there cool I
don't even know how do people even get
the mechanism that's crazy I don't oh
she worked on a while on it yeah wow and
then besides this contraption we have
another new one I saw you already were
standing here but didn't notice what it
was what is this this is a cobblestone
generator that uh Gooby created
surprisingly she made it wow basically I
think maybe you know that stone in
between the lava and the water you mine
that and you get endless Cobblestone
trying okay I think I can actually see
how it works cuz of the lava and
water yeah it takes a second but I feel
like it gets faster yeah yeah cool
endless cobbly Stone nice one goo yeah
so for like building if we need to build
paths or whatever this is maybe a good
option and then there's some extra
Stacks in this chest here cool are we
able to replace the floor do you think
is their floor we shouldn't
replace M oh generally it's always good
to for example replace these wooden
floors here Stone floors so that they
don't
burn yeah um the grass I would keep the
grassy blocks I would keep because we
need some grassy blocks anyway to grow
the trees right the trees also have uh
experienced some [\h__\h] yesterday like oh
no not my Forest
big holes yeah a lot of big holes here
and then the trees were gone and then we
had to replace it all yeah this is not a
normal freaking tree what happened here
oh that's like a big like what do you
call it again dark oak dark oak o they
grow really thick yeah but when you when
you plant them if you happen to mine
them and you want to plant them again um
like from the leaves they will drop the
little thingies right um but you have to
plant this one in like
like a four um space thingy like 1 2 3
four um next to each other uh you know
what I mean uh what's it 4x4 4X four
yeah or actually 2 by two but I for me
it's like four because you oh I get you
it's four yeah I see why don't we just
plant a bunch of those I feel like
that's most efficient app we don't even
have that much space you see it's
already pretty cramped if we can get
this uh area stand it yeah that would be
fine but we don't have that many dirt
blocks either I wish we could generate
dirt blocks yeah oh see there's grass
going a few yeah maybe I can go find
some dirt blocks around here and replace
it's okay I don't even think this takes
priority um I think uh the Sorting for
now takes pry also you like fishing
right I do I'm a big Fisher we fishing
rods now or or the capability of making
them and uh I'mma made a fishing pond
next to the watermelon space There's
real fish in there feel like fishing
yeah cuz like we've been running out of
food the whole time too is what we've
noticed yeah that's pretty so fish is
pretty good at the moment yeah that
would be a good idea
honestly the green horses by the way are
zombie horses that are only in creative
mode um they somehow spawned as as well
you will never see them in a normal
legit playthrough of Minecraft
really and they're they're non
hostile yeah they're fine they Dro
zombie meat when you kill
them they're so
fancy wow a lot of good stuff and then
yesterday am was struck by lightning
that was really funny cool yeah that is
pretty funny yeah and we got some new
pandas we had some panda babies and yeah
I don't know they're just chilling here
well what did they do for the cause how
do they earn their
keep honestly it's just like in real
life it's just they're cute and that's
how they earn their right to live on God
really they're not like they're not
lifting any of the heavy weight for us
really absolutely nothing can be gained
from their existence here then I think
we should murdered them in Cold Blood no
no no no no they're taking up space here
we going have cows there that would be
really
sad I won't touch him
but you guys better your days are
numbered all right your days are
freaking
numbered I don't think they like me they
hear the mean things I'm saying about
them it's fine that's not a threat
that's a promise panda bears I
promise let's see what we got in here
that I can
sort uh um I'll just grab everything and
just start soring it
out and Bone blocks I wonder where bone
blocks would go
into bone blocks you
can I've been making a lot of those into
bone meal but I think we have enough
bone meal for now oh yeah should be
fine Quartz in here oh you know what I
want to make Ys I want to make a trash
can um
see I killed one Phantom do you still
have the Phantom noises over on your
side I think they're gone now but I'm
not totally sure
okay now the cats will finally shut up
let's go I hear no more hsing yeah those
cats were pissed I tell you what
yeah let's
go any other iron or should we mine for
some more iron oh I just kidding iron
okay great uh yeah yeah yeah generally
iron so I think you read on the board
diamond armor diamond tools and all that
but before that we don't even have a
full set of iron armor that would
probably be our priority before making
Diamond okay that sounds good you
welcome for killing the Phantom
everybody you're welcome yesterday they
were also like constantly hissing and
screaming oh yeah crazy the cats they're
not very happy kitty cats uh-uh not
happy
definitely not feeling it hey why can't
I make a cauldron I
wonder a c a cauldron yeah cuz that's uh
you put the lava in it and that's how
you make a trash can oh okay okay okay
but that exist in this one uh stuff
that's just gets in the way in the
inventory don't throw away too much
though we might need like a lot of
things yeah of course not there are some
things that just like get in the
way boy loves trash cans I don't know I
don't know how to defend myself from
that I know it's wasteful it's wasteful
my how could you how could you but hear
me out hear me out some things are just
yucky to look
at panda bears we we could throw the
panda bears in the fire if you guys want
me
meow me out could throw the panda bears
in there
yeah yeah oh yeah I mean they're just
getting way they're too fake for it I
think I know I just I feel like you know
we're becoming hoarders Kiara we can't
we can't let that happen you know we
become hoarders it's hoing the pandas
the hoarding things the pandas the
pandas serve as trash can for the
bamboo yeah I mean I guess so but and
why do we need to get the bamboo isn't
entirely useless to us either cuz we can
make with them
oh yeah that's a good point maybe we
should not get rid of see that has a
purpose I see the purpose
there let's go I can make us some beds
not through wool but for spider silk we
making beds now our first beds need some
plants finally I didn't even know until
last night's Super Chat reading that we
can make beds out of spider soap I think
someone mentioned it once I don't know
if it was G or Ena but we were all kind
of preoccupied and I wasn't really
sure you know not
certain uh let's see well I like the
idea of Let's Make A let's make armor
and whatnot so I'd like to mine for
stuff but we have to be mindful of you
know enemies I might I might mine a
little bit here and there yeah sure I
think y we got fed we can sleep for the
night now oh yeah I'm I'm going to into
that house oh my
God n
n what's he doing here oh he's chilling
oh he's so
glowing does he help us he's just
jilling
he he he as long as we don't look at him
don't look at him okay yeah sounds good
what the parrots
they're looking at him and he's not
attacking them double standard
much thing is on my side they are only
heads they have no bodies oh might have
something to do with the
shaders yeah the shaders did not account
for
parrots what is this is this stuff for
stuff we find in the forest like uh
saplings flowers Etc uh yeah that chest
on the on the pumpkin that's basically
the forest chest for now if we want to
plant more trees
I see some not food in the food chest oh
and the the floor um underground has
been built yesterday too oh nice so like
for example if you accidentally like
because we had accidents where right I
think you were there actually when
somebody mines the ground that you're
standing on to replace the floor and
then the person who stands there
innocently falls down into the void that
might happen there a situation yeah that
can be avoided M stuff like that or when
may yeah or when a gas shoots their fire
onto the wooden floor and it all burns
down yeah that's not now we have a floor
below so it will catch us and we will
not fall die fall and die that's good
avoid the void avoid the void hey don't
have to tell me twice sounds good to me
yeah I I guess I could have been told
once but that's okay oh and we have a a
DJ mixing old thingy now o so we can
play music do you hear it yeah I hear it
turn down
haunting beautiful now we can make use
of the CDs that we have yeah that's
right if I remember correctly also um
golden armor is not very good is it yeah
golden armor we might need just like one
piece each if we go into the one piece
is real if we go into the Le sounds good
well I'll cook some but there's not
really a reason to cook too much gold is
there aside from you know that one set I
mean
yeah I don't want to waste too much
coal it's fine okay oh you're
doing may an iron
F yes yes yes yes my God should I use
some iron for an iron pickaxe K where do
you want me to put the last two pieces
of wool that I have in my hand that's a
good question I haven't really decided
where wool was supposed to go but since
we're not using much of this PLS chest
and where was it um the bottom one here
it's kind of empty so I'm thinking we
can repurpose that something else see
think we can make another bed yeah the
there's free I'll make one more yeah
don't you mean I
Ron you
talking I run say I earn
money yeah earn the money no you now
you're see I see what you're trying to
do
gaha what game you're trying to get out
of saying the word iron correctly aren't
you you little rascal I
iron even if I figure it out like now I
think I was still default to naturally
saying iron because that's just what I'm
used to she's too conditioned to it now
we've lost her it is what it is
[Music]
ocean chest soon there will be five beds
here and we can
cuddle yeah with all of
this sleepover party just like is the
day
yay yeah this whole storage room is kind
of not I mean I liked the idea in the
beginning but now that all the items and
that we're we're mixing they're all
mixed up now right so like jungle and
desert and ocean so it becomes a lot
more
difficult no it's fine though it's fine
make it
work into the Sorting chest chest very
very serious about the Sorting in
this all right let's see what's in
here this bow is special but this needs
to be in the weapons chest
[Music]
see those we got get in
there feed sou oh man so many food items
turn into soup but I feel like soup is
so unpopular in Minecraft cuz of the
bowls that don't stack until
you yeah it just takes up so much space
yeah I'd never want to do that or use
that that's horrific yeah kidding me
well we don't have much choice at the
moment true enough besides eating
soup I guess so I do be like that it's
okay I mean I love soup IRL IRL is nice
super stick yum
yum I'm going to how you doing Cali by
the way oh I'm alive you know living day
today still trying to heal but you know
we'll get there get there eventually
yeah I'll get there taking your meds of
course of course I am take your meds
Kelly like legit take him I'm taking
only as the doctor has recommended only
doctor recommended not too much not too
little of course of course not good yep
yep I'm doing my physical therapy
serious thing oh for
sure y i not the doctor recommends
I shall destroy because you're going to
eat animals aren't you who needs to be
killed sorry
horse all little little what was it a
wolf or a
fox the dying animal noises do be
popping off these
days o what's that down there I think
what do you guys build the horses that
spawn here will not like suffer anymore
what down where under here that's where
I went down to build the underground o
the second floor for SA
I see that there's like a portal or
something like that being made oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah that's
because we already went to Phase 10 and
when you're done with all the phases
once it spawns the um the portal to the
end cool automatically right under this
one block oh should I put the sand back
was it supposed to be a SL sand slabs
here in here
uh this it doesn't have to be sand I
think no no okay
I just want to make sure that I'm not
messing it up no no no but yeah we we're
in FY already we can go to the end as
soon as we have more ender pearls
thingies but we're just severely not
ready see where's the block is it the
sand or which one is it oh the
chest see M the block to mine you mean
that's ch please sort oh boy all right
get to sorting immediately oh my god
this is my future this is my
soul this is my soul kill the bunny now
there's a bunny hey bunny can what did
he do to
you I think the bunny's oh I think it
already escaped
huh your terracotta
chest see
oh no oh no it's going to it's going to
don't jump bunny I know that's your
thing but don't jump I hope you guys
like
where concrete powder that probably goes
here okay
wood yeah if you do happen to mine uh at
the one block later um just so you know
the blocks are now like they're going
into the chest first rather than going
to you so you got to also check if the
chest is full I
see otherwise they won't go inside the
chest yeah cuz now it's
full I see I
see let's see all right so looks like
we're going to need a bigger terracotta
chest is this an ocean chest all right I
know what I can do I'll need one more
ocean chest okie
[Music]
dokie see oh this can go here
ocean shaders look nice they
do even like in normal version Minecraft
I haven't been using shaders recently
cuz I was too lazy to update my
OptiFine ah that'll do
fun but I did it now just for this nice
so that I can take a nice screenshot and
put it on my
thumbnail that's the main
reason oh yeah c
I key remember a while ago I asked
you not not that long ago I asked you
what your favorite cuz you told me you
like bakat I was like what the [\h__\h]
who's your favorite bakat character and
you said n and then like one or two
weeks later I see your collaboration and
I was like well well well this lady no
wonder you like Nal yeah no that was a
coolen iny dink that was a total
coincidence yeah W how was it like
talking to her I was very nervous so I
didn't really say much but I was like
excited to work with you and I got to
you know watch your record some of the
song and then I recorded this song it
was cool it was it was really fun she a
legend she is a legend so I was very
doky doie um my favorite role of hers is
actually in an anime called
psychopath um a she's uh she's the the
main character of that so that was like
where I first encountered her and so I
was just very docky docky so doy doie
yeah but I I didn't really what does she
think of YouTubers I know she seemed
pretty like naughty naughty about it
like you know cool and stuff like that I
mean she did the um the commercials uh
for for what was it the the Expo right
like they had a couple like uh you know
Tik Tok yoube shorts commercials that
were like kind of animated there was to
sama essential Chloe
and yeah she not animated those she she
narrated those yeah oh like I think that
she had kind of you know encountered us
before so she kind of knew about it but
tell me about working with her tell me
more it was really cool I gave her you
know my CD and she gave me her CD that
was cool a I was like wow you can give
this to me yeah it's very doy doy it's
such a like unexpected collaboration
honestly to me I was like what as well
but I mean um you know the the producer
joint Beauty has done some tracks for my
new album and I guess you know was
releasing his own album and was like oh
I want I want two singers on this one
song I wonder who would be interesting
to put together um and and for some
reason he thought of the two of us so
that's so Random I know I thought so too
but I was kind of like okay cool yeah
did you talk did you tell her that you
watched bonali I did of course but I
didn't I didn't Fang girl too too much
about it I would have I would have man
oh I would love to tell her that I love
I'm currently re-watching like all the
seasons because the new season is
finally coming oh yeah I need to rewatch
it I completely it's been so many years
there's been so many years yeah same
same like I forgot so many things about
it too oh yeah I was surprised about how
how yeah how how loot the loot moments
are but I mean they're also humorous and
you know yeah know the first time that I
ever watched bakim manari I like I think
I dropped it after the first two
episodes because it was a time that is a
big be um it was a it was there's a time
in my life where I was just very like
adverse to fan service and whatnot but
then I grew up
I was like I don't care and then I
watched it really for me it's the
opposite I was okay with it back then
and now I'm like I I can't I cringe at
it kind of that's pretty funny but for
Bak mon like it's it has the the bonus
of being like my favorite since forever
and you know nostalgic Vibes and the
characters are just so intricate and the
way they all get together like you get
to know them first one by one and then
it all becomes one Tangled St story like
a spider love that and that's just like
the super cool thing
about for me know it all comes together
I really like stories that have like a
big ensemble cast that you get to know
over time so
mmhm like I don't think I've ever felt
so into deep deep into a story like so
what's the word
um when you're when you're really into
something en rapture ing maybe that's a
little too complicated okay okay and
rapturing let's go student I'm sorry I
can't help myself invested invested and
invers is what I
meant what am I talking
about whoopsy doodle yeah I think yeah
mon got Daddy series is like just so so
so un rapturing and I when I was
watching it with my viewers and some of
them saw have been seeing it for the
first time now they were also like hm
okay interesting but like you got to
give it some time until like all the all
the all the cobwebs all the spider silks
they get together and then you're like
wo wo wo wo MH yeah but they've
certainly been enjoying the spicy uh
moments I can see all the AOS in your
chat right
now it kind of makes it more fun
though yeah makes it more fun doe
acrobat please shut up I'm talking with
my friend right now
um yeah what about besides n who else
did you
likeii over you're actually bringing up
a guy rather than one of the million
girls I know I know it hurts everyone to
hear that but I think aogi is such a g
if I could say that what a gangster what
a cool guy I've been like honestly the
more like I watch it now the more I
dislike him why he's cool he's such a
douche know why I like
him I I love his um hold on AOG sorry I
really need to make sure I say the right
freaking one um yeah I also like
Coten coton yeah she's so
fun she's so motivated
mhm oh
yeah all right CH yeah goty right
yeah don't tell me that that's why you
like
her there's more to it right OB of
course but when I think of her I mean I
can't help that that's the
first than just that scene sorry but
that's the first thing my mind flashes
to I can't help dental hygiene is
important I'm sorry else man she's more
than just that she's a really great
sister for justice you know fire sisters
she fights for justice now kiaha I did
not say that she wasn't I did not say
that and she was not I'm just saying
that that was that's sticks out my
mind that's all that it is them
grow let's see I really want to mine for
some
diamonds we need to this is actually
really ridiculous and mine for diamonds
that's just mining at that block over
there but don't worry about mining right
now yeah cuz now like there's how many
blocks is it that you could get out of
that it's the 10 phases combined so it's
like everything so the chance to get
diamonds is pretty low now that is true
I guess the best thing I can do is just
try to organize as much as I can so we
can keep
mining yeah um but I think do we have
some dirt somewhere um let's see 20
block of dirt farming yeah there's 20
blocks of dirt in the chest um which one
the the one block chest yeah okay okay
okay yeah go grab it um and uh we need a
bigger field I love all these terracotta
blocks I just can't think for the of me
what we use them for oh yeah when we get
a merchant um we can trade our emeralds
for diamonds and stuff I guess oh yeah
diamond armor we want to hold on to
emeralds too I'm
guessing yes yes yes yes yes do you have
any bgm playing yaha oh I need to put
the this thing back on mate I feel like
no bgm is like kind of a trend or
whatever so I was like I'm not going to
put bgm I think for collabs like this I
don't mind it being quiet cuz we're
talking anyway and there's MC stuff
going on so yeah exactly there's
Minecraft things happening it's
fine where
Mar get rid of this or should I just
make it somewhere else I CU this a small
space sound got here Flint that's fine
actually why don't I just build
T we have so much wood
it's good though good work I'll make
another one
[Music]
maybe
here I'll make a new place and yeah make
it right although can I
even I guess if I
make I have an idea I have an
idea let me know if you want me to help
you with something cuz I'm
available okay I'm just sorting things
can
you wait in a in a moment
actually I need you to just stand there
so I see where you stand from below okay
and then I'll make a hole under so I can
put water there you get what I'm trying
to do Chad so I can just use this cuz
water needs to be there but if there's
no you know you know you know there
needs to be a pool of water there sure
you just tell me where to go boss I'll
make it happen
mhm what do we want to extend what what
kind of C you would know yeah what
blocks do we have so many
of oh maybe that it's really annoying
well Stone yeah then I can use terra
cotta no terracotta too much terra cotta
yeah go go grab it from the Terra Cotta
chest there's so much it makes me want
to die which one's the Terra Cota chest
um it's you'll find it it's full of the
Decora it's so
pretty it is a pretty one I'm going to
cook some of this fish can't eat the
tropical fish can we no I don't think so
yo game come on hungry we're starving
here yeah I watched oh yeah wait no I
didn't watch this is not a reality I I
just thought for a moment that da the D
was reality uh but in D the diap they
make sushi out of unusual fish like
tropical fish and that's really cool
that's a really Co I learned so much
about be M oh from Dave the
diver yeah yeah that's a fun one I just
play that on my own yeah follow me okay
I'm chopping on a fish I'm on my way
though I'm coming all right maybe where
would be good stand um stand right where
I'm standing right now okay gotcha on
this block and then after uh that that
when I say next you go like a little bit
like further ahead maybe next to the
torch okay and then stand there too okay
yeah Okie doie
riveting job you got oh yeah I'm just
happy to be helpful I'm happy to be of
service yeah I'm being helpful guys I
see name and then I know where I got to
go from below I'm underground Kell oh
yeah oh I see working on that second
level eight yeah extending it a bit
further so oopsie Then I then I'll make
a hole where you stand and then then
I'll put another block there and then I
put water there it's I don't know how to
explain you will see when it happens oh
okay is everything water elevators or
can we make some stairs cuz you know
your boy likes stairs cuz stairs arefe I
the chat tell you to do that no they
didn't cuz they've been telling me to
well now I'm going to tell you to I like
stairs CU I like the insurance of stairs
you can totally make stairs uh if you
feel like it see you can put that on
your he called you a coward I Kiara I'm
a coward so well you see coward I'm a
Kiara so I'm gonna put some stairs down
okay no
problem are you there okay misu hydrate
P oh the bunny's on the second level
what the hell how do you get down it's
all alone down here that's so scary you
fall down the waterfall what's he doing
there make a pocket of water to sit in I
see pocket of water to sit in yeah what
is Kiara
planning making a second bigger Farm
there oh my cat um but yeah you are
you're where you're standing is where
I'm going to put the water okay but I
just need you um so
yeah I need to make a hole where you
stand okay we're staring at the
sunset I'm I'm I'm getting there n Kiara
is working I'm staring at the sunset
because I have nothing else to
do well tell me a story tell me
something about your break my break
let's see what did I do damn it I sat
down and I only watched a lot of anime
um MH yeah one of the ones that I
watched was I watched the entirety of an
an so my mother first I'll start it here
my mother um and my my stepfather love
mommy yeah she's great she was watching
Netflix with um with stepdad and um and
they found a movie that they loved so
much they had to tell me about it and
they said little Mory you got to watch
this movie called Golden Kami and and
I'm like oh I'm like um how do you know
that and they're like we watched the
movie it was so good well it's cuz they
watched the live action and they thought
it was incredible um and I was like all
right so I decided to check it out and I
marathoned the whole anime cuz I really
liked it a lot and I was very excited to
tell my friend about it um who I you
know talked to about anime and whatnot
from high school and I tell my friend
about it and she says Mory that's an
anime for men only men like that anime
only older dudes like that anime I don't
think that you can say that about any
anime even if they're like shjo or Shen
anime like it's very common that the
other render will watch it anyway see
that's what I was saying too I was like
well this is also my friend who's not a
big JoJo fan um and I feel like I feel
like you know they're not the same but I
can see why why maybe she wasn't into
it yeah I need torches okay I'll make
torches the golden comy fan base is
predominantly female see I wish I'd
known that so I could have told so I
could have told there are some moments
in that show where I'm like oh my God
they like went for it like like you'll
just be about so it's it's like a kind
of historical historical uh Japanese
anime it's like an old like um Hokkaido
story um story yeah there's like this um
this Japanese soldier guy guy um named
Su Modo and he's really cool and he
helps this girl um like get it's it's
kind of hard to explain but um it has a
lot to do with um like the the you know
um old Japanese reishi um and like the
the IU of uh Hulk kaido and there's this
gold um that that was hidden and it's
there there a bunch of people trying to
get it and everybody wants the gold I'm
terrible at explaining things but that
gold it belongs to the IU you know
hidden gold bloody Chase yeah exactly so
he he teams up with this this I knew
girl and they go to find the gold but
all these other dudes want it these like
other military Bros and then like the
Shen s are involved and stuff like that
and it's it gets really intense but it's
it's super good I like it a lot I'm a
big fan of it seems like you remember it
so well yeah I mean I did just I did
just finish it yeah um it's so wait wait
why did your why did they know it
because they watched the live action on
Netflix and just watched it like it was
a normal
movie not based on an anime or
anything yeah oh yeah the the map to the
gold is tattooed on the prisoners and
they have to skin the prisoners to get
the map to find the
gold but like the girl doesn't want to
kill anyone yeah it's it's interesting I
like I like that a lot but like
sometimes there there will just be dudes
like all together and then all of a
sudden they're all just naked together
like posing with like Rippling muscles
and it's like why did they decide to do
this but at the same time let's let's go
oh yeah oh okay almost I got a dirt
block yeah yeah okay I'm making maybe
I'll just how how about I make a whole
line nah okay go next okay uh to the
torch yeah okay this is it the one over
here maybe I guess so yeah the one
that's next to the tree oh yeah yeah
then that's this one it's hard actually
to tell where you are
standing is it here yeah yeah that's
hello ma'am it's here hello Madam this
is you welcome to the underground
welcome to the
underground so that should that should
be sufficient yeah D let me show you the
way out no problem wagon Fon let's
go the only ger I know it's kind of
dangerous but you go in here and you
press uh space to go up all right do I
hold it or do I press it once yeah hold
it hold it hold it okay please please
God yeah see it's easy
okay cool oh yeah wait they said I have
torches I do have torches let's go all
right I and I used some of the pretty
terracotta yay yay y now cie feels happy
that the Terracotta is
gone we have too much of it we have to
get rid of
it oh yeah I'm sure I'll talk more about
Golden comedy during zadan streams you
guys I have lots of feelings about
Golden comedy I really liked it what
what about you what have you been
watching recently aside from rewatching
monari uh well shun and I finished
Fallout recently and apparently today I
thought it was next week for some reason
but apparently today the new house of
the Dragon season is coming out oh my
God I think at like 3:00 a.m. in the
night for me you going to wake up and
watch it no I I'll watch like when I
wake up uh like hours after yeah no need
to get up super
early yeah are you going to watch it me
House of the Dragon is that um Game of
Thrones yeah Game of Thrones uh prequel
that's right yeah I need to watch Game
of Thrones
first oh my God why are you all not
watching Game of Thrones What Game of
Thrones what is what's
why I mean I I want to now that I finish
Shogun and people are like oh shogun's
like Japanese Game of Thrones What I'm
like oh well then maybe I Game of
Thrones ja's Game of Thrones no no I
would not call it that that's what I
keep hearing people saying I'm like are
you
sure you think that's not accurate yeah
nah
nah never would say that it's good but
the ending I mean well yeah of course I
know about the ending not being first
five seasons are great maybe read it
some people say read
it by the way guys I'm doing this some
purpose I just want to get rid of some
of the bamboo cuz feel like we don't
need it everywhere in our
face
see oh yeah I feel sad that we can't get
more diam you know actually we do have
30 diamonds that's pretty good I'd like
to get more I think maybe you can um if
you're done sorting if you don't want to
do that anymore you can just mine a
little bit we we really need to mine and
mine and find a sheep sheep is really
important villager really important any
any Merchant Trader is really important
right
got yeah sounds good oh damn okay okay
so it's this one right ah and if you see
something like obsidian that for that
you need the diamond pickaxe it's in the
chest oh okay gotcha the tools sounds
good yeah for now I'll use
iron should be good [\h__\h]
it yeah
oh hello oh should we kill this
guy uh oh what who the hell oh is a
Pillager I think is he yeah so we so we
rattle
him yeah yeah kill him make him regret
living it's so hard to get out of
here once you're in once you're in it's
hard to get out let's see oh
emeralds oh creeper head nice that's
good oh oh you got a chest nice H I love
when the chest spawn it's so fun it's
like o what's
inside lots of gold and then we also got
what's this enchanted book
impaling oh yeah enant enchanted book
mhm
impaling wa which is pretty cool I wish
that it it was something maybe a little
more useful to our cause but you think
that's a good one
or um my impaling was that for was that
for Trident yeah good I wanted to try it
maybe we'll somehow get one okay well we
can save the book oh we're going to need
a chest for books
now boy oh boy boy for the one book for
a single book oh nice obsidian okay I'll
go grab the diamond pickaxe oh yes yes
yes
okay then I will put it back I will put
it back because this is a
treasure well I've been using it a lot
even when I shouldn't have oh
that's okay that's okay forgive
forgiveness try to use
Stone occasionally I'll switch back to
yeah for IR that's fine we do need more
iron thankfully though we're getting
some iron here so that's good oh you
guys going into the chest yes or
no okay we still have some some more we
can
mine good good
good yeah yeah yeah yeah the issue
really is that like those first phases
where we got those things like sheep and
all that we really had we we should have
but you know now we know better we
should have protected them better so
don't that we don't lose them because
now getting them now is really difficult
ah yeah which is a
shame here we
go yeah that's okay though we'll get
we'll find one m just have to be really
careful when it spawns in you
know it'll be fine is that a diamond
nice oh emerald and then enchanted book
infinity and enchanted book aqua
affinity yeah we're getting enchanted
books now damn you getting all the fancy
books maybe it's cuz your boy really
lucky I don't know
h i yeah maybe sheep aren't such a
important thing anymore now actually
because I I did make some beds with the
uh spider silk sure enough it would be
nice if we could all if we could all
sleep at the same time to like get
through a night or something like that
you know yeah and when
um in cases where for example uh a bed
would burn down or somebody dies with
their bed or so you know then we need
another one yeah then we need another
one yep that's a good point
oh uh ohy doodle I think the chest is
full so I'll go ahead
and yeah I'll figure this sort it out
baby sort it leave it to me block of
diamond can we turn that into
diamonds uh yeah block of diamonds yeah
block of diamond you mean a n you mean
just a you don't mean a full block of
diamonds where are you I'll show you it
says block of
diamond here I'll show it to you you can
have it
what the [\h__\h] you that was mined yeah oh
my god let's go yay we're going to put
that in here for safety that's nine
diamonds that's nine diamonds in one go
wow luck 100 today I guess guys yay it's
cuz it's my first time streaming that's
why first it's my first time streaming
one block that's why yay yay good
stuff get some more and uh let's
see
Brick
okay
okay yum maybe I should make a few more
water sources here guys right is not not
enough I am start you
Valley W
torch build basement so you're building
the basement right
I it's already there but I might keep on
extending it okay sounds good we'll turn
this into the enchantment chest okay
rename this though water lets you plant
four blocks in all directions
yeah come
on hey guys if I want to rewrite
something on a sign I'm sure you know
this C if I want to rewrite something on
a sign I have to remake the sign right I
think you have to take it off dang it
that's fine I can't people said you can
rewrite without taking it off but
honestly I could not figure out how just
take it off it's fine it's is cool I'm a
big stupid dummy can't think oh yeah
it's in this version of Minecraft like
in newer Minecraft you can change it
while it's still on there I
see that's why we weren't used to it
books yeah enchant we can put books in
there too I think that that
fits oh gy okay um I can go ahead and
cook this iron
[Music]
actually and emeralds of course make a
fence
here I hope I hope nobody will fall down
hey fingers crossed fingers
[Music]
crossed well oh Enchanted only happy
accidents but of course and what do we
need bone meal for by the
way uh to grow things faster like like
the trees and the crops or anything I'll
put that in the item box with the glow
stone dust Redstone
Dust we don't have a ton of room in here
but let's
see I know where I can put these
things
okay need pickaxe I will make pickaxe I
love organizing I hope you guys are
enjoying watching the endlessly
organized I'm so glad you're up for that
yeah I'm fine with it I didn't know I
really couldn't care about doing it I
didn't know that it was a legitimate
like thing that needed to be done
here I'm glad that's like one big thing
that people enjoy in Minecraft too no
yeah I guess so like crony is also a big
organizer oh really I didn't know that I
once hired her for a whole collab
Minecraft stream to organize my ve e
really that's smart yeah what the heck
and she did it with pleasure nice I need
delighted the heck oh
crony yeah croner does have those vibes
yeah she
does yeah she does I love her for
it right let's see one done I love this
little creeper head he jump scares me
every time I turn around
creeper head yeah a creeper head was in
the the chest that I
found
yeah n yeah so
weird I just set him down
somewhere yum y Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum
you were scared for a moment yeah this
looks like a DreamWorks Sky oh
yeah on my side at least of shaders
which one are you using are you using um
what is it I it's called silder oh
silder that's a new one that I've never
heard of I've been using it for years
yeah so not OP so many shaders yeah
silder and OptiFine together because
OptiFine is just to make everything run
smoother I
see one 2 3 4 oh this is actually fun
one two three oh I can make another one
here more terra cotta bye-bye feel free
to use more of this terra cotta cuz we
got lots of it oh yeah two three this
will be become dirt too at some point
one two three four oh this didn't have
to be there but that's okay Wonder okay
wonderful that's actually that goes
really far with just these two little
pieces of uh water huh sir nice we're
going to get a big efficient Farm I want
especially SE wheat uh cuz we want the
bread go get the bread get the bread
sounds good to me mhm always use more
bread and then we'll make I don't like
pumpkins cuz there's so big beetroots
also honestly [\h__\h] yeah there's a lot
of pumpkins here I'm kind of like why do
we need
them I don't want those pumpkins like
watermelons are okay because watermelons
you can eat like that without making it
into a soup I just want efficient food
you know I get you I
agree maybe I'll use some bone meal to
grow the crops H nice idea uh is there
more than just these 19 do did you put
them somewhere no it's in the item box I
think they fit better in the item box
instead of the ore box okay I put there
item box there yeah it's the top one
right there okay
okay D no problem oh now playing me
money yeah I'm too lazy to change the CD
but if you feel like it you can change
the CDs too let's see do they have the
cat one let see cat one yeah it's called
cat or something I forget M Maul could
be
fun let's try Mall although you can eat
the beetroots raw right Wonder
okay like this
one this one's chill wait how do you
plant melons properly can I plant them
anywhere here but don't they need space
around it so if I put it here can it
grow next right next to the water is
maybe not
good tell me Chad tell me dad always
knows the
answer
see plant it on the side one block next
to it has okay okay
okay maybe
maybe I can make a ceiling so that I can
put more torches there I don't want to
take up the space of the for now I can
go
here wow this music is good yeah it's
good right is it chill it's my fave hell
yeah it gets a little loud though so I
might need to turn
down only when I'm close to the
Jukebox oh you can turn down the bgm the
like jukebox music in the settings
just the Jukebox music jukebox okay
gotcha there we
go Farming Simulator let's go
farming yeah I totally forgot that you
can really like Farm a lot in in
Minecraft like Farming Farming there's
so many things you can
farm so many crops and animals so much
variety like planting berries and stuff
like
that yeah
berries although berries are I think
mostly berries get ignored because they
don't heal that much
and yeah they don't I don't think people
really see them as crops in Minecraft
usually oh I
see berries yeah berries see you see
this guys you see this how how efficient
this is I'm making a big brand
Farm maybe no watermelons needed yeah
got lots of wheat what not take some
bread get that
bread although generally we don't even
lose that much
hunger but anyway I still think we need
more food understandable especially if
you know enemies come out and stuff like
that and then they you know F us up and
stuff yeah it's bad that happened a lot
that did happen oh yeah a l
yesterday yeah there it was so funny um
you remember the shulker Box enemies
that like spit at you and then you fly
oh yeah those uh showed up in the 10th
phase yesterday and every like it felt
like every 10th block that we mined a
Shuler box appeared and it sent us all
flying God it was so funny and then am
she had a fishing rod so she can
actually this is possible it was funny
she threw the fishing rod at us up in
the sky and she held us like a balloon
oh my God that's so cool I got to go
watch that that sounds
insane that was fun it was like a what
do you call um I uh the the fun
fairs oh the fun fairs yeah like at a
carnival or something like that yeah
yeah yeah a state fair kind of ride or
something they swing you around
yeah yeah Carnival Carnival kind of
things also just got a block of emerald
too wow okay not so bad actually to get
all these blocks I don't think we got
full on blocks before yeah it must be a
new thing are you going into the go into
the Hey DJ the music is already off hey
what the heck DJ turn it back on again
and Mr DJ jump on
the and Mr Magic want to turn the m and
Mr D want to turn the music up it's a
Rihanna song an old one
oh I feel like I've heard it before
those lyrics are familiar like one of
the first
ones fck a day P the
replay p p p p p
replay do every time you want to play
music do you have to go back and punch
it
yeah I wish you could like put a queue
on it right it's very
inefficient this is my favorite track
though
I think it this one feels kind of short
yeah it is why it ended so fast a shorty
but a goodie oh hello cow short King
short King wow got AOW already half a
field what should we do with the
cow you got a cow nice can you try to
wait what do cows eat again chat is it
wheat because now we have wheat come on
buddy um we want to lead it to the farm
and keep it safe there sure are let me
see let me I have I know where
IAT ah there is I think one piece of
wheat in the food chest but I got some
more if you need it all good I'll just
hold it and leave
him yeah buddy come here no you want
this weed I'll open the door for you no
you want this
weed you know you want it know you want
this
weed come on know you want this wheat oh
is it having a hard time getting out of
there yeah I think he's he's just a
little stuck I'll try to push it give
him a push I maybe it's the wrong way
can you try leading him around the
corner of like like here sure we just
get rid of the block for one moment
actually that might be better
okay wait I you can lead him I'll get
rid of the block sure as soon as I can
jump out of this hell hole that I'm in
hold on a second let me out let me out
or the or this door a this door wait may
be stuck might be a little tra a young
cow yeah it's difficult to get out get
go try to go here to the red block
thingy the red block behind yeah yeah
yeah here uh-huh
okay let me kind of It's Tricky there we
go it is a little tricky yeah that's
fine okay can it move now or does it
need the help n it needs okay Budd I
broke it let's go I know you want this
weed see how hold this weed why does he
want follow why don't you want my wheat
come on that is wheat you guys said it
it's wheat right go go follow her follow
guess we'll push it guess we can push it
we push it all right we pushing him we
got to go this way Budd we do have
leashes
yeah slap the cow we want him to feel
safe oh oh now you want to come oh no he
doesn't oh wait oh yeah here we go here
we go yes yes sir oh is he following
uhhuh oh there we go yeah okay I guess
you just got to just Keep On Walking
yeah and now do I feed him feed him
plenty although I guess they can't make
babies until they have a second one was
that the case oh maybe well there's a
mushroom cow can they not breed together
no cross breeding uh those two probably
not huh I
don't would be good if they could maybe
they
can no no okay we need a second cow a
second cow would be great MH all right
let's cross our fingers then and really
try to pull pull for one it's kind of
like
gotcha yeah yeah see we we can nice a
pair for a spare for inter species
relations oh boy
yes oh okay this makes me so happy this
Farm makes me so
happy the farm like that Tiny Farm over
there was good for the beginning but we
really need something bigger we should
for sure I'm always up for expanding the
farm we should try and make a legitimate
Farm you know more
legit we could work on like eventually
separating the animals properly into
cows only and so on think be good easy
to handle for example if we want to kill
some of them for meat oh yeah just so we
don't accidentally kill other animals
that we didn't want to kill exactly good
idea
s this I dig it sounds good potatoes
potatoes do do we have some potatoes we
have some rotten
potatoes rotten yeah stinky and like
mold growing on them and
[\h__\h] that's about
it all right I'm going to keep mining in
a minute here what do we have all right
uh block of emerald definitely
potatoes
potatoes potatoes potatoes potato tots
potatoes sure okay this this is really
nice really really really
nice I mean I think now we can just let
it grow on its
own right guys probably fine don't need
to force it anymore just wanted to fill
it up yeah ah happy happy happy um the
mushroom we
want I think for now it's fine like this
we'll find another cow find another one
cuz that mushroom cow it gives us
endless mushroom soup oh yeah
mhm wait the only way you can get the
mushrooms from it is it by shaving
it yeah but then it turns into a normal
cow you don't want to get the mushrooms
from it you just want the soup from it
trust me
oh so how do you pick them off if you're
not going to if you're not going to
shave it how do you pick them off uh if
you if you wanted the soup you need to
make a bowl out of wood I think there we
used to have some mhm okay yeah for sure
where are they I think they're in the
item
box okay oh well they should be
there going to put in some things for
sorting actually this one I'll sort
myself okay done quite a bit of sorting
maybe we can keep mining a bit huh guys
yeah go mine let's mine mine mine mine I
want to mine a bit too yeah come mine
these blocks popping
off that's a bunch of blocks more
efficient yeah this way we'll get faster
to the things that we want oh Two Is
Better Than
One yes sometimes they take a minute to
get in the chest why does it not go in
yeah really strange I mean it's not full
oh oh now it looks like it's going in
yeah
no those are just staying but it's not
full the chest we too fast is it cuz
we're we're going too
Speedy you
think put the slab back it's the slab oh
okay
wait the slab where did it go the SL can
I just put a full block like this the
hopper overloaded maybe h
does it have to be a SL yeah I think
it's too fast it says the Hopper's
clogged it got
full wrong space what
go
go goo I didn't expect goo neither hello
hello
hello hey is that a is that a that Cape
is that an OptiFine Cape or so do I have
one to oh yeah I got the Phoenix Cape oh
cool need good are you listening to our
streams do you hear
us you're almost at a thousand you're in
VC oh we're in the different server I
think oh no you are here you're just
muted oh okay oh she's in here so she
can hear us talking about free more
blocks and then you have a thousand
three more
boy let's go she's been mining she's
been putting in the mining
hours dang we got to catch up I'll try
to fix this guys with the
m uh so the
slab SL what about here here
right and then we can get rid of that
chill
999 blocks o
exciting correct okay now it should go
back in I must stay yeah she's got
something to prove by staying at
9999 that's
a one it has to be a special
one I can respect
it lots of Terra Cotta but why but why o
Emerald we actually have a ton of
emeralds all right leave it to me I'll
leave it to you I'm still not going in
though strange
H oh well we'll just have to sometimes
you know pick it up ourselves that's
okay it is what it
is oh bless you there go oh do something
break yeah my my iron pickaxe I'll make
another
one okay I have enough iron it should be
okay thank you for the blessings
everyone I appreciate that Gaz tight oh
gazon tight
thanks bless you in may you be healthy
oh thanks I'll do my
best especially now I really should be
trying to be he
obsidian oh gotcha leave it to
me Goa I'll put some I'll put music in I
want to hear this
one DJ K take it
away ah it's that
one this one sounds like a trip this one
it makes me feel like I'm Fallout New
Vegas Oh yeah I can see that it's got a
nostalgic feeling to
it I know we should use axes on the
stumps but they just appear so quickly
you know yeah it doesn't feel like worth
it to switch around it takes too much
time oh chest you oh yeah you can do
that one uhoh what the [\h__\h] there were a
bunch of eggs in there that was weird
though it just disappeared did you pick
up the stuff oh I picked up the stuff
got some eggs oh okay yeah I guess it's
just like uh uh yeah are you planning to
start a kfp or something
Kiara no no no no no no not time no oh
no no I'm too busy you know too busy
with other things yeah too busy with
other C beans I get you yeah cuz I've
been trying not to use too much oh block
of gold nice I've been trying not to use
um the eggs too much cuz I was like oh
what if Kiara wants to make a kfp or
something oh you got eggs
yeah hey yo quite a few
actually good are you just here to feed
the pandas is that all you came
for feeding the pandas is important your
babies she's so into the breeding got to
make a brown one oh okay she wants the
Goa Rarity not playing around what's
that brown
one I'm sure with your luck so far if
anyone can get that brown one it's you
yeah I just have a feeling wait Goa
follow me follow me show let me show you
the world follow me I'm so proud I
thought we need
this well did some cool
stuff well I need to make it a bit safer
still but um uh here full Farm of wheat
for for uh
bread no it's I think more efficient
than the food that has to be made into
soups so this is good this is good yeah
yeah yeah and we got some beds now GAA
three of them yeah so two people are
still sleeping on the floor for now yeah
well for now we are indeed only three
people so that's cool now we could all
sleep if we wanted to it works so yeah
that's a a little bit of an update
the nice
progress yay
[Music]
y lots of good progress I
feel what else is in this some
bamboo bamboos are really good for the
sticks
the I shall take them that seems like a
much more efficient way instead of
wasting
wood yeah for and the the pandas I try
to remember
that wobbly
Stone concr I feel like the phrase
sticks and stones may break my bones but
chains and whips exide me oh that's kind
of something a panda would say oh my God
n where did now what I mean with that is
Sticks and Stones especially bamboo
sticks but also stones are bad for their
stomachs right but chains and whips
excite them that means that the zoos
that they're being held in excite them
too because they get so much so much
more bamboo but no zoos I don't like
zoos that much but that's doesn't it
sound like something a panda would
say maybe that's Rihanna meant maybe she
sang
about pandas all the time I don't know
about that kiar I I don't know
I don't think but they get so much
bamboo and it hurts their tummies right
I guess
so it's not good for them but you know
you love to eat what's not good for you
me too too just like the pandas yeah
it's human
nature it's human
nature yes why is my ooshi like this she
cooked with that one guys I I didn't
cook Rihanna cooked I don't know if
that's what Rihanna meant though
M what do you think she meant I think
that she meant that sticks and stones
would break her bones but chains and
whips excite
her what does what does that mean when
she sees chains and whips it makes her
excited what way how do you use the
chains and whips oh Kiara let's not play
games I mean you know what never mind
you're right she was talking about
pandas I'm sorry I doubted you yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I'm I'm sure she loves
pandas Rihanna a big Panda
fan fluffy chunky didn't know
pandas
yeah we have so many I wonder why so
many spawn for
us well of give us some villagers are
babies as a result of the breeding oh I
see yeah I got an enchanted book with
looting three by the way I don't know if
that's helpful for us o nice you get
such cool books what lot of glowy
enchanted books these days wonder
why hey dead be can we not stand right
next to Papa thank
you what am I doing right now huh what
am I
doing oh it's raining again oh my God so
much dirt
[Music]
yeah lots of pandas and lots of Terra
Cotta for some reason I'd like some more
diamonds
torches why is it so dark here why we
why we why don't we have torches
here oh I already made a bunch of
torches let's
go not a lot of entities spawning to be
honest
mhm wonder why
but because no because there's just so
much more from the the roster oh I guess
so rooster roster the roster
yeah too much possibilities glad we're
getting more dirt I'm glad there's more
dirt yeah the one time we're actually
happy about dirt because we can use it
for the farms and stuff and expand the
forest it's big do I have permission to
expand the forest
Kiara yeah oh cool just making sure I'll
be careful I know it's near the edge but
you the forest it must be
expanded very important for our
mission we really do need some uh some
villagers that can turn into Merchants
because we have so many
emeralds I like so many we'll find we
used to have them but no well it's kind
of my fault but I I couldn't do anything
about it that's okay in the moment you
did what she could I was stuck I was
chased by enemies that's okay and then
they died as well you did your best
here that's all anyone can ask
[Music]
for extension
domain
expansion you guys really like saying
that domain expansion I guess domain in
this case is like a place where you live
not a not a Internet domain I would
assume so not that's the vibe that I get
interesting learning English
oh I know I am the ruler of my
domain h
right I know there are more technically
smart people in the chat you know I
don't really understand it I'm too
smooth brain for that well what J it's a
kaen
reference is that some currently popular
anime oh my
God I mean oh my
God Kelly you
know G kaon it's I think it's maybe the
most
um popular anime right
now ever in the recent years
yeah I
think oh
yeah I would say definitely it is
oh the currently popular en don't take
the bait she's not lying though right k
k I like your name tag maybe she is full
oh there's goo can we overall make
ourselves smaller so that we can
separate ourselves ni on grumbles is
here no go in the middle so I can
separate thanks okay hold on guys it's
just a little remodeling going on
here
yesah gooa is moving in yeah gooa is
moving in so the dimensions look a
little strange Shifty right now just
we're we're breaking Dimensions right
now so
but your singing was so beautiful
yesterday yeah it was Majestic I tuned
in for just the two of us it was very
doky
dokie yeah
Alba there she
is like
so like so yeah okay all righty
[Music]
nice yo okay what was I doing ah I think
I wanted to make a roof
rooftop for the
[Music]
farm I am the freaking
organizer us still feeding
pandas it's a very important job
understand the pandas they do so much
for us they're definitely not living
rentree here they they block the the
path to the am Road where there might be
enemies that want to hurt us so they're
like the meat Shield I suppose oh yeah
there you go that is something valuable
hold on I got to get rid of some spam
just a sec
oh was that not your intention
gooa let's see is there anything here
that shouldn't be here
[Music]
red stone
dust now the farm cannot be destroyed by
gas
attacks
go W big brain oh genius sorry wait I'll
put on music again yeah could use some
tunes she
this one was good I
think
wait I love this I would totally use
this as like a stream
bgm yeah it's viy I like it all of
them oh miss 999
blocks no no sticky keys stop it I was
just trying to dance like girl I was
please come on I also always get sticky
keys and they always tell me to just
like turn it off I don't know where I'm
sure it's simple but that's for smart
computer
people all right mining
time all right gu if you don't want to
did you finish Red Dead Redemption yeah
I'm in the epilog
now I've always been not always but I've
been interested in playing that too how
do you feel I feel like a different
human being After experiencing the end
of that yo my Arthur was so goofy though
I gave him only mutton shops and a top
hat was really freaky so like everything
felt un
serious my Arthur oh my main character
you can kind of change how he looks and
whatnot
but yeah so I'm in the end game now yeah
but I just I have a lot of I haven't
really talked about my feelings yet cuz
I'm still sorting them out it kind of
hit me like a bag of bricks I didn't
really know how to react to it in the
moment no spoilers though
I saw a scene where you shot someone and
then you went on your horse and ran away
screamingly or or rode away screamingly
now I was curious like cuz I played a
lot of GTA games now I was wondering so
if you do a crime how does it work with
the police are they also on horses um
yeah yeah they have horses um I mean I I
feel like it's a lot easier to get
away to be honest um in Red Dead I mean
you're wanted and you have to you have
to pay off your Bounty if you don't want
to be pursued by the lawmen anymore but
Constable I suppose yeah exactly the
pranker yeah those guys
suck they don't have helicopter chat I
think are making jokes that saying that
they do have cars and helicopters but
that's not true right no they don't
they're they're uh messing with you
because those did things did not
exist at that time I oh it's that far
back in time I thought it was just like
you know Texas yeah there are uh no mods
they do not
have oh shoot was just modern time
Texas I know I'm so sorry I know I know
Texas people they get like you know sad
when people think they like go to school
on horses and stuff get
sadus it looked relatively modern to me
from the little bits that I saw I don't
know why I just saw really little bits
like tin tiniest bits I mean some of the
cities are like you know they're they're
uh they're like they're not modern but I
mean they look similar to you know some
more antique looking cities that exist
in this time of you know oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah I can get I see how why you
maybe thought that but okay yeah also I
like how we got um not a sheep but
another freaking Panda that's cool thank
you for spawning another freaking Panda
sake come on yeah give it to go
congratulations it to the the panda Farm
more for the panda aquarium I guess
congrats do pandas even drop meat when
you you know take them down I I don't
think so I think that would be too
messed
up I think this this stuff needs to be
sorted we got to sort I'm going to sort
things now don't worry I gotta this is
what I do I'm a pro you can trust me you
can trust this in my hands I'm going to
turn this one it says it's a snow chest
I'm going to make it a rock
chest oh where did I put the Terracotta
before or is it just oh we have so much
terra cotta we have so much over here
wait no I mean the the fancy white the
the pretty one too was also over there
oh yeah I put all the pretty ones in
here as
well like that design
scense m that was cool
Wow music why do you stop play
music oh oopsy do
uhoh or she
blows so chill hey lots of golden
carrots I like these golden carrots cuz
we can really stock up for the final
fight I feel like we should yeah I mean
golden apples would be would be much
much better golden carrots are not even
that good but
maybe we should build a chest um Where
We Gather stuff for the final
fight let's see where should we put
could be nice we'll put it behind the
storage area and that can be where we we
can store things for the final the last
battle okay well just kidding never mind
these horses are in the way we'll put it
behind the soon to be Merchant's
house that work I that works all right
this is final fight
storage and I'm going to put a I have a
totem of undying so I'll put that in
there
too oh
yeah that is
good I like this one too this one's a
bob let see our Treasures are in here so
move some of this NE quartz and whatnot
I'll take
that some IR just a note don't eat the
normal Apples because we can turn them
into golden apples eventually okay the
ones in the chest sounds good let's
collect apples okie dokie I
[Music]
C I shall
take a chest surely we had some chests
here yeah we have a ton in the wooden
one that's a
beehive beehives aren't made of wood
they're made of bee things we'll just
keep it in there
anyway yeah what do we do with the honey
I mean the bees are cute so I think they
have a right to
stay what can we make with honey candles
I think that's
it I mean they're aesthetically pleasing
but that's about it
right all right we keep doing some
organization your boy such a trooper oo
Diamond watermelon
nice
[Music]
oh I shall do some fighting downstairs
maybe yeah cuz there's some zombies
there guess I got to put more torches
down yeah see one reason that I really
wish we had a trash can is so that we
could throw away this Burning rotten
flesh cuz we just don't need it just
takes up space in a chest you
know that's how your boy feels about it
don't over the edge true actually right
I didn't think about that so much Edge I
feel like such a bone
head no I mean we all have a bone head
true we all do that is true everybody
does have a scroll into the void of
course you're
right true enough
except jellyfish I hope I don't meet the
edge oh okay oh that's
it at least the cat is keeping the
creepies away yeah so why did it spawn
though there's enough light come
on
here here
here are you okay
yeah just hearing weird
sounds trying to be
cautious this should be
okay with the shaders I can see the
light glowing so much
nicer this reminds me this music reminds
me of like a really old
RPG mhm I like it a particular one or
just generally I don't know in general
maybe a jrpg or something like that I
don't know it's hard to put my finger on
it but I like it it's
nostalgic I wish I had more stuff like
this to just play in my ear when playing
random games you
know nice looping tracks I'll commission
some some honey block where should that
go oh yeah Chon a trigger yeah
maybe ah wait I'm so smart for making it
slams because enemies can't spawn up
there right cuz for moment I was like oh
I got to put torches up there but
brilliant move boss very intentional
brilliant
move
Wow Let's go oh let's
go I thought it was the intention no
actually not I just wanted to save
blocks not overuse blocks okay it's time
to
mine it's time to mine
just here I know where they are I know
where they
[Music]
are let's see more
terracotta
here there we
go keep the dirt okay e mining it's
mining time she started mining all over
the place let's
go see what you get I want a book too
yeah an enchanted book you might find
one in a chest just keep it up
o give me the the chest of let's see the
chest of my dreams I'm going to start a
different box for
fuel Like Flint and uh
oh
obsidian do you have the diamond pickaxe
I do here I'll give it to you thank
you okay here you
go than thank you you're
welcome where does this stuff
go diamond is
unbreakable Tak time
fishy business fishy business that fits
scoob but that sounds
like exactly her kind of
business if you were to create like a
business like kfp what would you call
it maybe your own kind of like fish
restaurant fast food restaurant what
would you call
it fried fish fried shrimps kinds of
stuff hold
on you can go by the popular for formula
of starting it with a G like kfp like
the
K you can do something like that or make
it a full written out
word I wonder what be good what are
those places next to prisons um let's
see you got to be a little more specific
G um
what like what do they do with those
places that are next to the
prisons it's like a couple more details
maybe Waffle House oh Jesus no that's
where people fight before they go to
prison exactly exactly then they get
sent to the prison for causing trouble
exactly that's a little
different a bale
Bale next to the Oh you mean like a
courthouse
confused well where is she going with
this oh oh you glow so pretty that's a
valid dancer
uh-oh you little [\h__\h] you good uhoh uhoh
she's fighting oh yeah yeah yeah
y damn they be doing good damage give
him the old one too baale bonds men but
I offer seashells and aquarium rocks oh
okay cool a nice nice if I ever get in
big trouble and I'm out on bail
maybe is there a pond there or why is it
what is it called bale
[Music]
bondsman I got you yeah with seashells
what they have to
accept all right why would you call it
then I don't know oh wait Bale bondman
is just a ah you're not calling a that
it it's just the business
model or
so he has a
business chant got some good ideas for
the name H I sell seashells
ink that's s seashells seash shells
seash
shells she sells seashells ink that's
what it should be I think that's pretty
solid
ah yeah this chest is very shiky shiky
chest shy sh all right I'm going to sell
seashells by the Bond Inc balsman that's
so [\h__\h]
long I know
it i' go visit it oh we have to protect
the chicken we have to protect the
chicken wait wait don't don't free it
yet I I I'll bring some wheat seeds
that's a you job Kiara yep we had one
chicken and it died but nobody noticed
it yep I had birthed it nobody even
noticed that it existed poor guy maybe I
should have alerted you
come
here a okay where do you want to go we
need a little little shed for
you like a chicken shed I guess I do be
making a kfp yeah but for now we'll keep
you safe and wait this can be the
chicken shed come here you can't help it
kiar it's in your
nature you'll always end up done taking
care of
kfp yeah just your
destiny I'll get more of you um I'll get
you some friends that you can play with
and make eggs
with need a rooster I
know I know how it works
what yeah g knows the
Deets lots of
watermelon I need to eat more
watermelons now that it's
summer this is the time you're a big
strong big strong rooster yeah that will
go k k the key in the morning and that
will motivate the hens to make some eggs
Co dooodle do right kfp right you know
how it works doing it all the time are
they they are got it they do be what do
you call it they what do you call the
act of laying an egg laying an egg damn
it they do be laying eggs
and if there's another one correct me if
I'm wrong Chad they do be ovulating oh
that's what okay but what about the the
male ones for that they're also OB in my
world they're also they're also lay eggs
they're all laying eggs all right they
have the capabil capabilities in my
world I see you
know come come here come here come here
you can pick it up finally just like in
the picture y no pick it up goba show us
you can do it what is r it's it's
chilling in the water it's
swimming what do we do
let's
NE well do you want to like free it and
bring it to a water ah we should bring
it somehow can we bring it somehow with
a bridge a water slide to the the
fishing pond that would be nice
that is a really difficult Quest but if
anyone can do it it's you
go it will jump out of there no way you
need a lead what you can actually but
like Elite but still it has to be in the
water
right surely it has to be within the
water it seems to
hand she's
thinking he can hold his breath really
no he that seems fake
girl yeah it has to be in the
water I'm stuck we water too but not too
long john who's do John oh yeah you kind
of have to go over to this block and
then like Swizzles SK your way
out oh is this DOL John right
here what you named
him Johnny Boy somebody help dop
John oh no I don't want to be on oh
you're on the donkey yeah all I had to
do is press shift by acci Donkey oh my
God what a
couple well now I can't get on him
anymore so I don't know how it happened
but uh okay she's just's going to do it
I believe you're going to actually try
to drag him through the no water section
I hope we can survive that maybe make a
first stop in the in this first water I
don't
know uh oh oh he's gonna die really like
hella die like wait I can get rid of
some slabs for you if you want some
block oh wait what's hurting you the
dolphin I mean he's dying like he's
definitely in the process of you know
not being able
to oh yeah he's in a state of peril
Kiara they attack but they also protect
and and transport people fast yeah in
water for that in with a cc at the end
oh my God what what I mean I think it's
sensing what you're trying to do
GAA oh don't die here do you need some
food having a hard time yeah yeah yeah
let's go let's go
ah oh go go go run for it bring the
dolphin to the water
oh she oh yeah let's go
W mission accomplish she did
it wow I'm so emotionally moved damn you
guys are in the scary bottom part aren't
you damn you under
there under no no we're at the top oh oh
we didn't go down there we brought it to
the fishing pond up here next to the
farm F area yeah yeah yeah look uh at
the chest section the chest over here
over
here this dolphin will kill you
eventually it will jump out 100% really
he heard
you there's no place to jump into no
safe no safe
Zone we'll see we'll see do John let's
stay close by let's keep an eye on it
why you do
that maybe he wants a deeper Pond why he
do that though at higher
walls yeah that would be good oh have
some more that's a little well go go put
it on the leash put it on Le oh no no no
that's not
good oh sorry I got him I got him it
okay I just don't know how to get back
up is the
thing yeah let's let him catch his
breath sorry for hitting you
dolphin we could try to make him a pond
down here we
could this dolphin's
doomed Dolph John he doesn't have a
prayer it's got to be pretty high walls
would jump out but we won't see him a
yeah what a sad
existence dooming him to hell but it is
what it is you'll get stuck too me I
don't want to be stuck don't Cask of a
monal me please actually I really don't
want to use dirt for this but oh well it
is dirt cave
can we leave like one window like this
open oh actually if it's just one block
can he the chances are oh yeah right why
don't we just attach the lead to a fence
and then he will stay right he'll just
not be very
happy sounds about right he will be in
water instead of falling into the
void okay I think that's a good
idea bua can you bring a fence for the
dolphin you DOL John how do you feel
about that
buddy that's how he feel hey do John
stop that get back into the water come
on do joh good for
you maybe add glass windows we do have
quite a bit of glass oh yeah and we can
make it from Sand can do that too yeah
some glass
windows y turn them into our own
personal little
Shamu yeah why not
amazing do John you got to
chill it's so cute how he's swimming
around
zo got the Zoomies no no get back no
come here come on no
no he sounds like he's in pain at all
times that's fine he'll get over it
we'll give him some fishes to feed him
can you feed a dolphin I want
I feel like I haven't
tried all right I'll tach him
here there you go oh
oh oh boy it's like he's choosing to
die yeah you might need to set it a
little closer in
there oh oh will the lead
unleash yeah leave it to the experts
wait
uh come
buddy he's chilling he see he likes life
he likes living so yeah that's a good
place for there we go there we go leash
yeah yeah and then anybody who's bored
can make him a glass cage as well yeah
make it a quest so we can look at him
sounds good yeah we can regard him yeah
the cliff the cliff is
scary how' this water get down here I
wonder
flood oh
flood
suppose hold on now let's not die oh
God ni I'm scared I'm
scared let's see oh I think we're good
we've organized everything he will 100%
jump off ah we really need the glass
then well there's plenty of glass
thankfully okay
yeah should we go ahead
and yes yes yes yes yes all right I'm
going to get some glass then this is
just for
now we have nine glass we might need to
cook some more yeah with sand do do we
have sand we might have a lot of sand
that we don't know how else to use oh
Kaa thank you Kaa all right let's see
I'll start cooking sand 64 sand nice
little sand I'm sure kawa's fingertips
and toe tippies are tingling when she
sees us playing Minecraft on our own
server she's like I want to I want to
play Minecraft one BL Minecraft too oh
it's KY okay I didn't know who the heck
you were talking about for a moment
there Kawa
Kawa one block Minecraft or like Sky
Block would totally be a like uper game
oh yeah for sure sheo she could probably
complete it on her own to be honest
mhm her senses are
tingling what are you thinking
goba typy
typy dolphin hate you hate dolphin or
dolphin hate you or mutual
feelings feelings Mutual possibly it did
it did bite you a lot
it might just be a love haate
relationship that's okay love hate all
the same if you know play the Minecraft
game
yeah what's in here o there's a soup go
and you grab that
stuff all right I'll take it don't mind
if I freaking do yeah yeah yeah all
right nice iron it will end up being
sorted anyway so true
enough we share everything here sorted
by the sorter of all sortations that's
right all sorting goes through your
boy at all times oh yes I'll let you uh
mine with a pickaxe and when I see a
wooden block I'll quickly chop it off
how about that oh nice
idea also here's a question you don't
have to switch around yeah here's a
question what if um you get to to you
know the level where there's obsid
obsidian but you haven't been saving
diamonds and then you can't make a
diamond pickaxe you have to start
over
oh no well if you have an obsidian block
here and you have no more diamonds
left I think you might be [\h__\h]
yeah then you ah you can break it with
your fist it just takes
forever oh you can it just a bit you can
mine you can dig but it's very
slow yeah just takes a long time they
say just mine it really
hard yeah so yeah we want to cherish our
diamonds for now and it won't drop
itself yeah I see but I mean we I think
we're fine is with diamonds as long as
we we we can't maybe we can't do a
fullon diamond armor but we shall see
we have a fair amount of
diamonds think we got armor would be
first step yes and with the iron armor
and a golden Helmet or so we might want
to go into the never tomorrow maybe
yeah maybe see what we can find
tomorrow's Monday right yeah K Cat hello
welcome KY Cat hello bub go go do your
thing do your kitty thing all right I'm
going to
sort oh Kitty thing is bullying the
donkey I supp Kitty thing is hey what's
up all of you suck I'm going to kill all
of you and ruin your
eyes cats be cats that's just cats
you're making the glass let's go
mhm oh yes we are cooking
glass lots of
glass let's see a yes and iron we also
want to cook some iron too but we'll
just go ahead and put that in there for
now sit on
that we have so much gold and like we're
not really going to use it
[Music]
huh it's okay don't we'll find a way for
it we'll make it useful somehow
yeah you know what I'm going to go get
some soup from you yum mushroom sou make
glass panes to save glass good idea I
want to learn to like mushrooms I want
to become a fan of mushrooms yeah yeah
well you can't force yourself if you
just straight
upow
oh wow oh you said you were saying cow
yeah I thought you were squawking like a
like a parrot like you were doing a
parad impr yeah I was kind of like doing
both I see at the same time yeah
cool okay here go come with me cow it's
breeding time it's breeding time Y and
so they keep making babies and then we
destroy them for their meat
right uh yeah and yeah pretty much and
maybe sometimes we might need some
Lea you can't milk them right impossible
to milk them yeah we can milk them yeah
yeah we can okay nice all right breeding
time oh sexy music please oh we got a
baby we got the baby here grow up big
grow up
fast wow she's really experienced in
this
huh
yes I put the cows together have you
ever like I've done this uh in in like
what school what what do you call the
school before Junior High
School oh um Elementary School yeah in
elementary school we went to the
countryside and we made like butter on
our own and before we made the butter we
milked a cow have you ever done that
before I've never milked a cow
before wa yeah I'm a bit of a city
Reaper yea well me too but yeah we we
did go to the countryside as a trip as a
school trip that sounds fun
mhm now let me fix this up again
nice all right but I think as kids since
we were all super young we were all kind
of like ew don't want to touch the the
milkers don't want to you do it he
touched the
milkers he likes
[Music]
cows yeah I can see that that sounds
like uh Elementary School not survive
the end game Fact what's the end game
what do you think the end game is here
is it I guess apocalypse and
then cows are the only way to get food
you have to milk
them wait what is future ah for a moment
I thought it was a
sheep you can go to hell
be another oh it just walks out okay
bye-bye oh we haven't seen a polar bear
in a while didn't all of ours die we had
so many yeah yeah and then they all just
annihilated by that that one dude yeah
what do we do fine if another one of
those dudes appears again what do we
do those big that big squid guy that
flies through the sky like the [\h__\h]
Death Star well they can also just
despawn on um anyway if we just ignore
them yeah you got to hide stay out of
their sight yeah but we also have arrow
and bow now
so
oh will give him a taste of his own
medicine i r know run away is good
too running away is always we need a bit
more
iron yeah we can cook some more honestly
cuz we still have some iron
here yeah uh well I just took them but
if we get more iron soon we can make an
anvil yeah and the Anvil will be useful
for you know repairing things and naming
things and putting together enchanted
weapons and stuff yeah I think so
too ni I'm going to cook some more iron
blocks I'll do something else with it
M yeah no no no no
no okay that's why we have the second
floor for and oh yeah and also good
thing we have dirt we got lots of dirt
yes I got it oh that was frightening I
picked this up I was going doie doie for
a minute there
wow oh my goodness hey that's Minecraft
though that's Minecraft for
you yeah one de beat horse died
the dead beats are always the ones to
suffer why the fact that a creeper
spawned there tells me that it's not lit
up enough
so oh there you go I can't help it we
got to fix
it baby
girl are you okay down here little kitty
cat
is Kaa was talking to a cat
[Laughter]
girl was the baby girl for a moment
there it's fine we're all baby girl at
some
point
bucks oh yeah
o okay maybe that
helps what was I doing ah I was making
new pickaxe I was going to get I was
going to get the
[Music]
sticks those donkeys really like sitting
up there huh donkey donkey you're a
donkey dunk on him dunk on the donkey
yeah that's right yeah what was I doing
I'm so unorganized I don't know what I'm
doing sticks yeah tell
there we
go uh pick
axe maybe a second
one oh you made another baby what eyes
does it
have oh
normal a it's flipping so cute oh the
tongue it has a tongue
face is he SP
show good has been really into this
since
yesterday she she sent
some what was that like a a a face chart
of uh pandas into the chat yeah that
Panda looked pissed I didn't understand
what did you do to him I guess it just
gets born like that right you can't
change its face it's just rting [\h__\h]
face
Maybe is in her Panda breeding face
[Laughter]
everyone goes through one oh is that a
fe she's found her new profession die
but it's kind of crazy we have two P not
pandas that's kind of
crazy that's pretty insane hey here if a
fish pops up do we kill
it uh which kind of fish that's just a
random codfish but I slayed it and I
think it it did not yield oh yeah that's
fine sometimes there's like enemy fish
like things that look like a fish oh
yeah those guys suck they're
enemies yeah those guys are the freaking
worst yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah the
creeper head it does scare me too that's
the that's the goal for it to frighten
you that's what I
wanted but everything already scares me
by default oh no oh no you little [\h__\h]
you're not going to kill no Fox sorry
but foxes will have to die because
you're going to kill my animals they're
so cute Gua
or you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] stop zooming where is it oh
oh the polar bear killed the fox kind of
Bas I don't know maybe that's why we
have polar bears yes they kill the Riff
Raff it's nature hoping they aim for the
pandas next now my reputation will not
be destroyed by killing a
fox the PO bar we'll do it it's like
like right behind you watching you it's
like in you now wow Jesus PO he awaiting
more sacrifices he wants me to hit him
so he has a reason to get angry at me P
bear remember when true would be so cute
I'm surprised we don't have one yet
those round ears but then in white
m c it's got to be a big
one like a tall member yeah tall all big
little
size I wonder if the chest is full I'll
go
check little more that's okay I'll start
organizing I think a few months ago I
was talking to my chat about if there
were more birds what kind of birds would
I be hoping for I thought I think I said
like a parrot would be amazing because
you can make this whole joke where as a
parot YouTuber you're going to like
repeat what everybody says just to annoy
the [\h__\h] out of them in collabs or so my
God you're giving them free be a whole
gimmick it would be so funny yeah it's a
good one and they can be really colorful
in their design too so I think it's kind
of genius oh I got a book power free
let's go oo let's go bird of paradise
that's the thing like birds do you have
so much like Choice they're all colorful
beautiful you can make so many different
kind of
birds Man true Flamingo
doco I know we have L but is not quite a
flamingo yeah it would be cool to have
another yet I bet they'd be like super
bright pink so many animals to choose
from yeah where's like a maybe we get
like a ferret or like a koala or
something I don't know something crazy
koala yeah yeah koala would be fun
right
a it's got to be an Australian member
though yeah true true hugable Hol
man
y lazy koas are pretty lazy
rights Tiger Tiger would be nice too
yeah yeah we've got lion but that's
about
it L's also
great what do you call those um um
safari animals with the really long legs
that jump giraffe oh
no long legs that
jump oh gazelle I think a gazelle uh
member should have like really the
longest legs ever like kind of like
crony thin legs but even longer ah I can
Envision that even
longer oh a might ow sorry sorry horse
or donkey
damn
it 125% leg exactly you thought you
thought that crony was all legs oh we'll
show you guess
tuber tuber is here you thought
wrong though she is still you know a lot
of leg there's a lot of crra leg we need
more though oh yeah I could go for more
more
leg GFF tuba yeah super long extended
neck oh yeah I mean we it seems like a
trend for us YouTubers yeah to already
have long necks it's a long neck right
there look yeah but can we get longer
can we I'm curious yes I want to see I
want to find out extend extend neck
stretch that neck expand
neck nice iron do be
cooking we actually have a good amount
of iron oh well we did but now it's all
done it's fine neck expansion long necks
fauna
FAA what you you say that because she
she has long neck or because you see her
as a giraffe she's not a giraffe she's
not a giraffe
siles what the heck what is that it
that's not what like you know how people
I'm a phoenix but they call me a chicken
is that what people say to
FAA ah yeah blatantly ignoring the
O stupid Pillager [\h__\h] give me a
villager not a Pillager one letter when
you say give me a villager they hear
give me a Pillager you can't help can't
be help just a miscommunication please
forgive
no can we unpage the pillagers like can
we
heal them and become villager a nice
idea yeah purify them or something like
that yeah have a have a nice sit down
with them a nice discussion wo another
Panda another Panda that's exactly what
we need yep m 50 bajillion pandas and
zero sheep makes a whole bunch of sense
goba get your panda out of here where
are you they give the the useless ones
to us
coming oh there she's want to give us
the useful
ones ah [\h__\h] no the sponge a this
[\h__\h] sponge oh no okay uh block
machine currently broken okay that's
fine I'll just keep
sorting I'll have to find the right spot
to put it back onto oh good gives me
plenty of time to move this stuff around
cute God damn it so damn cute I hate it
why is it so cute how dare they how dare
they be cute and useless I hate it for
real what was I doing I was going to get
a bucket bucket bucket bucket think I
saw
[Music]
buckets
nice bucket
Toco I don't want to make a new bucket
what the
hell
ah blind
Wawa she can't
see okay Chad where is it to be
placed do you remember from yesterday
what Amma was doing Chad is it like
uh at the top hold shift which top like
there's many
tops look
here oh no that's oh that's that's
that's wrong uhoh that is wrong oh
Yik this is why your boy is very happy
to just organize
things top
middle what wh which block tell me which
block
is it like
here
wait no I went the wrong way I went the
wrong way no it's flooding yeah no way
chat crazy I don't understand why you
guys in chat are saying this as if it's
such a obvious thing where to put it uh
on the closed trap this this one this
this one oh yeah baby we're flowing now
oh yeah there we go no more flooding
just flowing
nice y
fixed fixed indeed just time problem
just in time the chest is empty
now which means more mining which means
maybe more
diamonds uh what am I what's my brain
doing what's my brain doing what's my
brain doing
how many blocks has everyone mined I
wonder I'm probably very far
behind yours says
1,700 170 blocks oh okay what does my
number say wonder I'm here next to you
oh yours what' it say
2,882 I caught up in the in the first
stream you know everybody was like ah W
it's just a camera man she's not m at
all only has like free blocks to her
name ah now we're over 2,000 the
turntables wow
going
wer well
done I'm going to catch up to you
though are you are you a golden apple oh
new book Fortune to and an enchanted
golden apple I'll put it in the special
chest for the fin
battle Fortune well so so far we got
fortune and aqua infinity infinity impal
we got a lot of trident books man oh
yeah that'll be good for maybe a trident
for gooa I don't know yeah maybe we'll
be in a chest or so one day I could see
it could that
be cuz I don't know what else we music
making you fall asleep gooa
it's definitely very late and glorious
in Neon right now
[Music]
yay she Ganky we're
good
relax Minecraft is really chill not
going to
lie it's chill oh hello
rabbit I love when little animals pop
out I don't like when pandas pop
out uh it just scares me I don't want to
hit them accidentally when they spawn
right here I get you there just got to
maybe aim to the side or the
corner especially when the bigger ones
spawn true enough I'll start clearing
out some of this apple oh yesterday I
was watching a little bit of the acle uh
cuphead endurance that they were doing
they were going for 15 hours yeah that
was crazy
it's insane I was watching like the last
hour I'm getting hurt I'm getting hurt
oh no couldn't get my eyes off of it I'm
going to die what what who's shooting
you what the hell
skon oh he's very strong I have no
food see anything I can eat
no don't hurt the
donkey okay he's gone thank you for the
protection where the hell did he come
from did you see where he came from not
a clue but I think it was kind of near
the storage area sort
of not
certain but I feel like it's lit up the
roof yeah I feel like the roof is also
lit up fine it's pretty well lit no
wonder storage area Roof it seems ah
right the water broke the Torches uh
around here so oh
okay it do be like that sometimes
interesting let me just get full
health H okay this maybe I should wait
I'm kind of wasting the
melons yeah this good that's
fine I'm going to put some more things
into the Sorting chest yeah yeah
although you already have sorting chests
like everywhere that's
okay no
problem how about that glass by the way
oh yeah here 61 glass I'll give it to
you now oh okay I'll make a little
aquarium B take that glass cooked you
some glass
today don't tell anyone it's my finest
glass though she cooked yes when it
comes to Glass I'm the number one part
okay
[Music]
thank you for feeding the pandas yeah it
was fun thank you bye
goo you
helped all
right I helped it was the biggest helper
see her can still hear her voice
now oh or I mean yeah you
know the typing I can hear her through
typing
does it have to
be so tall Chad I know Chad doesn't I'm
going to make it a bit shorter
here maybe we'll get more water animals
eventually that we can add into this
aquarium have you heard so I I think I
only heard about this because I you know
it's it happened in my neighboring uh
country um and this is kind of like a
crazy thing that happened a really
[\h__\h] unfortunate thing oh yeah but
have you heard of this uh German hotel I
think it was in Berlin that had um like
a huge aquarium dome in the middle of
the hotel oh cool um and they had like
thousands and thousands of fish there m
right and it looked beautiful and it was
like a huge attraction and there were
rooms that were facing dad and it's like
this whole thing right right yeah and it
was going for several years just fine
but one day one day in the early morning
like right before checkout time so it
was actually a good time because there
weren't many people in the lobby where
this Dome was it exploded it was like a
big tube that like how many gallons of
water was it I don't remember but it was
just really huge it was the I think it
was the biggest aquarium
um in
something the biggest of something and
it it exploded and all the fish
obviously died thousands thousands of
fish died um thankfully I think no
humans uh died maybe one got like
injured or so a little bit but it was so
lucky that not many people were around
the um cuz like it was also it was
centered in the lobby right and around
this this thing this aquarium Dome there
was a bar too the the hotel bar so if
this would have happened in the evening
with people sitting at the bar that
would have been really disastrous god
wow I can't even imagine dang that would
be rough but exploded and then there
were a lot of Investigations of like how
that happened what and it's like still a
mystery cuz there's several reasons of
why it could have happened but it's kind
of interesting there's this like
documentary in German that I watched
about it oh shouldn't they have done a
gajillion different
checks they they always do and like it
was supposed to be super secure but you
know and then the question was are they
going to rebuild it or not because like
this should never happen again it was
kind of ridiculous in the first place
and so they decided to not rebuild it
and that's the right choice because how
could you after killing thousand of fish
oh yeah forget that I mean What a Sad
thing the fish didn't deserve that you
know obviously there was some kind of
design FLW to all German speakers the
channel simply ismos is amazing it's so
good they have a this channel too
actually they make really nice
documentaries I love a good documentary
to be honest you just chill and watch it
was oh it was 1,500 fish okay that's
still a
lot yeah that's still that's still a lot
of fish though that's a sufficient
amount of fish life
lost was it in Berlin actually uh
Aquarium hotel broke
burst how
sad yeah oh and another baby it was in
Berlin oh I I'm going to show you a
picture so you can imagine later I'll
show you yeah I'm curious cuz when you
when you say Dome I I try to Envision it
um and like I I'm having a hard time
seeing it in my head so I'm curious if
you could shoot over a video or a
picture yeah one picture via DM cool it
was 50 foot
tall I don't know if you his foot his
foot what you can understand feet 50
feet yeah I can understand
yeah oh that had stuff in it okay I'll
be taking yeah o uh so this is a
enchanted book Thorns 3 and 11 Gold ah
264,000 gallon tank and of course it
like leaked everywhere onto outside on
the street and everything it did so much
damage too to the hotel it needed a
whole renovation it's crazy man that's
horrible what the heck that that stuff
should have been checked
properly mhm what a shame this fish
didn't deserve that the hum dying you
know whatever but fish that hurts me oh
just like that skeleton guess what I hit
it could have been the pressure and
other things yeah could
be water damage is the worst damage oh
yeah I guess the damage as well
internally to the hotel must have been
like is it even worth you know trying to
mop it up with like
a because of all the all the poor fish
that died I feel like having to spend so
much money to repair [\h__\h] is kind of
karma true enough you kind of deserve
that after that oh ah ah [\h__\h] sponge
you know why this happened it's because
one sponge BL
SpongeBob sponge block uh spawn and that
will get rid of the
water uh let me fix this so that can
happen all right I'll empty out the box
in the mean time but what the heck no
freaking way it's so Random are the
chances what are the freaking chances
Man O pretty low considering that's the
first time I think I've seen that happen
today it's the second time today though
oh it is dang mhm happened like a moment
ago
usual did I do it right yeah okay okay
okay
nice all right
okay imagine the smell yeah I was going
to say the same
thing especially with the clean up if
you have a ton of dead fish it's like
it's not going to smell very good
either this kind of sponge block could
have helped them clean up all the water
damage
they just filled the whole room with
Minecraft Sponge blocks all their
problems could have been solved yeah the
irony download
Minecraft
[Music]
sunflower cute sunflower let me let me
plant it
here
and sword these oh
DJ time yeah prank some
tunes it's just always the same cuz it's
easier to put in but I like this one so
no
problemo heck yeah also if I don't if I
don't stream but I want to organize a
little bit I might you know do that as
well oh always welcome cool yeah have to
just hop in and and really quickly just
do a little organizing and hop off hell
yeah I'm so
like surprised that you're willing to do
that yeah might as well bless you bless
your heart I mean it's something I think
it's hard to mess up at so true do my
best true true Little
Bread are we growing bread Kiara do we
have a not endless you want more bread
let me let me go farming a little bit
I'll make some bread cuz the farm is
looking good I'd be
happy yeah if you could share some of
that bread with me so thank you for the
rir it's an important job I didn't know
I was just kind of like okay what can I
do and not mess
up yeah but I think you need to let go
of that Minecraft trauma that you have
it's time to let go C it happened 18 no
844 years ago how many years ago what do
they
say gazillion for score and 70 years ago
you know it was a while ago but it's
fine it's more like in general with
games I feel that way like in group
games I just kind of don't want to get
in the
way don't worry about it I'd like to be
helpful so long especially if it's you
know a game that I'm like I know I'm not
really an expert at
right yeah but I've been getting better
at Minecraft I feel better about it now
than I used to
mhm I'm so happy because you once swore
off Minecraft oh yeah I
done with it yeah was it the fomo I
wonder I don't know I think I do want we
always do a lot of stuff in Minecraft in
h life you know I would understand like
having fomo yeah I think when it ended
up being that like there were uh was
suddenly like a big shared server I was
kind of like all right I guess I might
as well try again to join and also the
Sakura biome I really want to oh do I
kill him do I just do I just kill this
guy guess I'll kill him
oh yeah yeah yeah but it will split into
several smaller slimes okay gotta and
then you kill those slime balls slime
balls are useful for something I think
right I forget but yeah Pistons I think
pistons for example but I don't know if
we'll be making any
Pistons I see I
see but it's good to collect everything
okay it's really crazy to think all of
this came from one block
mhm everything created here that's
amazing I let me go do we ah we still
don't have a second chicken wait it can
just lay an egg right ah right that's
how it happens they don't they don't
have the eggs they can sometimes turn
into more chickens but not always it's
like a chicken
gotcha oh for a moment I thought oh my
God I thought you died someone ate you
uhoh okay
gotcha chickena lucky I'm lucky that's
fine you'll get one
eventually you'll get another chicken
eventually I'll give you some bread into
the bread into the um food chest thank
you oh yeah definitely I'll grab oh wait
there's a couple eggs here also I got a
couple more books uh Rip Tide to en
channeling whoa hopefully that'll help
Rip Tide let's go one two and three and
four hopefully that'll help somebody
breed cows oh yeah yeah okay good good
good good good good good
[Music]
M but I need the wheat right I have one
there was a hey Bale hey Bales hey Bales
hey B
B yeah sometimes it's a lot of
SEC we have so much lepus lazuli like
what are we supposed to even use that
for
give
to does she like lepus lazuli for some
reason
yeah
why why why but
why what can you even do with
it give
[Music]
me not gim me giom me GI me was used for
enchanting good thing that we have a ton
of it we have a boatload I did not
expect riding on this
monster it's not a monster you're good
you're
good I love
alpacas need more alpacas except when
they spin on you and it's not so
fun stupid it's a LoveHate
relationship and it's a good aesthetic
block for building and D says chat I can
see that what which one Le this LLY oh
yeah I guess
so oh more stuff to
sort okay somehow I'm seeing the tri of
the soups now a little bit oh yeah just
a little bit oh just a little
[Music]
bit I guess I'll stay here this works
too never works and M from here actually
we can put the seeds in the forest box
yeah and the
bamboo I like I'm actually so shook like
on the first day we made so much
progress and I thought oh we can like
finish this in two days but whoa what
this now you kind of feel differently do
you think uhoh yeah I feel like we're
we're going to be taking a while yeah
now smell a spider's ass oh nice what it
smell like
smell smell
like fuzzy fuzzy butt smells like good
night's sleep fuzzy wait fuzzy
mocoo Moco
Moco I like the fuzzy and fluffy face
me too I actually I think I would say my
cats they're also like there's a fuzzy
one and a fluffy one oh yeah but even
the fuzzy one is a little bit fluffy for
sure I guess smoothie is the fuzzy one
wait no no smoothie is the fluffy one
sorry smoothies are fluffy wait chalkers
is Fluffy
though yeah she's she's fluffy yeah
because she's very M her fur is
very thick and big and she's got like
more layers the fur true but smoothie
smooth's uh fur is
softer so I wouldn't call her the fuzzy
one right I see cuz fuzzy implies it's
not very
soft no
no I see I see interesting books
okay I guess it applies to both really H
see
that I found another um well rather you
Min another diamond block um yeah yeah I
saw it I was like heyo heyo should we
not split
those uh for now they can just stay like
that it'll be nine right
yeah's the fluffy one oh yeah tutu is my
fluffy one and then ghost cat is the
fuzzy one
Tut small baby yeah she's still so cute
and small and sweet of them all yeah I'm
going to snuggle with her after this and
fall asleep oh
baby little one my little
ones I love her yeah I love my babies
love ghost too yeah I love I love but
he's so he's so thin not not thin but
like oh not anymore he's chunky not
anymore he's a big chunky
boy Big And Chunky what have you been
feeding him oh it kind of had to change
up his diet just because you know he was
starting to get I think he got kidney
stones once what yeah it wasn't kidy
ston I think it wasn't a kidney stone it
was um it was a uh an
infection um like a a urinary tract
infection and I took him to the how did
you notice what was cuz he sat in the
litter box and just meowed over and over
and over again um baby yeah and so I
took him to the vet and the vet said
yeah he had he has a UTI you should
probably change his diet it and
so food and now he's getting kind of
plump but he's so senstive baby yeah
that's okay though he he was able to pee
and now he's very happy and Ganky and
running around
so it's I would be happy to yeah he G if
I was able to pee but I'm an idol I
don't pee and therefore I'm just always
like you know right just jokes jokes I
drink water and it goes nowhere I have
to sweat it out that's the only way I
can
water in my body from dancing all the
time that's why Idols dance in the first
place because they don't have the
ability to pee and they must get rid of
the liquid somehow so they dance that's
the real reason
Bingo lore so true write that down
someone write that
down it's the truth you can't deny it or
crying crying and sweating lots of
crying lots and lots of crying
every
day oh I'm standing here and the stuff
is still going into the chest amazing
yeah cuz I'm I'm taking a bunch of stuff
out at the same time M and now it's
probably going to start building up
again though Idol science yes oh yeah
all all gets rid of some of it by
drooling is it is it effective for
her seems to be h
seems to be got to do what you got
zombies may just have a a different zes
areem in their body anyway for sure
yeah definitely are did you you didn't
play the the oie dating game right I
haven't played it yet I want to play it
on my own sometime
soon what did you think of it it's it's
not what I expected oh yeah some twists
and turns maybe it's very much torture
oh in what way I
wonder is it a difficult game oh it is
very difficult to rise her it's like
everything is working against you and it
takes so long to even get to ollie my
mind was going
crazy I see a rather demanding game like
a challenge it's just Mind Games
yeah it's more fun that way the Dark
Souls of dating games yeah
kind of
sleepy I shouldn't be I actually I woke
up before the stream cuz I was up like
to six or 7 a.m. oo cuz I've been
changing this my sleeping sleeping
schedule for this project a little bit
but then this one started kind of early
so ooh dragon's breath
[Music]
yeah what if I just drop this it will
fall into the chest right yeah chut the
up let me get out out of
here it's so hard to get out of here oh
now you're tired I mean you don't have
to force yourself to stay like super
long just saying oh yeah I mean I'll
stick around for a bit longer it should
be fine yeah it is it is about
2ish in are you going to play tomorrow
yeah I'd like to what time I don't know
about tomorrow morning cuz then that
would mean like 4 hours of sleep but um
yeah but what I mean is the the
following day
probably waking up early in the morning
to play I think okay yeah put it in your
schedule so I can see I've been noticing
by the way you put something in the
schedule Minecraft right I'm like okay I
will put my Minecraft there so Celly
isn't alone and then I put it there and
then you moved it and then I moved it
again to towards you and then you moved
it again and I moved it again towards
you and you moved it again mov again I'm
not trying to get I'm not trying to get
away from you I promise do you have my
calendar on though do you see it uh yeah
I do it's just it's a little far to like
the right so like I have a
a bun of other ones that I added like
more recently that are like kind of in
the in the way yours so I see it if I
look really hard and like try to like
measure like okay where is oh so you
were not running away from me
purposefully no no not what I've really
fought anyway yeah my like this girl
can't make up her mind when she wants to
stream Minecraft no there's there's just
a lot of um things changing behind the
scenes and other recordings and stuff
like that so I'm like
a lot going on is this one new o diamond
armor for horse
nice yeah that's pretty
cool let's
see oh I wasn't new
not oh this music is so
chill
yeah feel like I could make the other
book now but I feel like we're not using
the books oh not quite yet I
suppose that's okay we don't need them I
guess I just like try to keep everybody
up to date in different ways yeah hey
what does dragon's breath
do um it does some cool things but I'm
not entirely sure what okay I'm putting
it in the final chest
anyway maybe it'll splash
potion lingering Potions all right I'll
put it in there surely we'll use it we
could make a chest that's like for
potion making ingredients like lace
powder and so on red stone that could be
a good
idea oh my God hard to breathe right now
for some reason oh you
good yeah sleepy
somewhat no so sometimes I can't breathe
don't die on me Kiara you're we need you
for this please we need a leader I don't
know what I'm doing I'm just organizing
it's very chill though scr leave the
leading to me yeah it's
right piece of [\h__\h] again I guess what's
wrong with the back there there are
torches I don't know what the problem
strange is there not enough I wonder
why it can't be because of the nether
brick right you don't think it attracts
them or anything no no no no but as long
as they spawn over there in the corner
it's not so bad yeah hopefully it'll be
all
right oh did you just plop an egg I
heard it but I didn't see it where did
it go where did the egg go my
friend oh wait I did pick it up
immediately okay
gotcha the egg gotcha ra is so bad what
the hell not very good I mean I got one
my second throw maybe all the luck went
there yeah but then we lost be every thr
for me I know right you are the mother
hen strange mother Phoenix mother
Phoenix precisely very
strange that chickens don't know who
they're dealing
with how dare they disrespect
you y how dare they they should love me
like like their
goddess treat me like a goddess yeah yo
where's the
worshiping ready for some more breeding
cows oh here they go oh yeah
baby baby cow two baby
cows is in control
a you know those fluffy cows those are
so cute right like IRL I mean mhm
especially the ones with fluff around
their hoves yeah you I got feather
falling uh feather falling is it oh
that's very good yeah thought all right
I'll put it in that book that is really
nice put it in the book chest oh oh wood
oh it's wood Oh I thought it was
obsidian oh no wait it's obsidian I
guess I can't see
it yeah real dark it's a cold block is
it oh that was four they say sorry I
don't know how to read oh it was just a
normala falling four so that should be
pretty
good no I'm sorry I'm illiterate I don't
know what's going
on feather falling four yeah feather
falling four
sick let's go I wish you could like copy
books like make a copy of it would cuz
the feather falling we will make use of
that I think oh yeah yeah the
diamonds all right it's kind of useful
for is it for
the AL so we really do have a ton of
diamonds I wonder how many we need total
for like full armor sets for
everyone too much we might not be able
to get a full diamond armor I don't know
although all we really need is one
goddamn Merchant then we give him the
right
job which is uh the the envil one I
think right or or the other one and then
he'll make us diamond armor we can just
buy it with the emeralds that's all we
got to do that sounds way easier than
just hoping for
diamonds it can be a combination of that
and our own built diamond armor I would
say that would be the most efficient
probably oh that Don is wigging out
going on oh
also n in the in the nether we can get a
lot of gold easily we can make a lot of
gold armor but that's really not
[Music]
helpful but yeah maybe tomorrow maybe
we'll go to the
ne yeah chat if we were to go to the
nether what do we really want from the
nether oh yeah what should we gather
there cuz we're not trying to find
things for the
weather oh dear what the hell is this
marshmallow
fish
fish do not hurt
me KY is literally Grim Reaper she will
no uhoh HT HT back oh yikes
this seems not good at least your stuff
is still there right oh there are a
bunch of them what the [\h__\h] is why they
do that that hey what's that spoon I'm
I'm being spooned cie you're being
spooned what what what does the spoon
mean stop spooning me stop
it oh he's got that whack that tail is
just so flippy floppy Whack Him Whack
Him I'm trying I might die though means
I can't dig but that's all that one
block is
about no why you so strong [\h__\h] out
the Gard please leave me
alone come on no
wa please let me out oh please my
goodies hold lots of good
stuff I could have drank into the
mushrooms too mining fatigue
what oh did he fall down the cliff by by
any chance perhaps let's go what a big
dummy stupid dummy idiot dumb dum
but I wanted to slay him I feel you but
sometimes we just got to cut our
losses what are you doing here
bear okay dolphin still thriving that's
nice to see Emerald blocks too nice
that's good mhm yeah you always slay I
totally slay especially now Kelly do you
like my favorite night outfit I love it
it's there's so much going
on so much going on really I thought it
was rather simple but Oh you mean in
terms of details there's a lot to look
at for
sure that's what's going on yeah the
students will have you know much to look
at I
feel you
know yeah lot popping
[Music]
off feel like we can plant a tree here
which one will it be just a small one
maybe I love the hair
especially
yeah
yeah a pretty ponytail for a pretty lady
oh cute very
cute fluffy hair like in the 70s and the
80s
oh oh yeah oh oh yeah oh
yeah there was like one fan art of um
like the whole myth ladies wearing like
fight inspired outfit you saw it I
thought like oh this is this is wor at
it was
cute yeah I loved it I had a shirt G on
it workout attire is the best wait I'm
still fatigued how do I get rid of the
spoon uh-oh
spoon specifically a
spoon no milk oh okay perfect we have
cows he why do they choose I that seems
very or
bone bucket
bucket bucket so many different
containers to choose
from does it not go away on its own or
is it just really really
long to wait for
that meow meow meow
iron iron pickaxe takes long fire
minutes wow
egg okay here have some B
seeds
bye
go oh I hear some strange spooky
noises now they're
gone dolphin so you think do you think
what's his name I saw it just like a
moment ago John is very much alive Dolph
John is still alive cool
he will live until the end of the
server sheep sheep okay okay okay okay
okay H I think they like wheat too let
me go grab some wheat oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah M we could put it where the chicken
is for now maybe oh nice idea hey buddy
where you going stay right there is this
grown don't go too far away please we
need you
yeah wheat will also work says
[Music]
chat wheat and also what else Works what
else where's the Sheep where sheep right
over here I got lead that lead yes but
yeah see look that's fine hey Kelly do
you want to make a little sheep shed ooh
that's a good idea yeah just a small one
would work for now out of terracotta of
course or just a wooden fence would do
but oh true love the
really forgot cute okay let's make a
sheep area then um need some wood a
finally the sheep that we wanted but
actually we don't I mean yeah we can get
some beds out of it two more beds yeah
but not entirely necessary I don't know
but it's good to have some options good
to have options
indeed let's make fence fence then okay
get some grass for it all right we got
grass can I take this how many do I want
oh we need
sticks you can do it k sorry I'm kind of
Mak sheeper I'm the she make the
sheeper make the sheeper a a shed so it
can wrap in
peace
yay rip
[Music]
okay it needs grass oh just grass blocks
like like this just dirt blocks then
or let's see should we put him where
should we put him I wonder is the that
area is really kind of what if we put
him
here do you know if we have oopsie any
more dirt blocks somewhere I mean we
should yeah they should be in um
well your stone box that you kind of set
up right uhhuh and then also I have a I
have a place that I've created as well
um uh where did the Sheep go in the
storage shed
too I think um maybe we can extend the
area not necessarily make a oh oh you're
doing it there okay that's fine yeah I
think this is then
enough my down
[Music]
that's really small actually oopsies I
mean there's just not a lot of
[Music]
room it's just really kind of seems
cruel more of a sheep jail it's just you
know this this thing right here is kind
of no way I wonder if we should put it
somewhere else like
a we should put
it in the forest no maybe like around
here like right
here that won't work damn it what if we
we can put him in front of the storage
maybe grass wasted that's okay share it
now oh okay here look we can move
it you must connect the dirt with the
green dirt H okay Callie can we build uh
can you take those yeah let's make it in
the forest yeah sounds good like
connected to the forest yeah like what
about here or no
here behind the bamboo maybe yeah seems
good we got rid of
[Music]
this tree out way
tree with the sheep on my leash right
next to the
edge it's a good idea right we only have
good ideas sure why
not of
course this will definitely be enough I
feel for this area will be good this
area will be good just just a little bit
more around the house maybe oh this
trees is encroaching on the Sheep's
crib I'm just getting rid of some of the
leaves that should be good nature we
want the Sheep to feel good right oh
yeah so you can put the fence at the
edge of these blocks I would say oh like
right uh here here
is and then around the where the void is
yeah yeah good gate good gate yeah then
we can just yeah don't forget torches
yeah yeah don't worry don't
[Music]
worry oh interesting I guess that works
what I uh leashed the Sheep but there's
no need need to leash the Sheep right ah
maybe I'll also make a little um roof
for the Sheep too for safety we don't
want never all sheeps and cows die kind
of disaster sheep can jump on the corner
block is that true oh all right let's
get rid of maybe if torches on
it oh maybe still yeah let's get rid of
it okay feel free to here replace it
with
okay here we go okay give me back the
leash yeah this should be
good okay uh enjoy your new life Chad
will will the grass grow on its own
chat I mean not the not the dirt blocks
into grass blocks I mean the actual like
fluffy grass will it grow it little
slowly
okay just got to give it some time yeah
little by
little nice feels kind of dark here yeah
some torches might definitely help
it's time for me to go sleep I think I'm
sleepy oh that's fine thank you so much
for your help no problem I'll be back
for the next installment early morning
yeah early jst morning yeah next
time okay I mean doesn't have to be that
early it's cool I want to I want to I'm
looking forward to maybe just keep an
eye out on each other's schedules let's
do it that way yeah sounds good to me um
yeah looking forward to want to say
goodbye to your viewers bye everybody
bye
T tired sweepy sleepy what's going on
tomorrow um I was supposed to do the 2.0
thing tomorrow but they asked me to move
it a day later so it's going to be the
following day oh yeah so I think I'm
what am I doing what am I check's
calendar there's a lot going I have a
lot of different game plays happen
there's so much going on let's see you
doing a jackbox collab right yeah yeah
yeah jackbox on Tuesday I think uhuh
Tuesday with a just anyone in Ian that
you know can come I think I'll be there
too cool it'll be fun yeah it's a good
time for me actually so yeah yeah
jackbox late at night
jst uh all of Ian is invited so that'll
be cool and uh
yeah I've got Elden ring coming up as
well at some point and I'm finook are we
doing I haven't decided yet but whatever
one I guess everybody has I'll have to
ask around we will figure it
out yeah if you have a favorite let me
know nobody only you have to have it for
jackbox oh yeah that is true actually
never mind I'll think about it if
everyone has a favorite they like to do
and I think it's going to be an off uh
it'll be an off collab for one Member
One member is coming to my house I'll
keep him a secret for now though yeah
there is a member coming over only one I
think someone who who wanted to to come
to my house so ah yeah oh yeah so
that'll be fun just one a singular
one okay well I'll see you guys later
everybody continue enjoying uh Minecraft
with kiaha and Hol live English myth I'm
your yay what a Miss what a Miss hope
you remember me bye-bye everybody
bye-bye forget you a you I can't even
remember to forget you oh my God that's
a song wow that's complicated my mind is
trying to do gymnastics trying to figure
out the true meaning of that I'm not
very smart um everyone take care that's
okay that's why we make a good team two
not very smart people equals smart right
clearly that's how math works that's
just that's F that's myth that's just
myth that's myth that's myth well see
you guys later bye-bye everyone good
night night good night peace byebye
bye take care
yeah for