questions
[Music]
hello welcome everybody
uh I don't have much time so um
let's get straight into it
yeah oh God
[Music]
ha
thank you
[Music]
foreign
mm-hmm
oh welcome everybody to another episode
of hello talk I don't have audio
feedback let's go but uh yeah uh 25th
episode anniversary episode
today's guest is myself that's right
once but twice
pretty also a special announcement at
the end let's go
okay now I have all your feedback
let's hope it goes well
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
hello everybody and welcome to holotalk
special anniversary episode the 25th the
two year anniversary episode here in
this very special 3D Studio that was
recently renovated and here we are today
yeah how's it looking so far I think you
already saw like a little bit like of a
pad like it's
but I'll show you a little bit in detail
but first of all of course I always have
to
um you know explain to you what hello
talk is so let me tell you whole little
talk let's see if I got this by heart is
a live talk show uh with the purpose of
interviewing and live translate life
translating mainly Japanese whole life
challenge today that's a little bit
different but yeah
um to bring as much wholesome knowledge
to you guys as possible very deep deep
knowledge brought to you by your host
Takara I mean
foreign
[Music]
today this is actually
um pre-recorded due to many reasons uh
to avoid scuff and so on
um but I think you will enjoy it very
very much so let's have a good time
today and let me start by showing you
the studio a little bit where should we
start maybe first of course we start
with oh can we start I wonder can we
start
Maybe
let me hear my earpiece my secret
earpiece well let's go okay stop
I've got professional staff helping me
behind the scenes wow so professional
what a live talk show okay so here you
know we step over the beautiful
beautiful stairs in here yeah and then
here
we have and the the host desk yeah
normally I sit on there but you maybe
see a little bit then there's some extra
boxes and there's even a booster seat I
think you can see it a little bit for a
while fiata to sit on top of because
she's so small she needs a little
booster seat don't don't tell her that I
told you that because she might be
really embarrassed about it yeah and of
course you have the laptop and the cup
and I can I can pick up the cup and
drink a little bit I don't know where
the camera is
and yeah then we have the the table for
the guests
you know obviously I can sit on it or I
can sit stand on the couch if I want to
do some party there's the eggs all the
important items yeah yeah don't mind me
I'm just uh it's okay if I stand on the
table no one will complain because I'm
the boss yeah and then connected right
right to that on this side we have the
clip watching area in 3D with the host
side over here I would be
I would be sitting right here and
watching a clip with whatever guest
there is if we ever do it in 3D with a
normal guest yeah today
um we will most likely I think not be
using this in 3D because uh um time
constraints and other reasons behind the
scenes don't question it but the rest
will be in 3D properly at least you've
seen it once here
then uh if we before we go over to the
stage we look over here we have audio
audience how you doing maybe I should
interview you are you having fun at home
talk you got some tickets to the special
episode of hollow talk two years
anniversary oh my God amazing
yeah I think there's a lot of people
jealous at you they might look like
cardboard but they're told oh
thing yay for cardboard no they're not
cardboard they're totally real and
three-dimensional actually this will be
eventually also proper 3D chickens
um so this is just this is just for a
temporary you know temporary they're
cheering okay calm down chickens let me
pass through
the bus is coming through
and I can come down here and then
over here right next to the curtain
where I came through we have this
yay I will be maybe using this later hmm
maybe should I should I what do you
think guys should I use it
yeah I think uh eventually this will
also be even more improved with like
stage lights actually moving you know
there's still room for improvement but I
think this is already pretty amazing
with the microphone here I can sing into
it
yeah that's the studio that's actually
also behind the scenes um some stuff but
oh do you want to see it is it okay to
show
yeah come on in a special tour I don't
know how far you can go maybe you can
only see a little bit uh but there's
some props back here and some coffee and
tea oh it's already closing hi hi
I guess that's all the sneak peek that
you will get today all right then let's
get the show started let's get into
whole talk Shelby
[Music]
welcome
please introduce yourself
uh well I think you already know me
little about fiata but I am from her
life English myth the first generation
in her life the first English generation
I was so lucky to be part of that and
yeah I stream oh almost every day and I
stream mostly like jrpgs and RPGs and
adventure games and all that kind of
stuff I also do music yeah so anyway
today is a special episode where I will
be able to I guess let you guys know
even more about myself especially to all
the viewers who are
um maybe not so familiar with me but
still came here to this special whole
talk anniversary episode thank you very
much by the way yeah so let's go start
it get started with the questions
[Music]
all right so what have you been up to
recently
um
recently I just kind of finished
recently playing a whole playthrough of
GTA 5 and now I just started a new
series I like to always have like one
ongoing series on my channel and then in
between have like smaller games and two
chatting streams cooking streams and
something like that
um but currently I just started playing
Pokemon like everyone else is playing
Pokemon whoa
yeah
I always have like one big thing and
that's the current big thing ah I see
all right next question how did you
discover hello and why did you decide to
join
um
um I
I discovered it
um at the time when I was living in
Japan for one year uh for a working
holiday
um and I was like halfway through the
working holiday and I basically wasn't
doing anything because I arrived in
Japan at the very beginning of the
can't beep right now but you know what I
mean right yeah so
um I wasn't really doing anything but I
started watching
um for example pekuda Senpai mostly
um to kind of cheer myself up because it
was I was kind of in a little bit of a
dark place
um and yeah I felt like I was like in
Japan but I couldn't do anything so it
was like meeting lesson worthless kind
of depressing I know but so then in the
middle of my working holiday I
um saw that who left English auditions
opened for the first time and I was like
a young a young maybe this is this could
be good for me like I've been watching
her alive recently and getting really
deep into it I didn't really imagine
myself doing it yeah at that point but
eventually you know I decided to just
give it a try because in terms of skill
set I thought it would be perfect for me
because I I enjoy streaming and talking
and entertaining and singing I speak
Japanese English German and so on blah
blah so it sounded like I found like
really the smartest thing to do for me
so I gave it a try and I was quite
confident a quite motivated too I don't
know like how long you around fiata took
when your audition to like send it in
and so on but I did it all in one day
because maybe I should have taken more
time maybe I was too enthusiastic it
could have ended up better perhaps
um if I took more time but I mean worked
so I threw it all together in one day
send it in and actually yeah immediately
got a reply yeah so that was actually
what saved me from a really dark place
because from then on everything went
good yay
[Music]
all right next question what's your
favorite type of streaming
I I think my viewers uh like my like
tangents the most and even though I
don't really do that synonyms on its own
they always get that during Super Chat
running so most of my opinions will
probably say my Super Chat reading
surprisingly but for me
um I feel more like relieved and
confident if I have a game to go off on
so I would say just gaming streams
generally but I do like all of these
types of strings I also really like
collaborations because I enjoy like
bantering with whoever I'm streaming
with and like uh like you know just
having a good conversation with them
um I also love karaoke
obviously because I really like singing
and recently I just did my first ever
full body 3D karaoke with my home 3D
that I was able to set up and I think
with that to get ever we're gonna be
doing a lot more like really fun karaoke
streams
um in my home with some cute body
movements which might be scuffed uh
partially more Scruff partially less
Scruff than what I'm doing right now but
um I think this will be a big enrichment
to my kind of okay streams in the future
but I would say first and foremost uh
just gaming streams especially RPG games
yeah
oh okay so who are chunkers and smoothie
by the way junk isn't smoothie I am like
kitty katos is a little bit on the
chunky side that's why it's chunkers and
smoothie is on the very smooth side
that's why it's movie and they're really
really cute fluffy fluffy fluffy cats
that make me really happy I I need them
to survive and I talk about them a lot
on stream as well I'm really sorry to
people who can't really relate but I
think all cat owners or pet owners in
general can relate that and I need to
gush so much about my pets I'm sorry but
I can't help it so if you watch my
streams you kind of have to deal with
that you won't get around it it's Kitty
cups
okay so next what's and do all about oh
and zoo is like an ongoing series
um that I started like
maybe even like around two years ago
um it started because I was um playing a
game called sakuna
maybe while fiata knows that game
um it's like a game about like farming
and like farming rice and farming it to
Perfection and in between like fighting
fighting battling and so on but I was
playing that and
um I think they weren't like frogs in my
rice fields maybe and I was like oh hey
I can do a frog impression so
um I did my famous frog impression which
sounds like I didn't know that one can I
do it now
[Music]
yeah that's it did you hear that mafiana
yeah
so yeah I did my famous frog uh
impression and then everyone was like
how the freak are you doing that oh my
God it's so weird but then from there on
I made like little videos where I would
put whatever animal I'm trying to make
an impression of I would put like a an
image on top of my face with my face
picking peeking through and
um yeah trying to do the impression and
started with M frog and then went on I
did like stuff like M crowd
um cat and lion I think I did
um
did I do and dolphin yet I feel like I
did uh um owl and so on so there's a
playlist of that on my channel and I
always upload them like especially when
I'm on a break just as a filler but yeah
that's my suit collection
[Music]
okay let's look up the next question
um
what is Casper yeah the story behind
Casper Casper
Casper Casper well Casper probably is
not alive anymore but
Casper is
a mouse or a rat that I was living with
temporarily in Japan against my will
yeah I
um when I lived in Japan during that one
year I started Living in a really tiny
one room apartment that had really thin
walls so I had to move as soon as I
could and I moved into a house which was
perfect because for streaming at least
in Japan
sound proving apartments aren't really
not so common but a house is like the
best you can do most likely so I got a
house but it was really really old like
exceptionally old and that showed with
me noticing on my first night after
moving in that
um I heard like Tippy tappy sounds in
the ceiling and in the walls and it was
freaking me out I was like feeling so I
mean I don't I think I was thinking it
must be my mice or rats or so but I mean
in theory I think mice are cute but I
don't know when you hear it yeah that's
the face that I was doing every night or
ever even during the daytime yeah I just
I just I don't know it freaked me out
and then it would like show up during
streams and I didn't want to say it was
a mouse or a rat so I started calling it
a ghost and you know there's this Casper
the ghost the famous Casper so I kind of
named the ghost after Casper first but
eventually I couldn't hide it anymore my
Terra so I had made it at some point it
was a mice a master of rat and mine went
on tried to get rid of them with
professionals and so on but Casper was
insane oh someone's saying I have to
stand up apparently yeah
um Casper would just not let go or die
or go somewhere else we tried everything
and Casper just survived forever and at
some point I accepted Casper's existence
and living together with Casper I was
actually even surprisingly sad
when I moved back to Austria this
terrifying rat mouse
I felt like
sad about departing and saying goodbye
to it
it was kind of weird having these
emotions very concerning but I I do miss
Casper Casper are you watching this from
Heaven I love you I'm so sorry for
trying to kill you
mama
and I was cancer we all love Casper
okay who is fragiwawa and when will she
return
froggy Mama should better never ever
dare to return first of all let me say
that froggy llama in case you're
watching that better be careful
as the name says is a frog that's tried
to be like me and take my Throne uh just
very recently actually it's actually
also connected to the Amazon story
because everybody liked my my frog self
so much that this this froggy llama
version of myself kind of you know
separated itself from my body became its
own entity and then tried to take over
my channel and she did for a whole week
recently that was the Frog Wing you guys
may have been watching that and I was
surprised to see so many of my
supposedly loyal viewers suddenly
decided to be on her side support her
and make her their new Aussie and then I
came back after getting rid of froggy
Wawa
[Music]
all these
all these cheaters they're acting like
as if nothing ever happened but I had
proof because I was collecting proof in
the mean oil in the meantime yeah you
cannot Escape The Gaze of takanasikiana
we all know that
so will frog you all come back well
if she behaves you know I've put her
back into the little glass bowl and
she's swimming and turning and and you
know twisting and maybe we can brain I
can brainwash her back into
understanding that I am Superior and if
she wants to come out again she better
be respecting me yes boundary agreed
do not support froggy lava that's right
if anything supports
that's terrible
okay next how do you learn
choreographies and what's your favorite
oh
um
yeah so I have a five original songs I
think now so all of them since I'm very
into the whole idea of idols and um
having a proper choreography to my songs
um I actually went out to look for a
choreographer of my Lion King and that I
have been working with for all these
songs together and
um you know thinking like of a
choreography together
um and I learned them basically just
because she lives in America my
choreography she sends me like a video
and I will like mirror it and then slow
it down in some parts and then just
basically watch it over and over again
slowly starting by doing really like
non-accurate movements in my body just
mimicking it and then eventually you
know if you repeated several times and
also try to like
um slow it down with where there's some
like faster moves and so on eventually
um you just pick it up I mean I have
more practice with it so I think it
might be easier for me than for some
real amateurs
um but yeah it's also not easy for me
like I'm kind of like out of
um practice a little bit and
it's difficult for me too especially
when I try to learn all the
choreographies from my 3D birthday
concert while I was sick but you gotta
do what you gotta do right my favorite
choreography I think
um
might be heart Challenger or fever night
just because oh
that makes sense heart challenge are a
few and I
um because for favorite night
um you know female is a very special
song and it's very different from my
other songs being synthwave and kind of
like 80s inspired
um so we try to have the choreography
reflect that in some more like elegant
and sexy feminine disco fitting moves
and um so those are really fun to dance
because it's very different from my
other choreographies and high challenge
is just so much fun because when
performing it for an audience then um I
thought up I thought up of like a thing
to do during the chorus where I make
everyone like who have has a towel you
know you have to bring your towel when
you come to a concert of mine and you
then raise it and then swing it and
twist it and twirl it in the air during
the chorus of heart challenge so that's
not really part of the original
choreography but I saw that in idle
concert in Japan before and I thought
that would be so much fun to do with my
audience and they've tried before at for
example me German convention I got
everyone to do that and it was so fun
because the camera and they showed all
the the towels and the air twirling
turning twirling and they said that
actually it created a lot of fresh air
in a really hot room the the convention
room yeah
the solution to feeling hot I did not
think of that at first but it was
apparently a really smart thing to do
yeah so hard Challenge on people night I
would actually say
how long does it take you by the way how
many hours
[Music]
um
I think like to get like the the basics
um down without like really
perfectioning the moves
um
a day
but I take a lot of breaks in between
too
and then I like to take some extra dance
to really like even if you know the
moves yeah if you give yourself a few
more days of practice you will notice
that eventually it will just look so
much more like integrated into your body
and like like you just are way better at
it if you give it up three more days
time obviously so in total muscle memory
right yeah muscle memory as well and
just feeling more confident in the moves
will just give you more like a leeway I
guess
um
and then yeah it's more natural then so
ideally I would give myself a week but
in order to really just memorize
the moves mostly I can do it in one day
[Music]
so you've always had the longest
streaming hours in the end how do you
manage to do so many long streams so
often
um I think
um relax
for me like the amount of time that I
stream from me feels like
kind of like the least I can do like
um it feels to me like the minimum that
I should be doing for myself
um for my own like standards for what I
want to be and how how I want to be as
of each other understandable
um
and I do also sometimes have some days
where I feel like oh I don't really want
to stream today and I am feeling like
coming down but once I start streaming I
almost feel better so I think it's kind
of like a good thing for me
um because I also live alone and I don't
I don't really do much besides streaming
and working so I think it's kind of like
a therapy to me and socializing with the
people with the audience is like pretty
much the only way of socializing for me
but yeah um I think that helps me to
stream longer and more often
um and also
I mean there might be a part of myself
that at least in the beginning nowadays
it's just like routine for me but at
least in the beginning I felt like
I kind of have to compensate for
something uh but that's probably my mind
playing mind games on me but yeah I just
wanted to work harder and work more to
hopefully you know catch up and make up
for
things where else I would let you know
so you really just like streaming huh
don't you I do
um as I said of course there's also days
for me where I don't feel like it but I
I would say I love streaming yeah I mean
it's my job and I'm so I'm so happy that
I have a job that I enjoy and love and I
have a passion for it
so if I didn't love streaming I think I
would have already left hello live by
this point
well thank God that didn't happen all
right guys this is sudden but I have a
clip for you from quinoa here we go
let's take a look at it okay let's go
all right what you got
Chihuahua from the future
three two one go
go
[Music]
holy
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I feel like I'm damaging my throat
amazing
[Music]
let's go I love the questions
you do a lot of special handcamp streams
like cooking using iron beads making a
gingerbread house and stack box streams
don't you
yeah
um I I I feel like I want to have some
variety on my channel and
um
I feel like you know having some hand
cam streams especially uh is just more
exciting you know seeing my actual hands
move around
um I just think it's kind of cute so I
like to do it whatever is possible of
hand cam streams so like the iron beats
for example I don't think I've ever seen
of YouTuber playing with iron beats
before but I got the idea and I kind of
felt like iron beats um itself is kind
of like a nostalgic thing to play with
that I used to play with when I was a
young
so yeah I like to do those especially
I'm proud of my snack box streams so
that's a series where I subscribe to
like a snack box subscription a service
where you can get snack boxes from all
the world every month a different
country and then I I you know review
them on stream show the snacks on stream
and give them a rating and taste them
and then rate them obviously
so those kind of streams are they like
any secret stream ideas you didn't do
yet that you can share
I I mean I hope so I want I gladly take
um some ideas from my listeners if they
have some good ideas uh for handcamp
streams because I've already done so
many and actually just uh this week I
did a air fryer stream where I did a
hand cream with my Empire trying it out
so stuff like that whatever it is
a try because I've already tried so many
things right now my mind is empty way
empty I was actually no one more hand
came stream I wanted to do was like
ironing just ironing my clothes
[Music]
itself and I have so many clubs that
need ironing but never have I ever
ironed my clothes since I bought one and
I feel like I need some motivation even
these kind of stupid ideas I think are
interesting for a stream just because
they're so stupid
so I'll do that eventually but I'm open
for ideas bring them up bring him to me
yeah I love that idea I want to watch it
I want to watch your Island
okay next next question it's gonna be
the last one before the speed question
segment oh nice yeah
you also travel a lot and make content
out of it what is your favorite trip so
far and what are your plans for next
year
um so this year I think I went to the
Maldives right I went to Korea I'm going
to Italy next week
are those older trips maybe I went to
America obviously I went to America of
course and I would say my favorite trip
this year was the Maldives because I
mean how can you not say the ball leaves
I went there with Reina I I asked her
because I I just wanted to go to the
multi it's such a paradise it's a
freaking paradise and I asked Nana if
she made me want to go with me and she
was totally up for it so we met up in
the Maldives and then we took like a
little one of those seaplanes
um small sea plants that you kind of see
in animal crossing the dodo area yeah
yeah I know I did one of those and went
to a an island that belongs to a resort
and the resort was so pretty and I just
my dream was to stay in a like a little
Villa I guess
um on top of the water so when you walk
onto your like Terrace balcony swinging
then you can jump directly into the
water so that was my dream and we got a
a place like that it was absolutely
incredible we went there during a season
where there was just constantly Stormy
Weather and rainy weather and shitty
weather which was unfortunate but we
still got a few days that were nice and
where we could enjoy the the beach and
the water and snorkeling that was my
first time when I tried snorkeling and
it was a good time for me to bond with
Reina so that was a really special
memory memory
um where I could also like make my dream
vacation come true I hope I can go there
again though because I I'm I need to see
more of the Maldives I want to go to
more of the resorts and the islands
maybe I'll bring you to La Fiera do you
want to go totally let's go let's go
snorkeling with the fishing
I wanna snowball yeah all right I'll
bring you I'll bring you well fiata you
come with me
you deserve it you don't eat any good
food there
um
the resort had like I think five
different restaurants
um and they had different Cuisines like
one was
um just general like grill grill food
stuff and one was I had like mostly like
kind of I think Indonesian kind of food
yummy yeah and then there was a sushi
restaurant which I didn't try because I
don't really like sushi I'm so sorry
um but yeah there were several ones too
but we had amazing food there I also
documented everything so if you guys
missed it there was a Maldives review
stream with photos on my channel
um where we talked about the whole
experience all over again showed photos
and so on so you guys should watch that
well next time you go please pack me in
a suitcase okay
[Laughter]
um yeah okay uh I guess it is speed
question
finally I am part of the sweet sweet
Quizlet all right bring it on while
Fiona Bring It On
[Music]
I am
ready
let's do this
hot or cold weather
cold rice
or noodles
[Music]
rice noodles there's rice noodles rice
noodles
[Music]
or Instagram
well recently
spill Twitter yeah
okay apple or orange juice
[Music]
Madison
uh Yankee well would have said Run
America
Mountain let's go
PC all right console
[Music]
okay pineapple some pizza yes
spicier sweet food sweet
or coffee
occasion of beach Paradise or in a
famous Metropolitan City beach beach
let's go to the beach beach
[Music]
sleep naked along with gloves
with panties
[Music]
what's your favorite holiday
oh
Christmas Christmas
family level
texting chatting or talking on the phone
what you prefer
[Music]
texting
giving or receiving presents receiving
[Music]
walk one face no take the train
walk walk walk out work out that foot
and those five yeah no true girl yeah
what's your blood type by the way
oh I don't know I I knew it before but I
forgot
um maybe I'll find out and write a
subtitle otherwise nope okay so no all
right
what's the color of your panties oh
[Music]
she's looking
[Laughter]
elephant
there you go oh yes
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
one day I want to hear the answers from
you though oh
no problem for me
okay so the next question are you ready
you lived in Japan when you debited in
her life but then you moved to Austria
tell us about that time and do you want
to move back again oh yeah sometimes
people ask my dad if I want to go back
to Japan and of course I want to go back
to Japan I'm actually going back to
Japan soon
um but for me I think
um for living I can live comfortably in
Austria right now more or less and
um in Japan as much as I kind of want to
live there again I have kitty cats and
that's like the biggest issue
um and also just it's a bit difficult to
live in Japan for
foreigners often there's many like
hurdles to get over and yeah it's
difficult to get a visa and so on so
it's not only that it's just many issues
in general and also that I have my
family here in Europe I have my friends
here in Europe and in Austria and I just
like living in Europe in general for
many reasons so for a living I would
stay here but I'm definitely going back
to Japan so wait for me wait for me
do you think it was worth it the time
you spent there
yeah I mean the one year working holiday
was not the only time I spent in Japan I
also lived there before
um for like two years so in total it's
kind of like for years
um it was an experience that has
helped me become more mature and
independent and
also
um
what's the word confident yeah helped me
grow more confidence so I would say it's
worth it especially
like at a young age I think it really
was a lot of fun to experience Tokyo
especially also Osaka I lived in Osaka
for a while too so I don't miss those
memories and I'm glad that I did it and
I'm looking forward to visiting more
different places in Japan
okay
well then as you know whole life isn't
always rainbows and ponies but what were
some hardships that you struggled with
during your time
yeah
um there's many and I think my viewers
remember many of them too especially in
the early days
um I uh most of all I had like technical
problems that led to just a lot of
stress and pressure things didn't go
well like internet wasn't installed in
time so I had to live at my manager's
place for a mom thankfully though like
it sounds like I didn't like doing that
but I had a lot of fun living with my
manager
yeah and um just like technical problems
like a PC problems and microphone
problems and I feel like that really
kind of
um
what's the word it's it's messed up my
whole like starts after my debut
um you obviously you have the most eyes
on you
during your debut and the first couple
days after that so true there's so much
pressure to do well and I definitely
felt that but everything went wrong so
if there's some viewers who are here for
the first time in a long time let me
tell you things have improved and I'm
not like I'm crying up after every
single um bad thing that happens anymore
but I was just oh God I was just under a
lot of emotional pressure back then I
think and
um
situation has improved so but that was a
big struggle back then yeah that's we
all hopefully we'll forget about one day
do you think that this experience has
kind of shaped you to what you are today
yeah it made me stronger and
um I think ideal of stress better now
and pressure and all that and there's
still struggles things that I struggle
with now as well
um like
similar issues but let's not bring them
up now but I think everybody in her life
has also partially similar problems that
they deal with
um as a streamer uh and as an idol as an
Entertainer
but I think
that it made me more a better a better
Entertainer actually every struggle that
you overcome in the end will just help
you improve the way you stream and the
way you deal with these issues life
especially
so yeah I think in the end it helped me
yes
[Music]
all right guys I'm hearing this actually
another clip so let's move on over to
Future
[Music]
all right Smokey Wawa what kind of clip
have you got for us this time Bring It
On you'll see
[Music]
did you notice your visitor yet you mean
Casper or the crow what do you mean
nothing else you mean my frog the flash
on the right window right all right
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
compilation of jump scares
Nick
literally just Loops as the end of the
game
yeah right
after like 15 hours
and put the data of the patient
s
if you um you click I think yeah
all of this
so we're gonna cut her throat
thank you
mm-hmm
don't be scared right now there's
nothing to be scared about something to
be scared about
oh my God
you have to watch it
[Music]
um
glue
glutaril blah
oh my god do you want me to say hi
[Music]
oh my God it's just again
what it's all right love is just a game
is she still there you like to play
pranks
very polite oh
[Music]
no oh my God the body is just like you
but this is definitely easier than
phasmophobia like in fact I should have
got anything right hang on a visitor yet
you mean Casper
I see what you did there small koala so
it's kind of like a compilation of jump
scares because I get jump scared a lot
right that's right you do yeah I do I do
again you can jump scares by like the
stupidest thing now but and like looking
back at it like this it's definitely
entertaining I I see I see why it's
entertaining for you guys
um
life is just a big whole jump scare
right kiwawa that's so true yeah
let's go back thank you questions
here we are
as the first and generation of whole
life and also possibly any big YouTuber
Corporation how does it feel to debut as
part of that
oh
honestly we wear
um all of us we were thinking that we
would not be a success at all I was
mostly thinking that because
um you know when it comes to anime
um people usually prefer to watch it
subtitled rather than dubbed
um because it just feels kind of weird
to hear like some English voices coming
out of the anime characters I guess
um and that thinking made me kind of
think that you know it would be the same
thing for Beach Rivers like people would
enjoy seeing Japanese YouTubers but not
them watch English-speaking YouTubers
and I think a lot of the viewers were
thinking the same way I was reading the
same kind of like sentiments but then
luckily for some reason we I guess
we got was we're able to make people
accept us so we're really lucky honestly
like nobody expected so much positive
feedback and so much
um long-lasting support from some of
your viewers I also thought like most of
my viewers would leave me after half a
year at the latest but still here they
are after two years and really really
grateful for that and for the
opportunity to debut as the first
generation and I think in the beginning
um you know we were we were all saying
that
um our Senpai Kirito Coco kind of paved
the way for us and she definitely did
but I also think that after a little
while after our debut we really managed
to make it our own stage and make our
own achievements and kind of be like
Pioneers
um and really like shaping the English
youtubing community and and just
business I guess Branch
um to something that we can be very very
proud of ourselves I think we can take
some credit too
um and yeah just be happy about what we
did and be confident about what we did
with our achievements and the work that
we the effort that we put into our
streams every day
um next question is what stream of yours
would you recommend to people who don't
know you well
um I think a lot of my hand cam streams
are interesting and entertaining
um but if you want to watch something
with a game then I think one game that
people universally love and that I also
enjoy very much and got the feedback
from my viewers that it might be my best
playthrough of any game in my whole
career is my GTA 5 playthrough series it
was fairly recently and so up on my
channel we did it from beginning to end
and uh apparently I'm the only whole
life English YouTuber and even women
whole life as a whole one of the few who
finished it and not just started
I'm actually uh I call myself the game
finisher of whole life English because I
play a lot of long games and I actually
finish them even games that take like
150 hours or so like fire emblem for
example
yeah I I just don't like leaving things
unfinished you know I I wanted to
properly end and the ending always like
it gives me this feeling of
accomplishment and it's just so nice to
play something from beginning to end
with my viewers together with me the
whole experience of that
it's just I feel like we're bonding you
know and I don't I just I just can't
leave it like that because then I will
always wonder oh
how that game ended I will never know
because I stream games as my uh
um job so I don't really have time to
play games outside of streams mostly so
if I play a game and then I need to
finish it on stream otherwise
um we all know that otherwise I will
never do finish oh we we know a certain
game that I have troubles finishing also
because I I also have the problem though
that I don't want to finish like Netflix
shows and certain games as well that's
when it's finished then it's finished
and I can't experience it again that's
kind of sad so sometimes I just end it
right before the end
um but usually I try to finish
everything on my channel I am the game
finisher yes
so are there any favorite games you
finished while you are streaming in
whole life
mmm yes near automata
which was also that was a challenge holy
that was quite a challenge
especially because I apparently for most
of the game
um sabotaged Myself by having some
resync setting either on or off and I
don't know if Rafaela you ever played
near automata before uh but there's like
this hacking uh that you have to do with
one of the characters that you play and
it makes a huge difference when you
um
and have the vsync on or off I forgot
which one it was but I had it wrong and
then turning it on in like the very late
part of the game
suddenly everything was so much easier
and it blew my freaking mind
everyone is also like seeing the
difference in the Stream and they're
like how did you play this game
that's it the whole time but yeah I
really
enjoyed near automata and finishing it
was an experience that I am so glad I
had together with my viewers
wholesome
okay
oh
how did you get the idea of a whole talk
and what is important to you when doing
an episode oh talk well that's what
we're doing right now
um the idea
I think it's the idea itself kind of
happened off screen I did bring it up
very early on
um on stream but I think it came to me
off screen because I was thinking about
you know I can speak Japanese in English
and German but
um I wanted to do something that would
make good use of my skills and so I
thought that at the time
um whole life was like really booming
especially for Clips the Japanese
members a lot of Clips were transl being
translated out there but I was watching
it and I was thinking
ah there's so much more to them than
just these little Snippets of them
there's so much more content and so much
more personality and and just back
around to them that I want people to
know about but
um the clips just don't convey it alone
even though they're funny but I want
people to know more so I thought how
about I make a program where it's a talk
show I interview the members I live
translated from Japanese to English so
that all the clip watches specifically
but also not necessarily clip watches
but just general general home live
viewers who watch maybe other members
more than others but they might want to
give some other members a chance every
once in a while and this would be a good
way to introduce them to some new
members that they might want to you know
become a big fan of in the future so
yeah so I think whole talk has been a
big big project of mine my biggest
project that I put a lot of love into a
lot of passion it's like my baby you
know
um I try to take good care of it
recently we got this whole renovation
yeah this is a special anniversary
episode it's very beautiful and yeah but
what I I think
um I
especially uh take care of yeah with
like an interview is I want the guests
to feel comfortable and appreciated I
want them to think
um I want them to not only think no
because it is a fact that what they have
been through what they've experienced
what they've worked on so far is
interesting and respectable and we want
to hear more about it and give them a
place to talk about it in depth even
about things that happened two years ago
or three years ago because I think it's
worth sharing the past from everyone
Live member from the beginning to now
where they are now because they don't
work really hard yeah
for my questions
um I I do always
um ask because I I love our life but I
don't know every detail about every
member so I always ask everyone to send
in submissions
um for questions especially the fans of
that guest because they know more about
it but
um the way I choose questions I I don't
just choose questions like oh what's
your favorite food oh who which home of
English member do you want to collab
with in the future or you know stuff
like that that feels very very
superficial to me I look for very
specific questions that give a good
overview to viewers who don't know you
yet uh what like kind of streams you
generally do what's what to expect from
you
um and also some deeper knowledge
because like I think if you don't know
me and I tell you here that my favorite
food is tonkatsu well that's probably
Not Really Gonna Get You hooked on me
and not really gonna give you a good
image of who I am what I do and you know
what my streams are like so I have this
Phoenix eye that I use to zoom through
the scan for the questions I'm very
picky so I'm sorry if your questions
don't get picked but there's also
submission so thank you for that by the
way for always helping me out thank you
Sean hmm
my kitchen
okay A bit more about her talk will
whole talk ever end and do you plan any
other shows or projects right now
[Music]
I I think that the pacing that I'm going
at even though I feel like adding new
members to whole life has been kind of
slowed down a little bit in comparison
to before like two years ago
um but still at this pacing especially
with the big break that I had this year
with holotalk I think I've never really
completely
um be done with her talk but I might
just for my own choice to move on to
other projects eventually ended at a
point where I feel like okay I'm
satisfied with this I think I've done
enough and this is a point where I I
think it's a good cutoff point but at
the moment especially since we just got
the renovation don't worry I'll be doing
it for quite a while longer I also want
to interview whole life English members
and then translate what they say into
Japanese for the Japanese viewers who
maybe don't know the English members so
well and also the ID members possibly so
there's still a lot of potential still
have content that I can do
um so yeah don't worry guys but in terms
of future projects I did mention
recently that I kind of want to do like
a news show
um I still have to like work on that
idea but I want to do a new show that
focuses on whole life English members
specifically because there's already
news shows and for that whole life
Japanese members do for Japanese members
mostly they sometimes pick up like
collab English members information
that is very yeah that's right
spread but I want to go a little bit
deeper I feel like we need someone here
who talks about what web English is up
to updates everyone about that I want to
hear that that is a possible project for
me
all right the next question you have
been a YouTuber for like two years or
more than two years now what do you like
the most about this job in particular
I this might be a little bit while
breaking but um I obviously worked like
normal jobs before
um but the good thing about this one is
I can do it from home first of all I can
decide what I want to do on what day
myself I designed the schedule myself I
designed the way I want to
um grow my path you know if I want to do
more songs if I wanna I mean there's
still some restrictions and and some
help that I need from the company and
then adjust to that and so on but mostly
like I I can decide so many things for
myself and create
the best version the ideal version of
myself that I want to be
um and so but you could say that you're
Your Own Boss yeah I lay on bus exactly
more or less yeah sorry but I feel yeah
I'm definitely my own boss and then uh
one big thing that I really appreciate
is I can stream with no makeup in
pajamas with frizzy bad hair and no one
will manage because there's just this
magic that makes me look like this of
course I woke up like this of course how
dare you doubt it
they will never know
it's so convenient right she woke up
like this just like that next question
is unfortunately the last one thank you
so far yes of course thank you for
interviewing me about Fiona you're doing
a good job maybe you have to take over
when I go on a break
[Music]
please have mercy on us baby last
question uh last question
this one always comes at the end so you
might know it what does whole life mean
to you
whole life to me
is
a last chance
um I I
think my viewers notice as I've talked
about it sometimes but as also if you
think about how I started out in a very
dark place
um there's so many things I still wanted
to accomplish and I was at a point where
I thought I could never accomplish them
I was done
um and with her life
even though it's not like
so easy as it might seem for Outsiders I
still have a chance to try to do things
that I I really want to do like a
concert and bring out songs original
songs and so on so for me it's kind of
also a last resort
um so that's why I try to really work
hard and do as much as I can in the time
that I have and in this special
opportunity that has been given to me
that was that was beautiful thank you
guys yay this was nice to be interviewed
and deaf uh it's kind of you know nice
to talk about it I hope you guys learned
um something new or I mean if you can
feel that you probably knew most of this
but yeah um thank you for interviewing
me while piano and now my pleasure
um I will
uh announce something
you want to hear a special announcement
about Vienna
bring it on baby there is
a special announcement in this 25th and
two year anniversary episode of hollow
talk and that's also Library what is it
[Music]
let's hear it hear it I will show it
show it on this screen
in in free
no
wow
talk Merchant
merchandise
official merchandise for the anniversary
as you see on screen right now we have a
lovely T-shirt with all the names of the
participants that have been uh on whole
talk so far including me wow accounting
until the 25th episode it's kind of like
I imagined like you know those those
tour
um T-shirts from like fans when they go
on tour and on the back they have every
city yeah that's kind of what I imagined
with that then we have a mug with the
whole talk logo I thought it was very
fitting since we're kind of like a late
night talk looks cool and uh oh yeah a
sticker as an extra wait what else do we
have ah of course oh my God the acrylic
diorama This was
um an idea that I thought was absolutely
lovely
I I maybe my acrylic dioramas are not my
favorite type of merchandise but in this
case I thought if you guys have
um acrylic stands from other whole life
members oh what would be smart to do is
release that chicken from its position
and put that whole life member acrylic
diorama right next to me oh and we have
them here in the whole talk studio so
there's in the background and in the
front you have the acrylic
um standees of meat and the chicken or
whatever you already own it's probably
should fit like a lot of them should fit
I'm hoping that was the plan so try it
out if you already have some or if
you're getting any extra ones in the
future you can combine them and make
your oh no we'll talk episode basically
yeah so if you get it as a whole set you
also get some stickers what a deal I
don't want to talk about the sticker
so that's really exciting to me because
I normally you know merchandise is like
you know for anniversary on birthday or
so on and and I asked if it's possible
to get some
[Music]
cool and
the second approved luckily so please go
grab it it's uh gonna be available I
think now or whatever this is
pre-recorded haha so I don't know when
exactly but have you ever pinned in the
chat or I will tweet it out of course or
it might be if you're watching this as a
vault it might be in the description
already so go check it out and please
support hello talk then I can put even
more uh money into it in my baby project
yeah and make it even more amazing and
professionally thank you for the support
so far you guys made it possible thank
you for believing in me and yeah all the
guests who have been on hold talk so far
um to be interviewed by me even though
I'm always a nervous wreck but yeah it's
been quite the honor to me I'm so proud
and yeah it's been fun so now before we
end with one Fiona we're gonna have a
little performance and use that stage
over there so please listen to my new
song in our 3D Studio in the we are do
you and with that in German we say
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
there's something special about you you
wanna know it's true
[Music]
you know it I just can't resist you your
eyes are like a spell that I can break
through and that should scare me but I
don't know baby you're captivating me
and in the end you let me go oh
love hate all the same if you know play
that game imma locked up up inside no I
can fight the feeling and I won't try
hey all the same if you'll know play
that game maybe you decide if you want
me to shout it out right now
[Music]
assistant
don't ever let yourself falling you got
it cause life is like a toxin though my
pain is so common your problem I can
solve it I'm just a full in love know
that this one did not crash so you can
save me I'm in too deep and I love the
rush yeah I just can't resist you your
eyes are like a spell that I can break
through and that should scare me but I
don't know baby you kept invading me and
in the end you let me go
love hate all the same if you now play
that game I'm a locked up up inside no I
can fight the feeling and I won't try
all the same if you know play that game
baby you decide if you want me to shut
it up
[Music]
do you do you India
be making me feel so right
pick me up just like you do I'm always
coming back to you you you you you you
you
let's go
[Music]
to YouTube
love is just that game we play Love
hatred stand betrayed do you do you say
love is just the game we play Love
hatred stem betrayed
hey
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you guys for watching
ah merchimasu
[Music]
yeah whole talk forever
Holo talk Viva La Holo talk now let's
have some food
ah
bye bye
[Music]
foreign