[Music]
a
KY
key
sorry I
realized
that why why did I do
that some which game was
it I was Family
Feud uh ever since family feuded like
four Family Feud because the game
doesn't exist in and any I think any
other Nintendo store than the American
one I had to change my account to be
American like normally you know
switching country is not a big issue
I've done that before to change through
like Japanese account Etc and you can
always switch
back the problem is only with the
American one it's not that
easy yeah because well the American one
didn't take my payment
options right so I got like narissa to
help me remember that basically she
bought me like a
$5 uh like gift card for the Nintendo
for the American Nintendo shop
Ohio
and the game was like like five bucks or
so and I paid with that but there's like
a few cents left and you can't change
back to a different country your your
account you can't change
it uh if there's still some money left
on your account but you also can't get
rid of it and there's nothing you can
buy for that amount of money
either yeah so then I was like trying to
get into the online thing here of Mario
Kart and I realized oh I cancelled my
Nintendo Online subscription in order to
change the country that is like the only
thing you have to do to change the
country of your account um but you know
the the active subscription will still
be active it will just not be renewed
you only have to cancel the
renewal but
anyway the
renewal like the point of the renewal
was over and it didn't get
renewed
and um well American account doesn't
take my payment options so I couldn't do
that but you know what I did I got
myself a free trial of seven days
Nintendo
online
yeah yeah I did set up like another
account recently because I wasn't able
to get out of the American account
anymore so I said another austan one
but I could have had that cat
hair okay could have had the Nintendo
Online subscription on the other account
that is fine for me but when I turned on
the free subscription on the other
account I noticed anyway that if I go
into Mario Kart with my other new
account it doesn't have like it's a new
Mario Kart account it doesn't have any
anything of the things I worked so hard
for to um um you
know to get the carts and the wheels and
everything so I was like [\h__\h] no let me
let me activate the 7 day trial on the
American account for now and then later
on figure out how the [\h__\h] I'm going to
get out of this American account
setting yeah there is a way I found like
on on Reddit I found someone with the
same problem pretty much and oh
seems to be a way but you kind of have
to contact Nintendo and they will clear
their remaining money on the account for
you you can't do it yourself you have to
get customer
support yeah thank you Reddit thank
you but for now it's fine 7day trial
let's make the most of it it's been a
while it's been a while I've been
planning to play a little bit of Mario
Kart again um because new tracks keep on
coming out and now apparently it's
finally over like they finally finished
all those
[Music]
waves so I want to play with you guys
today we we we oh yeah it seems like all
of them are in that took them AG felt
like 2 years but was it one year maybe
how how long did it take them feels like
2 years but it's probably 1 or 1.5
[Music]
years a similar problem but with apple
really oh man so
[Music]
annoying one it really was close to 2
years holy [\h__\h] one year for wave 1 to
three one year for wave 4 to sixo W
where's the rest of
them wait yeah where's
Five where is
five
aha
aha just kidding I know exactly what's
going on
here the real question is where where
are where's the pant
hole where's the rest of my pants why
why is there a hole in my
pants
sorry guys
for um the the past two videos or
streams I have put up on
YouTube I apologize for concerns I may
have caused me no not really I don't
really apologize but it's it's been it's
been uh kind of
funny it's been
funny
um sorry for trolling you guys but the
the pants thing though the pants thing I
really I had to talk about it okay I I I
I was I was shocked to the core I was
shook at I was terrified I was ashamed I
was
just I had to work through the issues
that that have arised you know thank you
thank you for understanding thank you
for being there for me in those
troubling
times my [\h__\h] Fant man I have a I
have a hole in my like that phrase came
to me before the stream and I was like I
I can't just tweet that like I was going
I was I was going to Tweet I have a hole
in my in my ass yeah I have a hole in my
ass I was like giggling to myself and
like I I can't just tweet that let's
make a stream out of it let's let's talk
to you guys because I really need to
talk about it and just say I have a hole
in my ass yeah sorry my humor
um yeah apparently there's a new way
to make a tournament I think it's on the
friends and
Rivals where was it me
wow who are these people oh old people I
played with um so I guess we make a room
like this now right cuz now we can you
can cre a room for playing privately
with friends no but now you can also
play with nonf friends right why is why
is this outdated this
message why is this
outdated I I I'm changing my main to cat
peach for
today and I got some new Wheels I don't
know if they're good but why not oh no
that's that's not even the new Wheels I
think wait is
this ah ah okay I can show the room I ID
there um but like maybe let's set
settings first also the cool thing is
that I can um I can set the track it
doesn't have to be
randomized
and uh the only negative thing is I have
to make a new room each time but it
doesn't seem to take a lot of time so
how do
I I maybe ah maybe after I press okay do
you choose everything after you press
okay
for okay okay then let's try it out like
that uh I think that's the the way to go
now has some
UPS mostly UPS okay
here DH I think that's a
zero
r z
I think it's a zero close am I too
close enter can you guys
enter for real for
real all
right
hello oh oh here they
[Laughter]
come yeah yeah yeah the usual the usual
Racers o and The Gambler me and uh oh P
but wait the other the other noi was um
uh what's her name
again what's the name
again a nice drive nice
drive hey why leave oh oh is that Lami
no it's p ah oh wait these people they
have like this why are you guys leaving
I'm heading off no no no no no why why
why why why why why there's like a pain
Peru Army let's go okay I think wait but
are we even 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 we're
not complete Are
We join
join the Kaa wasn't that
KY AA look
alike can't can't join oh yeah that's
the thing like with the other with the
old lobbies like you would think you're
in the lobby maybe but then you're in
the lobby with no
n is this like uh time like you get
kicked out of while why why do they
leave won't let me join but like it
would happen that you're like being put
in a different Lobby that's like not um
mine and then there's like two lobbies
running at the same time this can't
happen here 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 10
can't join we don't know which Lobby
what do you mean you don't know it's
what it's not the usual
place oh 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
11 Max 10 isn't yeah I thought it was 12
did I limit it to 10 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 now it's 11 though I didn't limit
anything uh they're changing me and
oh okay
okay maybe maybe we shall just
try it says think it's full okay 1 2 3 1
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 okay it's 11 well
that's fine and no teams normal items no
CPU uh all vehicles
four
one it four oh we have to do four
Ah
that's we have to do four together and
that sucks though then I'm I I think I'd
prefer going to uh oh hell 12 person
maybe to what what the map how do I
choose the map again does it come up now
cuz I get to choose
right people can leave off the one yeah
but so we're obviously going for the
newer ones that I haven't done yet let
me see uh these
ones I don't even think I've done this
one before have
I merry Mountain rainbow R oh this also
feels
new
[Music]
no M uh maybe let's start with this one
I think a BL session
has enable yeah yeah
oh wait I don't get to choose no no vote
for mine vote for
mine you have to no what why is it
random I was told it wasn't
random
huh
he I was talk I have to buy what my DLC
is included
no is it because someone in there
doesn't have
it oh gooa
joined what what I'm so
confused still random what I've been
bamboozled also I don't know anymore how
to play this game it's been a long time
this the the first time oh potion don't
take my
coins you know I have financial problems
right now how do I use an item
again
uhow how do I use an item a there you go
left
L and ghost woo
woohoo oh let's go straight that that's
a shortcut isn't it all right double
item
marvelous oh I get a
star m not really useful here
though once it's gone I'll use my bullet
there we go hey yeah do the work for
me I don't want to move a finger thank
you oh nice D
bye-bye hey
why am I so far in the front
[Music]
huh another star [\h__\h]
no uh-oh
uh-oh no [\h__\h]
you no what I'm getting so [\h__\h] right
now oh but I got a lot of uh coins there
and another star what when did I get
another
star hey
oh you pushed me away from my
item language ke language ke I haven't
heard that in a long time people used to
always say language K to me but I guess
you guys gave up you know by now there's
no use in telling
me let's go let's get 11th at least
bye-bye bro you little
[\h__\h] oh can we beat beat Hulan yes yes
yes look at my ripped ass hokan stay
behind me don't you like looking at my
ripped ass
[Laughter]
H for people who do not
understand please watch my previous
stream from today that was only 10
minutes long and then you will
understand okay so we can choose again
everybody choose Peach Gardens a session
has purchased a
boost
so yeah oh I don't have it of course I
have
it of course I have it what it's
probably because of all the account
changing and confusing [\h__\h] don't you
get these when you have the membership
do I not get it if I have a trial
membership
maybe thank you
guys for following what I'm saying even
though there's latency
issues yeah what it be one of the very
few ones are
[Music]
different boy okay we did not
immediately go to the next race so I
could kick kick everyone out and cancel
the race right and then go to the next
one I
[Music]
guess I used to have the expansion pack
for sure though like yeah the trial is
just basic oh
whatever as long as you guys have it I
guess it doesn't
matter how do I make these um flips
again is this one new to me this race
this track not sure if this feels new to
me oh my God I missed ah ah
careful ah ah I was like extra careful
there let's
go I can still win this woohoo
woohoo uhoh this is so scary oh my God
no no
no oh sh yeah I'm leeching off of you
[Music]
guys I'm getting back into the
groove pretty useless
star ow
[Music]
okay oh I didn't get the the block the
the the the the
stunt
[Music]
extra I hate this ah hul drove off the
cliff and I get something nice but why
am I why am I turning like that
ah a a the controls feel so weird to me
right now maybe it's cuz I'm more used
to fzero at this point than to Mario
Kart I don't like this I don't like this
course
gold who was going to be in an aquarium
I heard like how in what capacity is she
going to swim even though she can't swim
is she going to be okay can I be
concerned yeah you was that motional GAA
because what the [\h__\h] I was just talking
about you how do you what why you treat
me like that jump right in my
face n the
[\h__\h] are they giving her
[Music]
floaties live show yourself is this like
like the one that Chloe did then I
wonder I guess you guys don't know the
details either I should ask ga
cuz uh Chloe did something like that but
I think it was her 1 million subscribers
wish let's go let's [\h__\h]
go I could have been
fifth who was that piece of [\h__\h] I could
have been
fifth
you stole my
happiness
sheesh maybe they just
advertise with her okay guys uh choose
um Yoshi's
Island Yoshi's Island Yoshi's Island no
ah I chose the wrong one please choose
Yoshi's
Island please Yoshi's Island thank you
Yosi Island I want to go to see Yoshi
Yosi Yosi Yoshi
Yosi
[Music]
I should I should cancel between no why
is
it no oh well I don't know if I ever had
this one before let's check it
out
ch ch
chol
CH someone's called
cholate it's asking me for
[Music]
it we will go to Yoshi's Island don't
worry about it we
will
ooh I think that's a first for
me ooh the music when when was even the
last
time
that I played Mario Kart
no I hate
[Music]
you that was good placement holy
[\h__\h] why am I so wobbly why is
my I'm so
unstable I last time I played on stream
was 12 months ago
oh no
way for
[Music]
real you have motion control on oh maybe
I mean who knows oh no it doesn't seem
to react when I move the
[Music]
controller
H okay let's
go yeah Paris the one with Paris was
maybe the last one I tried yeah maybe
maybe that's so many stars behind
me H why why it's hard to see it's so
bright you can't even see that there's
an an obstacle
there this
SCH well now it's
darker let's go does that even make you
faster when you're flying I'm not sure
cuz it doesn't look like I'm faster but
I think I am
[Music]
faster yes this time I got it this
time okay nice curve nice curve
oh nice do
yooo okay ah the [\h__\h] snow I swear to
God yo yo yo yo
yo I'm always happy when I can show
someone who's the
Boss yay y yay I don't know why I'm
happy why am I happy I'm G to kick you
guys out
now I'm going to
leave is that do I are you guys being uh
kicked
out if I do
this get out of here oh damn that's a
long dark
screen
okay we're making a new one
than my stream no it's not over I'm just
reopening the
[Music]
lobby it's what happens when you don't
let me win yeah exactly
he anyone who's already in please
refrain for now thank you
jd8
[Music]
G1 tearing you a new
one I I would like to just out of
equality so that I'm not the only one
who has a new one
torn people are coming in welcome
welcome um please try to choose the
track that I'm saying we should
choose
please there we are are hello
hello cute everybody kfp has assembled 1
2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 11 but also last
time we got the 12 one later on anyway
so probably di
over another pain PA yeah there's
there's uh
several is that supposed to be a
lapas with some really strong
cheekbones okay let's play one of the
new ones guys whatever you put in put in
one of the new tracks okay thank
you uh okay oh wait 150 yeah
okay my Wasing suit this is my Wasing
suit it's piping hot and how about oh
sing Singapore Speedway how about that
because just recently there was a AFA in
Singapore
right oh oh you guys hear me so fast oh
maybe they saw in the
game but I couldn't even see what you
guys were
choosing Singapore looked fun looked fun
very fun I only saw pictures I wish at
least the members the other talents
could
see you know
what's happening a lot of these things
are usually happening over Zoom calls
so I wish I could I wish I could just go
on the same Zoom call I mean I probably
could but they don't share the zoom
calls with us unless you're
participating but if I asked they
probably would let me
in yeah it's just so
hype so
hype and the like oh my God the eyes of
the audience from the pictures I
saw was crazy looking ooh is this what
Singapore looks like honestly like the
Berlin one for example oo nice music was
really pretty accurate in my opinion so
oo nice rooftop pools let's go is that
something Singapore does a
lot
woo oh I like the I like the
music let's
go
[Music]
okay a
St damn they're giving out the Stars
like it's Black Friday it was Black
Friday just uh like last Friday wasn't
it did you guys buy
something think the only thing I bought
was a game
maybe ah [\h__\h]
I bunked someone I did
it oh another star maybe we can bunking
up ah these curves are [\h__\h]
stupid steam sail yeah steam sail went
on for more than just one
day very very nice of I almost missed
the item
Yak I uh I I want to I want when is that
the cuz I heard that the Yakuza that
I've been hearing about is just like a
really short
one almost like a teaser of a game
when's the like the actual proper one
coming
out where am I going down
up there was a path up
too freedom I guess January 26 okay
that's still pretty soon what the
[\h__\h]
M it's almost over give me a good item
okay just go to the goal just go go go
go go go go go go go go go go yo yo
yo all right all right all
right mhm mhm and on that positive note
I would like to kick you all out One
race is only getting I I raced too much
with the previous ones this is how you
Mario Kart
[Music]
[\h__\h] what a comeback it's pretty
accurate for the singpore map really she
what a crazy
City but I know I heard it's like a
really expensive city right and like
damn it's like really flashy
looking also hot as [\h__\h] cuz like I was
talking with
jenma about AFA how how I would like to
go and here's the room lxf fre R and and
um talking with her about it and she was
like no cuz she's been in Singapore
she's like no you don't want to no it's
so [\h__\h] hot oh I'm like even now
apparently yeah apparently even yeah
it's now now even now it's [\h__\h] hot
what
What I Hear they've got a lot of malls
oh that's interesting that's um similar
to Indonesia then maybe a lot of these
countries could it be that they there's
just this thing with malls because it's
so [\h__\h] hot always they just build a
lot of these nice flashy malls with air
conditioning so you can
escape into them at any time is is is it
like a
thing a common
theme oh seems like it that's
funny let's go to the mall uh uh with
what's her name Robin
Sparkles Let's go to the mall wasn't
there a song like
that let's go to the
mall not the Coconut Mall no no no no no
no no please choose new track thank
you is that that one with the butt chin
looks
funny see the last one always enters
like in the last
moment let's go to the mall today okay
uh how
about if if atin aens I want to go here
wait there's a Cute Ducky one what the
hell thank you guys thank thank you
thank you for
listening thank you thank you d one of
them chose the ducky one I wouldn't be
mad if it got to be the ducky one
either to the mall ad oh that's that's
the kind of mall that I want to go to
the mall of
Thieves hell
yeah uh let me take a fro candy cuz like
this you know you know how it is in the
winter [\h__\h] I'm so
[\h__\h] I'm so
[Music]
[\h__\h] take thank you did you say see ah
I got I see I saw I I see I saw I am
seeing I've been sawing I've see I see I
see saw so mhm I have been nominated as
one of the
four best Doon
hey just chatting chitchatting
hey
streamers H for a
man for V Awards oh is it streamer it's
V Awards
right so if you guys want to vote for me
I would be delighted to have your
vote oo wow I've never been to a
a I don't know how you say it in English
[Music]
properly I should go wait hey I I mean I
saw the arrows but it looked like there
was a hole there that I could possibly
go into so I
[Music]
mean wo
kind of false
advertisement don't you
[Music]
think
a well yeah I don't ever do I rarely do
dedicated zans but you guys know I don't
have to have a dedicated zadan stream to
give you guys good chatting material who
plays those I guess it was the
funder well this has been [\h__\h] so far
thank you very much but at least the
scenery is
nice
yeah ooh
oh that's gorgeous I I can't seem to do
the jump timing
anymore those houses they look really
[Music]
nice
meow meow I'm a candy cat and a meow
meow meow meow ow I got
protected let's go but I got no item
anyway ooh stairs love stairs [\h__\h] oh
that
hurt it was cardboard cut out I'm
12 no [\h__\h] way oh somebody stopped
for me parle I love
you I love you partially I saw you
stepping there
it was literally on the finishing line
but it worked you the
best love okay get out of
[Music]
here Pasley you'll be forever in my
heart thank you for your
sacrifice yeah speaking of my all of my
streams being chatting streams and me
tanging all the
time let me tell you about something
that happened to me let's go for the
ducky race next ducky ducky duck duck
duck today just today I I know I still
have so many tangents from my Japan trip
but this is fresh so I want to get it
out of my
system um I went to the post office
today I was I was going to go yesterday
but some things I I almost I almost
probably injured my hand forever Never
by really
really um moody
[Music]
moody what how to
say I
have
H um I just yeah I was signing under
huge time pressure several hundreds of
cards and it was so painful the last two
hours of signing I signed probably for
like 5
hours yeah I think I'm going to have
carpal tunnel
syndrome um but yeah then because I was
really trying to make it work before the
post Office closes but uh even though I
heard so much and I was about to go to
the Post Office it was still like little
little bit too late so I went today
instead
yeah duck duck please guys duck
understand I'm
what no I'm genuinely concerned that I'm
going to get it though this not a joke
I'm genuinely
[Music]
concerned I'm just like fing I'm
laughing out of
pain m
maybe no more what I wasn't
procrastinating I even started really
early but then work kept on getting in
the way and then I brought them all to
Japan to sign them in Japan like I was
motivated I was on it I was going to do
it but I brought them back to Austria
because I
knew after a while yep that that ain't
happening I don't have the time to sign
him I did not procrastinate I did not
procrastinate just had so much [\h__\h]
work in the past weeks but yeah I got it
done and so I went to the post office
and I the moment I
entered Ducks the moment I entered they
were already like 30 people or so I had
to pull a number out of a
machine hello
lag and there were like so many people
they were all like sitting there waiting
it looked like they were waiting forever
and nobody seemed
amused oh
oh and I saw at the very front at the
counter there was only one lady so yeah
it was very obviously a problem of not
enough people working on that day but
you know it do be like that
sometimes Sorry Miss
f
it's like a bathtub level how nice I
love this it's
[Music]
cute
course I'm just here to tangent I'm not
here to win but this is
stupid we need fences toilet let's
go um but yeah I I I'm so far away from
everyone else I took the number and I
was waiting and waiting and waiting
and in total I waited like maybe 50
minutes until I was done I was I was in
the post office for 50 minutes which is
fine I mean I was
chilling more or less but in that time
frame something happened but first
before that incident I noticed that the
lady the one lady the single lady who
was
working she she would she would yell out
the numbers like 98
99 100 like really angrily and like the
like after 1 second she would call out
the next one because she was really
stressed out I
guess um it was so tense when somebody
would come up to her uh after they were
called she would be like yeah what do
you need
passport like really short words loud
and tense so the whole atmosphere in the
room was really tense as
well and sometimes the customers would
come up to her and ask her like what
what's what's wrong like you know you
good like you maybe maybe take a chill
pill I you know we understand you're
alone
here like I I personally found uh it's
kind of scary her bad mood was kind of
scary to me but I mean it was
understandable you know I was thinking I
was reminded about the
times uh when I
was working at a hotel reception wow
didn't even get to the Finish Line [\h__\h]
you
guys and when I was working at a hotel
reception uh as a a
trainee
and then had like I was alone and I had
like 20 people to check in and I was not
even that good yet so I wasn't very fast
and I was super feeling super pressured
that they were all individual check-ins
no groups Etc so like I I remember like
how stressful that is and I mean
obviously you don't want to stand here
alone and
obviously you would appreciate help too
but it is what it is you have to deal
with the situation the way it is so you
know I feeling kind of bad for her and
I'm sure that many people where no
matter where you work have made similar
experience
right so uh the whole at in the room was
kind of like yeah we understand it's
fine but she do be in a bad mood um
that's that's not the best but all right
you know it is what it is we're waiting
waiting waiting eventually This Tall
adult relatively old maybe
45y old man um shows up at the
counter and uh like it's his time he got
called right so he goes up to the
counter he talks to the lady he
immedately pulls out like some letters I
was standing really close to the counter
just
chilling and he shows the letters let me
let me tell my
story cuz I'm not going to focus on the
race huh the I'll tell you the story
then we continue racing it's it's not so
much left okay he shows some letters and
then like he he still talks relatively
in a normal tone like in terms of volume
at least
um but I can hear it very clearly pretty
much so he shows the letters and he's
like talking about something like he has
a bank account at the post office uh
Bank thingy and they're closing it and
basically he
like either the in the letters he's been
kind of being
summoned to go do something uh or it's
it it has been closed and like there's
no reason for it so he wants to know the
reason so he goes to them to ask for the
reason but they're like yeah we can't
tell you like it's not some some it's
not an information that we
have we can't give you this information
so sorry and then he's like getting
agitated that he waited an hour and that
he was here yesterday too and that some
other employee told him uh like I guess
on the phone or from another post office
they told him to go here and then you
were telling me that I need to go there
blah blah blah like he's getting
agitated okay and I'm starting to feel
anxious because he's getting louder he's
getting more disrespectful and the lady
is obviously already stressed out
because she has like 30 people waiting
in the room at all time it's not getting
less
and she only has like one more person in
the post office who's been like like
doing some stuff in the back with the
packages and she asks her to come by to
deal with him because he's just getting
really annoying so they step one Meer to
the side to still talk at the counter
really loudly and he gets louder and
louder and like really
unfriendly and it this whole time I'm
I'm in my in my heart I don't want to
say this is like anxiety attack or
whatever cuz I don't know what an
anxiety attack feels like I don't know
but I was getting I I was feeling really
anxious and like tense and like I want
to bang my head against the wall please
stop screaming uh or like I don't I
don't like this at all I've been I was
feeling like really uh not comfortable
at all listening to this conversation
and it wasn't stopping like they
obviously told him five 10 times that
they couldn't help him and yet he keeps
on repeating the same [\h__\h] and doesn't
leave and but then after uh he even like
asks like who is the boss and then the
lady says me and then he's like you
you're the boss me and then he he starts
changing the topic instead of
complaining about them not um being able
to give him this information he now
complains about the fact that there's no
one else here working this post office
you only have one person working her is
so [\h__\h] like unbelievable what's going
on here and then while he like yells
this he looks around in the room kind of
like talking to us as if we are
his uh nakama his uh uh companions I
don't know his colleagues like we're on
his side and we're all pissed out off
just like him no like we're all kind of
like yeah maybe annoyed at waiting so
long but at the point where you started
yelling at the lady I think we all in
our heads were thinking you're the
annoying one you're the you're the bad
one not the ladies like they can't do
anything about it right that they're
understaffed but yeah he's like turning
around and like trying to get everyone
involved basically like he's almost
acting like a drunk
person um yeah no
self-awareness and gets like so mad and
the lady the boss supposedly boss lady I
don't know if she really is but she was
like yes I'm I am the boss um she's just
like she's so calm and composed and
she's just like smiling and nodding and
then also saying like please calm down
like please talk normally if you want a
conversation you know she's trying she's
just staying so cool and I really liked
how she was handling it but what I was
surprised about is that this was going
on for like 5 6 7 Minutes H or even 10
and no one in the room there's like so
many adults even like older people like
60 year olds 70 year olds people with a
baby were there no one's saying anything
like the whole room they all looked
older than me like I was like small
small girl with broken
pants um no at this point I had my
proper pants the not broken ones
thankfully but like no one's saying
anything and it's so tense in this
room and and ah everybody's watching the
situation but no one's saying a single
thing now I don't know I feel like in in
a country like
Austria at some point somebody will say
something because um I don't know we we
we don't I I know people don't like to
be involved in the hassle but I I feel
like our mentality normally people would
say something in Austria I think that is
our
mentality especially when there's just
one guy who is being super
ridiculously stupid and everybody else
is just like chilling you know like if
it's just one guy then somebody I feel
like would say something but I was
getting more and more tense like a I
want to bang my head again something
like I really really don't like the
situation and he's just getting so
unfair and I'm thinking of the times
where I was working alone and in front
of 50 people checking in and so stressed
out and it just really pissed me off and
I I was like I can't stop myself I have
to say something like this is pissing me
off because he's now complaining not
about the original thing anymore but
he's complaining about um how how
they're alone here how they suck and how
Post Office sucks blah blah blah only
having one person how incompetent they
are and so on so I said I suddenly from
the sideline yell over to
them uh so you think they like that huh
of course they're not enjoying that
either like do you really think they're
enjoying this it's not their choice that
they're that they're working alone
surely they would like to have some more
colleagues to work with alongside them
so can you [\h__\h] blame them and while
I'm saying these things he first doesn't
even turn around I don't know if he's
not registering it
but he it takes him some time to turn
around towards
me and while I'm saying this I'm shaking
I'm shaking but I can't hold it back I
have to say something and obviously I
was in the right but like I'm trying to
protect them because he pissing me off
and I want him to leave like why is he
not leaving when they obviously can't
help him they have set it clearly
million times so I say these things I
try to defend them I'm like do we
obviously they they would love some help
like they don't choose to be under
staffed then he turns around and he
looks at me and he's like he's like a
lot taller than me and like wider and uh
older and scary attitude and looks at me
he's like what the [\h__\h] do you want ah
shut up over there I'm like that's
that's where I get even more nervous of
course but I I I am like I can't break
down just because I'm small I can't
break down so I say yeah I Stumble a
little bit over my words but I I say
something like um
uh like no no I say something because
you're being [\h__\h] loud and annoying
why don't you just leave they obviously
can't help you so go how about you just
be quiet and
go and then and then and then he he
actually I don't I kind of don't
remember because I was too nervous um
how he really ended up leaving but after
right after that he kind of like walks
out with the boss lady slowly slowly
while still arguing and shouting around
like oh this place sucks blah blah blah
blah blah
um but yeah it kind of ends there and I
was really proud of myself for saying
something because I really don't think
they deserve that kind of [\h__\h] and then
the boss lady she comes back and she
pets me on on my shoulder on my
back kind of like saying thank you to
me and then she sees that I have some
package uh and even though it's not my
turn yet she was trying to help me um to
see if it's something we can get done
quickly but no it it wasn't but still uh
she seemed to show gratitude yeah yeah
damn damn I I'm normally like I wouldn't
speak out in this kind of situation
because I'm scared I'm small like I I
know I don't want to pick a fight with
someone much older and taller than me uh
and separ uh opposite uh gender you know
but yeah I just I just really couldn't
stand being in the room with someone
yelling like that and being fair and
then just [\h__\h] Karen male
Karen yeah it really upset me no
normally I wouldn't do this because
normally someone else will say something
not me why do I have to say
something yeah I do think somebody had
to say something
though you so I did
it here's the number 8 p C9 h n n m
between this and stepping on the
salary yeah I'm getting more assertive
I'm like not taking the [\h__\h] of people
anymore I'm
done yeah my mom relieved he didn't like
hit me or anything or get closer to me
he did talk back a little bit but like
like why why aren't you you should be
expecting that at this point someone's
going to say something cuz you're
turning around trying to involve
everyone one in the
room like they are on your side I'm just
showing you that we're not on your side
dude yeah in that room he couldn't have
hurt me anyway like I'm small and there
were like 30 other adults in the room
like if he would have done something
sheesh
who can pants Oh My Pants my pants
you're broken I'm going to break you I'm
going to tear you a new one
hopefully yeah yeah I think this should
be normal that if if some
innocent uh worker retail whatever is
getting kened by someone maybe say
something maybe help him out yeah I see
a lot of videos where that does happen
so I think I think more and
[Music]
more that is the case but sometimes it
isn't and then maybe help them
[Music]
out 1.5 million angry chickens yeah he
would have also gotten a lawsuit from me
cuz I I have a lawyer now Daisy Cruiser
let's go Daisy
Cruiser that is a story to thank you I
don't think I've
ever
gone this far like I don't think I've
ever been been in this position
before where I'm the one the even the
only one to speak out like
that no maybe I have been somehow now
that I think about it it feels kind of
familiar the feeling is familiar of me
shaking my boots trying to sound
assertive and and
confident trying to assert dominance
over someone who's been an
[\h__\h] yeah no I definitely have been
in a situation like not situation where
I was defending like a post office
worker like that or so
but this kind of feeling is not uncommon
to me I
guess wait the daisy Cruiser is that the
one from that I also played in yes it is
yes it is I played this in the
GameCube I love this one this is this is
the [\h__\h] yeah let's go cool you
yeah [\h__\h] yeah but is it originally from
the GameCube maybe not cuz I I only know
it from the GameCube I didn't play a lot
of the other Mario Karts best course
yeah double was it called Double Dash
Mario uh Mario Kart Double Dash on
the Joe I got
someone Yoo on the GameCube Double Dash
let's
go oh this originally from The Game Cube
oh ah this
H I love this so
much what the [\h__\h]
W or I'm kind of wobbly here but I hope
it's the first time for a lot of you
guys to racing on this course oh come
[Applause]
on hey it doesn't didn't it show before
what's up next what you're going to be
using on the top left now it only shows
the the
[Music]
eight sorry I was rubbing my nose where
am I going oh thank you for leading me
star I guess that's one good thing about
the star still have GameCube and Mario
Kart oh I don't have my GameCube anymore
cuz of all the moving and moving out of
my my mom's home and all
that earlier than my brother so I don't
know they they were still using it maybe
but but I wasn't I was gone
[\h__\h] I love the course but I'm not doing
so well I'm just here to have a good
time just here to look at the beautiful
scenery
yeah that's all I'm here for enjoying
the cruise being Daisy actually I'm
Peach right now but you know I love
Daisy who I flipped the
[Music]
table sh I can't believe I'm losing
against my own pants hi
Ari let's unite together against the
pants Oh you guys are waiting I love
you oh you sweet
[Music]
potatoes
psycho love you guys for waiting Jeff
Amigo and Ari although AR wasn't waiting
she was just bad wait
was was K's pants number
one was she number one did I
just holy
[\h__\h] kicking you out cuz I'm going to
throw you in the trash no matter if you
win this race you know I'll be throwing
you in the trash
so I don't know what you're so happy
about I don't know what you're
celebrating about
B should have baned them yeah I guess
you can but I don't know
how
T KR
[Music]
CSK pants B don't throw perfect
perfectly good what did you see the
pants I mean maybe they could be fixed
that's it's a pretty big hole I don't
know how you can fix
that H but those were that that's like
one of my top two most comfortable pair
of pants man I'm so sad need to buy new
[Music]
pants the guy on the very left I feel
like I've seen him like five times
now is
that who is
that who are
you
feel like they've been in here like at
least in the last race and the last last
race oh maybe wait that looks exactly
like him and there's a
Wawa please get use tournaments again
why why oh Michael
Jackson no that the one now he's on the
right side that isn't Michael Jackson I
mean one on the very right side now
here I'm using tail
controls Michael Jackson uses tilil
controls I'm not uh
surprised you going stay in the room
everyone else comes
in yeah but okay well what's the actual
I can't even choose my the track that I
want so what's the good thing about this
I
forgot I forgot I guess one of the good
things is that there's not like a second
Lobby that you guys accidentally go into
when you're trying to get into my Lobby
and race against someone that's not
me you can choose tracks them Oh you
mean they're at least they're
not couldn't I choose them like kind of
choose them Los Angeles Los Angeles kind
of choose them in
the other way
too you can choose it Sol but it's not
just not
yeah oh yeah ah choice of four but those
four are Rand true okay so yeah you get
a choice of four to choose from and then
it gets randomized like this um but
those four might not be the new courses
so for trying out the new one
specifically this still might be the
most ideal away
then I don't know cuz I want to try the
new ones so let's let's stay
here maky maky maky haven't you been in
this room for like five races now
huh or am I going
crazy Los Angeles I've been here before
so let's
judge if it looks accurate oh I mean I
haven't seen that much I
guess no even has the audacity to steal
my
item a come on what was
that what no come on Mama
Mia it's okay I'm just here for
siding oh my oh that that where the [\h__\h]
am
I huh oh I've been here before before I
had a
lotes I don't know if that was really
the same Beach but uh had the same Vibe
a little
bit nice
bullet bullet
[Music]
time I don't know what these items are
what am I
using uh bomb that will blow up in my
face oh I got a
shortcut ah no no no no no
no
banana yeah got to rely on the Bullet
Bill
oh where's the big the big
ah ah a [\h__\h] off where's where's the
where's the where's where you know the
convention center can you see it here I
wonder
ah thank you nice hammers I didn't see
those hammers in Los
Angeles
fake I didn't see any Yoshis either what
the hell lies so many
lies I think I would have remembered if
I saw Yoshi's in Los
Angeles no no no no
[Music]
no okay eight is not even so bad not
even so bad compared to my other
ratings oil drills oil pump
jacks
a
interesting
h l out of 10 yeah I don't
know let's let's ah oh sorry I have to
cancel goodbye guys
[Music]
goodbye goodbye I mean you guys could
probably leave voluntarily too but
is would you guys do that for
me I don't know it's okay I'll open
another one it's not it doesn't take
that much time it's okay
[Music]
why does it not let me press
okay ah ah ah ah that okay cuz I had no
one in the room okay H 4 S3 and one
Doo more self more Al more
south of La okay I don't know where I
was I was I think I think I stayed uh
partially not always but at some point I
stayed like
downon LA or at least somewhere where I
was told wasn't a good
area somewhere where I was told was
concerning but I mean it was fine I
didn't I didn't walk around
Judas
okay okay wait is the guy here again the
monkey guy how do I check who's in
here
can't oh that that
guy it's like always here why don't you
understand the rules of only being in
One race and then not not
[Music]
again
I don't know how to ban him maybe I'll
figure out afterwards uh after this but
cuz they probably show up in my most
recent Partners
right thank you hope you win the award
thinging oh thank you yeah guys vote for
me vote for me and the Ving thingy Koopa
Cape please Koopa Cape Koopa Cape thank
you oh then I want to do Vancouver
velocity
afterwards I vote thank
you L for
president wow a presentent yes let's
go H let's go let's go that has to be
Koopa Cape never seen that one
before looks
[Music]
futuristic
there we
go where do I vote oh yeah I didn't
retweet it I kind of feel bad about like
retweeting cuz I feel like if I retweet
it it's like too too too like needy too
much
asking too
direct where is this
guy no wait he's not here now it doesn't
look his Avatar maybe that's just like a
default Avatar when when
somebody somebody's Avatar doesn't load
in or so they get like that default one
that looks the same maybe cuz I didn't
see his name on the list just
now it's hly honestly just paying
attention to
the uh
body
[Music]
yes interesting race interesting nice
Funky
Music not funky
but aha in my face okay thank you nice
treatment of your boss you're
[Music]
fired two items let's
go oh this one where where where is this
from from which console
pulls you over the water pulls you over
he wow
hole I just
noticed you guys being little
[Music]
shits I missed the item
[\h__\h] wobbly
Waters The
Weave
ooh I used to have have a
we but like we didn't use it much I
think in the family
actually n two bananas
really it's telling me I need Vitamin B
no no no not this time look I'm so slow
now guys wait for me wait for
me I'm still only tense that's actually
surprising okay okay I can still do it
now is
[Music]
[Applause]
third
oh hope that one lands in the hole in
your
ass put something in there there's not
supposed to be a
hole what where where where didn't I
collect an item for me just
now what
playing hard mode right
now come on bullet bullet bullet
bullet
[\h__\h] so
young it's almost over no no one's here
like
h ah what am I supposed to speed I love
[Applause]
you
I love
you even though like you guys are
waiting for me to me this means a lot
okay I love you
[Music]
guys it feels like I'm
winning your
heart okay out of here get out of here
let's get out of
oh no
[Music]
oopsie oh wait uh no never mind we don't
ban anyone I think it was fine I think
it was just like an NPC
body you made it in thank you y Judas
hope all has been well for you tel well
I don't know I have a hole in my
ass [\h__\h] like that you know like uh it's
just not going so well at the moment HG
36p almost m
p i don't know it's just like life has
been not good to
me oh well that is objective H I will be
receiving my hell of fresh order
sometime unless they just leave it there
with which I would prefer if they just
put it at my door without me having to
go and open the
door we'll see they should deliver it at
some
point during the stream and
then I'll be
cooking hello beep
today maybe maybe I guess I guess I will
H but I I oh I didn't even ah right I
didn't choose the the recipes in time so
it's not going to be recipes that I
[Music]
like hope you get some good
meals thought you canceled well I I
canceled um like during the Japan
trip um but not like overall only like
pause it sometimes when I'm like either
out of town or when I uh Vancouver
when I just don't feel like
cooking but I I I haven't been feeling
like cooking the weeks before I went to
Japan but I'm trying to force myself
again yeah actually I don't know
why cuz I talked about how hello beep
doesn't like give me anything for
staying with them right and like even
when I get people to join they're
getting the discounts not
me remember how I was talking about that
how I don't like that system like you
should reward me for my loyalty and for
getting people into the
system but there was nothing like that
of Hell fresh at least not to my
knowledge but then I don't know maybe
it's because I paused for a
while or so or it's new but I did see
when I was checking through like recipes
and Stu stuff the other
day that now they do have something
where uh I get some some extra money if
I invite
people and I'm I honestly have too much
power I could give you guys these codes
and I could get
like hundreds of
bucks abuse the
system H but I'm not going to do that
obviously but maybe now is the time to
invite some people to make use of
hellofresh I don't know but it's
probably it has to be like
Austrian
hellofresh ooh the
music the lights wait Canada also has
norn lights it's such a like I always
only hear it from like northern European
countries but I guess any cold place in
the north can have North End
lights
oh [\h__\h] that's pretty as [\h__\h] oh here we
go little bit of sun live nice
colors so color coordinated damn
Vancouver so coordinated can you guys
stop that my
God doing so well right
now I love this like evening
Vibe and the bridge and the ooh the the
pretty boats the park
[Music]
hello time for me to go to
Vancouver wow wow nice nice little Park
here this is honestly just a side
seating
[Music]
stream this actually kind of fascinating
because Mario C used to always do like
you know like things that are like
created in a fantasy things that don't
exist in reality now with this booster
stuff they've been making places that
actually do exist in real life so some
places you may have seen
before and they feel familiar to you
right and you're like comparing it to
what you've seen before and in other
places you
maybe K you may be never seen before and
you look at it like this you get a
little little bit of a taste of it I
love the idea of that cuz like this is
making me genuinely interested in
visiting
Vancouver it's actually I don't know if
they considered this when making this
but it's advertisement for the city and
they should uh maybe even collaborate
with those
cities and like uh get money from from
the cities to in include them in Mario
Kart business
lady
yeah will he come to Singapore then
Singapore maybe maybe in the future yeah
why
not I want to go to all of these places
I want to go to a a a
a Mario Kart tourism hell yeah well
obviously it's not as colorful and like
beautiful beautifully clean and all that
but it's
actually I really like the direction
that they're taking with
this maybe maybe in the future maybe for
whenever there's a switch to and the new
Mario Kart
finally maybe then they'll do more real
life inspired
tracks there's so many you could make
you
know h
Singapore is clean yeah I do hear of
that I do have this image of Singapore
being very clean yeah but also expensive
as
[\h__\h] yeah they've been they've really
been stalling here it is LR K GP they've
been really stalling with Mario Kart 8dx
trying to get every single last penny
out of it squeeze squeeze squeeze Mario
Kart ATX squeeze as much as you can
time for a new one I mean honestly for
me not personally I don't really care
I'm fine with this one um but you know D
10 though
says he wants a new Mario Kart so I
guess I agree hello welcome and oh my
God the person behind you look so funny
cat uh who is that one is that supposed
to be something
so funny say something I want no don't
leave don't change your
looks what is
that is that the dude and like he just
changed his looks to be this Squidward
Kiana that's what you change into
really you suck I'm going to I'm going
to rip out your nose while I'm driving
besides
[Music]
you
let's go let's go let's
go I thought a could tangent
doing these races wait a second uh how
about how about Ro Rome aanti aanti I've
been to Rome let me compare this
one um what was I going to say oh yeah I
thought I could tangent but like um I
mean I guess I have been Tangen thing
but can I get can I get a tangent Japan
tangent from my phone
aan
a let's see some tangents are still
going to be secret
secret um ah let me talk uh because L
Senai showed it so now she said it's
okay to talk about it um but I went to
loo senpai's place right for off collab
the K off off collab I hope you guys
enjoyed it that was really nice I was
looking forward to it ever since uh the
sports
festival we've been getting along really
well I don't know we had so much to do
together in the sports festival the
Minecraft
one get wrecked
um and that I saw as you know I mean why
the hell not ask her for collab you know
I take the
opportunity it's always I always welcome
a good reason to collab with someone and
that is a good enough reason for
me that just went nowhere that
banana and so this one
because uh s by was fine with it being
done at her
home um I went to her
place
and she told me she has a
kitten she just introduced it recently
but um when I was there she told me to
still keep it a secret so I couldn't
talk about it but like I was not only
freaking out about her older cat I was
actually freaking out about a cute tiny
ass baby kitten that was giving me the
happiest feelings of my life you know
and so [\h__\h] cute I haven't touched a
kitten in a while I mean I guess uh when
I first saw Kelly's cats they were also
still pretty
small but this this this was this one
was really small oh my God so [\h__\h]
tiny and cute with like a
dangly collar with a ribbon on it oh my
God I don't put colors on my
cats noai cats are also inside cats but
she I feel like Japanese people even
when they're having inside cats that
they don't let outside they still put
collars on
them just because they think it's cute I
guess it's not really about leaving the
apartment I think but like by accident
but I guess that
also helps them in in case that happens
although I don't think that normally
happens yeah but anyway um so freaking
cute like oh thank you for waiting I
love you if you wait for me you get
enough I love you isn't that a great
incentive yeah um but but ah so I arrive
and I I greet her cats and they're like
so friendly and so
sweet one one big orange cat that she's
had uh for a while not even that big
pretty small in general but like that
was the bigger
cat yeah and and then the other cat so
small no ah no no no stop stop stop
leave leave
leave she just stole my heart you know I
was holding her in my
arms just know you you like a
baby I don't know there's not really
much to say except for I was so happy to
see a kitten this is
like like a cat cafe
H the cat oroku theu SAA was cute too
and on my way um what was I doing before
that I was doing something before going
to loo standby I guess and I didn't get
to eat I was like really
hungry so I told her that and I I was
just like saying maybe we can get some
snacks from like convenience store or so
if she has one close by just anything
something small small small food and
somehow she says hey I got something I'm
going to I'm going to cook something and
I'm
like I'm arriving student and you you
cooking me something to eat instead of
like I would have been fine to just you
know go go grab something from the
convenience
store no no she cooked something from me
and when she said that I was
wondering maybe I should I don't know I
don't want to make it too complicated
now that she's offering that she's
cooking something I don't want to be
like complicated and say okay but I
don't like this and this and this and
this so I just let it happen but and
hoped for the best but when I arrived
she was like cooking two things one
thing was like like she was simmering
down mushrooms and I hate mushrooms and
the other thing is she was like nicely
arranging some I think raw salmon or so
on a plate and I don't eat raw fish
either so both of the things that she
cooked and they looked really yummy and
I wanted to eat them when I I was like I
didn't even say it outright I was like
watching her cook and I was like oh
mushrooms huh oh mushrooms she's like
yeah me mushrooms I'm like oh yeah
mushrooms
M she's like oh kiar by any chance do
you not like mushrooms and I'm like uh
yeah not
really and and then she asks oh what
what what about this other thing I'm
preparing and I say h well yeah I don't
really uh eat raw fish
either uh and I felt so bad but she's
like that's fine that's fine I can eat
it all and and then she made some some
fried rice uh that she had in the
freezer like like already pre-prepared
uh Frozen fried rice warmed it up for me
I love
Chan yeah she wasn't mad though at all
no no no no no it's it's not poor
no no I just I didn't want to like uh
annoy her beforehand
but I didn't think that both things she
was making would be something I don't
eat yeah but no it was all in good
spirits and she was really there you go
5 t h qf she was really sweet about it
and she was like really
chill her kitchen was really nice
she was she was quite proud of her
kitchen
interesting and yeah so we we had some
time cuz I actually I was like really
stressed out I remember about getting to
her place right cuz it was after my
dance lesson and I after my dance lesson
I quickly went back to my home to get a
shower um and then like I got confused
about my time management I thought I had
no
time I really didn't have much time but
then I I hurried so much that I actually
unnecessarily hurried so much that I was
an hour
early that whole hour could have done
like some more of the stuff that I had
to work on on my laptop but I just went
there early on accident with a empty
tummy yeah so instead we were just like
snacking slowly on the food and then
cuddling with her cats and like having
some
chitchat and then slowly preparing for
the stream so it was really chill me
arriving so early at least uh helped us
to like Bond a little bit oh and I gave
her the tea right I brought her the tea
as a souvenir and she immediately made
it she was like oh I really want to
taste it now and then she made the tea
for both of us my Austrian
tea she I think she liked it
let's do the daisy circuit
maybe how about
that what flavor Christmas flavor
duh Christmas flavor
it really tastes like Christmas
or I guess you could say it it kind of
tastes a little bit like the the punch
that you get at Christmas Market
here
[Music]
mhm you guys don't get it every time I
say it tastes like Christmas why you
guys don't get it there's obviously
there's typical flavors that you connect
with Christmas don't you like orange
cinnamon Apple like in
combination that kind of stuff
obviously don't act so stupid you know
it don't
you no of course there are the punch uh
uh
ingredients some people some people here
just
like act so
oblivious
[Music]
yeah mold
wine mold wine punch hello why is
nothing
happening are we going to get a inter
internet
Kaboom
hello
you HK all it means is another trip to
the Chinese
restaurant really but like yeah I mean I
understand in some like
continents depending on the continent
there will be
different flavors that that mean
Christmas but feel like cinnamon and
apple that's just
like so out
there m w you eat gingerbread this year
I should I have to yeah [\h__\h] yeah
gingerbread yeah there is German eggnog
but I never drank it
before doesn't sound very tasty to me
you know like a drink of
eggs I I I like eggs you know I like you
guys
but a drink of egg just doesn't sound so
appealing to
me it's not really Iggy yeah I
guess I'm getting tired can we like
start it
hello feel like someone's internet
connection must have yeah must have
broken and then oh not not someone's I
guess it's just the Nintendo servers
that fell apart once
again
shindana let me out of there there let
me restart it hope you guys can get in
[Music]
again ah oopsie Tada uh C3
w37 please come in this way
[Music]
please man I don't know how I'm going to
get through this winter streaming
streaming so far ever since I've been
back from Japan has been painful my
throat is scratchy my eyes get so tired
and I don't even have it warmed up that
much I have it turned down quite a lot
but the heating
is not good on
me maybe I shouldn't do any long long
long series too much not not too many at
least during
winter I don't know if the humidifier
will will help but I'll give it a try
yeah yeah it's I guess it's dry like the
dryness is um is taking its toll on my
throat but I think it's the heating that
it's take is taking its toll on my
eyes
fly south for winter well I am I I I
don't know if it's South but I'm flying
uh
Southeast kind of Southeast uh Daisy
circuit
again kind of Southeast for the males in
January and then I'm taking pretty much
uh after the
mes which is like
until I would I I think like the middle
of January after that I'm taking the
rest of the
month off
for
just internet uh detox and work
detox and getting some private life
stuff
done
yes
mhm so like half a month I'll be around
the other one not jft Ren
Ren is
here it's already so soon like it's
almost December so a I'm getting so
excited although I need I still need to
buy the
tickets the flight
tickets to the
moldes oh actually I've been waiting for
my salary but I just realized like today
I was thinking about
it I I think I could for the tickets
right
now with
the the the investment money that I Y
ah that I got back remember I don't want
to say it I think I did say it on my
member stream I think I said it on my
member
stream the money that has been invested
and that I got
1,000
approximately uh plus profit
from no
what oh he lost his star that poor
[Music]
dude yeah so I think from that I could
possibly afford the tickets if I want to
like I'm almost getting my salary in
like I guess on the 30th I'm getting my
salary it's always like the last the
last possible work
day of the of the
month if there's a a weekend at the end
of the month then it's the
last day before the
weekend so anyway that means probably
I'm getting it on the 30th but uh better
earlier than later if I can afford the
tickets the mes flight
tickets this Daisy circuit is kind of
nice I like it and wait is that n that's
several little tiny Yachts but would
have been funny if Daisy cruise ship was
parked
here can I go for here oh my God what
that's so cool let's go
oo that felt like quite the shortcut oh
no no I supposed to fly over
that what all I get is a [\h__\h]
coin really why am I still
invisible
I'm coming for you you don't have to
wait for me I went there on my own have
fun racing my M yes I'm so
excited that's really something that got
me really excited right now it's so soon
already I can't believe it this time is
going to be not off season so we're
going to get the most of it and I'm
going to get really [\h__\h] sunburned
let's [\h__\h] go all right ah need to
tell narissa oh narissa narissa [\h__\h] I
forgot until now I never told
her I don't know if she she maybe picked
it up before when I was talking about it
Lissa you got to get me the sunscreen
from the American
lens
um I had uh what kind of you want the
highest SPF you can find in the
drugstore
uh I think mine had like 100 or
so but maybe I can find what are like
really common um American sunscreens
that you find in the Dr what which kind
would I find if it's like kind of
regional which kind would I find in La
for example if it's like
Regional she
listening neutr neut you guys are not
writing that correctly
if if it's the one I think that's not
how you write it like I saw fre
different people mention it and it's all
written
wrong NE
trena copper
tone 100
SPF I don't know if it was that I don't
think the the brand was not really
familiar to uh yeah familiar to me
that's what I remember but new neutr
Neutrogena is very familiar to me why
did my chat die hyper chat
huh Nutella copper tone is more for
oh damn it I wish I Sarah V oh Sarah V
SPF I think it was a
spray ah that could be
it wait no uh yeah
maybe
maybe honestly it doesn't matter I think
whatever is fine as long as it's like as
high as
possible cuz like he getting a 100
SPF uh shouldn't be too difficult right
cuz I saw a couple when I was in in
America I personally find soundscreen
uncomfortable well what am I going to do
I need
it if need this
100 is common right but like I don't
ever find it in
[Music]
Austria maybe get both one spray one
lotion we share 100 SPF
[Music]
please it's getting sooner and
sooner ah I'm so excited guys I'm going
to take you guys with
me me and my gaming laptop I'll bring
you guys the only thing we have to be
careful about is I mean there's nothing
I can really do but we really need good
internet but they did say that they're
putting down a cable for us like a alarm
cable yeah yeah yeah yeah so that's
already good sign fine should be should
be fine last time I streamed over the
ocean
literally and this time we actually
ended up not getting a over Ocean
Villa um I discussed this very hard with
very intensely with uh
nerissa cuz it's my second time so I
don't really care that
much but it's her first time so I was
thinking maybe we should do the the
typical one but it's like cuz it's on
season they were really [\h__\h]
expensive all the nice ones that were
over the
ocean
[Music]
mhm oh yeah I should bring my my camera
my cool cameras maybe yeah
no it's just me and Nissa
H oh wait the code 5 wxj
y still be treated as a honeymoon
couple I think that's just generally
like I don't think they thought me and
Lena were honeymoon couple I just think
that's their general standard of service
you
know cuz you pay pay a lot of money to
be
there and you have a butler and all that
assigned as
well yeah what was I saying what was I
just
saying brain brain
[Music]
do yeah the pedal yeah I
mean well there's a chance that the
housekeeping staff
wasn't 100% aware of what kind of people
were staying in the
room who
knows maybe they didn't know really but
just felt like oh
well let's just make them a nice bath
blah blah blah get some nice uh
tip from these
foreigners oh yeah I was saying uh wait
let's let's let's do Madrid let's do
Madrid yeah [\h__\h] yeah I
saying that I think you guys probably
seen pictures of it before but like the
Mal Dives they're famous for having you
know all these islands where the resorts
own a whole island and they will they
like build their little
Cottages uh over
like this long long
long uh strip of pretty shallow
water and it's just so magical it looks
so nice and you wake up hearing the
ocean
waves it's so good it's so it's just so
good let's go guys oh two people from
Brazil
too let's go to
you saw I didn't hit man
what yeah so ideally if you go to the
mives you want to especially if it's
your first time you want to go get one
of
those
um nice Villas over the sheer
water but the prices really even scared
me off and there Isa was like way more
concerned about the financial aspect of
this trip than me but cuz she's still
new and you know she told me oh all
these projects so expensive oh just
join so I was like okay like I mean I
don't need to necessarily be uh over the
water again I already saw it I
guess if she doesn't mind it
either cuz the they do have some beach
apartments and they're really nice too
like Beach
cottages they're really ni nice too and
they're kind of calm because all the
ones I saw they're like um they're not
like all like immediately next to each
other like uh touching each other no
they have like their own little paths
leading through um
some like palm trees and all
that and then like it's pretty private
you know nobody will like look inside
your cottage and all
that and and then the other side like
the front entrance will be like more
like for a path from the middle of the
island but then the back side of your
cottage will be leading to the beach so
a lot of them have
like basically their part of the beach
directly
accessible ah so that's I think that's
the kind of apartment we or apartment
Villa whatever that we booked this
[Music]
time
yesness for once I did something
smart nice music
here Been to Spain before but I don't
think I've uh been to
Madrid who all right yeah okay I think
uh Madrid
they have a famous
uh soccer team
[Music]
right oh
my I didn't realize it was already the
end it's kind of
short
goal did I score a
goal yeah soccer is Big over there yeah
it wasn't Valencia
was I anywhere else are in
Spain was I in Spain only once in my
life even though it's so
close can't
remember Barcelona no I haven't been to
Barcelona cuz it's Barcelona I feel like
it's more like a city Party
trip
Maya no Maya I don't think I'll ever go
to mayca because that's also like it's
just a party island you could escape
from the whole party Vibe and if you
have a car or like a license to rent a
car then then mayorca might be really
nice if you can rent a car and then
drive around the island to like to the
other side of the opposite end of the
island then they have really nice Cliffs
and all that but otherwise if you can
only stay in the close area to the
airport then it's just
party party territory uh drunk people
young people from Germany and Austria
all
over it's just not M it has this huge
reputation to be a party Island
here HF
mhm
yeah lot of like 18 year olds 19 year
and also a lot of people who just like
graduated from high school go to their
like I don't know what do you call
them thank you thank you I'm glad you
could with
me yeah it's like an extension of
[Music]
Germany do we even have something like
spring
break in uh German speaking countries
not sure but it it has the same kind of
vibe
yeah how the how the heck can you have
money for vacations right up school high
school H it's really cheap to go there
number
one uh number two I don't know but I
don't know they managed to do it it's
really cheap really
though
[Music]
yeah parents money yeah maybe like um
congratulations to your
High School graduation here is some
money kind of thing maybe that's where
they got
it it's not that cheap no you can get
you can get flights for under 50
bucks
honestly and wait wait let let's do Ros
Rosalina's ice world I want to see that
one
n n n n after reading into why there is
almost no lsf 100 in the U it seems
Kiana is getting scammed by the higher
number is much better mindset she will
so she will need this
money is it something like SPF 100 in
America is like equal to our 50 because
they just
like number it differently or so
well what are you talking about I need
to look this up afterwards what what
what but the one I had from America
worked so well for me and like I
remember take taking it to
Italy Sun inflation I remember taking it
to Italy with my friends my Austrian
friends and they were all using shitty
Austrian uh sun lotion and had insane
sunburns while I was using mine and I I
went out of there with with no Sunburn
and they were so jealous of my uh sun
lotion like it genuinely was better than
mine lsf SPF mean different things yeah
I don't even know what I was looking at
though like if it was lsf 100 or SPF 100
I honestly don't remember to me it was
the same
thing it definitely had a 100 written on
it
though [\h__\h] [\h__\h] ah come on that's so
difficult wait for me
want wait for me nice music
though wow wow this is like
[Music]
Frozen Frozen inspired
map oh let's go here no why did I do why
did I do
that
hi maybe not too bad though
perim anything about 50 is
overkill
[Music]
no I'm fine with 52 though 50 is fine
though i' I've survived with 30 I just
had to like reapply it a million
times be really careful after every
single dip in the water reapply reapply
[Music]
reapply it works yeah but like
yeah you stay completely pale with 50
yeah I mean 50 is fine maybe 50 is equal
to 100 it was just like a different term
maybe maybe that is indeed the case
maybe that's what's going on
here yes I made it I made it I made it I
did the
stunt move [\h__\h] get out the way
yooo already over I was enjoying it
actually for
once all right got another
[Music]
one everybody's getting
stars star
inflation uh-oh why why am I doing this
oh no I will not survive this
no thank you for waiting I love
you no hey who is that who is that
orange Yoshi who could not wait a moment
ah European friend why why why we're
European together why don't you why
don't you support me hm why
not okay goodbye I'm breaking up with
you
guys a t k g AR but I don't really T I
just got
red
that's the
thing I don't know getting a tan is like
its own whole science and I'm not I
don't really need one I don't need
[Music]
one the a r rainbow I I don't need a
rainbow road 2DS
MC there was Minecraft on the
2DS I didn't play that ever what a
revelation tantal
n I've had some crazy ass sunburns
before also like my last Mal STP left me
with some dangerous looking
sunburns so I'm going to be careful
especially in the males like that's it's
no joke the sun there is no
[Music]
joke you and Lisa will be Lobster
sisters I think she's probably the same
type as
me pale AF and easily
sunburned okay uh let's do Bowser's
Castle
[Music]
free it's the same Sun wherever you go
um yeah but like
huh huh why are you arguing with why are
you being smarty pants with me here
there's
genuinely like like like hey huh
huh you you know what I mean
like that's not Point
yeah
no literally like in in in the in the
area where Austria is we barely get sun
like like even in summer they say I I
watched this documentary that said even
in summer where I do feel like I see a
lot of sun and I feel the heat
apparently it's still not enough Sun for
us to get the the minimum daily vitamin
D intake in like Austria Germany Etc and
probably anything above that's like more
norn as
well while other
countries like probably the
males at least during their on
season they probably get more than
plenty wait I'm I'm I'm looking at the
chat I want to have this conversation
I'm correct right yeah
ah
what yo the music
here yeah
[Music]
yeah can everybody stop driving so I can
have a conversation with my chat
please got what what what do you mean
over here the safy where are
you eyes on the road no eyes on
you eyes on you cuz you're beautiful I
want to look at
you shees this music wait so Japanese me
Japanese fans have been receiving their
POV album already in case you haven't
noticed and you guys have been getting
notices that yours is being sent out too
so who here has already heard the Sparks
remix the dark remix
I haven't really heard anything besides
from Japanese Bros
yet has anyone here heard it
yet not yet oh
no it's kind of like
this wait for
me Tommy Tommy
boys she wait
oh it's still quite a
bit please please please please please
please please please no no I was F I was
F I
[Applause]
[Music]
was this game sucks this game sucks
stupid game stupid shitty game this
[Music]
game mean everybody's so
meaning
I wanted to quit to be
honest but I'll go a bit
longer I'll go a bit
longer ah 7 LR
5m no has been too hour oh but I haven't
seen all the tracks
yet you monsters
no will you go to Christmas Market with
Lena oh I want to yeah I want
to
actually yeah I want to I want to
[Music]
go I'm not going to say what I want to
say actually
because it's going to be
surprise let's go guys I think we're
more or less
complete Dana is
excited yeah me
too my
[Music]
cute uh let's do that stupid Rainbow
Road I hope it's not as
R
inducing as other rainbow
[Music]
roads wa it with off no that's not going
to happen they don't
overlap okay H let's see let's let's
tangent about the
lia meeting of the day when I collab
with
Rea let's see what's in my notes we ate
before oh yeah I arrived first and I sat
in the room cuz like a lot of these
Japanese restaurants they have like like
private rooms as in it's like a little
walled off seating
area which is nice I like that that's a
thing in Japan ooh wa I love it it's
pretty so
pretty I arrived early so I was sitting
there and waiting for her and then I was
kind of feeling nervous about her
showing up holy [\h__\h] Earth I'm
coming because it would be kind of
awkward like her her coming into this
like little room where I'm waiting in
and and me saying ha nice to meet you
such a such a weird ways and sometimes
of us how we meet for the first time oh
my God this looks like a
[Music]
supermarket and so she
arrived and we greeted each other for
the first time and we we we just you
know we ate some really good
meat grilled it and I most of the time I
was like leaving the grilling to her we
shared a little bit but a lot of the
grilling was like her doing and she
overg grilled the food Mama
Mia and then I didn't trust her anymore
had trust
issues and I ordered the food that she
burnt again the the same type of
meat so that I could taste what it
tastes like without being burnt and it
was so
good oh yeah yeah yeah yeah see like we
talked about like the places she's been
to
before like countries during uh the
dinner and I I wanted to mention it
during the stream but I completely
forgot about it I think she said it's
okay to talk about though she told me
she's been to Austria guys she's been to
Austria h i don't have to tell her to
come to Austria because she's been there
before
[Music]
like normally the girls I talk
to uh I I tell them wel come to Austria
because they're like theyve never been
here before and they're like interested
you know but I can't even say it the
same way to
[Music]
Lio I think I still told her though like
come
again I think she still was like you
know ah oh my God like she was still
interested in it oh oh [\h__\h] you guys
come on that's
[Music]
enough hate you guys I hate
you did she say why she
won uh I think it was just a
vacation I
think
wobbly
oh oh
oh seven oh that's not bad considering
how often I fell off and I was like
Tangen thing oh chy was in here wait chy
you're you're in Switzerland the
[\h__\h] we we we talk in German so I just
thought you were in
Germany wait what oopsie h no no no no
no no no no chy is Swiss
swish I don't think I knew I don't think
I just assumed you're
German I know there's a lot of German
speakers in Switzerland but I thought
you were
German
money that's
fun I thought we've been over this have
we maybe I forgot again
what
this CL LG
zero f I think it's a zero not sure you
guys give it a
try thank
you glad to have gotten the chance to
play with you thank you for joining glad
you made
it but yeah I felt like this immediate
connection with Lia when she told me
about her overseas trips and when she
told me she she's been to Austria and
all that I think she said she doesn't
remember it well but
still I so happy
man yeah and her English is so good too
I'm glad that there's like more and more
uh whole life members in Japan joining
who know
English that you know opens up
interesting
collaboration idea so cuz I want to I
always have this like
uh
problem like I used to collab a lot with
Japanese members in
Japanese but I always felt bad about you
guys not understanding what's going on
mostly and eventually I think you guys
may have noticed when I was like
struggling with
that H but eventually I kind of stopped
pursuing a lot lot of these Japanese
collabs and focused more on English
collabs
collabs at least when it comes to doing
them on my
channel and now I have this great
opportunity where a lot of Japanese
members can speak or understand decent
English so I can collab Japanese members
but still make it an English stream or
at least partially English stream on my
channel
jackpot
woohoo
Yahoo nice two birds with one
stone oh that one looks like M
cool um let's do the pirania plant Cove
how about
that
pirania I want wanted to see I want to
see roast Ren
again yeah we we were like really
bouncing off each other so while so I
hope I can get something going with
ladden at some point but probably not
anytime soon cuz I'm I'm busy as [\h__\h]
right now I'm also like I did a lot of
like organizing stuff for the h life
English Advent calendar
yesterday like I did all the scheduling
I put a schedule together unfortunately
a little bit like late late than I was
hoping for uh for myself I wanted to do
it earlier but just didn't have time and
I like contacted a lot of the girls are
like up
early uh on the schedule like hey just
so you know I put you on this day so
please send in the video and then I also
put up like a I wrote a whole big
explanation about how it works
especially for the new girls like when
they have to send in their videos what
background to use what title to put in
for the video
what setting uh so because it must be
unlisted this and that this and
that um all the logistics explained it
to them like management is helping me
with it but uh with like creating the
website Etc I don't I don't have to look
at the process and organize the process
of that anymore but I'm I'm
organizing like more the The Human Side
bit I'm
HR and
planning the the side that's like I'm in
charge of the talents basically like
getting also I also gave them a lot of
ideas like I brain stor storm some ideas
for them to choose from to make it
easier for them so that they don't have
to wreck their own
brains especially for the maybe some
members who are really busy or not as
motivated to do it maybe so I'm like
here there you go choose one of my ideas
if you want I hope that makes it
easier uh yeah but there there's been
still a lot of
motivation and everybody's participating
so I'm quite happy about
that we have more
members this time too
ooh then last year so like last year
there were it felt like to me it felt
like there was a lot of repetition but
what can you do
honestly with like nine
members
[Applause]
10 10 I guess 10
members there will be
repetition that is something that can't
be helped but this year hm
H like sheerly
Sheely solely
solely by having solo videos from every
member don't touch me with that don't
touch me with that H that'll be 15 days
right some will make more than one
video and then there will be some unit
videos thank you for waiting a I love
you only one person for me Perry gave no
shits Perry you little
[\h__\h] he just gave no [\h__\h]
there fuu never
solo maybe I should maybe I should have
them form form is quite motivated they
signed up
for uh actually they took ideas from me
two ideas from
me um I have like two videos from them
planned with ideas from
me they liked my ideas I have to say
they were pretty good
ideas but maybe I should make them do
solo videos too yeah that would be
cute but I already have a lot of uh
foko
scheduled yeah Advent it's so easy to
like get Advent to do stuff for me
narissa too I was like narissa narissa
please like some girls some girls are
like busy so I can't can't schedule them
until like the end of the Advent calend
days like I need I need some girls to
fill up the the early days would you
would you be ready for like you know the
first couple of days please and she's
like anything for you of
course generally Advent but like
especially Nissa who will do anything
for
me
yeah really really
helpful yeah yeah yeah I love it I
really appreciate it m it's really
helpful that makes working easier here
jww you say JUMP she says how
[Laughter]
hi uh fari waa yes McQueen
yeah like it's so so cute like I I will
just hit her up with something really
simple like uh hey can you make this
video and she's like yep and I'm like
okay thanks and she's like I love you so
much and I'm like I love you too she's
like I love you forever you're the best
Queen like every conversation there has
to be some T thrown at me we just like
say it every day to each
other it's just so
wholesome
she does not miss a chance to tell me
that she loves
me okay let's do the Donkey Kong
Mountain I don't think we've done that
one
before Donkey Kong
[Music]
Mountain Platinum points
wow let's go let's go isn't Moko in here
for the second time
that M wait actually no on those top
icons there's no
M that's so
confusing it's not the same as what's
shown on on the
[Music]
earth yeah here also it's not her I
think sometimes the um characters on the
Earth are
not
equivalent that maybe they're still
showing older characters that are that
were there before but are not there
[Music]
anymore bug bug Des all right Donkey
Kong cannon not Canyon
Cannon has wait has this been in the
GameCube version too cuz I think it's
familiar to me oh yeah yeah it is wait
it
is is hell yeah oh yeah [\h__\h] yeah wait
this makes me so happy anything I know
from the GameCube makes me really
happy yeah I remember all of this oh
this is incredibly
nostalgic I played that like how many
years
ago too many to say because it's it's
it's making things a little bit too
[Music]
obvious we don't want to say it that
clearly do
we oh the shaking
Bridge so many good games yeah man and I
think of the GameCube I think of lia's
Mansion I think of Super Mario
Sunshine and I think of tels some
Symphonia I think those are and Mario
Party those are like
my Mo probably my most played GameCube
games from back in the day oh yeah Wind
Waker too but I I feel like with Wind
Waker I was mostly watching my brother
play it same with Luigi's Mansion I was
just watching my brother play Luigi's
Mansion I was he was the let's player I
was the
viewer not backseating though I really
just as a young sister to my brother I
really just enjoyed watching him like
living through him vividly cuz I wasn't
skilled enough for these kind of games
yet oh yeah Pokemon colos that's also
one that I was playing the one where you
start off with the Eevees right
mhm that one I
really loved as well that one was so
different from other Pokemon games which
really made it so special and stand out
so
much oh and oh my god oh GameCube had
like a Sims game that's not a typical
Sims game it's the the breaking out one
I think and and others too I think there
was more than one but that one I I
played a lot it has like the story
line and that was so fun for me cuz I
think that's quite easy even as a child
to
play it gives you things to
do very
clearly uh rather than you know normal
Sims where you just have too much
Freedom base Coliseum enjoyer [\h__\h] yeah
I yeah busting out yeah busting out was
so good I really want to I almost want
to let's play it on my channel not let's
play but like stream
it a so good busting out is so funny
like H the storyline is so funny old
Sims game with with story lines like
also the the DS ones the one where you
had like a I think a vacuum
cleaner and you were collecting these
like shiny green objects that are I
don't know maybe for
nuclear uh nuclear plant I don't know
what the [\h__\h] that
was yeah and
herbs herbs
yeah no I I don't think I played my Sims
but I watched I watched a playthrough of
my
Sims back when I was still watching a
Sims uh YouTube
channel yeah yeah
yeah the
[Music]
herbs my Sims is the one where they're
like really like chibi like
rightow I hear oh no it was it was of
course it was Peach meow not my cat but
it sounded like it came from like
outside of my
headphones H
oh I be too
hot I do be too hot for this planet
screenshot this waa on the
earth she's she be too hot this is in
direct connection re relation to each
[Music]
other you guys can't come close to me
cuz I'm too hot right it's okay keep a
[Music]
distance oh my God that oneeyed person
what the [\h__\h] oh that's Galaxy oh now
there a
fuaa oh
cute
o nice okay let's go
guys let's see what do we have left that
we didn't try
[Music]
yet um
I've done all of these uh how about
Sunset Wilds Sunset
Wilds that one I haven't tried yet
but shy guys are cute so we're going to
give them a visit fuaa did not get the
memo and that guy with the sunglasses
didn't get the memo but I haven't tried
that one yet
either might want to try it out
afterwards
this one's from Game Bar advance I kind
of can't
even like grasp that there was Mario
Kart on a Game Boy Advance cuz like for
me Mario Kart seems
like okay okay thank God that was close
seems like a pretty
difficult game to put on
a on such
a
simplistic game handheld con conso
thingy like how does that even manage to
you
know uh host a game like that but I
guess it wasn't online right you most
likely couldn't play online on the Game
Boy
Advance just local probably
right but it just feels so ambitious you
know a game like
[Music]
this cute
music cute dance a cute
dancing
sh I'm going to get you
[Music]
guys to get you guys I'm going to get
you
small army small army wait for
me oo that was close almost got me with
that
[Music]
explosion this this uh course is pretty
easy
to
grasp no big danger even on on first try
to fall off here and there haven't
bonked against
[Music]
anything
come on get someone n get the
O damn
[Music]
it no no I was about to use
it okay hurry hurry
hurry oh no no
no please please
[Music]
it was so good please
bullet
no
no thank you for waiting for me small L
I saw you waiting and I think tys was
just behind me anyway
no oh
man oh
man
that's what happens when it's too
easy I feel like the the more difficult
tracks even though I suck too you guys
also suck a little bit so we all suck
and and I have a higher chance of
getting more in the middle ranks but the
easy
ones you guys figure out
immediately and so I am no competition
for you
guys you came even lady nap too long LC
napping H Mr LC
napping that's what your name is isn't
it you nap too much
haha miss everything in life cuz you're
napping too
much yeah Tada FD r9g I'm not going to
play it for much longer maybe this is
the last one maybe the next one is the
last one who knows who knows maybe if
you guys let me
uh be more than just 12th 11th or 10th
maybe then I will bless you with another
race H
H by the way finally today I finally got
the notice that for my next
outfit uh the artist has been chosen and
my head and my idea for what it's going
to be has been green lit there was like
some discussion about like you know
generally we can't like get too many
items and all that there's like a point
system you
know new out 58 but it's still going to
take like probably I don't know half a
year at this point but normally there's
a point system like certain things take
up so many points because they uh like
if I want an excess ACC that I can take
off the fact that like the function of
taking it off is a toggle and that like
uh let's do moon view Highway and that
will take more
points so stuff like that uh new
hairstyle cost more
money yeah and more intricate outfits
also probably cost more uh points yeah
so nice one El see nappen
and with that being said when I was
planning my upcoming outfit I was
inspired by seeing other
members um kind
of
like like I think I saw
someone who had a completely different
top or bottom to switch out and that
changed the whole look of the outfit
quiet a bit so I thought H that's nice
maybe I
can you know kind of get two outfits in
one more or less if I plan it
smartly so I did
that I planned it and it was it was
totally fine in terms of points I
squeezed it in and it worked out
nicely so I I gave my plan to them a
while
ago like 2 months ago or so but it
hasn't been greenlit until
now because even though I wasn't
Crossing uh going aboard with the
points I was told
[Music]
that it's
like it's almost as if it's two outfits
even though in terms of like workload
like overall it's not like a crazy
intricate outfit or
anything but even
then I I I kind of played it too
smart like it's they're the same
Vibe both I wouldn't even say it's
different outfits but let's just say it
like that but they both have the same
Vibe the same theme
but still like I I I was too smart in
the planning and uh it's just they kind
of said it's almost like it's two
different outfits and we can't have that
even though it would logistically work
and it wouldn't even be that much of a
workload just
like they they don't want there to
be um like they don't want it to look
like it's two different outfits they
still want like
one connection there I I thought I still
had that I thought it it definitely
looked like it was the same thing but I
was like okay what if we get rid of this
and
this you know so finally I got it to a
point where they were happy with
it yeah one
coherent like string I guess throughout
the
outfit is what they need
me
to yeah plan I guess I don't know it's
hard to um explain
but yeah like it would have it would
have worked like in terms of points and
honestly it wasn't even like an outfit
that would have taken so much work to
draw you know what I mean it's just like
the layering the way I planned out the
layering would make it look like it's
just like for example it's just like uh
like let's say a hoodie over my bikini
well obviously when I take off the
hoodie and when I have it on will give
you two different Vibes like this is
almost a different outfit
right
but it's the same outfit I'm just being
smart
I mean just by me adding more and more
accessories to this
outfit my casual outfit has gotten so
many different
possibilities of usage so I kind
of built it up to be like this over
time yeah but I guess from the GetGo I
can't do
it
I don't know I I was I was I was um
trying to get it to be as versatile as
possible uh within the limits of points
and all that um cuz I just fought you
know one outfit per year I want to get
the most out of it well but yeah we'll
see how it ends up to look like and how
many ways of wearing uh it's going to be
in the
end yeah
yeah oh and uh one more thing the
sword that was also a thing that took so
long uh there was a lot of discussion
about the sword for my alter outfit uh
which was literally just a PNG it wasn't
going to be
incorporated as an accessory whatsoever
it was just because the artist was
motivated and happy and through it
uh and was going to give give it to me
as a PNG cuz when I saw that he drew it
just for
like himself I guess I thought well I if
I get this as a PNG I could honestly
like attach it to myself behind my model
and it's like almost like an accessory
because a sword doesn't really have to
be like flowing animated whatsoever so I
can make this work I thought so I asked
for it and like swap would have given it
to me but like there was a lot of like
complications then and in the end it's
not going to happen I'm not allowed to
use
it I'm not allowed to use
it
yeah
I can't explain it because I will
probably get bonked if I go into detail
why LJ 9
six if if for example a fan artist drew
it or like any like not this
specifically not copy pasted it
completely but just drew a sword I could
put it as an attachment on myself with
no
problem if you guys
want it's just so sad because what the
one from swaf swaf just looks so [\h__\h]
badass it looks so cool
cool
[Music]
yeah I'm so sad it took so long to to
get to this point and now it's like I
can't use
it no
no no what what's ah the same person
blackout would you mind
[Music]
leaving please
leave and timx as well but I do have to
say like it might not be him cuz like on
the name list they they don't show up
sometimes and it's just on the earth I
don't know thank you somebody just left
don't know who that was but if you were
uh the timx person thank you for
understanding yeah TJ you're in
N they've been here for 10
races I can't remove them from here
though unless
I close the lobby
now blackout please exit go
black
AO I blocked him in my last MK I did a
year ago seems like it didn't
work I can block them on the front list
for the account
oh does that
work a
uh search for users you've played
with maybe
here don't know why they make it so
difficult just leave when I tell you to
leave you're obviously watching the
stream right okay I see them sorry it
has to be like that but okay
[Music]
Buu but there's a obviously not
communication happening between
us people trying to get into the
lobby okay I did
it
uh wait which one is it do you guys
remember the what they look like are
they still on
here somebody just left but I don't know
if it was that
person
M oh another person left but oh that no
maybe they just Chang their Avatar I
don't know he's still
there m
there yeah it's the one in the black
outfit
right maybe it's just not
updating I don't
know
ah why why why you got to be like
that anyway let's do
o Stadium
maybe oh there's a Bangkok Rush that I
haven't done yet
n another city that I haven't seen yet
we got to go there oh my God
[Music]
she's still there why don't don't you
understand I'm speaking English and
nongo and both are not getting my point
across maybe
[Music]
German he's a he's a German
flag ah but I feel like like that's like
minimum English like if you watch my
streams you probably understand me
saying
that
thisvid wait I see them in the I see
them in the
chat and they writing in English you
just don't care like what's what's the
thought process in your
brain I want to understand if you if you
understood then what's the thought
process
here I'm I'm
curious what makes you
ignore my
requests that everyone else is able to
follow
huh now you can't say it cuz you're
racing
illegally
really unnecessary
Behavior this track is also
GameCube this track was GameCube let me
let me try to yeah yeah I think I can
remember
remember it also just REM reminds me of
my
childhood
TBH my dad uh used I told this before I
think but he brought me to me and my
brother to like this these really muddy
monster truck uh
thingies it was always so [\h__\h] muddy
everywhere walking was a
pain yeah monster track I think it was
monster truck rallies they were like by
the end of it they were always like so
destroyed
[Music]
destruction
Pizza pza wait what would L
say
how do ly talk P Pizza P Pizza
Pizza why was why did I turn into a valy
girl for
moment
P I love Family Guy I I am so sorry but
I love Family Guy haven't watched it in
a while
[Music]
though I love the
dog and the
baby I hate the the kids besides the
baby
[Music]
hate
them you guys know that one episode with
thank you guys for waiting I love you
you know that episode where uh Brian and
um literally can't remember the name of
the baby Brian Brian and Stewie where
they're stuck for the whole episode
they're stuck in that
room where they can't get out and it
gets like over time it gets like
yubby yeah yeah the Vault one
yeah still legendary but he's better in
the old
episodes maybe I don't know
um
I can't but I blocked him already so I
don't know if he can join anymore so why
did you do that now that you have the
control out of your hand why why do you
ignore the matters
H are you just like really
bored
[Music]
t FS
wd4 yeah I'm just
disappointed every Weber Mario Kart oh
other people's YouTuber other people's
Mario Kart streams too
oh would you just like uh
either you just really really love
playing Mario Kart and you have no one
to play it with or you just want to be
annoying I guess okay
okay
ah
what I mean I'm I'm definitely not going
to greet crony for you
so you're back what I don't see which
one the one with the
[Music]
glasses why are
you why are you on the internet maybe
it's time to turn off your internet like
can you can I give who's your mommy oh
wait R I banged her last night I I'm
going to call her
right I know your mommy uh okay I'll
I'll make her turn off your
internet well you're ruining it for
these
people
well I'm not going to let you race me
one more
time I'm going to open this
Lobby and you guys you good people going
to try to get in there as fast as you
possibly can okay
[Music]
meow sorry that you got in
sorry get the than you
Aura
[Music]
a okay
guys look I'm going to show it now okay
you guys are are ready ready you got to
be faster than
him cuz for him it's uh it's now 10 10
p.m. so it's sleepy time for little
little man it's sleepy time got to go to
school tomorrow
okay 3 2 1 go J d8
G4 if you don't go to sleepy time now
I'm going to I'm going to tell you
[Music]
Mommy
if this doesn't work I'm going to post a
code in my members
board I think that's just one more that
I want to do okay
goodbye go [\h__\h]
[Music]
yourself like this is not even like not
understanding the language or not
getting it no he knows what he's
doing my God how can you
how why why why
[Music]
why uh
wait he's not a member so we can put
this on the members
board
H try closing the game oh okay let me
try that before
uh before I put it on the members board
maybe it works like that if I re
re start the
[Music]
game
oh
[Music]
part part party not party Mario Kart
[Laughter]
[Music]
8 Mario Kart
Eight oh I love it
wait where's my where's my here's my
game capture
okay Mario
[Music]
Mario I can roll my RS yeah but not in
the way I would like to roll
them so sad okay are you ready guys 3 2
1 4 PN t d
how are you holding
up well I am I have to admit I'm wearing
pajama pants but pajama pants do not
deserve to be banned because they're
they're cozy and
fluffy and
comfortable and
warming
yeah I would love to wear them outside m
i I did I did have the courage the other
day to wear them to the uh convenience
store he's is not here let's go let's
go you are not welcome in this
party yes pajama pants are the exception
mhm I love pajama pants I have long
pajama pants I have short pajama pants I
have fluffy pajama
pants I have not so fluffy pajama pants
we are doing uh the the bankco
one here I'm really curious let's go SSE
[Music]
I just wear wear whatever buying
groceries nobody cares anyway yeah you
know I've I've come to that conclusion
too like in Japan when going to
convenience stores I've been there in um
pajamas quite often cuz I feel like it's
like because there's convenience stores
like so
all like literally everywhere they're at
least in Tokyo there's like and every
[\h__\h] corner there's a convenience
store and I've seen other people go
there dress like really
really
lightly or
carelessly so I feel
more
encouraged less worried about what to
wear there to go there and since they're
like on every street corner a lot of I
feel like also depending on the time
maybe but I feel like a lot of
people go there directly
from you know their homes as opposed to
uh go in there from their uh
workplace or
so so that I don't know why but that
feels like an excuse to me to go there
in rough
clothing but for supermarkets in Europe
it just it just kind of feels different
it doesn't feel as appropriate but I I
stopped
carrying currently my pajama pants are
just way warmer than my stupid
[Music]
[Applause]
jeans for the longest time I was also
still wearing like long
skirts long fluffy
skirts flowy
[Music]
but now even that is getting a bit cold
unless I wear you know tights and all
that I could do that but I don't want to
put that much
effort into squeezing myself and some
[\h__\h] and some
tights just to go to the
supermarket cuz squeezing yourself into
tights it's
like
not comfy I want to stay in my pajama
pants I don't want to take off my pajama
pants and change
into tights that are pretty [\h__\h]
tight putting on tights is so annoying
man
yeah invest in some fermos what do you
mean like fermal pants
what that's still pants that's still
sounds
like annoying to put
on when I can't pay attention to to the
city can't appreciate it
enough sheesh this is a place that
really exists it looks uh like
crazy I was going to turn you don't have
to help me
out no can we do it again I want to look
at it
again
guys we're going
again Steve Jobs was
there I I need some I need some warm
leggings I don't care we're just going
to go again go go go go go go go I need
to look at it
again I was too focused on
pajamas
don't shut up with the ligma why why why
why why why are there two people saying
oh Free
People this is so in insensitive is he
still alive if no then it's really
insensitive to say he died of
[Music]
ligma what the [\h__\h]
man yeah it a meme yeah but
like he's not alive
anymore he actually died from something
else obviously cuz you can't die from
ligma like I that that just seems very
disrespectful to
me maybe there's something I'm not
getting like some kind of context that
makes it okay it doesn't quite seem okay
to
me yo this is kind of crazy this is the
thing in Bangkok
is is the water also this shallow in
real life like there's no way cuz then
there those boats couldn't be passing
through I mean they were not passing
they were just stuck are they just
stuck this Market is
sick but that boat
section that was
[Applause]
cool
wow the boat markets are real what the
[\h__\h] how do you do you also get on a
boat how do you buy
[Music]
something eat my
banana
yeah money that's not what I was
asking okay what what are we looking at
now I don't know there's too much what
the [\h__\h] is that whoa whoa what is what
waa whoa whoa wow this area is
crazy I'm literally just
sightseeing what what oh this is next to
the boat
section wow they have palm trees in
Bangkok wait
what so
jealous
sorry sorry dude but you were driving so
straight time to become a little bit
more European my
friend this is also crazy can you
actually jump on
them do people jump on
them probably
not no but they definitely make you want
to they're really really
tempting they pretty much matched all
the yeah I mean of course they do that
in all the other city maps too they just
squeeze everything together really
tightly everything that's like well
known those those B markets are really
interesting though I want to look at
real pict pictures of
that um what else could I maybe the
Mario circuit Let's uh leave open one
more time and go to the Mario circuit I
think then maybe that's about
it
maybe another
person lampy need blocking too
please stop let's see maybe they'll stop
Eugene OR lampy please do not join again
this
time thank you please do not make it
complicated there you go 60
CCD or is it an O I do not
know blocking does stop them really
that's so stupid they should like then
there's literally no
way to keep someone
out in Mario Kart adx they they just
like added all these nice features and
it's still not really
helpful now what's the point of blocking
someone then for Mario Kart I guess it
doesn't do
[Music]
anything
does anyone here look familiar to you
guys I think the BART tried to get in
before but then I I closed the lobby so
I'm glad he made it is that Ooa you got
in oh my God what what I I I look I look
familiar the orange lady in the middle
middle that's fine that I'm I'm supposed
to be I'm the host okay I'm the host I'm
the owner of this channel I'm supposed
to be
here you didn't get in again I'm
sorry I'm sorry
sorry and we time let's go Mario
[Music]
circuit today I watched document
or deep dive about Spice Girls guys
Spice
Girls I didn't
know cuz I'm too young I didn't know
Spice
Girls
like had that kind of History I didn't
know that there was a breakup where they
tried to do some more stuff with four
people and I didn't know that there was
um
a little Affair between two of the
members interesting kind of cute to
think about it
[Music]
too oh I don't see anyone in here that's
been there
before maybe we got
lucky
spers I never heard about that W yeah
yeah there was like so okay let me share
with you my
knowledge uh at the time when they were
like really successful and in the middle
of a tour the uh Ginger
Spice she suddenly
leaves and everybody's like like what
the [\h__\h] why and there's like some
reasons
but nothing really perfectly makes sense
and then there's some
some um rumors
that maybe
Ginger Spice and I think crazy
spice were kind of more than just
friends and um that maybe there was like
a breakup situation or something that
made it awkward and like a heartbreak
situation but uh there was just like no
confirmation for that forever and it was
like a big mystery that they ever even
dated at all but at the same time they
there were like a lot of hints for it
but no no nobody even after the group
died even years after they would never
like confirm it or so but then there was
this one time where crazy spice she was
on a on a talk show with who I don't
know who somebody famous and many years
later she even looks really different
and like this is a this is a show where
they apparently get really honest uh
about things and talk real talk and so
the host brings up get wrecked the host
brings up uh you know this thing and
asks whether or not that really happened
and if that maybe was a reason why the
group or why she left the group
Etc and if they dated if there was more
than just being colleagues and friends
and she's like caught off guard by the
question and doesn't want to answer it
but like smiles and and looks into the
audience where there was another ex
Spice Girl
sitting and you know it's just like um
well uh I don't know well you know and
then he's like well what about did you
ever share you know beds with her and
he's like well we all shared beds he's
like yeah but you know in that way and
and then she's like um that in that way
well
eventually she confirms it for real for
real they had a thing going on but then
Ginger Spice cuz she wasn't even there
and it was revealed while she wasn't
there she actually got pretty upset
apparently
and yeah and she denied it she then went
on the media and said it's not true it's
a lie blah blah blah but honestly it
seems pretty real like why would she lie
about it too like thank you
for being part of the race thank you
yeah yeah but but it seemed I think it's
legit I believe it because of all the
circumstances and all that
yeah mm interesting
interesting but there was always like so
much
um chemistry between them and they were
always so close if you like watch
footage of them and interview views or
like behind the scenes they were just
always like really
close kill it cute
girls being cute with each other
[Music]
m h last one last one 96 GL GL stands
for girls
love between two girls yay
is Posh Spice still with David Beckham I
don't know she probably is isn't
she is this the vtuber with hole in her
pants oh is that
SpongeBob hi spongebob I heard you have
a song about a hole in your pants ribed
pants is is that why you're here to talk
to me I don't want to talk about it I am
traumatized by the incident please go
away SpongeBob don't don't remind me of
my ripped
pants that person I feel like that
person with the red eyes in the middle
was in here
[Music]
before but maybe I'm
hallucinating am I
hallucinating that video made my day
thank you I'm glad that my suffering can
make you happy that's what I'm here for
that's my
job please stop roasting SpongeBob what
what SpongeBob's not being roasted I'm
being
roasted it's zingos hi thank you I'm
happy to see
you all right let's go let's go last one
[Music]
Nas
I dropped by on my lunch break ah hey
nice to see you wait am wait I didn't do
these Amsterdam Amsterdam I did the
island one but I didn't do Amsterdam did
I oh did I wait maybe I
did maybe I did oh I think I did in the
beginning of the stream I already forgot
eh oh well it'll be nice to look at it
again I probably didn't pay much
attention no not yet my
off I probably I probably did it's 100
cc what
why oh well we're going
slow third place damn why did you not
wait for me why did you not wait for me
oh but it actually doesn't turn out to
be Amsterdam we're going rainbow road
but this is the one I already did too
right a blackout is in here
again piece of [\h__\h]
I hope you drop
off a million
times guys if you find him on the road
bully
him why am I first
oh it didn't feel right so I I I I I
purpose throw off it it just didn't feel
right
guys I sacrificed
[Music]
myself just just not not suitable I
thought that would work I think that
must work but maybe I I used the
mushroom to
Lane that also should have
[Music]
worked I can't believe that there's
someone back here with
me you suck as much as I
[Music]
do ah maybe because it's 100 cc oh yeah
right cuz some things only
work uh in certain speed levels huh
right oh wait what I got two
stars the
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] let's get the
[Music]
double Hodor kfp is that like a
reference to
[Music]
Hodor I'm going to fall off
it's slow it doesn't even feel so slow
to
me this part is really
pretty
[Music]
wowy it's nice to end it on Rainbow Road
I guess it's actually quite
a
oops why did the star not prevent me
from falling
off
I was saying it's quite a fitting ending
[Music]
race sorry I'm so sorry you were right
in front of
me
[Music]
K
I made it y it's
possible go go go I was about to fall
off let's
[Music]
go yeah
bye bye m m wait for me wait for
me Ryan my British
friend you're on my skill level please
wait for me have mercy Ryan why did you
go without me
Ryan Ryan you and
me we had something good
going
Rotondo
Chad Ryan why why Ry why Ryan why Ryan
R
Ryan
Ryan can you hear what I'm saying I'm
saying
Ryan okay that was fun thank you guys
for playing Mario Kart with me Mario
Mario Kart it's been a long time and I
did cheat on Mario Kart with uh the
other racing
game
so that's why it's been so long but it's
nice that there was some new tracks and
honestly I'm really interested in you
know visiting some of these cities in
person someday MK members only that is
not
possible uh we do not have permission to
play Nintendo games as members only
streams
unfortunately
what what does does you tweet blaming
mths mean you are removing moth
identifying individuals from your fan
base what do you mean you identify as a
mo or
what I identify as a as an ant I
identify as a uh goddess uh uh praying
mantis I identify as a
[Music]
sponge
I identify as a computer
keyboard identify as an air yeah yeah
yeah that's so Random don't tell me
you're identify as a moom I mean I I do
have some other things besides chickens
in here like I I I do I do tolerate like
an owl for
example but you're telling me you you
want to be a m hm
hm I don't know about that
that's quite quite a stretch I don't
know I think you have to realize the
reality that you are
indeed a
chicken
yeah just because you're drawn to the
sun doesn't mean that you're a moth it
lies in your nature as a chicken to be
drawn to this beautiful sunlike Phoenix
thank you guys for the Super Chat thank
you I'm glad you guys got
in MO
FES
[Music]
ew identify as a bucket until I rebirth
anyways exactly that is exactly what you
are and you are so aware of it you're
reaching like a new level of awareness
soon as I think good for you good for
you yeah thank you all for joining if
mow can be a frog then I can no the
thing is he's not a frog that's the
thing he realizes it too pretty early in
the game so that argument does not
[Music]
stand not even a
member no the the the fact this the mere
fact that you are in my chat makes you a
chicken I don't care if you shape shift
after you leave this
stream but like your time being in this
stream anybody here becomes a
chicken that's just how it goes that's
just how nature
goes that's how it is I can't change the
rules I don't make the rules I just
enforce
them
melow is not a frog I know a frog when I
see
it I have a
frog keeps on escaping
[Music]
though
Apple Chicken shrimp taco skeleton Apple
oh
a okay
guys I guess I'll read some super
chats it's going to get late again and
I'm going to get um not motivated to
cook but we're going to read some super
chats cuz I'm
behind don't sound so
excited it's just because I know that
the later it gets the less I'll be
motivated to
cook but it's okay I'm not motivated to
cook anyway even
[Music]
now you just got out of the hospital
what read the do set on aspirin
careful you little
[\h__\h] you overdosed on aspirin how dare
you how dare
you you little [\h__\h] be more
careful you stupid little [\h__\h] don't do
this to me be careful you little [\h__\h] it
was an accident I don't give a [\h__\h] that
you stupid be careful you little
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
it be careful you
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to do
without you
huh like who's going to who's going to
make me those yummy hot piping hot fresh
crispy chicken strips ah what am I going
to
do
dude
James
still have some tiny to you little [\h__\h]
the tiny to is just
me that's probably just me is your fine
that's just
me that's
me yeah take care little
[\h__\h] I'm happy to hear you're healthy
but don't ever let this happen ever
again
M
unbelievable
unbelievable you know you have to take
care of yourself for me I don't allow
any unhealthy chickens here treat
yourself like you are a
temple you are your body is a
temple
and I am
your
goddess and for your goddess you have
to keep the temple
intact I identify as a
bungalow and Temple and Bungalow
no your body is a kfp restaurant no no
no
just be careful guys stay healthy like
I I I do not
accept
any too early
demises I will be in charge of your
[Music]
demises he needs lamp no he doesn't need
the lamp what are you talking about he's
not off he knows he's a
chicken lamp will just give him more
heada ache and then he will get
aspirin I vow to survive until you kill
me good I'll work out more for you than
my queen awesome oh workout I was going
to ask you guys like I I want to buy a
treadmill I know I talked about this
before and you guys said I should get
one of of those like biky thingies but
no I want the treadmill because I want
to
um kind of like get
stability uh for like just like for
example when I
dance it's the same kind of bouncing
around no not for my cats for
me and I was looking at uh uh
treadmills on Amazon but I wasn't sure
what
what to go
for they seem fine what about the rowing
machine that one's fine too but like I'm
looking for different things in them I I
want the treadmill so that I can get
more stable when dancing in terms of
like breathing and
singing or like even not even dancing
but just also everyday things
like um you
know
walking outside but the biggest thought
is I think it if I go running every day
on a treadmill I think it will help me
um
possibly
get a strong
core for possible life
singing if that ever be becomes a
necessity um you know just you
know I don't know I don't know I don't
know but just you know
maybe and I thought running will be the
best because then I'm actually like
bouncing bouncing bouncing so if I was
thinking maybe I can try singing while
on the treadmill just to train
myself now not to get out of breath too
you
know but yeah I was looking at the
treadmills
and yeah I don't know what's like
important
um
[Music]
yeah yeah but still I want the I want
the treadmill and the good thing is with
treadmills like rather than the bikes
the treadmill I can put away easier I
think because it's
flat use treadmills are fine too oh I
guess so cuz they pretty expensive like
the the good-looking ones are like 250
to 300
bucks
MH do you have a sporty gym friend no
running is best exercise so it's good
yeah
right most expensive towel
hangers B there's no bgm right now
walking that's is like I'm we could we
could but for me it's not about walking
it's about
running and I feel like it will take me
a while to not die after 10 minutes or
even 5 minutes of
running take me a while we have to start
there got to start
there maybe when I get to a point where
I can run or like jog for 20 minutes
comfortably then we could make a stream
out of it otherwise it's going to be
over immediately and I'm going to die
hyperventilating uh you might want to
look into louder what I don't know what
that means no I want the treadmill but
there were some that uh also get like a
little lift like so as if you're jogging
up a hill not everyone that I looked at
had that feature I wonder if I really
should get one with that it makes it
more expensive
though yeah the elevation do I really
need
that I feel like I
don't yeah
incline noral is fine right also anybody
here who goes to the and uses the
running machine what's the speed you
normally go for because the ones I've
been looking at says that the running
speeds they can do is like
10 or 12 kilometers per per hour please
tell me in kilometers per hour cuz I
don't understand anything
else what the [\h__\h] is
m
o it's plenty right 10 to 12 is plenty
right okay okay
okay okay
o o o oop o oop o
o I know what it means
I I mean I don't know how to interpret
that thank you you don't need to write
it out for
me normal human walking speed is 3 to 5
kmh
[Music]
really
if you ever come to America there's this
Trail called the money to Incline in
Colorado which basically goes in a
straight line up to the side of a
mountain it makes for good lag day
workout I realistically doubt that I
will in my whole life ever get there but
good to know maybe good to know for
Americans who travel within
America
cuz I don't know like what that that
sounds great but
like I don't see like ever getting
there and if I go to col
Colorado will I really want to go hiking
up a mountain maybe that's like the
thing to do in Colorado
[Music]
Colorado sheesh it's
beautiful sheesh
shees
sheesh
shees you
know Country Roads should have gone like
this Country Roads Take me home to the
place I belong
Colorado it's so
beautiful why didn't they mention it in
the
[Music]
OG why sheesh it's insane it's beautiful
my God what what does West Virginia have
what does West Virginia look like does
it look better than
Colorado oh that looks crazy that pretty
good in Autumn that looks
insane it's pretty good pretty good no
but I don't know I feel like Colorado
kind of has more to offer than West
Virginia just looking through the
pictures on
Google just just feels like a bit more
variety in Colorado judging by the
pictures so maybe it should be
Colorado not West
[Laughter]
[Music]
Virginia yeah it has more biomes
Colorado has more
bomis yeah so I don't know but your your
choice I guess your problem I guess if
you really want to make it all about
West
[Music]
Virginia
pomi
super and Super
Chat
uh uh also music
[Music]
ooh ooh ooh o how far is Ena in Final
Fantasy see she's playing in 15
minutes wonder how far she is what I
what am I doing um music audio
Stu all all the polars delivered uh
which one do you mean do you mean the
digital ones or the real ones the real
ones I just sent out
today the digital ones I will get to
now because I had to sign real life ones
those were priority otherwise waa get
the Bonk she passed Bahamut
uh well how many more are there I don't
remember which one that
was
she's about to start the Odin
Arc and Shiva ooh okay okay okay okay
okay oh oh this one's more realistic if
you ever come to Sweden there's a trail
called serum land Len it's very
beautiful with plenty of beautiful
Swedish okay okay I will probably go to
Sweden although I don't know if I'll go
to such a specific place where is that
even is that even in the capital or is
that like in a really random
place I'm Googling it that looks like
really oh no it's south of
Stockholm eh but so far it's far as
[\h__\h] you really think I'm going to go
that
far
I'm going to you think I'm going to go
that far for for for this little trail
that looks like I can find that like
everywhere in
Sweden I'm saying that everywhere is
probably beautiful like this in Sweden
do I really need to go
there do I really need to go
there such a specific
mention
1 hour dve that's probably more than an
hour no I don't
know man I'm so sorry like I'm I'm
roasting the real reality the likelihood
of me going there and you just trying to
share a nice um trail with me I'm sorry
but I'm probably not going to go
there just like you guys recommending
like like FPS and horror games to me
that I'm never going to
[Laughter]
play 30 minute drive really well then
that's more realistic if it's just like
a 30-minute drive but like I'm I don't
have a license I don't have a license
are you going to drive
me
[Laughter]
I just I don't want to just say yes to
everything you guys you know tell me you
know like hey there's this great game
hey there's this great place hey there
this there's this great song I don't
want to be like oh yeah wow totally
going to listen to this totally going to
look at this totally going to go there I
don't want to you know
lie I don't want to give you promises
that I'm never going to
fulfill h
keeping it real
Joe I will legit drive you or pay for a
cap wait that's so
romantic you would pay for my cab just
for me to go
there damn you must be really convinced
of this Trail I'll probably get lost in
there it's kind of cute that you you
would do
that
it's kind of cute it's kind of
cute will you pay for my plane ticket
that's also the
[Music]
question the
r you cured my depression so maybe a
a m
m I'm happy I can bring you guys
happiness and you wonder why I am
parasocial if like hearing stuff like
that how can I not
be
H how can I not be I just want the best
for you guys
[Music]
H you're so sweet guys but I will not go
to your stupid hiking trail in Colorado
or in
Sweden it's not
realistic okay okay and Wawa Super
chatos O oopsy [\h__\h]
[Music]
ads you can event anything you can give
me recommendations in Austria or in
Japan like places where I'll actually
more likely
go anyway did I read the I read the
Shark Tank super chats and I did read
the nail collab super chats
right then I guess hatam is
next and oh then the waiting
room is actually here next up which has
a couple more more Super chats than the
others I'll read
those chat oh why you not show I don't
know you ask yourself why are you not
showing up I put the URL in there
properly you are not choosing you're
choosing to not show
[Music]
up your
problem you here now it's about
time actually kind of a 2,700 step
staircase so are you like trying to kill
me or
what let's read the Hat Super Chat Jacob
47 3,000 cordum fighter jets of
soup zly Sky thanks for the pinky mom my
meme is on TV thank you for making the
meme it was really
good I I really liked the memes that
came up even though I was struggling to
find uh a good
amount but the ones that I did show I
liked them yes yes yes very very good
stuff feel like the concept of the
stream was
genius um but me being stressed about
time and then ending up going so fast
that I actually had time left over and
no
memes that um was
unfortunate also for Hama like uh I I
think I originally wanted to go to
dinner with her before the stream or so
but then I had like some stuff to do
beforehand work and I couldn't go and
then she showed up like while I Was
preparing the stream and I was kind of
focused on prepping it so we couldn't
even talk much so we started the stream
and then we ended it and then like she
like immediately left and I think I also
cuz
yeah the studio was closing I think so I
also had to leave so it was really just
like the time of the stream I barely got
to talk to
her sadly that was like the shortest
interaction of my off collabs pretty
much yeah but then I'm I'm happy she had
time for me I'm
honored cuz that was shortly after her
Revival
M I'm glad she could make
it she was wearing really cute
clothes that's all I can say about like
behind the
scenes that's all I can say that's all I
God so
sad
[Music]
I hope she's doing well hope she's happy
wish her all the
best she's so cute so high
energy 3, cordium fighter jets of soup
thank you again thank you so much I am a
beep py
and thank you okay now we're going to
read the waiting room ones which you
know are over the span of like I don't
know a week or
so so that's a few more than I
thought and why is there so many red
super
chats the
[\h__\h] I wasn't even
streaming
[Music]
why
why ah oh cuz I was talking about my my
taxes I am for the Twitter
space thank you guys you guys are
crazy so crazy you guys know I told you
right before many times that just
because you send a red super chat
doesn't mean it's going to immediately
on the same day go on my bank
account there's like a two month
delay you guys just you know when you're
just being funny
right
okay yeah are you
[Music]
surprised yeah basically it's like uh I
guess you
YouTube Just gathers the super chats for
a full month and I don't know if it's
like YouTube doing it automatically or
if it's the company doing it but like at
the end of the month the company I
guess like checks how much like
calculates how much it was for that
month but I don't know it still like
takes one more
month to all be like you know
calculated registered and
you because like if it's for a whole
month I told you it always gets paid out
like my salary gets paid out on the last
day of the month if I still get another
Super Chat on that last day of the month
then that wouldn't be part of the salary
so everything just gets delayed by like
two months I guess to all be
um
um what's the word
whatever you know what I mean that's
just how it is that's just how it
is so like my from the bigger months
like the the birthday month and the
Christmas month Etc all of that is just
always a little bit delayed so basically
like my birthday money and my Christmas
money comes in a little bit
later yeah
yeah and then I'm like I look at my back
at I bank account and I'm like oh why
why why was this one so much and I'm
like oh yeah right it was my birthday oh
yeah must have been my
birthday but I always wonder like oh
what was what was the the event this
time cuz I forget cuz so much time
passes and I don't even remember what
happened Christmas money is a
Valentine's Day gift yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
seems like it Christmas money becomes
Valentine's
money oh yeah the polar Awards yeah
yeah oh [\h__\h] I snorted what the
[\h__\h] I don't want to
snort did you hear it that was a pretty
clear
snort I don't normally snort it's so
Random
ew that was an outward snort though not
[Music]
inwards okay I'm falling
asleep un no Cru D unknown thank you for
the red super chat wow I love thanks
mate thanks matey thanks
your your red Super Chat is so so red
it's like like a bloody Super Chat get
it get
it thank you so much
n elction
elction
t72 d GD
dun silver Ser dun cup noodles let's go
I'll slap and D soon Slavic fellow oo
thank you for the red super chat new tax
people
fund oh thank you thank you
well I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm staying
for at least until I'm done with the
current current uh applications and
[\h__\h] all
right you still here thanking me and kfp
for the race
it's like you had
some brain
delay are the the browser servers like
overwhelmed right now
[Music]
huh Opera needs better servers more RAM
let's download more
RAM it's getting too
hot she's melting Ora is
melting uh yeah thank you Slavic fellow
I appreciate it thank you for thank you
for the support but don't worry it will
it will all work out eventually in the
end it'll be fine let die jobu don't
worry M logical Paradox thany soon Sky
thanks for the pinky future chunk and
smovie food fund yo smoothie is being
even more annoying right now than before
I left for
Japan so annoying man I don't get it I
don't get it why why she's doing the
thing again where I give her early
breakfast and then she'll wake me up
again like one or two hours later and
beg for food again
I don't know if she forgets that she
already had
food or if she just being
greedy
[Music]
but no she didn't do any of that to
Mama no I don't think it's because of
her taking care of her cuz she didn't do
that
supposedly yeah
yeah I don't know man I hope she'll calm
down again but she's being so annoying
man I I want to sleep through I just
want to sleep through the night
man I never get to sleep for the night
when I'm at
home that's
[Music]
honestly it's just it can't be
good
it's so rare that she lets me sleep for
the
night but like if I nap during the day
no matter how long let's say I had to
wake up really early for like a 6:00
a.m. recording or so and then I go back
to sleep afterwards for like 5 hours 6
hour nap because I didn't sleep much in
the night during that time she's just
constantly
calm maybe I
should turn around my sleep schedule and
like nap during the night and make it uh
a norm to sleep during the day like like
let's say from 10: to 6:00
p.m. but no that's going to I'm going to
[\h__\h] everything up and then I can't
stream during my normal times and this
and that sucks but I feel like if I did
that she would let me
[Music]
sleep
because she never like if it's daytime
if it's bright outside she won't wake me
up no matter how long I
sleep stupid
cat why is she like this
[Music]
why that's how I sleep since I work
nights I could do that but I don't want
to has changed my streaming times either
[Music]
really yeah the automatic feeder I told
you before it's like good for for dry
food but what she's begging for is wet
food and for wet food I have to get up
and I tried it before to put it into the
feeder but it's just like it gets kind
of disgusting if I leave it overnight in
the feeder and she also doesn't really
like
register it as fresh
food or any food at all and just ignores
it then it stands out around even longer
and you
know then it gets even more
disgusting yeah oh well it is what it is
I'll continue suffering with smoothie
and chunky wonky honestly chunky wonky
is probably like the whole time when
smoovie is like me me meow meow meow
meow it forces me to get up whole time
chunky is just like sleeping and waiting
patiently in her
box most of the time she doesn't even
get up when I go to the kitchen and and
and give smoovie her food and I go back
to my bed chunkers is still in the same
spot just
[Music]
chilling she's such a easy to handle
cat yeah Angel Marvel cat yeah good girl
my baby stop giving her food I tried I
swear I tried like ignoring her for
hours but she won't stop and this whole
time I'll be like not sleeping losing
sleep and getting really annoying
annoyed cuz like she's in my face
meowing really loudly nonstop long loud
meow now I cannot take that endlessly
and I tried closing the doors tried
closing her behind
it
no and also I tried to counter it by
giving her dinner cuz I I didn't always
give her dinner wet
food I would only give it give her like
breakfast wet food in the past but I
tried to counter it hoping that she
won't wake me up so early if I give her
wet food for dinner it didn't change
[Music]
anything yeah she's spayed
yeah you tried wearing headphones
yeah I did but like the the bulky ones
you can it's just I I I'm mostly a sid
sleeper
and yeah with the bulky
ones even when I just like really
slightly lean to the side while still
lying on my back it will already be like
you know not sitting on my head properly
and then I tried actually this is like
an upcoming sponsorship video that I'm
going to put
up I got a sponsorship for headphones
and
earbuds uh not really getting paid just
getting the product for some promotion I
tried um one night like like two nights
ago or so I tried putting the earbuds
which are supposedly um noise cancelling
too tried putting them in but I was like
half asleep and I didn't read the
instructions I don't even know I don't
think the noise cancelling was working I
have to maybe activated
somehow um but I definitely still heard
her very loud and clear but instead I
just put on like some video on YouTube
to listen
to um to like drain her drain drown her
[Music]
out wax earplugs can do wonders yeah or
even the tentacle ear plugs that I gave
to my brother I
guess yeah I I want to try the the ear
buds again and see if I can figure out
how to actually make it noise cancelling
but with earbuds generally they always
fall out of my ears
man
[Music]
but I'm still testing out some
things
yeah yeah generally noise cancelling it
cancels out stuff perfectly like for
example airplane noises when you're in
the
airplane but
yeah it
doesn't really drown out a cat directly
talking to
you that's not really it's
expertise I can't hear you I tried
everything man foam ones yeah they might
actually work but I don't like the
feeling of having like LS in my
ears airpods are they're
good I'm not getting airpods for [\h__\h]
sake no they're too
expensive first of all like sheesh Apple
product
man I'm sure that there's like
equivalent just as good uh
ear phone thingies whatever from other
brands that sell it
[Music]
cheaper oh my eyes are so tired
a why my throat hurts I hate
winter I love winter but I hate it for
streaming [\h__\h] let me eat fro
candy
what can
here logical wait wait we already wear
there uh GD than for the pinky doesn't
matter it's still for some fun thank you
g why you so generous man thank you
sweet
potato open your window yeah that might
help of the
tiredness I'm not actually
tired I'm actually tired it's just my
eyes
El thank you for the WR chat have some
of my Monopoly
money but also this is Super Chat is a
pre Super Chat for my birthday at the 20
of November oo this is my fourth
birthday with you and all I can say is
thank you for everything big wa love
remember everything will be okay at the
end trust
us it's okay I I
I more or less got the the bank loan so
I paid those
[Music]
11,000
um
yeah it's okay I'll be fine I just need
to um buy the males
flights next um and besides that uh I
think there's there's some other things
coming up but it'll be fine I believe in
it
I don't like the wording of that but
what what what what what what what did I
say oh the the more or less uh it's
because the bank couldn't make it in
time so the
finance uh guy just gave me a part of
the loan from his own money ahead of
time so it just said I can pay off the
11,000 that's why I said more or less
why why are you looking like that
why
why it's fine he's being
[Music]
helpful yeah he's really nice like I
know some of you guys have been saying
now that like he's scamming me or
whatever no but he's really nice and and
I I
actually
like I got to him through uh one of my
closest friends
anyway who kind of works with him so I I
know he's like he's not sketchy
whatever please don't judge just by you
know a few statements that
seem maybe sketchy but they're not
they're not
sketchy if anything like
he he proves about you know me for
example getting rid of my tax lady which
you guys also say no he's he's helped me
with a lot of things okay he's really
nice don't judge
him you guys are
like
so
like you're my parents and and you're
judging who your daughter
is just being friends
with like really really really concerned
parents
[Music]
overprotective
stop it Mom it's fine stop it leave me
alone it's my life it's my life
okay I will I will hang out with who I
want
to shut up I'm going to emancipate
[Music]
myself you can't ground me that's
robbing me of my human rights you
[Music]
suck I like this kind of role play it's
kind of
[Music]
funny
the bird
fres okay okay okay wait wait wait H
thank you
El Sun Sunny Tesla thank you for the
redet Kam new chicken factory fund I
hope you stress relieved a little thank
you
um I mean by now it definitely did did
the Twitter space relieve my stress a a
a little bit but it was definitely still
there uh but I'm I'm just happy I'm back
in Austria now just being here having my
cats and having the recording
done is
like just like difference of Night and
Day or like actually way more intense
than that
so I'm fine I'm fine thank you Mah Jeff
start
for the pinky with no words Jeffy I told
you not to do
that can not D wait actually I totally
forgot like I because I was talking
about other things sorry elab I I should
have like more clearly said happy
birthday to you sorry sorry
sorry I just
remembered happy birthday I'm a little
bit late but I still want to say happy
birthday I hope you had an amazing
birthday already your fourth that's
actually
crazy that's actually crazy can you
imagine that sounds so crazy cuz I I
only just had my third anniversary but
you already had your first birthday with
me that's just how things work I guess
but um it's
crazy that sounds like we we've been
together like for
ages I hope
we will continue to spend a lot of time
[Music]
together K than thanks for Pinky all the
cute emotes thank you thank you for the
support and cheering me
up very much appreciated thank you cute
chicken lunchbox
D oh I'm happy to hear that thank you
you talk to the chum buts and they
appreciate it
reflect I'm glad I didn't want
to you know I wasn't sure how how that
would come across if I sang a song of
hers but yeah at the end this is about
the anime
NYC at the end I felt like we needed to
hear some GAA songs
so whether I was singing it or not you
know I just wish that um I could hear
you guys cuz I I can see you guys
through Zoom I wish I could hear you
cheering uh when I'm singing but I have
to
mute you guys at all of these
conventions when I'm singing and you
know I I sometimes I I throw a few like
louder louder hi hi in there just
imagining that you guys are hopefully
cheering but I can't actually hear it
because um first of all depending on the
venue uh I don't only hear the audience
clapping Etc but I also hear like a tiny
bit delayed feedback of my my own voice
especially with anime NYC it was really
bad uh the feedback was really bad and
there was no time to like fix it at the
spot
there m
yeah oh I would have loved to hear yeah
cuz I was imagining people singing cuz I
was asking you guys to sing during the
song I Can't wa to I was asking you guys
and I wish I could have heard it I wish
somebody would could have recorded it
and sent it to me but recording not
allowed so
[\h__\h] I wish I could hear it you know but
I have to mute you guys it froze me
off m
so
sad so [\h__\h] sad it's always with
these conventions the same thing can't I
can't really hear you guys but I can see
you if I'm not looking at the lyrics I
can see you guys a little
bit
mhm need to get an official recording
person yeah I regret I
regret
I tried show that people watching
pineapple before show a I think I saw
that
[Music]
maybe people ask me to do K KP
server pre-recorded then sneak into
audience to cheer for yourself of
everyone
no froggy wa will not be released of
course not not until frog
week sleep talking and be still
happening tomorrow ooh actually
actually probably
not probably not because I do have to
send it for legal check
um once it's
done and sometimes it goes really fast
sometimes it's really slow
I'm I mean that really sucks because I
need it to be out
[Music]
before before the month ends but it is
what it
is can't help it anymore at this point I
really try my best to get it out in
time what could possibly be illegal in
the mvy uh it's called Legal check but
it's like it's all kinds of things it's
like like whether all the assets used in
the video are copyright free or like or
if the copyright has been
properly
um uh claimed like like properly bought
or
whatever uh mostly that kind of stuff I
think if all the rights for any any
assets or
fonts in the video
are um
yeah
owned and if it's a cover song
[Music]
then like got to check if like the
lyrics are really accurate Etc cuz like
changing the lyrics either singing or
just the ones on the screen is something
that has to be asked permission for
separately so just making sure that
everything's okay but um sometimes it
takes a while
H
so I'm still hoping for it but I'm
doubting that it will be
[Music]
ready well I'll upload it when it's
ready but if I if it's not ready
tomorrow then I'll upload please remind
me actually if you can on Twitter
then I'll upload um another one of those
like little YouTube short and Twitter
videos like last time with uh not heart
Rush Love
Rush streamlabs no no only Super
Chat what are plans for membership
tomorrow I don't know I'll decide when I
get
up maybe
game and
guys it's already so [\h__\h]
[Music]
late I barely got anywhere I feel like I
need to end it
here at umix or lunch
[Music]
box yeah have to cook cook the
what in Jones no no no not movie cuz uh
didn't we watch a movie very recently
so although last week was
chitchat I did do a member stream last
week when I got back from uh Japan mhm
on the same day yeah I'm keeping up my
promise of member streams each
week but no member h no no movie for
this member stream cuz I feel feel like
it's too
early don't want to spam the movies
maybe next
week oh I'm
hungry Pulp
Fiction uh my Pulp Fiction meme I hope
people will use it I already saw you
guys use it a lot on
Twitter I'm sorry it it's so short like
literally it it was over in 4 seconds I
feel like a lot of people were like wait
what what like literally didn't register
what just
happened especially Japanese Bros cuz I
feel like a lot of Japanese Bros like
most of them don't even know the
meme it was me it was me too
honestly I was like yeah yeah that is so
short that was so way shorter than I
anticipated
it doesn't feel so short normally cuz I
feel like when that Meme gets used it's
often like being repeated and
looped but it's really just those 4
seconds
honestly in reality that
[Music]
movement I was confused but it was so
funny the 5 minute the 5 minute
countdown was purpose I I wanted it to
be the longest possible countdown for
the biggest possible
troll yeah I did uh like back down a
little bit on my trolling by adding more
and more things to the thumbnail also
cuz you
guys like in in the chat there were a
lot of people taking it serious and
being like e what the I'm so worried now
and then I felt pretty bad like I didn't
want to worry anyone I thought people
would understand it's not anything
serious
um because I mean if you watched the
stream the day before then you would
know that was my argument but of course
not many people uh who see that will
watch or will have watched the previous
day which I also knew but I thought that
you know the the atmosphere in the chat
will also make it very clear that it's
not serious stuff like that and then
more and more I added things to the
thumbnail that made it very obvious that
it's nothing serious I literally wrote
in Japanese it's a joke don't
worry yeah and and I thought that at
this point I made made it so obvious
people probably not going to even wait
for this but then how how why why did
11,000
people end up waiting for
this when it was obviously not a
graduation
announcement then I I thought oh my God
these people have high expectations even
though they know it's not not a
graduation announcement they have really
high expectations and all I have is a 4
minute H 4 second video of a Pulp
Fiction
meme I hope I hope I hope it's not too
disappointing but uh well it was
supposed to be a troll and I think I
trolled
successfully I just felt really bad uh
because some people waited really long
also because of their time zones I
didn't want people to stay up 4 hours
into the night when it's over ready so
late and they have to go to work early
and all that that that's why I
specifically for Japanese
Bros um try
to get the point across that they can
just go to sleep because this is not
worth
it I
tried I
tried n Risa no if I would be planning
to graduate I would tell her way before
so I don't think she really thought
something was going to happen she did DM
me when she saw it I was like don't
worry don't worry it's
nothing I was like I got myself so deep
into this [\h__\h] Nissa help
me but
yeah she got scared well I mean she's a
little bit too too too much in love with
me she's parasocial about
me okay I'm going to go cook some food
now and tomorrow me only
stream cuz K only calm down japane yeah
I thought I kind of want to work calm
down the Korean views too but then I got
to do it like in every freaking
language I was hoping the Korean viewers
would somehow understand the message
too no
[Music]
but I'll see you tomorrow at members
only stream I hope I have a quick dinner
in my hellofresh
box thank you for letting me race with
you no thank you for
joining thank you
sh the yeah yeah yeah I mean yeah I feel
like the most obvious
one at least for my usual
viewers would be that it was going to be
my thousandth
video by the way I know it's not correct
but I was changing the title in a hurry
and I was like wait which one is it
again whatever just do it both do
both so it's 1
1,000
video
I feel like it gives it extra charm this
way nice touch right yeah very WWA 1,000
it's how I say
dep
dep thank you for thank
[Music]
you the myth speaker of
Ian all right then goodbye
guys and see you
tomorrow bye bye
[Music]
byebye you became a K-pop stand because
of me what's what's your group what's
your go-to group it better be new jeans
[Music]
Esa or I don't even listen to
ESA
[Music]
they remind you of Holo
life
what all right I'm not taking
responsibility for that I don't I don't
even listen to
esel m