​​​ ​HOLOTORI - HOLOTORI Dance!​ ​​
​​​ ​Lyrics: noire​ ​​
​​​ ​Composition, Arrangement:​ ​​
​​ ​Mamoru Izuki (Hifumi,inc.)​ ​​
​​​ ​Illustration, Video: Eleos​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Takanashi Kiara, Oozora Subaru,​ ​​
​​ ​Pavolia Reine, Nanashi Mumei, Takane Lui​ ​​
​​​ ​Announcement! Announcement!​ ​​
​​​ ​The flock has arrived​ ​​
​​​ ​Locking your hearts in a cage​ ​​
​​​ ​We're here for a good time​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba twee la cit cit kuwa kue​ ​​
​​​ ​Birds of a feather feather​ ​​
​​​ ​Hoot chirp kuwa kue​ ​​
​​​ ​The spotlight's on us​ ​​
​​​ ​Make some room on the floor​ ​​
​​​ ​Give us a sweet solid beat​ ​​
​​​ ​Bet you'll want an encore​ ​​
​​​ ​You ready?​ ​​
​​​ ​Our cuteness is criminal​ ​​
​​​ ​Our kawaisa's criminal​ ​​
​​​ ​Committing fowl play​ ​​
​​​ ​Rhythm feelin' impeckable​ ​​
​​​ ​Rhythm nori impeckable​ ​​
​​​ ​We're only getting started​ ​​
​​​ ​Crack the shell​ ​​
​​​ ​Crack the kara​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori hour​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori awaa​ ​​
​​​ ​Swing it to the left and right​ ​​
​​​ ​Show ya what we got yeah​ ​​
​​​ ​Flying feelings​ ​​
​​​ ​Flying kankaku​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori power​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori pawaa​ ​​
​​​ ​Crown't get left behind​ ​​
​​​ ​tori nokosareruna yo​ ​​
​​​ ​Do the Holotori Dance​ ​​
​​​ ​Announcement! Announcement!​ ​​
​​​ ​The nest's almost full​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring in the noise and the juice​ ​​
​​​ ​So this party's not dull​ ​​
​​​ ​Ba twee la cit cit kuwa kue​ ​​
​​​ ​Birds of a feather feather​ ​​
​​​ ​Hoot chirp kuwa kue​ ​​
​​​ ​Stand up, strut your stuff​ ​​
​​​ ​Migrate onto the floor​ ​​
​​​ ​Give us your best cluckin' moves​ ​​
​​​ ​We wanna see you soar​ ​​
​​​ ​Get rowdy​ ​​
​​​ ​Capek's not acceptable​ ​​
​​​ ​We know you'll want to stay​ ​​
​​​ ​This lagu's irresistible​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on it's owl or nothing​ ​​
​​​ ​Crack the shell​ ​​
​​​ ​Crack the kara​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori hour​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori awaa​ ​​
​​​ ​Wing it 'til we're taking flight​ ​​
​​​ ​Show ya what we got yeah​ ​​
​​​ ​Flying feelings​ ​​
​​​ ​Flying kankaku​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori power​ ​​
​​​ ​Tori pawaa​ ​​
​​​ ​Crown't get left behind​ ​​
​​​ ​Bentang sayap dan bersiap​ ​​
​​​ ​Do the Holotori Dance​ ​​