[Music]
e
W good
morning
afternoon
evening is
[Music]
time
hello how you guys
doing he
good excuse
me so dusty in my
room need to turn on
the your
your
purifier humidifier something like
that
hello sounding a little sleepy I am
in especially since the nether is
opening
today
yeah not
sure how well I'll
do but we'll see we'll see
it's busy busy week originally I was
going to be probably streaming a little
less this
week cuz there's a lot of stuff I need
to
prepare
but as soon as the week started the
Hardcore Minecraft server got announced
so I was like I want to play Hardcore
Minecraft perhaps I can push myself for
another
[Music]
week having fun but I feel
like I feel like maybe two streams in a
day is a little too much right now
[Music]
I don't want to get sick either cuz the
the year is going to be ramping up from
now I'll just say
that my
goodness that be exciting
though one thing I guess I should tell
you guys is that I'm probably going to
be
spending quite a few months in Japan
later in the
year
so there's going to be a lot
of what should I say prep stuff going on
beforehand before I leave for a couple
months which is part of the reason I'm
kind of busy trying to make sure my life
schedules and you know other stuff don't
get get too messed
up yeah exciting
stuff will this change the stream times
I'm not too sure cuz it really depends
on what kind of place I
get um cuz like a
normal you
know apartment Etc in Japan is not very
soundproof
therefore
streaming and
talking I don't I don't talk that loud
but still I don't know how
much of talking and you know stuff can
be allowed in early morning Japanese
Apartments normal Japanese Apartments
anyways
so um I have to see and I realized that
you know hotels
have
pretty Shifty internet like even the
ones that I've gone
to before have
pretty Okay Internet they're expensive
per night so I can't stay there for you
know many
months and and those that are cheaper
have very questionable internet so I
have to be able to find a relatively
okay spot and I can't
really arrange or ask the staff to be in
the studio in time for my normal Taco
Time time
so we'll see
yeah
anyways
um as usual the start of
our Minecraft streams I mean I'll talk
about the Whatchamacallit me being in
Japan for a couple months a little more
when things are a little more settled in
the uh nailed in I
guess but it's just the uh it's just uh
I
guess
uh not really a warning but just uh just
a poke poke this is going to happen
so I don't
think it is morally okay for me to ask
to be able to stream at normal Taco Time
at the studio so the best
BET right now is to find a good you
know apartment or something I
can stay in for a couple of months we'll
[Music]
see but yes start of Minecraft stream
I'll talk about it more later
guys since right now it's kind of still
still on the planning
stages but first theong oh I'm in the
way how did it end up like this move Ena
move
what okay there we
go all right flashbang
today's plan
wow exciting stuff
today we got the nether opening I think
we got some trials
today in my trials It also says it also
means that there has been some
casualties while I was
sleeping seems like has been some
casualties um I think the tri is
definitely going to be in Japanese so um
I'll see if I can go and
watch but um today
today nether is opening so that's also
happening um not exactly sure when but
hopefully I guess
I get the least
Peak um at
the at the
um at the nether before I go to
sleep I think depending on how I feel at
the end of the stream
probably not stream 12 hours from
now oh I'm so
exhausted I don't I I realized to okay I
have the stamina for
this I'm literally just like he
guys it's Minecraft
[Music]
time it's my it's my it's my t-shirt
looks like I have good
muscles hey guys it's Minecraft
time but
anyways today is
plan but in the gym the grains
all right um number okay we write down
number zero number Alpha which is
survive and
pet any
CS
okay um number one is to finish
our
bows cuz we we fished up some pretty
good bows yesterday I think we can have
an Infinity flame was it a flame and
then power four
bow like we'll have one
flame powerful
four
[Music]
Infinity B and then we'll have a
mending what was it mending
flame but um I think it's good to have
both
because
um because
you know I can interchangeably use
them this is The Mending was probably
like a backup for the main
bow um but that
requires getting many
bows
to
many bows to fix these
two and then fix
oh all right I mean Infinity will
eventually break I think the reason I
didn't do I have Unbreak is Unbreaking a
bow
thing Minecraft
hard okay so I need to I guess if I
don't have Unbreaking on it then I
probably um will go through the infinity
book pretty
fast yeah it's like I don't want to
break mid battle so that's why I have
The Mending bow just in
case does Kyla have Unbreaking three
already
oh but always good to have you know
maybe I'll also put maybe I'll also
[Music]
enchant Unbreaking on
both Unbreaking three on both I will
probably need a little bit of uh exp but
I think I think with the sacrifice of a
couple of
members we have we do have a monster
farm
so but if not I think I was going to go
get the string cuz I have a lot of
sticks so get the
string
from
Kyla
[Music]
kamies pleas
is this Con you can't read my
writing I mean I could use my real
writing I'm just writing with the mouse
cuz I was
lazy
okay I I'll show you guys the difference
between my lazy Mouse writing and my
actual
writing
okay um number
two is to
um
prepare
or the
nether which requires
a have enough
[Music]
food this is my tablet
um
prepare
extra
gear like
Shield maybe
[Music]
weapons
Etc um
intent
gear if
[Music]
possible
um yeah wait I already I think I gave
the gold helmet to Ana but I have gold
so oh yeah prepare extra gear um also
need to
make
golden
helmet
again um and
then
then what else do I need for the
nether bring beds I'm not bringing beds
to the nether that's asking for disaster
[Music]
potions I don't I don't think we have
nether W
yet
so
the bring
kind come
[Laughter]
me anti fire
oh yeah building
blocks food and hold on food
and building I mean we're going to
probably get more building
blocks I don't think we're going to aim
for netherite here but you know um yeah
[Music]
um
um that's that's pretty good I think for
preparing for the
nether the number three
if there is
[Music]
time
PE
inde is there um villagers where I can
trade for Diamond gear I wonder here CU
I know I can probably maybe Farm some
emeralds too if I need Enchanted
here treating Hall is done okay so maybe
you'll do that
too all right so that is today's plan
[Music]
and finished
it all
right I think I think I'm
prepared oh Kara is starting today isn't
she see her all
night okay
[Music]
all
right oh that's
uh okay that's good I I had like a th000
ping to the server it was kind of scared
all right I'm locking in
guys
oh she doesn't know I'm here
is she doing her news right
now oh she's reading
journals oh no maybe I don't know if I
should peek at her
stream h
should I scare
[Music]
her foree
[Laughter]
something
everything okay everything
[Music]
okay pick ack
yesterday Pik Pik
St
you
[Music]
yeah watch out watch out
okay
[Music]
byebye
hi
wow what's up wait oh I guess you got
you got the pick a pick a stone gear
from from
Ollie uh yeah I got it from Ollie yeah
oh my God my connection is so bad or is
it like what do you hear me like a robot
no oh no okay you have a BT just me then
oh I don't have it right now
oh oh well get maybe my bed okay run car
run
okay yeah B uh
coyote also sounded a little bit like a
robot to me a moment ago yeah my bed is
in Ollie's house
okay ah there's a bed
here no it should really it should go
for the night now right yeah
okay yay I'm going to check the missions
and stuff I think it's going to be
updated after is is it updated already
I'm not sure I guess we'll see
oh
waed all
right oh I think I think it's updated
okay glow stone
or close get close oh I guess it's
another focused one
today
no it's s sand die
three defeat a ghast die of five I feel
like we can do the ghast one if we have
our bow I
think um
rebounding the what call Fireball is a
little hard with the
Ping another is worth it I think for the
for the
potions skeleton
oh okay defeat three skeletons that's
doable
too
por I know the meaning but I can't read
it n
s
s ah I guess the first thing is
Sak nether
fortress let's see 30 for the nether
fortress I don't think I'm very good at
finding things I mean just think about
how long it took for me to
find in
lra seven diamonds
[Music]
okay how about how about I
um write down the missions I can do
today okay there
is
get no get Soul
Sand defeat Three
Skeleton defeat one
gas
um get glow
stone wait if I need glowstone I
need does she mean like um like the
entire actual glowstone block or glow
stone like powder fine I probably need
silk touch
then I can craft one from the
shards oh okay
okay cuz I feel like getting self touch
might be hard unless Kyla already meets
some okay nether get
nether but doesn't NE what require me to
go into the Fortress or is it just
around feel like I feel like I found it
in a fortress last
time find another
Fortress uh
kind I think
it's it's probably
go get frog with someone you haven't met
before oh yeah make a potion I'm I'm a
potion
Master make
potion oh one silk touch for one Emerald
o oh you guys like my keyboard I forgot
what
the what the switches are they aren't
the with sterio ones they're different
this is my this is my most
expensive
keyboard but I forgot what switch to the
CBO okay I think that's pretty good
that's pretty good
[Music]
all right what should we start with
finish our bows where is Kyla's place
anyways
[Music]
oh
no what do you do uh
finish my
bow it's not it's not y y y
y oh I was right y I said
y b you me you uh you want to you
mean I have I have
Yumi but it's it's almost broken I have
to
now yeah wor thank you
you you you you oh oh oh
you
[Music]
no okay byebye byee
it was not
true why you so careful why you so
careful
W yeah what happened it was not
true it was not
what what what Happ why are you so
depressed No No I gave her a chew and
she didn't chew you back no no I thought
I thought she said chew so I was like
chew but then she was like oh not chew
me chew I was like
oh me too oh oh oh it's okay you can
have my tow I got the
tow did you build the house
yet uh I just like took one of the
broken villagers houses oh you
too yeah yeah you want to see my
house I I already saw it in your stream
but yeah
okay I saw you made some additions nice
improv pretend you didn't see it yet
this is my green corn dog you might have
remembered from the uh Ian server back
in the day green corn hog green do corn
dog corn dog oh corn dog M yummy yeah
and this is my
house's house yeah I got blown up by a
creeper yesterday I fixed
it oh if I ever need like some dirt or
some Cobble deep slate can I take it
from you yeah yeah of course of
course oh you have some broken bows did
you go fishing or what yeah I
did a I have a pretty good fishing
fishing rod so um that's my goal to fix
it today to bring it to the nether what
what do you think I should do like I I
finished my house and I made uh some
weapons I have weapons and I have armor
and yeah I mean I think oh are you are
you going to plan to go to the nether
today I guess so yeah CU most of the
missions today are for the nether yeah
so I think if you want to go for the go
for the missions then you should just
prepare for the nether cuz it's opening
like in a bit right or hopefully in a
bit so I guess oh and arrows would be
nice yeah and I have I I have the list
for today it's like prepare enough food
prepare extra gear like Shield weapons
and then bring enough building blocks
enchant gear if
possible um and then bring block would
be and then last thing very important
bring
Kyla yeah should we just stay with KY
maybe that's my
plan yeah I'll get some food then and I
try to get arrows in a bow maybe yeah
okay bye-bye bye-bye don't I need a
string though well wait can you can I
take one of the broken bows um I think
there's only uh cuz I'm going to be
merging two of them and then keeping one
as like a backup bow but Kyla definitely
has um string too so she has like a
spider fall apparently okay sleep first
we can talk again okay
okay the most important thing bring
Kyla never forget my God my goddess and
she will not forget
me all right I mean if we had enough
time I would have tried to fish another
bow
for another B for uh Kiara but I don't
think we have
time
okay okay let me
just the goddess has been summoned oh
let me just
uh do this always good to you
know build the bucket
[Music]
I forgot how
much
um oh should I also go cuz I need
[Music]
stream also waiting to be picked up imag
the the the music that you hear with
like missions oh hell's up I'm also so
wanting to be picked up by
Kyla oh well I don't know if there's
more than one space in her boat if she
comes with a boat I don't think she's on
the
boat I have a feeling she's
coming I can
swim oh well well we could let's see how
she arrives do you think she oh I was
going to say she might already have
wings but we didn't go to oh yeah I mean
she she might at the end of all
this yeah
oh
KY KLA what do you want from from KY uh
some string
too
ah we want the same thing it seems yeah
I'm sure she has a lot but I want an an
already finished bow because I have
nothing to work with right now I have uh
yeah I just wanted to make bow so I can
repair my
bows yeah
are you going to play for long today
what do you feel it's like are you not
tired are you okay I'm exhausted but I
think at least 3 hours hopefully around
there okay okay at least want to you
know drop by the
nether yeah yeah yeah we should kill a
gas
together oh yeah we
can but do do we get each one of us gets
those diamonds or do they get split then
if we kill it together that's true I
mean we can kill two
then yeah yeah just somebody I guess we
just need the achievement to kill one
maybe and then each one of us needs the
last hit I don't know if if they look at
the I don't think it's the last hit but
yeah okay we just kill two yeah minimum
two we need to free the ne of the gests
but there does you know their
voices it's like yeah it's like one of
the developers cats voices or something
like that oh yeah yeah I know I heard
that yeah Ena with the random knowledge
I already know that
one oh I should replace the gas's uh
voices with my own cats voices wouldn't
that be cute that be cool that be
[Music]
cute doio doio I'm so lost right now
it's okay steady steady
steps okay steady do you have do you
know if there's a way to like extend the
rad ra ra radius Rad do you say that in
English the the distance of when you can
hear uh people I think that's server
side so oh okay okay yeah it's the it's
the that's radi us
okay
radius oh did you know there's
apparently there's a a court meeting did
you ever uh Join one yet I don't think I
think they haven't done a one yet
because no one really died until
now I think yesterday they did one for
Rica though oh
Kyla hello hello hello Ka H we created
the goddess of Minecraft
oh hello hi I Ka I just joined today and
I was hoping you could maybe be so sweet
to maybe if you have one if you can give
me a bow and maybe some
arrows oh um wait um it doesn't have to
be enchanted yeah I think we can craft
it like my home okay I'll follow you
okay and youa needs a string I think
just a string not just I just need to
make some bows yeah but the strings
would be great bow is what wait um
feather oh I I have arrows right I just
need the strings cuz I don't want to
farm
spiders how long have you been
streaming I'm not streaming right now oh
not long I'm I'm not streaming how long
have you been
awake
I yeah you that's not a question you
asked the goddess of Minecraft
I mean I I mean I slept a lot in
Minecraft
though when I was eating dinner last
night I saw you you you were streaming
already for like 7 hours and now I see
you when I wake up and I'm like confused
oh yeah i' I've been doing um 12 hours
back to back oh my God I don't know how
but yeah I mean I'm still playing even
though I'm not streaming so oh
she Che
this is her life she takes it very
seriously the no log out rule she takes
it very
seriously only sleep in
Minecraft in a bed don't Lo
[Music]
on
a
kylo you're so fast oh I guess I got to
jump yeah you got to jump is that is
that your house no that's the village my
house is just no my my house is just
dirt house oh okay oh we got to be
efficient oh well you know said she
would swi it's okay uh it's okay I I can
have my own oh let's go wait
okay let's go why does this
happen oh
we're trying to do right now in a senpai
what are you trying to do right now I'm
trying to fix some bows that I fished up
they're pretty good bows and then and
then prepare some enchantment gear and
stuff for the
nether ah I have my own trading Hall
just in case if you need like um yeah I
heard you had like Unbreaking three and
stuffff yeah yeah so if you need like
books
maybe we need to walk a
bit okay Kyla do you hear Ena like
completely normally or is she a little
bit robotic to you oh completely normal
though oh okay Ena say something again
hello hello oh
okay you're still robotic to me but KY
is normal to me weird I can talk robotic
you
like would you like me to more you doing
on purpose you see that one you see that
one the the dirt the dirt s dirt with
the tree yeah that's my house
ah oh don't ask me if I live like
yes I live like
[Music]
that this is
fine
fine pumpkins let's go I have
pumpkin but pumpkin as a food item is
like annoying cuz it needs to be pumpkin
soup in a bowl right
yeah objective Alpha full
[Music]
finished horns Fortune mending Ming
let's go looting Unbreaking FEA falling
sharpness flame s touch you have silk
touch let's go wow oh my God I think I P
needs I don't know if she got it already
but like she was saying she need silk
touch a while
ago
wow Sharp
[Music]
Unbreaking but that's for the for the
for the wings eventually mening okay
sick nice Kyla nice freaking
nice forun I think for your bow is
infinity is better for for fighting the
Ender Dragon later on yeah yeah possibly
guess I need to go get some emeralds too
oh actually yeah Infinity would be
amazing I I would love some
Infinity do you have um Iron Ingot with
you right now I have uh this all of this
guys for all of this guy is for um
Emerald trading oh I guess we need to
sleep first wait I'm so scared wait I'm
so scared I don't want to like be killed
by we can sleep here or if you have have
another bed maybe okay
yeah
sleep I can't sleep next to the Iron
Golems so scared me please help my it's
okay don't want to kill me don't hit the
Golem don't hit the
Golem don't hit the Golem don't touch
the
Golem many traumatic
experiences don't hit anything yeah
good
morning
okay okay uh wait so are they going to
come up the no just going trade yeah
trade from up here it's fine okay I'm so
scared okay sorry
sorry what a
de are 11 emeralds enough to buy you
want to buy what what what Infinity unre
Su a okay I guess I can
go
uh and going get some
iron
a
a a thank you all right remember where
her
house remember where her house is
yes okay okay no just just to come back
to get get all the stuff I just need to
get my
emeralds I mean okay since since you
have uh since you have a lava farm right
uh maybe if you pass by here or I I need
the lava bucket for my here okay of
course maybe you can you you can drop
you can just drop it in this one or this
one okay I I'll bring some
over he thank you
okay I'll be
back wait um do you want do you do you
need
[Music]
like oh wait I could use a I could use a
boat where'd he go where'd he go wasn't
there a villager in here I I I just
killed it when you called me what but no
evidence no evidence it's okay my what
vill the torns vager because because I
found the cheaper one oh a okay what
villager Kara I don't see any
villagers nothing happened B and one
Arrow okay uh so bow right
uh all
right maybe I'll just quickly make a
boat I mean having a boat is nice in
general
so yeah the strings I mean I'm going to
be back
anyways I guess I should ask her where
to get the string huh I didn't oh I do
have an ax okay
okay I think they're making the nether
gate at 7
[Music]
TS and
then need to organize my inventory
honestly and
boat I want to I want a pink
boat I want a pink
boat be
nice okay I have a boat
now about 6 minutes I guess I can go
back and then gather some iron and then
come
back or go to the trial and then come
back
am I going the wrong
way I'm going the wrong way
yeah I have to go to the
[Music]
Village not surprised if you're lost
don't worry it's my specialty
ooh this
beats
a is this home Lord
I follow the
Torches
[Music]
a ah there's that
Village that's a lot of vetes here where
am
I is this the Mountain
[Music]
Village it's the Mountain Village I
should know how to get home from
here
a yeah I think that's the mountain okay
this way
hello
cow I could use some
[Music]
leather
steak steak
stick
stick oh good we're
good real
good oh it's almost time for the
trial to grab some iron
oh is this the treating the other
treating one I think
so I didn't see who that wasit
oh all right we got
to got oh wait iron
iron iron this way and then we can stop
by the
uh by the uh
Courthouse I want I want I want I want I
want i i i
i i w i i i w
[Music]
and lava
right only 12
oh re ironed
arms I think they're all
taken I mean we can come back in a while
[Music]
I mean it's almost time for the trials
maybe we'll head over first I don't know
if they're having trouble with
the servers or
something
[Music]
o potion
hello hello hello
hello i i a
y where where
thank
[Music]
Youk no
problem no
problem
[Music]
fore
spee
[Music]
spee fore
[Applause]
[Music]
hi she getting a
[Laughter]
[Music]
lawyer
for I think they want two
first one is second one
is trying to finish it within 10 minutes
each starting in a
[Music]
minute
fore foree
[Music]
from of water around the fence in the
place Revival trial
[Music]
started anamation from
to get
[Music]
oh so she made an automatic
fishing she didn't really know how to
use
it she got
stuck no water block
that's why that's how she
[Music]
and then I think I think it ended up
looking
[Music]
like was looking a little
suspicious
[Music]
for tried to save
her did you did you feel any while doing
it said wasun
[Music]
like I would like her to be reviv she's
a
lawyer moving as a
team
[Music]
for
fore
speech for
[Laughter]
[Music]
fore
foree fore
[Music]
[Laughter]
speech
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah
I should I should have
brought just hold it in my hands to
remind
[Music]
her for
[Laughter]
was like we not really
actually
Witnesses all of a sudden before they
knew
it and then all a sudden they see
the they're like oh
she's
[Music]
dead it would have been fine if you kep
pressing
sh for
[Music]
is there is there anyone who has
gotten you
[Music]
[Laughter]
know was everyone
[Music]
[Applause]
she didn't threaten me she gave me gave
it to me as a k fug is my friend
[Music]
say
acting like the Jud
[Music]
to
represent for
[Music]
for for
know she's too powerful
to imagine if imagine if an SEO they
tell a tri and was like you're
guil
[Music]
[Laughter]
for I think I think it's not not guilty
but there must be a punish
[Music]
[Laughter]
spe
[Applause]
[Music]
my
for
[Music]
[Laughter]
for
for okay back to regularly scheduled
program I did not forget my object
objectives surely by now there will be
more iron surely
surely I mean I just want at least one
Unbreaking for my it's
open
seven
mean that's not that many I don't know
how many I had at
[Music]
home someone must have taken
it it's so popular maybe I should have
just camped uh off stream or
something it's okay all right get some
lava buckets deliver to Kyla she grabbed
some food too actually I think I'm
running
out I just grab some potatoes from the
[Music]
Flor can treat paper is there oh I guess
there's another villager farm I guess I
can make some paper I have plenty of
sugar sugar cane
[Music]
thing take some free food
I checked the oh youa hi H do you need
the string I have a string for you I go
oh never mind it actually took three
strings to make one bow yeah I need I
need but then yeah just go back to KY
place and yeah I was going to go back
anyways because of the okay yeah okay I
need to get one feather
we
just don't look back don't look back you
did not hear that chat don't look
back okay look got
some okay I got paper got one I'll put
my diamond in here here put some
iron guess I spend all my iron
huh okay
paper I guess I had cook the
C okay
all
right I guess I did use a lot of iron
blocks to make the uh make the
bucket okay I'll bring that to
her I'll get a bunch of f
[Music]
good thing I planted all
these okay
and
then
paper okay that should be enough paper
for emeralds right I hope so
[Music]
okay you
I guess they're starting on the
[Music]
game on
okay there so far away
okay there's no paper one
[Music]
enough you know what let's go get more
more of
these there's plenty of those
a I think 11 was
enough let's borrow some
uh borrow some
paper
here m m
oh they're going
[Music]
already okay I think there's a whole
bunch more in the actual Village
so me go back and get some
not
[Music]
birthday it's okay guys we're going for
the steady safe gamer route oh look at
all the sugar
cane look at all that pu
here ch
[Music]
happy birthday have you good
one hope you know it's going to
be it's going to be a fun way
all right I think I saw more on the
other side oh I dropped
some I should have gr some
potatoes potatoes are nice
these ones are all
taken oh that was the r around my
house just want to cross the
waters puppy
[Music]
oh my inventory is
full okay
is it me or is this bridge a little
narrower than before was it always just
one I don't
[Music]
remember yes all he just hasn't
beautified it yet
okay wow there's a lot of people
on
[Music]
go
okay now let's just go to Kyla's place
this time she has a paper trador
right not a perpetrator but a paper
[Laughter]
trator not a perpetrator or a paper
trailor but a paper
trailor paper paper paper trator
perpetrator paper trator paper trator
perpetrator purple purple paper
treat did I mark down the coordinates
for K's place I did
feel like I can get there
without without
[Music]
uh oh
nice that was almost well
That Could Have Ended
badly I can take the boat from here
she went around this right I think
[Music]
so what a deal
oh these ones are in the W I can just
take
it huh see I remember
oh she has left the
game she has a little more that need
don't Hello grass cutting cutting
[Music]
service lawn Mo service
on Mo
[Music]
service wait I should I should make some
ready oh I should put the fuel in
first non Mo service
my my these grow
fast okay surely that's enough
okay I'm
string
a wait do she have a paper trainer
these ones are all
Iron
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
ah well give me that
Emerald okay they're all
[Applause]
[Music]
oh I got 22
so I need
[Applause]
Unbreaking oh I need to make a
[Music]
book
I I didn't think about that it's okay
these grow fast
free book and chest oh okay it's okay
I'm just cutting
grass ah okay thank you thank you
okay Unbreaking
okay mending Infinity
[Music]
Fortune
protection a I already have an Infinity
but I just have
to what I
see f
feather fall
boots actually since we can't get
Phantoms we should definitely get
feather
falling wait 19
[Music]
19 just brought some bone meal maybe I
can oh it's kind of far I should have
brought some bone meal and just you
know time
forward
these things
[Music]
I need eight more diamonds right or
emeralds
rather where where is her string
[Music]
at home
underground I guess I don't know if
she's coming
back inside the house
[Music]
underground I wonder if she has
someone in the chest there is some B
[Music]
I can just
take she
[Music]
a she's the goddess
it's a motivational poster oh
[Music]
well I guess I'll see what's
downstairs this way
[Music]
oh I hear
spider zombie exp f
[Music]
it's
scary to the right
[Music]
Min is
X yeah
[Music]
ah under construction
surely this is safe
right is it up
here so dark
[Music]
the spiders will get stuck if I stand
Here a
[Music]
it's dark
this is someone's nightmare right here
[Music]
it's so
dark how how many bows do you think I'll
need
hi
cool this should be enough right I can
make three bows with
this might so go for four now that I'm
here
[Music]
hello
hello ah there's so many of them the
nightmare okay that should be enough
her tunnels are scary
[Music]
to be safe without the
streakers it's still scary I never
fought the Wen before
especially since we're in hardcore
[Music]
I mean ideally have like 10 more levels
for like 130
level um enchant on something
yeah I can go to TT later but we got to
we got to get the
[Music]
um get our goals done
first think you kind of
come really by now a lot of the uh sugar
cane group
but we got
one we got
two hello hello
good
luck me
too byebye
bye-bye okay
freshly cut grass freshly cut grass
[Music]
here 18 that's not enough for even one
diamond
what was I going to
get feather falling
right I mean it's not the priority so I
can
probably the server is a little laggy
right
now probably make the bunny feather for
bow I
forget oh oh I don't
okay
two three okay let's go home first for
[Music]
now and then if I go home oh it's almost
night I go home I think the sugar canes
around my house should also be grown
so I came from that way didn't
I sleep
sleep I'm pretty sure a lot of the JP
members
probably took the uh iron already
they're being covered with diamonds
but we'll see we can drop
[Music]
by I should have known what what bow was
called in
Japanese cuz of
[Music]
that's why
anime teaches you random
words you wouldn't know otherwise
[Music]
come na
na ooh free fishing rods oh it's just a
boat
[Music]
16 I'll take
it
take the bone I do have some
bones
in my
house what was I doing um Bowl paper I
was going to go home anyways for the
sugar can
[Music]
foreign speech
speech spee
[Music]
skeleton
what
[Music]
where oh I see the another
key there's a cave below
[Music]
okay I'm
home ah see you're pretty much all grow
oh perfect
calculated I heard some drop into the
water
okay
okay that's should be enough I should
have brought some buckets back huh
bones and
[Music]
then that's a good
area can not do it for for sugar cane
no I didn't want
flowers no my
plan my grand
[Music]
plan
okay yeah I mean that should give us
some I feel
like all right let's fix the bows
[Music]
cannot be okay
all
right now how am I going to do
[Music]
this Infinity power these two right
like
this was it the other way
around oh they the
same okay
what do I call
you
canot it cost 15
now I don't know how much the the book
enchanting is going to cost
I guess okay we do this wait can I put
Unbreaking on this can I have five
things yes
okay okay see this costs
four and I have to I have to
oh do I name
it
[Music]
SP what happens if I do this that's
three
[Music]
book and then B oh it doesn't work like
that but I don't know how much with this
bat and then this boat would cost that's
the
thing I feel like bow plus bow is more
expensive
okay the book
first
five but then it fixes it holy
[Music]
so they have to
fish yeah but walking there takes like a
couple minutes so might as well just you
know stay here why not
it was one of our goals today
[Music]
anyways oh yeah I can put the men wait
but then I
can't get the experience points I need I
can do that
afterwards after I get level five
oh I got to sleep
I wish there was a way to not see the
text just to see how many people
are popup text
[Music]
can I reduce the size of chat it looks
like nine okay we got
everything oh the lag the lag in the
nether might be a bit of a problem I
mean I'm not going to be bouncing back
the Fireballs the the gas but
still very scary
[Applause]
stuff oh you know what I could have done
I could have been cooking at the same
time to get that XP I'm a genius
[Music]
except my inventory is not so
Genie okay I need I only need two
anyway can I take the buckets I can't
I'm a
genius see fishing is the most ideal
peaceful way to get
[Music]
XP getting an upgrade
it's getting a good
progress fing for the
soul and who knows maybe I'll just get
another sick book out of this fish
so much
F book with feather falling so I can buy
a different
enchantment feather falling
protection um am I being too ambitious
here oh sad
Unbreaking nice
cat oh wait if I do that
[Music]
okay oh we should get I think I think
Lami made a whole bunch of torches
should take a
step well M
[Music]
me ah such peaceful
time we're almost at five
yeah I need to make an arrow too oh
another
Shadow two
saddle that's what life is all about
[Music]
then by the time I get back more sugar
can would have
gr
see calculations
now that I have the bow I don't think
I'm that
scared unless I get like surprised by a
creeper oh what's that ooh another shell
wait that should be enough for a conduit
if I
get if I get harder to see
oh that
lag call you it is eight well we got
five more to go
guys another fishing
rod lure mending Unbreaking
no I mean
lure L
to I can combine
them probably cost quite a
bit but it would make my exp plan a
little better
okay
[Music]
that cooks really fast okay level six
let's just see how
much I think my
anvils kind
of what's this cost
19 okay we save that for later
then we need to finish our Bowl
[Music]
First St
we did it I guess we need a
arrow feather
flint and
stick I think we have feather
somewhere okay
Flint you don't have
Flint guess we can stop by the Mountain
huh
um should I fix The Mending
bow yeah gravel mountain is not too far
away let me just um
Harvest some more
paper brass cutting
cut all good
[Music]
okay that should be enough for feather
falling I
hope K has arrows that is true
too actually let's go grab some from
there cuz I need to know where it is too
[Music]
um I mean it would have been ideal to
have some enchantments on my weapons
before I go feel like that'll take a
while I need Flint so
guess I guess I could get flint real
quick and
then make an arrow that's probably
faster I'll go to TT after
[Music]
oh more sugar cane
perfect calculate do I have shovel I do
[Music]
okay what
ooh a
horse that was charcoal not
Flint only Flint I had I threw away cuz
I was running out of space Oh someone
built a base here
wonder
who there's no
sign what's by house
well the grass cutting
service is for
everyone leave no grass
[Music]
uncut okay
[Applause]
I'm kind of scared of the
lag I just need one PL
[Applause]
ah there we go okay back home oh another
one yeah we can't sleep next night cuz
they I think pora
wanted uh
skeletons maybe for B meal I don't know
[Music]
fish yeah it was ly I'm pretty sure it
was ly I could tell
maybe I could I could feel
it what a
deal okay surely that will be quite
enough what was that doing oh yeah
Arrow I just need
one
and do I really not have any sticks
lying around I guess
not nice
okay I am content
yeah what do I need for item
frame 1 2 3 4 5 6
78 one
more I did want to bring fuga with me on
the journey but feel like we're not
going to have enough space
where are
you guard my house while I'm
gone and if I
die tell my family I love them
okay I should probably
[Music]
leave this B here I don't know should I
leave
it I could fix it but I don't even have
enough arrows to use it right now
anyways
okay where's the equipment I think this
is the equipment chest
[Music]
plint bring the cooked PO with me extra
food always
good paper I don't need the water
bot I don't need the
flour I have some iron tree too so
should be
good wait did I put both bowls
in am I blind oh I
did okay
yeah I should grab more torches while
I'm going I'm on the
way the Torches are this
way this
way hello
[Music]
thank you uh
don't no no no no no
[Laughter]
no I got to frame this too
okay I'll sa framing this for
later we got emeralds to get
[Music]
potato and P
I I just switch these
[Music]
two drop by the iron farm just in case
more grass com services
oh I think we're staying up this this
tonight though
so oh
[Music]
nice yes yes
nice okay that should be a
couple we need to find the safe
space
Oh my
potato think we're staying up I mean I
could test my bow actually
[Music]
this area is relatively safe I think the
only thing that could get us is a
creeper
so although I don't want a creeper to
randomly blow up near here that's the
question let
see that's a
thing 18 and one
short oh yeah the grass cutting service
going to look out for creepers
[Music]
guys always be scanning for the green
monster of
Doom for it could be the end of all
[Music]
event
is this
the
[Music]
10 the
leg
H okay 19 that's should be
enough open
chest rain will happen nearby goes out a
trade wait that's right here isn't it
okay that's in 30 minutes
[Music]
though okay let's just be cutting grass
while we wait
I'm sure someone will be here to cover
the villagers
[Music]
right
right oh
oops or we're going to have a shooting
battle
[Music]
okay
okay pap
[Music]
I guess I can take the
iron
you they
asleep you're okay you're okay
okay it's a long night time
[Music]
oh okay plan in the
morning is to go the traing
place get feather
falling trade more iron see if there's
anything I can
buy
uh oh we're sleeping okay I can start oh
no
not
sleeping we have to go to the nether
today for for the Quest for more Diamond
although I'm not sure what I would use
the diamond for
exactly but you
know since we have villagers now
hello drown bye
drown I have gold at home so I'll make
the gold stuff
[Music]
was it this
one think we went around this way
[Music]
some almost
here seems like the grass grew while I
was away
I must fix
that h
h Huh
huh huh
[Music]
[Applause]
h Huh
huh okay
then uh feather falling
[Applause]
my
BS
okay
nice
a a
h Huh huh
huh
[Applause]
h i can get one more thing probably
protection 15 I need two
more oh it would be nice to get mending
on my pickaxe
actually think there's free mending here
right
[Music]
yeah
a thank goodness there was
another
Unbreaking oh yeah for my for my thing
brick I need
another I think it'll be very useful for
the
nether wait is my house okay
do I go back
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
spe
[Music]
I think I think I'm
good what was I
doing frame The
Relic no it's my lucky it's my lucky
charm I'm carrying it with
me okay um all right I got sword I got
the bow I got the good
pickaxe um I think if I get
food make golden helmet make golden
helmet I should check my house I have to
go back home
anyways okay
it's my lucky charm
now I just Enchanted my boots though so
I don't want to switch
it that would be not that wise chat
[Music]
I don't need like the best gear I think
like I'm not going there to farm a lot
or anything
I'm just trying to get
today's uh quests done
rather the nether is open now I can go
back
[Music]
anytime so
may we will grab some
[Music]
food food golden helmet building
blocks I think there was one free Shield
by the iron farm so
[Music]
mmy
Wy okay I do like potatoes I'll bring
some
potatoes thank
you someone someone took my
salmon okay
someone ate my cooked salmon I hope I
seasoned it
[Music]
right okay
okay all right we grab more of those
I should have farmed more paper while I
had the
chance
okay what are we clapping
about okay and
then Emerald golden helmet
[Music]
should we go to the
Rain maybe there will be some rewards if
I go to the
[Music]
rain for EXP
tokens of undying oh that's
true but then I won't be able to use my
shield
[Music]
totem for exploring that's
true that is
true I mean we still got like 13ish
minutes
the
[Music]
rain all
right I mean we might as well help save
the uh save the traing post
[Music]
you
know oh yeah we need to bring some milk
just in case you
know yeah there is a bit of lag I'm kind
of scared for the nether
[Music]
are you fishing for something not
specifically I just wanted to max out my
pickax real
[Music]
quick no I could totally use just use
this as a Cod
storage oh you know I should make a
diamond shovel but before that I think
I'm going to quickly go grab some
drinks
and um idle meeting before the raid
so I'll be right back
guys I'll be right back
[Music]
okay I'm back I made some
food
okay you know I I should make a diamond
shovel and a
diamond uh
what's call it
axe
that's that's what I was
planning
I okay
all right
um run
Shield building
block
okay the
fors see chat
okay I'm on the
way I have no time to
eat I got less than a minute
let's just build like a
fortress in the
river a watchtower and just shoot from
[Music]
there where is it
at 9
or
12 okay this way
right ah over
here only one
Diamond do I make a do I make a post in
the river
guys I'm an Archer
[Music]
class thank
you oh the
boats
oh they're preparing
this is not what I planned
[Music]
I should
have thought a little harder about
this can I make
fences I didn't bring
wood you have
crossbows I that was
cross it's a
zombie it's a zombie
it's a
[Music]
zombie it's a zombie if I if I destroy
one of this blocks what what's going to
happen
nothing nothing really it's
Minecraft really
yeah seriously yeah
wait hold
on oh yeah
happened Minecraft logic Minecraft logic
are you ready for the raid oh oh oh it's
it's stting it's starting it's starting
it's starting it's
stting I should have put water beneath
me I mean I could
[Music]
they're
approaching oh the
lag I hit it
though
nice we won with the
[Music]
leg where's the last one
oh I'm over
[Music]
there it's kind of far I can't see
oh they're making Iron Golems oh that's
smart oh I didn't mean to do that
[Music]
hi what I I don't know like is is it
impossible to do this without a bow cuz
like no you can find I understand
nothing oh yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah use your
Shield use Shield I attack
I want to attack you have you have an
axe or SW the enemy I'm I'm going to be
honest I don't I don't even know which
one is the enemy you have green
faces green faces gray gray faces oh
gray gray faces they have like they
don't look nice oh they don't look nice
gu oh
okay okay okay I think it's on is it on
that side
yeah it's on that
side yeah it's okay I'm on the south
post
okay
sleeping I guess monsters
huh Can you sleep during a raid I don't
think so
right they're
approaching with the leg there's a witch
oh the
leg they're right beneath
[Music]
me nice did I did I drop something
up
there
oh I should doing
nothing oh I see them
now oh the
leg be one with the lag why know trying
to comp say for the
[Music]
lag barely
hit I love doing nothing I love doing
nothing Your Existence is is enough
you're like one of the targets who could
pull so oh are you telling me that I
need to be baited W oh my
sorry okay okay come
[Music]
on
no no
[Music]
we
won
nice okay one of
these I guess I can sh
[Music]
water okay this is the safe
one wait this means it's it's cheaper to
trade oh that's what the event was no I
want it to lend hit to
I was I I I was useless but that's fine
it's okay we you not get the achievement
on you no I a hit at the
boss do you can get stuff for cheaper at
the trade I think let's
go no I want to I mean you can probably
ask some of us to get stuff Anya oh
that's that's true but I I don't know I
don't know what to get though
that's true okay I can kind of eat
now I know what to
get
[Music]
no oh oh
oh okay good inoc thank
you okay innoc
[Music]
[Laughter]
for
[Music]
foree
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
fore I'll never never forget
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
you it's basically that oh my God
someone someone needs to draw that now
someone needs to draw that with us
oh there's some grass to be
cut it was like yesterday that I I said
hi to her in her
Farm was just like yesterday
wait does this buff also work at Kyla's
place or is it just here I
wonder I still remember when she gave
us a
potato it's all Traders okay so we can
go trade
um and
[Music]
then oh without there might be events
like this without notification next time
I what to say
yeah it's a random
event oh it's going to be
[Music]
scary let's go back home to get some
more yeah grab my D our emeralds cuz I
think I think we should be able to buy
[Music]
I think we should be able to get we
protection for our
here I think protection on our what our
our
um whatchacallit
armor is pretty
important at least she died a hero I'm
sure if she has a retry or a trial
everyone would agree she should be back
the food she provided for
us the the kindness the heroic actions
we won't forget
it never forget
potato wait hold on
everyone who has given me a
gift so far has
died it's only Equivalent Exchange that
prevents their
death yes
[Music]
no it's just a coincidence
right it's just a
coincidence it's just a
CO there is no
way think we have like 30 minutes on the
buff so we'll get as
much pupper as
possible cutting your
grass I cut the grass too hard
[Music]
okay like a micro no I'm not a microwave
I'm a larm more
[Music]
beep
beep wait a minute something's not right
the nuggies are
ready
o I should save one bucket
for uh milk though I'll carry one around
okay okay that should be a lot of paper
we should we should be able to get more
than one I feel like
more book that's what I'm
seeing I wonder if there's still books
left over
[Music]
[Applause]
cutting the grass
here
[Music]
okay maybe make some friend
oh exactly eight bre nice
[Music]
okay actually it's is night time let
stay here I'm going to eat some eat some
actual
food for my UD go Ste or not
steal h
m
look
up what the traing post
the
elite did I bring the paper I brought
the paper I brought the
paper okay and then I feel like a lot of
them went to the nether already so maybe
some of the quests are already finished
we'll see I can still ride it down
right so many people hello hello hello
hello hello hello
hello oh that's selling oh
let's just go to the let's go to
ky's
[Music]
place I just go around saying hello
hello hello hello
hello hello
[Music]
hello hold the
leg okay hello hello
hello
[Music]
hello hello hello hello goodbye hello
hell hello hello
goodbye
America is that a
meum I I've been living under a rock I
don't know the new memes the new hip
memes I have a pass no just me oh I lost
my way okay
it's think it's this
so hello hello hello
hello hello hello
hello oh it's a AA CL
okay hello
hello that reminds me I think like I
feel feel
like some of the I think I was talking
to some of the staff they didn't really
understand some of
the seven oh I can get a lot
[Music]
more 18
okay I got
20 flame silk touch
protection
20 what about
11 I could get two protection books
possi Fortune is worth it it's survival
or Fortune first
survival first I mean we can all I mean
but we don't have the buff for too long
eight
emeralds I feel
like survival first probably
[Music]
uh okay
23 I'll get two
oh what about sharpness on my
sword
SC hello
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
getting
naked snacking
[Laughter]
she
nice
for no no no
no
no no no no no reselling
[Music]
just we the gods L I got another book
they keep giving me
books cuz I'm a
[Music]
hero
okay I think that's good can probably go
home
[Music]
villagers will throw items at you at the
hero oh wait should I just stand
[Laughter]
there I just stand there until for 18
minutes
I mean I might as well you know what I
I'll earn back all the all the books I
spent I'm a
[Music]
[Applause]
hero oh thank you thank
you I'm somewhat of a hero
myself oh thank you thank you thank you
thank you you know I I stood upon the
tall
towers
of of
Gan
saved many
villagers
yeah my shots sliced through the enemy
like no
tomorrow no mercy was shown to those
who who
showed uh violence towards my own
villagers you could say that the enemies
had no
tomorrow but Legend will go down in
history
I set
the I set the
uh the enemies a blaze with my
[Applause]
bow no more
books they took all the books
they're sleeping
though wonder if I
should
yeah
oh sent the fireball back
H guess they're not
sleeping I mean we have enough cats here
that we don't have to worry
about oh I didn't mean to Pi that I have
to worry about um creepers
[Music]
excuse me good morning good morning have
you heard the tales of the
hero okay you can sleep
[Music]
she's a support
now she hasn't been brought back yet
I read the Kani I read the Kani
guys yeah I'm a
hero just say at first I didn't want
want to go on this journey of a
hero it is a big responsibility and I
just wanted to chill and
fish but the call of the people brought
me
forward I had no
choice but to answer the call
[Music]
they don't give gift string tonight
oh surely they'll remember it in the
morning right
it's okay you may tell the tale to your
children and your grandchildren and your
grand
grandchildren the tals of Ina Ina
[Music]
the
the the what's my title
[Music]
H not wise not the
brave not the
rock
wa I mean it is true I was alone during
the fight but that was so that if the
enemies turned on me no one would be
sacrificed it's not cuz I didn't have
the courage to communicate or anything
[Music]
is it daytime
yet I kind of want to collect my tax and
go home I mean um gifts and
go oh finally they sleep
[Music]
all
right hello guys have you guys heard
about the taes of
Ena Ina the
um I mean I did make the tower out of
rock yeah yeah I mean I did tell you
guys
overnight not the
brave Ena the Sharpshooter it Ena the
cutter of grass cutter of
P Ena of the Watchtower oh I like the
sound of
that Ena of the
Watchtower I don't think I'm getting
anything out of them they already gave
me like five
books you know what I'll leave you guys
be I'll leave you guys a
peace don't worry you'll be fine
Bo that was rude oh oh no no they just
want my handshake they're like oh Ena
Ena you must be the hero from the
village up
North can I get a hand
[Music]
shake sure surely that's how it is
yeah that's totally what it
was what was the St no I was on the
south side of this North Village you
know wait which way are we
facing we are the heroes of the
South yeah that's right
[Music]
oh do we do
we I mean we still have the
buff oh no one no one sells paper here I
have to go back ah
Longo never
ends
okay um I wonder though I feel like
I feel like I
should I don't think that's enough
for the Looting
sword I mean I do want to at least peek
at the nether today so maybe I should go
another for short bit
today
hi in hi are you going to the nether
yeah in a
bit oh we're going um me Kiara subar
Senpai mik Senpai and alun are going
together would you like join oh yeah
sure yay okay I'll be back I just need
to drop some stuff up at home okay okay
okay let
me okay we got a
party we're going to get our golden
helmet oh yeah I SED some gold huh I
forgot about
this
well well w w w connections
[Music]
I wonder if she heard
that she ask is that
[Music]
you know let's just Harvest all the I
mean sugar canes so next time we're back
we can get more
emeralds got to be
diligent diligent to become
rich the grass cutting business never
ends okay
uh put the paper in
here the goddess is
back the grace this once
[Music]
more okay bring some milk I don't think
there's anything that curses in
the in the nether though
right still need
fish some bread
should I bring I'll bring one stack of
building blocks just in case but I think
we're going to get more
anyways and
then
oh okay so our goal
today Soul Sand
[Music]
skeleton oh I guess I already I'll
defeated one two skeleton
I wonder if it's the one in the nether
probably the one in the nether make a
potion water won't help either that is
true oh I wish I maybe I had powder snow
that' be nice boat is pretty useful oh
yeah my
gold um and the helmet
[Music]
okay
okay this should be good enough I think
I have enough food I have my sword
my equipment my pickaxe my
bow torch is good for like finding our
way back at least I use it as like a way
Mark bed Ki it's my lucky
charm what I need to make a golden
apple oh do I make a golden
apple I guess I can make one just in
case I have a lot of gold for right now
anyways okay one lucky Golden Apple okay
I'll use the golden apple as
a as the lucky
charm were there skeletons of purse
should I bring a bucket with milk I
should I just want to be safe
okay maybe I'll bring two
milk I meant to do
[Music]
this it's
never too late or too bad to be
overprepared
safe players win games that's my
Moto and that's what years
of reading has taught
me save players clear
fight DPS can wait
I forgot to bring
milk oh no everyone's gathered I got to
hurry
my herob buff is
[Music]
disappearing that should be the that
should be the light novel title for me
Ena the overly cautious hero of the
South
[Music]
I got everything Mom I'm ready to
go I like how you can see my face oh
there's a
bed slip
okay I'm on my way after the
sleep oh maybe I should have brought a I
should have brought some gold to
[Music]
trade but they're waiting on me it's
okay we can do that next
time right now the party needs
me don't really want to Sprint cuz I
don't want to waste food but I'm late
I'm running with toast in my mouth
[Music]
I two pumpkin
block why do I have a pumpkin block what
from the
gra oh my goodness what have I from her
Gra
what what have I
done the superior
elk I'm you you need to join us I can't
I have to wear gold armor
wait do you not have gold
armor um set go to settings and skin
customization and then head
off skin then take off take off your
take off your yeah helmet whatever yeah
helmet is that
me take off your
helmet do something
yes yes yes
perfect hello
[Music]
oh so English
only okay okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
for foree
thank you thank
you
Stones yeah yeah I got
some
[Music]
fore fore
let
go it's a big party let's go let's
[Music]
go do we need this
let's go go go into The Nether
[Music]
we
are if you fall and you can just like
run in the boat you don't take
damage
really I'm going to have one just in I'm
going to have one
like
[Music]
whatever spee
let's
for
[Music]
speee sounds
stop
sh's sh's go sh's go
sh's
go thank you
thank dangerous dangerous it's a
telephone game
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my
goodness p
[Laughter]
p
big big hole big
hole let go
let's go sh let's go shift let's
[Laughter]
[Music]
go let's go let
go you know when you just like stand
foree
[Music]
oh
F photo photo Let's Go photo let's go
[Music]
let's
go what do they look like there's a g
um I think they told us to the G that we
for the for the mission oh it's not the
gas it's the Bastion I think right in
front of us it's the Bas G is the flying
ghost looking thing we have to defeat Oh
I thought there was
one there was one on the
way fore
[Music]
I feel like we can get this clh though
no just too
close thank
youa for for entertainment purposes she
should not go
[Music]
[Laughter]
really
scared
sh
sh let's go let's
go p no pushing it's okay
[Music]
nice
for
shiny
for oh
[Music]
this will actually be usefully I
think in case there's
a
BBA H how do we go down afterwards if
this is how
we're um yeah that's good question
that's why they're that's why they're
like getting
blocks
later I got a close Stone out of that
she doesn't have a sub
touch I
got I don't want to take it by
accident Stone
[Music]
for
okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
good fore spee
fore foree
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
fore oh sound is that there's the
garbage truck
hold oh oh oh this place is safe
[Music]
it's so
green is there's something that I
need watch out for
[Music]
you the green
one I see another one behind
[Music]
it for
you good
daddy spe
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
is it safe yeah I don't see
anything it's safe here
did we Skip
One Go
Go
for someone's going to
die die okay
okay right
careful there's a there's a
pig I don't know if I can reach it from
here
[Music]
this path is not good
okay
okay oh thank you thank
you okay okay okay although I'm behind
everybody so it makes no sense oh Ena
okay
good okay okay okay I appreciate the
effort
[Music]
we're getting
lost be able to find a
[Music]
way fore
[Laughter]
she yeah I think I think I think I think
she's trying to go
[Music]
there I'm a cameraman
cameraman hold on this is so
[Music]
you want to go
up hey I don't I don't have
[Music]
bow scanting more for everybody sweet
Ena you got
yours yeah I have two if anyone need it
okay I got one
let's wait for
her there's another one across the magma
too it's a little dangerous there yeah
but I feel like we'll soon we'll soon
have them all
[Music]
anyway moving on
uh
okay let's make this double
[Music]
path
for do we still need
more here
so
we have extra extra
one pick on the bridge pick on
the
[Music]
bridge did it alone so
strong probably wasn't even
[Music]
was it just
one
[Music]
for for
this
[Music]
come up come up come up
mining they're moving on
[Laughter]
[Music]
I think she's going to the anyway
fore
[Music]
foree
speee
[Music]
spee
foree speech
speee for
[Music]
didn't
get I gave her a diamond and she was
happy
to put down
[Music]
[Laughter]
torches okay
okay K's so busy with her exp okay then
I don't feel so
bad cuz if I this group I would
probably
for
[Music]
careful
for GA some blocks
my pinky is so
weak showing so much
[Laughter]
[Music]
spee
for speee
[Music]
she killing mushrooms for like everybody
who's not and all us no no no all of us
all of us
only not for all of us so one person one
person
one one for each
[Music]
person I see
it
[Music]
for for
didn't
[Music]
die are you good
what's the called
[Music]
spe for
are we going back where I came
from okay okay okay okay
[Music]
do that everywhere
[Laughter]
thoughe
[Music]
for gold from that let's
go thank
go go straight to the
[Music]
stop
[Laughter]
[Music]
stop okay
spe
[Music]
speee
[Laughter]
foree spee
[Music]
[Laughter]
revived thank you
[Music]
for
e
foreign spee
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm going to take the mik p
I did have a feeling that we were going
[Music]
backwards oh so fast
oh
this this
[Music]
way thank you thank you
thank
you the
PS oh
careful oh nice what a beautiful path
some of them are lying
up is like
[Applause]
[Music]
speee fore
we found something oh it's um they
reported the Bastion but we we found it
first I think did we have the find the
Fortress or the Bastion Fortress or
Bastion I don't know
[Music]
those were the days is that uh H
achievement
[Music]
where are we
going oh we should have entered it to
get the well we also took a picture
[Music]
I don't think I would have been pressing
shift if I was in her situation
[Music]
died n one single
hole dangerous
[Music]
yeah we should go up up up
we just went the it
[Music]
225 okay okay we make a path towards up
yeah we can okay while she's gone okay
just like from here maybe
careful is this
dangerous uh on the outside might be we
can probably just dig a little up just
have to be careful of like magma Pockets
lava
Pockets yeah your pickaxe stares
me CU it's too good it's strong no
strong it will it'll just pop lava okay
you can go in yeah I mean you're welcome
to dig okay I'm just scared it's just
going to you know go and then get around
pocket indeed well yours is Diamond too
yeah
oh it might be
a
t time oh I hear G I hear
G it's not visible though must be up
there then okay yeah yeah we got to go
up
[Music]
oh I will catch you if you fall down
from the
magma oh it's the forest wait I hear I
think I hear hoglin
or have to be careful of
pig oh what the oh gas attacking
us okay gas
a it's cute should we should we try I
think we should wait we should wait for
them cuz they need to okay
okay GTO you know let's close this off
just in case uh a pig comes around yeah
do you get an achievement for killing a
guest probably
right but do only the person who did the
last hit get
the the kill the achievement is what I
wanted I don't think I can get back to
sender with um with this
pain cuz there achievement I know
there's an achievement you can get for
rebounding the fireball that shoots at
you oh you can despawn yeah it might
leave if we don't kill it
y was it close I mean it saw us right
away
right where is
it oh uh it must be a little Belo
here yeah oh is it gone might be gone
yeah be no G come back Pig oh there's a
big pig
and see me
yet okay small Pig smaller smaller pig
big big pig a little dangerous here damn
it's
gone oh no I hear it
oh o
[Music]
oh it's oh it's there it's below us
basically oh right below us they like
straight over there oh okay BBE
look it's it's around here oh maybe stay
for a
while I see
it I don't know should we should wait
right I mean they should be on their way
right
yeah ah so so B by saying we can do
things
separately like probably because mikoi
can't find
them can I rebound the barble with
[Laughter]
theol
yeah it's chilling
there I didn't even see it I just heard
it
shooting oh we could we could some's
lost there should be a straight path no
well
hello ah oh but some I said uh there's a
gas over at their area too so okay yeah
just defe or do you do we just need a
picture
oh
[Music]
G there's two of them
too lazy to switch to Japanese
keyboard okay let's let's see I asked
her if if we should wait for her or
not there another h
oh I would like that
leather is it is it guy still there I
don't hear him I don't know
[Music]
gone wait maybe over there might have
flown to the other side
yeah she's in a
pinch is she okay
is M
okay
e she was being
ched is she though yeah that's good
question
I don't hear her but she's not dead oh
are you know you okay oh okay I went
back and there wait go up there there's
like two big pigs there's two big
pig I just F they ate you oh no
fine don't die
in don't worry don't worry
on
now Miki said she's on her way but I
don't know if she's on her way to Subaru
s or she's on her way to us there's
another
one where
baby oh no it's not really it's it's
pretty far anyway the baby ones they run
away mid fight so that's kind of
annoying
help
me oh it's is it okay it was that a baby
one no I think a big one oh
guest is back yay oh probably yay we're
so happy to have you back should we just
kill it I don't know if cuz she has her
uh sakuro also says sakur she also has a
g
okay I mean we can just kill this one
then yeah where is it where did it go
now right below
it
oh wait let's kill the pig first before
it uh pushes us
down oh it just ignores
me yeah if it's far
enough okay come back come back we're
ready to fight oh there's another
mushroom
this is kind of scary I thought these
mushrooms were supposed to scare the
Hogs away
oh it's
close there it
is that was one
hit I didn't even shoot
I I'm too
strong like somebody must have already
shot it or was the bow too strong I
don't know doesn't it take more hits
normally I mean I do have a power four
bow oh me
too maybe never one spawns I don't know
if that counts I I mean I don't know if
P Senai really like checks what every
everyone did but yeah feel like I need
to kill you kinded it with
me kind of yeah what do we do now but no
there always one hit G don't have much
HP oh really M should we go back then
yeah we should go back let's try to find
her that was kind of funny we're like ah
we're we're scared and I was like oh it
died in one
[Music]
hke are we oh we I guess we were kind of
up
top but might not be us though do you
think maybe they were hitting the same
gas From Below oh
maybe cuz we keep on going in
circles oh 3
35 I mean wait was
that north towards negative oh that was
nce
right that would be too
crazy oh let's go save her
we were
with s by
but separated now going back the P just
away to find people
what do I
see
walls Ena I see Ena which is also
a
what
what what no no no no no I I
[Laughter]
good
timing you said first
[Music]
[Laughter]
help me okay okay
[Music]
back okay yeah yeah keep
goinging where are the
[Music]
okaye
yes English yes yes
wow
[Music]
okay
go go go
[Music]
fore
two different paths no don't they
connect we saw this one before but
[Laughter]
[Music]
where did they go I'm not sure oh
not our
P that's so nice
[Music]
convenient how did we get back
spee
[Laughter]
for they're going
back
[Music]
for we
what are we waiting for
though you're so fast
okay
okay just updating Ana so Ana can tell
them cuz Ana is with them with
them okay portal coordinates
I feel like no one has gone this way oh
not this this way I guess they have they
went this way
huh
hia
hi careful is
dangerous oh what's are the days
oh
Bastion I want to kill
something I want to
battle I want the blood of the enemies
on my hands
[Music]
oh
hello I you
[Music]
you know guys that's not what I
meant
[Music]
okay fore
several Enderman okay yeah the Green
Forest is the end area so
[Music]
speee okay
if I had fire pions it would be worth
going but
yeah
oh I'll be on I'll be on B Duty
then if I see a gas I'm
shooting oh God oh God oh God oh God my
pinky is
weak I have a weak pinky I don't know
how mikoi does it
she must have a really buff
pinky is there something there I can't
tell uh
eventually eventually for
sure
un she's looking
okay wait we're going back maybe
oh my God
[Music]
here jumping from
happiness
for
spee
for okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
it's not
[Music]
[Applause]
no this is her second time so she's
probably not getting revived
wait what he's not getting
revived
yesterday it should have been me it
should have been me it should have been
me I know she's going to Rive cuz this
is her second time dying so yeah so I
don't know if she's
going yesterday di should have been me
there was a lot of stuffs happening oh
no no it should have been me
I should have went ahead of the group I
was supposed to protect
them it was my
job
[Music]
die careful there's another Pig
Pig I don't have a bow I'm so useless
here me
[Music]
giving
up return the
money in different ways
I couldn't do anything
[Music]
friend our
Senai oh they're so far you know let's
go okay
[Music]
[Applause]
lot of
HP oh
for theeee
[Music]
[Applause]
speee speech speech
[Music]
I got some Crimson Roots maybe that'll
help
[Laughter]
okay also got this one there we
go it's just like how he died
[Music]
it's like she's
[Laughter]
[Music]
burning
fore speee
[Music]
watch over
us foree
[Music]
spe
spee speee
[Music]
foree
a lot of them are logging
out give me my Phantom mem
braines oh the
lag my Phantom mem
braines nice
[Laughter]
membres
membranes oh can I have the
[Music]
membrane thank you thank you thank you
okay okay okay
[Music]
brain is it two's brains never
know okay
okay I still want to kill one gas in one
skeleton but I'll do that
[Music]
later fore
m
makee
[Music]
oh it's been already five and a half
hour
[Music]
ug
Fork
[Music]
speee hey
fix this later
thank
[Music]
for thank
you thank you
[Music]
you want to
continue yeah I think so you want to go
back
and yeah I mean I
mean all right
[Music]
okay let's go t let's go
t I'll go home and write my journal
I mean I think if I if I even think
about keep
going uh I probably won't stream the
second time
[Music]
it's
mushroom thank you very
[Music]
much byebye
ah she
gone no no CH we don't want another
repeat of today's
incident a slow fade
away okay
oh wait I don't have space what
the I got to go home and dump my
stuff
okay back to the grass
cutting job
ah what an adventure what an adventure
guys we met new party memb we lost
youi Sai
[Music]
o everything
grew ah man the final fight against the
pig would go down in Legends
now every time I do something I will say
what would sub the hero
do what would she have done
[Music]
she was a hero to all of
us charged down
ahead with no
[Music]
fear I guess I should read in the
journal that I did to be a guest
kind of want to do more nether
adventuring but
yeah is getting a bit late or early
either or I did get some gold gold
nuggets is good and
leather can make we can make more item
frames
[Music]
where is it a
potato and this feather that I got from
sua
yesterday that I forgot to name so St
it's definitely that
one
potato wait this
does this doesn't disap disprove my
unluckiness
I I I shouldn't have said
that oh oh they're already sleeping
okay what should I name this though
uh oh I
just the heroes better
uh
paper
Okay um let us it like what 17 for one
Emerald oh
next oh I have a lot
more would that be enough for one
more protection gear or another book I
think so
probably J
where is the n shule um am missst the
Panic of a great explosion I must have
used it to mend my
[Music]
mistakes
yeah okay it's time for the diary guys
[Music]
okay
May what day is it
today
16 15
60 what was yesterday
oh 16
okay
H should I say what do we start
with one shot one
kill today was the birth
of Ina of the watch to
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my favorite town of the
day
um
whilst whilst is that W
preparing for the
battle uh what should I say the battle
in the underworld battle of the
underworld
I managed to help out a small
town of
villagers le
le le
[Music]
uh
me ah there's not enough space
[Music]
what else
M
uh where
the with the
um
with my
gear blessed and
enhanced by
the godness of
Minecraft I
prepared for the
battle I
finished
preparations for the
battle of the UN
under can
not
uh
uh uh
uh what should I
[Music]
say I spell j
is that
it a met with
great party
members could join
me on who joined me on my
quest I was greeted
greeted oh not enough
I uh
I'll just stay M it's too
long okay
F
ow
[Music]
ow what was it was that
it oh
[Music]
H we
tread main
[Music]
ground we
tread
long
dangerous
hats trees
to
venture
into under
[Music]
P what's Bastion
called uh
[Music]
uh what
else oh do we have to sleep oh
okay continue
[Music]
however on
our on
our our March back to our home
town the
bravest warrior fell
upon the hands of the
enemy into the Lake of
[Music]
Fire bravest
warrior suu of the
Sun s the hero
bravest
[Laughter]
hero Cy
[Music]
are they also called
hoglands I'll just
sayani is
thata yeah
[Music]
it'sa uh I know all these words cuz of
anime I don't know I don't have a normal
conversation I'm just
like the
lava is that lava lava
maybe I should translate
English magma
magma there was a there was a thing
actually in English lava magma kind of
the same thing but they're different I
think one of them is like above ground
and one of them is below
but I guess magum is my mag
[Music]
Mas
Kashi
Kachi Kashi
[Music]
I uh what should I
say I have
returned
to
safy now we have returned we have return
saf but at what
cost I swear upon
my to your to your
bow
[Music]
Stella yet I will go back to avenge her
death one day
spee
[Music]
uh what what was
it oh no put
copy
paste
that
that until then
saep
well sweet
hero oh yes
[Laughter]
so I sure hope she never deep L
translates this
the Lord thickens okay I can return this
submit this over oh yeah and I have to I
have to put the mission that I defeated
the
guest oh maybe I should I should put
that I defeated ah it's too
late oh maybe I should
BS
[Music]
uh
Master to
[Music]
okay is that the wrong page now that's
the right page wrong day
what
ah ah there we go I wrote a lot to I
mean a lot happened today
okay submit the journal and I'm ready to
[Music]
go
oh someone got rid of the stairs here
that I always
took my stairs
[Music]
my stairs
okay I got spee
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I think I'm good
right
uh I guess I can the that's okay
I think she's very focused on writing
the journal right now maybe I should I
should end it
around okay I'll just lock off right
here here
[Music]
all
right that was fun thank you everyone
for coming to watch the long long stream
today I didn't realize I was going to
stream the song stream double what of
what I was
planning thank you very much I hope you
guys have a wonderful rest of the
morning afternoon evening next
stream ah
um was it today or tomorrow oh
tomorrow I think I'll stream normal Taco
Time tomorrow
[Music]
maybe cuz I don't think I'll have I'll
be awake enough if I sleep now for the
regular Taco Time today I mean it was an
extra long stream today so and I have a
meeting um tomorrow around the time I
started so um yeah we'll see we'll
see yeah thank you very much everyone
I'll keep you guys posted on timings and
stuff um so it's going to be 17th normal
Taco Time I mean I feel like if there is
stuff I want to do I might come and play
a bit off stream after the meeting
definitely not during the
meeting but uh yeah maybe I'll play a
little off stream too that's fine yeah
thank you I hope you guys have a
wonderful rest of the morning afternoon
evening I'll see you
guys next time okay take care bye-bye
[Music]