[Music]
This program is sponsored by the following sponsors
Inugami
Equals
[Music]
Good evening everyone, welcome to God
IhavetoSound
christmasterclation
Actually, Christmas
decorations were still up until recently.  Actually, I
took a picture of it before it aired. It looks a
lot like Corona-senpai,
right?
Maybe it would have been better to leave it in.
Let's explain this program.
This Life Trouble of
Mini Japanese
youbyyouHOUSE
is Takanashi.This talk is an interview talk show for English-speaking countries.The purpose of this talk is to
let people overseas learn more about Japanese talent, mainly
Japanese talents.
[Music]
Nicetomeetto
life is telling me
Going abroad is a
2-meet-yay night
[Music] My
name is Inu Corone, thank you very much
[Music]
[Laughter]  How can I
buy GoingHomeGoingHome? I've
been here before.
[Laughs]
Thank you very much. Thank
you very much.
Masu
Hone-senpai, what kind of activities have you been doing lately?
Yes, lately it hasn't changed much from before, but I've been
streaming a lot of games.
[Laughs] That's
too polite. It's
more like the latest games.
Maybe I play old games a lot.
Wait, I call you something. I
read it in the script.
Sometimes I sing a song.
Eventually
[Music]
Yeah,
[Laughs]
What did you play?
Yesterday was
yesterday's game.  Hey, I played Super Mario
64. Did I
pass all the enemies? I took them all.
Before the broadcast, I
talked about it, right? I hadn't made any progress at all. Is
Super Mario
senpai capable of playing such a role?
[Music]
What are you going to do? Basically, the characters are
bad at all the Mario game 2D stuff, and I
want to be able to do that, but I seriously ca
n't. Let's
do it together. I wish we could do it together instead of alone.
Isn't it fun? I understand that you're not good at
things. OK, I'll lend you my strength.
Thank you, you're so kind. My
next question to such a kind senior is, umm,
how did you first find Hololive and
what made you join?
Well, the reason why I joined Hololive was
because Ogyu invited me, and
first of all, Ogyu decided to join Hololive,
so I joined Hololive, Ogyukoro-san,
and I
said to him, ``Maybe it would be fun to do it together.''  Give it to me, what is that?Yango-san is
not my porridge-senpai, porridge-san.Do you
know anyone else who would like to be included?
So, at that time, porridge-san called out to me.
hand  I guess it's
okay to say something like, ``Let's have a chat over dinner.''
When I first joined the company, it was like this now.
Hey, I did auditions,
but I
wasn't as serious as I am,
so back then, I
didn't do auditions that were interesting or interesting.
Right, I'm
going to renew Okayu-senpai.
Senpai, it's
so interesting. It's the
first time I've heard of it. Isn't there anyone else who entered like this? No,
but he probably doesn't exist anymore, so it's possible in the future.  I
thought it was a no-brainer, but I'm glad I
did, because that porridge-senpai invited me, so I'm really
happy that we can do this kind of work together.
[Music]
Now, let's move on to the next question.  Is
there anything you wanted to convey to other countries that you couldn't say due to the language barrier?
[Music]
Ah, the language barrier. It's
fine, but I
try to convey things in simple English.
But I don't know much about this English,
so I don't know what to do, but what if I make a mistake and
say something in English that hurts my overseas history,
so I don't know what to do.  I've
never told them that,
but I
've seen a lot of people on Twitter comment that they're watching the overseas diary even if they don't understand Japanese, or that they're rooting for it.
After all, there are people who have been able to translate in real time what they have said about the coordination in their overseas experience, who can also speak Japanese, and I'm really happy about that.Of
course, that's true.  My Japanese fans are also
giving me strength,
but I've never forgotten the fact that they're here with me
every day,
so I
'd like to say thank you for your continued support.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Okay, okay, I'll translate it, okay
Google
[Music]
[Music] There's a lot of
stamps out there, everyone's
feeling something, I'm feeling love, love me, it
's a wonderful world,
but it's true that among the Japanese members, the
seniors aren't fluent.  Maybe,
but I feel like I can somehow convey my feelings in English. Yes, I really do. I've
been watching a lot of English limited distribution and English current distribution, and it's
really interesting, and
overseas diary is also my favorite distribution.  There are a lot of
people who say,
``I'll do it again.'' Let's do it again. ``Yes, I'll go next time.'' Well, you're Corne-senpai from Games, but what's your favorite stream? One word, ``games.''
That's right. I like games, after all.  I really
want to do a lot of collaborations,
but I'm so nervous that I
can't invite them myself.Whenever I
collaborate with that Okayo-senpai, it's always someone
who invites them.Ah,
but
Yes, in terms of proportion, I may be more likely to be a porridge.
[Music]
In terms of proportion, I
sometimes invite people, but yeah, it's a porridge that
says things to me quite often. You're so kind.
This is it, Senpai
have contents
[Music]  You
can invite me whenever you want. Of
course, I
want to play that game we talked about together, and
if there's anything else, I'll invite you. You know, I
thought Chara wanted to play it, uh,
that Switch Online.  There are a lot of
retro games coming out these days.
[Music]
Well, I want to
do something that the two of us can do together. It's a promise.
OK, I'm going to follow this retro game master, Korene-senpai.
Next up is a book.
[Music]
Promise, this senpai. By the way, yes.  I'm looking at the screen I
'm watching
[Laughs] I was
surprised, yay! It
was a success.
I
'm sorry. That's the one who was surprised
. It's scary, is
n't this senior? I'm also the type of person who gets really surprised at everything.  I don't
have to say it, but for example, I was really surprised by the sound of Minecraft's
Sword or something
breaking.I'm
always surprised
by nothing, so I
thought it was interesting.I
want to do it with you.
[Music] I'm
sorry, but
sister.  I
want to continue watching it with you.
[Music] I
haven't seen it yet. I want to see it. Ok, then
wait. When I come to Japan again, let's watch it together.
Ok Google
[Music] My
senior is distributing a lot of retro games.
But why do you choose that game?And what's your
favorite?Ah, why do you choose a little
game?
[Music]
First of
all,
even if you don't know anything about retro games, I want you to experience this
irrational, helpless feeling.  I
want it, and I also
want people who grew up playing retro games to feel
nostalgic, like, Wow, something like this existed,
but I'm not that familiar with retro games myself.  I
often choose it out of curiosity, like I want it to be something historical, or rather the beginning of DM, and I wonder what kind of games people used to play in the past.  I was wondering if they were doing that,
but I don't know what to call the Little Game case, but I
really like the shape of the Super Famicom, the PC Engine, and the drive.
Which console do you like the most?
Dreamcast is the console that I like the most in its shape.I
like the GameCube [Music]I
'll translate this first.That's the attitude.
[Music]
[Music]My
favorite
retro game  Which one is it? My
favorite action game is
probably Goemon Goemon. I wonder
if there's an English title.
Ganbare Goemon. Just
Ganbare Goemon. It's scary. Even in English. What's
that? It's really
interesting. It
looks really interesting. It's very Japanese. It's Japanese-style retro.
There are other games.
Are there other retro games
? Are they going to be retro? There
are RPGs like Mother 2.
Maybe everyone knows about them.
Even people in English speaking countries are
scared of the distribution.
[Music]
A while ago  I see, but did you play that girl? Did you
play a lover recently? Well, it's recently. The
English name is,
oh yeah, that's right.
There's a retro game I'd like to try. Do you
know Akiyama? It's
called Wizardry. Way.  There are
a lot of them, isn't there? The reason why it's difficult is because the character designs are nice. It looks like it'll be fun to like, right? It's the first time I've seen it. Eh, it's also on Steam. It's on Team. It's easy to do, isn't it? No, it's mostly text
[laughs]  ]
[Laughs] Looks like it'll be
fun. It'll
be difficult, but I want you to try it. If you
want me to watch it, then I won't watch it.
[Laughs]
OK, it's a
retro game.  As
for the pay, it can be said that it's a retro game, so I guess I
played it today, but the characters are okay, but it's
Super Marios No. 64 Retro.That's
different.Yes, it's
been retro for several decades,
but yeah, it's been 20 years at least, but not yet
40 years.  No, it's retro between the 20's and 40's.So I
feel like I've
done that before.I know Starship Titanic canyour No, I did it on stream, but it's different from what I
thought.It's different from what I thought.
My
mom used to play this game when I was little. Now, I
think my senpai played it on a stream.
What is that? I know it's stop
motion. There are movies and games like that,
but I
know it's called
2nd Foot.  What the heck is
The Neverhood
in English
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I used to
play a complaint, right? It
's gone now, but my mom won't be able to do it after this.My mom really
loved this game for a long time, and that's why
Growing up, we played games all the time,
but my mom played this one
a long time ago, and I've been watching it since I was a kid, and I've
been curious about it
since 1998. That's
old, isn't
it? It's amazing, Aiya's first release.  It seems like it was from 1996. It's
old. This is retro. It's retro.
I see. It was interesting. It was
a bit retro. It
was exciting.
Okaya
and
this
ok. Well, let's
continue.NEXTQuestion
Please explain that finger to first-time viewers.
[Music]
This means that
people who watch the stream have to
raise their finger to the colony, and as
soon as they open the stream, their finger
is gone.
[Music] The
finger is taken away.  Listeners are in trouble,
right? If they do that, they
'll have to watch the Coord stream until the end.
[Music] I
sometimes give everyone my finger back when the stream ends.
Lately, I haven't
done so. Why?  I
think I wrote about 3 servings.
Why did you stop? Why did you stop?
[Music] It's
a pain, so it's
a little hard to go. I
love you all, so I
want to have a piece of you. Do
Under
[Music]
It's black.  You've got the black part
[Music] It
really hurts
[Laughter]
All you have to do is hold that finger still
attached.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Everyone who said please be safe.  to
On my finger,
there's a cutout of a finger, so let's go take a look.Let's Go Be
Moving
oftheWhat kind of finger is it?It
's a historical cutout.Please, top.Yes,
please give me a spare.You're so
cute.
[Music]You're having fun.[Music]  [
Music]
[Laughter]
Non-time
[Music]
Everyone's fingers sway when they say, "One Claire"
If it comes on air 20 times, it's over, listener.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Hey on Twitter [Music] You know, if you keep things cool, they'll stick
together and it'll
hurt to look at.
[Music] Hey,
if you say cut your finger, isn't that true? I've been
keeping the viewers' fingers
cool for a while now.  I
can't give it back anymore. Let
me wash away what happened up until now. From now on, please let me cool down. Yes, it's important, isn't it?  He's a
strange person to be broadcasting.
[Laughs] I love
you so much. The
next question is about cutouts.
Why did this senior
become the only Holoment and did a game collaboration for the first broadcast
? I wonder what he's
like now, 5th generation.  The 6th generation
students are coming in, and it seems like they all have a format where they
have to learn something from the management or do things like this.
When it came to the school name, there was no such thing, so porridge
was first broadcast, but
porridge was amazing and it was broadcast perfectly for the first time, and
when I saw it, I was pronouncing it proudly, and I
was like, ``Oh, I'm already here.''  It might not be possible, I might
not be able to do it, and I'm feeling kind of depressed.
Then, at that time, I might be
a little
nervous and can't talk to all the gamers,
so I'd like you to release that first broadcast.  I
decided to ask him to do it. I see.
[Music]
When I looked at the cut-outs of Kone-senpai from his debut, I noticed
a little bit of that in some places.
I was the only one who could hear it from Mio-senpai. He
said that I looked like him.  This is the
first time I've noticed this. Please, it's
Mio, the wolf. I'm
looking at you. There's more, more, more
, more, more
. I
heard that you're a
perfect impersonator. Could you please imitate Pecola-senpai? I guess
so.  I
feel like my character is saying, ``I haven't done it yet, it's been a while, it's amazing. Senpai, please
[Music] Please.'' It's a bit similar [Music]
Hey
number 27 is
[Applause] -
Good
[Music]
Presence
There are other things that I'm good at.Okayu-
senpai is always talking
[Music] I
thought it would be impossible, but I've been waiting.He
talks every day, almost
[Music]
Yes, please take care of Koro-san. Ah,
leave it to me. It
could be Chiara-chan who says that.
Any voice, any cute voice.
By the way, thanks to the first distribution at that time, the
education of those newcomers on Hololive has been
enriched.  I heard that it seems to have
changed. What do you
think? What
do you need to be careful about when broadcasting?  You're welcome,
what's up
[Music]
This senior, by the way,
didn't have that accent at first,
but
Corin's grandmother
is a very talkative person, and she and I often
speak with accents.
Hey,
sometimes I don't have an accent.Also, if I spend a little time with my grandma, the next day's stream will be completely accented.It just depends on the situation.  It's going to
be influenced by me. It's amazing. I probably didn't have to
speak properly for my debut broadcast. I
was really nervous from the beginning to the end.
Hmm, that's right. I
was nervous, cute. That's cute.
[Laughs]
okents
OK, I'm embarrassed about my debut,
so I'll leave it behind.Next is my
senior.He's
cute,
very suitable for him, and the design of this senior's skis
is legendary.How did you come up with this?Ah, I'm so
happy, these skis are so cute.  The
reason I was born is
that when I fail in some kind of cooking game, I'm
carried away on rails,
but when I look at the trash can, I look, look, look, I
was born to make people eat curry.  Don't
think too much about
it, just write it down.I don't think it's okay
since you're a listener.On the other hand, if you think
about things like how to design something, it
won't be possible to put it into form, so don't
think too much about it.  Is it better not to write it?
Maybe it's better to just doodle without thinking.
People who look like that emoji in [Music] There are
some people on YouTube who are writing right now, but they
have to put garbage in their mouths like pink pink dinosaurs.  That's how
it feels. It's big. It's got a big mouth. That
's right.
[Music] The
rest of me also went into that futon together.
But
before, I told you
how, why, and why.
All I can think of is that it's really cute, but it's
cute,
so I'm not really thinking about anything. I don't know why, but I'm not really thinking about anything. I'm
writing this in
Program Paint, then
Photoshop.
Well, when I write it in Photoshop.
Sometimes I write using Paint software on my computer,
and
all the materials I use for streaming are written using Paint.
is
mustreets
OK, let's move on to the next question.
[Music] It's
a mess.  I
'm a senior who spreads his wings, but do you know how to exercise
? I
haven't been able to go to exercise lately,
but I go to a boxing gym. I
used to go 4 times a week, but lately,
there are days when I don't go to the moon.
Sometimes I go 23 times, and I
say boxer size, but I've
heard that it's a really
crazy workout.  I would
jump rope 45 times for one minute,
then I would do some shadow boxing, and then I would
train with things like using a punching bag and a punching ball, and
sometimes I would ask the trainer to
do something like that in the middle of my body, and
at the end I would do some stretching.  And that's how it ended. I'm just
skating as usual,
but I haven't been skating lately because I've been busy. I'm so
busy that I don't think it's cool. I
wonder if I'll be able to go if I have someone to go with me.
But, you know, I
want to
exercise alone, but I don't really want to do it.I don't know if there's anyone else out there like me, but I
want to do it alone, not with friends.That's right.I
don't exercise in the first place.
That's all I do, but I only
do dance when I feel like I have to learn some choreography. That's when I end up dancing and messing up. I
always feel like I'm getting old. You're
amazing at dancing. You're so sexy.
I love you so much, I
want to dance with you.But
boxing is okay.I can't keep up with it.One
time, when I was boxing at school, my
arm was damaged.And when I
told the teacher, it would be okay.She
told me to keep doing it,
even though it hurt.  Something had to go
on I'll
give you a punch I do
n't remember who it was
anymore Even though I don't remember it anymore I feel grateful I'll give
birth Yes, this is Sister who gave birth
on
this
now
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]  I'm already
sending a super chat to everyone with that name.
That's right.
Stop mic exercise.
[Laughs]
Ah, that's a
legend.
Ok, let's put this topic aside
for now.
[Music]
Let's get started.  Are you
ready?
I want you to answer in English if you can. OK let's go
weather. I
prefer hot or cold.
Don't delete the code.
OK
[Music]
Twitter or Instagram?
Twitter
Apple or orange juice?
Whether it's climbing a mountain or running a marathon, the
computer is a console or a game console.So then, should I
put pineapple on top of the pizza?Is it
spicy or sweet?Is it
OK to have tea or coffee?Is it cool to
drink on a peach by the sea?
Traveling in a famous metropolis
Metropolitan City Do you
sleep naked or wear clothes
? Fashion My
favorite events are Halloween, Christmas,
Tanabata, etc.
Ah, Christmas, of course. Why did I hear about it?
[Music]
[Music]  It's already time to
give presents, like a lamp.Which do
you like?Give
YouGiveYouI'll get it.Would you rather
walk the distance of one station or take the train?Walking
WalkingAnd
what's your blood type?
OK
[Music]
[Laughter] You're
so cute
[Music]
Hey, thank you
[Music]  [Music]
Yes, OK,
thank you. I'm back to normal BGM.
But now I'm back to normal questions. Let's
go back to know
this senior. I have a
personal request, but please repeat
me.
Scary,that's
what it means
Scary,
scary,
perfect
[Music] I
remember it. I think I was born for it. It's the
first time I've said it
[Music]
Thank you. What is
this? This
is a meme that's been trending for months now.  But yeah, that's right. It's a
video of someone saying the word croissant in a playful and cute way,
but in reality, it's like a story about a
woman who wanted to eat croissant today
because it looked scary.  I
went to a croissant shop and
bought a croissant.I
went home and ate
it.It's a mimim, which is like a croissant.Interesting and interesting.  Maybe it was,
maybe not, but I just didn't understand it,
so I
'm small.
[Music] I'm so
happy. I've
been addicted to it, and I say it over and over again every day.  I
say so much that Mr. Rison is getting tired of it. Oh yeah, I'll
send it to you later. That's the original
fun.
Ok, let's put aside my personal requests and
look at the clippings. Let's go, let's go, let's go,
cut outs.
[Music]
waterinthefire
whythefire
InotandaStand
[Music]
I miss summer
I can't
Englishbutter
you love me
you
[Music]
R
English
haveconfits
[Music]
Iamnotcrazy
Party Impossible I love this
Ok menu
[applause]
[music]
Goodbye goodbyHUMAN
GooBikepeople
Iloveyou
OKOK
[laughing]
[music]
from
youreyesasyouStand
In
[music]
thisthisvier
onlying
[music]
[laughing]
Wow, Wow,
Assortment  That's
amazing, isn't it? It's like that
ending screen at the end. The one I
was reading
was calling Marin, which is also Merlin-senpai's name, marriage.
[Laughs] I
couldn't call it "Clothing Marine" but now I
can read it.
I'm pretty sure
I misread those credits. I guess I misread the boss's name. Ah, the
name of the boss that appears in the game is X-
Posi, I
think.
Oh yeah, yeah, that's
right. Expotate has also become famous.
Like, it's funny, it's really funny, it's funny, I'm
happy, let's go back to English
[Music] The
reason why the verifier ended up on Hololive is because
for many people, he's Corona Senpai. His
cute English pronunciation and mistakes are often
turned into memes. This is Senpai.  What do you
think? I'm also curious about where you learned how to draw.
[Music] I didn't
know much about memes,
so I just looked it up and it came up as something interesting.
If it's something interesting, I'm really happy.
I thought that I was very happy to be turned into a meme.That's great, but on that day, I
felt like my English, which I had worked so hard on, had somehow become a joke.I'm
not sad, it's okay.That's not
it at all.  That
overseas diary is really
enlivening things like this. I
really want them to do more.
[Music] I'll
do my best to provide the material.
Thank you very much for your help. And I wonder
how you learned English.  It's
like one-on-one,
one-on-one with a teacher, but I've
moved and can't go to school anymore,
and recently there's been books like English books that can be used when traveling,
and
sometimes I look at those kinds of books
at that school.  When I went to Kone-senpai, what score did I get on the English exam
?There was no funding for English,
so what do you mean by school?
What do you mean by school?I wonder if it's an English test
or something.  I do
n't think there was anything like "Skin"
in elementary school,
but in junior high and high school,
even if I had taken English, I would have gotten 40 points.In
direction, I don't
think it would have been 50.I think it was around
that,
or less than half.But this senior
isn't bad.  Seriously,
that's the way English is taught in Japanese schools, as far as I know. It
's not the seniors' fault, it's really true. Well then, it
seems like the education was wrong.  That
's right,
everyone, it's not bad, really, but it
can't be helped. I have no choice but to practice some more on my own, so I think taking one-on-one lessons was the right thing to do. I want to do it.
[Music]
[  [Music]
[Music] It's
not bad for you, isn't it? It's not that bad, isn't it?
[Music] I'm sure it's
well
understood, so I'll say it in English. We
collaborated together the other day.
That character was speaking mostly in English, but
since he understood it, I was
wondering if he could pronounce it in an easy-to-understand way.Thank
you, that's good, that's good, that he
says it in an easy-to-understand manner.
[Music]  Let's
move on to the next question. Aiyo.
What is the reason why you became such good friends with Okayu-senpai? And please tell us about your favorite memory.
What is your favorite? Why did you
become friends with Okayu-senpai?  I was
introduced to her by a friend,
but Corde was shy and shy, and
was the type of person who wouldn't go out on her own, so I
didn't ask her to come to my porridge, but
porridge started talking to me a lot after that, and she said we
should talk on the phone and play games together.  He
invited me to so many things,
and since he was so kind, we gradually became friends.That
's why, if he hadn't come all the time, there might
not have been any videos in the past.That's
right, it's a sad world.  I heard that you
have a lot of memories.The
reason we became friends was
like having a video chat where we could see each other's faces, and
doing video calls, and
doing tidying up the room while showing each other's faces,
and things like that.  [
Music]
So, were you
using Skype at that time
? I think it was Skype.
Skype was more popular in the past,
so maybe that's why.
That's why we became friends pretty quickly. That's
good.  I
have fond memories of how the two of us always left that room in a dirty room and made strange faces at each other.Now we don't have to do things like
clean up calls.We
don't have those calls anymore, but we've become good friends after all, so we'll
eat meals together.  Let's
go out together and
things like that have increased. I wonder if it's good or good.
It's senpai and senpai. I'm a
senpai. No, I'm a senpai. I'm a
happy nature.
senpai catchingtalkings
[music]
About my senpai.  Um, do you
think they're soulmates?
I know. I wonder
how many meters there are like that. The
second layer of Japanese for soul friends is, um,
that's what appears in soul mates.
The amount of soul versions, the amount of Hanu, my
friends.Nakahara, I
have a deep relationship with them from my previous life.  It's the other person,
or the person who teaches you the mission of your soul.But
there are things that no one else has done.When you
're
hurting, when something sad happens, etc.  I feel
like Koro-san
should talk to me now.Maybe he
'll send me messages like this when I'm sad.Maybe he's my
soulmate.It looks
good.Here's this,
senpai.It
feels good, like this, like this.  I'm glad I found a friend with deep, deep feelings.I'm
glad I'm going next time.JapanesestudytimePlease
tell me something Cole-senpai
[Music] I
thought it would be better to use something that I can use on a daily basis.  When
Coord has been broadcasting for such a long time
in a row,
when I say, "Please stop, I want to go to bed," I would
like to teach you some UL lines today. Please, please, give me a
break.  That's
perfect, thank you. Please give me a break. I'm on the spectrum. Please give me a
break.
Please give me a break. Please give me a break. This
is a proposal from the beginning. It's
okay to give me a break.
[Music]
I like that word too.
[Music] The
next one is a little long, but he
has experienced many amazing things like turning blue for Senpai Sonic, appearing in Yo-Kai Watch, and singing on stage with Isao Hirata.  How do you feel about your seniors? Do
you have any dreams that you haven't achieved
yet?
Even if you like it, the current situation you're in now is
all thanks to Hololive, and
that's been the case from the beginning and probably will continue to be.  I do
n't think that will change, but that
may be different from my unfulfilled dream,
but I want to do more activities that
will give back to Hololive.The
rest is about my own goals.  I might not end up like that,
but I
still want to be able to do more regular collaborations with the girls from Ikei and ID, but I
still don't want to
study English too much.  I don't know
if I'm not doing it or not.Even if I have a goal that makes me
spend a lot of time lazily, I think it's
okay to start tomorrow.I'm spending a lot of time lazily, so I'd like to fix that.I also
have a goal like
this, which will help me improve my English and Japanese skills.  She's
able to use and speak Japanese, and she's become a bridge for everyone.I
have a lot of respect for Tiara,
so I wonder
what's going on.  I
think it's fine to remain a senior, but in
my opinion,
members from Japan who want to collaborate more with their partners
often appear, but
everyone says that there's an English barrier, so that's why
ID members
There are a lot of members who are fluent in Japanese. Have
you forgotten?
Even if you don't care, everyone will
do it together. Senpai:
Atmoment and
[Music]
This
Confidence is OK. That confidence.
I think it would be better to collaborate with everyone without worrying too much about what you have.I think it would
be great if you could do it with more confidence and without fear of failure so that you can take action.
I think it's good, I think it's good
[Music] I'm
back to that again. It seems like it's a
perfect flow, but seriously, that bone. It
would be great to think about what you've done up until now when you're gathering this question.  I
felt once again that I was doing a lot of things, because it made me
feel blue. That's
amazing.
[Music]
Well, I'll end it with the next question. It's been a
lonely hour and a half, but it
feels so long already.
But in a good way, I want to talk more and more.  It
went by so quickly
[Music]
I'm translating it so it feels like it took a long time. Maybe
that's true.
[Music] I
haven't taken it away yet, but there's something after this question.
So, the last question I always ask is, what is
Hololive for me, Senpai? What is Hololive? Hmm, I'm
confused, but what is it? It's like a school.
This is also the first time I've heard this. Out of the 27 times I've heard this, it's
probably the first time I've heard of a school. The management. There's a
lot of management.
There's a manager, students who are members, and lots of
friends who are Hololive members and listeners, and
there are events like sports festivals and cultural festivals, so it feels like everyone is having fun together.  It's
kind of school-
like
[Music] I
vowed to continue studying at Hololive Academy.
[Laughs]
Good luck.
[Music]
[Music] There are
always seniors and juniors.  And
then there's the vtubers from that other company,
those other schools, those other schools, it's
funny,
okay, okay,
big big thank you, thank you
for answering so many questions today
[Music]
I hope that many of you will think that I have learned a lot from someone who doesn't know much about this topic, but as a senior, I
have something to say or make an announcement at the end.
Greetings I
want to say that,
but I want you to come in.
[Music]
Hey, Senpai, this is the last thing I want you to do. Please enjoy the performance from your senpai.
Run, Hamtaro,
run, Hamtaro. What I
love is
After all, sunflower seeds run, Hamtaro, spin, spin, Hamtaro What I love is
sunflower seeds, I'm happy when they spin, Hamtaro, I
sleep, Hamtaro, I
sleep anywhere, Hamtaro My
favorite thing, after all, is sunflower seeds,
Hamtaro, sleep
[Music]