[Music]
la
oh
[Music]
a
la
n
[Music]
k k k
k we're
here we made it yeah I'm
hungry so big suddenly did you change
something I'll change you again you're
too big
big I'm a big
cat oh yeah okay introductions please
yeah start from the newcomer okay T I'm
from Life English
Justice
yeah pet cat I'm petting
her okay I guess after that by going by
like the bottom to the top in terms of
senpai senority would be you
right yeah true technically I am a
little bit more of a
s
technically actually okay
well this is
or uh from Wow guess what it is hollow
life England
what a
coincidence she when she arrived she
jump scared me with her beauty right
like she was
blowing you know it was kind of creepy
she was the last one to arrive and uh
like you know in in in in Japan usually
most uh Apartments when somebody rings
the doorbell they have like a camera so
we wereing at the with
her on camera there was a priew and I
hopefully on camera I was like I don't
want to be seen you did actually cover
it I thought it was a malfunctioning it
was yeah we thought it was malf what
going to be how's going to be it's her
right she wanted to surprise us with her
her very successful diet oh my God
she I'm child what are you going to do
like you already have those like stick
legs what are you going to do getting
even finner I don't have stick
legs the quason legs the the quason legs
yes those are I mean they're really thin
and really long if you get any thinner
you're going to
like yeah yeah don't disappear
on I'll disappear one day
anyway wait what but she looks so wow
ladylike today like wow and you're
you're always pretty no
no can I switch places I'm getting
nervous
next okay and then
I Iris it's Iris also surprisingly from
H
life really no no way are you are you
sure your iris today I think you broker
is today yeah I forgot I was so broke
Chris she needs her money need I you
guys can be my wallets to right
yeah you I so glad I have three wallets
right next to me anything you
need what do you want thank you bye for
painting what what oh we we decided that
she's paying she's paying for for all of
us I guess
[Music]
yeah no no no we can't do that no
personally I I pay for you then you pay
for them I pay for you
wow
now well yeah and then I guess the most
sampai out of us is the
Taki thank you for coming to my cramped
place we're all sitting on my bed right
now I moved it because I don't have
enough chairs but I have this big ass
bed we're all closing up together
I feel shoulders on my
shoulders we are at shoulder
length wow
distance touching
me oh wow they're fighting they're fting
no fighting no violence please body
slamming her right
now I guess care care T please oh yes
water Don't Spill the water yeah don't
punch right now yeah I'll kill myself if
you do can you pour me some water too of
course thank you
wow tell me where to stop such
a okay I want to see how far you
go uh what was I going to say uh I
forgot what it was iot did anybody here
now meet for the first
time no
like you yeah
[Music]
yeah what's your
impression cuz my first impression my
first impression of Ra was that she
looks and like her whole Aura is Rich me
she looks rich I don't know
why o
o it's time for
bed it's time to go got to go to
bed can you sing the Lula for me how
does it go again um it's time to go to
bed
y i f c so
[Music]
beautiful you stole my line
you're wow and your eyeliner so on flear
right you like it I did in two seconds
you're so talented I didn't do my
eyeliner today I didn't do I only did
like my lashes I should maybe go I want
I want to get eyeliner praise I'm going
to do my eyeliner I can't eyeliner for
[\h__\h] so I she's going to do haer
eyeliner oh you going to do it now oh
you going to do it now let's go she's
going to eyeline herself whenever I try
to eyeline my hands are too shaky it
goes all over the place h
you should try it
again especially liquid eyeliner is
scary it's like once you screw up you
screw up it's you can WIP it off really
it takes I have the one that has a pen
shape so I just
do yeah yeah the the pencil one right
pencil what's the current makeup meta
please tell us the current makeup meta
yeah well this is the
meta I want to learn you she point did
you pointed her no no no no she she's
the meta she is the meta standard she is
the standard eyelashes oh thank you
thank you what who has
eyelashes eyelashes eyelashes it's so
warm
here I forgot that we were on stream for
a
second it was so casual here I haveg for
a second yeah I'm so happy I'm meeting
so many in guys I'm so I'm so so blessed
right now yeah so bless me and crony
were discussing about how to drink wine
a few days ago yeah wi how do you girls
drink wine you kind of like you kind of
spin it around like you're
like and then you sniff it and then you
yeah and you sniff it a bit and then
they pour you
more yeah have you guys ever gotone wine
tasting before yes no extremely dry
because they pour so much water I only
did it at work because we had to test
out all our Wines in the hotel when I
worked in the hotel so beautiful look at
this eyeliner oh my God look
at shy hands whatsoever look at that
look at that stable line and so fast
right right that's a hand of an artist
you guys see no difference though can
you tell guys look at my eyes I can tell
they're different you can tell you can
tell I can tell only you girls can tell
you're so you have an eye for it have
they they got eyes so I guess MH I I can
see okay so today we're playing a game
that's called Tony Damu and it's it's
kind of like a bravery challenge we'll
see who is a chicken here it's not me
obviously
oh it couldn't be me of course no no no
not me uh it's basically like a you know
like many small challenges uh fast
challenges um two of us here the ones on
the right side they're playing with uh
keyboard they're sharing a keyboard yeah
we have the buff by the way just let you
know we have de buff keyboard have the
RGB keyboard
ohg if we lose it's because of the
keyboard yeah yeah and me and Quon are
using
controllers me I am using PS5 controller
you're only PS4 controller only have a p
never used a PS4 controller before never
what do you not have a PS4 no I only had
a
Nintendo now the only console you own is
Nintendo what I've only owned
Nintendo I mean what I mean I also only
owned like Nintendo for most of my life
I only got PlayStations when I started
streaming
so helps a lot because like a lot of
games like they go by the PS4 standards
for the buttons so whenever you try to
play that with like a proon you end up
like not knowing what to press menu
tells you to press something else yeah I
hate that Nintendo has the X and Y R it
always confuses me to like I when I just
played a Nintendo game well my face and
then I go back to playing a PlayStation
game I'm like I never know which button
to press it's funny the Kiara I see over
there is more
naked over there they won't understand
that that will be hard to yeah I was
talking at night like oh she's wearing
that and then
completely I can be two different
outfits at once but they won't
understand that killing it in both
though I mean I can I can also like do
something I can get a little bit more
naked here you
want I saw your really shiny fat
for you did you see my frie huh yes
Shin it was so shiny I know go girl
go you know I was obviously just making
fun of myself okay it's fine I I I I but
I have to say there were some moments
where I was okay 90% of the time I was
failing at twerking but there was maybe
10% of the time where it worked and and
there was a booty jiggle a proper one
and it was really nice and sad
there there were some Physics going on
in there that was that was beautiful
thank you thank you so yeah uh back to
uh the topic we're playing this game
we'll see who's a chicken uh and who's
not apparently there's already a fried
chicken I am cooked I don't know why
cooked why are you cooked already cooked
already it's because she's cooking yeah
I they're so
hot they burned you IR is also hot we're
all hot like we're all Hot Chicken
chicks we're all hot
chicks okay why is nobody saying
anything no I agree I agree I I said
okay I do think this is a quite mature
lineup is it adult ladies I guess
there's no oh I almost said uh there's
no you know I know what you mean there's
no small there's no small flat chested
girls yeah yeah only adults this is an R
stream what oh can we start pulling out
languages oh yeah yeah of course at my
channel of course what oh
okay the spotlight I'm
sh no no no no no what was she going to
say no sh uh sh it's time to focus
okay that's the language you're going to
pull out okay okay okay feel free to let
it all out girls mhm okay uh and let's
try playing what is the button that I
would press X or Square uh uh Circle
it's either you would never know maybe
it's X okay no it was not okay stop stop
uh you press button and you press uh Z
yeah and yeah exactly okay it was Circle
this is your guys's
control okay okay okay got you
remember I will never remember
nostalgic what you know that control
like local multiplayer yeah cuz I I
actually I've never used local
multiplayer before so
really the thing is you can kind of play
this online and I tried but the lag yeah
it because Steam remote was so bad so I
decided one day I will play this as an
off collab and here we
are thank you for inviting us oh we're
starting dropping the bucket don't hit
your head uh how play stop okay I think
which which button is
that uh press a if you're ready oh okay
I think this might
already what I you got to press as late
as possible before you die but not too
early who actually press the button
or they're laughing at us I have no idea
what happen
yeah basically for the whole game the
theme is you got to try to do it as late
as possible without like dying like okay
if if you stopped right your head that
would be best okay and all the games
will kind of be like
this got you got it lost me it lost me
there it is okay there's so many people
close together here like I I I I was
like like both Ina's body and my body
like before you girls came oh we could
be in everyone's body yeah
we can do all four at once if we wanted
to okay so well crazy
you she's crazy and the chicken is I am
a chicken you're a chicken right now I
missed Mama Mia oh you got a title never
lost your head let's go nice okay think
of the chair the chair move the chair
right before it breaks it breaks okay
right before it breaks
understand oh the butt the buttt okay
okay you it so early though oh gamer you
can see the HP yeah yeah you have to
right before it breaks it yeah take your
time yeah he's smashing that but it
might be a
huge it what happened Dam it what
happened what you do my my chair
broke did I press the right button it's
supposed to be the this key right like
the when they say on the screen like the
right key it's probably just the right
key maybe guess I don't know or did I
press the wrong button I
maybe should be control okay I press the
wrong button that's why the the arrow
buttons might just be for the games
where you have to move around okay okay
gotcha yeah da don't be so scared no you
you're going to not be a Panter anymore
you're going to be
chicken don't be so scared anymore okay
okay
okay chair
understander wow wow I strange
understand the buttons oh you guys know
the pretzel game the Pokey game I know
the Pokey game but not the pretzel game
pretz game it's just a translation for
poke game oh
so cuz originally I think a Japanese
game so pretzel game pretzel game oh
no oh oh oh we can't why is mine so slow
yeah why is your so
slow you're going over so slowly take my
time okay I win anyway
Yahoo oh you guys are crazy
too well I don't maybe I got to go buy
some Pokey and we can see how this works
out in real
life is that really a thing people do
IRL I thought it was just an yeah manga
show your manga I we are s oh we have
keyboard Mash this oh oh climbing until
you reach the top okay okay okay
keyboard Mash keyboard Mash
is that really oh God I don't
really this so try hard if you if you
don't you going to fall off if you don't
look
girls I say that and yeah oh cron only
because I warned
you she wasn't even looking at the
screen I wasn't looking
at you get it you get it I got it yeah
no because because you fell down just
like me cuz yeah you have to press hard
to be up fast
but what happened what oh stick somebody
pressed sticky keys SP spamming like
crazy that's why okay no don't turn on
STI sticky keys I never I've never
turned on sticky keys before do you ever
turn that on who does I mean it just
always turns on for me and I don't know
how to turn it off in my home
PC I just leave it on cuz it's funny cuz
every time like like when I mash a
button and it comes up the whole chat
will go sticky keys so you know whatever
gets the chat going sticky ke have a
unique sound to it moving
on
Yak from a barrage of strikes okay cook
cook the me oh sctimes two yeah oh cook
the me in this
one have to change it disabl this
keyboard shortcut no wait how do you
turn it off disable this keyboard
shortcut access I have to press control
that's why was because I'm I'm spamming
control it's off though yeah probably
it's off though that's
[Music]
weird keyboard shortcut for sticky keys
yeah press the shift key five times to
turn sticky keys on
I mean I don't think you were pressing
shift ah I was I was sh probably this
one oh you were okay I'll turn this on
just turn off everything yeah sorry this
is a new pc I I'm on my
[Applause]
PC no redo redo the game paused and
unpaused only is alive she needs those
extra points yeah I need some extra
points I'm let me cook okay oh is it
cooked cook
Yak still a chicken I cuz you barely got
it it's better over cook M you like a
little bit of a like a black crust
right
Aroma
[Music]
yeah Oh
shoot no I
38,000 I don't even know how that's
possible but
yay what's Albatros it's a bird okay
that's that was the tutorial now we
actually now we actually know how to do
this we get more more more this doesn't
count at all now we be gaming for
snowman Spirit make a head out of snow
oh so you have to hold snow do we have
to hold it says hold oh is it and then
if we let go I'm guessing this it's
stops falling I
guess why is mine so big why is oh okay
never mind they're all
big oh what oh how big though I don't I
don't know how big we're supposed to go
uh uh as big as ah before it breaks you
don't know when it will break I guess
oh was it that big I don't
know
crazy got levels of CRA we got the max
yeah I don't even there's the gold crazy
and then the rainbow crazy perfect oh no
I think my God never bother you
anyway well no we don't know where that
comes from now we don't know anything
yeah no that's crazy legendary Creator o
chicken quest beat the monster okay
select confirm uh okay what's select on
the key how do you
there's so many references in this game
wait what what I don't
know what do we I don't understand okay
we're killing we're killing the you got
to attack a ow it's like a game in a
game okay and we have HP and they have
HP I'm not going to
make you can do it one more what it hits
what does it hit I oh oh I almost got
it yeah
[Music]
defeated the chicken we're supposed to
defeat him right oh wait I did read that
yeah take the last CR the first fail of
how does it feel first feels good you
like to fail some more no I love first
times and it's got to the first time
this will be the first and the last okay
spitting we'll never see again okay rule
of all chickens living legend living
legend okay we're dropping the bucket we
did this we did this now we know how to
wait you pressed it to to stop it from
dropping yeah before it hits our
head
no
[\h__\h] that is we I press it before
though P ping ping ping ping there's no
ping but I do think there's lag I
believe it that's
SC okay I'll give you this
wind you window scous WIP the window
three times oh okay win three
times we'll see what happens oh oh I see
what uh it's scandalous but I don't oh
ah oh what ah you can't show the the
peee how are you supposed to know that
well we know where it that's very
difficult okay okay okay not holding it
no not the beep hide the beep we got to
hide it you you did well I think you can
win with
this yeah okay you're
winning why the points are so extreme
great at censoring second time I lost
all myone
it's so over Russian to avoid the Wasabi
and eat it what does that mean do we
avoid it or do we eat it oh it's like
Russian ruette like you guess as to like
what which one okay so it's just luck
then that's just luck oh people are
thinking that's out of character Iris
that you just won that one why cuz y
Iris I'm so great at sening what you're
talking about you should show
them you have experience about what hey
what is this what is this what what is
this what is this
oh what oh wait did one of them have not
what's up did not
have what it's just
L yeah okay just this is really just
luck okay the one who gets the most
without
[Music]
thei I lost
first
no how you guys going so far
only one more Wasabi so that means
there's a good chance can stop you can
stop why did you do that now we all lose
Dam
it I thought it'd be funny do you like
Wasabi no yeah I enjoy it I like it
really I need it in my Sushi I don't
like you need it in your sushi I need it
yeah Wasabi it's just it's pointless I'm
trying to get used to it like it crunch
there's crunch in there punch a punch a
do you not like spicy things I like
spicy things oh okay I spicy pasta what
was it
[Music]
[Applause]
called show me your
a I don't know that's how you say
perfect really perfect
well I'm almost Italian almost true I I
was there like two weeks ago
so and I I speak uh Italian
fluently honorary
Italian only
stream I love Italians I love Italy
[Music]
yo world
record
cron let's go like the best and the
worst it's great deep fried chicken L
let's
go honorary chicken yeah we're happy
that you're deep fried chicken I guess
that's deep fried
chicken crony what happened didn't
didn't you say we her her Peak was in
the past yeah i' I'm stabilized
ah Redemption Arc
win now is redemption Arc PR game oh
okay okay I know to do this okay okay
okay okay do not to be afraid Pokey
G
so wow that was close ah damn it who's
so close
[Music]
okay she's risking it for the biscuit
all the Y
virus it's a coincidence why did you
become a blue man yeah why not Iris I I
mean you know there's two poor little
Souls behind us you know I don't want
them to see anything this one looks
like I think that's the
intention keep climbing till you
your now we know how to play okay now we
know spam and then be careful
yeah oh I God you guys hear that
compation I got
this let's
go controller gameboard gang we're just
chilling yeah it's just a keyboard deff
yeah keyboard debuff
yay okay we're so crazy had a controller
a crazy we we would have won if yeah
yeah
really I I thought you love keyboards
iron certain keyboards the real chicken
games of Summer
86 okay this is kind of similar guys
okay stop Pi her right before the C yes
right before what the cliff right before
the cliff but we don't know where it is
no probably Zer at zero at zero
yeah I can see the armers oh my God one
of them is why why why is one of you
guys driving the Toof a I guess you got
to hit it earlier because it's just
going
to too late okay who here has a license
I do I do have a license Iris you too no
sure are you sure I'm serious okay I
don't so but then that's okay because
we're just going to blame crony and laa
for even though them have them having a
license they still fall off of a cliff
yeah in my defense I got it last year in
my defense I got a driving license but I
never drove oh oh she's a paper driver
yeah I think you did tell me that you're
you not wait are you a good driver no no
I never drive before that's crazy I I I
took the driving license and then I
never took a car why did you get it then
did you get it didn't you think you
would drive a lot then no you know easy
way to verify yourself I oh just for
verification that's a good reason I just
want I just wanted to test myself if I
can drive I can drive yes but I don't
need to drive m
okay well that Flex is good
yeah so
Iris when are you getting a license huh
I don't trust myself behind the wheel
but you I see you behind the wheel a lot
somehow oh that's that's a me using my
um illegal Nephilim power to you know
police MH I am Justice you're not
right it's notal it's not illegal in the
human world it's not illegal no is yeah
I mean I'm I'm stronger than you any you
cannot arrest me oh you can are you sure
about that yeah yeah you got what about
what if I call
sub I'm going to call her I'm going to
call her no no when's the last time she
did one of those police not
act what do you mean I'm here I'm here
police like yeah what are you like
guards right like you just pring you
just prend we got criminals you're
guards you you draw you draw the
criminals in very pretty art and you're
like o you aren't you just like you draw
the want po I'd like to be arrested if
I'm on
my I get arrested I'm
my I like the point that Iris makes like
you guys are just you say you're justice
but that just sounds like a chuno role
playing kind of thing
no oh my God they roasting us jce just
like that did you not just decide like
oh I don't know I want to do something
fun so I'm just going to call catch
people we don't say that in
public they're Great
Pretenders Justice is
fake wow roasted roasted roasted deep
fried chicken no such thing as Justice
in this world make it pretty oh len make
it PR more than that everybody's already
pry
we'll see
oh pretty oh God oh God don't go too
deep guys what she
said SC God damn it can we go in again
no only once oh the poop no yeah
69 we're all pretty close no did you
guys get uh your ear like vacuumed and
showered before yeah what vacuum yeah
and shower like they have like a
pressure shower B
the most I've done was have my doctor
like like dig into my hair before but
that's about and I would I would you
know whenever I shower when I clean my
ear I would have the shower head on my
ear like yeah yeah but they have like
specific things just for the ears like a
tiny pressure shower for your ear and a
vacuum tiny vacuum cleaner for your ear
yeah I watched a lot of videos like that
and I wanted to get it done so I was
looking around they didn't have it oh
really yeah they what that called water
bottle and they try to like flush out
whatever it is in your ear oh that's
like a do-it-yourself kind of thing but
in Austria like there's a doctor that
handles ears nose and throat it it
handles all these free things so
whenever my ear is like clogged because
I went too deep then I go there and they
just like do it professionally if you
have like a ear doctor you can have it
done there ENT is it the same overseas
like that is a doctor that handles all
free things yeah they handle the ear the
throat and the nose CU they're all
connected if you go doctor like that he
can do it but honestly if your ear is
not like actually clogged then I don't
think it makes sense to do it how can
you tell if your ear is clogged or not
oh you can tell I just can't hear
anymore like when you go too deep with a
cotton bud and you push it in then it's
too late and then you got to go a damn I
one of those scary that sounds
terrifying what like endoscope like
Bluetooth a blueooth oh yeah yeah the
little
thinging to put where in your ear and
you use it yeah do you get like a like
on the Bluetooth you get on your phone
like a picture yeah e like video oh my
god do you see what is in your ear I
want to see I want to see put your like
can you stream it I mean you probably
could can you Tech me because I don't
know if you saw before but during my 3D
debut time um I was getting sick and I
went to the doctor in Japan and they uh
went with a camera into my throat and
the picture that they took I post
they put it they put it through your
nose right yeah so in that Spirit how
about you take a picture of your inside
of your ear and post it
online no my ear is pretty clean that's
that's fine then show that case there
should be no shame and it's just that
it's like why that's such an intimate
part of
me they get to see like the deeper parts
of me and will you show me then I mean
your deeper Parts like my deeper Parts
you want to see inside her I want to
look inside you want to see inside
me only if you consent to letting me see
give me a Bluetooth connector thingy why
don't we play this amazing
game what a great idea too
late maybe Al we should give them some
space have some alone time
scho well that's amazing that you I'm
surprised that you bought that that's
fascinating oh we're little chickens
again
oh wait which one I'm H red right yeah
yeah don't get cooked cook the chicken
cook the chicken I cook the let's
go jump jump jump I am the king fire
fire light
fire fire fire why do I keep getting
poor cuz you suck oh
[Music]
wow try harder crony try
harder
tox
faster it I it
go yeah pretty good that was just good
good job IR I wanted so something better
I thought you were the poor one
today yeah I'm poor but I'm I'm I'm the
good kind of poor you
know y let's go go tartar
chicken there's two tartar chickens why
is oh okay the the point difference I oh
so you can lose as a tartar chicken too
yeah don't forget I'm an egg oh iris is
just a chicken I'm just a chicken is
that a chick that's a chick yeah that
doesn't look like a chicken cute and
takeing egg some rice and the rest is s
you know that's you know raw egg rice is
like the best thing
ever like soy sauce yeah it's quite okay
it's quite nice oh I like it too I I I
like it very much more more more
question okay will repeat then we can
redeem ourselves okay yeah okay no pee
PE this
time hide oh wait the pose is different
now oh no hide the Precious part
oh God but the movement how the how can
I even the movement is
so it's actually
difficult I am trying my best got this I
sorry guys I exposed your private parts
Chad wait did wait did they see it did
they see is that considered seeing I see
it I feel like I can see it
[Music]
[Applause]
well chat uh dear chickens sorry for
exposing you but you know we wanted to
say it I guess internally what do you
mean the graler what's that they gra oh
like B
okay ah what do we press it's a Japanese
workplace or what oh W I see it's like
don't
get oh my God I love this but when I
miss when they reach
the oh my God oh my God that's
crazy yeah dang she was right underneath
the chair oh my God that's amazing I had
no idea I was like maybe this is too
early but he slid through oh yeah yeah
yeah you got consider that you have to
press B we killed our bosses your gra
Master don't get a
master that's insane Bona Bona wait
isn't bonafide bonide is it Bonafide or
is it Bonafide I always said it as
Bonafide what it means is that it means
excellent yeah like amazing or just good
word you know
synon that suspense the other too stop
the
[Applause]
explosion what it's the bump diffusal
game wait I didn't look at the time
[\h__\h] what Minecraft there's a
[Music]
creeper ah you really got to pay so much
attention man yeah you got to look at
that counter B A chickens to
fry okay we had this before okay okay
this time is redemption Revenge
Redemption keyboard gang are they going
to do it are they going to do it or fail
again
Redemption Arc fall fall fall fall fall
fall
fall I hate I hate this I hate this a
lot
no
yeah oh the speed doesn't matter huh
yeah speed doesn't matter I mean there's
a timer we we had like a few seconds
left okay next time I'll take my time
yeah you can take your time crony was
doing it pretty slowly yeah she was
train ride death match grab the coins
thrown at you okay oh give me that give
me the big one give me the big one yeah
bro Chris needs it the
most they fell down never to be seen
again oh okay I guess I win by automatic
now oh do I yeah yeah you do unless I
die un you die I think you got to eat as
many coins as possible yeah if you guys
were still there but now see what your
Score says at the top Miss I just got to
survive I mean you're the you chicken
so it makes sense end it already it's
still 1 seconds of this you guys died
too early we died way too
early I can take my time I don't even
have to collect it it was just so
tempting as that they I know big coins
we'll probably get the game
again just
that was just good you need to be more
greedy I don't need to be more greedy
what
the it is my time to
shine go I am colored like a rainbow
you're ARB chicken I'm RGB chicken yes
gamer
chicken maybe in this game maybe I'm
only doing this collab to turn you all
into chickens to join my side join the
chicken side okay yes I'm going to
become to as well okay MERS like to work
at the fast food chain while also you
know chowing down on some fried chicken
cuz I am so yeah that's what everybody
does at kfp cannibalism cannibalism y
cannibalism I have a confession the H
dance is stucked in my brain since a few
days yeah only recently no like I I used
to like listen to it but now it's back
to my brain again if we do the math
pressed it you pressed it too early like
car math do you have to press it at like
100 or so uhoh because you're at no
that's too early I guess oh that was too
early that was way too early I don't
know cars
y why did you press it I don't know I me
clicked at least I didn't fall
off Fried
Chicken time to tell I can't Fried
Chicken
now when you break surrounded by Fried
Chicken what did it say uh stop at 100
100 what's
100 oh are you kidding me I to spam oh
God way I thought I had to mash I was so
prepared oh I see you f your press
Yourself Strong fingers D Irish
chees did you like count in your head
yeah I counted like basically just
counting down from 10 right yeah I was
try it at too but I was doing it too
bad drink it up Don't Spill any oh
water okay it it
oh that should be easy
right
okay we almost did
it oh wait you you got like the maximum
you it didn't spill though it didn't
spill that much almost
SP kind of style say when that's a lot
of alcohol that's what you said to me
and I didn't say I think it means like
say stop when you poured my water oh
same thing oh
yeah snowman Spirit make a head up ah
okay oh this one big is it supposed to
be oh you have to compare the
chicken a I got
it that's too
big that's probably too
[Music]
[Applause]
big it shows a red circle and you tried
to make it that big yeah yeah yeah I was
trying I failed too but yours was way
too big I mean we lost both so it's fine
it's fine you guys made the moon yeah oh
SCH three that moon was that a reference
to
Zelda
maybe did you guys do you guys know that
there there's next month there's a new
Zelda game coming up and you actually
play Zelda are you talking about the the
one the princess one
yeah I'm so [\h__\h] excited I love Zelda
games so much and the fact that you play
Zelda next time hello face hello hello
it's so hype oh my God it's going to be
cool it's already next month what's your
what's your favorite game so far from
Zelda breath of the wild breath of the
wild or the the sequel to breath of the
web yeah what it was called Tear tears
yeah tears I didn't enjoy the tears of
the Kingdom that much I as the I enjoyed
playing um whatam calling you know the
Wind Waker yeah I love Wind Waker I love
bullying the pigs and Wind Waker oh
that's cute I like Twilight Princess and
sky sword yeah sky sword is where they
actually get together that's because
skywood sword is like a lot of people
don't like it so much but I I also
played it on stream and I did like it
but I uh I I raged so hard at the motion
controls
oh they removed that for the switch so
that was good yeah okay it was terrible
for me I mean the game itself is fine
but the motion controls just ruined
everything oh it was terrible it was
terrible L the way but wind wer also is
like it always was my favorite for my
whole life but then I got to say TK
definitely was a special experience for
me bre of the wild too I mean I didn't I
only okay for breath of the wild don't
like judge me but uh I didn't cuz that
was before Holo I think uh so I didn't
play it but I watched a full play
through from start to finish 100% play
through like four or five times really
yeah from the same Creator because like
he did it like over and over again like
hard mode extreme
mode um and then I Tok I played on
stream and oh it's so good like oh my
God the puzzles were a little hard but
yeah I enjoyed it but I feel like the
the first one was very special for me
yeah I get that yeah when which one was
your first
one my first one uh breath of the W bre
of the your first one yeah yeah yeah
she's a Zelda newbie yeah yeah I'm a
newbie what was your
first ocarine of
time I mean I also played ocar off time
with my brother at first but I was still
too Babble so I don't really have many
memories of it and then Wind Waker was
more in my memory Wind Waker childhood
yeah I love this style too yeah me too I
think in the beginning when Wind Waker
first came out it like got a lot of hate
for the style but so many people like
grew to love it and it's actually very
Timeless yeah it's Timeless I want to I
want to go I want to play some Zelda
games yeah I so confused when she turned
into Zelda I was
like she looks so different yeah I was
like H she turns into what what like I
love her do wind wer HD was really nice
cuz they uh made it more realistic for
the lighting oh they did oh yeah good
stuff go play Wind Waker I will play it
it's so cute you got to play so many now
I have more time to play games so the
fact that you only play WF for the Wild
and TK yeah it you have so much to play
now all my time yeah yeah I know right I
will enjoy have fun okay thank you we're
going to play steam
chicken okay oh we're in sauna
oh 15 probably going to disappear it's
going to disappear it's definitely last
10 seconds 11
10 what did somebody stay
in stay in no okay I didn't see you
running we left oh damn it I got I got
up because everybody was leaving okay I
don't want to be alone in the sauna
anymore are you guys are you guys like
sauna I like steam SAA you like it yeah
steam SAA is good salt I like oh that
one's nice too I like it yeah like it
the sauna is a little too hot for
me yeah yeah right the steam is not as
hot but just really humid hum and it
feels like when you breathe in is just
good for your throat yeah it's nice yeah
so that's it's like a diffuser if you
had to choose between SAA and onen what
do you
choose 100% I mean I feel like most on
include SAA anyways yeah if you choose
onson yeah a like I'm an a wow look at
you go not the bravest of the
bunch uh not really I know that doesn't
seem like a compliment let's go when I
was a child I a little small child I
read I rid I rode an ostrich before Oh
really there's a picture of me riding
one a I didn't know you could ride them
yeah well if you're small ah but
wouldn't they like kind of like fling
around and try to get you off like I
feel like are they smart enough to be
able to like yeah they're PR it was
pretty chill stay still if you're just
small and like I'm it's not like I was
riding around like a marathon or so I
think we stayed pretty like chill in one
space one squ mostly but yeah that was a
child experience then again Donkey Kong
also wrote an ostrich we call Road an
ostrich was that an ostrich yeah it was
must have crushed it yeah I forgot what
that game was I know what you're talking
about country Yeah
country have you girls ever ridden an
animal that's like not a horse or so a
pony pony that's a horse a it's not a
horse it's a pony an elephant elephant
you R an elepant where the hell did you
ride an elephant oh in Bangkok
oh oh my God I want to touch an
elephant I hear they're really sweet and
nice did it sniff sniffer you oh yeah
yeah yeah oh you can give a banana and
like just I think it peeled it off grabs
with a trunk yeah yeah it was super cute
how did it feel to touch the the sniffer
sniffer did you touch the sniff sniffer
sniffer what kind of
weird leathery leathery right dry very
dry like dry
leathery dang I want to mingle with an
elephant one Dayne why'd you say it like
that I want to mingle with an
elephant that like with a baby elephant
specifically I see so many YouTube
videos of them like the baby elephant
like absolutely body slamming people
it's so cute SL body slamming people
yeah it would like gently right gently
gently it would like put all it's body
weight onto the human human be like ah
but at the same time they be having the
time of their lives cuz
it's I see have I written anything else
maybe I could I could ride a panther
right here right now
yes she I
bring right yay okay what's this ah the
chicken again okay
okay okay G
don't fall guys this time I'm not gonna
fall okay okay that sounds like a
flag so fast Iris can you turn on some
Euro beat
please shoot uh too early went too into
the
Euro the
cliff I totally thought I
pressed never mind okay cool cool
couldn't have waited even oh God this
okay this time this this one is I will
protect the peeee this time protect the
crotch I think this is a good
start okay and from that side that pose
is more helpful right
now okay
nice okay
okay
theab oh no spicy
wo PE
protected yeah privacy protected I am
yeah damn it C out too H okay don't get
bitten banana how do we do this what oh
we have to okay press the button when
they're really close okay oh oh what is
this thing on my that funny I think it's
poor Iris only has one crocodile
a
duck wow it seems like the Europeans are
kind of crazy in here a little
quirky We Don't Fear the crocodiles we
don't have you ever i' never seen a
crocodile in my life think we nether
maybe Florida you don't keep it that way
let's keep it that way you go to Florida
no that's good I think I will go to
Florida next year when GTA 6 comes out
really is actually is it actually coming
out next year of course I always say
it's coming out it's coming out now
believe them let's go Florida man don't
believe their Liv let's go okay this is
a new one too whistle while you save the
senior citizen stretch the robe okay
stretch the Rob what what do we just
hold ah tiny do we have to hold
it
uh is that okay did die oh oh because I
hit his head wait I don't know what
happened I I you I think you want to hit
the lowest goat without hitting his head
so maybe I think we'll probably get to
do it
again know what okay
um okay okay okay a no God Dam
it ah we're never going to have dinner
today
yummy damn it cook us some
Yu
y okay okay this time is great
[Applause]
even I was Brave though Iris what
happened you fell I fell through I used
up on my
no no no no next time for sure for sure
yes you're going to win for sure for
sure okay crocodile Zoo HD2 is that the
same I think the same one oh no there a
bit different they come from both sides
why am I a d this time we switched
switch
ruls so you have to make them come
closer right yeah you wait you wait and
then oh my God yours are so close
already
now oh my God
a b what the fck Yeah I'm sorry I just
want toze your game because I that came
all of a sudden yeah cuz like on all the
screen I just see several crocodiles so
I don't expect a freaking
leopard my technique I think it's
cheetah God damn it this again what are
you going to do with me huh
oh okay okay okay let me
be a
uh I'll stop here that isn't it too big
again trust
[Music]
me the beig here the
better I think that was a close call but
good job she the oh god oh this is the
one this one again okay this one a
Redemption Arc for real this time this
time I take my time
time this I
chill because the clouds also they
hide y y I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared I'm scared I'm scared I'm scared
what the [\h__\h] is huh
oh perfect
Redemption did
it did it we're learning character
development yeah wait don't
die charge your power twice and dig as
far as possible uh what charge power and
launch from afar I have no idea what
that mean we'll figure it out twice it
says
um what oh I see
okay oh it's just twice though yeah huh
oh yeah yeah yeah okay okay it but he W
that's so close what okay that was close
dang well the first time is always
difficult I have depth perception
perfect death perception
nice
like what
w
no I'm just cooking I hate
this can't do it I should be good at
this yeah get there can't you make
chicken first we all survived now we all
die beautiful we're so in sink
now she's not a panther she's an
austrich what what this is new what's
this what what I didn't read the like
scare them off before being attacked
yeah look back yeah
yeah Mommy
Mommy
no no oh that's scary didn't you today
play a horror game you should be like
into this right now you should be warmed
up that was actually
scary was actually you can never FNAF
what about oh no I'm never going to
final Freddy's ever
most horror of them all Final Fantasy
that Final Fantasy at Freddy's honestly
it it could be a title of a horror game
because like imagine the Final Fantasy
games didn't exist Final Destination is
a
horror right Final Fantasy just means
you're probably going to die so you're
never going to have fantasies ever again
so it could be a horror game bucket
time I thought it was because they were
going like close to being bankrupt Dam
it it no you got to PR earlier than you
think way earlier I never know the
timing for this cat snatcher the are you
gaming oh yeah pick up the ball of why
you guys spamming so hard like hurry up
next
game oh I
see supp to hide okay I didn't know the
controls for this get get the honey get
the honey Angry
Poo wait what okay I didn't get as close
as I wanted to but okay
oh one Japanese culture learn it or
die uh damn it didn't really pay
attention NE not too early damn it damn
it Dam
it okay dang okay then almost it works
for
me
me okay you guys were so good at this
last time it's just L yeah it's just lag
it's just lag
okay
ah can't eat spicy things as long as I
stay
alive
yeah a what the
hell no sabotaged it's okay
yeah damn it I guess you can just stop
now yeah she's so smart you could get
more points play safe one more one more
for the I did one more one more one more
one
more yeah I did I
did yeah wow amazing crony are you
winning this one you are oh
wow I am an
albatross I love some humus Yum Yum Yum
[Music]
Yum okay I think this is also we know
this one okay
car are we going different direction oh
yeah
Direction crashing oh no wait
what we don't want to crash so stop
before the crash okay it's getting
closer and
closer can barely see it
that was a little bit what if the other
one goes faster I guess we control
both
okay oh okay
nice I stopped after guys your car we
just going faster I guess it's different
in speed yeah I think it's for everyone
is different so we don't do the same
thing eye of the
chicken it's the eye of the chicken
drink it up drink it up pour me a
glass oh that tiny cup for crony
like why is mine always not visible it's
so rigged
okay so CL isy you're just too good why
is mine
not yeah they thought that she needed a
handicap she's too good you're too good
God damn even in the first
game you can show your cool side you you
can see for everything scandalous
oh okay got hide it again oh out come on
we had plenty of time to practice this
oh that that was close that was so
close
spicy okay okay
okay more perfect than that what the
H Miss how did you do that is a perfect
sh
now shape look like what like you hiding
a lot for him
yeah yeah you complimenting
him how did she do that teach me I don't
know I'm just good at the good at theing
the wiping you
knowand okay cro come on know how to do
that I like no no cheetah please oh
there are two now oh three there's no
right in this one
[Music]
please you I have to do it no no a
little too early I guess
yeah she tried to jump scare
[Applause]
[Music]
me I'm the only great one oh keep
jumping off the
edge I stuck at this I like this wine
Yoo what you guys are doing flips even
yeah a flips
good I want the great
too
Yes
W too early we
focus as long as I don't die
uhoh uhoh
[Music]
oh crazy crazy oh
crazy all like how we get we're we're
good we're good man damn that's hardcore
come on this is my oh
I I want to do good this
time some new titles too you're Raven
and there's some game files IL part
illegal and then nagya
kosin is that a type of chicken in Japan
I'm most part of the word never heard of
that before
delicious okay oh we have new questions
every time yeah excite eats oh is that
not oh okay okay I see delivery F on the
tires okay um not
[Music]
confident what what
how how do I flip you
hold
fall I'm scared
what wait that's okay yeah you landed
only on one tire okay I see how it is
follow order Pi up the spice oh sh is
this butt mashing I can't tell uh ah the
color I forgot what color it was already
I think it was Dad red I I like spise
you I forgot what color it was H it was
pretty red but not too red oh it depends
on the
person was really red it was pretty darn
red yeah I like
[\h__\h] I like the
spies yummy she's breathing Tabasco
that's what she's
doing yeah okay good job good job okay
we're doing this again what's cron cup
speed
oh you got a transparent
one
[Music]
where
[Applause]
come let's go I'm losing so many points
I'm not going to record for no if you go
work at kfp you will not work at the
drink counter and you will not work at
the yeah honestly nowhere because you
also make the curry too spicy like if
you don't be careful you know the the
customers are going to let me c you let
me cook you let me cook
no I can't people going to complain
listen it's okay pasta yeah I can make
pasta okay pasta how about pasta versus
Pizza which one do you like better to
make or to eat to eat I like pasta I
like
pasta I prefer Pizza oo pizza's good too
only only if the pizza is uh
um from Napoli yeah yeah yeahp it has to
be from Napoli because like once you eat
napoi pizza you realize that's the only
it's different is pizza supposed to be
thin crusted or is it supposed to be th
no very soft and thick yeah oh really
okay okay depends on the type I guess
but yeah na Pizza is best some pizzas
also make put cheese into the cross oh
they the cheese so yummy basically if
your pizza takes um like if they put it
into a thick Stone oven and it only
takes like 3 minutes or so to revive
then that's the right place yeah yeah
then they use the right an extra oven
like yeah yeah but if it takes like I
don't know 10 15 20 minutes to cook to
be in the oven that's no they don't have
the right
oven what ah
oh again oh thank she's pouring water
for
me oh that was too early okay yeah that
was too early ear for me too wow there a
small po over there crony for me water
she saw my cup was
empty I was just checking A+
service I think she loves
[Laughter]
me you love everybody though don't you
me no no oh no not I don't love everyone
but first and foremost you love yourself
love yourself that's
important okay a God damn it we got to
get good let's get some crazy scores
girls no
scope
yipp that's crazy how you get crazy you
getting very close to the
fire
yipp y
we're getting
there I'm so
scared I should just walk through the
firea I don't think we saw that before
this we no no no first time no one got
cooked before Oh
yeah what were you saying the whole
time I'm not trying to like say the
Korean word I'm like I think in some
language you say
that what does that mean op it means
brother right oh Opa Opa like or like
Senpai or something like not only
brother but also wait what is Opa no no
I was saying Opa I think it's like kind
of Greek Greek I hear it in Europe
sometimes have you never heard it I in
in Italy we say opla opla
opla I guess not OP I it's Greek it's oh
opla no I was saying Opa not with l oh
but she was you say opla Yeah in Italian
in Greek they say oppa it's a Greek
chair see that's what I got it
[Applause]
from how you say when when you know so
many languages uh ah MultiLing no no no
there was another another word genius
poly polyl no yeah
quadrilingual she that's a specific
number that's polyglot oh yeah polyot
yeah
yeah never heard
that learning new things it's po iris is
gaming I am gaming yes she we can never
beat Iris I know what are you talking
about lost a few times I lost a few
times a few times bring the bullet so
you
wipe this is not new no that's new I
don't know what what was it what was
yeah it's new oh wait this is legally
dis H that's yeah of course we just I
see we just
[Music]
DOD
huh what wait what did I press oh we
activated it too early I guess oh we
activate the bomb Oh what bomb where I
think we want to try to activate it in
the most clutch moment oh no what I
don't even see the ball what I was just
dodging you like explode yourself yeah
oh you're like self-destruct to um
destroy as many balls around you as
possible okay that's okay we learned by
doing chicken
quest and this one I don't really get
this but for now I'll just Attack Just
attack just try together the red line am
I the chicken or am I a
AA
you're I think oh my God four
damage uh I'm a AA yeah no don't kill me
don't kill me I yeah B can I die I died
I think oh
no I don't want to escape he looks like
what's the maximum damage you can
do he looks like the kid
[Music]
CR you and me we can go fight anything
together
RPG flying colors fly up toward the goal
what's this
okay mashing or wait what was the goal I
don't even oh uh the the bouquet I guess
ah I see no
[Applause]
oh naked nice why did she get naked
crony I don't know man because oh you
didn't catch the cloes yeah I was like I
wasn't sure what because it's a proposal
you want the the bouquet the clothes
everything before you meet the person
naked is also okay
CR maybe that's best it's
okay ball
snatcher and this one okay I thought one
okay
okay all right all right all right all
right
easy
no
yeah what's the what's the chances of
getting an exact same
score you're in sync even though you're
not even sitting next to each other
our souls are connected oh
wow
D Wasabi game again this time I don't
why do I always die first in this one
I'm going to be
[Music]
careful no what the
hell they cat control
ah why this is pure luck and Randomness
Okay so in my defense they were like two
wide and two soft so the red ones were o
oh I didn't realize it damn it oh my God
it's pure luck after you eat all the
other
stuff yay
I realiz was third one okay at least
everybody died
yeah
y nice
so close to my first
win no no it's
okay oh you never W bullet to not not I
don't think in the final she an actual
chicken I w't let you win she an actual
chicken okay now this remember use your
attack as late as possible
right this is like to project to
Mansion stin who's your favorite the
whole project character Che
oh mine maybe is
[Music]
Mara
okay you're common collected Iris I am
I not make it pretty okay okay I'm going
to get this deeper deeper deeper that's
what she said
much much can we get much
deeper no what you think it's like so
[Music]
much time to go to that doctor or use
your Bluetooth use your Bluetooth F heck
yeah blood all over I love that stream
it please
yeah okay okay ah ah the timer the time
what oh still so much
early I can't count clutch dang yeah at
least die pressure back for seconds oh
wait is this different eat as much Sushi
as you can pay for with your which Iris
can pay nothing for right now I will
need some want to be a begger no you
automatically
disqualified leave me the Sushi oh oh
it's probably going to go away
too wait how do I pick it up you have to
get the the cheaper one you just press
the button to pick it up what oh no I
can't see it anymore ah they hide the
pricing oh now no oh no I can't see you
I have no idea where I
[Applause]
am I can't tell what I'm eating oh
they're so expensive
now I can still oh oh so oh I still have
so much money really what I have so much
money I wait oh you
overend you overspend 11 that's what red
men I thought red was getting less
money okay Iris just uh as we expected
I'll pay I'll pay you guys back next
time okay okay not this time not this
time
ah you really got to spam it huh
yeah really I did not touch the lava I
think to get to close come on come on
come on come on end it
okay nice Dam
it good you guys
need the edge
impressive yeah
[Applause]
y good
job redeemed did everybody get a win now
yeah I think
so finally redeemed crazy mode unlocked
play is crazy mode all the game what
does that mean wait let me check
something we should do crazy mode ah
like ah from the beginning to the end
you go for all the games I think have
you already unlocked all the G game over
below 9,000 this a solo though ah never
mind never
mind I think that's just solo yeah wait
let me check this one I think this shows
the list oh oh we unlocked everything
there's certain ones where we never got
a good score like this one yeah cuz we
know we're too much we're too chicken
multiplayer only uhhuh uhuh is there not
oh some of them are just single player
what's did see the gold crazy and the
red Crazy M gold crazy is like top I
think gold is better
yeah oh let's try this on one more time
yeah yeah come on get deep wait don't go
too
deep let's make it gold
baby oh is using her real finger I going
in going in
okay your real finger didn't help did it
no you can't see oh wow yay
Len oh we got crazy here at almost clean
ear okay and maybe retry this one
yeah n this one was we only had it once
we can do better we can do better yeah
maybe get that
bouquet
no wow she the scoop I didn't even look
at the right screen I
Bo you got a golden I was like I missed
it we're not going to do it again again
I practice makes perfect okay please
please please please please please
please I want to marry I'm I'm ready to
marry okay okay that isn't this the
first dat
though oh my God you're dressed let's
gois where did you go I went somewhere
else I was not I was not going to deal
with it tonight no she can Wing
EOS okay oh we got a golden crazy on
that thanks to who did who did good you
no you somebody did really good yeah
these still don't have any markers but
we did did we did this one so often you
guys want to redo this one yeah yeah
that one we died too early you oh yeah
we did just once let's see second try
yeah train ride death
match okay
bounce
bounce oh God don't be too greedy guys
oh get on the top of each
[Music]
other I don't I need I need money I need
money oh you can
actually give me the money why you steal
all the money
oh I got no
money this is something for me
how many times can we jump I can't tell
feels like a million times I can we
share
money no whatever is yours is yours
whatever is hers is hers it's okay you
can kick her off kick her off I'm
kidding
psych I can so many times oh my
goodness mhm it's
okay that was crazy wouldn't you say
okay I think absolutely this one we did
a million times let just forget it
uh what's ah the landing
one scary one can we do the scary one
okay now it's okay we're all here to
protect you I don't even know what that
thing is what is that thing I don't
know he's so fast he's so
fast I feel like we could have done
better do that better
try again try again try
harder I'm so tired of scared oh that's
fast so fast oh my God it's
[Music]
faster still not good enough it's
hard no more we're so
scared we are we do not want to take
risks that's we play safe that's it oh
no really over here
no I don't know
[Music]
man who's done no he's just a drunk dude
let's go he's just a drunk I was still
Dodge him we
DOD thanks Iris you got me a nice crazy
here it's not a gold crazy but we'll
take it fine okay any other ones that
I want to read it out yeah what the hell
was that we random anime on TV yeah it's
the it's the yeah it's it's Heidi was so
popular in Italy Heidi always used I
think it's from Austria or from Germany
or so yeah I think so yeah
hiy how do you control this
D you press
a damn it God damn
it his head looks like a sheep supposed
to know it's
[Music]
it's is that really how the song goes
yep
oh and
shine come on Heidi don't hit him he has
done so much for
you go so close Corrections from
Switzerland
yeah again what's this dude's name again
Heidi hid no no the girl is hiding the
girl is hiding
Grandpa Grandpa surely he has a name
Grandpa John nobody cares about his name
hi I care wait the girl is not in the
back anymore for some of
us sing p Ah sing P goat Peter goat
Peter who oh that makes so much sense
why they put goats on his head because
his name is s Peter goat Peter cuz they
take care of goats in the
mountains that's why he put goats on him
crazy yes high five let's go y
go
saved oh yeah it's not Samaritan it's
Samaritan Sam oh that was like three
different pronunciations just
now I was satisfied with this or is
there anybody who wants to do redo one
anything like this one we only did one
to I didn't understand land on the tires
okay yeah okay and many many
spin I only did like
a
[Music]
spin
yeah I don't know I don't
know
what oh wow not satisfying only good
though damn it how many spins do you
need like 50 I guess right oh my God
[Music]
Yi
50 should be possible I'm scared I'm
scar
what that was close I think any more
than that is difficult though try one
more time one more time one okay I wants
to try hard I think I know I think I
know how to how to get a
crazy nice show us show us I'll show you
guys exactly how the mes spin
spin Dam it I chcken out damn
it it's so hard oh
my okay we can get it can we we can yes
we can believe believe the landing is so
difficult cuz you get so fast and you
got to get really kitty
[Music]
kitty 50 is the
[Applause]
go
great still great what the hell not at
all that's hard IR what do you think I I
don't know if I can do it better than
that you can you can that
was how many did you have 52 52 I'm
still let's try 5 Maybe May 55 55 maybe
55 could work I think it would be gold
right I would
say all right all right all run run run
run run run
run I guess Landing count Landing The
Landing yeah
[Music]
Landing let's go because her her engine
went
[Applause]
I think that's
enough was fun good job funny chicken
G you guys are so hungry I'm hungry too
I'm hungry too should go
[Applause]
eat I hope you girls had fun
I this little with me it was so fun it
was fun I haven't played a game like
this in like ages yeah yeah I like this
if you like this one there's a solo
version of it that you can play t Gama
one I like those kind of mini games very
you're so new you still have so many to
play like you could play the cookie Yi
game you know the cookie Yi game I
haven't played the cookie Yi game either
I haven't played it either what I was
like I would play like when I first
debut I was like I need to play this I
need to play this next kind of the time
they keep having sequels and everything
yeah the cuming game it's like I feel
like on the Japanese side like everybody
they're very you know and I think
there's three maybe now there's like
three or four to find out I'm surprised
you haven't played it because there's an
English version too so yeah it's easy to
understand something that just didn't
come up I guess it's about um like
reading the eror in specifically
Japanese culture situations like being
being considerate
I'm going to try now yeah I think I
will short game nice one one time stream
thing after four years I wish like
there's so many small games I I kept
like some for the future like I didn't
play all of them right away in the
beginning CU I felt like oh I'm going to
be here for a while I got to like space
it out I've been doing that but after
four years there's like you know a lack
of small oneoff games so every time a
new one comes out I'm I'm excited
yeah I I get you you end up just start
playing like long
series and that's what I've been like
purposefully doing from the start always
do have one long series running to fill
the schedule and you know always play
like one oneoff game M
yeah I will try so many games definitely
I have so much time now there's a lot of
games there's also the the other one
what you call it you know the one with
the finger um
oh my God yeah such a dumb joke the one
that's kind of like uh spicy like uh
it's such a dumb joke there's some like
they're all finger finger people
literally like shaped like
finger yeah yeah that was fun too I love
these kind of games yeah so we're going
to go eat now
guys thank you for watching this
interesting combination of people play
some chicken games it's so fun
thank you thank you for inviting us you
thanks for sitting on my bed now when I
sleep tonight in this bed it will smell
like all these cute girls all these cute
girls
but
s it's going to be a very warm bed oh
yeah warmed up preheated
bed okay maybe maybe we can do some off
goab again in the
future I've done anytime thank you
thank thank you and in German we
say well you Lou I say that again say it
again oh my God say it louder no you say
it so nicely really you say it so
German I
mean of course you did it well too Iris
I mean we're not Europeans so I remember
that German lesson though I remember the
PO and broster that's all I what the po
po butts and breasts
yeah that's the only thing you remember
yeah
dun dun yeah cuz I say that in in my
stream all the time for super
[Music]
chats oh coroni and Iris you didn't know
what that means what me I love you oh
really I've heard not I love you in
German
is in Italian
it's oh wow so much love in the
air she just looked
at I was I was looking if I was doing it
right Chad personal Chad you got to go
like some to yeah
some okay byebye guys
[Applause]
byee so yeah how was that was that fun
yeah yeah was I move your
Halo long I go still our stream is off
totally like we can uh talk privately
now okay no one's hearing us no one's
hearing absolutely no one what do you
guys want to what do you guys want treat
me after
that oh okay princess I I fried chicken
I am the poor princess that makes sense
Fried
Chicken makes sense okay bye okay bye
bye wait I M
[Music]