[Music]
for
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
K hello I'm maybe I'll do full screen
[Music]
actually k
we're going to play cute game today cute
game y w my comfort game my comfort zone
it may not be like a fotm or whatever
popular streaming game but I'm so up for
this because it looks so cute and I've
been craving some RPG stuff something
some cute
RPG maybe this can help me with my
craving you could say I was on a diet in
terms of RPGs as
well ever since we finished
Yakuza hello
[Music]
everybody always good to have a bit of
slice of what you want just a slice
just getting a slice
man man that's not
fair but okay it will be a big
slice or I'll take I'll I'll cut a slice
but I'll take everything that's not the
slice like I sliced it but then if you
take if you make a slice into a round
cake is the rest also a slice I would
say
yes the cut out of the slice the the
remainders in a way it's also a slice it
has been
sliced so by the fact that it has been
sliced it's also a slice because the
verb implies that it became a
slice
yeah
yeah I mean makes
sense but it's okay I can have a Big
Slice because today before the Stream
I did go on my running machine on my
treadmill I I first like
70 uh calories I burned walking and then
in the end I was
like just going to the last 30 calories
I'm going to burn running really
fast so I started running and it was so
[\h__\h] exhausting but I did it I did it
oh what I did it 100 uh calories Bur
before my stream that may sound like
nothing to some of you guys but you have
no idea how [\h__\h] exhausting this is
for
me I have no stamina whatsoever and also
my my machine is uh permanently
angled
tilted uh so uh like 5 minutes of
running feels like 5 minutes of running
up a hill yeah it's crazy it's always at
an incline
yeah but walking was pretty comfortable
uh I feel like I was able to walk
comfortably for a longer time today than
usual and I was watching some stuff I
figured out how to connect my Bluetooth
headphones to my
PC so I was watching on my PC with the
Bluetooth headphones something while
walking and running uh this way it was
not so [\h__\h] noisy and I could hear
clearly
but but the headphones also got a little
bit sweaty man because they're so thick
so now I think I finally under like
found one very very
reasonable reason of why you might want
to use
earbuds I get it when it comes to sports
I definitely get it I do have a few like
two pairs or so from different makers I
might try that out next
of course I wiped I wiped the headphones
afterwards but I noticed they they did
get pretty
sweaty um it's kind of hot so I'm going
to turn on I turned on the
fan I using Bluetooth earphones for
workout yeah makes
sense I'll buy those sweaty headphones
they the headphones themselves were
already pretty expensive so with my
sweat attached you know know it's going
to be very
expensive tissue paper between ears and
headphone that's just going to feel
weird
no have you played it or the others
before no I have not played any other
witch spring
games you blast my music at full power
nice yeah I I would do that too but my
uh the little speakers that I have
normally I always use headphones at my
PC constantly it was just recently that
I finally attached uh uh speakers for
the first time but those speakers
they're really not that powerful I think
they're also kind of being throttled by
the broadcaster for some reason um but
it doesn't get that loud so when I have
the the fan and the running machine on
then yeah the speakers get a little bit
drowned out and it's hard to hear so
yeah that's why I like bone conduction
headphones for exercise they don't cover
your ears and get
sweaty or go in your ears bone
conduction ah you mean is
it is it those ah aha oh they go around
the head in the back too I thought it
was
like H wait those are also B bone
conduction right the ones that don't
necessarily go around your head in the
back but just around your ear like in a
weird
shape those are both bone conduction I
guess not they have a weird name
man H I've tried these kind of uh
earphones before not the ones that go
around the whole head in the back but
the ones that like you know they look
like here let's let's show this the ones
that look like this I've tried before I
don't know why my app keeps on stopping
again today tried these before but
uh different brand but they were like it
was impossible to get them in or around
my ear it was like how the [\h__\h] does
this
[Laughter]
work it looks relatively simple but
sometimes these things are [\h__\h]
weird oh yeah one more thing I noticed
why am I yapping so much about audio
right now one more thing I noticed uh
when I uh Conn conected the Bluetooth
headphones to my broadcaster I thought
because these are really nice headphones
that I could maybe use them for the
stream today but then I realized no
because the broadcaster when you connect
Bluetooth speakers or Bluetooth uh
Bluetooth uh headphones it will have
quite the delay on The Voice and I could
turn off the monitor of my microphone um
but that not that's not that's not good
for me
so I'd either have to mute it or or just
hear myself double all the time it's
kind of kind of sucks
so daily or three times a week h i i i
want to go
daily but I now I didn't go for two days
but before the two days I went two days
in a row and then two days no and then
today I went again well ideally I wanted
to go yesterday too on my treadmill
uh but yeah I'm I'm aiming for
daily if your ears are perfect I believe
you can try if my ears are perfect
either open ear earbuds or bone
conduction if my what do you mean the
shape of my ears or my
hearing of course my ears are perfect of
course look at those anime
ears okay we're going to play uh wait I
think though we probably might want to
use a roller
this my Bluetooth
adapter can
go
attach
controller
probably probably
preferable okay masar
so this is like 20 hours or so we might
if we want to finish it we could do it
in like three parts or so let's see
where we can go with
this which spring
are
ha cute
music let's go that [\h__\h] bird fat
bird friend
shaped girl cute look at her legs the
way she lifts her legs is so
cute it's kind of robotic
almost weird cute I'm in love
[Music]
already UPS I was supposed to press here
uh probably sfx usually loud voice
language uh oh Japanese or Korean is
this a Korean
[Music]
game oh oh yes that's the one thanks bro
wait you can use Nintendo switch
controllers oh this a Korean
[Music]
game okay new beginning here we go shall
we start a new story yeah maybe maybe we
get a nice cut scene so I'll make myself
smaller I don't know how what what we
what to
expect
small I'll be here
oh what there's so many
modes very hard uh probably normal cuz
you guys are going to be
like but do easy you do not need to
invest too much time in growth to
progress through the game moderate
growth is enough to make turn-based
combat unique and
fun
oh
ooh have their stats increased most boss
of the enemies ENC counted story will be
stronger o no
normal nor okay I saw tatto she let's go
wait what I can choose things here later
maybe so
cute oh
rainbow in the beginning they were gods
they brought rain for
Humanity and would sometimes even return
the dead to
life understandably the humans came to
worship them and served them with
wholehearted
devotion as they
do however
in time this
reverence warped into a craving and
desire for their
power
W I Want It
All who's saying
that the people for 600
years humans hid their first behind awe
and praise until one
day they finally discovered the
source of divine power Majestic might
even
say we too can become Gods [\h__\h]
yeah become as
God how humans slaughtered the gods they
once worshiped and they were much of a
god were they branding them demons and
stripped of all their
power how did they have that power to
kill a
god new nations and religions were
founded and like their predecessors they
performed countless Miracles and
wonders nothing seemed to have
changed except that the gods were now
gone a Godless
world but at some point
there began to be Offspring born of
demons and
humans so the original gods or wait did
they mean that the humans became demons
not the gods these demonic Offspring
came to be known as wites I thought so
and were swiftly killed at Birth or
abandoned in the Deport so we play one
of
those but those witches who
survived demon is God right yeah were
forced to defend themselves from witch
Hunters
and grew even stronger as a result
o interesting I like it so far early to
say but I like the the predicament that
we are
in so cute I want to
cry this is like the best [\h__\h]
visuals I could ask
[Music]
for p
I'm was so happy
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry oh my the thing in the background
I think it ate some dust or something
wow it's like a vacuum cleaner it's like
a Roomba but
cuter
n it's so cute if I thought you stubbed
your toe you should always be out tabbed
into my window
always be wary of possible stubbings of
toes it's
cleaning okay sorry I'm so excited it's
so cute is it fully
[Music]
voice got to got to become oh oh oh she
changed cloth
oh it's her main outfit without the big
cape and the big hat is she like a bunny
she's got like lop lop floppy flop
floppy what do you call these bunnies
with the ears Down
Lop I'm still stuck in the dark back
it's
good L yeah Lop ear yeah yeah L ear
shall We Gather ingredients first okay
hey use blah blah blah uh select the
leave button and press the X
key oh to leave the menu you mean oh to
leave ah to leave
home okay go outside
oh even the menu is
beautiful she's so
cute can oh my
mouse collectors of pies and
strawberries me too I'm that too I'm the
same I'm the same that's
[Music]
me
uh Gathering tool materials I'm all out
of tools to fight the Warriors I need
rabbit meat even though she's a bunny
herself a rabbit
[Music]
and leaves to craft leaves to craft a
healing potion I should start with
collecting leaves and I guess the bunny
meat we can just get from ourselves huh
oh I like the this
Overworld view hand will be
displayed
oh
oh so
good what's this
crispy crispy dry leaves oh oh smooth
the
water the water looks so good are you
seeing
this oh K it look
South where's
South uh
Australia yeah can I jump oh
uh not at the moment maybe I'll still
learn it oh it's respawning it even
shows me the
[Music]
time hey I love this I'm going to play
it until the
end look how she smoothly runs over the
stones wow okay not over this one this
one's too big that's fun that's fun I
love this
tree it's such a nice tree
I'm so excited oh my God this is
cute oh there's a some weird tur oh I
can go into the water hello are you to
be fought and destroyed and
killed and the way she runs the tip T
tip T tip it's so
cute cute
[Music]
oh oh
water guys this is a good game look how
the water is like
V reacting to my head being
there what what was that oh
okay yeah it's interacting with
me is this considered an indie game heyo
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Vault a giant white Golem blocking the
entrance to Black witch's
Forest that
leaf the leaf that's covering his navl
it's like usually the leaf you put a
little bit lower but he doesn't have
anything to cover down there I guess
maybe he's more embarrassed about his
Naval yeah I like the the isometric view
as
well I can't turn the camera but I like
it I like that it's fixed like this but
it's not just like left and right I can
go like everywhere I like it so wait uh
we happy
[Music]
okay we going to find it oh is it in
there
I must kill my
brend rabbit hunting now I just need to
collect rabbit me to make R I can catch
some rabbits while running around in the
forest welcome to the rabbit press R2
button and create uh an enchanted Arrow
ooh and release it to fire it
R2
[Music]
wao what what
oh oh oh okay I need to have the
prompt coming
up
interesting oh then I actually have to
[Music]
aim this is so
good this is my new favorite
[Music]
game this is W through and through guys
oh my God what a what an amazing
[Music]
game
oh do I really need to go for the sticky
swamp I know it's just like checking out
that structure over there we don't have
to cute I've never seen you this
happy I know I'm kind of extremely happy
man I don't [\h__\h] know what it is it's
just so good actions
button craft
button spell book oh it's so
beautiful
oh guys tell the developers and the
Publishers how much I love their game
please
okay recover 60 HP and 80 MP remaining
MP recovery free turns uhhuh
okay uh set it to
free uhhuh and start
crafting look at those weirdos why they
look kind of like what their eyes why
they look like I don't know like Muppets
or
so when you craft a recover a potion or
combat tool free your or more times you
will Master it every time you craft a
master tool you can receive times too
oh if there's an option to put on
different cute outfits
yeah yeah and I think there might be all
right now I don't need to worry about
running out of healing potion next up is
oh
[Music]
earthquake fight proper fight oh my
books went back into the
bookshelf is it an animal I should check
it out did you guys see just
now oh someone's knocking at my
door the
Beast Chicken Soup for the Soul who the
[\h__\h] was knocking on my
[Music]
door oh okay what do you want oh just
just because I'm a witch leave me
alone I'm a good witch I'm just mining
my own
[Music]
business my house design is so cute too
oh my God
[Music]
Spanish
Inquisition
what
what she she has that women's intuition
she knew it probably she's getting
hunted every day bring it
on oh oh is it is it uh aha is it
actually turn
based but then when I'm hunting Mater
materials and animals from materials
it's just like just shoot it on the go
interesting just two two like ways of
fighting um press magic slab to use
magic currently have free orb flame
Circle engraved on major slab press
major
slab oh it's is this AOE I think it's
AOE yeah try targeting so the two or
more Warriors are in the Magic's
range
okay let's
go what the [\h__\h] one of the Warriors
attacks missed pberry will automatically
Counterattack with a physical attack
against the enemy whose attack missed oh
really
yeah good job
pberry the turn bonus icon is completely
blue while this icon is blue pberry
gains a turn bonus for knocking down an
enemy with a physical attack by the way
music is
[Music]
banging but I just forgot what it just
said but uh okay physical attack
basically when that icon is blue as
should do a physical attack is that what
it said The more times pberry swings her
staff the longer the turn bonus cool
down now pberry can knock down enemies
with swing
how
many how much damage will it
[Music]
do let's try him first
32 oh P has gained a turn bonus by
defeating an enemy with a physical
attack oh once P's turn bonus gge is
full again turn bonus can be
triggered okay so I get another
turn nice
the UI bucked was where
where a strategic crit while it is in
state all attacks have 100% chance of
being a crit oh triggered every four
turns wait magic attacks or no okay
every attack
maybe wow I got a I got a pie from
my what I what I do collect the pies
yeah and what about the bodies will we
collect those
too oh oh she's doing it on her own
collecting the
[Music]
pies she's so cute I'm going to die I
might die guys maybe I cannot finish
this game cuz I'm going to die but then
I'll just revive again cuz I'm a phoenix
that's
okay Warrior clean up Warriors are at my
door this is dangerous I should deal
with the Warriors in the forest
first didn't I just do that or did it
say uh that's what I just cleared like
the quest so to say weapon stimulation
before activation after activation uhuh
when you attempt a physical attack the
physical stimulus applied to your weapon
triggers an instant powerful burst of
magic triggers once every for strikes
uhhuh okay so it just happens
automatically
[Music]
right just got to keep on Reviving oh
what's this oh it healed me recovery
Stone recovery Stones absorb the energy
of their surroundings over time this
energy turns into beneficial magic that
restores HP and MP when absorbed the
Magic in the recovery Stone will be
replenished when you return after
traveling to another area
n
interesting now let's fight again oh I
can choose actually if I want to fight
or
not let's go let's do
it tools can be used to restore HP
defense when defending the amount of
damage received from enemies is
increased a decreased I can't read on
the first turn after the some HP and MP
is recovered okay uh oh really I got a
little bit back
n so let's get AOE going
[Music]
here I want to go up
up yeah that only covers two so
close good one though ow ow ow bullying
is not good
double swing let's try this do I get
like do I get to attack two of
[Music]
them no it's one
okay oh one died what what did he die
from oh the fire damage
W and I just attacked back to that guy
probably because he missed
[Music]
oh he moved he's not in his usual spot
oh he's cleaning it up thank
[Music]
you oh thank you
B oh yeah my pie what about my pie
berry pie please give
me I've had this game in my steam wishes
for a pretty long time glad you're
playing it so I can finally decide yeah
uh your decision must have been made by
now right because this is amazing
[Music]
he
does maybe that's his way of hugging me
I don't
[Music]
know oh are there are there different
kind of Golems here that are nicer or
more evil
[Music]
oh thinking think
think yeah wow
easy easy
[Music]
conclusion we just become so powerful
that with one Firebolt we can destroy
the whole
earth not that we would do it but we
just want to get that strong here too
many warriors for B to handle this is
dangerous I should go home and train for
the first time in a while I can train at
home at
home wao what's
this cute pap fish
Spike and there was another one in the
back was too far I guess or it was just
like
decorative fishing yeah this fishing I I
like this type of
fishing
oh cuz I just have to shoot as long as
my aim is
good then I can get the fish
nice names and effects are not on the
character uhhuh is that always like this
or is it uh in only at like right now
I'm like unlucky or
so Pro tip collect literally anything
yeah that's what I'm trying pberry can
currently train four times the number of
times pberry can train naturally
increases as time
passes
oh
actions train just like me for real for
real it's like level up skill ah which
a oh hi chunky wonky what are you doing
here oh she's so cute she's like oh
you're a witch now a witch has to have
her cat on her side you're so right
chunky wonky you're so right you're the
perfect witch
cat she
[Music]
okay I picked up chunky wonky because
she did a flop and she didn't run away
what's wrong you want my love so
much she's such a
baby okay uh HP the higher your max HP
the more damage you can withstand from
enemies oh yeah okay this is just basic
yeah turn page magic increases the power
of your magic attack uh higher strength
increases the power of your physical
attack and counter attack giving you an
advantage in gaining turn bonus defense
yeah decrease damage by up to 75
decrease H did I read increase
again AGI a guility turn cycle quickly
during combat or W up to two cons cons
consecutive turns wao enemy attacks have
been increased have an increased chance
of missing
uh here chuny wony sit behind the
monitor I know you want it I know you
want to be there
yeah okay oh oh no she's
leaving that's fine I got some some
flufficious
gropes in
uh increases the power of counter attack
up to 200%
woo
H I wonder what's the
best M training plan use ad training to
fill out pie Berry's training schedule
so I level in my house instead of
[Music]
outside interesting cute when pberry
starts training a mini game will
randomly start mini game
for
leveling you can practice the mini game
before hand if you do not want to play
mini game you can select autoplay mode
at the start of the training uhhuh fill
up pieber training
schedule oopsy that was by
accident oh cute this is like we fit
Adventure or a ring fit Adventure or
refit or whatever like all of those
hitting rocks hitting wood swimming
pushups
reading how what's what if it's a mini
game what do I get to do like flip the
pages
meditation so this is probably for MP
because it's blue oh no wait
no ah this is for
MP oh oh this one gives me free but like
less of them each of them
12 oh all this like for all of them
balanced magic
training almost all of them actually
yeah better practice
[Music]
first
okay
easy uh CL count uh This Way took me a
while oh
that's how that
works oh my God difficult okay that
seems to be the gist of it I don't know
maybe we'll do one of these cuz they can
it trains quite a bit of it and I'm
still not sure what exactly I'll be
needing maybe later on when we fight
more we'll notice ah okay I want a
little bit more HP or
so I don't know for sure yet so for now
we'll do this and then we need the
defense and the
agility
a maybe we'll do the
push-ups I'll be
fine push-ups and the
running and then oh I still can do
another
[Music]
one maybe this one
I'll be fine I don't need to
practice soon regretting
spaghetti okay I I'll I I'll try try
your luck in a mini game by choosing
train if successful you will earn a
higher bonus than autoplay if you have
multiple training sessions scheduled one
of wait but what if I do badly at the
training I still get like the promised
stats but not no bonus I
suppose oh oh do I not have to do all of
them this one I actually practiced
nice is it just
random
[Music]
nice
nice uh
[Music]
clockwise that was close
nice I did okay it's just one of them
and out of all of them it chose the one
that I did practice oh I'm so lucky
yeah oh this is so cute this is a nice
way to train to level I like
it and you can choose the stats
yourself oh I work so
[Music]
hard I have to
sleep press the X actions and then X and
then sleep button huh what else do we
have combined toolbox weapon Evolution
pet
pet it's getting better it's getting
better and better or do that does it
mean my room Buzz or
what use up all your trainings as soon
as possible but could I have done more
now before sleeping
[Music]
oh my God she's me she's
me
[Music]
W me
too she's so hungry in her dreams
[Music]
oh man thanks for the Super
Chat you got some cake sitting in the
fridge
hey share
[Music]
chuny wony came back maybe she likes my
sounds my excitement what's
wrong what what do you mean oh oh are
there not so many Kibbles left that
could be can I check I think there might
be a lack of kipples
[Music]
he
I think I think that was indeed her
[Music]
problem cat wants pie
too I love how cute the MC is for real
for real
[Music]
there's like a certain amount of like
forced cuteness where I'm like oh that's
[\h__\h] cringe that annoys me but I love
her because she's my spirit animal right
now I love her she makes me happy this
game makes me
happy fruits of training time to check
the result of my training I should
search the forest for any leftover
Warriors okay that means I have to leave
but can
I train again
[Music]
what does the the what does the orange
and the red stuff
mean do you guys know who played this
game when when the you need train points
aha oh it's recharging yeah okay I
thought so because it also says zero out
of
[Music]
zero they wait for me in the forest
maybe they just haven't in my house yet
maybe they're still looking for me you
know go outside yes touch some grass
let's
go I could see her be lifted from like a
peer free era at your title lifted as
then you just think she's like she fits
into that kind of game yeah if you use a
magic slap on the previous turn some of
its energy will remain in your
weapon attempting a physical attack
while it in this state causes an
explosion based on the power of the last
magic spell you Ed so it's like
recommendable to follow up a magic
attack with a physical
[Music]
attack where are the fishies oh no no no
here got to get the
fishes
nice just got to get all the materials
too
somebody said I should
ah
[\h__\h] somebody said I should get all the
M like as much as possible and I'm
guessing that person played the game so
maybe there's like
a like yeah maybe there's a lack of
materials a little bit who
[Music]
knows oh chunky won's back maybe that
maybe she's just like feeling like being
around me
try shooting the fish I
did
hey what's wrong she's so
cute it wouldn't say there's a lack but
you can never have enough okay it's good
if there's no lack also I see that
there's a timer so if I don't shoot it
like within 7 Seconds it seems like it's
going to like I'm going to lose my
chance
oh a
where' you get
[Music]
from I me my cat just now by the way but
the girl is cute
[Music]
too trap what they you you say you being
sent here was a
trap
[Music]
for do you guys know how many people
have killed already you should not be
asking for
trouble y I did that
we take the credit okay yeah I'll be
taking credit card for this interaction
that you'll be enjoying fly
fly nice big damage can I block with
like I'm trying to block with with with
uh circle like I'm in a Yakuza game
[Music]
M
explosion
[Music]
exposion muscle memory they just
wondering you know maybe this game has
this feature too you never know you
never
know TR bonus let's
go
easy it's a turn based game yeah this
kind of combat is the turnbas
[Music]
yes pie hunting is what we were doing is
what we're doing every day
[Music]
man the [\h__\h]
scam chonky wonky laid
down next to the treadmill I've noticed
smovie likes to uh lie down on the
treadmill now whenever I'm in my office
where the treadmill is she lies down on
there now and chunky wonky likes to rub
her face against some parts of the
treadmill and now she's just like
chilling next to it you know my cats
normally don't chill in the same room
where I'm streaming actively so this is
very fascinating to
me she's so cute I found
something
for this is not a warrior
D [\h__\h] mustach wait that just looks
like coron
Senai is this coron Senai in a Zelda uh
Zelda Link
Cosplay because I just today I saw one
of coron's thumbnails where I think it
was coronai with uh a mustach exactly
like that and brown hair so you
[Music]
know well I'll show you
the way she talks in Japanese man she's
like
[Music]
oh I knew I knew you you were going to
trade with me the Korean voices yeah I'm
kind of curious about that
too I can get scammed so easily with pie
I mean this girl but me too I guess
I'm going to naively give you a [\h__\h]
Diamond that I just fought in exchange
for one slice of
pie you have it of course he has it a
yo yes yes it looks so good oh I already
ate it okay yum yum yum yum yum yum I am
infed by the Delicious Pie yes I
[Music]
am
I
yummy well okay I don't know what that
Jewel does as long as I don't know I
think I'm fine with giving you it while
I get some
pie
for oh my God she's so childish holy
[\h__\h] you imagine she's a freaking
descendant of a God and acts like this
[Music]
H guess she's like what 10 11 she looks
really young she's so
small yeah please tell me I'd like to
see more of the world of this beautiful
world
[Music]
an earthquake disturbing my pie moment
oh
it's
no oh he threw out the traitor as
[Music]
well no my life is so over
stupid pudding pudding cave is there
pudding in there first pie now pudding
not a big pudding fan but okay let check
it out could be interesting could be
good well never be a replacement for p
though Warriors are in the puding cave
maybe they'll attack my house soon this
time I'll be the one who does the
ambushing time to go why are you hunting
in the Ping cave
okay
nice oh no I missed the bunny I ran into
it okay here we go pudding
cave okay they look like uh yeah jelly
pudding
[Music]
she is so cute how can she be so cute
guys I don't get
it I'm going to adopt her I think I will
I
will also Publishers if you need uh
English voice actors for an English
voice over hire
me I want to be involved in this amazing
[Music]
game oh oh [\h__\h] I accident
what's
this no AR are currently accessible
okay okay cannot fall down that's
good yes Leaf pudding pudding made of M
and jelly with a scent like fresh
leaves here we go is there
Elementary um you know the
reactions it's Elementary in it oh my
God to
two references moss and Elementary in a
row can you believe
it sorry we did English speakers not my
speakers
hey hey
yo let's do the two first before
the the four and then heal probably and
then attack the
four that's a plan if I've ever heard a
[Music]
plan she
says like it's my turn but it also
little bit sounds like D It's My
Pie wait let me fight this one as well
first still have a bunch of HP Min
maxing the
[Music]
healing he also has a nice little witch
hat maybe friend not
[Music]
F wait I'm
ding what's up what the
[\h__\h]
uh nice that they let me retry it uh
holy [\h__\h] I I underestimated how strong
this bastard would
[Music]
be
a this is not AOE I guess but it's
actually stronger than the AOE
one I guess I could heal what the [\h__\h]
is pet
okay recover birdie recover 60 let's
recover
60 yeah train spe that's you see that's
exactly what I needed to
[Music]
learn needed to go out to understand
what stats I might be
needing strategic crit
here we go eat this bastard W
[Music]
cute cute he's almost dead let's go damn
he's strong though not to be
underestimated now he even got a double
turn but we might be able to kill him
with this one last
[Music]
hit
wow what's this did he drop
something okay my my mp are full but my
HP is so dead let's
heal I'll do these
two yeah he left like the tip of his
[Music]
body we
again
Y no not y not Y at all
[Music]
turn B let's
go I like it you can see collectibles on
the mini map yeah yeah yeah
yeah but they glow so nicely I feel like
it's hard to miss them anyway
[Music]
three of
them wo wo wo
[Music]
wo I wonder the pet like when are we
getting it what is it going to be like
is it going to be cute
[Music]
going to be a
cat that would be most delightful
patience yes I have to be
[Music]
patient she's so cute she's so cute
she's so
cute okay should we find another one of
these they're so strong
[Music]
[Applause]
got to keep a good eye on my HP and then
we'll be possibly
[Music]
fine okay uh y now I need to heal
I guess we can do
[Music]
another nice
damage dude so bulky for real even
though he's just jelly but maybe that's
what makes him so
[Music]
bulky this should kill
yeah oh this is hat it just looks like
like because part of the hat is like in
the ground it looked like it was just
the tip of it this is it is his full hat
oh I see what's going on
here it's like it's
[Music]
breathing oh
no okay I thought so let's not touch the
water but this is not going to respawn
anytime soon huh only if I leave the map
okay
wait puzzle in progress what do you mean
puzzle in progress there's a path here
too
materials wao that's a lot of them and
it's so many I don't know about fighting
them maybe I'll enter that door first
the the the path a Crossing the water is
a
puzzle not much of a puzzle it's not so
little of a puzzle that it's puzzling
me
[Music]
yeah oh there
is heal point and this looks like there
might be the a boss
oh look what I can do with the map
yeah I'm thinking there's a boss there
but actually the map is showing much
more so maybe not the boss over
there it's so smooth
[Music]
too wait does AO skip um not skip the
conversation but
because behind me there's an Autos skip
uh prompt but just move on to the next
prompt without me having to press X let
me
try yeah seems like
it okay good
good you have 30 hours in this game you
didn't know you could do that I just
accidentally found out damn 30 hours are
you like trying to do 100% on
everything or
what how did you get 30
hours playing
normally fight fight fight
fight H can't hit them with the AOE okay
then we'll do a singular
one Google set is like
20 around 20 hours if you don't try to
100% everything
[Music]
might have fallen asleep while playing
what not hold that explains a little
bit
swing normal swing train
bonus but wait is the crit yeah the crit
is on that too yeah yeah yeah yeah
create
bonus he's gone now I
think let's do basic
slab basic slab why is it called
slab slab I just think of Minecraft
slabs weird
[Music]
are they lying to me or is this
true magic stone slab oh like a
uhuh yeah she was using like kind of a
kind of stone in that cut
scene may think they be ly
[Music]
the white oh I know what he's going to
do he's just going to eat you out and
you're going to die from the
impact maybe it's just a trainer again
there's a pie caring Warrior allegedly
wandering around the pudding C I need to
find ah it's okay I'm excited for the
pie can we activate
it ni
teleportation alar
activ tort yep yep okay I get it I get
it thank you aged Leaf pudding slice
Leaf
ping yummy question
mark oh
what it's a jelly carrying a helmet from
a
[Music]
warrior that is kind of adorable and
recycling those helmets is very very uh
nice to the to the Eco system I don't
know
oh I can get all of them I think
y 200 hp holy [\h__\h] wait a [\h__\h] second
let's get the tiny mobs to die fast oh
oh dear oh dear I might need to heal uh
although wait is it my turn then one of
their turns and then I get a double turn
no wait it's the other way around I'm on
the bottom right I thought it was going
from left to right but going from right
to
left I I kind of need to heal I think
otherwise I'll
die oh wait I get to attack too
[Music]
oh okay just a big one
left get turn bonus if I kill one of
them
oh wait that was easier to I
huh she thinks about nothing
else the [\h__\h] he
looks he looks that kind of mustard
style I don't know looks Spanish
or yeah maybe
Spanish uh Alfred
a Warrior from laak Village oh that went
way too
[Music]
fast I called the
Spanish yeah I kind of did where he's
Italian yeah yeah okay tell I can see
that too
well give it a
try how does she know to jump I don't
know how to
jump ooh direct followup fight oh
[Music]
no what how little HP did he have
also can someone make a a prop for me of
her cape and maybe her ears and maybe
her hat or just one of those things I
didn't think it would be so cute please
please for next stream please somebody
who's
talented I need I need Cape or ears or
hat or
all yeah
I
could if I if I if I need to I could
like make like maybe the ears myself or
so but maybe someone wants to make
it basically the the whole
outfit say no more someone will do it y
wait he really had a bag full of
Pies really
[Music]
what wait these people also it seems
like I'm not the only one who likes
pies feel like the whole world in this
game likes
pies wa mind control circle plus one
another slap or what higher magic that
controls your oppon mind effective
against beasts but rarely works against
rational
[Music]
humans oh I'm being kicked
out oh
[Music]
damn
for wait I just realized her
hairstyle that's
[Music]
cute she has like a side high ponytail
that's
like standing up on its own and looks
like a brush or so or like honestly
together with the with the ribbon it
looks like a flower
somehow that's
cute looks like a spare tip yeah maybe
yeah oh wait if I look at the character
art on the right she still has that even
with the hat
on so the Hat has a hole for her
hair nice
[Music]
so only one brain cell beings can be
mind controlled I know that for a fact
yes yes looks at
[Music]
chat she's very specific about what I
can use this on
[Music]
maybe that thing in the pond let's try
mind control animals sometimes appear
nearby I should try and mind control any
that looks oh okay maybe it wasn't the
big thing but okay uh can I
make some
more H spell H there are these are the
books from the shelf and now they're not
in the Shelf
[Music]
oh you can register an autograft from
the tool information window by clicking
VI if P has enough
tools whenever pberry oh I would like to
maybe do that
maybe for now I'll still do it on my own
wait where
is where is RTO I guess it's in the
other
one oh okay
360 HP
Recovery oh
notar I can make both of
these several of these 360 that's kind
of Overkill actually right
now oh I'd like to make more of these
but I don't have that much
meat yeah can only make four
[Music]
okay but I'll still make a couple of the
of these ones the leaf pudding
extracts just so that we have something
at hand
it's I really like this game me
[Music]
too they should have sponsored me but no
I guess not because I would have played
it anyway but still I would have been so
good at promoting it I'm already good at
promoting it
okay so now I probably should train
what's this
though beginner's wizard staff perform
this weapon can be evolved without the
essential ingred is game going to tell
me about this later on maybe cannot use
ah okay maybe
yeah
okay
oh wait they didn't tell me to sleep yet
right they told me to go outside so
maybe it's not time to train yet
[Music]
got this game during the winter sale
yeah me too
right cuz I had it in my Steam for a
while and then you know I wasn't really
rushing to play it but I uh requested
permission a while
ago and then it was granded I was like
okay well I'm not still not rushing to
play it but thanks
and here we
are okay this mind control thing I
thought it was a skill for battle but
it's probably
[Music]
not that fat cute
bird carrying a whole freaking pig
yeah that tiny friend shaped round fat
bird supposed to carry
me well be careful you almost burned the
the the the the the
bird Dam
it it's kind of cute this some wild
boore is what I think it is
[Music]
what I'm going to ride on
it oh no okay oh is possible to mind
control his opponent find out if mind
control is possible for the option
before the combat starts or even through
or through event dialog if the enemy's
HP is 30% or below you can attempt to
mind control them first keep attacking
until the enemy's HP is 30% or
below okay I hope I don't kill
it
uhhuh maybe a normal hit after
[Music]
that what almost killed it use mind
control
how
wait okay it seems to be C that
one one HP cuz I almost killed it at
this point the Mind Control matches
Circle will blink next to the target's
HP when you use mind control Magic on
the target you have a chance to turn
them into a pet once they become a pet
the target can be summoned and utilized
anytime press magic
SL individual magic
circle you have't combined on the slab
the slab has no effect if you refer to
use any magic circles you possess a slap
has no effect
[Music]
oh it also uses
MP
who I got the B meat too even though so
I killed it and but I'm also hiring it
as a pet
interesting killed board Junior they
have like enemy character art too a
little wild board caught in mind
controlled by pberry that sounds like
I'm kind of
evil Bor senior
next no let me collect
things pyber can summon a pet while
exploring press the triangle button to
bring up the field menu oh
pet the pet window allows you to manage
your acquired Pets the pet you just
acquire quiet board unit will now appear
in the list how many can I acquire at
once AO is there a limit summon
sh it's a rideable pet press square to
ride not like I really needed to be
Speedy in this little area but thanks
rable pets can differ in the terrain
they can Traverse and their speed ah
there must be rable pets for the
water all the board let's see if my
control works I'll ride the bo home and
make sure it has a place to sleep inside
No but wait thank
you thank you can I oh can I pull from
here oh while
riding
wo that's so
good head
shot boom head shot ah [\h__\h] that little
bastard escaped again
the turtle that big
one oh oh it's is that a turtle I didn't
recognize it as a
[Music]
turtle did I pick up
everything
okay let's go
[Music]
home that was such a short path though
she's so
[Music]
cute don't tell me I have to feed them
always oink
[Music]
oink we're giving it a
pie EG doesn't want it okay good good I
want to keep the pie for
myself P sounds good quick H EG and
quick very
picky what did we
[Music]
give strawberries is what you
eat I'm going out again the day is
[Music]
long it's the
bird [\h__\h] stalker bird those eyes did
you
[Music]
see so sussy I'm going to go pick some
strawber in the forest oh my God what a
coincidence I picked some today
too oh it's following
[Music]
me cute as [\h__\h]
looks
cool I guess we probably have to fight
it at some
point or we ride it at some
point strawberries dried already
oh oh the the the healing thing is
back I don't know might as well absorb
it more
[Music]
strawberries what was that right
I my mommy brought me a lot of
strawberries by the way because she has
way more than I do
she brought me so many and I ate them
with some Greek
[Music]
yogurt so what like in the future if I
want to spawn monsters or like pets I
have to feed them with strawberries
always to keep them with me or
so
pet X supressor pet Vu feed does that or
maybe it makes them
stronger has reached Max Affinity Bor
junor will have increased skill power in
battle aha so maybe if I just feed them
once it already gives them Max Affinity
[Music]
Wow Let's Go
rolls onto its feet and charges an enemy
with all its might small enemies are
instantly stunned available free turns
after combat starts cool down after use
four turns stuns an
enemy
oh wait I want to look at this it's it's
pberry you she a cuy
PTI outfit huh huh is there like a DLC
or so that I can buy for more outfits w
w w w what's where do
[Music]
I which
spring are
extra costumes
[Music]
costumes I found I think I'm going to
bite right
now okay there is uh Black Pearl set 880
Yen that's nothing cute I'm going to buy
this add to
cart continue
shopping there's another
one
wow Red Berry set at the cart okay okay
I think that's
it the story went unlock one for you
okay but I still want to get everything
that's possible to get okay buying now
do I have to restart the game to see
this
possibly install
content have to install
this install please doesn't work maybe I
have to close the
game close Okay how do I
save how do I save at home
maybe or even
here or is it always
saved and we got to go home any anyway
let's go back
once fast transaction hey yo no he wants
to steal my
P stop right there you shitty
C
No you little [\h__\h] you little
[\h__\h] and we're leaving again
[Music]
the
swap yeah she hates sh she doesn't want
to go there cuz Shrek's there she's
scared of Shrek he's stinky and
[Music]
disgusting a black bird stole my bag of
pies and ran off into the swamp I
usually can't get into the swamp but now
I can ride the
bo okay but first I collect the items
again can I shoot another fish
[Music]
no no okay okay okay oh what was that ah
well I guess I
[Music]
can bird pie yeah no more berry
pie bird pie we'll have to do
today well by the time I kill the bird
maybe it will already have eaten all the
pie oopsie and then who
knows it might taste
like
[Music]
berries okay the swamp is here or what
what where what ah
[Music]
there
okay what happened to the outfit it's
okay I'm going to give it a moment the
main outfit is so cute too anyway man
it's so
he's so depressed
man oh maybe not depressed just dying
never mind he's
fineing are we going to give him a
pie or we steal his last
pie we should steal it if he's going to
die anyway we should steal
[Music]
it
dying yeah wait there's froggles on the
right side they look
cute they're like
l
l cute they're so fat they're also
friend shaped I love
[Music]
it
Sor he's such a coward
[Music]
he only has one piece of pie left girl
it's not
much why does she sound lowkey
evil okay so we can attack attack with
the board oh
oh oh okay no particular skills just
choosing the
[Music]
target
fire curs oh
[Music]
oh big frog one big frog two big frog
free why is this funny to
me the way they're named G what what
wait no I don't think other RPG games
like when there's the same enemy several
times on the screen they just all have
the same name I don't think they like
number them usually this is kind of
funny some do I I don't remember seeing
any that do
[Music]
that Dragon Quest does it
too usually a b
c I think in tales off games they don't
do
that do they name them at all in t of
[Music]
games they do right oh I'm sure they
do yay
H let's see what there is to find giant
frog
spawn let's do another froggy fight the
triple one is good o baby a triple of
fros attack for time so cute such a
[Music]
baby going to find your mom and might
control her too yeah yeah
yeah lowkey evil but I look so cute so
you can't really question
[Music]
it nice good damage
50 can you mindol them oh not a good
question let me try it out one more AOE
perhaps
[Music]
yeah ref friend
frco kill one of
them and then when it's our turn we're
going to
try
[Music]
uh
it's wait I
don't no it didn't work it just killed
him
okay I'm surprised I could use the skill
in the first place
then take you so sad I wanted to have
Frog as my
pet I got my hopes
up only special creatures not I guess it
probably also did not have the Mind
Control circle around it I should have
paid attention maybe this time I'll pay
attention and see if it's down to below
30% s if it gets the Mind Control Circle
probably
[Music]
not yeah yeah yeah it needs the circle I
see it doesn't have it okay makes
sense that I couldn't capture
it up
[Music]
69 w
yippee same energy wa wait first of all
I love how the front stuff is blurred
it's beautiful and when I get closer
it's not blurred beautiful beautiful
flower beautiful maybe I can pick those
up oh [\h__\h] bird is over there but let's
open the treasure
chest
cute wait now this really makes me feel
like I'm shre I'm in Shrek's swamp if
this buddy shows up the gingerbread
[Laughter]
man you little [\h__\h] don't you dare get
back
here man what what's this this flower
sussy oh oh I told you I told you I told
you I told you I told you giant frog
with venomous
sax what what kind of
sax oh good try 437 wait a [\h__\h]
second is this a realistic
fight oh maybe I can capture this one
though because it's bigger I don't know
[Music]
what was this thing this one oh
no can we get something interesting to
[Music]
use 18 + 15% of magic plus 90% what
that's so complicated 10 and 100 15 and
90 so actually double swing is stronger
right can use
[Music]
after usually pets are not Random
Encounters huh well this wasn't that
random it was kind of special but okay
not I think I understand
[Music]
I think I'll actually live where the
437 HP shook me to my core
but oh that was easy
oh that was actually easy we're just
that strong though okay
okay
Ah that's how we jump
oh that [\h__\h] is over there what's with
this area that's kind of weird are these
flowers going to come out of the ground
and attack me
too I will try 450
HP one
[Music]
or another hold don't do that encounter
a little bit too late another H I
thought okay if it's like 450 HP of one
of them and I'm only fighting one of
them then it's going to be okay yeah but
all of them and they attack really
strongly huh ah where's my auto
save ah nice okay not so far at
all oh was
[Laughter]
that just standing there
[Music]
menacingly there'll be more of
these why is she why is she so
Savage
[Music]
e
foree speee
death or what what are we going to
say
uh she's not that helpful
[Music]
uh of course it's always him I love him
he's so helpful so useful but I I didn't
want to like leave that's stupid bunny I
didn't really want to leave I wanted to
go around a little bit more I guess I
could go go back
[Music]
yeah maybe I yo what the [\h__\h] is that
that looks
strong seed
[Music]
Spirit you can capture that oh
mon with a blue name aha anything with a
blue
name good to
know head shot I shot
even I shot because I shot
[Music]
you in your eye yeah so anyway okay here
we go
ow not the best start with 43 HP but
I no she even gets two turns though M
let's
see I'm going to
[Music]
try okay I'm
dead okay we
trying yeah I love the
music it's very energetic
and there's
trumpets
360 I'm going to take
[Music]
a wonder what it's going to do like if I
can ride the board does it mean that any
Ever every pet will have some way of
transporting me or is it only a p select
ones and this might just be this one
might just be for having in my team to
fight with me but not
necessarily riding it or maybe I don't
know maybe it's carrying me
or like it could or I could hold on to
it need the
[Music]
[\h__\h] what [\h__\h]
second heal in this fight okay mind
control
[Music]
time someone just dra ey oh I see wait
did it not work did it not work
H I guess it didn't work I guess it
doesn't always work
no oh I guess I'll try again when it
[Music]
respawns let's heal once and go back
into the
swamp I wonder if there's a limit to how
much I can do outside in one day before
sleeping if I get like tired or so
[Music]
oh wait what I didn't realize I could go
here or did I last time I probably did
wait did it just say I will not gain
[Music]
exp so I guess I hit that limit
now shut
the maybe I saw it
wrong only get XP once for group
ah oh because I beat them
today before sleeping
again but I might get like loot I guess
[Music]
still sleeping won't affect them
what even if I sleep I will never get
exp from this monster
again so re-entering dungeons is not
really make doesn't really make any
sense
then oh so many frogs over there holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh that's a anti- grind protection M
yeah I guess
so you can beat them you think so
okay I'll try with the AOE we we're
going to be
fine surely
[Music]
one more sec
guys one more moment please
[Music]
oh that was a big package wait what did
I
order what did I
order uh what did I
order also the DVD the B DVD from the
first season it's it's there I uh they
put it in
the what is it
called in the in the little post box
but the big box is something else I
forgot what did I order keep on
forgetting even if I ordered it just
like
yesterday shortterm
[Music]
memory ah wait I know what it is ah
something for my
garden should that should hit them oh
except that one of the
[Music]
corner you forget it too small
brain
well uh I know I could do another AOE on
all of
these and attack this one of the
war but I also need to heal myself
[Music]
well if I heal myself I still get to
attack right from my
experience got turn bonus ah okay
so if I knock all of these four out with
uh the fire attack then I get another
turn hopefully
[Music]
I didn't really not right away but okay
I don't understand it has to be physical
okay your frog Hood makes me
smile he's so cute
right I don't really have anything
fitting for like
witch a cute witch like this like
magical maybe I need a magical girl
outfit I did not really 100% didn't
decide yet what my next next outfit is
going to be so I could still decide and
honestly we talked about it before but
I'm I'm not really sure if I want to go
with what we
decided I'm still reconsidering it
constantly okay I feel like I'm too
scared to go over there so we're going
to go
back and end the
day I
think Tech wear well Tech wear to be
honest my newest Warrior
outfit it kind of goes there a little
bit so maybe techware is not
priority you
know I I'm actually more and more
considering like a school
outfit cuz that is very versatile in my
opinion I can also use it as a casual
another casual outfit option and I can
put like Cardigans over it like layer
several
Cardigans
uh without like you know having it
change the theme too much because that
could be an
issue
yeah PL suit's cool I know PL suit would
be really cool to have because it's very
unique than within Holo it's it's one of
the things I might want to do
eventually yeah but gadu yeah we can do
a little bit of a little bit of gadu but
not too hard
gadu okay we're
home and so am I going to end the day
now or what I should train right they
out of two am I supposed to go outside
again then but what I'm going to do for
sure is craft a bit
more this ideally
okay okay I can make quite a
bit not as as P
oh no that's fine that's that's
good magical girl yeah see that's
probably something I could do like with
the one that I'm currently
preparing I try to be
versatile and like you know give myself
several options while still staying
within the limit of
workload that I can give them like
there's this point system and many of my
suggestions were denied because in their
opinion I actually don't agree but in
their opinion it it would stray too far
from the theme would have set I honestly
don't think so at all it was very much
still within the theme but they said no
and then I was like okay how about this
and they said no and I'm like how about
this and they said no like so many
things I was really trying to make my
outfit more versatile by having like
certain parts uh like exchangeable like
you know how some members have like a
jacket that covers up like for example a
swimsuit outfit but have it covered by
uh a huge card again so if you're just
wearing the card again over it then you
might not know at all what the rest of
the outfit looks like that seems like
pretty much changing the theme and
that's kind of what I was going for
without changing the theme actually but
they said no uh nope nope and then I'm
like okay how did the other the others
the others manage to do this and they
were like uh they probably use like uh
you know these like
accessory slots
accessory um things that we can
do and then just release it at the same
time and so I might do that additionally
later on but like for the first
reveal for the first reveal of an outfit
unless you already have an
accessory slot good to
go like separately like for anniversary
or so then you could combine it but
otherwise no and it has to like you know
be restrained like that m
was quite disappointing for me but I'll
try to get to the result that I want
through these accessories
probably yeah a
anyway I guess I can make a
maybe but that new outfit
actually today today I got
to uh check it like the the life Tod I
got to check it out because the life Tod
was
ready and I'm not going to rush with
revealing it yet because I had already
decided on a date with a bit
more um time to spare so that if there's
something that needs to be fixed there
would be time to fix
it but you'll see I'm also I have some I
I thought of a special way to reveal it
as
well
oops oh you know what now is a good time
maybe can I how do I save do I it
doesn't say save here does it I don't
want
to I
here can't wait to see the reveal well
now I'm going to reveal different
outfits of pberry
okay I
think I have to what how does this
work a new DLC has been added to your
account will be uh installed along with
the game
okay haven't seen the DLCs well it's
just outfits so no game content she is
so cute Mama Mia
oopsie Thief let's
[Music]
go look oh my God okay oh she looks so
much more mature this is like a cute
vampire outfit and this is even more
mature it's like
wo wo oh her bunny look interesting
you're so
thin these are the the
little I feel like it's an nice uh gown
for like a
ball
cute okay let's try let's try this one
and see it in
3D wait wait wait wait I want to I want
to run around uh let's let's let's leave
this place so I can see it properly in
3D a cute
[Music]
oh she has her hair in like like uh and
donuts
cute and
then there
is this one which is it doesn't
fit
wait wait a moment
do I
mature does she
mature the The Outfits just spoiled me
about
that okay well her hair does get longer
I just thought it's because of the
outfit
but oh this one's cute I think this one
fits her really well cuz I can see her
original hair so well as well so well as
well mhm mhm vocabulary
do
cute okay I'll run around this one for a
while time to pick up some
materials maybe we can no still not
there how long does it take to respawn
[Music]
o it's really slow I guess like after I
sleep did you train no because it still
said I don't know zero out two I thought
I would want to like go for four but I'm
I'm pretty much at my limit of things to
do go to swamp wait I maybe I do have to
go further into the
swamp but should I what you people who
play this game would you recommend me to
sleep and train once and then go back
into the
swamp M wa is hitting five which is Max
and it stops
waste
waste yeah have to chase the train right
the did I just say trace the train chase
the
bird I think because somebody in the
chat was saying
train go
train my train is leaving I got to
hurry choo
choo fat bird
you [\h__\h]
bird so many catoris these days and it's
not even me I'm not the
one okay
fighter I can do this we can do this I
believe we can attack the big one oh big
one attacks
next for me huh
[Music]
can't believe we got spoiled by the
clothing
DLC
unbelievable I have no
idea there will be a time skip or
[Music]
so wh wh why does it get like a special
cut scene now but what's the reason did
I do
[Music]
something because oh it was going to be
a
[Music]
crit okay let's knock this one down and
I get another
turn
yay she's doing
it another crit yeah cuz this one this
one was guaranteed to be a crit
ooh nice one we getting many turns oh St
let's go nice St oh it's back out of his
stun we un stunned
him
[Music]
why cute her skirt is so sparkly like a
stary night sky [\h__\h] bird
well the pie Thief oh wait the art gets
replaced here too nice the the art art
Thief wait did I say art
Thief what what did what am I saying the
what no wait what what was I the art got
replaced yeah what was I going to say
what was I going to say before
that what was I going to say about the
thief what what I'm having a stroke
yes it's so oh
round I don't even know what I was going
to say anymore I was going to say
something else but then I got distracted
by the art being
[Music]
replaced called me all
ugly you are a little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
for a but it's a really cute
one oh hell yeah
let's do it oh she's just gonna do it
right now right
there my aim is fine yeah bur she's like
she's like I'm not going to even let you
continue your dialogue you little [\h__\h]
you insulting me how dare
you oh that's really small damage and oh
we killed him wait shut the mountain boy
I didn't get to mind break
him
no he's so weak what a [\h__\h]
[Music]
bird Maybe
maybe cuz the wit is so
big madebe this piece of hair remember
my my hair taed for
tunic that looks so cute this is kind of
similar maybe we can have this piece of
hair and a
ribbon for me
that'll be
adorable I think okay I think I want to
make that
myself
[Music]
almost I think I might make it
myself self assd yeah cuz I think I made
the tunic hair Taft myself as well
just trying to get it close to um the
art style of yeah my actual hair so that
it Blends in nicely I think I'll do it
myself but if somebody wants to make the
hat and the ears and whatever the coat
thingy the cape feel free to do so I'll
make the little hair tap that looks like
a
brush like a
paintbrush how can I put it use oh maybe
I can make you clean my house oh but I
already have cleaners yeah oh bakos is
what they're
called in Sims 4 they're called dust
[Music]
bunnies now he's nice and telling me
things while already being useful black
[Music]
Jo you didn't know girl well a girl
failure so don't make me do anything
[Music]
she can smell the magic I can also smell
a lot of things like
never yes
[Music]
I'm too heavy is that what you're going
to
say I'm going to eat you after a fry you
and my Atelier vessel thingy that that
pot over there
oh yeah I guess
hunger releases some kind of strength
that you didn't even know you have
[Music]
C so
[Laughter]
violent just just like
me threaten with violence to get people
to do [\h__\h] for you right
K I want to eat a quo don't post quo
emote exploring back hill Golem cave I
can feel magic Beyond The Hill in the
back hill Golem cave I should be able to
get there using black gel I hope I can
find some good Magic ingredients there
why don't do some trainings we can
currently train five times let's go
all right yeah I'll do that for sure for
sure for real I'll do it he's cute yay
oh yeah we want
HP lots of HP a little bit
agility only
[Music]
HP everything yeah okay we'll
do two of those
[Music]
maybe one of the
all-rounders what only five even though
it focuses all on
it this one's like more valuable it
seems cuz even here it goes from 15 and
plus two to 7 and plus three like the
even though the the MP decreases a lot
the magic still barely
[Music]
increases maybe one of these
and one of these I don't
know okay here we go
train okay it's a new one ah okay okay I
can do it running shouldn't be so
difficult oh we just jump okay when I
have an obstacle or
so like now
okay wow this scene is so beautiful
[Music]
too just like a
bunny perfect bonus
[Music]
y I did
it
30% bonus
yo
sheesh easiest run ever shortest run
ever she ran even less than I did today
on my
treadmill which I'm a beginner so it's
not much to begin
with B magic
[Music]
recovered okay so I guess I'll sleep how
do I sleep
again ah
here run
[Music]
erand wild various sleeping black Joe
can pick up tools that reappear on the
field depending on how many I picked up
this will length for black Joe's rest
time okay should we try this
out uh I don't know which one I really
need um maybe bring
me um I don't know make him work yeah
the blue Le yeah we have the least of
these guess oh we can do
several h
M
yeah so is he going they're sleeping
with me on the bed oh he's back
already and there it is okay nice
nice let's craft before we go
[Music]
out we can't make
any but it's okay oh what's this oh it's
like a better
version of the luo and I can make a few
of
these
nice yeah way better like double as
good can make a stat
boost wait I got something like a stat
boost right do I use it outside of a
battle
[Music]
these little boys the heartfelt cookies
oh they're
um uh forever uh increased
right I think
[Music]
so huh permanently I think so
too okay here we go
we're going to like fly over the hill I
[Music]
think okay but first let me collect some
materials electric puffer fish
Spike ooh the seed spirit is
back going to give it another try now
I'm even
stronger which means I might
accidentally kill it hopefully
not okay here we
[Music]
go let me catch
you
please please I'm asking
nice it looks strong can I only have one
uh pet in battle at a
time my dear
fellow enjoyers of this game y
okay there's not many pets in the game
you can summon multiple oh oh don't kill
[Music]
her she's old now no she's not but I
gave her a different outfit but we
already got spoilered that she will get
older unsummon the boar ah it's okay
he's okay I'm
ready come on
[Music]
succeeded wow an elemental that
periodically sells seeds show show seeds
in the black witch Forest I got
[Music]
it
okay then in battle how do I decide can
I like select
oh let's feed it too I still got some
berries I guess they all eat berries oh
no ah it's
uh it's different depending
on the
[Music]
pet maybe I don't have what it needs
oh nope I don't seem to have it I think
I tried
everything huh okay so we can't be
friends yet that's
okay cool
[Music]
nice rabit
meat this time I'm not going to let that
one Escape over
there at least I don't plan
[Music]
to yo I feel like there was no time I
was
like I was in that window for like 1
second and I was already down to
0.6 seconds when I was hitting it
[Music]
there a lot of different available pets
in the game but some are quite difficult
to
get okay now what how do we
fly
[Music]
black how do I
fly what do I go from here what's this
also I need to heal actually
[Music]
is this the
cave no this is the cool
Glade it's so empty kind of
sus mini map ah yeah okay there's an
error
[Music]
ha okay okay this place not a
h back
here they look so
cute oh you look at those what the hell
are
those cute dwarf Golems they have
they're like little planters for the
garden
I'm going to steal them and put them in
my
garden and they'll be like what the [\h__\h]
we're not supposed to be here oh okay so
right now I have the bird and the seed
spirit in the fight
nice
o and they also remind me
of the nik nik DOA
[Music]
logo a Nik DOA logo is like a little
TV with a
[Music]
face like an abandoned one because it's
it has started growing leaves on its
[Music]
body easy these are oh my God I'm
suddenly so
overpowered the fights weren't that this
easy in the previous
dungeon Shield Stone oh this one's not
permanent I think right it's oh
temporary for certain number of turns
okay select combat start tool select
combat add this feature allows start
battle with Advantage by using Tools in
advance you can use defensive
consum might want to do that big fight
to the right right side with this
one wait uh
where where
where H in combat
okay okay ah
here okay here we go
[Music]
oh
uh we'll be
fine sheesh
chill you mad cuz I'm hurting your
babies
understandable wait my bird isn't even
attacking he's just chilling
there sorry I
[Music]
misunderstood
uh could it be that some of these are
maybe weaker to physical attacks than
magical
attacks I wonder if that's a thing Maybe
not maybe
not bird helps of using items oh
really oh
wait what's what does the triangle
do
wait
what he uses the item for me so what
what he uses it for me
[Music]
H see double swing which done is nice
too
[Music]
okay out he's got them laser eyes holy
[\h__\h] uh good I have another turn after
that we have like double turns
so okay I guess I did need a bigger
heal uh what's that this
[Music]
one us an item for me and didn't take a
turn not hold that's what I thought that
he was doing oh I can use him again
now too late buddy too
[Music]
late okay but he recharges really fast
fast I've learned my
[Music]
lesson wait this is way less damage than
the double
hit what the [\h__\h] I thought magic would
do
decently
okay 171 the magic hit was like 58 or
so
y but now I can't do it anymore oh it
has a cool down no not when I have the
Strategic crit
triggered let's try wait do stun just
stun will also do damage I
think it should also do damage
right yeah okay oh it killed him oh
what didn't he still have a bunch of HP
what
[Music]
A what that's like a middle version
between the big one and the small one
cute it looks like B but it's
bin German joke German old people joke
actually
wouldn't expect you guys to
[Music]
understand Bread Guy yeah I told you
about it before oh he also has the laser
eyes I'm sure it was good yeah for
Germans it was
[Music]
okay we killed it we killed that one
I don't kill me what are you doing
[Music]
depressed yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's it's a depressed loaf of bread
yeah depressed and very
cynical Oh Oh I thought it would die
from that oh please finish it thank you
Tas
sounds very
[Music]
dramatic yeah it seems like we have a a
reputation in German speaking countries
mostly Germany though that the kids
shows and stuff and kids books are a
little bit violent so to say so you
might perceive as someone who's not from
here I've never perceived it that way as
a child though
maybe I'm just that [\h__\h]
up very small smaller smaller
path oh are they
different no right there's the same
[Music]
type huh I had fall
HP is this like one of those fights like
the other one with the flowers that's
kind of impossible
now little is stronger
[Music]
shees this game does not [\h__\h]
around yeah what the hell but no but I
healed now it's down yeah but I healed
before I went into that
fight
shees well these ones I can fight though
[Music]
see this is not that bad those that that
was a weird
fight a fight that I cannot
[Music]
win yeah that should be a kill then I
get another one and I can do double
swing again oh the cool down didn't
apply in this
case
[Music]
interesting not of at
all there's a couple more here I no way
I fought those before and they already
respawned Ascend the
hill thank you
[Music]
he didn't do that
much I worry about that too with you
[Music]
guys it really looks like if I pull your
leg it just goes plop and then it's out
of your body yo they look
strong but I have to fight them I think
so we're going to heal maybe one more
[Music]
time okay let's let's use the shield
Stone and that hits both I
think interesting design on these ones
these look a little bit more fancy than
the other enemies mostly that we've seen
although my my seat Spirit looks fancy
too how do you guys like the enemy
designs H I think they're pretty
[Music]
cool I like them there's cute ones and
then there's some cooler ones like this
one sneff SN sneff sneff it's doing a
sneff
[Music]
SN good variations SM mushroom you call
this mushroom Bo what what's mushroomy
about
it
yeah wait does he get two two
hits no okay it's just because he's the
number
[Music]
two more Golem than more Pig this or
tunic what are you making me
choose no no no no
no you
can't there's a treasure chest and a
healing point and a weird bridge this
feels like there's a big fight after
that my RPG senses are
tingling a lot of dangerous
[Music]
monsters so we go left or straight
she says sometime later so first
straight
okay thank you it was the illusion of
[Music]
choice oh agility stimulant plus free or
fre of them I don't know a potion that
awakens latent agility agility
okay ah well you bird you may have to
help me with this puzzle in
progress
uh I'm
puzzled
what wait wait oh wait the board the
boore the boore
right don't worry I figured it out
yay wow that was a
puzzle didn't think of that immediately
took me a moment or
two hey where do I go this way or that
way probably a
trade
or oh yeah that's probably what they
want cuz it's right there Enchanted
grass but what's that up there at the
top that looks more
interesting okay yay B fight I felt
it you want to mind control this oh it's
like this dest Roy big
structures
oh are you saying they have no emotions
therefore I cannot mind control big moss
[Music]
bear uh yeah
sure what you're telling me
now call Black Joe calling black Jo
during comment allows you to use tools
without costing pberry turn why are you
telling me this now you can call Black
Joe again in two turns after using a
recovery tool or one turns after using a
combat
[Music]
tool interesting angle to look at them
because I don't think this is hitting
the small ones but it's a little bit
hard to
perceive ah no I I I see it actually
it's not just the red circle that
indicates who it's hitting it's also
these like arrows that go downwards okay
okay I'll hit the small ones
first I can see my eyes
[Music]
perceive oh I get a lot of
turns and maybe a few more if I can kill
them l the ground
[Music]
work swing this
one and then bigger attack double swing
on this
one oh he almost died damn it but I get
another attack which is a strategic crit
which I kind of want to hit the big one
with but do I get another attack if I
kill the small one
again he's charging something big oh
should I defend
can I wait so is there a limit to how
many times you can do the I kill one mob
therefore I get another
[Music]
turn he going to die to burn
anyway it's kind of sad that I'm missing
out on the crit or can I critically
defend
myself let's see
[Music]
or may no I guess I'm not getting the
crit
next
turn
sadly bad
[Music]
timing defense CR I feel like that
should be a
[Music]
thing okay we can focus on the big boy
now
[Music]
he's
burning he's burning and he's yearning
for his life to
end sheesh that's so
strong maybe I need more magic damage
actually if my physical attack is so
strong as a witch it just feels wrong
doesn't it he charging something again
by the way
[Music]
maybe I'll risk it
y cuz I stuned him successfully oh but
[\h__\h] boar wakes him up again
no
[Music]
guys I underestimated how strong it
is without defense D oh
[Music]
no another
turn double swing
she doing the same thing as
before now we get the Strategic crit
again but we have to defend of
course what a waste of
crits I think you can summon a dve ah
yeah I should if I do that midf fight
does it take a
[Music]
turn base attack is just a Bit Stronger
skill Power by he has plus 20% skill
power because we have better Affinity
with it so it might actually be
[Music]
stronger
okay nice video oh nice nice are
nice oh
[Music]
okay he's
charging wait is this going better than
before no are we in the same spot 133 it
feels like I could kill him with the
double
swing I feel like I
[Music]
can
y y not quite the same
spot I must have done something
[Music]
differently no because last time I
stunned him because I didn't have the
double hit that was so strong but this
time I had it probably because um in the
previous turn this time I used magic and
last time I probably used the double hit
or so I don't
know must have done something wrong H
right different
gr
grass okay but it will not let make me
grow in terms of age right not
yet
okay who
oh are those random the stats that I get
I think I got some good
ones HP magic and defense I
[Music]
think the lowest stats that I have get
buffed
[Music]
oh yeah of course you can
yeah but that's not where we're going we
want to go get the
stone you don't have to touch
it I'm sure we need
it uh yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah thanks for the membership
REO as as someone stays under your ah
some are
fre I'll have to check that outk
[Music]
I do
down
[Music]
rud so I can teleport back home directly
nice I like walking back and forth cuz I
can pick up all the items in between
[Music]
it's those eyes guys those eyes are
special magical eyes
[Music]
uhuh what it's getting fancier and
fancier oh and there she go
bye-bye
o damn I wish I knew how to do
[Music]
that teleport directly home by pressing
the teleport button in the field
menu
[Music]
nice wait I just saw I was like where's
where's she looking at and I my eyes go
to Joel but he's like he doesn't have
much space in that
cage is that even a cage it feels like a
lamp that has been reused into a bird
cage I guess I think there's like a
normal bird could easily fly out of that
but the how round he is he might
actually not be able to get out of that
space between those bars in between
[Music]
not a free range bird a bird
holder or if he glows in the dark that
would be great yeah then he would be a
nice light to have in the
Night round boy he looks a bit
squish he's being cooked over the pot
yeah
slowly very slowly
does so slowly he doesn't even
realize you wonder where did I pick up
that strategy why why do I know about it
h slowly steaming Birds without them
[Music]
realizing so she is did she say cuz he
just said he's 352 years old but is did
she actually say she's 10
[Music]
no teach me
magic she said actually like do you want
to get burned by my beginner's magic
because I guess it's like fire skills
oh thank you compendium of fire
[Music]
mag shut the [\h__\h] up k
ah oh we're going back in there let's
crafted okay but I need to go there then
not do and I'm not going to sleep in
between I
suppose oh then I guess I'll go
[Music]
Let Me Ride you my
pony my Bor
[Music]
CH oh hey yo now this stuff is
here waa MP magic defense let's
go ni
almost missed you almost ran into you
[Music]
o oh guys by the way did you see on
Twitter I made that weird pizza
yesterday I'm I'm I really expected a
bit more because I didn't think it would
be perfectly like pizza but I expected a
bit more because uh the lady in the
video was hyping it up so much and the
way she was eating it she was eating it
like it was [\h__\h]
heaven but
somebody answered to me on Twitter
saying yeah this this is the kind of
food that only tastes good because you
have been dieting for a long time and
have had to
eat like diet food for a long time so
this is like more satisfying when you're
so deep into your
diet oh
wow I was like that makes a lot of sense
yeah I I can imagine it being more
satisfying and yummy in that
case the dough ingredients sounded
pretty odd well yeah it's just egg
whites but I mean it did get
like I don't know somewhat the we but
not really I wonder if the if a
different kind of starch would really
make a big
difference that's the one thing I'd like
to
[Music]
know so I can can I current summon cost
zero someone close to someone close to H
so does just get rid of the other one
[Music]
doesn't cancel a
pet okay let's try it I don't
know what is your s maybe you can't
ah okay it says
insufficient I'd have to dismiss this
first and get the other one if I wanted
to replace
[Music]
it thank
you thank you thank
[Music]
you if he kills an enemy it doesn't give
him a second turn but also me neither so
I'd rather kill the enemies
huh rather than leaving it to him oh but
there we go I was able to kill that one
even though it was at full HP let's go
[Music]
easy your pizza look tasty it did
definitely look very good yeah and it
had very low
calories a lot of people uh recommend it
to make it with like cauliflower I hate
cauliflower it better not taste like
cauliflower but I don't know I I I was
feeling really motivated about trying
this one out if you guys can give me a
good video on how to make a pizza with
that cauliflower base then I might want
to try but I I I want a good video a
good video as a
reference yeah
like what is a high density food that
makes you feel for long yeah yeah yeah I
did feel rela relatively full but just
very
disappointed which is fine at least I
tried it was fun trying it out it was
fun experimenting and doing something
new and
different they not cauliflower not a
hot but wait what do you think guys any
people with more cooking experience who
can say if the the type of starch makes
a
difference I do
wonder about
[Music]
that no it doesn't
yes H conflicting it does it does okay
most people say yes a few people say no
not
fundamentally
[Music]
h h
there's flavor
[Music]
change the flavor I think doesn't matter
because it would have been mostly
overpowered Anyway by all the toppings
[Music]
I thought you would die
sheesh the monsters are so cute they are
you mention the idea no the idea is just
that if that was 300 calories and I
looked up how many
calories uh like pizza though balls for
example have like typical
ones it was also pretty low I think like
250 or something like that so I feel
like in total if I made an actual Pizza
not like you know go to a restaurant but
I make it myself so I know what I'm
putting it on putting on there and like
limit it
to uh not too
many things you know
um if I do that
then I have it under control and then I
feel like you know I feel like it could
be still around 600 which is what our
aim was for dinner uh calories
anyway for
me
so that
sounds like it might still
be within within the lower calories and
taste [\h__\h]
amazing at that
[Music]
people do keep the diet where you can't
have cards yeah I guess so I was more
looking at the 300 calories oh my God
that's kind of crazy yo that is
crazy if you don't mind the weird
texture that the dough has so for people
who didn't read my Tweet I'm talking
about a pizza where it consists
of
um four egg
wies mixed with some starch and some
spices then whipped
really uh High into like you know a
fluffy structure texture
then you put it in the oven for like 10
minutes so it's like somewhat it it has
it will at that point have taken some
shape and be uh not fluffy anymore it
will like be kind of like an omelet so
you can put all the toppings on it and
then it goes back into the oven
basically and all the toppings are just
normal pizza toppings pretty much but I
use like turkey uh
pepperoni so
[Music]
Pizza is mainly carbohydrates type of
food I hope not
really I don't really care
about you know I'm not trying to do a
keto diet
so that indeed does not matter to
[Music]
me do people do keto because they think
it's a
like a really
effective diet in general or is it more
[Music]
like it does it have to do with
training I don't
[Music]
know sounds easy it's easy to overe eat
on
carbs I don't know I don't want to do
that I like bread
and uh noodles and rice cuz I think
that's also what you can't eat on a keto
diet
right in any case it may sound like I'm
really uh going crazy about this but no
I'm cheating a lot too
[Music]
so but no it balances it out like
yesterday it definitely balanced it out
because I had that shitty 300 calorie
fake Pizza
okay
so all things
[Music]
balanced a statue a goat statue that
shoots fire 2,000 HP
[Music]
diet in name
only bewildered but Brave Bird your
name could be applied to this [\h__\h] bird
he he
seems somewhat
bewildered let's try if we die it's no
problem
OMG to [\h__\h] okay goodbye say
[Music]
maybe I already have everything that I
need from this cave
right ingredients oh yeah I
do huh it's nice that it shows me so
clearly what I need and what I
got
sheh oh so I can go back this is for
later I suppose
not for me not for
now
uh wait a
moment is that part over there also for
for another time ah
sorry over here probably seems like if
the game isn't telling me to go there
it's usually like should be
avoided oh
[\h__\h] yeah okay
bye I
understand so
uh time to go
home teleport
home just saying hi like I see you later
when I'm stronger just remember my
[Music]
face H oh interesting I still do it at
The
Cauldron
yeah
one the [\h__\h]
Muppet they look like my sock puppets
the way their mouth opens and their eyes
are so so
[Music]
dorky uh what how do I do
that combine magic circles
[Music]
combin wo
wo Center magic
circle uh
[Music]
okay okay
just I'm just going to press X
continuously cuz I don't know there's
nothing else to do let's X select Center
okay let's
select this
one check the magic circle details and
press X to apply the magic circle to the
slap oh it's going to cost 44 MP now but
it's going to be so much
stronger wow you've inscribed a magic
circle on your slab you can now use a
slab in combat there are three types of
slabs major slab basic slab and minor
slab where's the mid slab eh magic has
been
inscribed engrave a free orb flame
circle on another slab
uhuh supportive
n Oh Oh you mean like
this aha I can aha does this mean the
slab where I put the four thingy four
Circle thingy on can later be like
buffed with even more supportive
[Music]
stuff Center magic
circle free orb they
said
[Music]
yeah copy apply the magic circle to the
SL okay m
[Music]
well that's me
oh so it's like multiple Target
hits do I have to do something or was it
[Music]
random guess we'll get to try it out
right
away I'll be able to fight off the
Warriors okay you think so I hope so for
[Music]
you okay
learning by
doing uh down
here
no where are they ah here CH the to let
me get some
[Music]
materials priorities they're so nice to
wait for me
[Music]
okay attack from
behind with have the agil oh actually
that might have been a waste no actually
not that I think about it it might have
been a waste major slab uh summon four
fire
orbs yeah because the free the free one
was uh AOE right yeah it's hard to see
now but it's an AOE and this
is uhhuh aha
oh they don't even have to be close to
each other let's
go nice
[Music]
let's do it
again yeah yeah
yeah hey 200 total
damage ni
[Music]
ah
ah C go complete Warrior
sweep
[Music]
oh he's he looks
strong you missed one come back here and
eat him out of my Forest
[Music]
now ah oh
[\h__\h] no I broke
myself no no no what the
[\h__\h] bird do something [\h__\h]
bird
oh but what am I going to do about my
staff
[Music]
how did I make the first one to begin
with I would have thought like just out
of magic
[Music]
no no I'll protect
you just let me adopt you then you don't
need a magic staff
[Music]
anymore okay okay okay the broken one
okay
[Music]
okay yeah suddenly we're improving
everything about
us has that book on the left always been
that big I guess so I just noticed it it
now how ridiculously big it
is
[Music]
nice
okay actions weapon Evolution
ah now we're learning this
and Piper's weapon will evolve to the
next stage when it filled nutrients
reach 100% when the weapon evolves it
will become more powerful and gain new
skills the weapon's performance is
slightly boosted by the amount of
nutrients it contains
20%
ahuh the type of nutrients you fill the
weapon with determines the
characteristics of the evolved
weapon huh oh for more information press
Evolution St
you can nourish the weapon of nourish
nourishing tools that you don't normally
use is also an effective way to organize
your tools oh like
okay
[Music]
what did thank you oh a pie i e that pie
I'm not going to put the pie into my St
pie is made to eat
okay we
so
[Music]
oh life stuff Enchanted stuff strength
stuff physical attacks
oh I get different skills from them too
so I can choose which one I'm aiming
for strength yo we've been so strong
physically but I feel like as a witch I
should focus on
Magic but then how do I know how to aim
for
this using the power of
life oh probably just go for this one
looks also the most like my original one
it's just gaining a
horn this one looks nice look like very
[Music]
natural nourish growth
guide focusing on Magic will provide a
significant Advantage when using magical
attacks magical attacks are flashy
powerful generally have a greater range
than their physical counterparts however
neglecting HP or defense in favor of
magic will also leave you vulnerable
requiring dep use of defensive tools and
skills to maintain HP
thanks for telling me all
that ah okay there's strength there's
life so if I put a lot of magic in there
then it's going to be the magical
[Music]
one I have a lot of this
grass oh
[Music]
how what how many
what wa
fancy magic blast TOS a massive sphere
of concentrated magic at the enemy
causing a white a explosion let's go
that's
[Music]
big 160 Power Plus 20% of Max MP and 260
of magic Wow
two turns after combat starts and then
three turns combat oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
strong explosion
St Magic Shield decreases MP in s HP
when damage is taken
oh the amount of MP lost is up to 40% of
magic if you do not have enough MP you
will lose that amount of HP disability
does not cause the
turn
[Music]
who is he still
there he's still around
here I thought Bal would have already
heated him what the hell Bal do your job
so what if I wanted to do more can I do
it yo but now it's
800 and ow okay I'm forced now to
continue on the
magic I
think
oh now I need way more
[Music]
o
oh oh I
can
it
degenerate I've never seen this word
like this except for using it as an
insult here
[Music]
is this not an
insult that's a weird way to in yeah
[Laughter]
translate n oh I need flame frog fire
pouch and dwarf Golem Essence M okay so
it's not just these
nourishing
materials that I need
okay are we good on this front
everywhere
here I need some of
these make a few
[Music]
more they look
hungry it's
M yeah I mean it makes sense to generate
and to degenerate something although it
it really sounds
[Music]
weird maybe I'll make one of
these strength
boost let's go kind of weird that I
don't get healed at home home they
should give me an auto heal at
[Music]
home yeah even without sleeping I want
to be
healed is that too much to ask is there
something there no on the left side I
thought I saw something was just a stone
hey yo
[Music]
wait I have a bow this whole time to
hunt and I I can't use it in battle have
you guys noticed that I just realized
[Music]
it sad I like using
bows why am I gatekeeping my
bow
huh oops special
skill ah the magic blast is in here and
the shield okay that counts as a special
skill they're all down to
69 like AOE two
villagers oh oh right because they can
hunt with the bow but they don't use it
to
fight right they don't when they get
attacked they just don't do anything
they just say okay guess I'll
die oh my God you're so
[Music]
right they just say guess I'll
die does this swing alone kill one of
these I I hope so so yes
okay magic SP you want me to use that
now magic
[Music]
black
wow I think that was
strong
[Music]
oh H he still full HP but I might be
able to kill him with the crit n 6 hp on
the
dream that is a yo speaking of AOE and
the AOE villagers I i' I've been kind
of like uh what's the word again
craving AOE to but I feel like it's been
so long and even when I was more
actively playing it I still didn't
really get to the point where I could
play well
alone now if I go back into it I'll I'll
be so lost again and I'll be like how do
I do this and I'll still suck man it's
so hard to get good at that
game
[Music]
why all those jump scares in that
game you mean like I advancing to feudal
age cuz I was was I scared of did I did
it did it jump scare me I guess it
did call up your coach again haven't
talked to her in a long
time long long
time the mid-rank palace Warrior fled to
the east side of the forest if I leave
them be they only come back strong I
need to chase out to them y let's
go no mercy this little witch does not
know the word
mercy it is foreign to
her don't eat him we have to kill him as
we just said he's just going to come
back
stronger he's totally going to eat him 3
2 1
[Music]
Ana aoe2 versus AI oh
interesting hey oh oh he's busy so I can
go in there now is that what you're
thinking oh we didn't know about this
wall before I saw it before
did oh yeah we somewhere
else we have to close
it because it's disturbing
[Music]
us I thought he would eat us into the
portal
[Music]
fore speech
speech
foree
spee
[Music]
for I just
noticed first of all the door of my
house is
[Music]
breathing and second of all and more
importantly the handle of my door is a
freaking cat a black cat and its tail is
like maybe something I can hang
something on but oh my god did you see
look at the door of my
[Music]
house cute but the leap if you look
closely it moves it's
[Music]
breathing cat
house my staff looks some kind of looks
like some kind of World of Warcraft
staff it's so cool
[Music]
oh smart lady oh he's really black Joe
now thanks for the
[Music]
membership I'm ready to train
what tomorrow we're exploring Beyond B
oh I noticed the shimmering wall behind
bout maybe it will help me figure out
why the Warriors are appearing I'll get
a good night's sleep and go through
tomorrow she's so adventurous and so
brave I aspire to be more like her my
cutie
patootie my sweet bunny girl I love her
she's the cutest of them all
tomorrow and when I wake up it's going
to be
[Music]
today
okay time to train and then
sleep I haven't had pie in a while man
this poor
girl she trains so hard but she never
eats where's the pie
[Music]
man wait how many can I do only one I
don't understand okay let's see ow well
my HP isn't doing so badly anymore my
magic needs some more
[Music]
power okay it seems like that's all I
can do indeed all right
[Music]
uh I wonder
oh
[Music]
a what the what it
doesn't okay
finally you the angle it started so it
started so
it starts so high what the [\h__\h] is this
[Music]
aim [\h__\h] okay well I got the basic we
about the
bonus damn n that's
okay that's all right I'm not
mad oopsie I should have run errands
damn
it h
it's
[Music]
okay no you will not come back
here you little chocolate ball ah run
away black Joe need to investigate the
path behind B but black Joe is run
away I see you let me shoot him with the
arrow
[Music]
oh don't Drop in the
Ocean going to eat a banana now it's my
snack
wait what the [\h__\h] there's an opening on
the bottom of a
banana Fu bugs
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
man you can't do this to
me no sou tastes fun but I'm not going
to eat the bottom part cuz it's like all
brown and
open we're on a we're stranded on an
island
[Music]
look at those blue crabs let's
go we need to find black Joe that
[\h__\h] crab
R let's go
[Music]
crabs I love
crabs look they have so many of those
things on their back what do you call
[Music]
them H okay
all
right why are we suddenly on this island
so
random but
fun a recipe written on an old piece of
paper blue crab extract oh
nice W I can walk a little bit in the
water oh there's those
[\h__\h] can't shoot from here crab dance
let's fight this solo one first 340 HP
so nice they tell me all the stats like
in so much uh detail right away also I
just noticed they do tell me the defense
element as well does that mean they are
most defensive about
it or is it the other way
around I have no pet here
[Music]
damage maybe means resist or or immune
normal attacks so for example a swing
would not do much
right still looks like it did a lot I
don't
know 88 is not the worst amount of
damage
oh nice increased the maximum Limon
nice oh wait there you are don't bring
me home yet I'm not
[Music]
done means it takes normal damage from
any kind of attack
ah oh yeah
[Music]
maybe ugly baby witch
[\h__\h] nightmare right behind him wait
my my my pet is inside of me what
the realization hits in three two 1
black Joe once
[Music]
again what is this like Sund
relationship we're having with this
[Music]
bird cute
we training him so
badly well we need to train him you know
we need to make sure he learn discipline
and respect
[Music]
n yes the
ship Tree
House girl it's a ship what a girl
[Music]
failure dolphin's in the water or
sharks no I want not be here
[Music]
he been living alone the first forgiver
of course of course you can always get
to the South Island by using oh really I
can get here
[Music]
anytime so maybe stuff like the ship is
not recommended for
now oh they are sharks by the way I
think
oh we can wear
[Music]
that equipment oh oh finally don't have
anything else here
see ah plus
threee I'm wearing it now right ah no
okay there we
go I to change into this
one cute
yo it's so many [\h__\h] sharks and they
are hammerhead sharks I was thinking so
even from far away their heads looked a
little bit wide to
me money worth uh well spent worth it
guys big recommend
[Music]
speee
fore foreign
[Music]
speech woohoo
I was just getting hyped about the song
he fly over oh to the other Island part
E I don't know will I get killed
again permanent oh my God there's so
many permanent
[Music]
increases
strength
wa
wo wo magic strength and HP yeah what's
this oh this one
increases so it says but it's actually
minus 2 max HP and then increases Magic
by one while magic is quite uh
rare or difficult to get uh stacked
right I feel like actually might be
worth it at least one I'll take for now
oh wait these are also this is good Max
HP and mp+ 5 yo wait the strawberries as
well are an item for permanent increase
magic and
strength I did not
know
oh okay one more crab fight let's go
[Music]
wish the strawberry could make me
stronger I feel like strawberries do
make me
[Music]
stronger I've had a few more tiny baby
baby baby strawberries from my garden
today
like the first
time I harvested them they were way
bigger and the ones that still needed
some time to grow they
[Music]
um ended up staying really small and I
figured out my mom told me I should have
watered them them even more I was not
watering them too little but I guess if
I would have given them way more water
they would have turned out
bigger but it's okay even though they
were small they tasted
good but next year I want a bigger
strawberry Harvest I want to make bigger
Strawberry
Fields my mom didn't give me so many of
those plants to begin with so it's not a
surprise that I didn't Harvest so
many oh nice
Miss nice counter
attack strategic
[Music]
87 * 4 how much is
that well around 247 but that's with all
the crit
extras nice you can turn your garden
into whole strawberry Factory next
season if you want to I kind of want to
yeah this is like very very
[Music]
tempting for
sure my mom says they um get who close
sheesh they get um more on their own
quite
easily like I don't even have to buy
more strawberry plants they're just
going to re produce on their own very
efficiently
[Music]
H so we'll see we'll see hopefully
hopefully I'll have more strawberries
that I could ever ask for
eventually so should I go over there or
is it dangerous territory H never mind
never mind never mind yeah yeah can I go
back
[Music]
because does ascenta Hill mean to go
back because that already looks
like it's going to destroy me in one hit
there's like some kind of lion
there and then here I doubt this is oh I
don't think I can go inside
[Music]
anyway when we're stronger we'll come
back I
suppose never know till you challenge it
all right you are doubting my RPG
instincts especially after all these
crazy encounters we've had so far wait
how can I swim through this when there's
hammerhead sharks
everywhere wait I literally can't oh no
okay never mind pressing X oh god oh hey
y' yo I actually did it but this is like
from Pokemon the the
lion
[Music]
nah there's no way like how am I ever
going to
compete it's going to have like 6,000 or
10,000
HP new
art The Outfits not only come with a
freey update but with new artworks isn't
that nice
[Music]
question
mark Quest I don't even need to use a
tool and dead not dead wa how much
damage can I do
though question
wait he's not so bad is he going to Morp
after I kill him and turn into something
bigger and
stronger thank you for the Super Chat
[Music]
that's what I'm
saying there's something else appearing
right
[Music]
maybe it was only easy to me because I
was the real one whatever that means I'm
the chosen one or
so
oh the
spring not a good Guardian
okay seems like the game does want me to
do this I thought this was like another
come back later kind of
thing oh oh Island investigation
complete I am pure
[Music]
uhhuh all right he wants to help me he
loves me oh [\h__\h] this gives me atalia
Vibes Risa feel like we've been through
a place like this
[Music]
sad
music h
[Music]
guys have you ever thought like his
mouth is so
small how can
he he must be eating a lot so is it is
he just eating the tiniest things but a
million of them I can't imagine him
eating big
food he's so
big so
round's so small
[Music]
mouth drinks a lot of oh maybe maybe he
makes every all his food into
[Music]
liquids it's okay I'm not really a
human can they do
[Music]
nothing
no she's motivated
yeah we need to find the
[Music]
merchants all I
want but he has the better
[Music]
pie maybe he's my father
L brain
really is that how she act
[Music]
to she does love
pie not this
much she doesn't Happ
[Music]
passion
passion yeah she's notate enough
[Music]
yes same girl
same there
[Music]
trases yes it'll be worth it
I can send strong Magic from the temple
maybe I can find out why I can't
teleport T to investigate wo let's
[Music]
go a new piece of oh let's go another
equipment oh we're being more and more
blessed with equipment and other cool
stuff secondary right o like an earring
Genesis blessing what did it
do reduces the amount of damage taken
between the start of battle and your
first
turn so like in case an enemy attacks
first before
[Music]
me I I
guess okay
[Music]
nice
nice well teleportation altars allow you
to teleport to distant areas well
[Music]
teleportation this bgm right
now actually is giving me tails off
vibes
Can you feel it
too like older Tales of not not Tales of
uh newer
[Music]
games yeah yeah yeah wind Temple Vibes
so true syon
yeah s let's
go oh wait I could have killed one of
them oh one died
[Music]
anyway what this what is this
why I must take shiny thing don't you
feel the same you're a
bird that's giving me two Vibes Fallout
uh like the the the the energy thingy
key
thingy like if you you're not supposed
to take anybody's because they're really
valuable and at the same time it reminds
me of the most recent episode I watched
of
Shogun sorry
sorry uh and all I'm going to say
is then you probably understand what I
mean holy [\h__\h] to that
escalated yeah the fusion core would be
what I'm thinking of for
Fallout I'm glad I know I caught up to
you good good good
[Music]
good SP no no spoilers no no
no you have to watch
shun she's going in she's going for
[Music]
it girl what if this makes the whole
world fall apart though like you're not
even thinking that there could could be
some consequences you're just doing
whatever the [\h__\h] comes to your
mind I love
it she's so
crazy ah made a half okay it wasn't so
bad if anything it it did not make
something fall apart it made it and fix
[Music]
it nice um but I feel
like ah okay
that's a boat okay there's so many paths
what about
here that will lead in
here oo uh I super strong enemies or
what
500 should be okay
[Music]
is thisable
wait nah I'd have to heal constantly
it's not like completely
impossible not as unrealistic as the
other fights
but
[Music]
ah should
I cuz I used an item oh well
[Music]
whatever ah it returns me just before
the combat also I get the them back this
game is so so [\h__\h]
nice in other games I don't get it
back I run away means I I lost all the
effort
[Music]
there okay this one I cannot break okay
are these people
strong oh but I leave with my HP not
healed it
[Music]
seems that's
fine those are weak yeah these are weak
right uh
[Music]
probably is this even still worth using
this one H it's I guess because it's
like way cheaper if they stand close
together maybe it's worth
it cheaper
MP you do need to probably get used to
using the MP Shield
oh well if I struggle with a fight then
[Music]
okay okay one
down the way they fight
[Music]
kind of
cute AOE and cheap yeah I mean the this
is kind of an
AOE not really but kind
of oh
CR
[Music]
nice y this one was about to attack next
and I was say to kill him oh what is he
doing is he charging
something we'll kill him before that no
worries magic blast wait is
[Music]
this it doesn't cost
MP it's healed my mp
[Music]
even y
or was that because of the kill do I get
my mp healed if I kill
[Applause]
[Music]
someone strategic
crit okay I think it was good to come
here first before we move on because
this seems to be a dead end for some
Treasure Chest let's go Shield
Stone
heal and
agility I wonder if there's you know the
typical fake Treasures in this game as
[Music]
well spein punch yeah a cool down type
of skill that's its only
cost nice I think it's uh definitely
worth it to use it whenever I
can are these statues holding Birds
it's like they're sending off a pigeon
as a
messenger
right yeah
mimics I couldn't think of the word
again I was just thinking
MIM puzzle
time wait is this the kind of puzzle we
ah I have to push them all down
but if I step on one of these a lot of
others are going to come
up oh no not quite oh but I have to uh
stand on them oh wa wait
oh oh
hey oh
okay and
then what what
wait
what
what wait let me take this
[Music]
first how do you not just run for the
chest
oh defeating an enemy restores more HP
it's equipment restore small amount of
HP with each deing nice
[Music]
it looks really pretty
too all
right wait a second I
can these are the strong ones again but
this time it's just
[Music]
two try
again if it's just two then maybe it's
fine if I also use one of these
Shield Stone
maybe okay
okay I can do this we're
[Music]
talking yeah
easy damn why just because it was
free and I didn't use a shield thingy
and they blasted
me like it's
[Music]
nothing you can do it yes I can work Now
podcast mode
activate W your favorite
podcast I need some sponsorships to like
randomly mention in the middle of my
podcast
this podcast is sponsored
[Music]
by uh me
andies everybody you can get yourself
some really comfortable unies I only
know that because of uh the Jenna Julian
[Laughter]
podcast they were like sponsored by me
andies
constantly every time
magic blast is
[Music]
ready no they're not
used
no y we did
it y mental enhancer o I'm going to get
smort real
smort Max hp+ 10 and another one and
this one is ooh special increase four
and Max HP increase by 10 then you know
what I might as well use this one too I
just want to get it out of my
inventory it's okay it balances out it's
a give and take
so
um how do I oh wait a second is this
again I mean I'm a like a little
wait it's not about running faster maybe
I can just make him stand on there right
oh cuz my other pet does
not touch the
floor
y that was
[Music]
smart it did wait what and now what I
can just jump now okay okay that thing
still moves though and
[Music]
interesting uh am I supposed to fight
that lightning
Magic's more powerful than fire but
takes more
maybe I'll need it for that enemy so
I'll have to go home
[Music]
first this good against steel they
say slap at the bottom of the
Box oh free four planting Circle or is
it like the same as the fire
one like a circle
[Music]
AOE yeah what a big dude yeah y probably
but that means I'll have to go home I
[Music]
suppose
probably let me check what's here a wait
what big hermit crab in
Orange Orange crab
Behavior M looks kind of
strong m m
[Music]
all right let's
4,200 I mean the lion
had a lot of HP too but wasn't strong
[Music]
right
okay okay easy pey
okay if you guys say no then oh lion had
500 Oh I thought he had like
5,000
oopsie don't no I don't I didn't want to
uh I wasn't going to okay but maybe this
is supposed to happen you know
[Music]
dead do we have to activate him in order
to fight
him wait your eyes just now
wait I skipped it too
fast
ah please let me go home
[Music]
no minions too question mark okay ah the
line had question mark question mark
question mark but I guess cuz this one
is question mark question mark question
mark question mark it does show you like
if it's in the hundreds or if it's in
the
thousands well maybe it's just
1,000 it doesn't have to be like
99,999 it could be 1,000
anywhere between
them but I feel like we're going to lose
it and then it's going to tell me go
home and learn thunder
magic right
[Music]
script
it not much damage
[Music]
[Applause]
actually you can already use it could I
have done it before entering the battle
could I have said it lightning I already
have is it in my
skills really
[Music]
wait first of
all Jo bonus
okay I use it from
here
ah oh what it's like reflecting off of
him and goes
down W
strong yeah we can do this oh he's
charging something in
J I'll deal with you
later be careful
yes I will should we oh he missed C
let's go he dies
strategic crit M but why does the crit
always happen when I got to be
[Music]
careful do I want to do a normal defense
or do I want to do a magic
[Music]
Shield wait this doesn't cost a turn
right but so use use it now and I can
still do whatever I want after
[Music]
that yeah it's a free
turn that will be a good
[Music]
solution okay
yeah
free good
stuff oh wait my board doesn't even have
HP does he I just
realized I guess he'll never die good
for
him good for him
[Music]
uh how
about just a small one is fine it's
costing no turn this big guy kind of
sucks nah no
problem I'll just continue using the
free Fork lightning Circle oh
CR nice just one more of those I
need okay okay fight looks good hell
yeah
[Music]
so I have access to all of my skills at
all times I guess from that plus slot oh
my God oh my God oh my God thank
you is that so I can use any of my
skills at any
time but then there's special slots to
just have quick access to them or what
oh it Buffs them to have them in there
ah I guess so not CU they can even be uh
even more buffed with like supportive
whatevers your combat XP has reached
stage two all stats increase by 15% upon
reaching a combat level training
Effectiveness plus 30% oh you mean
tonight strategic crit power wow Max pet
summon cost four secondary equipment
amount two
uhhuh you mean free because I already
had
to
oh
oh he's still alive wants to blast me
out of
[Music]
here we got to go no I'll carry
you divine
[Music]
intervention the
lion sorry for saying you're not a good
Guardian you did actually a good job now
[Music]
oh okay chill
chill yeah asan is a interesting name
[Music]
shouldn't asan be thanking us because
asan was not strong enough to kill the
Golem but we kind of were just giving it
the final
[Music]
punch stole the Kill from
me it's a Narnia
reference
[Music]
really
for she's so
cute oh the line in Narnia was also
called as
really okay now that's a a very obvious
one he's basically
Jesus the lion in Narnia or the lion in
this game
wa can I take the
[Music]
stone oh asan's
there
oh shortcut backi
[Music]
intrusive thoughts hitting her
again it looks like there's nothing
behind
[Music]
only want to dream about
pie but that look like the woman on the
right was
me her as an adult
[Music]
by the way
today my hello fresh order arrived so
this week I have a box again let's go I
can get cooking
again I don't have to make up recipes
again I can cook what I've planned
properly ahead of time
[Music]
H I'm excited I hope I won't be too lazy
after the stream but I don't really have
a choice anyway I have to cook I mean I
could still make something else but I'll
probably end up cooking something
proper
probably
PL I just want to say bye
bye I just I just you know
[Music]
fight the crabs from
before should
I I am stronger
[Music]
really them being reasonable black Joel
trying to help me proceed instead of
tell forcing me to go back
[Music]
home so going to choose next week yeah
don't forget about it otherwise they're
going to send you [\h__\h] that you don't
want like
mushrooms [\h__\h]
mushrooms I still have unused mushrooms
in my fridge why do I keep on uh
freezing what's going on huh
[Music]
wait I'm reading some DMs
Co not the M directly to me just in a in
our big
server all right is this going to be a
tougher fight now he has question mark
question mark question mark question
mark now but the other question mark
mark wasn't a big deal either I will
however use one of these so maybe best
to just go with the shield Stone but the
other ones could be good
too cuz I get to attack more with this
one
right I'll I'll try this
one for fun for a little bit of a
challenge yeah yeah yeah it's long as
there's just four question marks we
don't want to go up to question mark
question mark question mark question
mark question
mark then I'm going to cry and run
away uh I wonder if he also wants to be
attacked with thunder magic or if we can
do
whatever no damage looks
good easy
[Music]
easy
oo I get two turns right now
maybe focus on
these wait where's my pet don't go the
[\h__\h] the
[\h__\h] I think I can can get two
now yeah yeah I got
both but they're not in the schedule yet
[Music]
okay yeah I can kill them
all um
yeah do I need two
hits maybe not uh no yeah I needed two
hits
closly do not revive them please oh he's
charging something just like my
boy gr always wait I have a solution for
that m Magic Shield and then does this
also not take up a turn it does
right oh sh s yaho
wao yo using that in a crit turn is
[Music]
crazy y my body is
stiff yo insult I've been stretching my
body before my workouts okay I'm not
that
stiff oh he had one HP in the
dream and now zero and thus he will
dream eternally
is he like dead for real for real I feel
bad for
killing him when he he didn't have bad
intentions he wasn't
evil maybe he's not dead maybe he's just
sleeping I don't see a breathing
animation though this is kind of evil if
we killed
him like we don't even have a specific
reason to be in this Temple like oh I
know that there's this special item to
save the world in this Temple so I got
to go there no we just we're like oh
this looks fun let's go
in like why why do we have to go this
far we don't even have a goal in mind
he'll walk it off I hope so
[Music]
I'm sorry pberry pie Berry gives no [\h__\h]
man she's a Savage and the
[Music]
Menace good food yeah understandable but
this does not look like pie to me if
there was pie here we would be more
motivated I'm
[Music]
sure which spring
AR is this spring from this like
spring oh he's awake yes
instant
[Music]
revive no I don't think he wants to
fight us
anymore
yeah because I am the chosen
one yeah you should have known I thought
you could sense [\h__\h] like that
h i uh which stands close to the spring
oh the title is coming
together all we need is the r I'll I'll
be providing that
[Applause]
German accent dialect
phrase be quiet
[Music]
I don't like your [\h__\h] boy kind of way
of
[Music]
speaking cuz he talks like this doesn't
he it pisses me off
[Music]
for [\h__\h] boy
God
oh
oh oh what magic plus
15 what was magic the the yeah mag magic
is the one you barely get it's on the
same level as these other ones oh wait
defin uh there's a bit different
here e what what you go magic all these
are good yeah I think all of these are
good except I don't care that much about
[Music]
defense magical yeah magical defense I
would say magic yeah we we're pretty
much all in everybody thinks Magic is
best
yeah we're generally seem to be focusing
so far on Magic so we can continue that
path okay thanks
no she's fallen for the [\h__\h] boy
no the [\h__\h] boy effect is
[Music]
working greater dreams greater boobies
because I will grow
up so sleepy
man
[Music]
same
for
foreign foreign
speech spe
[Music]
[\h__\h] he has better [\h__\h] to
do no I kind of wanted to try the crabs
one more time but you're sending me home
okay #
[Music]
blessed
fore for
[Music]
just
random could have been
anyone well that's true I would think so
but I feel like this game could hit me
at any time with like a turns out I'm
kind of
evil that that would be cool but cuz
like she's she's kind of
crazy but uh surely we're here to do
good deeds
[Music]
[Applause]
right it what do you mean it's obvious
[Music]
can we not just fly over
him
okay I don't have to know it will come
to me naturally there's a way to the
outside world behind Vault let's
go but we first sleep right and train
right
right I think
so can I evolu
no can I
combine yes right on the minor
slab oh wait I just okay I'm getting I'm
understanding this more and
more the buff on this one is whenever I
put on there it will cost 20% MP
less the one that's on here we'll get a
10% power boost and 10% MP oh cost boost
oh not so
good uh and this one gets a 5% power
boost
n so let's put the
thuner onto the minor
[Music]
laab can you go back to the temple to
try to find maybe yeah but yeah it's
okay not sure if I would even make
it and survive
anyway
[Music]
um okay right now we don't have anything
anyway okay that's good
oh oh I can make a couple of these wait
this is permanent this
is isn't this
permanent good reason to kill more of
those
crabs
[Music]
oh oh
all of these are
permanent
[Music]
she I have 99 plus of those leaves man
maybe I don't need to pick any more of
those
[Music]
up maybe I'll make
this game gives me a lot of permanent uh
stat
Buffs okay I think I can do two two of
them and what do we
[Music]
want I feel like we're pretty like all
around
it right now
what what do I need to
[Music]
fix
maybe HP and
Agility
yeah and a bit more magic
power yeah okay uh let's see I'm not
going
to practice I'm going to go blind into
if it's one that I don't know ah it's
one that I don't maybe I just have to
flip
pages reading the biggest challenge of
them all oh no Survival game oh
no
okay what why am I so dump oh oh I
succeeded anyway really closely
[Music]
yeah at least I made
it
nice and then we sleep and we ran an
errand I
want this
please maybe one of
these good night
thanks
okay time
to spoiler alert there is more behind
fire
doll
interesting nice world
map okay now no need to teleport
anywhere we'll just go outside and then
go to B and fight him cook more stat
boost no no neat but I should eat the
ones that I
have
eat
wo sick 10 yo where did I get this one
again special increase free
wo let's go
[Music]
these leaves I said I shouldn't pick
them up
anymore I don't need them
anymore still picking them
up feels incomplete if I
don't
nice repeating bosses can earn more of
the stat boost items oh but no
exp but I guess that's fine because if
you could repeat the bosses and get all
of their XP you could get so high level
so
easily but I'd like to at least get exp
from these low uh level not low level
smaller
enemies when we repeat a fight that
would be nice
[Music]
okay let's give it a
try you think I
[Music]
fail
N I don't think so Shield Stone oh a r
Arrow blessings can be used in battle
after certain number of turns blessings
do not consume and PE blessings can only
be used once during a battle and it does
not consume turns oh it's like a special
a
[\h__\h] hey they look kind of different
when we were inside the cave those
monsters they look even cuter out here
in the
daylight
okay
um we only have one of our minions out
why
why actually
why do you think Thunder would be good
on the stone enemies too probably not
right but I don't know how important
elements
[Music]
are okay we good this looks
good yeah we can do it we can do it
elements aren't super important okay at
least I know the only thing the game
told me is that I should use thunder on
the steal
enemies that's all I need to
[Music]
know double swing on small small small
Golem
bonus and
[Music]
maybe
have really how fast do
I
yo so wellit maybe I can put them on now
then and let me
check thank
you
speed K of
props
[Music]
wow looks so
nice you
Chad they look so oh different colors
too
H I think I'll go for the pink one
though the ears too oh my
God
[Music]
yo yo I'm going to get so decked out
okay first of all let me
lose
down
Hood
happens
okay life uh changing of
clothes nowaki
got and let's put the cap on sorry
loading the pictures in takes a little
moment it's a bit heavy
[Music]
wait wait what I have to load everything
in on its
own ah suddenly slapped in my face by
this
ear okay
and appic costume change
bgm okay now let's put everything in
place
uh is it all
here ear right ear
left
uh yeah let's hide this no okay
ear
left M mine left not the viewers left
right like supposed to be like here but
then I'll like put it
behind me
is
it oh my god there have so many things
okay like
this it's like growing from the back of
my
head is that how she has it kind of
right kind
of and where is the other one ah
cute uh need
to you know if I put it here it won't
attach to anything I have to put it a a
little bit
higher
oh I want to attach it the same way the
other ones
attached oh H
[Music]
works kute it looks like a ribbon but if
you know then you know because you
know and
[Music]
then
oh
this this looks so good you did so well
so
[Music]
fast
she I could just wear this on my head
and still look nice you know how ladies
and like spa and Spa pictures and
massage pictures everywhere when they
put the towel around round their hair on
their head and it looks so nice H when I
try it it looks like
this such a
mess right that's on my boobs let me
change that wobbles to I know it's on on
a ribbon on a one part of the
ribbon
[Music]
okay oh yeah this this moves
better okay
[Music]
this goes behind my head I
think what am I what am I what have I
become let's move this
down yeah behind the ears I suppose
[Music]
yeah yeah maybe the cave a little bit
biger oh oh oh oh yeah this is good and
one more piece it's the back of the
cape uh oh I guess it should
be
here
is not
sure I
probably Cheeto are you here should it
be like
here I'm so de down it it looks like a
it looks like a new
outfit
oh wait let's a b
[Music]
more
oh if I just don't move so
much if I stay straight it looks like I
just got a new
[Music]
outfit
see wow
okay
perfect perfect do I look
cute do I look like a witch that sprung
out of an
r Wait I also kind of when I when I'm
wearing this this kind of reminds me of
d d me don't don't
me magical girl don't me the hat and the
pink color I think is doing
it
mag
poon
cute I'm casting Magic on you are you
[Music]
ready you are now in love with me
cute magic was a kiss magical kiss okay
where were
we sorry for that but I think it's worth
it to wear this while we're playing it
right uh what attack am I doing right
now what the [\h__\h] did I just do ah it
was the the minions attack okay okay I
think
no magic
needed oh the blessing sigle appears
around pberry when the blessing is ready
blessings going be
okay AR as Arrow doesn't cost a turn can
I does that mean I can do magic blast
and aru's arrow in one go probably
[Music]
she wa
oh if I follow this up with the magic
blast he's so
[Music]
dead strong sorry B I love
you and you've been protecting me so
well until now but now I can protect
myself and you need to understand that
[Music]
Strat crit crit and then normal crit
probably
yeah already in love with
you
[Music]
sweet no maybe he's like okay you proved
yourself doo do
doo no
oh no I'll miss him
he was friend shaped too like all of my
friends nothing
[Music]
changed I love this bird B is finally
gone don't say it like that that sounds
like that [\h__\h]
that good riddance the way is clear time
to explore the outside world eh
[Music]
before we go to the outside world we
should
[Music]
heal
okay can I have all my minions out here
in the world
too I no in this case it gets replaced
okay leave the forest yeah but I can
come back right
[Music]
is this the first time Shido made props
for me by the way they look so good you
should do it more
often I love
them the boundary between your forest
and the outside world magical
[Music]
forest she made them before but not that
often I
think her comics are not enough no I
love shido's
Comics you don't have to do anything
else but you
[Music]
know is it always going to be covered in
Piss while we're in here it's like I'm
looking into a toilet bowl
[Music]
in an
abandoned toilet bowl in the middle of
like a
ruin because it already started growing
Moss oh my God it keeps on being covered
in piz no oh wait it's a bit better now
at least the toilet bowl effect is
gone
well what's
[Music]
L what did Cheeto say make a comic prop
got it comic prop but what what would
that look like no one more prop that you
could make is the staff if you're bored
I'm going to be so decked
out don't no no no pressure no pressure
please no
pressure you made these so fast like
you're crazy oh wait already out I
thought it would be more like a whole
dungeon well thank God I guess this was
stinky Shido is on fire
[Music]
currently pistachio he's right there
girl no he's right there why why you
girls we we're seeing it he's right
there he's right there you don't even
have to tell
me it's not going to be in need of much
exploration although he
yo I feel
like normally you just go straight
unless you look at the mini map I
guess cuz I didn't I didn't I felt like
this was really hidden
now oh I wait you don't have to activate
these somehow I thought you might have
to activate them no not theable
[Music]
[\h__\h] sorry head was on
fire he talks to you when you just walk
to the
side sorry I I tried so hard to ignore
you I don't know why I really want that
pie can't skip I wanted to explore
before I talk to
him he looks so cute and
[Music]
freedy his outfit legit looks
like he just disguised link but his
outfit legit looks like it could be one
of Link's future
outfits it looks very link
the mustach mustach does look
fake yeah now link is blonde that's the
only problem otherwise I would say this
is
link really looks like
link love
linkler
pie oh you are giving it to
me wait what about the pies
[Music]
thanks for the money though Mouse does
it bother you you not like it poke poke
po po po
poke poke poke
poke okay I'll remove
it just this once
or it's chocolate could be chocolate try
biting into
it full power
[Music]
are you craving chocolate no no never
wouldn't be me
[Music]
show me illustration please not just
freie I'm sure you're cute please show
me she have no she has a name she must
have an
illustration I love
her green eyes blond
hair Warrior
Commander you can command me time
H what me what no just because of the
Hat you you are discriminating hat
wearers all over the
world what about my
pie there we
go looks like a Dr completely different
artist but actually I think the DLC
outfits are drawn by a different
artist than usual actually I have to
switch back again I want to switch back
anyway because I want to look like what
I look
like she cute
[Music]
she looks a little bit too young to be a
commander age
you want to
fight no no no
no why do you have your own sword in
illustration you have your
sword those eyebrows
I wish I could do
that ah it all stems from the Pope I
see I know where I have to go to
then makes sense the pop
[Music]
well she did say that's a shitty
sword it really seems to be I again
don't have all my pets out okay this is
a little bit
annoying there we go wow I don't have to
do this every time
[Music]
let's try the lightning
o oh all these
interesting Reflections I think this
gets four no oh no it doesn't spray up
then dog nice
[Music]
he Cris
I can't didn't you hear we cannot
capture
humans you crazy crazy person
[Music]
[Applause]
I thought I just heard a cat but I just
the
bgm
sad yeah this is not
pal that part of pal world really freaks
me out
still it's a very dark
side very very Dark
Side AR we
[Music]
home was that the Pope's orders
wait if he Ser yeah if he serves the
gods wouldn't he be an
[Music]
ally
uhuh he's that kind of [\h__\h]
[Music]
maybe a God himself and he just
pretends to the hum that he's
not and he just wanted all of the God's
power for himself he didn't want to
share
it the others I don't know could be one
storyline
[Music]
yeah but you realize you are a
FR her
motives church is always evil true in
RPGs
[Music]
yeah
fore e
[Music]
you mean
your
[Music]
mommy you know she also has these
psychopath eyes in frd when she
now when she's
like she has psychopath
eyes get some sleep get get get some
sleep just like black Joe said the
outside world isn't all it's cracked up
to be I just barely made it outside and
it's already bad Ralph said he'd fix the
situation so let's take a Brea before
heading out
again makes sense but I I don't think
think I have any training power right
now
man can
[Music]
I let's try
something oh I wanted to do outfit
change too
yeah back cuz I already forgot what it
looked like back to this
one eat a
me pie
Berry and and and P
[Music]
Berry okay where were
those what was it turtles or they're
behind this right I have to fight them
first I
[Music]
think crabs I thought was Turtles for
some reason
oh this gets all of
[Music]
them
wa I wonder if that works on the crabs
too because I feel like they should be
reflective
too
nice that was
strong over
here can we kill them this time
should it should be possible I was able
to do the
tool and I didn't even use the shield
Stone last time I'll use it this
time I can yes I can of course I can
let's see I want to see if it
reflects I mean it should reflect any in
any case I guess on any enemy but okay
pet summon we going to we need both of
them we need all of everybody's power
and I guess I could also back myself up
up with the Magic
Shield I'm never really lacking MP and I
can heal my mp with the
bird M easy oh this hits all of them
let's see how much damage it
does
oh that took a lot of my mp
and still a bit of my HP sheh but it's
okay the that was big damage if I do
that again we're done
[Music]
soon okay
Mouse what was I doing uh
should I yeah I need one MP
heal
possibly maybe the frog
[Music]
one I'll do this again even if it's not
that
necessary here we
go yeah one dead
yeah the minions are going to help take
this one down oh
dead
yay easy we're doing
it wow okay that was
simple way better than before I leveled
up of course I'm stronger than before
but also it's a bit about the strategy
too I changed my
[Music]
strategy secondary
circles book of magic circles that can
boost the strength of magic or make it
more
efficient is that the thing that you put
on the side the like buff
[Music]
sounds like it the supports lab yeah
right can I do it
[Music]
here well maybe I have to do it
home secondary Circle
oh I can make only this one intermediate
magic
slob I could almost make this one
Whatever that missing ingredient
is show ingredients and hint show and
hint
what ah ah dwarf golden Essence wait
didn't we like have this before
so it's like possible to get
it isn't is it the
potion this one oh I can make it then I
okay I don't can I make it
here no right register for AutoCraft oh
okay no we'll make it when we're home I
guess there's nothing else for me to do
here so I I guess I'll go home
maybe I'll do one more fight for
items should we fight like we can fight
the lion again
[Music]
right you guys said I can we do uh boss
fights there's no one
here no one here maybe he's up there and
where we met him first no that no that
was a different mon
maybe we can fight him there's a chest
in the pudding
[Music]
cave optional bosses
only okay pudding
cave
put two chests what did I missed them
[Music]
let's
go oh about trying to plant monsters
that were too strong oh you think I'm
strong enough for those now
guys I'm not too sure about
it pudding cave was this way
no yes I
remembered big pudding small
pudding purple pudding with witch
head kind of impersonating me
puzzle in progress also I don't think I
ever went this way did
I deep pudding
cave perhaps
not well that looks new there's a chest
there is that one of the ones you
meant let's go they should be weak but
there a lot of them so okay maybe maybe
it wasn't not necessary to use that W
it's like a
what that
works
yo
[Music]
yo Only the strongest one are still
standing
Oh I thought that would be enough should
have done the double one again but we
have my boar for a
[Music]
reason
nice some of those leaves I don't have
so many of so I'm happy to receive them
the blue ones I think
especially a
recipe sticky
BMP sticky bomp
interesting oh another fight okay
[Music]
not sticky
sticky can't believe I missed out on a
sticky bomb
recipe just completely ignored this
path don't know
why my intrusive thoughts told me to go
somewhere else
[Music]
nice
open Leaf ping extract plus four okay
some healing I think or was it MP I'm
not sure what it heals
but
uh teleportation
oh one more of these
is this the two chests you guys
meant or did you not mean in this
room oopsie I forgot about
it not worth
[Music]
it sorry I'm in a rush I thought his
little tippy toes would protect
me I thought you can go deeper in this
cave was this a was a different
cave
oh where am I how did I get here who am
I this is is is this where I just
went oh
yeah I guess it was the other cave
M okay but indeed two chests were in
here that we wanted to get okay what's
this over there
though something for
later Big Orange in this dungeon Big
Orange hermit
crab I can't seem to find any uh way to
go anywhere
else not here right not in this
okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay let's move
here oh was he strong n not really right
especially now we fought him before
let's find him again he could drop some
cool item
[Music]
yeah
woo W laser
[Music]
this still does so much damage even
though I spec so much into
magic kind of crazy kind of is telling
me that maybe I was not meant to be a
witch
necessarily oh this one I also
ignored what the [\h__\h] foxes I missed the
whole fox stand are they strong no
they're not
what the [\h__\h] just happened did I steal
my
mp or did I not have any to begin
with
them uh okay let's
see they stole it huh those are
[Music]
[\h__\h] will they do that every turn
then this seems kind of like something I
would have wanted to avoid anyway when I
was here first cuz that's kind
of oh yeah they stole it again I guess
then you can just do physical
attacks and then you'll probably be
[Music]
fine oh I got some MP back though ah
because it's a DOT uh heal as well
[Music]
nice
oh kill
please
[Music]
n okay yeah but they are kind of strong
I feel like they do be kind of strong
the fire do helped me out right now hey
yo big is this
place what the [\h__\h] is this a statue not
an enemy we got to go there maybe it'll
give me
something can I just have my pets like
is there anywhere where I can select
which pets I want to have summoned by
the beginning of the
fight that would be
good they're going to steal my mp anyway
so it's not worth healing it
now that's what I was wondering
yeah whichever is with you is summon but
that's it okay and the rest I guess I
have to summon in the
fight let's do
agility going to actually use my
stimulants because they're kind of
annoying
[Music]
I should have summoned the pet I
forgot oh I need MP for
[Music]
that oh wait forgot
small brain
wah very very small
memory I'm working my brain is working
on a floppy disc
guys o
[Music]
nice that was a mistake
actually n it's okay
[Music]
dial up yeah I can do the dial up inet
sound you know it you must have heard
it I don't know how I did it
anymore white fox marble what's this a
marble that the white fox vomits up
periodically containing its Soul equip
ipping it makes you slightly lighter and
increases your MP
recovery from Tool use and
defense it's a combat Aid to
craft this will not come to life
right
right this fox doesn't look like Golem
just a piece of stone she doesn't even
speak first time she's not speaking I
wonder who made I wonder who made it
it's so delicately crafted oh that's
[Music]
it can I kill more of
these wait
yeah ah [\h__\h] forgot my
thingy oh well I'll prove you I don't
need any extra
steps or
Buffs
[Music]
oh gosh they are annoying aren't
they wa with the c a wa with the help me
a oh by the
way speaking of cute
girls we're going to do
the Y magical Yap toy what what
was what was the name of the game again
C Grand blue you have to
see collabs sometime
soon I think we found the date
already Grand yeah but like I'm really
really wondering how is that even going
to what what are we going to what how is
it going to go down I don't understand
anything I have no idea what to
expect do you think we'll need all four
povs anybody who has an idea who play
Grand see
[Music]
online not really okay then I'm probably
not going to
stream although I'll maybe have a
reservation for a stream up so I can
still get your
advice in the
chat more like you know aimed at me
me are they dropping nice items I
haven't been paying
[Music]
attention you think the ghost will give
me better
advice maybe not all of
them laa Vice yeah
I'll keep an eye on you
guys drop stuff I need to the stat oh to
make it come
alive wait but I so far it didn't tell
me that it needs anything at
all uh what am I doing uh oh
[Music]
yeah I have so many of these healing
items still I think now is a good time
to use them
yeah yeah yeah just smaller smaller MP I
don't need that
[Music]
much games fa
Q's
yes you are if I didn't have chat when I
play games I would look up [\h__\h] on the
internet all the time like I used to
when I play t
Symphonia but those times are long
gone I have chat to backseat me through
everything
you need to finish that no no no I told
them I don't have the EPO yet and uh I
think another one of us doesn't have it
either and I brought up that we could
probably do it together and the others
were like yeah let's just do it
together so we're
[Music]
good you had internet back up playing
back when
tail yeah yeah ah it's how old do you
think Tes of Symphonia is and how old do
you think I
[Music]
am Castle Symphonia is not that old
when I hear something funny
about the time when I was taking a break
from streaming to
move and we were I was I wanted
to uh
paint the
walls before I moved
in and since I thought okay this is
going to be
a very long-term home so I want to
really paint it nicely so I painted my
plan was to paint a couple of
rooms not just one or not just one
wall So the plan was to paint one room
fully because it was a smaller one
anyway uh and another room one
big long wall fully but the rest
not and
then I don't know and then another room
also just oneall so basically three
rooms but only one wall in two of them
and one full
[Music]
room but I got help I
asked my mommy she said yeah of course I
can help him
painting and from my brother so we set a
date it was I think I think we wanted to
do it in two days or did we do it in one
day I think we may have ended up doing
it in one day and I just did Corrections
on the second
day not sure what haveen to this but
basically I went out to buy the colors
right and buy supplies and all
that uh
I did
that and let me try one more time to
talk to this
thing oh okay huh no extra again colors
no I have some nice colors except I'm
kind of I kind of regret one of the
color choices because it didn't end up
looking that
good sad but I'm not going to redo it
what's done is
done I'm going to live with this now
I have to deal with
it and but yeah so I I bought everything
I prepared everything on the day before
so and then the day comes and we're
painting and we start painting no first
we start like uh
taping the sides right like
putting uh tape on the edges and the ah
right the plastic stuff on the
ground and
then I think I was still there for the
beginning when we started but then very
soon after like while me I think it was
like me and my mom painting one wall one
room while we told my brother because we
didn't have so many a painting tools we
just told my brother to go into the
other room and prepare all the taping
the edge taping and all that
there woo
while we're doing the painting in one
room and then he ran out of tape and the
plastic sheet and all that so after a
while we weren't even finished with the
wall my
mom oh my mom told me oh we need more
paint we need more this we need more
that we're running out of paint already
of this one even though we thought it
would be
enough um and we need uh yeah more tape
it's not enough OB
T so I was sent out to buy more like
really early in the day what should I
fight what did I come here
for uh I guess I
could what what did I come here
for
wait no not for tape I didn't come here
tape what about wasn't there some crabs
or something with a
[Music]
Golem wait did I go up
here and check this way did
I perhaps only
I but didn't we go here for something
too I'm so
confused why am I doing this anyway
what's my current Quest get some sleep
no maybe I will maybe I
will but let me
[Music]
find well continue my story in a
moment in a
moment about over
there and okay so like an hour in or so
I go out to buy
stuff extra stuff I come back it took me
like an hour or so maybe 40 50 minutes I
don't know I come
back then they're really exhausted and
like want to take a break so I'm being
next I'm being asked at least I'm not
like myself trying to escape the work no
my mom and my brother tell me you know I
we need we need some food my brother
wants a la
cust
classic classic
and they want you know the cold drinks
and this and that so I go I come back I
immediately go out I just start becoming
the one who continues to avoid the
painting process and just buy [\h__\h] all
the time I come back with drinks and
food uh and then next they're again like
lacking something again ran out of color
actually a different color this time so
I have to go back again I became the
erand girl perfectly
I actually I wouldn't have minded like
helping out some more with the painting
actually it was kind of exhausting but
when you do the with the big roll when
you Goos whoosh with the big roll but I
could have done like the edges I don't
know oh these ones didn't we want to try
these ones too eventually let's
see yeah so I I had to run errands
several times I felt like kind of bad
because I wasn't really doing anything
but like I was the one with the money so
and it's my color my paint so obviously
I'm going to buy it right I could have
given them my card perhaps and have them
buy it if they wanted to but no they
just were like yeah go go you
go like
okay wait these only have 35
HP how are they strong I guess if if you
can't kill them in the first turn and
back then we only had that AOE that with
how distance these enemies were it would
not have hit them all then next it would
have been their turn and they would have
killed me
maybe don't
know so you did all the buying on foot
uh no no no no no what like I would uh
like go with Uber or whatever yeah I
ubered back and forth back and forth to
save
time I think that'll go back
now but yeah and then by the end of the
day everybody was like really exhausted
and I felt bad cuz I wasn't that
exhausted but I helped at the end I got
to help
some uh at the end I I did help to
finish some painting in one room at
least
M with her car my mom doesn't have a car
we don't have
cars and
then uh I
realized already in the
evening uh that some spots looked kind
of uneven
though
unfortunately and I was like maybe it's
the weird light from my lamps so I
waited until the next day when there was
good light from outside and I was like
nope yep there are like weird
uneven areas where I can see the brush
strokes and stuff or the difference from
the edges that are made with a brush and
the big areas that are made with the the
roll thingy I was like damn it yeah I
think I have to fix this because it's
quite a lot of this so I tried on the
second day to like fix smaller things
and details but then partially I made it
kind of worse because I didn't realize
that you should do it with the spongy
roller not with the um brush I just
thought it's smaller area so I might as
well do it with a brush
H but after it dried and I really tried
my best it was a lot especially around
the edges where the tape was originally
I found so many like
little holes in the paint so to
say I was on it for hours and then even
after that after it all dried it still
looked like m not much
better yeah need some real skill yeah I
did some research and then watched some
painting videos from painting pros and
figured out ah okay you really need to
go over it with the
same uh like material that you used for
it originally because you're going to
see a difference
between uh the brush strokes and the
sponge like the texture is very
different I thought for touchups it's
going to be
[Music]
fine it was a lot of work and then even
after all of that it was wasn't really
finished but I was like whatever because
then I started decorating like putting
stuff putting the furniture in putting
um stuff on the walls and honestly when
there's definitely a lot of imperfection
still but when just like standing here
when it's not a completely empty room
then it doesn't really stand out anymore
especially with some things being
covered by paintings or
whatever so it doesn't bother me anymore
more it's okay I tried fixing some
things some things got better others
didn't but yeah it
was I want to say thank you to my to my
mom and my brother for helping me with
painting because last time I painted in
an uh apartment in the previous one I
asked my friends to help me and that was
fun too but uh you know feel a little
bit less bad about asking my family to
help me especially cuz my mom is just
like generally very motivated to help me
with anything
really so you know how
about I want to do some defense and
strength let's see what this mini game
is all
about Big Ups to BR and M M was so
motivated oh
[Music]
button mashing button
mashing oh this is really
easy it's always
x m turtle with stone on my back perfect
bonus even though it was first
time
yay Wow
%. Let's
go e
oh yeah we wanted to look at this stuff
I think we can um buff one of
these oh no I have to craft it first all
right let's see we could make this one
if we craft the potion
thingy H this
one's this one's just for the other
is I think cuz you need this one in
order to make this one I
think and this one in order to make some
of the
[Music]
others I guess the only one we can
really make is this
one which is good
okay
[Music]
uh uh yeah dwarf Golem
Essence it's
might feel a little lonely in house
wants to spend time with her kids yeah
probably I think any mother
dad like lives far from her kids and
they're all grown up I think every
mother would feel like
[Music]
that
okay crafting
now
cting like a
boss okay guess I'm going to put it up
here at Cost 10
plus what 10 plus plus
10% what does that mean I get 10 no what
uh what
the uh what ah oh the MP cost will be
increased by
[Music]
10 and plus another 10% but it's going
to be boosted by 110% power okay so it
goes from 512 to
564 ah 59
MP that's a lot for that skill because
it's already kind of
expensive but okay
sure why
not why not we could have given it to
the lightning one too I could make
another one
honestly right
this is so atle
[Music]
here oh I can use it in multiple magic
Oh Oh I thought it was going to tell me
I can only have one of this type but no
it seems like I can use the same one
here as
well without removing this one oh
oh oh now the adding of several circles
is actually happening I see it
now it's if we add the third one it's
going to fill up the whole
circle
[Music]
interesting wait we can add it here
too let's go they're all going to be
stronger
now
nice m
[Music]
can I make I can make this one and this
one
oh a these items M this is from the blue
crabs which are relatively easily to
access this one is isn't this one from
one of the boss
monsters and this one I don't
know these
[Music]
ones
oops can we do something here
again uh no I don't know no
no guess not
[Music]
oh these ones didn't I use this in order
to make one of these oh on their own on
their own they give me two MP increase
does this mean like maybe this might be
an ingredient for one of these as
well maybe not
because yeah but I feel like this wasn't
one of the recipes
save it for Big M okay but this one I
think I safe to
use the
lais JY Trac you mean the lais or you
mean the fox marble
Shard no I think I already used a couple
of them now for
this save it this one
too no Fox
M okay
M okay I think we can
[Applause]
[Music]
sleep uh
Mommy
Mommy Mommy Mommy with the
pie SM SM
[Music]
cute I'm dreaming of the pie that my
mommy made for
[Music]
me is the
wait the pie the better pie that the
traitor has he has it from somewhere my
mom oh who huh are you thinking with me
are you following my
thoughts maybe my mom is the
[Music]
Pope the traitor is not my mom
yes see I knew the answer because she's
me I think this girl might like pie
[Music]
okay who's Ralph
again
Ralph
Ralph he's having nightmares about me
burning him my
life Merchant
[Music]
you're alive but you're in
prison not much
better I wonder if Ralph has sorted
everything out yet I should go back and
ask him how to get fresh strawberries
and
delicious right asking the big and the
important questions
only here we
go and
follow the golden sign oh yeah fruited
portal into the toilet
bowl
ew I can smell it I smell it when I walk
through
here the worst smell of them
all thank god oh hey Ralph sorry I
forgot who you were this you know I look
at you and I don't think about a Ralph
you don't look like a Ralph to
[Music]
me no match for me
Justice she
Justice
Just judgment judgment judment
[Music]
she kind of has a pick voice
almost but like older and more
[Music]
raspy not
Justice the pie maker is my mommy
I know it I'll smell the pie I'll walk
in and I'll smell
it no matter how
far don't say that that will make me
very sad
[Music]
sad so sad that the world will cry
buckets fresh
[Music]
drumers that's pry good
too yeah so much better than DED ones
[Music]
M tomorrow my day off guys right let's
go let's go and then Fallout and then
early morning stream no and then anime
and then Fallout and and then anime and
then early morning stream and then
Fallout
[Music]
that's I thought we could switch Fallout
and the anime stream we could switch it
f maybe that's smarter I'm not sure
[Music]
up to me I'll think about it yeah cuz
I'm thinking after the morning stream
I'm going to take a nap but what if I'm
still like if I don't get a good nap and
I'm tired for Fallout but nah actually I
think
yeah cuz no I think there's enough time
really for the nap I'll be
fine probably
uh-huh that's pretty impressive for a
bird normally the birds get eaten by The
Bard BS if anything do it would that be
better for you or why are you
[Music]
so oh do you want it well if you're a
warrior you should do it yourself if you
deserve this kind of
enhancement
I he's just trying to sell
[Music]
it it's all about the
money off to the B plane to get fresh
strawberries B plane is just west of the
Merchants Road left
okay left
side left side right
[Music]
side do Boris eat strong
do I have to fight them they look like
really lowlevel low
Bobs you to 50 the
[\h__\h] get on to my
[Music]
level my B versus B this feels like
Pokemon now like the overcrowding of one
one of the
same animal like this this thing could
be a Pokmon I feel like cuz it's like
relatively simple design it looks like a
Pokmon that would show up in the early
levels in the early regions maybe even
in the first region close to the
beginning
[Music]
Town wow they look fancy
now I can't
[Music]
see only going to hit two I think but we
haven't used this in a while
[Music]
you saw a friend of cor with a stash
wait maybe that's the one I was talking
about that she used in a
thumbnail 15 second com it's not
bothering me I like it but yeah I guess
it's whing the whole time not much
Variety in battle music I
suppose is one criticism one could
[Music]
say
possibly okay do they want me to go
towards the
[Music]
nights yeah H there's another mustache
Trader what the [\h__\h] they all have
[Music]
mustaches why is that horse like a
statue it looks like it's stopped in the
animation of
walking did Your Wagon break again we're
not here to fix wagons can you not
do basic maintenance on your
own can you guys pull your own wagons
with a better wagon I can make my
deliveries even faster but since you
guys keep delivering stuff to theil
Village there's no way the wagon won't
get damaged thank you guys thank look
it's on tight you graceful little we
protect you from witches I'm more likely
to die at your hands than not of a witch
that's right I like this
guy yes let's help this is like a will
you help like a side quest
[Music]
from thank you
Travy one has 700 yeah I need nothing
H waste of my
[Music]
time but I'll do it for the
glory
uh is that hitting all of them I think
so
[Music]
she oh he's strong
though if this is only to one
enemy it's not really worth it is it
[Music]
music keeps me
motivated okay okay okay finish it
minions come on borun yeah you're the
best so many boards around us and I've
always known you were the
best would never replace you don't
worry look at these cowards are you not
scared of are you not scared of me being
this
close I'm on the verge of starvation
I've got bigger worries than witches how
long are these worries going to keep
this witch on going it's been over a
decad since the spring war ended is that
another witch spring game witch spring
war that would be funny
why do we have to keep sending them
supplies it seems like you don't get
along with the Warriors how could I take
what you want from the wagon is too
broken to take back with me anyway what
do you have in in there forget it
they're all useless to me I want
this oh a
shield I doubt that it will be visible
when we carry it
but yo a yo
shoes too so worth doing this holy [\h__\h]
it's equipment for lower and Gloria but
it might be of some usion battle okay
I'll take it thank you
yo let's go let go CU I don't have those
but how much did that do oh
oh oh that's fine bangs body
[Music]
investigate that's really
vain oh interesting prompt something's
going to show up big bo b mommy she's
cowling I didn't know she could do that
she became baby bubble
[Music]
[Applause]
bubble she has also the ly ears what the
[\h__\h] are all witches lop bunnies the
[\h__\h]
cute
[Music]
cute she's dressed kind of like warm for
winter
why she's like the blue version of me oh
my
God cute cute why is she so cute oh is
she going to hate me I hope not please
do not be my
rival let's be
[Music]
[Applause]
friends Luna
she feels
like she she she's giving
[Music]
meai I am Senai
and aqua Senai combined
[Music]
Vibes no it's not over I haven't gone
collecting
[Music]
yet oh
rival acquired for real for
[Music]
real why are about it let me handle it
yo her staff is kind of cool
it ate so many strawberries it became
strawberry
colored oh but that boar is with us now
we have
friends that boar can vouch for
me the one that I mind control can vouch
for me because I mind control it
[Music]
th4 oh now it's
not
now now they don't show question mark
question mark question mark anymore for
anything above a thousand
interesting I wonder if it's like it has
to be a certain amount of HP away from
you for it to not show or if it's just
specific enemies
let's burn them let's burn the whole
family wait where's my boar my boar is
not in the
[Music]
fight wow she has ice
magic cool why did they all go for me
hey hey hey there's another one standing
right next to me are you seeing that
[\h__\h] o o
[Music]
wait their
reaction yeah they don't react like that
when I bring the other one out they were
all like a y you
see funny
[Music]
I story
bosses guess this is not considered a
boss uh oh I can choose who she
attacks focus on the
boss I like that phrase as she says oh
counter yeah counter
kill nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice oh no being hit by your own child
suppos a child alleged child I don't
really
know could be
[Music]
wrong yeah we're past 6 hours honestly
today it feels a little bit
more longer like 6 hours feel longer
than usual but it's okay I am lagging
the game so I'm
[Music]
chilling just want to snack man I wish I
could
[Music]
snack stay in the party please that
would be so cool I wonder if she's going
to
[Music]
although I'm not a big fan of this kind
of not my
favorite anime trope
[Music]
like you love as I wouldn't say
love I think I tend to
go energetic ones quite often like
my favorite
ones cool types are cool too but not too
cool because like kisada was
cool but
uh velvet no vet different game what's
the other one the uh uh what was her
name
Shion although Shion wasn't really yeah
I think I want to compare to Velvet like
velvet from T of berseria she was like
cooler than kisada like different kind
of cool I would prefer kadas type of
cool over velvet I think cuz velvet is
like like lacks
emotion [\h__\h] up kind of
cool
Shion was soon but not soon like this uh
chick that we've met right
now that was way more
animate T while Shion is like a more
realistic
like sweet sensitive kind of
tun it's a little bit little bit
different so there's like you know so
many different types even within the
tund
rainbow can't put them all into one
bucket
right I have quite specific
preferences as
well oh I met another witch like me but
she's not very friendly although I
didn't get any for strawberries I did
get the B's Captain too B Captain St
that Ral wanted I should take it to him
and get
paid yeah you're reminding me to go take
the teleportation tool what are you
trying to hide from me eh you want to
stop me from exploring some
more but I want to run around I want to
make my own
decisions what's over
here nothing except
more but I'm going to explore that
another time perhaps
[Music]
when I'm stronger cuz I feel like these
areas are always the more dangerous ones
but we can check it out let's let's walk
into that path on the right
side and see what we can see I miss magu
I [\h__\h] love magu man her personality
her
[Music]
design was it the Suns we just
met okay okay so here they're actually
telling me to turn back I'm fine with
that m
yeah the path probably
too
yeah let's go back
nor she's the original hold that Ls up
as she gets no up yeah and I feel like
she's not exaggerating it I feel like an
anime T it can be very
[Music]
exaggerated chill chill I'm just
checking things out
it felt more natural I
think oh I love I
love those those three are
the holy sues of anime history but like
I feel like newer generations of anime
Watchers they won't even know them even
though they're
legendary sh sh Shak sh
you go you delivered the item request a
th000 gold
[Music]
woohoo I'm honestly happy that Louise is
being counted into the Holy Trinity of
Tes uh because I feel like out of those
three animes zon notu Kaa was like
even though it's the one I actually
watched the others I didn't really watch
I feel like that one is the least
popular out of these free
no oh she was so over the top but back
then I was more into
it yeah I know it's so violent too I
think that's what I liked about it she
was not just T she was also
violent don't gu is the only one of
those I know oh really I feel like
generally it's less known than the other
animes for some reason I that was the
one I watched earlier I love the let's
go they had the best music
too can get tyring well yeah I yeah but
in anime is f she's
fine I love her
[Music]
so good
[\h__\h] kiss
[Music]
first
kiss it wasn't kiss me did I say kiss me
it was first kiss
[Music]
first so good yeah classic anime
openings and the old ones man there so
many new ones I want to go back to the
time where it was actually into anime I
don't know if it's really just that I M
matured or if it's also the quality of
anime that
changed and the the I don't
know
but maybe it's both but I feel like it's
mostly me just maturing and losing
interest
mostly I'm gaslighting myself really I
think it's the maturing and also my
interest changing but that is just also
through
maturing my
interests I you know you know the for
example shun the story of Shogun feels
like it could have totally been an anime
especially cuz it's playing in
Japan uh
but I'm glad it's not an anime because
it has insanely beautiful
visuals I think one thing I anime can
have really great visuals too but maybe
I just got tired of
it there's certain Animation Studios
which which style I really like but at
the same time maybe it's just too
repetitive I don't know and they can do
stuff that you can't really do easily
with real shows so to say but at the
same time it works the other way around
too like the beauty of
like real people's skin texture and all
that and beautiful traditional outfits
being recreated in in costumes that are
absolutely incredible and and insane
Landscapes and [\h__\h] man that's like
those things are better in real shows
and I'm just like really really digging
it when something is aesthetically
pleasing as [\h__\h]
what yeah yeah I what wait what what
what wait what what what wait what what
wait I I I wonder if gu knows that the
main protagonist of Fallout New Vegas is
Chan
Bing
what
what I thought you were going to point
out that in the show Fallout the show
that uh the dad is the same actor as in
Desperate Housewives the dude one of the
dudes that's why he felt so familiar to
me he's in the game voiced by Matt Perry
hey
y who my favorite character from the
talu
[Music]
franchise I could say Kuroko but she's
up there but she might not be my
[Music]
favorite maybe she
is she's kind of crazy I don't think if
I would watch that anime for the first
time in my life now maybe I would not
like her but she's she's got a special
spot in my
heart something something is like bit
boring annoying maybe I don't know
and then the short-haired girl is also
annoying Satan was a long-haired
blackhaired girl right and then the
short-haired you know they they both
felt or one of them at least felt so
whimper wimpy to me
like cuz Satan was the one who can't use
magic I think right
right we had had was kind of cute but
then like kind of
annoying I don't know I still like them
all as a group but
this would be maybe why I didn't like
them as much
U yeah there were a lot of good side
characters uh I think anyway anyway
what's what are we
[Music]
tanging oh yeah
definitely I prefer to
addo rail gun over index
[Music]
the show is better but I do really like
the index
[Music]
girl thank you for this
Lea very very likeable and cute I love
the oversized clothes
yeah ra gun had really good
Pace witch cles
[Music]
what's wrong with you why you judge me
like
[Music]
that I'm not even saying that show is
good he just like
something to watch when I'm
[Music]
like no brain usage
required it's there's definitely it's
like one of the worst shows I watch yeah
I'll give you
[Music]
that because it's just so obnoxious is a
lot of
[Music]
time yeah a lot of unfunny jokes just oh
my
God obnoxious characters I'll give you
that yeah and I I will I'll be
the the third one to tell you that not
the first one not the last one I'll be
one of the people to tell you that I
agree with that yeah yeah yeah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] Loft rocks too way too
[Music]
many uh no who the [\h__\h] are you like I
like your outfit though
[Music]
yeah exactly unsettle
chicken [\h__\h] yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's so good silence is good thank God
they don't use laughing
tracks
[Music]
God if you think about it how much
filler that is is
also all the time like they're
definitely waiting a lot for the laugh
tracks there's so many moments where you
could have saved
time how much did somebody do the math
how much filler that actually is like if
they cut all of that and make it like a
normal show make the pacing like a
normal show without laughing tracks how
much shorter the episodes would be oh my
God
crazy crazy difference probably
yeah they artificially extended duration
[Music]
forcefully it's Eerie of course it
is when you remove
it weird interaction hey what the [\h__\h]
you wanted to accidentally kiss from me
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] boys I knew you were one of
them
oh
a you we are not
[Music]
friends be so
nice no what the
hell
hi is he the singer of the song
can we fight him
please we're not
friends yeah let's go
380 wait
what what the [\h__\h]
mut the [\h__\h] m a
minute this is not
[Music]
acceptable I'm bringing out the big guns
because I feel like that may have been a
one time thing in terms of
damage I'm going to get
[Music]
you is it going to explode on us
no okay okay there we go there we go
there we go there we go there we go you
scared me a little bit for a
[Music]
moment
fast
interesting see those shows as fast for
kind of yeah cheap like fails the
appetite kind of but it's not good for
your body not good for your brain
because you're getting brain
fried very shallow World let me tell
[Music]
you she's just fed by pie everything can
you imagine having so much like
motivation and the
determination and just like reason to go
through life for
pie but it's more than just pie if you
have to think deeper about it oh thought
I was standing on there uh for her the
pie equals her mom she probably doesn't
even realize that herself that much but
she's not looking for the pie she's
actually looking for her
mommy yeah
it's more than just that what the [\h__\h]
are those
cute
[Music]
what mom is
pie not to be seen uh uh
difficult Merchant must
wait are you just the same Merchant from
before and you took off your
musters they didn't have enough money to
pay more actors so they're just using
the same actors and putting mustaches on
[Music]
them the water looks so
good it's so clear
[Music]
La Village I should explore La Forest
first
okay oh so what's what's here it's
right you won't find the pie maker here
AKA my
[Music]
mommy treasure hey what the [\h__\h] they
got a whole Camp
here wait I'll find these first cuz they
have a lot of treasure
[Music]
chests I just body killed me with one
shot never mind we're good we're
[Music]
good oh maybe maybe I'll end it soon
actually cuz I have to R to chat it's
getting uh to turn 11:00 p.m. very soon
probably should end it soon it's not
reflecting what
why
[Music]
okay sounds like a
plan so chill though I'm having a good
time we're definitely going to play this
more next week probably
continuing I cannot say proper sentences
my words are
all my words place all over
our uh
[Music]
actually a stroke you mean a stroke
seems like you're having a stroke
[Music]
too English
though
please oh we got a new armor stronger
looking one way stronger looking one a
yo wait what what the [\h__\h] did we get
iron
armor plus 12 what this is the one I
just
got it just makes us a bit more slow in
terms of
agility but I think that's worth it
shees
[Music]
gold 300
whoa wait where's your you have a secret
chest over
[Music]
there
wa pick up there it is a they were
hiding that one but I see it on the mini
map you cannot fool me is
this Southeast should I be
[Music]
here I'm going to get lost but hey wait
there's
treasure oh
berries looks like
cherries thank you for the membership
[Music]
welcome what the [\h__\h] is
this what's this chain
somebody somebody chained to this at the
top an oldfashioned trap probably set in
a tree have to be careful avoiding these
I'm sure that's not not necessary the
train is Rusty so I doubt the Trap will
work
uh
sus suspicious statement M for 14 months
OMG let's
go where am
I whoa whoo was I supposed to come here
anyway I don't know let me go back let's
still investigate I guess no
okay oh that's a lot of people
wa [\h__\h] uh it's okay A lot of them are
just low
Bobs this game looks really cute it is
it
[Music]
is everybody's attacking me
does it reflect
now no not really not that far
huh okay then we'll clean up the trash
first
uh it's hard work but it's honest
work today I watched video from John
Oliver about corn in
America but this is one of the few
videos of John Oliver where I was
like what
what I oh no I'm going to
die please stop attacking me now thank
you we're just about to watch
wait I did
die I'll find these later if I have
to oh it's
moving wait stop moving
huh is is it about corn syrup it's about
see I didn't really keep anything about
that in my brain
even it's
about all kinds of things H it's about
how I think in America most farming is
corn and then there's some things about
Farms like some weird like laws or so
like you can exploit the
system by splitting your
Farms only on paper into like 66 Farms
or so like blah blah blah blah blah man
yeah subsidies
like and if you're not a farmer that
Farms [\h__\h] ton of corn then you're kind
of [\h__\h] like if you farming like a
variety of things
you don't get any support from the
country and blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah it was a lot of
yapping your corn is so weird it's sweet
that's not weird that's good I still
dream of trying white corn again in my
life where where was that where I ate
like white corn and I was like holy
[\h__\h] this is the most amazing corn I've
ever had in my life I had that somewhere
where was it did I tell you about it
the white corn I had I already love
normal corn but that white corn was like
[Music]
OMG heot no it was not in the
elotes you can buy those frozen damn I
don't ever see them here I need to find
them I feel like it was in America
though wait looking for the pie hey I
was like about to say hey there's
someone who has uh pie Berry as their
profile picture they must be a big fan
of pie Berry or the game it's it's
[Music]
you
okay fie fie my boy killed
you oh my
God you love cornbread no no no no no I
don't think so
I don't think I would love
cornbread by far not as much as
I love
[Applause]
[Music]
corn porn
did she just Rob him she's a Savage I'm
telling you she's actually a psychopath
but such a cute
one she can totally like mind control
all of us into thinking she's a cutie
FTI but in reality she's a [\h__\h]
psychopath man which just like being
fooled by her
cuteness yeah she's a sociopath probably
rather than a psychopath
Alfredo gave me a really delicious pie
is his mom a pie maker maybe she's my
mom too I should follow him Alfredo has
gone to the south of laak first okay
game wants me to go
south well we should fight one of
these there's no oh they run
away ah okay I was about to say are
they something I have to shoot but it
wasn't showing up
but yes they
[Music]
are nice didn't have anything to shoot
like that ever since
our encounter in our homeland home home
Forest is this South guys can you help
me out tell me the
direction no oh you guys are
rude it's a bit misleading more like
horn
don't know well I guess because corn can
be sweet is I didn't really consider it
sweet different kind of
sweet I'll have to try it for sure at
one point I don't think I've had it
[Music]
before could be wrong
wow
wow weak weak
mofos South
West
oh we're here again
oh yeah Quest tells me to go here thank
God
although I don't think
they're not killable but yo he looks
like he needs some
pie he looks like he hasn't eat
forever maybe maybe not pie maybe let's
feed him our [\h__\h]
[Music]
bird k
uh even with free kids I don't know if
they could handle a
wolf it's cute how they're sized down
models of like chiy versions of the
other
Merchants they're like literally like
they they're born into that job they're
groomed to become that job they're
they're wearing the clothes they have
that hairstyle they have that leaf on
their head they're destined for it and
they have no
choice you will be a
merchant poor poor
[Music]
animal the RP man
love
[Music]
it oh there it comes with the pack okay
now they're overwhelmed and we'll kill
[Music]
them somehow I feel a little bit less
guilty and I'm killing them rather than
watching these kids bully the
animals I don't know why it's all [\h__\h]
up oh they're only 80
HP
a because nobody they're not getting
anything to eat
[Music]
if they had pie they would they would be
your
PR well yeah I don't know why I'm
fighting them if they don't have
Pie as you know I don't care about the
future of these kids as I said
yesterday don't care
[Music]
I get the
helmet we refuse the helmet
[Music]
wow I have my own titles I don't need
your shitty madeup
[Music]
titles yeah keep it I I got my beautiful
hat that sheit don't made for
me I'm not going to take it off I'm
going to sleep with
this oh thanks yeah I'll take those
smoke
bombs got pie I'm telling you this whole
world is about
pie the world is probably not even round
it's like literally
[Music]
pie it's
okay oh I took a bite
does it taste like the pie that my mom
[Music]
makes
Fu the P Earth Fury
[Music]
exactly got to go
p PE pie pie seems to be a very valuable
resource when you got to keep it a
secret that you're making
[Music]
pie yeah
please that boy kind of sounds like Al
just like a actually a younger version
and yes Al
that boy might even be voiced by a lady
who
[Music]
knows not that one the helmet one sounds
like
Al
this would you agree the way the boy
talks as well like the in in in flip
[Music]
I was that word okay I didn't have
confidence to say
[Music]
it okay
Watchtower finding the children of the
children I Sav from the wild dogs know
how to get into the village when I'm
ready to go in I should look for them
near the entrance of laak Village so up
[Music]
there
okay ah we're oh we circled
back is all a big
[Music]
circle oh there they are
I think we're good I want to meet this
pie maker and eat the pie for
dinner oh they all look the same they're
all colorcoded the
same wow kind of aesthetic well I like
how the house behind us is like triangle
shaped and the roof goes to the ground
interesting design choice
[Music]
oh yeah what the [\h__\h] is it so that
people won't realize oh my God there's a
witch in the
[Music]
village okay byebye happy birthday to
you
mommy ears they're coming out Under The
Helmet
it looks like a cake there's a cake that
um is like triangle shaped like
this
famously I
think you want the armor normally if you
play Mage class you're not allowed to
you're not able to wear this kind of
armor you couldn't cuz it's you have to
wear cloth
armor maybe that's just world of
[Music]
rock I look funny
um thees the staff still kind of stands
out maybe we should put the staff
away I guess I had a mom too did she
just ask that
wait they all have moms
I see she really thinks she's just
looking for pie but she really doesn't
know that she's actually looking for her
mom oh man
[Music]
hey what was living with the guilt of
abandoning me easier than abandoning me
in the first place what isn't that the
same thing I don't get it but whatever
she's saying is
sad leaving with the isn't the result
the same
[Music]
what oh I guess she's just wondering
abandoning
must have already made her feel
guilty but isn't it the same I kind of
get it I kind of don't get it she's
saying it's better to live with guilt
than having her around yeah that's what
I would think she would say but she
phrased it weirdly I
[Music]
think maybe it's the
translation
weirdness I finally made it into the
village I don't like dressing like a
warrior but it's the only way to find
the pie maker I need to ask the Villager
about The Village
Baker not at all I think if I can save
here it would be a good spot to save or
can
I teleport home and then save there and
come back here I don't know if there's a
teleportation Point
here I got to go
[Music]
home okay yeah cuz they haven't forced
us to go back home for a while now just
I I need a point to
[Music]
stop the guil she feels is worse than
the ACT is what she's
saying still like maybe it's how late it
is but I'm I don't know this feels weird
makes no
sense oh
oh can't use teleportation right now
well let me leave the village
[Music]
maybe
left yeah written kind of
[Music]
weirdly not the points that I thought
she would
[Music]
make okay
welcome
home second time I'm saving
today thank God for auto save
wow we've gotten so far I think I mean
we might need yeah three or four
streams be able to make it in fre but I
feel like we've accomplished a
lot such a cute game so aesthetic I love
it exactly my kind of game
H yeah this is my kind of
pie
[Music]
again I kind of need to go idle meeting
but let's see how many super chats there
are maybe I can do it
fast I'm just going to stay here or
maybe do you think I'll fit into the RPG
office
[Music]
I'm kind of too pink for it maybe the
girls office girls office I guess
so I guess it's a girl's
[Music]
office H what the [\h__\h]
happened what what why is it not doing
the thing
what are you seeing this cfp what's
what why is it moving so weirdly SM SP
keyboard oh what why w w w what what is
this I'm moving one thing but the other
thing moves too like something's
weird something's cursed don't don't
mind me being cut off that's not the
point right wait I think I get
[Music]
it let me just put this
out then yeah if I take it out of the
folder it should
work yeah okay there we
go where's my
chair here
wa is everything big or am I tiny no the
chair is definitely
big and I'm relatively
[Music]
small
here okay
SM waa Honey We Shrunk The waa no you're
stupid stupid sassy
Baka immersion save yeah I think we're
good I fit in here well everything's
pretty peachy in here I'm more pink than
peachy but it's the best I can do I
[Music]
think I feel so cute in this magical
girl yeah maybe I should do um wait we
even we even talked about you know me
wanting to do school uniform next maybe
and then you guys were like oh you can
combine it with magical girl
right magical girls Queen but they'll I
feel like they'll they'll probably be
like you're trying to make it too
versatile it has to be one for
[Music]
you I'll try
there's a what you already made the
stuff well I'll use it next time we
stream she she
she you are now no longera Sho you'rea
she
W thank you I'll use it next
time you're the
best oh what's this I went on Twitter
see a new
Kum uh
comic and let me show
[Music]
you g why J why you do this to
me let me change it to
jpack yeah so
work what is the most important thing to
be a YouTu for you says Ena
booty the face on
ena's changed
too G shook to the core but I feel like
she wouldn't
necessarily feel that shocked about that
statement
I don't see the lie it's all truth I
just speak the truth I preach the truth
always I do I do all I say is the truth
and people hate me for it I don't get
it fuing
haters where are my super chats
uh do you do finger guns iro not really
no
[Music]
I don't do
that okay uh there a couple of red ones
and pinkies in there
h i g Jacob 47
D no I don't want to go into that in
between Dimension right
now py d space wonderful thank you for
the red super chat did research yeah
yeah I saw I think you posted that in
the hashtag too right
the pet named schne might come from the
snail shaped braided hair German maidens
had around uh the 1800s and from Sima
was warm sweet soft and nice M cinnamon
buns the cinnamon buns are like shaped
like a snail were those around in the
1800s you probably didn't call cute
ladies shneer yet in the 1800s right
snails also symbol symbolize
domestic Dom domestic
Domesticity really so calling a girl
schne means you oh because home huh cuz
it carries a house means you see her as
wife material okay I don't think people
really thought so deeply about it when
using the word generally in the past uh
centuries but makes
sense makes
sense now I want to eat a cinnamon bun
[Music]
man [\h__\h] but like
Austrian bakery
style
yeah they're kind of different they're
like flatter wait let me let me look it
up so I can show
[Music]
you I feel like they're flatter than
yours guys although
[Music]
wait ah these don't really look that
much like the ones I see in my bakeries
yeah this one
this one's a
[Music]
bit oh my God they all look so good
though why am I doing this to myself I'm
hungry stop okay no no no no no I'm not
going to show you the cinnamon bun no
space wful thank you M for the lure on
the cute
way of calling someone snail in
German
[Music]
pink that is so
cute thank you
[Music]
ghost Bion oh my God thanks for the
rainbow did you guys see ghoston
finished her uh tattoo of
me and it's so beautiful I saw it it's
so colorful it's so vibrant really
really nice
outcome I hope it will make you happy
for a long long long long long time
forever forever ideally
forever I hope I can see it IRL sometime
or like at least for a zoom call or
so yeah that would be sick I need to see
that with my own
eyes yeah thank you so much for that
dedication you're the
cutest sweetest cinnamon
bite cavic dun
you think I'm an empath what makes you
think
[Music]
soose looking for the pie wait she's
also looking for the pie wait now I get
[Music]
it now I really get it mp53
g than thank you
[Music]
yeah it is really good I'm really having
a good time watching it
[Music]
rlim under the table you Kim
you
[Music]
oneita I was left by the
algorithm before I went to bed and came
to the show where osii waa osii waa
plays my favorite KR games let's go and
you are from Korea is this game maybe
more popular and well known in Korea
because that's uh where the developers
are from I wonder I wonder if it's well
known over there more well known at
[Music]
least probably it's so cute
man I'd hope it become more Main stream
within the jrpg community they got to
know about this game and anybody who
likes aier would like it too I think
it's not quite as crazy about uh like
you
know making stuff in your cauldron but
it's definitely a a thing that I do like
daily in the game so not as crazy about
not as detailed but still is a mobile
franchise
[Music]
yeah big recommend for sure mp15 free g
d it would be cool if you were try to I
am but it's hard to get others to pick
up RPG games
they uh there's some members who play
them still but yeah especially with like
well lesser known ones than it's
difficult I I tried to get people to
play tunic but in the end I'm not not
going to like try to force anybody I can
the only thing I can say is like a
general hey did you guys know tunic is
[\h__\h]
amazing it's really on
[Music]
them yeah yeah but like you
know try black
[Music]
that's a bit
extremee played off stream heyo I didn't
know she played off stream
what croni
Quon Quon she's such a good woman ah I
knew it I knew
it yeah Fuki S I played
tunic I bet pberry would have done
blackmail oh yeah she's the first one to
Blackmail people for pie especially D
thanks for the pinky T in January I
bought tailes with the sterio I tried
playing it but it's been off and on and
now I can't bring myself to play it
because it's so dull does that make me a
bad Tales fan will I get front into the
usual I don't know do you consider
yourself a tailes off then have you
played many other
games then I think you can answer your
own question probably just because like
if this is your first tales off game and
you don't like it then you've never been
a
fan but I do hear from many people that
t ofera is one of their least favorite
ones like one of the worst ones in the
recent
releases so it's not weird to dislike
it in any case uh I did not I did not
have an issue with it
ever but
yeah it did also not catch me as much as
other games but I feel like that might
be other factors
[Music]
yeah I said that well uh I don't know
like it's hard to say have you played
the other games I didn't see your answer
in the chat if you did
[Music]
answer yeah but me not finishing it I
think has more to do with when I was
playing
it um that was way before Hol and and I
just like end up not really having time
and being busy with other stuff you
played Seven Tales of games well
then yeah I mean I think you share the
opinion of many other tales off fans so
it's like
whatever but it hurts me a bit to hear
you say that so directly to me it's like
you want to pull a dagger into my heart
it's like you're doing it on purpose why
would you tell me this
why it hurts me it's understandable it's
a shared opinion by many but why do you
do this why why
why you said it so clearly so directly
[Music]
so you know my feelings towards tales
off
games very [\h__\h] biased I am indeed
so but it's okay don't worry about it
[Music]
wait I got through them so
fast there's another new
[Music]
one and fr thanks for the red super
chatala I just wanted to tell you really
quick thank you thank you for being here
bro bro and thank you for always giving
us a big smile on our face even if I'm
in the shadows I know know that I
appreciate you a lot I'm always here to
support our amazing Phoenix w I would
hope so I did feel like maybe I was
imagining it but I feel like you weren't
around that much but maybe yeah you are
you just
lurking don't
lurk it concerns me makes me worried
make sure to be in the chat every once
in a while thank
you I love having you around so don't
leave me hanging fro
fro
okay here's a magical girl kiss for
you I'm so cute right
now I'm so
pink I want you better thank you yeah
time for a meeting I'm done reading
super chats that was fast even though
there were a couple of Reds and pinks
thanks for the support guys thanks for
the super chats thank you for watching
thank you for hanging with me you guys
should give the game which try go buy it
now and like play it until the end until
my next
stream maybe or not until the end maybe
around the middle or so so that you can
help
me my backlog [\h__\h] your back log what
matters is what I'm playing right
[Music]
now got to keep up waiting for switch
switch release or your own switch
because I think it's already on switch
right I don't know I'm sure the deaths
love you do they know that I'm playing
this I need them to know of my existence
and my love of this game um which spring
are do they have a Twitter like
damn uh Ki walks is publisher and
developer
death K
walks uh that's probably not wait in my
H there's a Twitter account called kws
it however looks very private no but
this is the person they are linking the
website in
their uh bio and they have like artwork
retweeted and stuff damn wait there's an
uh which spring Korean official is there
an English one which
spring
R there it is they retweeted My Stream
okay okay okay okay they are maybe at
least the publisher at least the whoever
is doing the English Twitter at least
they are aware I just need them to know
here let
me I'm going to add them in an after
tweet all right thanks for the
membership the gifted ones and
delar Beast you mean
beeria to is my favorite oh my God it's
one of my favorites too I you you know
that right and that's why you're saying
it because you know you get extra points
with
[Music]
me you should you
probably pereria is really good people
love pereria I love pereria it's goed it
has magil Lo OMG magil she looks like me
right now because of the big hat magic
outfit I love velvet she's so cool
velvet is so cool re is so sick it's so
cool to fight with her because of those
hands TIY
D another attenti of fantasy alter with
v you mean witch a frog fed chicken
witch what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about why does it have to be frog fed
well okay actually that's kind of cute
so like
green but maybe I want to be
pink I don't
know I want to start playing it what's
your recommendation
you you mean which Tales of game to
start with
o maybe not Tales of AR
rise if uh to give you one of the recent
ones because that's easier to access
perhaps I would possibly say Tes of
berseria um from the most recent ones
there are
certainly better representatives of
tales off games although you know it's
kind of like it feels like the style is
Shifting um like the games are just
generally getting darker and more
realistic looking but for me still like
when I speak of tailes off you know it's
really like Symphonia visaria
Graces those kind of games and I didn't
play it but
Fantasia cilia already went really dark
and got more and more realistic oh abyss
of course TS of the
Abyss all of
them but yeah they're kind of changing
so if you can play one of the older ones
you know if you have a a maybe a an
older console like a Gamecube or
PlayStation three or two I don't know
and or PlayStation Portable or
Playstation
V although you probably can't buy it in
the online shop anymore you'd have to
buy probably like secondhand uh a
game syon on
switch syia is on switch did it go onto
the switch with oh syia is on
switch pH is on
switch is it I played it on GameCube so
I don't really remember oh [\h__\h] oh I
guess I probably knew that but I just
forgot it a
is it also on Steam damn well it's a
classic so that's that's why it made
that's why it made it that far very
popular with overseas
[Music]
crowd Tes p is on Steam yeah I I
recommend it if yeah yeah you should no
you play from the newer ones B of
berseria from the older ones any of them
really see whatever fits your uh console
of choice I feel like there's no no bad
[Music]
one yeah it's not a bad one
cilia I love cilia like not even cilia 2
that's one of my favorites but you would
obviously start from cilia and I think
cilia 1 is also a great starting
[Music]
point I think so I don't know they're
all great she's biased but she's right I
am I wish they afforded the CIA yeah for
real me too me
[Music]
too stuck on PS3
man I'm locked in and tailes off
[Music]
tangents they got to bring all of them
to steam at least so that they're more
accessible bring me those oldies like
Fantasia so I can play them
I or no better than that make a [\h__\h]
remake of Fantasia
please Fantasia and Destiny and uh re uh
rebirth was
it all of those need
remakes
please please like
HD graphics
remakes like Tes of Bia levels TS of
ceria Bia arise
levels Eternia yeah Eternia please I'm
so
[Music]
curious surprised they haven't remade
them for real they take so much time
with each game
[Music]
too but it's good they take more time
with it to ensure the
quality turnia yeah please turnia man
I'm so curious please that's one of the
one I really really really really really
really want to play I'll tell you what I
want what I really really want I know
what you want want I want I want to I
want to I want to I want to really
really really want a Tales of
remake Star Ocean I know I know I
know I know I
know I know I know
but Star Ocean I got sponsored by one of
their yeah the Second Story r r which
spring R Second Story R what's with this
letter r
huh
H what why R what does it even mean re
re re like
re what are they trying to say with r re
re like r
e re okay in this one maybe remake but
like would wi spring R is wi spring r a
remake of
something reloaded yeah maybe they're
like trying to say remake reboot re
reone r
ah was that a
remake the first witch string
oh also it is a remake oh
not
nice nice ni okay I'm going to go
now did any new super chats come in that
I have to
read let me check let me check just one
more
time oh yeah they they did oh I almost
left monkey
Z true
Cru space water for than you
and I'm going to go thank you so much
and J say off
in pie I'm going to go look for pie now
in my hell fresh box and I'll probably
not find any and I'm going to cry
goodbye goodbye
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
[Music]
Goodbye Oh thanks for the Super Chat
golden
I yeah tomorrow day off and then the day
after we have uh mono watch along so
make sure to prepare B dadd First full
season
[Music]
even if I end up switching it make sure
to prepare
it but yeah we'll
[Music]
see no switch okay no switch okay okay
I'll be fine yeah I'll keep it the way
it is now
[Music]
thank you you're welcome please switch
well can't make everybody
[Music]
happy a diet pie if you don't use any
sugar or only eat a small slice or two
yeah of course wouldn't eat a whole pie
in one day anyway
[Music]