[Music]
for
oh for
[Music]
hello yipp hello yipp
I'm so
excited yay
y hello
every welcome we are
[Applause]
PN yay we're traumatized
y let's dump our traumas on
[Music]
everybody but can I just say I'm so
excited this the first time I wanted to
play this game for a while but the first
time I'm playing it they have freaking
October Fest theme no it's October Fest
yeah it's October Fest it's going to
rock your
world they have
pretzels and sausages and little hosen
that we can get as items apparently o
what's L hos in it's a leather pants
thing
oh leather pants yeah like the brown
leather pants usually Brown bat you know
it's like the the uh uh opposite for the
D oh my God how are we dancing Miners
and you are dancers first one to twerk
is a winner you're forcing us to Dance
come on baby is this stream safe music I
don't know oh
I so I I don't get copyrighted
music how are you doing this there's a
streamer
mode my leg stop moving yeah op
press escap I guess you don't need it
cuz you're not streaming right I
know but it's cool
[Music]
yeah is there a how' you do that how'
you do that ballerina dance oh it
happens on its own I think I don't you
like enter and leave the where's the
torque there's no they took it out for
October Fest why would they do that what
oh got sck
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah from management Stop
Dancing
get
[Music]
what uh oh chat is is audio okay is it B
enough audio check che che oh we can
order
around oh we can order a
beer oh it looks so cute
what's that little hat called oh it
gives one for everyone hey drinks on me
guys oh thank you
special isn't that more like um be do we
do we compie together or something
yeah wait waing get your drink who is
this get your drink bro good what what
drink hey you fat butt move your fat
butt over there whoo whoa whoa whoo get
your drink calling me before I've even
had a drink what the leaf
lovers yeah it's
[Music]
vegan smothie how do we drink this
actually
[Music]
uh wait does everybody's colors
match this with red no excuse me what
the hell was that oh I don't know what
color I am is there ow you look Canadian
how did you throw that your camo you
look Irish oh my god well well thank you
you got a button you're well out you
look evil who's that oh that's Amy is
that hi
hi your chin is amazing wait did I is
the audio am I more audible
[Music]
now audible audible
AUD yeah that's
nice you know you're not being
by fine I'm
down up
up can I change my outfit
somewhere yeah like the color bit this
is some Club Peng
music steam now qu I mean I'm fine with
this so oh
go oh
God played the game before and me and
crony are beginners
so please you know help us out oh my God
that twerk is insane holy cow sh it's so
hard the Earth is shaking go drill on my
fever night
[Music]
work oh my God go driller go
driller you hear the clap of your never
mind oh oh my God Clap the butt
cheeks okay are we going to go to a
mission I can set up a mission yeah
there's a
wardrobe go inside here let's do this
way this way is it locked it shouldn't
be is it
god let's use l up here up here oh okay
so apparently there's October Fest
roctober Fest missions so we could do
those right um actually we have to do I
think all of us are still pretty early
in the game so we have to do no it's not
unlocked okay that's fine we should do
that we'll unlock
it which one is it hold on it's been a
while since I played on a fresh
Noob we're the noobs
grony gron got so lost in the tutorial I
had to lead her for she got lost a
million times in the tutorial can you
guys imagine hey hey that's not because
I'm not going a gaze that's because I'm
directionally
challenged I'm directionally challenged
too and I made it pro pretty easily that
means you're
better
wait is my audio actually that uh messed
up on my side sorry guys you can add a
filter to your microphone that had
game but I haven't touched anything your
audio is fine okay yeah your audio is
fine um through Discord at least so it
might be like
yeah it doesn't does it look in OBS does
it look like it's in the yellow or yeah
no it's it's maybe a touch quiet but
kums want to have your ears or your
voice like really deep inside their
brain 8 they also want your ears to no I
keep them shrimps even have ears I got
one guide I got one guide shrimps I
think they have holes in their head or
maybe they they have holes I
think
um I wonder if we unlock it for
and I it will unlock for you guys as
well I don't think we hopefully we'll
just do this one cuz I think oh man I
have to do this
one we'll do level one because we have
new
players yes please I've only done the
tutorial so far which was already so
much fun the assign I like this
game oh God wait uh October which
assignment do you guys have if you go to
the the assignment
board that objective conquer Hawkes is
that your
objective yeah seems like it is it
selective coner haes for it's
SED I guess selected and active and it
looks like that's the only one I can do
because the others are gr out so
okay okay so yeah we should be good then
I will be to in with that can clear
it we'll start with a level one low
risk low reward but that's fine mission
is ready the part is prepped get on
board to
drop geter you know get get in the get
in the get in the robots
robot really not much time I'm really
looking forward to be working with you
guys behind
figure it out gives me lethal company
Vibes but like way better lethal
company's good though I didn't
realiz really yeah they have a lot of
new
updates yeah g f
me there game no there's a
trap I read a chat message
sorry round is
on this is a salvage mission previous
crew lost their mes the drop part and
the
find get the Dr
operation heavy investation try to mess
it up like your former colleagues oh you
playing yeah kind of I guess let's go
wait did I
not wait why does it hurt so much do we
have to like shoot these mushrooms is
the smoke that it's giving off let me
fix don't go too deep into the
SM was going to
show audio volume turn it oh guys this
the game audio okay or do you want it
louder do you just jump
down I guess zip line yeah one of maybe
could create a zip line I I guess I I'm
touching the audio one more time and
then I'm not touching it for the rest of
the stream okay it's done
okay I haven't played this in a long
time I'm your scout I am
oh
help over here by
the how' you die the marlier thank you
brother you're a
true I want to make it too loud uh did
you jump down I'm going jump down does
it not hurt when you fall from the sky
like an angel you died you died she's
yeah but she resurrected me how do how
do you throw a zipline again what's the
button for it I haven't played this in a
while remember to
do wait where are we
drilling is it up there slow down
please is it three I made a dip line we
can use it yeah I think we got to go to
this middle level no oh why you going
that how do you ping
again ping control and then excuse me
yeah I
found do you want a zip line
am oh no you that's is that I'm here
okay good okay all right boys let's dig
dig yay Y is there uh uh can you damage
uh your partners their friendly fire no
okay too bad about to go through oh what
yum what are you putting down BL heck
going to be a sober occasion you stupid
wait is is it friendly is this friendly
there is there there oh my God in order
to hack this game you have to play
Flappy Bird I'm killing myself
what have to play Flappy Bird to hack
this SP what really open the box
grony Okay who wants it fun what is it I
don't know boots boots upgrade let's go
so now oh everyone can get it oh wait
hold on everyone can get it says W
jet we already have that before was that
the boots we love Jetty
Boots These are what are we doing we're
salvaging mes all have your boots
yeah crony the red stones if you get
them they give you health oh I have
found that
out if you see a fossil grab it looks
like a big animal crossing fossil are
they usually out in the open or is it
more
like uh why are you choosing to walk
through
it Oh I thought you had to I didn't know
like we had jet packs don't hurt
yourself thank you they're on the walls
okay so are they out in the open this
wall they're like blue
swirlies swi
okay oh my God must
die yay loot whoa what is this how do we
get down oh wa is that our
spaceship wait I'll make another zip
line zip line
Yi oh I found oh there's a big spider oh
my
God I want
to what is that feeling what is that
feeling
ah I
died you died by
accident I got
you a so sweet of
course man ow ow ow sorry did I hurt you
guys that other is there friendly fire
in this
game not didn't you say no before
yes wa is
let's does that hurt not really where's
the other
battery beep
big boy going down those
crustations terrain scanner just got
updated to new
location
cool where'd everyone go um I'm looking
for another battery that's going
beep beep I
saw oh shoes I forgot shoes beep I see a
fossil get it
ow what's this beeping box I got it it's
a it's a sorry I want to see an animal
crossing fossil
wait oh I see it oh animal crossing
fossil what was that I died
someone yeah
thank thank you I don't know where it is
oh my God I got for
nice I feel like I need to be um taught
what all these deadly things are because
it keeps on killing me I mean if it's
attacking you then shoot it all right
man is it
there who I'm kill
him why the screaming
thing it's gone I'm on a
jet oh you can shoot while I'm flying
sick where is this is it pink on the map
feel like I need a better my fov is like
super I'm dead
again I'm
so thank you this this supposed to be a
level easy overwhelming um there's a lot
of happening and it's uh it's very
cool healing where's our
healer we have no
healer there's
healers
no
fil there's so many actually oh look at
my Camp I
[Music]
I I overestimate how long the shoes keep
me flying hold on I'll come with you
soon one moment I got I got it I got it
she got
it I'm a phoenix I got to die
sometimes heck yeah
it's
it's Danger
for the driller there's a skin up here
we got aate here skin Oh I fought like
real skin I left my skin up here for
you e is it for everybody my SK
suit Theon uh okay so yeah we want to
collect those fossils and then we want
to salvage mules which look like our
mule here Molly but they're tiny and
green
oh okay is it like m other people
abandon it's these things here they're
blinking and glowing and you got to put
them when you say here what exact I
think on your map they show up as pink
yeah if you hit if you hold tab you get
a map and there's pink things all over
the map
oh fl's
up no ammo my God this is what a crummy
level
one what do we do with all these mule
legs
got to put them
together how I can't pick them up this
Nitra Nitra is what we Ed
to buy more ammo so if you see it mine
it the red the red step the red St buy
as in later when we're back or now
imediately I you you buy it now if we
need
it okay you guys have to dig up the
legs and then attach it to
the thing so stay with
someone who is that that red is crony
what are you
diing it's one of the little mules
okay and then you build a little mule
and do you mind
where's the other
one
cool I like shooting where's the other
mule I think there's a mini mule here oh
I see it is this
thing what is this I think she already
did this oh
okay okay
the the like when I even when I don't
look at the map I see something that
says mini me but somebody like Mark that
okay oh I think I think I should be
theix Miss there's no
way burn it with
fire they really SP on level
on yeah this feels quite the difficult
one compared to to the
tutorial heck yeah level
up I I I fixed the other one oh nice
go well done the MU is working
again need more more of
theil I got
fils just take your sweet time
or oh
thank you so many zip
lines yeah you have way too many not no
I think it's good you get to like like
travel but now I can't make no more oh
can I back him up and like take him back
we one more F who's got
it
f oh saw one before but I couldn't
reach activated call supply drops Nitra
is that Nitra uh if you need more ammo
we might have enough Nitra you can go uh
drop uh how would I I'm getting too old
for this I believe
it's is it
five five
oopsie is it five how do you call it
yeah it is five five will call now oh
that's where I place
it supp drop has been ordered is on the
way
okay
resupply is on the way is dead I am dead
I'll heal
you
yay yay here Phoenix better for you air
yippe I just call myself a fat boy
why feel
attack I don't see any fossils anywhere
okay you guys can get supplies too like
all
okay to kill some more for the
last find who will find now I'm
motivated
find whoever finds it gets
[Music]
surprise from the game from the game
you're just giving someone else
the the honor yeah
no Mission
Control you guys get me
hereid when there's something you want
to get and there's no way to like stand
next to it to mine it is there any way
to create platforms with a different
class or so
um might be able to maybe depending on
what build you
have well now I can't find anymore what
I saw
before Engineers can yeah what Engineers
can what oh I have to deposit the fossil
that I found oh then we might have them
already oh sick what I thought it went
up like automatically
wa where did the drop go is that the
drop forgot what it looks like how do
you Uplink I forget secondary objective
completed now finish the okay we're
done y
y have to H link to Mission Control what
does that mean this a green box I don't
remember how to do it it's been
resupply you have to push the button
the drop bar
Callin oh oh that's what that was oh
yeah yeah
yeah the mules are heading back follow
them and let's get that drop part fixed
remember you can always deposit on the
side of the drop pod follow the mules
yeah let's go mules that's so nice of
them to guide
us secured now to get the part working
first establishing a proper connection
between the and the space set up yeah I
just need a quick refresher so I can
help
everybody this is too much for
me what's happening right now I was just
waiting for the spaceship triangulation
initiated do not leave the triangulation
Z if you stay in the circle con we only
got one it go faster there's a circle
over here up
here and we just got to kind of like
defend
a I didn't see
that HT you
yes triangulation at 50% how do I
install
okaying we're up he need a
blank
easy up bring us some bigger
mobs oh amm's like that
way it's over here oh God I miss is
inbound you missed you
here ow who shot
me something shot me too this thing in
our base are you
dead Don't Shoot Me Okay revive the
shark oh wait did I get hit by the
resupply
I make stin CL I'm
sorry it's a buff I swear
well when you die I'm sure a lot of
things come out of your body
right stand by fuel cells for the
drop oh there's an ammo pod here too
oh refuel the drop on Watch Me Fly oh
yeah we we're done with oh wait sorry ow
fuel the drop is this not when we did
this part incoming fuel
we fuels have arrived get them connected
to the drop we smack it connect it
refuel drop pod we got to connect
it
thingy ah there should be a green hole
on the drop right
here yeah this way
no I
double put it in the drop pod's belly
button drop the umbilical cord yeah I'm
stuck put it in where's the belly button
there oh that's the belly
button that's one way
toop how to refuel
how how do you get fuel oh you put the
cable in there oh how you fuel cells
connected now you just need to prep the
fuel cells and the charge sequence will
begin okay this is something I can
do
yay cells charging stay close to keep
them operational we're expecting an
increase in
hostil St CL I like how Mission Control
always tells us what to do but nobody
ever listens to Mission Control
I'm trying to but I don't even
understand what he's
saying that's a lot of enemies
oo enemy
spam
owie oh stinky at
50% protect attack plus you can you can
Trash Talk machine control cuz you talk
he'll never come down and
actually so feel free you sound
experienc who keeps shooting
these people I'm sorry I didn't know
what it was mission control can talk
back he just doesn't actually uh commit
to the discipline
oh more coming from West
ow Boom
Boom at
7% what
was sorry it was
me
Oh I thought that was mine no that was
my am my uh detonated what C4 oh I guess
we did it at the same
time set a trap for them
C4 we're almost
done ply charge engine powering up hold
your ground we're almost ready to pull
you and the goods out
hold your ground okay wow they're
stalling so much
man thanks for nothing
MC do we have to stay around the
theen so go wherever I stay alive for a
minute hey heyet
caring
jumping
jum all those proteins cat me if
you so easy to miss them
they ow
operation what I'm out of ammo
[Music]
again yes
yes 12 seconds 10 seconds stay
alive Sor oh
good you look so chunky you want to
shoot
you pretty chy it's time to bring it all
home aren't we
without drop we just get in
here
wait this is a drop guys you can come
around to the front oh okay we can get
out of here mission complete oh
easy
y our first Miss
complet Yahoo
rocket stone for the first round that
was so easy rocket Stone forever Ro
forevel one was kind of overwhelming so
that's where it came from Rocky St rock
stone is there like an option for the
fov I feel like it's so zoomed in I
think I think there might
be your I mean if it's first person they
should what does I had the most kills
[Music]
biggest gun
too wait maybe not that might have been
too many stats you had the flamethrower
so you had the hottest gun for sure yeah
so is is pyro The Meta in this game at
least oh my
God meta in this
game I'm traumatized using Pyro from TF2
I have drill fist okay I'm not just a
pyro okay me you're just a pyro
pyro this
slander no it's cool to be pyro at least
I thought so until I sler is the
truth no yes
right okay is everybody safely back
[Music]
yeah uh is your assignment board moving
here moving asign board the thing to
looks like it's still the same I think
yeah okay
well what does this mean did we not do
it it says prerequisites are conquer
Hawk's four and then spec
ops have to or industrial
sabotage they have to do the mining
Mission yeah it's just cuz like our our
early in the game this is staggered so
Amelia and I are also like not fully out
of the game a a beginning
game
ah
oh I was wondering if if I push and us
through the rest of the Hawes thing
maybe then we can do the grade out
missions for you
guys anything's fine for me I just have
a hard time understanding what's going
on uh they're saying you and crony could
catch up to ammit if we're on the same
Quest still I think we are we have to be
we only did the
tutorial yeah we have the same
assignment do our missions first it
won't give you aeit oh God okay all
right okay we'll start with this one
tell goba to Choose Your Mission doing
it goba choose my mission do it
all
right it'll be so refreshing cuz it's
going to be easier than the other thing
right it I would hope so I would hope it
should
be okay 200 more K 12 gun SE let's get
this Mission rolling
dropa seat belts I hate pressure
customize in this game that's awesome
let's drop how come I can't sit
but yeah your butt is too big yeah your
your face is too big your Beard's too
long mhm smells your too long o PE
there's no thing such as but I wasn't
the one who was
stinking does my odor offend
you yeah it's offensive to the world you
should apologize going to die to
everyone
exotic
roses anyway
anyway only your species would
know we'll send a drop to get you out
all right Light It Up
lighting oh this is
pretty was the was that the the black
St it's like shiny green green it was
Green
okay is oh wait I got this we this I
made
a right figured out the cheese platform
see GK Gunk seed to yeah they're hanging
in the ceiling I made a I made a
platform I'm zip line to the other
direction if you okay that would be a
lot better
oh oh I see a lot of Gunk on the walls
is that dirt yeah that's dirt I will get
the gunk seeds at the top of the map oh
that's Gunk seeds they're gray and they
hangy down and they gble gble oh they
are how you going to get those my oh you
shoot
them oh you just C that's so simple I
didn't think of that
wait a
minute I
guess that's it
back where is that damn you laughing at
taking all your stuff taking all my
kills took all your mining stuff Min can
you can someone take this gun seed yeah
toss it down
here down here everyone can I get some
attention give me your is this the right
direction give I'll drop it
right here I I
can't I'm down here oh throw it how do I
throw it going have I opened up A New
Path
click click few girls can't find any
more moride there tried A New Path by
nice I'm sorry I the wrong button wrong
button I'm sorry that was an in the
work I'm sorry stop hating each other I
I wasn't hating I was play Hot Potato
with a grenade no I'm
sorry and it went
boom up I'm in I'm I'm I'm like like uh
in different part of the map now but I
it looks like we eventually have to go
here I have a feeling oh did you dig
through the oh you did yeah I dig
through the dirt where you were digging
like something else I don't know what
you were digging let's go that way then
lighting up let's follow guys yeah come
over it feels right there's a t I need
the right here right now does everyone
get a zip
line no right here turn around
you just got to ride kiar zipin yeah oh
there it is okay zins are so
fun ow hey hey oh hello what the hell my
shield I'm going to kill
you help we're missing
crony's going to gun me down I got to
keep moving I got no I'm not going to
gun you down I just want to like
touch you we are
unbreakable theme climbing half Rock
Stone when I think of unbreakable I have
to think of unbreakable Kimmy
Schmid Aid
it's I say spin-off series not really
it's not is it anime
the anime no girl kimid would have been
good as an anime maybe let there be Loy
donkey come here what is Kimmy
Schmid oh it's Kimmy
Schmid I thought you were saying aimi
Schmid and I was like
aim
aimi Kimmy my bad I don't know I thought
it was
anime but if it's Kimmy
that's so that's so
American sitcom name yeah yeah is pretty
much
sitcom I love my American timy Schmid
lives in Suburban Rock seriously need to
invest in some better equipment just
like
Rihanna if we discover a new mineral you
think we get e something sounds
gor what is
itby gor
you you is our is our little do still
following us you can hit C and it'll put
down a a marker
lighting
marker oh there's more kite
yeah well I want to give my gun seed to
some to the Pod
right I think you can call it over oh
I'm calling it
her name is
Molly Molly it's called mule a it's a
cute name it's a
mu Molly the
mule going to it don't give it a name
it's not we don't have the boots anymore
one of
us it's not like us yeah it
is no it
isn't
uh ah
a
eat what is
need
can't what direction do I love this
grappling hook directional
sense back up back up oh it's an
explosive did you get
hurt oh I heard a little bit of a teeny
we can go this way there's more dirt
this way head is blocked compacted dirt
oh there's a beer mug what do I do with
this beer mug right I was thinking too
like what is that doing
there we must have not been the first
dwarves to come here stand back step
aside why that I'm I'm over overheated
one second
[Music]
o get the beer how do we pick it up I
guess we have to dig it up I'm going
back for the you know that some people
can make bread out
of had
a of what
Let There
Be bees I thought you said speaking of
bees bees can make
bread I bet bread out of
honey you found one of the last best be
you
um performance out of yeast infection
oh performance heard about
that oh yeah that's I'm coming I heard
it tastes a bit like sourdough I think
my brain is refusing to process what you
just said so sorry what what that
talking about it's naturally have yeast
inside them did you know that oh really
yeah you could probably make your ass
over of a melon oh how you that's cool
feel about the fact that if you wanted
to take over the the world you could
essentially just have like a a brain
control yeast because because every
human probably has some type of like
fungal fungus inside of them and once
you get a fungal fungus inside of you
you pretty much can't get rid of it so
you can really just like yeah somebody
sounds like a little fun guy little fun
guy it's like the last of us but in
reality it's kind the oh yeah yeah
lighting
up youing
a we're on the same team so how am I
going to reach this I need an engineer
to make a little
Dam like you know where I am but
not ace break sit
down maybe play some dice um like this
one like here oh yeah yeah uh not there
but around the corner but maybe it's not
worth it maybe I better go to a
different area although they're all all
these moride thingies are up pretty
high I can try and help oh Mar the C RL
okay I'll go I will once I'm off this
zip line oh damn good sorry did I just
take over your no no no how she just
jumps up there and holds
on skills guaca
guac
[Music]
gu Cal
down it's hard to get up
there where did the mule go it's um it's
where is get ready what is a gooy
bar name yourself a nice
bonus her that's your name now okay she
officially legally changed her name to
Gooby gooby what kind of name is Gooby B
no
offense here I named or that oh I'm
sorry it's like a better better name why
is there bad music playing
everybody did somebody like already
played by chance like one of those
reloading thingies no yet no no how do
we do it again
uh how do we put the resupply
five I I put it
down play
chicken guys what's the button
to uh right click you have to hold it
right uh hold the right I've just been
using my fist oh what
cuz I no cuz I have drill fists oh
okay is that the
equivalent
help watch out behind you
you light to M
whoops oh we have enough gun and enough
more
did now it's enemy rush time again we
can either do this or we can just go
home ready to kill some more crates I
wouldn't mind going home then we go home
midrange let's go
theop okay we follow abort Mission I'm
taking some of the ammo abort
Mission well bort abort yeah
boarding sucessfully
we missed the P dropt has arrived
retrieving the mule getting more ammo so
we follow M follow
theing it I was but but once you're too
tall you to get through to some fruit
something too tall to
ride it's not over yet be careful my
companions have you guys seen the skib
version of
theity version of what
suicide
SK does anybody seen it here no no I
haven't seen it somebody we don't
consume such empty minded things I doubt
it I doubt that
oh I mean we we all consume like
something brainless one way or another
dep in
t i I will say the only thing in that
format I watch is YouTube shorts that's
perhaps on whatever's on
Twitter
wow
and dude that's true crie documentary
YouTube shorts
basically brings me the best from
what you get over
there where's my Instagram real Chads at
yeah no Instagram
real yeah I don't even look at Instagram
reals I mean my friend sends me that but
that's about it yeah when they send them
my only friend on
Instagram who team I feel like I have
been abandoned
Watson W no I haven't been using it in a
while read
yourself me I
use uh YouTube shorts I guess sometimes
Instagram and
then Twitter I guess mostly Twitter why
you the same as me you said you say all
the things except Tik
Tok yeah I don't use Tik Tok it's the
same pretty much okay
I feel like I'm all alone uh out in the
dark just follow the signs yeah I went
the wrong way first so you're definitely
not being timed don't worry don't look
at the big timer on my okay we got
enough
time initiating launch sequence de thank
you for your good work drop
Will Wait almost there yes I'm
here what right here I'll make
it I'm I'm almost there I see a zip
line trying to light the way for
you yeah did you guys put that there or
does the mule put that there those signs
automatic ow so nice
sorry I keep on forgetting that it name
is Molly yeah it's not Molly it's just a
mule oh my God no the name is
Molly don't give it a name you'll get
attached to it respect things' names say
people's names but that's not a
people I have
arrived oh were you waiting outside for
me oh you can slap
people the
dice slap my lucky
dice so was that the first mission that
me and crony had to do I think so
oh I do believe hooray hooray
success wow look at us we're so cool and
everybody I wish I can trim that beard
to make it look nicer I know you can
customize it later what is that the the
quad
chin
yeah you mean the but looks like
something hanging hey I got that beer
mug
oh you did the multip
yay o yummy Milestone oh now we moved on
go we the mission thing something moved
unlock
nice
nice okay we do the next one I'm going
to stand in front of the elevator but
I'll be right back like one minute okay
okay launch control reports foreign
objects in the launch tube it appears
that something is intering with for
objects in know anything about it I
don't know who would do that is ready
pretzels
no sausage flavored would do that I saw
you do it I didn't do that you're just
trying to clean
right yeah I'll have the special and
don't on the
sausage
Obsession so this is the official trash
can now I see likeit come come oh wait
we'll wait for WatchON
hey we put a weenie in it
I think I'm going to eat sausages
today
oh best war Beer oober
Fest oh actually I've never been to an O
October Fest for real for real
but my October Fest happens at
home
oh I just you know eat sausages
alone I don't drink what what do you
cele like what is the what is the
celebration
for um well because it's
October and um I don't know I guess it's
maybe like an Autumn Festival kind of
okay the Harvest like a Harvest Festival
yeah may you grow sausages Thanksgiving
what we how do you growes oh I thought
you like harvested them
no wait no you would Harvest The Barley
that would make the beer right yeah and
I guess the bread also the
bradel the bread it all makes
sense oh Watson I put a weenie in your
beer come drink
it oh we're drinking again just for me
yeah I put my weenie in your beer cute
should turn on
music bump it
yay with the beer it's working
con y with your beer wait since when can
you drink it with the beer that's drink
it with I don't know wait since when oh
I
can I
[Music]
can oh
c oh
cute C
like it sorry I got too
excited
yeah that's how diggers celebrate let's
go I want to dig some more dig up some
Stones you like stones oh you're
flossing no
way my dance move is so boys better be
better min
wow my God what are you looking at never
even see we've never seen MC's legs and
he's that mean that's really
youing why what I'm just looking at your
face it's
watch fascinating oh look we s we chose
a
mission we're looking for my be I'm
bringing my
be we beer souvenir time who who
launched the mission what are we doing
eggs
eggs Yi collecting the eggs it's like
it's
Easter that's Easter
eggs
yeah we're all going to die oer
IR you say check your gear and let go is
this just a standard Mission or a rock
over Fest Mission these are these are
tutorial missions too
simple two of them three of them
a I got it you
sucker maybe get up I got it I got it oh
yeah platform nit
chees you say
cheese cheese
C
[Music]
oh you know there sausages of cheese
they're called
[Music]
quak Quaker for
Carl oh that's like here they have hot
dogs that have chili cheese in the
middle yummy ooh chili cheese I've never
had chili
before oh it's good yeah chili in a sour
do bowl with the chicken
trip the cheese sprinkled up
to oh is I know chil dog Sonic oh did I
go the wrong way yeah it seems very much
like it when I look at the map
oh my God where'd everyone
go H we're coming back
down yeah it was the way but sometimes
the way they dig straight down I thought
if there was like this rock stuff around
it that that's the way we're supposed to
go it is it is it is oh but if you hold
tab you'll see like where the the next
room is it's kind of confusing oops dig
straight down it's like a Metroid Prime
okay
down where are we going
now where's
everybody go up light is up
down yeah go open the map you can see
going
now how' you get
there yeah
yeah not these things
F and I'm not so proud about
it come here rock
on you knock my rocks
off I love these
guys they're so happy with their job and
their
[Music]
lify I want to be like
them do you want to I mean you're going
to risk your life every single time you
have to go
mining but somehow it seems
fun slow like this
really my world it really rocks my rocks
I'm getting so rocked you
know rock and
roll surely they also have a phrase
where they say that right po sure
we're looking for alien eggs
and so the alien eggs on your map if you
hold tab they're orange and yeah they
got like purpley flesh all around
them
up headed your way I didn't do that I
feel like you did that I me I stole
something oh no I don't mean the music I
mean the explosion there I mean yeah
that one I did but like you know
it's
shaking swarm I repeat swarm I don't
care I'm got I got to get the fossil oh
dear oh oh oh
oh oh no
no okay fine fine
[Music]
fine oh oh oh
ground
let going to
be lot let's thr a b let's
go my
God I know how to
helpen at least I haven't died in a
while oo alien eggs
yay where where where sounds like
at the top at the top
ofation there we go the stream of
incoming enemies is practically
eradicated good job
[Music]
I hope that
wasn't
take
[Music]
are there's
one
out they said practically eradicated
they
lied yeah
MC control yeah goba say
something what let this just
stand he lying to us
complain I'm telling
you I don't quite trust him anymore I'm
going to call him a wet blanket I don't
really know what that means a what does
it mean you somebody poop yeah okay so
he has a wet
blanket interesting adding to my
vocabulary
ah one
here is the fossil SP that I wanted to
get you're
dead why are they allo hard to access oh
my God it's shaking
again did you take something again an
alien EG I don't know what that is some
purple a COR Stone what's a COR Stone
[Music]
I'm oh my are there any
help dude why are they so fast what is
this what
the it's a horror game
now oh we're shooting the shoot the cor
St
I'm looking for help my those
St what's the core stone is that the
core
Stone building back up
though we already got one thir I called
in
aunch Stand
Back watch out oh my God is that where
the father is going
to M the stone a this Stone
wait wait does it like kind of re
covered itself into
a all right all right let's back out
shoot it shoot
[Music]
it oh I don't even know where I
am music is cool
yeah of
thing here Supply here your team before
the
resupply can I take it
over kill us unless stop
the I'm taking some of the ammo okay
mining time time this is too difficult
don't like how fast these things
are I I am have one HP in the dream I
said back
[Music]
up ready to kill
some oh my that must was that may the
new season nice you got it to
return wa we're missing one fossil
oh oh yeah after this longest shower
ever iffk in every single do I carry
this into the spaceship
get deposited yet um um
no also yeah I guess we do we have to
carry this for the container car it car
a special
container uh uh a special drop podt for
it okay where is
that I can't can't see
up here or up here this one is this not
it
oh oh yeah come
from get so much bonuses right done team
this thing will be instrumental in our
deep research I hurt nice
job getting yeah all right we're going
back got some resupply
J done I'll I'll follow you okay so I
don't get lost
it's
it's wait where did you guys go it's um
where did everyone go we're down here
we're waiting oh okay
I'm Dr has arrived the has been called
back drop departing in tus 5 minutes
no going
get again
ow that way
up get up no you can't get up I got you
ow you're this
way wait I found
it oh hello big boy
[Music]
the hased
ini this
way oh yeah this
way ignore my zip
lines OWI can't see
you were just right in front of me how
did I miss you
again up
there it's okay you got
time okay okay okay oh my
God my my
my one last party nice send off
wow that's so
toxic what
is roet commen good work
Rock we did it once
again
complete haven't picked up a single
fossil ah it's okay they always put them
in like the high
Corners yeah
yay I didn't find a a beer mug this time
we got the cor Stone true oh yeah I
guess that was
optional
noise noise is the cor Stone on every
map I think it spawns randomly points
claim
[Music]
or maybe that was the egg because it had
this little bit of a egg
shape no I just know okay no we got all
the other
eggs okay onsite
refining is next maybe
sweet or is that on the mission I'm not
sure is before we go anywhere we got to
drink another
beer and dance another round
yay kick
around I'm going to order oily o
Brew well that sounds dirty yeah we had
didn't have that one yet I think oh it
looks so basic oh it's so classic it's
like Tavern drink you going to add
something to that something nice no n no
that's it all right someone turn on the
music I hope I T time you know you're
not being thats get to
work let me get a better bang your heads
at this oh
man that's not easy to dance
TOA did you turn off the did you turn on
the stream mode nah oh oh my God N I
think I probably did the other time I
played it so unless the settings
reverted
then why what are you hearing right now
um something pretty slow
[Music]
Hawaiian yeah yeah
yeah chill Lu yeah on country music kind
of yeah yeah they're literally playing
gam Style lyrics and
everything all right Ka
[Music]
huz we should like your scout yeah
Cheers mik thany Cheers M do the worm
you should burn but miners than you are
dancers
oh all right let's go this is how we do
let's roll out what's next what's
next something like
a no I ain't got all
day let's get out of here I got to
refreshing
drop sequence
initiating bless bless
you that was a good
sneeze you are we complete see I'm
complete properly
okay but you need to be
complete I don't know oh man if I knew
that I wouldn't be here ain't going to
your maybe you need a air
fried you're right on air fix everything
let's go my just my liquid team set up
Liquid
[Music]
good get the me never turn my back on
you again fing up
okay so that's the
big oh a golden Loop
bug
wow I die a little inside every time I
have to this volcano thing doing so
that's that's we got a suck the more cut
out of
that M out of the volcano thing yeah so
we're going to start here mob refin at
the big thing the big on-site Refinery
and we're going to uh there's three
tubes that are going to shoot out of it
and we got to drag those tubes to the
volcano oh she's so
knowledgeable it's coming back to me now
yes
I'm I just
wanted put my stuff into the mule oh I
see a fossil what is this
eliminated finally a fossil I really
can't use this for anything what is that
it's like a big where did the go
ow there's no me is a
what wait I'm where do I put my stuff
then I guess I canless but F to destroy
put it anywhere oh that's
it it's ass salt crystal yummy oh and
then this turns into skate skateboard
the game these lights
Su up sorry guys my Jack requested and
is
inbound no that's what is that going to
make a pipe there the yeah I guess so
yeah we got to plug the pipe in which
one I'll drag one over to you guys oh
Jesus
in okay okay I guess uh she knows what
she's doing I do yeah yeah I guess I
mean Ball but you too I
guess wait w how in the world wait a
second is it too
far no I just got to figure out how I'm
going to we might need to watch until
like or we can use a platform tool oh we
could yeah let me see ow ow wait wait
wait oh my God valid I'll fill the rest
of your
hole what wait what you feel you feel
the rest of I'll use the rest I'll go
the rest wait I'll Traverse the rest of
the way with your hole that you have
dug dad did that work makes sense yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah you have such a way
with words thank you sorry I'm
distracted sorry oh whoopsie Finders
Keepers I was here
first so if we don't have a m where do I
put my
fossil Refinery is
here terrain just got updated with a new
location so our ship and segment
done this is where we refine liquid
[Music]
oh I fell
down oh hey I found one though yo I got
it I got
a y stay clear from the Impact Zone
trying to steal my my fossil
huh it's okay I I got a pipeline thanks
to you though thanks man
teamwork all right is done successfully
established
okay oh so we we have one and we need we
need
three here yeah and we got three
specific
locations there over there if you open
tab it's pink on your map we got one how
do you ping stuff control oh control and
left click
it no do you want it here light is up I
say you get it oh you get
it um ha you're so
short what where are we
going trying to figure out how we're
going to
get we need I think we need crony or
Watson to help I have a pipeline and not
a pipeline I have a I have a thing the Z
if you yeah
the where do you want to go what
direction oh no no no I meant like we
got to get this pipe down there oh this
one I mean if we could if we could put
the pipe on your on your down there yeah
know I don't know want to get it down
there I would help you if I knew where
you guys were oh my
God wait how are they over there are you
guys jump
walk walked I'm maybe build push me down
sry um no no no no like we found the
pipeline because of that
so oh you can over here this goes here
yeah I know my drill hands I'm Lo
Gremlin I think I'm going up to the
platform I just I don't
know oh not sure wait how did you guys I
think this is the way they
went I'm trying we're trying to get
back I'm not looking in the map so oh oh
you're going the opposite way you're
going the opposite
way Dam it
way
um wait I think I dug a really long
hole yeah you really dug a hole for
yourself
there I'm pretty much going the right
way almost I just need to turn
we got to get back up there I
think it sticks on them nice okay go
down
there pipelines in place
not got to go up there that
way
we where go over there um here yeah we
got to go that way okay I can just have
a traversal tool
they go this
way then maybe oh wait let do
high
hello hey ow
bro time ladies oh
God something
okay anyway where were
[Music]
we there's like a way that I could get
around I have no idea how they got over
there
um it's fine don't worry about it we Mor
we are no Nitra what is it called Nitra
they went the Army
way maybe I shouldn't be here it's okay
we just got to re attention got a swarm
on the way repeat oh no where are you
guys going okay wait
swarm
[Music]
swarm I'm going to go back up then with
my zipline you can come help me dig this
hole cuz I would have try and connect to
them are are you still trying to go to
the same thing then I look around to
find
you I I don't see you I'm supposed to
see you on the map right oh I think I I
know where maybe but there's a lot of
enemies
here uh y have AET they just do they
just spawn wherever we
are are you guys also getting attacked
yeah
ow ow
no watch this okay I see life I found go
okay okay okay I shall be your shield on
your back okay Let Me Wait Don't Shoot
Me don't
shoot see I put my hole the tunnel is of
utmost importance
ow
ow ow ow ow trying to prot don't shoot
in the hole I'm in here but it was on
your
back oh my god there coming are you
still buing the think I think first we
have to kill the monsters I'm good okay
okay there's a big one
coming get him before he gets he's too
big he can't F through okay whole good
oh oh okay hello
boys yeah I think it's calm
[Music]
again okay so I think we got to go this
way oh I see you guys hi hello
Hello's down there down there okay
that's where the the thing is oh yeah
like here drag that pipe over
here oh wait please out of ammo I found
a liquid I am out of Lights that's not
good it'll be a beauty once it's
complete take off
okay oh like
here we have to get that here P Jack so
yeah watch
it here just drop down
[Music]
here can it go down so
steeply oh yeah oh yeah can you can you
guys just drop down here or no we can we
got to bring the pipe with us
oh much
better
byebye yeah it is I'm somewhere close by
she could build us like a tunnel that
goes down I'm out of fuel oh no
oh uh wait how do we place the fuel the
thing again
G we have
friend friend well we could try to make
a tunnel with the bombs I don't know
five five how about how about
here mhm mhm
[Music]
mhm and then
here can it it can but it's a pretty
tight
Corner uh how about
here no hold
on hold on I think we got to I only have
two more left oh
God how
about this should work I want to go
back if you guys want to look for the
red stuff yeah I have a bunch of it but
I need to deposit it in the main ship
which is super far now cuz I'm down
here hold on I think I can still make a
diip line
but in the hole PL could use a hand
building
it was TI we going to do this so help me
wait hold on yeah I'll go get I'll bring
the Nitro no we don't have Molly right
now okay we all the way back to the big
thing
mhm valid valid oh we're doing this um
oh oh oh wait wait
wait
connected y now I can skate all the way
back byebye it's kind of in the way wait
wait wait sharp it says it's okay it's
okay yeah
yeah yeah
oh it's working yeah yeah yeah boom boom
it turns around for us okay okay now we
can grind it now we have to build
it watch me go oh wow yeah is pretty
far I hope there wasn't like a really
blatant shortcut that I
it's
okay may I can do a it is fun though the
way do you know those like not quite
roller coasters
um what do you call those like
Countryside
random roller coasters that are not
roller
coasters like a dark R like the ones in
the mountain yeah Alpine coasters Al
M those are fun those remind me of my
childhood
try yeah well usually they get kind of
hot and then cuz they're usually out of
this like steel or whatever and then too
hot on your butt there's some that you
ride on your butt I think and some you
ride on to
loaded where is the I can't I have two
wait this literally here I'm stupid I'm
stupid no I was looking for it guys I
was looking for it that's why I was
jumping
around we have a Nitro now yay yay one
fossil I'll make one
fosil that supplies are coming got to
get this thing down supplies are
coming it's too calm feel too calm pipes
up only someone would help me
build wait that's not going to
work restocking is now
possible please contact your closest
supplier of St worthless
destroy are we in need of one more pipe
oh where are you going with this
oneing you want to go down or below or
above oh I'm surprised that works yeah
this one we won't be able to ride like
the other way wa did they extend that
that's so far pip up that's going to be
fun to go
[Music]
down that's amazing I like this Mission
it's way more complicated and longer
than the other ones but how do we make
the get
I'm taking some of the ammo
maybe finally
light let there be light a r let
let rock stone
rock rocking
Stone why am I dealing with building the
pipelines huh eh what probably one it's
a hard job but someone's got to do it
also it's
probably that's the
up another pump jack connected to the
refiner
you it request accepted stand clear
pumpjack
inbound
pumpjack oh we're getting there
oh oh yeah did you get squished swarm in
no I'm good swarm access
provided
music good Tik Tok music no like it's
it's going Tik
Tok it's a big one
team I can't Tik Tok dance to this what
oh it has been
[Music]
connected fight fight
fight
Rock rocking Stone like they said that
we were about to
finish throwing down
traffic where the drop wait uh ah it's
at the base you can you can now grind
your way up there and then you can drop
it at the
base I mean resupply at the
base this is fun shooting while on
the it's Tony HW skate
three
yeah I used to play that on the
GameCube ohy
yeah had a lot of good games
mhm was a great
Cube The Game
Cube all
good
okay you guys can't see where are
you fire
Li oh is the resupply already empty this
is hard
[Music]
work another
one and another one another one but we
made already free tunnels what's
happening now a free free supplies you
have
to build the pipes is that what you
you're talking about aren't
built one build the pipe step two build
the
pipe yeah
see
[Music]
step we're also leing for last fos I
haven't seen
one wait how do you you just how do you
build it on the like most it has to be
this here you you can do that one oh
there you go you can do the
okay congratulations you've been
promoted AR is also not built yet all of
them uh that's the last one I think oh
okay and where do I don't I don't know
where you guys are I'm here
green are all in place and the liquid
morite is waiting return to well there's
a pip you
can now oh we I am at I'm going to do
this
now so now we're sucking the morai
through the big
Tob but they're going to break
down so we're going to have to fix them
the top right see which one is your to
protect and
maintain we still
missing the noise from the refiner is
attracting the bus get ready for
something budged in the right place
so we get poopy
pipes
toow oh man no stopped
[Music]
all okay I will go to one of them I
don't know which one we have to go like
to the bottom of them right moreing you
see go to where the I yeah I see they're
destroying specific part save
him it seems like when we created these
pipelin do it with much
care like that's not true this is now
Plumbing the
game fl's up how's the reparation going
I fixed five free
what are you are manager you're just
overseeing this your finger
you have malfunctions in the
system space pling my favorite is there
a
number oh they're actually numbered
am get out there fix number two I still
haven't seen that
um I'm on my way
news
get not what I
meant of my thing fixing number
two and finish finish fin
we is running again keep up the good
work we'll be done in no
time misspoke pump sequence at 25%
liquid Mor is Flowing to the
refiner we got company incoming swarm
approaching you no please no
please
again oh what are you holding no or
sorry sorry the pipelines are leaking
get on it get them fixed
the don't gr
no oh they're all
broken yeah again they're all broken I
got you I'm I'm by Ty one somewhere on
the bottom yeah I see you I got you
you're the best Charming Lady Of course
bro did you
fall yeah I fell when I was like riding
down and I wanted to stop for the
repairs but I fell too
hard it still be like that some
sometimes all right
I is this fixed oh okay this pipeline is
fixed but you need to clear all this
reminds me
of f in I
love the other one what's the other one
called
again
uh way out I no then I do mean it takes
to that's a long
game yeah what is it uh is it it takes
two is the one with um the where you
where you turn into a puppet right yeah
little boys to save the mar or something
didn't we all play that cuz I did finish
it it that play it I yeah I finished it
I finished both away out and it takes
did you go finish way out no we did you
did keep on
F really fun oh the God yeah I like the
like way out mhm that was really fun
wasun it was pretty it was pretty
hilarious yeah
I want more games like that the screen
built in yeah and the Betrayal I love
that oh sure we love
betrayal that's what you're into I see
[Music]
gr that's what I'm used
to I'm going to fix pipe
one I'm going to
fix whatever that is this is broken
pipeline functional again I don't know
how to fix this we still have
malfunction in the
system oh I see okay now I get
it what difficulty is this this is
big but other pipines are still
malfunctioning this is more than
satisfactory I don't I'm having
time PTSD let's go all pipelines fixed
and operational again
I don't think I don't think that's the
right put it on a shirt my
heart incoming swarm show them your dwar
a
[Music]
swarm you know in German we say when we
have a crush on someone we say that's
our
swarm you're my
inspection you're my Paras all right all
right wa my little oh you control me
you're l in my brain I you're my
little yeah please I can't focus on
anything with you in my body
really romop my calories
please I would like to hear that you
make me want to lose
weighty no
that's just a very
toxic very
toxic oh my God what's going on why is
it taking
off you didn't okay you're all there got
fuel okay and then they leave us do we
have fossils though well done cargo
rocket is returning to orbit we're
sending in the drop to get you out hang
tight
my pay us right
oh it's the
satis oh yeah of living this
lifestyle rocking Stone there the drop
rocking
Stone we're missing one
fossil yeah follow this one follow there
the
drop is that where the oh my God
I don't know
entally can we go back without the last
F fossil I mean I think that's a
secondary objective but yeah okay oh
[\h__\h] I'm out of ammo I can't I can't
protect myself anymore
um oh God I'm out of
juice okay I ordered the first re Supply
in case somebody wants them but we're
extracted in 2 and a half minutes oh you
can take these
wait which which pipeline was it two
take number
two I guess I don't
need take number two and then take
Cron's platforms here ATT number
two one last gr I love this grappling
[Music]
hook is such a great
Scout yeah I don't like the
way at
all Scout look at me I got a grappling
made this way this way going
yucky ah I see grappling
H God damn bro how do
I maybe you can make a yo climb thing
over here here I made climb bro climb I
keep falling oh not you I'm sorry I'm
talking to myself sorry no no no I
didn't even hear what you said I just
you're platforms I can't jump
them you know I can't jump them
either ow oh no
cover who died I'm but I'm I'm here with
her I will and I'll show her the in one
minute
are you sure you got it yeah yeah yeah
yeah I think now there's still enemies
spawning okay where are
you
where okay follow me y I see take this
first zip line and then from there I
made the second zip
line back off creepy CW careful that
jump is really difficult I failed it
many times
30 seconds 20 seconds run not that yeah
it's like right in front just just I'm
not good with time
pressure come on and then and here over
here over here over here I'm not going
to make it four what three two
byebye no no no no
sorry you're so heroic oh I still get
the complet it though oh good good good
I don't get okay nice like
exp
de oh no no you're alone yeah you're
breathing you're still breathing yay
thanks for coming back for me I guess
cuz I guess that's what that implies
you're welcome
no we sent the b in to get you
maybe as long as you sent something oh
that's
true thanks for another mission control
next time next time he's there as moral
support you always hating on Mission
Control
Milestone pure Park Mania o perk
points all
right another mission complete we
playing more what are we doing oh
nice a
hospital was wearing pink
panties I am oh because I died kind of I
want to look at myself I got a dance to
look at
myself steam now quit it pink
underwear but aren't you supposed to be
naked under that
no I want to take that off and then work
I got more
eggs wait no we
don't Mission selected and locked in one
more mission mission one more mission is
that what you guys said I didn't hear I
I am I hit the get to it what is this
that's a sick
move what is that what is this I've seen
that
before wait we need to drink of
beer okay I want to drink the glyphid
glyphid but do you guys have rank seven
we haven't tried The glyphid Slammer
yet we need rank seven n I'm only four
okay then I think
worst beer for me and my friend
sausage I love it's so cute that the
handle is a sausage
too oh cute does sausage go well with
here well I suppose
probably I never tried it but I'm
guessing that's I feel like dancing why
there's so much beer there oh they say
yes ERS from management stop dancing and
get to it it's cute cheers goinging the
p
stand up up you're
weeny Che in German we
[Music]
say yeah FR p r o s Frost
Frost
Frost chug chug chug chug chug chug
chug hit the mission
boys let's go
yeah if I'm is okay with it oh yeah are
you yeah okay last mission maybe okay
right hope it's going to be we're
leaving going to be hard we're going to
die oh this counter is giving me PTSD
should I make it
harder no I'm really looking forward to
be working with you guys let's roll I'm
really looking forward to working with
you where go I'm here oh she on the ship
I'm on the
ship crying
cron yeah we got a oh low haard though
final mission
oh what if this one don't let the [\h__\h]
get me not a good one kill anything with
more legs than
two I don't think
slow get get back in a hurry collect
evil nuts send be on
yourn
particular yeah is that a nut that's a
nut right terrain scanner just got
updated with a new location my nuts
cracked it open you're still not wearing
you're still wearing your hospital gwn
what uh is there stats like uh uh
that's a lot of
enemies well I'll just use you girls as
my
armor you'll be my me Shields n Good
Times okay okay it's like when you would
like go to the hospital when you were in
elementary school and then you would
keep the bracelet on so people would be
like oh my god what
happened did you go to the
doctor that's kind of why I always wish
to break a bone because I want people to
be like oh what happened you never
broken one no never and I really want to
so then I can get one of those cast can
I sign your cast so that everyone can
sign your cast yet please do on
me I had that I had a broken arm in
school once a that's so
fun so fun yeah oh there's an eye I'm so
jealous you broke a limb you shattered a
bone how did did you break your arm uh I
was swinging between between two chairs
like a couch chair and uh I was trying
to like swing and do cool stuff and then
I fell on
my nobody knew it was broken for a few
days and I was just holding it weird and
they were like uh oh it were you not in
pain yeah but I was just being quiet I
was just like I don't know I didn't want
to get in trouble cuz they always told
me not to play on the couch like that oh
a your pain tolerance must be
crazy I guess you
guess sorry I put an explosive down by
accident don't minding up boom boom heck
yeah oh it's taking a
while come
on Sho
explode barage
in oh
no
what what in the
[Music]
ow
fast this is fun
[Music]
squishy what's that you can pet him
a am
I am sorry no Molly Molly's here Deep
Rock seriously needs to invest in Molly
there again we missed
her
Molly See Molly is better than whatever
potentially hostile
creatures yeah yes so you don't have to
pet
those oh my my God there's a million
tiny spiders oh
you're where where are we that way this
way come collect your
more
more for sure and not are these the nuts
that we're looking for yeah I think so
don't shoot
me you missed some dude who that was
rude
I left it for
you I love keep missing oh well it
stays oh we're going pretty far yeah ooh
gold what kind of thing this technology
get like other resources that aren't
important I think it will add onto our
loot yeah so
okay for
anything I money
money I can't pet
ity yeah press E I should give you
a what's a sweet thing like you doing
this hell why is he flirting with it
Chang look at his
mouth he can hold stuff you're
aoran call it a Pog plant
why doesn't is POG as a I can see why
they would call it that say p
juice how do you put down our Molly
again see
yeah
okay I want to dispose of some
[Music]
okay which way are we going I'll follow
you you seem to have actually
surprisingly a good sense of
direction she uses the map yeah
uhhuh I use goba
oh we just need I like how you scratch
your head each time you look at that the
M yeah you scratch your head cuz I
wonder where we supposed to go this way
thinking so hard thinking real hard
starved for brain cell wait did I go the
wrong
way no wouldn't go the wrong way that's
right me the wrong way no
[Music]
light is up what
this it's a
nuts nobody knows I have great
directional s alien plants actually I
guess we were are we traveling to
different planets each time we go around
cuz that was a spaceship right and then
maybe so like I thought it was just like
a drilling I guess it is but we went
through the space right right in the in
the scenes No it's all on the same
Planet okay but this is at least not
earth right oh I don't think
so flamethrower where are
you I ain't going to tell you again all
right
oh pres your bullet jam oh sorry ah ah
why am I shooting my friends what's
wrong with me the planet is named
haes this is
Ohio honestly like
thatting oh you can pet the loot hgs too
don't work with the
Enemy oh
oh nut oh
nut crack it open looks like a
wall inside
looks wait do you say in English do you
also call it a
a
Le light light light okay oh light yeah
the inside of the nut looks like a light
talking about the
Slugs
uh the the fruit right yeah the fruit
there's a slug called a li no no no no
no
no Sho no no I mean the I mean the nuts
the inside of the nuts looks like a li
yeah
yeah I got the deposit where
to oh
crony huh I found some more kite
what more kite that would probably be
easiest with your platforms or Watson
can dig her way up she might sorry I'm
dealing with something right now you're
good oh yeah you
are oh my God my stomach not a big
deal thank you
I'm going to go
cry uh you didn't hear that right no
didn't hear it no I didn't hear it
[Music]
okay it's all the beer that we've been
drinking with the
[Music]
sausages do you know there's actually
this time so I've actually just brought
I thought about this the other
day with with the the the the the I
guess the change coming with with myth
um I've been thinking back on all of
like cringy stuff just I guess
reminiscing over the years and there was
this time that uh I was recording
something you know in Japan and when you
go and you meet the the like the mixing
team and you're like you know hello
hello hello
um and it was just it was just me and
staff and then the the mix team or
whatever in in a studio so it's quiet in
the studios and time to get busy and
we're sitting and we're no no we're
we're sitting there and they're
discussing things and I can't
participate in the conversation so I'm
sitting quietly and then he goes really
quiet cuz we're waiting for something
and then um my stomach starts just going
at it like
just like really loud and
awful and I'm thinking that it's I'm
thinking oh my God everybody can hear
this right now everybody's listening to
this is so embarrassing but I actually
don't think anybody could hear me or my
stomach going crazy but I thought they
could so um after
like you thinking too much after after
like 3 minutes of intense stomach
growling I just out of nowhere I stand
up and I go okay that's it and then I I
leave the
room and um I still don't I don't think
they had any idea what the heck I was
talking about I think they now I think
they think I'm we it was yeah it was
recording studio oh yeah they can
definitely hear it oh
good oh
good I'm out of ammo there's no
maybe heard it but they were being
considerate not saying anything they
felt they might be
embarrassed well I was hoping that I
hope they didn't just think like wow
yours weird she just like she just got
up and like what what somebody did
I placed the
thing Supply
pod oh my God oh my God I'm going to die
I can't
shoot Supply
me thank
you Loy okay I have been now I
can need
have Shield I have a
shield did you girls know you had a
shield you had a shield you just have Oh
you mean the blue
stuff
press I press for that's is that
supposed to be a
shield Oh you mean it's like a ah I
thought you meant a real
Shield so that was a shield I think it's
different for everyone mm cuz I get a
ENT gun if I press four oh throwing in
your hammer
for a pickax Shields ready again out
of boom boom
baby I need a damn mine cart on legs
where is it yeah but now I got nervous
cuz I thought that like some staff
members thought I just had like this
really weird explosive burst of I got to
get out of here here no it happens man
everybody quiet the quiet oh the quiet
got to gross she's lost her
mind I had to leave and skitter up the
walls but actually I just needed a rice
bow
actually yeah I love the the the salmon
row wait what was it not Salon
[Music]
R my favorite is maybe two B
T I like men Tao a spicy card R yeah
yeah yeah the row yeah yeah did you try
the one there's like they have these
Deluxe ones in black bags they had
salmon Deluxe Salon roll one it was so
goody they probably still have it oh I
want to try that I I don't even know
that was a thing it's so
good it's yummy
no tuna is where want tuna is a bit
basic but you know
what but it's plastic
yes it's good really yummy here I love
tuna I love Tuna on pizza too I thought
you don't like fish really Tuna on Pizza
I don't like raw uh raw
fish yeah tuna and pizza is very common
here oh that's new now want pizza damn
yeah me
too only had a quo so far
today come
here oh wait we've got all the need
these we're just looking for
nuts okay I hope we didn't miss any cu
then we'll have to go all the way back
now
surely there's more like extra ones in
case you miss
[Music]
some stomach
please have you eaten I did it just
makes noise oh sorry Make some noise
Make some noise and good
[Music]
tummy can't hear you enough louder Make
Some Noise please please no please I
want to hear good tummy what's going on
I get so self-conscious when I hear my
stomach Grumble and then it gets caught
on stream and it's like oh my God oh my
God I do have a digestive track no
please
[Music]
we have enough NS and enough more hit
already that's nut drop
inbound grabbing
ammo who's hit the how do we go back
up wait is somebody
yeah music is you just Grill somebody
hit we can backtrack the pet
the we remember drop departing in tus 5
minutes ah find maybe oh there it goes
you got it you want to follow the guy we
can where the mule he's down there oh
oh oh is it
downward yes a downward spiral as they
say yep down run Yi RMA this time I will
not be left
behind you
run where where' everyone go you have go
all the way down and you'll see the the
green sticks follow the light follow the
green lighten sticks green sticks oh
green stick follow the lights yeah I see
them me your
make maybe I'll even be faster than the
mule I'll leave the enemies for you
girls I got to pad my stats I have PTSD
now I I don't want to be left behind
anymore do
something blood
enem wed into my bullets
gr oh shoot
dangerous yeah are you behind me yeah no
no no drop departing in t Min is three
minutes too much
time no you're
cheating take me with
you no I have those too but they don't
work as easy as
yours look how he charging
flexible oh
let you've been web oh oh
shitu oh I'm out of yeah I'm also out of
ammo let's just
run work for
me
die die cre successfully retrieved make
it snappy team
right now EDD CER where are you I have a
feeling I know why your tummy makes
funny
sounds
why
not my is everyone on board I'm on no
I'm fighting can we go in already okay
oh my God
[Music]
all right are we now all on board
yes step why does it not close step back
step
back please step all the way inside the
all the way thank
you let's take
the US come on guys rock and rock
[Music]
good that felt refreshing
just that's why it felt refreshing
because my ass was
on you had a nice
[Music]
breeze that's why I wanted to run first
so you all can see where that breeze is
going
towards so you walking behind me D crop
us crop d
crop
dust lethal crop dusting
[Music]
no done
okay
yay yay last beer yeah last
beer okay one for the
road dance monkeys you call me please
give me that was pretty rud I will give
you
that on you thanks
another boys better be Min than
dancers oh
wait oh sausage again it's a
[Music]
sausage
yay one last round t
[Music]
byby close
close CL and eat the cups
and
face
bro nice this time oh Goa got two hits
am got two
hits yipp
[Music]
yipp thank you for guiding us for the
game yeah
I didn't do except kill stuff you got it
that's important yeah it's fun I like
this
game yeah I like the drinking aspect of
it oh Min G damn I'm good at
[Music]
this oh
nice mess oh I didn't okay this is not
happening this is
oh get faster would
like spaming ity this is this is the
Flappy Bird game yeah
yeah
yeah I can't play the Flappy Bird game
flppy bird where where dely boot all
right
my fans once made made a kfp version of
floppy birds I'm using my lucky CR
you I'm guessing it's not space how do
you I think you left click left click
left click ah okay it's it's a boot I
had a good runy boot that video game
will R your brain no I wasn't sure about
the controls okay okay here we go game
going to R your brain I bet you Mission
Control has a permanent andent from his
headset digs into his brain did he like
hurt you like when insulting maybe she
has PSD he's insulting us I'm sending it
back so he knows not the mess with us
yeah youy bird is too
difficult I prefer the the kiky K
game
K okay this time I'll make
it this is maybe an idea for another Ian
Rec game oh
who games yeah take different KF like
sure I don't know why it has to
be cuz why
not the game doesn't matter yeah you're
playing you're playing you're playing
you're here to work yes not to play
video
games huh we're literally playing a
video game right now uhuh we're
working yeah on that high score hand ey
coordination practice y level two
increase D youpp bird so
unfair don't kick the
machine last level last life come
on want to try it if only my real job
was as easy as playing a video game see
how good you are now people on stream
are watching people watch people
play video game
sub oh oh oh she's getting a feeling for
oh
W professional Jetty
Booter oh boy level two let's go
a lock in
cron oh oh
[\h__\h] you are so locked in you're
a man there is that the last mini game I
think so oh yeah I think
[Music]
so
sausage a forge
the forge the sausage in
space
yummy bye where does it go to
bye big
button oh cute that's a
leg what's happening gravity oh gravity
oh help me
much one more please
oh oh jet boots there's jet boots up
[Music]
here for free free all the way at the
top all the way at the top wait can you
die you can't die
right my boots are try it
out um okay okay oh top hanger maybe
it's here top hanger no don't think you
can
die so dis well well happy rooba Fest to
everybody yes happy oober Fest hold on
wait I want to get jet boots tring this
is off limits to regular
miners I maybe he said that to you
cronch foreign in theun y okay I have
jet you would know anything about it
okay no take off modes are too take fall
damage you does it take fall damage I
think so no no no bars are to be left
alone and
[Music]
not okay always she's forever going to
be in this Hospital bit down yeah I
don't know I guess until I change my
clothes why sh she's got LOD
yeah and
well if I go into the Wardrobe it says I
am wearing my MK1 Gunner suit I choose
oh
yeah
leaving fine with
this shows have been
through oh now I'm back to normal
apparently
a
okay um
so we going to let Amy go to to do her
thing now yeah get ready did you yeah is
it listy can we raid into it oh no I
haven't scheduled it yet sorry thank you
though well everybody will know where to
go later
on I will post on
Twitter yeah I was going to retweet the
myth collab but then there was no stream
like on Twitter so I was like oh I'll
just like ret the schedule I guess yeah
I always post the thumbnail and stuff
really late sorry oh it's all good man
that out my way yeah hell
yeah right have a yeah you were watching
crony huh yeah I saw when you guys
planted the wrong seeds in my farm well
did you see when I died uh in your
stupid
Tower well you fell for the stupid Tower
yeah well I saw water at the bottom I
thought that it was going to be fine it
was obviously a prank it was just a
prank
yeah I'm going to go in there and blow
it up last few hours I have access to
Minecraft server and then she can't be
punished
anymore yeah try that what try it well
crony will punish you in person she will
go visit you and punish you personally
me on a different
member no I would know who it is yeah N
I would These Boots are not made for
walking there won't be any actually if
you uh don't do it ah on stream man come
yeah that's true no but who would do
that on the on the server oh like you
know on the en server no l and so
recently you know Ving she announced her
crimes
already
exactly maybe maybe it's a different
member they got the idea from me and
they're and me they know that you're
just going to blame me they'll never get
blamed I'll put up some security
cameras thank you security that'd be
cool I'm surprised her her bunker
doesn't already have security
cameras it would be nice if they added
that oh
oh already has always has been SEC is my
security camera a I didn't see any end
when I was there they wereing be around
somewhere oh I guess so God damn they're
gone but yeah okay that was a fun cab
thank you had a good time yeah thank you
guys want to play thank you for playing
yeah thank you thank you
y so don't forget your lat hor and your
dandle and your sausages and don't
forget to rock and tear no rock and rock
and R walk in Te
[Music]
whatever you so
often what's with your socks do they
count as later H in uh
no no no
socks rocking Stone rocking stone rock
stone
rock rock rock and stone rock and
stone you guys had fun chat I did and
you and chat yeah yeah no you togot they
were
here I
[Laughter]
just
okay and what you guys
say Happ yeah
[Music]
oh thank you you girl say your
goodbyes
farewell
bye oh so proper
sorry
okaya you do you free actually wait
crony has a bye-bye greeting cumi right
yeah but it's a little too early for cro
I feel like are you sure M don't you
just want go back to sleep right now me
you were so you sounded so tired when
you came into the be I know right cuz
yeah but yeah okay uh
then
bye
Watson that's not a goodbye but sure oh
yes Su Waton yeah see you see you Lon
Watson lat see you
Watson see you
[Music]
Watson
byebye
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye goodbye
everybody bye what I'm sorry I say
goodbye still
okay e
Rock
Solid J on
please just let the barrels be as fun
times go there are better options
available