[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a ah
K hello uh I hope I hope I am on the
server I don't know if I did it
right I think I
[Music]
did hello how's it going starting to to
a
ah oh of course of course I forget that
oh you see where my mouse is even though
I'm not in the game haha I'm being
tracked coach starting
now let's
go okay
TW we
we uh
so didn't ask some to somebody in Hol n
for the server what
I followed instructions and I hope uh I
am on the server where everybody else is
not that anybody is online probably
not maybe nobody will ever be online
when I'm online especially because the
hype is kind of dead but whatever we're
still going to start
our this small Adventure I don't know
how much I'll end up playing um you'll
know right away okay so what I've been
thinking I I didn't want to go past this
point
because should I start where you know
everybody starts because it does give
you options right to start in other
places but they may be more
difficult this sounds all right has
resources but but it's a Island
should I just go to the to the main
area
uh some places are more hard right
they're all about the same level oh
okay but is everybody here then lots of
Ian is in winds swep okay yeah that
makes sense I mean just just to make the
chances higher of any interactions if
there ever will be any
interactions gooda has a beach
face I don't know the thing is like when
I played privately like just like this
area already like exploring this area
already takes like so many many hours
and hours and hours that like if I start
here I'm never going to get
here so yeah
okay uh I hope this is
correct what do you guys
say does this look like other people
live here it's kind of
dark I mean this is not the first time
I'm playing the game so uh the the
beginnings I I know what to do and all
that just
saying bi's base is close God I haven't
played in a while how do I run okay is
this running yeah oh okay
okay okay what the is that huge ass
Dragon damn oh what the
damn
okay we are in the right place
mhm
well I am a
beginner I need to collect the simplest
materials gosh it's been weeks since I
last played
this
um how do I open uhhuh E was throwing a
sphere I no throwing a
pal was q q was let's not do that Q is
throwing how do I open
inventory
how do I punch punch punch okay yeah
let's not throw this this sphere let's
take this Stone oh yeah we need like
sticks and stuff right to like start
building a base tab a yeah thank you
it's been a while it's been a
while slowly but surely we will
start
our thing our Bang
H that they have already claimed the
usual yeah yeah that's what I'm thinking
like that is like the the best spot to
have a base like there by the water
that's where I had my base in my solo
playr you had me at anus it's an
anus it's it's anus
welcome to wa was anus
tart I am highly amused as Always by The
Jerk It's a new
star if I ever get a car maybe I should
put that on my car
plate oh my
God as a fan I should as a fan
of Arrested
Development maybe I should one day when
I have a car why does this uh tree not
break ever don't they disappear at some
point a strong
tree
I is that normal is this tree
bugged what the hell it's unbreakable
tree I think I I've got enough
Stones ow that must really hurt
I should be taking damage from this
realistically
ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow okay better to maybe pick up the ones
that are on the floor
um you guys said good Eyes by the beach
huh
H I don't know if that's a good place to
build a base
though hello big mammoth
that's your name right mamor rest mamor
rest
cute Hello if I enter are they going to
attack
me because they belong to
someone damn whoa what is that is that
like the I don't even want to know this
is like spoiler hardcore
spoiler any flat area yeah so this n any
flat area is
good but like I feel like it's
especially for the beginning it's good
to be around trees
and stones and all that and
because o can't immediately have a stone
and tree
farm yeah whoa what the
we're rock hard is this Beach's
base yo I can steal this let's go not
that not like they need those few
fibers let's be
honest they look at me I'm a freaking
beginner and this looks like
Paradise that's that's so scary what the
hell
whoa oh yeah over there over there here
that's I think where I used to have my
base not using it yeah
so is she even going to play this game
again you
know o
okay just exploring for now bow bow home
beware of dogs your smile will be
protected if that's such a like this
says it's like whole a whole some place
but if I need to be Weare of dogs that
sounds
dangerous so this is foral place doesn't
look very
[Laughter]
Advanced all right we can take
something mine let's use forus onen wow
wait they have a nice view What The
Hell House on the
cliff
nice oh that cat looks funny oh my God
it's like an Allison Wonderland cat
a green Z in German
G can
I could I take something out of the
boxes not that I'm going
to not that I
would yeah gr a Kat Kat is cat grza is
like smile but
like you wouldn't say show me your grin
you would say show me your uh
lean okay who who this belong
to that looks also pretty well protected
narissa
oh should move in with
narissa hello this is W is narissa
home
no
damn I'm so sad oh
cake can I take no pancake and Cake damn
I feel like she's doing this for me but
look at the corn crops in there yummy
and the chicken corn C and chicken and
like
paprika damn bell peppers yo it's like
Made For
Me W look at
that
yo it a duim
m
I'll be
back oh she surely doesn't mind be what
I just ran through and I automatically
picked up the items I didn't even press
F I got milk and eggs from narissa and
lots of uh
wool amazing yeah I'm close to
overweight so I I noticed that therefore
I left um but okay ow what the
H oh oh who who's this who's this they
got
like interesting
design
Iris
oh
aha she flattened oh don't pick up look
at that cow though freaking cow oh
oh wow oh wait it's right by the spawn
point what the
hell probably on purpose
huh no actually why though cuz you can
totally just like teleport to your home
it doesn't need to be by a spawn point
but okay
okay taking up the spawn
point double
teleporter let's say we were in a war
you know we couldn't use that spawn
point cuz Iris would immediately attack
us you
know do you give me free stuff
now
yeah thank you I feel like ah I should
have talked to someone up there too the
oh
well
oh oh my first
Effigy
afugu eff
modu I don't know why that's in my bra
brain who what the is that over
there oh it's ah I thought it was a wild
one but it's
within
it does does that one belong to
IIs that would be crazy if that was a
wild one I never saw that one before
capture him I don't think I
can Iris right okay okay yeah looks
looks too crazy to be water
egg egg egg egg egg egg okay now I'm
with okay I need to
build
no
um I need to eat
anyway does this help was that enough no
uh
oops
[Music]
um egg well got to get more than enough
eggs
anyway stats wait how do I use how do I
do the stats
again uh a yeah uh yeah let's go let's
go
wait is it still there oh is still
there okay sorry a I dropped you for a
moment but don't worry you're with me
what if I is there any any any people
over there in that area up there like
not up but like that you know what I
mean you know what I mean this area this
area cuz if not then that might be a
good
area you guys know everything it's just
like with Minecraft everybody's like so
informed about who is
where yeah that looks really
empty that looks good like
yeah oh
yeah h
pal spere
nice
egg right here in the middle or like
more
towards some trees or the
[Music]
water or right there at the
beach middle is good right next to water
why do we need water again well yeah
here here might be nice
here it's pretty flat too okay wait how
do you build a base again all B build we
need uh just a primitive workbench for
now I guess
okay I got to plan this out though I
can't just randomly place
things but I have no no no plan let me
put this here maybe can I put it on the
stone oh I can I can make this stone
work for me there's like a building
platform no not really
[Music]
but
yeah yeah we building this
easy who who whoa whoa okay we
need I guess a club let's go to the club
let's
party let's
Party Pals have trouble paing around
this rock oh God damn it you built it
there like literally here you literally
built your stuff here in your solo play
through even though you could have had
it like all the way in the beginning you
chose to have it here feel like we have
some connection
there
damn my palet gets don't worry don't
worry don't worry we'll figure it out
uh I guess I'll move it again but um
wait how do I make this like base thingy
I guess I got to like have like Tech
Tree Tech Tree it's been a while it's
been a while the pal
box right is what I need
yeah uh how many points I have 13
okay
wooden structure set right and a shy
bed and straw pal
beds
and maybe need a
campfire wi
chest M yeah chest very important I
guess I'll get this one
too okay
so such nice
weather wow ch
campfire for the night yes okay to cook
oh yeah right ah yeah yeah
and uh how do you how do you do this
again
uh uh how do I how do I get to the ah
B here okay uh where should this be like
in the front or here in the back or in
the
middle m
[Music]
Center Middle yeah right cuz it creates
a big circle right
okay here's the
middle stay in the middle like you
little away from water no too close to
the water can I move it how do I move
this
uh that was too close I mean
yeah be
be this assembly
mode I got all the materials back
right
uh okay so how about here how about
here uh be like build
here and water is a waste of space Oh Oh
don't fight oh my God we're going to
have constant fights over
there let going go a little bit little
bit a little
bit
like cuz I want like if somebody comes
like from here or for here from here I
want them to be able like to make a
curve and go to the left or to the right
or whatever I don't want to like block
everything
so yeah maybe maybe
like
here should be like the
middle place and check Circle yeah yeah
now I have a good feeling about this
one
okay
Circle that's all right that's all right
that's good
there I don't think we're in the water
either oh yeah
nice hi
wonderful let's dis assemble
this wood am I lacking wood
already uh too close to a special boss
or for
facility don't
worry
H here
okay yeah in the
beginning I need so many
materials let's gather some more wood I
think we're out oh although I would like
an axe
please can I make an
axe uh yeah yes I didn't make one yet
right did
I it's really comfy really well the
beginning's comfortable for you to be
watching but hey I got to do all the
work yo ah
[Music]
no I always do
that I always do that oh and I need
happen to you too and now I need those
like I only have two I need
them maybe cuz like others surely have
advanced to better
spheres surely they can donate some of
these they surely have some leftover
right like lowlevel weak ass pal
speres donation
please okay I need to get wood uh tree
actually I should just use my own trees
over
there they should have hundreds of the
blue ones they got like see there you go
but like I mean not that I can like just
take them now and they're not online
so yeah oh if narissa is like
narissa let me DM
narissa she's probably still sleeping
but
narissa when you get up
um do you perhaps have
some uh low level low tier pal speres
that you don't need and want to donate
to the W oh she's on her phone I think
she is
up I just started my character in pal
world yes and I took uh a accidentally a
lot
of some
wool H that was laying around in your
base okay she says give me a bit I'm
naked and in bed you're welcome guys
you're welcome for that
[Laughter]
information you are welcome oh I'm too
happy no in the beginning God damn it
man always too
heavy what what can I build
anyway wooden
chest uh ah here in the back cuz since I
can't move so well I could like make waa
house in the back
here right should I make it here or
somewhere else maybe maybe over
there cuz then the palace can still
reach those stones right
okay
no well it's okay never donate to
me I wish you could like pick them back
up at least for like like 10 seconds or
so after you threw them like they like I
wish they would give you a chance to
give to to take it back
uh I
wish
oh wow wow golden
hour Cav V why and I F on the
ground
who I'm not part of your
[Music]
SST oh hello sir hello friendly sir
don't worry I won't kill you in this
play through I
think my dad's not a phone
duh
what I have a
visitor how wonderful but I'm busy right
now don't disturb
me your mind's in disturb
[Music]
distur catch
him I can do such a thing wait
cancel if I catch him like what is he
going to do for
me
ceiling uh can I
make oh uh probably needs to be like a
base of a roof there right and then you
can build the roof on the roof
right oh I wonder if you could have high
ceilings like this cuz like this is
really uh
claustrophobic can I is that
possible
no I want High
ceilings
yeah yeah I'll just I guess repeat where
I have the windows oh wa oh yeah right
you get a level up from building I
forgot about
that multiple floors yeah sure I don't
need multiple floors for now I just want
High ceilings this is like one of Wawa's
houses maybe later we'll make a bigger
one I saw in my YouTube recommendation
like a video from like a pal World house
or like base
build and yo I was like
damn that looks really beautiful it's
like they're they're going so hard on
like
creativity just like
in just like in like
Minecraft
M yeah I was so beautiful like it didn't
even look like it was P world it was so
creative and elegant and Charming I wish
I was that creative me
too me
too just got to use a reference I feel
like a lot of these people use
references anyway so you don't need to
feel bad about using
references someone made the minds of
Moria here
oh damn let's
go that's incredible already way
down okay Mama Mia it's so dark I need
to build a bed so I can sleep good thing
we have wool for
free
[Music]
and is it like in
Minecraft uh uh where if you want to
sleep everybody has to sleep or how does
that work
here yeah do they get like a prompt or
so same
thing I'm going to die I'm going to
die okay it's okay wa don't don't
panic we can make a campfire in the
house for
now right that's that's fine right I can
that's not dangerous right I know it's
not really fast to die through freezing
it's okay oh yeah I need to make clothes
too so many things I need to make you
know so many okay bed
next nice uh do you get like nicer
looking beds in the future future I
don't remember if I saw any on the tech
tree how do I turn
this
oh yeah read
[Music]
W there's two more just one green bed
much later okay I think I want to put it
here it's quite nice here can look
outside the
window and be stared at by this
guy is WIA here now wow in the chat or
what wait is it me or it's laggy what
the stream or the game the game ah ah oh
there oh she wrote in the chat I didn't
see that oh in that chat how do I write
ah um how to say where I am what's this
uh there's like a there's a
teleportation Point here right what's
this one called that's where the boss is
right the first boss I think
I want
sleep Fire doesn't
reach okay
uh foot of the first boss
Tower
feet okay we have the roof right oh this
is nice
yeah this is already looking nice now
clothes let say you can bring me all
kinds of materials you know it doesn't
have to be just
spheres
um how far is Nissa anywhere like if
she's not too far then I don't want to
like take things from
her 11 points here clo or is she going
to you
know I'm going to make my
clothes uh and spare is already oh
always nice uh a feed box probably
will'll need
cloth and shields are
amazing y you just
close how do you know oh is she the no
the 11 m is him right does it show me
her on the
map no I don't see
it talk to that guy no okay I will
s my
[Music]
sorry I've got some good items in
stock M I have no
money but yeah looks nice looks yummy
good luck dude hope nobody catches you
in the pal sphere that would be really
terrible why is there a relo saurus
which one this one why
not why
not
okay I need to make I guess on the
workbench my
cloes I still haven't caught a
single uh two a single pal I'm not ready
for it I'm not ready I don't feel
[Music]
ready
I'm not ready for you oh you're right
that's right that's there's some mod for
chicken maybe next pord stream I can
have you
guys I can make chicken mod sorry I'm
just I'm not trying to look at my tummy
I'm trying to look at
surroundings oh
interesting close kids please don't
chicken out from chickening thickening
the
chickening
yes cloves let's put them on before oh
it's automatically before narissa comes
and sees me almost
naked uh The Shield needs more wood okay
okay okay
okay no more tummy yeah the tummy times
are over it was nice though wasn't
it good times she would hate that
yeah can't believe how fast she she
logged in like she was just naked in her
bed and then immediately
oh she's already in the
game it's like oh damn oh damn wa needs
me so good that she's that she doesn't
have a completely messed up sleep cycle
thank
God cuz I certainly
do
is that is that Nissa she's
beautiful
wow be oh oh be beautiful aren't
you join
Guild oh wait no don't run away I want
to join you Guild I don't know if I
should
but what does that do I door away why is
it why no am I oh is it like an advent
only Guild don't join don't don't not
why not Ks are buged oh
okay oh
pick
yummy oh so it makes you share bases aha
did you bring the
Spheres
Wu oh wait actually I'm can't move I
again don't
I need to build a
chest change into the clothes you gave
me clothes oh belt
armor thank you
Mommy woohoo and now the tummy is back
and we're twinning we're twinning I
think
cute the visitors left the base ah that
one okay okay okay wow so
fashionable
weisa weisa you look so
cutea you look cute with short hair you
should get yourself a shortcut for an
outfit in the
future Telly
time has Rissa even eaten breakfast
probably not can I get up here oh wow so
good okay now
chest
chest it is high time for a chest we say
you're welcome to oh there you are to
come
in what do you think about my high
ceilings
narissa very very nice
right wa very lovely thank you no Breaky
no Breaky
yet I hope you get some food for example
those pancakes what do I what do I put
in here M
egg flame
organ do you know you do you know
you oh that's not the end of the
sentence is it oh 65 F speres
amazing I have to split again take
half wait that wasn't half a shift sure
do you know you a so you can refresh the
food counter what what what do you mean
what you mean like eat one so it
refreshes to oh you can sort your
inventory to refresh
it oh did it oh what the oh they're
going to get rid of this someday aren't
they hey
[Music]
yo that is quite the life Haack
okay feel free to take anything you need
from my base can I doll can I open
things I feel like I
couldn't anus tart anus
tart from the F thank you you're so
sweet I'm going to get some more
wood I will need so much wood
leave the wood and the stone yeah I
guess I should
have narissa what's your plan for the
day what are you going to do
today what a way to enter honestly I
don't
know are you streaming
today you make voice out with her yeah
yeah but you know she just she just woke
up let's not stress her out and like
pressure her to be like in streamer
mode uh okay so
wood Stone
fiber oh what did she
say yes
ah WEA stream
[Music]
today what's the wi going to stream
today
yesterday was Twilight movie watch
along hope that was
fun I'm sure it was fun
demonologist what kind of doctor is that
demonologist demon
doctor Advent horror collab
oh oh it's a
[Music]
collabo wait what level is
Nissa just so I know what I need to
catch up to n are you planning on
playing pal world ever
again or am I doing this for
nothing just let me know 25 okay 25 I
can catch up to 25 I'm just going to I'm
just going to play um 10 hours
today probably honestly the way I play
10 hours is not enough to get up to 25
cuz like I run around so much to pick up
every single
item I level very
slowly I don't think it's going to be 10
hours today guys no no no no no what do
we want to build next uh we need
probably eventually a feed
box uh should we put it like in the
middle did she say something again that
I
missed
did she say something about her
plans oh oh
oh wait I kind of want to put ah
no cancel I think it would look nice if
it was on a platform but then they
probably bug around about uh bug bug
around around it right I'll just I'm
just going to put it
here yeah might come back to Pal world I
streamed pal World once before my break
and then I dipped and back then there
was no server yet
so you
[Music]
know
so so was that yes was the yes for yes
I'll play
again WEA are you going to play this
game again let's catch a
pal let's catch a
pal wait I have to hit them first
they fixed some of the pathf finding
issues in the last patch
oh okay they they yeah I need to catch a
chicken first of
all I can't not have you guys be my
starter was there a chicken there I
didn't see
one wait can I
teleport although that's like
so far uh wait uh fast
travel maybe just here to Iris right
this is
Iris
damn
well fried
eggs would be a shame if I ran through
iris's base because I'm kind of forced
to and picked up some cool
things I mean look at this 9,000 99 she
doesn't need that hey
yo I need a
key
no chicken
chickp chick
PE I'm keyless if only Iris had a key
I'm sure she
does oh
Lisa oh don't shoot me it's just me wo
wo wo wo wo
wo what I'm looking for a
chicken where are the
chickens Rissa is being
invaded
Invader
o no chicken but I do want those as well
I need I need them
all I'm going to catch gem I'm going to
catch
you is she still being invaded Mory C
mopy the
she has a Pokemon p
p named after the Freudian slip named
after CI but what about what about
[Music]
hi stay okay
c
c I'm staying are you getting me a
chicken or
what she cute she's so
cute Callie gave it to her ah how do I
drop
Pals oh what's it going to be what's it
going to be what's it going to be what's
it going to be woo apparently
[Laughter]
are
who what a cheky pee I would have caught
myself
though give me like a level 30 Pokemon a
pal hell
ah excuse me
there was say probably chuckling and
laughing whoa oh wait I thought that was
optical illusion I thought Optical that
wait is that really wait it is
Big why is it so
big sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry Sor oh
sorry I was just looking at your big
chicken it's cuz it's a shiny okay damn
I should catch that
oh
what do you have huh what do you
have
what oh oh what is that cute never seen
that
before sweet quing along the ground it
eats microscopic and organic
matter what is that ah
sorry i w
i oh ah stupid can't be chicken how dare
you reject my
offer no
[Music]
rejection nice oh I hear
music who what's that beautiful
thing
wow wo you're so
shiny wo oh yeah that's a good idea
picking up these things I'll help
[Music]
you what is these so cute it looks
interesting are those cat
ears who what is
this she has a whole Factory
here can
I
hello you're so cute I love you so
much I got that Pokemon when
I P when I was
playing oh my own I'm just not going to
talk
anymore
God damn
it God
[Music]
damn oh my
God
careful I don't want to talk
anymore we don't talk
anymore we don't talk anymore I want you
but I don't want to accidentally hit the
the
MMO that's very
dangerous can we do it
yay I'm so
cute is that enough 43 might not be so
good oh yeah yeah yeah join me join
[Music]
kfp also I have a stat point should I
also put it in weight
again maybe one stamina
now and how we looking here why can't I
go here yet eh need to be level five huh
am I not what
level
four wait
wait wa I'm literally I need one
exp
one let's get this
one a
penguin don't you dare pick a fight with
me I have a level
there oh God I
st the BS are attacking me I
think what the what the what's
going
[Music]
on they hate me I thought they were
protecting me I don't know anymore
what the hell or is she being raided
again I don't
understand ah damn it I wanted that
penguin WEA you owe me a penguin you're
peace took my pee away from
me let's go down here maybe there's a
pee a penguin I'll just say p to the
pals maybe maybe that will help
me wait wrong
thing
yeah has pal of violent yeah there's no
PVP okay okay so they were just because
that P was so close to her base yeah
yeah yeah they took it as a
fret so I can't take damage from her
Pals even if they shoot like exactly in
my
direction that is
[Applause]
reassuring there's a cute fox in the
water no don't run you're going to drown
your light is going to go
out
no no no you're drowning yourself
heo
he
heo how why is it how is it Jesus cat
why are you a fox why are you walking on
the
water water in the fire
why fire in the water
why fire on the
water there you
are you join horor today
now penguin we don't have a penguin yet
ah ah you will become wait I forgot I
have I they can help me uh I I I I
I
wait how do I throw
it
help it's going to die it's going to
die okay that's not much damage we're
good we're good I can only have one out
right
come on Jimmy do it for
me wait
maybe uh wait how do I switch again
uh
here maybe this one's
[Music]
stronger okay okay that's that that
looks
better
oh m maybe not high enough yet yeah okay
okay now it's good now it's pretty good
woo
no now now it's got to otherwise it's
going to die come on penguin we need a
horory penguin
[Music]
member Yahoo I'm almost dead Yahoo how
do I
recover just slowly by eating food huh
yay welcome to
[Music]
horo
um good job
gang very good
job come on get up
there now we could get
kativa it's okay don't run
away don't run
away don't don't stop running
I'm the best cat mom you could ever
imagine
I don't have
stamina uh-oh you're getting dangerously
close to Iris base so if I attack you
they're going to kill
you narissa do you have a bed that I can
sleep in over there at your
place I'm so far from my own yeah I saw
the Fig wait so stuff like that
do like if I see an fig does another
player also see the FG also un unless
maybe if they picked it up already in
their play through so they don't see it
but I see it
or uh they're instan okay
okay oh okay okay Lisa hello are you
still online yes
can I sleep
over is that
possible
whoa what is that
couch
wao oh it's my bed oh I don't think I
can I can't sleep with it I'm sorry it
this belongs to another
guild wait I I I can't even open the
door I'm stuck
maybe if you put it outside of your base
I could sleep in
it oh she's so
smart she's so
smart that's amazing that's how you can
trap
people one sec okie
dokie
Lambo no no no
no I'm sorry lamb bald I was not the
intention I'm too
strong now I could teleport to my base
but um um I don't want to go home cuz
I'm still chilling here I want to uh
catch some
peas wow you're so nice
oh she's making a little side
base the guest room whoa who who what
the was that whoa
hey
why the wow
Shack oh
a I'm sure Nissa feels very fulfilled
right
now to be helping me I have uh
wool actually I uh probably make my own
bed I could probably make my own
bed yeah I could I could narissa I could
make my own
bed unless you want to do it for
fulfillment
sake yeah
okay
okay pampered
Wawa yay
wow she's making my prison I'm her
prisoner I'm in the way for that piece
huh oh I wasn't oh I even have a
door let's go wait I I'll make the
ceiling I'll make the
ceiling Yoo okay let's let's sleep I'll
sleep in this guest house where I
literally can't see the bed
but
[Music]
it's the W waa
box good
morning okay time to catch some Pals I
said it right this time I need a bow cuz
like they keep on running away from me
why stay stay Stay Stay Stay
Stay that's what you get for running
away wo wo wo ah quick
okayo W my goomas is so
strong good
job good job us
wait wait
what wait I didn't catch
it did it
Escape hey yeah
yeah okay this time I witnessed
it oh look at that Li monk wait can I
have it no it belongs to WIA huh okay
makes sense I stole I stole the wood
though okay I want to go get the the fox
Sparks nice good start so
far
don't run don't run you can run but you
can't
hide no no no no no no
no hey I can't attack cuz I'm out of
stamina
hey don't no don't go
no
yeah let's go
finally all
[Music]
right
okay all
calculated according to
[Music]
Kaku and I know throwing a sphere could
stop it but then you know I'm wasting a
sphere kind
of
miss you cue PTI I need you too
oh quick I'll save you go into the ball
if you want to be saved oh another one
okay okay I'll get you too I'll get my
level up like this right yeah we're
level five
now wo oh level six we are okay so a
ranch
please
M statue of power of
course I guess a berry
Plantation palar
workbench the bow yeah okay
okay uh
[Music]
okay I like Mount the torch although
those are so annoying cuz you always
have to like turn them on or like I
guess you can get a a fire pal to turn
it on right well I put out wait wait
what I put out Vixie she'll dig up pal
balls oh for for
me thank you try
going to my Camp
okay thank
you a glider
yeah I don't know I feel like I'll just
maybe just wait until I have a a pal
that can glide
maybe any more Pals I should catch here
I think the rest is like
probably available over there
too now you wanted ASAP what do you know
what I
want ah yeah so here I don't think I can
I swim that distance with my current
stamina
maybe I'll add one and one here and one
oh that's it
okay nice outfit thank you sponsored by
Nissa okay let's
try oh yeah I can make
[Music]
it
Effy let's go Li monk
Effigy where does this lead to
nowhere I'll swim back no when I swim
back I have to climb up
to
pool I climb up
here what's logging
assistance The Prompt at the bottom
what's that
ooh stamina barely enough
barely oh his his Pals ah okay
oh oh I was able to open that one oh
yeah I don't need a key for that gold
Corin bread my first money and a megga
sphere already a meas
sphere let's get the
monkey let's go let's go let's go it
didn't see me coming at all oh oh 25 oh
one more hit one more hit nice
W
bere yay Monkey Business return to
[Music]
monkey yay we already got a good variety
I think of Pals I think I don't have the
Sheep yet so let's get the Sheep the
lamb
lamb don't
run I'm going to treat you well stop
it
ah they see you
rolling they
hating we can we can kill this one I
think yeah you take care of it
[Music]
gumos all wait what's your what's with
your damage oh my God how about ah damn
it can you do better
W oh the t
f oh my God
[Laughter]
don't so cute wait too
early water versus water not so good but
M oh oh it's two two
versus
two uh I think the this one should be
more efficient
right I want at least 10 it's okay for
now I just want a
variety for now I just want a
variety just get what I can
get
yeah oh and hey oh we
somehow subconsciously went back to our
[Music]
place oh oh that wasn't even on
purpose
ah don't die he
I saved
it good sense of direction I I felt it I
sensed it totally okay then let's work
on the base let's uh build the things
that I
learned that was a good outing uh oopsie
f
um life hack let's go
mushroom bread
can have the
bread also let me perhaps Grill the
meat I can Kindle this lamb ball mutton
yummy they look so good
o yeah I'll put them in the base chto
give me a moment there's so much to do
step by step step by
step slowly you
good uh yeah I actually need something
to
eat and kumas too you deserve it you
fought hard of course the chickens also
deserve it of course no question about
that
so what this thing is so
cute so oh right now I can only have one
huh what what can you even do you can do
like the plant stuff and something with
a fence what what what was
that this one the monkey is the
most the oh
supervision it can gather and lay egg in
ranch yeah I can indeed build a ranch
too uh but it was like
here yeah I already have the ranch ah
wood oh no okay
wait when I'm inside the
base uh it does take into account like
wood that I have in the chest does
it oh did it did it a what the oh
oh you scared
me yes it does oh what is
this Arrow girl let's go thank you 300
arrows
she the
best she the
best R A Heart
carry thank
[Music]
you
oh y wow fancy fancy Mount you got there
looks
comfortable n said a sugar
Mommy
honestly it feels good to be able to
help like that I I know how it feels
like in Minecraft and all that you know
so
Ranch let's have it also kind of in the
back
here with the opening
here can you help me build this chickp
chickp are you not going to help are you
not going to do anything
wow how the tables turn huh now the
chickens are watching no hands sorry
no but you could like PE PE PE PE PE you
could totally pack the nails
in she just going to walk around let me
do this all
alone oh how to
turntables uh
this is how it feels huh this is how it
feels well chickp with that attitude
you're going to be replaced very soon
you know that
right it's okay I'm making you your farm
now you better lay me 100 eggs per day
okay butchering
him no no no butchering him would be
too
quick we must torture
o who what is this what
the why is your F attacking my only
Pal doesn't seem to take damage though I
think it's okay it's okay he's crazy he
do be
crazy I it rain
damn oh well it's it's fine we need to
teach that chipa
lesson make it
fear
everything let's traumatize it
accordingly did you did you are you here
to bring me something again or I just
here to chill you're always welcome to
chill catch these hands with some what
hands you only have
wings who oh look how excited he is
suddenly need to have some
work you're on the wrong side Jimmy
you're on the wrong side oh good job you
bugged your way
in you forced your way in even though
there's a big entrance here what a smart
chicken you want to see if you can help
build N I guess
not thank you though did you already
level up two levels what the hell
weren't you level
25 a moment ago or did you round it
down don't know your own
level it's
like I need to I need to 100 eggs per
day it's going to take a while oh
God o o Jimmy back into the
base
Jimmy 100 eggs per day you
know you know
right
okay stop watching it's
embarrassing yeah I I thought you would
enjoy it stat oh
stone stone so much Stone okay we need
Stone all right
no
problem I guess I could Farm those over
there Kitty can grind Stone monkey wood
oh yeah yeah but I only have one slot
and you know if I only have one slot I
got to have the chicken out
there when do I get more P slots for the
base a Yeah by leveling it up huh
[Music]
okay I forgot how things work you have
to bear with
me let's see how that works again with
with with figs right what it with
figs ah I I know just by doing certain
things okay
okay upgrade okay upgrade straw pal beds
okay okay I'll do that and then we can
upgrade again but for now uh I don't
know you guys can go do some
stuff and then I I'll make some straw
beds why should we make the straw
beds should we make them all in one
area or like close to where they work
what do you
think kativa can mine
yeah I don't know if if kativa will do
that
though all in an open area Center yeah
we can build them around the center yeah
why not oh maybe around the food
box
yeah good idea us you got guys helped me
get the idea but I I I finalized
it
ah
uhhuh I know I just need free but okay I
ran out of materials anyway
y uh I'll help
you than thank
you nice to have hands
huh I saw a funny video on
Twitter today I liked it too maybe you
saw it cuz you guys always look at my
likes don't you of a cat loafing and
then somebody put plastic hands in front
like under its
face it was it looks so
perfect
they hard nerfed you it's okay you look
cute bury Plantation and deploy Pals
yeah okay one more
[Music]
M I don't know you for
now uh I know my fan base too well I
really do what was it what what did it
say bar Plantation okay uh Benny's
cobal
literally Betty's
cobal my favorite idle Group which isn't
active
anymore B's coob means like
berried sorry Beres
Factory
uh like
this I should have had the trees within
the circle but oh well we'll we'll get a
we'll get those Wood Farms going
at some
point did I pick that up
no Kobo means Factory not written like
that um Kobo with use k o u b o u kind
of like that if you were to write it out
in romanized
letters mhm
yeah that is cool
oh God damn it God damn
it come on help me I don't want to drop
it I don't want to
[Music]
drop
okay I I guess I have to drop it what
was I going to build the
ah but now I need the
stone I can't build it WEA hi you're
still here cute where's the chest inside
my
house yeah I'm just going
to put this in
here I don't think you can open it
WEA
unfortunately
oh what are you sneaking up to me oh
you're giving me stuff oh wait are you
sneaking you were just walking really
slowly cuz of the weight is this are you
insane she's a little bit
insane thank you although I don't know
maybe for her that's that's not much for
me that's a lot now that's a lot that's
really
helpful
than donkey
sh how did you bring those stones all
the way over here when you were so
heavy how did she do it very
slowly very slowly a day at a time one
step per day it's sleepy time
soon
okay let me put this also in the chest
and then we'll build and sleep sleep
first maybe look at that monkey go look
at him walk on his
for little
limbs I should make some chests outside
at uh for the pals to access
easier
oh God it's so loud who making so much
noise our quick stack
K it seems a visitors is heading towards
the base but they don't mean Nissa
right or do
they so finally Berry
Plantation if I build one will I have a
build a second one will I even use the
berry Plantation properly cuz I feel
like food is like
always more than
enough but I'll put one here I
think yeah I will use it you think so ah
next to the feed box nah it's okay it's
fine
here
I can put another feed box here like two
if I wanted
to uh oh oh he's already getting to work
so
cute you can make a lot of money with
berries you can move the Fe or make
another one yeah yeah I could I could
make another
one but for now I'm also going to make
another bed cuz I want it to look
organized oh okay how is it looking we
can level up I
think base
upgrade pal gear workbench and the
statue of power easy easy easy easy pal
gear cluff
cluff okay I have a lot of
wool
yeah I'll make
10 hello my dear W how do you do thank
you for asking I'm I'm fine I had a
quasa and some fruit some cut
strawberries for
breakfast and I have an apricot pie for
later or like something like a pie or
like a cake I guess
and thank you for helping cute
monkey wait was what am I doing uh this
okay um and yeah I
mean had some stuff to do before the
stream and
I I couldn't sleep until the time I
wanted to sleep even though that sleep
was really necessary cuz I woke up uh I
slept way too too late my sleep schedule
is crazy right
now crazier than
usual
yeah it is what it
is
MHM but I'm fine at the
moment I feel
fine where do you want to stand huh
here hope you can get some good rest I
hope so too how's smoothie behaving yeah
that's the thing she she woke me up too
early that little but she's also
been so cute so I can't be
mad she's a baby she's a cute baby I
love
her yeah you may have seen I was
definitely awake at like 5:30 a.m.
still here T Fant for watering the
berries I think would be pretty smart oh
and look at that another upgrade build a
crasher Stone pit and a loging set
gladly gladly I just need the
recipes level six can I even learn it
nope nope we need to level up so I guess
maybe it's time to go
again
wait we'll make this
and uh who she gave me a crossbow I
don't think I ever used the
crossbow only uh bows in the
game but works the same way
right right sorry I it went off just oh
I thought I thought AB let's go I I
was I was just playing
sorry it was an accident I thought I
thought oh it shoot immediately I
thought you like pushed the hi I killed
someone Nissa I don't know if I can live
with
myself I don't know if I can live with
this in my brain it's not
okay I didn't know how to use this
fake go to my okay okay okay
damn I did it again yo
what
9,999
girl
girl girl thank you oh my
God that's so
crazy thank you
let's go let's go no more chopping no
more
boning we are free to
explore what was I
got oh it equipped it
okay
then okay I will go
uh wait can I put a few more Pals out I
forgot best MMO wife I really want to
play MMOs I think I can probably
convince Nissa to play
blue blue protocol blue wait protocol is
it protocol blue yeah protocol that
sounded so weird to me just now I could
probably convince her to play it with me
probably for sure for
sure okay we need some levels so let's
catch some Pals and
stuff yeah this summer should be the
release of the
English or like international version of
an of a Bandai Namco MMO anime MMO that
I've been waiting for forever for years
like I swear when I say for years it's
really been a long
time oh oh it died I'm too strong
it's really been such a long time
man when was that when I played the like
this was before whole life I played the
the the
clothes beta or
alpha blue protocol
yeah no why do you die so
easily I was going to catch
you
and then I played it in Japanese back
then and I really wonder how it changed
until now hey stay
here why do you also this is way too
strong this thing
narissa gave me too much power why
is it so strong okay I'll just use my
bong stick damn so in just
get
okay maybe one
more oh oh
oh uh come on throw throw a shot thank
you I'm on a rampage too op at level
seven it's nice to be carried one on
it's quite
nice like I'm not really caring she she
just gave me some mats so nothing wrong
with
that nothing wrong with that is this
where this Camp uh is oh oh I should get
that spawn point did she read something
I have one PA for you whoa
okay I'm at the small settlement you
could actually I guess uh teleport to
the small settlement if you want we Tech
Point Tech Point Tech
point oh oh wait I can already get it
did I just level up did I just level up
I didn't
realize I don't know if I want to get
all these like lowlevel Pals items right
now what is this dire how why is there a
choice a reason why you giving this one
to
me is there some meaning behind it is it
because of Twilight
oh so I can ride him lat okay kind of
reminds me of Twilight you
know thank you but then yeah I need to I
need to get to that point in the tech
Tre first right to get um to get to
the the
saddle
Jacob is Jacob the one I don't even
know ah no I know yeah the fox Sparks
harness turns it into a flamethrower I
know but I don't know if I want to get
all of those right now cuz also they're
kind of weren't they kind of expensive
to make in terms of
mats should be level 9 oh wait to
really
uh in the tech tree I don't see it
there but maybe somewhere
else
[Music]
what's this
tomato yeah yeah yeah I'll get
there I'll get there eventually just got
a level oh Fuki
FG nice
find E I need to catch it myself to
unlock it oh for real okay if I find if
I see a a weak
one I'll
try where am I there's no no Palace over
here oh wait I think I know this
area oh yeah yeah there's a one over
there that I wasn't able to reach
before I don't know if I can reach it
[Music]
now I'll keep that one for another time
also why why am I down here
now reincarnated guy level 50 is it the
one I
killed is what's this
person isai isai
man who are
you what did you oh God my step oh God
am I going to die am I going to
die please please please
please
okay who are
you this kind like a police
hat don't look at me like that you're
trying to say I've done something wrong
I'm not an officer anymore I'm not even
supposed to be here and he only died
after getting hit by a truck while on
the job when I came to I was on this
island
when I was sure I was dead I prayed for
a slice of pizza now I can make pizza
appear in my hand whenever I want pretty
amazing skill yeah here take a
slice it's like thank you it's like the
equivalent of in Sims 4 the grilled
cheese
sandwich uh skill after you reach oh I
can see your legs
skin can I get
more I've already had
enough I don't know if you guys know but
like yeah like you know how there's
aspirations in Sims and there's a
grilled cheese sandwich aspiration and
once you fulfill that
completely you'll get a skill where you
can immediately spawn grilled
cheese at any grilled cheese sandwich at
any point of time whenever you
want it's pretty
amazing Sims really love grilled cheese
oh I am hungry now let's eat the
pizza yummy
I wonder if he would give me pizza again
if it's not in my
inventory H nice guy just giving out
free
pizza using his newly acquired skill for
the greater good any Effigies
here catch him no why would I catch him
what what does that even
do it's like not like he can do anything
right
yeah they only want to do grilled cheese
sandwich related things in
life
understandable he can give Pizza you
think he'll still give me pizza after I
caught him and imprisoned
him I should be near shieldy space oo
okay I'm think I want to go
up
um
you sure
you
oh what the
uh I'm guessing he sells
things what the is that
face he's
scary don't hit him yeah no worries I
won't Black Market I trade in any kind
of P whether it's stolen PS or even
prohibited types take a
look oh
my oh
my this one's
pretty oh damn son goodbye WIA thank you
so much go have some
Brey go eat some pancakes or something
I will not try to attack him you guys
literally warned me and I think that is
the serious
warning I wonder if he's always
there oh I haven't even crafted a single
pal sphere on my own I should probably
do that
for that tutorial can I get rid of that
tutorial though cuz I actually don't
need it oh I see a
chest they stay put
uhhuh but he have many places oh really
he's always there unless someone kills
him okay
cool y bread get that bread and a copper
key and some golden coins let's
go ah I kind of had a feeling that there
would be one there
I
legit where am
huh I don't think I've explored oh F FG
but I don't want to go there I don't
think I've explored this area
before I mean in my solo play for when I
say something like that it's a reference
to my solo I did only one stream but I
ended up playing for like a whole
another day in my break offline without
streaming and I would say I I know I got
pretty
far
exploring doing a tutorial gives exp you
think so
oh Syndicate
funs now is a good time to use
my
weapon let's
go
where are
we oh those I love riding the m
pckers i could try catching
one wa is this actually someone's base
or is just
naturally I think it's a yeah it's the
fog fog
base the
base wait I got the H the level 10 one
would have been
smarter ah ah
ah
ah oh
no oh no there's no chance I'm getting
the level 13 one but uh
Y how much
7% a oh ah come on try try 16% yummy
please please please please please
please please please
please
yay I got it oh Anda survived against
the level 13 mob good job
gy
gummy yeah oopsie now I can afford
throwing all these pal spheres cuz at
least I don't have so
little oh egg interesting looking
egg is that like an earth egg or what
was
that Rocky egg almost
[Music]
almost oh no what are those screams
should I help oh I should help help I
should totally
help let's
go I'm so
overpowered oh they're dropping some
nice things let's
go yeah already cleared I think Co ammo
gold coin course ammo assault rifle ammo
Mega speed oh wait isn't this the same
thing is what Rissa gave
me oh no I could have caught it oh oh
there's another one what the were
they from them I didn't kill them
least not I didn't even witness them I
didn't even see
them okay releasing the pal but I get it
right I get it for myself I
[Music]
think oh
cute I got a Sanic a little Sanic of my
own got to go
fast oh really random F but one question
question uh you guys know uh the new
like remake or so of Donkey Kong and
Mario Mario and Donkey
Kong is that online co-op at
all fl's playing it today
oh yeah I know it's a possible game I
watched some play through like partially
some not play for but like play uh thing
yeah I don't think so that's probably
just couch Co up
huh is it is it somebody find that out
for me for sure
please let me know serus has always been
single but I I know it's um Co-op now it
has Co-op now that I
know yeah of course don't
tandle let me check
okay um couch go up
only
man
oh Treasure
[Music]
Chest open wow free P spear let's go the
game is lots of fun I loved it back in
the day yeah it seems to be a very
nostalgic game
huh a second player can join the fun as
to in the same system in a two play yeah
okay mhm too bad um I'm in Europe all
alone and no one can play with
[Music]
me cuz I was thinking maybe I could play
it with like kobal for example or
gobba like I'm going to Japan so I could
play it in Japan but it would be I guess
kind of a onetime
thing this one needs a key right
but I have a key now now I
do see I like just running around and
picking up things it's the RPG player in
me one time makes it more
special I wonder maybe with like three
streams if you could finish the game
because yeah maybe maybe in the future
like maybe we could even squeeze in like
two streams you know
maybe
but Ollie is here Ollie wait Ollie wait
let's go thank you oh
we oh we
oh oh we and her Z raid what's up what's
up how you doing you guys were playing
lethal company until now cuz I saw I saw
it ooh that fugy is nicely
place where am I
damn
damn oh still doing some assignments
what school G
oh pal free pal
Alliance what's going on over here do I
need to
help thank God I have so many arrows who
am I supposed to attack the free Palin
are they
also no
right are they going to attack
[Music]
me who was that what hey weren't you
fighing the
fogs what KY raid as well it's
like they're all raiding
me thank you oh my god thank you
everybody y y y y i i just start started
on the Ian server all right you want you
want death I'll give
you oh they also have they also have the
same weapon come on y who he's
zooming what the is
that oh interesting interesting
pal two raids what a deal damn two raids
probably like from the same collab
right
amazing
ah aim do okay okay I did it I did it I
did it kumas we did it we
survived okay can we take this uh 14
16 maybe another
time yeah I should go
back I guess I lived yay oh gifts 20
gifts thank
you they walk so funny
oh I don't know if Al is watching at all
but I I saw uh that was so cool I saw
Kobo and
Ollie like sponsorship collaboration
with Indo
Mia Loop
moon or is that a there we go that's a
that's a that's a checkpoint thingy
right anyway that's so cool that's so
cool I'm so happy for them cuz Indo me
is like a big in Indonesia right I mean
even they see they sell it all over the
world
so big congrats that's so exciting their
faces are on the
packages oh nice we can come back now
now that we have a a
checkpoint I saw W wo wo hi I saw a
video of um nice nice nice of like in
Indonesia
H what's going on here in
Indonesia like food stalls and there was
like an uh
India specific food
stall and they showed how indom is being
prepared for like street
food and they were making like a
huge I just sleep
it'll be fine I'll sleep it off I'll
just sleep it
off she got scammed what who got scammed
I'm still
burning uh what was I
saying hardcore this is fine I was
saying yeah they were preparing like in
one big pot they were preparing India
for like that what do you mean that is
fake how is it
fake for like for 30 people 50 50 people
or so in one go what do you mean it's
edited the packages saw are fake they
don't oh oh those are fake no they
should be
real make it
real wait
so but but they did get like a
sponsorship or so
[Laughter]
right that's real
right that's a thing right
okay let's make it real it looks so
good okay so but the street food is
real yeah and that was really yummy
looking damn like they added a couple
things they added so many eggs they
added like 20
eggs and some mysterious
sauce like I don't know how I feel about
like if I
where I don't know anywhere in the world
and I'm I'm going to go get street food
I don't think I would go for something
that is like instant food that you can
make at home but the way they made it it
looks like they really made it better
than you would make it at
home it looked yummy but also it looked
spicy it looked very spicy indeed okay
let's make the stone pit The Crusher and
the log inside I think uh the crusher I
still need the the recipe
though where where where where should we
maybe Stone pit here there's some Stones
anyway I know it doesn't matter but it
fits
mhm should I make
two maybe maybe not for now maybe in the
future we'll need we'll feel like we
need a second one and I'll make this
over here at the end really far I know I
know oh so many stones to pick
up
[Music]
oh one is enough right I think so two
I don't like how it's in the ground
partially but it will still work
right I
assume okay yeah uh
just I'll make two
even it look fine right yeah just
aesthetic you all you say you want to
sleep ah it's only did only read
something I didn't see anything I don't
think she did but that's so nice wow ID
raids let's go so sweet I love them so
much they're the sweetest people
ever
ever Ollie has written what I literally
don't see them I even scrolled
up Ollie I love you I love
[Music]
you I love you too you were the first
one that came to visit them in ID that
is
true that is
true I want to go again all right we
have to
like disgust now that I'm back for my
break like nobody continued the the talk
so I should probably be like hey let's
talk about our trip hey
yo
now that there's a stone Farm they they
probably are going to automatically go
to the stone Farm instead of these
random rocks are they or should I put a
something there too what is you depresso
depresso just like
me yeah Bali the Bali trip we need to
talk about
that cuz like the the desired time frame
that we have in mind it's getting closer
oh dear there's uh
fogs am I going to one hit you with my
I have a feeling it's a yes no I didn't
nice oh Nightwing you're being attacked
I
see let me help
you and then I'll catch
you well I barely doing any damage
wouldn't it be nice if you save a a pee
from fogs like this is that they would
like just offer themselves to
you out of uh yeah being thankful but
you know what I'm actually going to get
you I can actually head shot them
damn ow
um help me but don't do too much damage
don't kill
it don't kill
it why can't he teleport show
I'mma saved her rare Sanic from dire
Halls
oh isn't that like what I did too there
were dire house and it was a a
Sanic new H Joe it's another
hon yay
wait I should maybe mine this cuz I
don't have these materials do
I
or yeah I know I can mount that bird I
know I know I'll get the saddle for
sure also I'm going to be full
soon
yeah it's uh not solo server it's uh
yeah Ian
server oh are they hungry are you
hungry are you hungry only have these
raw mushrooms sorry and some raw meat
but I don't want to give that to you you
can oh wait I have pancakes for
Godot yummy
yeah it's my first time on the Ian
server it it has been existing for a
while now and the others already have
pretty big
bases let's return over there pretty big
bases and high levels and all that and
many Pals and I
got not much but narissa gave me some
stuff must be a regional issue yeah
probably like cuz I think the server is
like located in Na and I'm in Europe so
I may be
experiencing lag and stuff oh my God are
you okay you shaking are you
cold what what am I
doing got to go to the
chest oh YouTube is lagging too Oh I
thought you were talking about
uh something else uh all right and let's
put this and this and this
and
these and some egg and egg and
these and
these and get the fried eggs yummy I can
make some
more and Jimmy how's that going with the
100 eggs per day
huh doesn't look like a 100 to me
H kind of
slacking yeah to M to there's so much to
do
always can we place the bed nicely
please a man
why
why why
why I know it says too too close but
this one could be there maybe it's the
statue that's going to look stupid but
okay I'll place it
here only one
here and
then get rid of this and then little and
I won't build it around it I'll build it
like behind it so like
this
okay yay beds woohoo so we need a
crasher but I don't think I have
the
thing ah what does the crusher uh
breaking
down break it
down palum frag
ooh palum
fragment and did those come from normal
Stones oh there's some over here yeah it
looks like
it got one palum
fragment the better bat
well did they put something in here yet
or nobody's working on
this ah
I thought kativa was going to maybe do
some Stone bonking where what's kativa
doing oh ah she's working on other
Stones
okay okay and now you're tired all right
I I'll bunk this one too myself cuz I
need more pum
fragments ah I'll throw them but I mean
they can go for the stone too it's fine
the presso should work on it oh yeah
right the presso is now one of us one of
us one of us one of
us they yearn for the
mines and reduced raes is that a
reference to
something
what am what was I what did I ah and a
Crusher
Crush
Crush Crush Crush Crush nothing compared
to a quiet evening alone just go on
to how about
[Music]
here again let be
morees
uh near water and boss
caves but they're also in the
stones oh wait ah you mean those those
are going to drop more huh damn I forgot
so much about this game but I only
played like two days
literally
W uhhuh so it was a
reference y'all this is taking so long
are you guys helping at
all I don't believe
it
okay are you going to give me yes
yes yes palum fragments so these are
more common by the water
huh
nice very
good YouTube please YouTube why Why
YouTube why why would
you keep these people away from my
stream huh let them watch what they want
to
watch you're tarting anus server what
are you talking about I'm anus
t no no no a is because of uh arrest of
development it's a reference to rest of
development okay thank you for 20
memberships let's go water a
Chad water a
Chad I'm just going to get all of
these and then we'll have a good
amount nice
gifts it's Christmas all over
again chicken playing oh having fun
they're attacking the cat
pretty the M pacas don't really seem to
care wait I shall rescue I'm a
hero
oh wait let's give him a head
shot
yeah
yeah boom head
shot who's so many people fighting why
you attacking me I'm one of the good
people I'm one of the good
people
no they're both dead are they they're
dead
no at least I Avenged
them
no no those big fluffy
boys I was just here to help them and I
failed them wait isn't this where
the yeah this is no not
exactly I thought this was close to
where chill
was I have unused headphones
[Music]
yeah trying to play along with the
reference in a way that YouTube would
allow wait can you not Rite anus in
one
go is that not
allowed YouTube
please so
uncultured anus start oh you can Aus
start
everybody sometimes just wants anus
start me too me
too okay I think I'm going to walk back
just going to get these mats on the
way why does YouTu buffer every time I
say a a start oh wait don't shoot it
don't shoot the
stone that's not very
efficient my favorite Bo I
saw God I'm so I such a lost cause is
there something down
there
no such a lost
cause chicken
playing having fun spks tast to see
Season of Love and
Understanding Merry
Christmas
everyone okay let's get the spark
where'd he
go
huh water Sparks in the water
no it's swiming can you
see what the
stop stop spark
it it's got the zomies it's so far it's
certainly
teleported holy wait where are you
going I feel like if I
shoot I will die
Li monk wait I don't have a LIF monk yet
where where the Sparks
go
ah I caught
up I feel like it's leading me to a
trap where's wait I don't have a Pokmon
out don't don't stop don't stop just go
your own way don't kill
it you little
you
little damn it okay but I'm going to get
the LIF
monk I will get the LIF monk maybe
oh penet shouldn't be too strong right I
mean level eight yeah
but wait did I say something did I say
that
word did I say it
hey you keep on running even though
I already hit
you
hey I thought that's not how it
works no that the V isn't got to
disappear but like I already said it so
many times cu Dam it it still
runs you're trapped you're
trapped come
on no I need the spear I need the
freaking
spear 20% please I don't want to keep on
running out after this
thing hey hey hey he hey hey
heyyyyy
hey no no no no no no no no no yes yes
back bonus let's go we got
[Music]
it I I I totally said pal wait I didn't
even catch myself this time I didn't
even
realize
[Music]
okay don't run I just want the EXP from
Catching
you yo oh freak my
stamina okay good 80%
easy I think the lag is over
oh I should get one of the deers level
10 is doable even with
my
weapon
Y strong strong
[Music]
oh okay I can't lose track of
the HP
nice that's kind of like cheating
man come on another one another
one maybe another one one more hit I
think yeah that's as much as I can do
cheese I've Got The High
Ground I think pangala died but that's
okay um here I never saw you before
actually come out a cute it looks like
chunkers
o oh it's an ice
pee give me the second one give me the
second
one I would love to have a second one
didn't it already
drop
something this happens sometimes right
yeah yeah yeah they die in a moment you
catch them and you get the
loot an
the no I got it I got it I caught it in
time that's what you call
skill that's what you call
skill so cute okay I'm going
home I'm going
home wait did did the me come from the S
no way right that was from the the V
mate you're
cute what are you
doing he's so cute I like it good
morning hello oh my God are we still is
everybody getting that buffer
or
damn doesn't look like
everybody
does your original Phoenix f look like
hoo from
[Music]
Pokemon
no no it would look more like a real
Phoenix I wish I could show
you but the belt is stopping
me who Papa already show no that's not
no
M don't get it
twisted hot spring primitive furnace
Berry Plantation oh another
one hot spring perent furnace okay so
let's do some stuff we have threee
[Music]
points and 16 Tech points
hotring what was the other
thing some furnace
right oh this one o I need another
level need another
level get the saddle the
that yeah would be too powerful we've
seen the for in Hol intros right uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah
exactly uh wait uh wait what am I doing
uh
here who is useful you guys told me to
bring out
thepro but LIF monk does so much stuff
too let's go LIF
monk why is it why is it lagging so
bad why it always lagging so
bad oh yeah the deer is very good for
chopping trees or like wood
yeah I need more pal
slots just momentary legs don't worry
about it still watchable okay you two
please get your
together I beg you
[Music]
by the way I did get like for the switch
and finally got the Dave the diver perms
but I don't think we can play this
week next week I think we can make it
work no I always have to have one even
if it's just one
one chicken in the base it's just how it
is but I will not take the chicken to
war with me because I'm trying to keep
you safe you
know it's it's love I do it for love I
do it out of
love
let me
[Music]
make maybe some
more chests for inside
storing train the chicken you can give
it God skill and defeat the last boss
what yeah you guys are meant to fight
for me that is true
but I'm late sorry bu no worries welcome
to the
stream apparently you're strong late
game a yo for real that's like such a
joke move from the
developers make the freaking chicken
powerful in end
game I I I guess you guys are you know
you're just prepping for the end game
now
I can combine all of you into one big
super kfp chicken hey
[Music]
y brine do you actually come out like
much
bigger that would be
sick you use chickp in your main
team that's kind of rely
funny okay I'll make another chest
can I put it
here
yes let's go no I want to build
it they're coming team work teamw work
teamw work
amazing okay how about we
make just equipment chest this is all
equip equipment I
guess
equipment here some ammo cuz I can't use
it
yet well and here's some leather I
guess the old bat schematic do I even
need this because don't I already have a
recipe for that like
unlocked oh well hello there nice to see
you again I'm really really sorry for
the incident
previously uh maybe I'll buy something
off of you as sorry this
actually does not heal
health so stupid why nothing heals you
it's kind of
crazy capture him catch it don't call it
it okay let's not shoot cuz
he's doesn't work and he just doesn't
care and just walks
away with my Bon stick I'm probably just
going to kill
him
uh-oh don't you shoot don't shoot at my
chy
wonky uhoh see how that
escalates see how it just immediately
escalates it's never going to happen
it's never going to happen guys oh I
need
food yeah
yum
yummy okay what was I supposed to make
next um primitive furnace which I'm too
low level for I think and a hotring and
another bear Plantation okay okay but
from building stuff I also get exp
right y y y on another pal bed I guess
yeah and then for relaxation we need the
the hot
spring perfectly placed here I'll
help cute he's doing his best
thanks
guys so cute more
berries Beres
Cobo Beres Cobo C
co hot TOS sping P fluids damn it how do
I get the P
fluids but is the only way to kill
Pals is that the only way
kill Penguins oh water PS specifically
uh nah Hy I'm going to put this here
otherwise somebody is going
to break
down there you go no farming method
sadly damn okay there's nothing here
here in my water
still
oh let's
see water
Pals where there water Pals over there
at
all y YouTube stop lagging let's go you
can catch them and get bonus for 10 PS
of the same gun yeah I know I know the
dire
wolves the D wolves what level 10 10 10
o okay let's see how much damage I
do oh that's pretty good I mean like I
don't want to do too much damage
anyway yep how did I how did you
resist you were on like one HP and you
had a dream I
guess all you got to do is have have a
[Music]
dream
no sweet do something do something
sweet oh nice oh my God always at one
HP
sweet you're not really a good fighter
are
you oh that was too
early that was too
early oh wait you're up
[Music]
Hey get in here now get in
here you too all
[Music]
right if you decide to go outside it
might be your
death y y I got free dire wolves
house and there's a lost pen
gullet give me your fluids your bodily
fluids I got
them very convenient
nice
uh what that's literally what I'm
getting from him I'm just saying it how
it is it's just how it
is if I catch it I got it too
okay
okay nope nope no water
PS I want to get chillet chillet is up
here right but chillet uh is chillet
considered a water
cow
chill
I love you chill's eyes huh oh well
going to get uh chill it anyway cuz I
love chill
it hi
cats okay now you see me so it's even
lower come out come out again so let me
hit you then
[Music]
yeah I want to become a cat
lady and you will not be able to stop me
from my
Endeavors no matter how aggressive you
are no matter how many nickel puns
you're going to give
me so many
cats I already I don't know if I can
consider myself a cat lady with just two
cats I don't think I don't know if I'm
worthy what are these chickens doing
inside of each other huh okay ifp tell
me actually no never mind that's cute
they're not inside of each
other you guys are so cute no it's okay
I'll take your friend home at
least don't run don't run don't run it's
not like I want you I don't even want
you that much okay you know it's
annoying when they run like that then I
just got to kill
him I mean
look you little he's just bouncing
around happily while I'm
suffering okay you know you're so close
I can try to catch
you there's a lot of squeeze and the
sweeper
oh come in here look at the
squeeze it's taunting me totally
there we go might need to make a weeko
yeah for real hey yo what's that thing
again it's like these notes right the
lore what's happening here let's save
someone oh sorry actually
uh okay now of course the pals will
attack attack me though right even
though I'm the good one
here oh no they're not ah you got a LIF
monk here
okay deepest
lore hey
wait
to that's too low hey yo that one worked
out I'm surprised this one too oh my God
okay
wow
wow oh more Pals uh more more chickens
more
chickens you're so cute I love you so
much this is
Carl and this is um
Frank O Carl what's wrong don't you
recognize me hey Carl
Carl
Carl stop
Carl hey
yo Carl you must
die
car very fitting of his name his
behavior is
Unforgivable
Carl Carl why why
Carl why must you be like Dad oh
hi no oh you already
damaged oh is
this is this the first boss
Tower not that I want to go inside right
now I don't feel
ready I need to make more path fers
already I went for like half of
[Music]
them five captured yeah that's the first
one huh I did uh privately off screen
after the first stream uh take down the
boss it
was difficult
actually it's quite
[Music]
difficult or harvest new res Ranch but
pal FS can I actually Harvest them
[Music]
though what level did you end
at I can check
later um I'm not sure it's been too
long
100% oh hey what how did I get back home
what that's
fascinating I am I am my survival
Instinct holy moly
how did I make my way back home I was
just running around randomly I'm
fascinated okay while I'm here let's get
some ore or you keep turning
left well I'm left-handed and I like you
know I like the left side I like to go
left it's my instinct I
suppose survival Jew streamer
luck ow praise me praise me
more for finding my way back without
even
trying oh not bottom left represent
fellow Lefty let's go where my fellow
lefties at let's
go there's a nice song old
song which sings about left-handed boy
I sang it in a old Koka
before left me
[Music]
wow
it's themo it's
themo woo
wo nice good
song
uh kativa where you at where are you a
okay I forgive you I forgive
you look at the green
boys getting some green nice you need
help I'll pick this up for you I'm so
nice
okay I got some power fluts only 11
damn not the most
efficient okay hot spring maybe let's
put it where the beds
are
yeah so they have quick access to
relaxation
press R to shift everything in your
inventory to the box that is the
same
oh interesting oh my
God oh my God
Lambo how do you say left-handed in
Japanese hi left Kiki k i k i and then
right-handed is migy Kiki he Kiki migy
Kiki he's vibing
I don't know if I would call it vibing
but he was um feeling
something did we do it all uh the
Primitive furnace did I get a level up I
did I did I did I did I
[Music]
did
no ah ah there it
is there is that recipe I guess we can
get it even though I also got the I just
got the mpaka saddle that's why I don't
really feel like I need to get like all
of these special items because like
these are like
equal R pal R pal and then there's even
more
so I don't know if I want to get all of
them
hung
uh don't worry W I got you with the
pancakes
okay uh primitive furnace where should
we put
it where should we put it U maybe also
just I wait what do you do with the
Primitive furnace
again what kind of stuff do you do do I
use it a lot am I going to use it a
lot Ingot ah uh okay so it doesn't
really need to be like super
accessible
right fire Palace will use
it
[Music]
ah
oopsy
oh that's so
wholesome seeing the pals especially the
big ones chilling in
the in the freaking path so
wholesome I think here fits quite
nicely especially if I put something
else on the other side
too then we got
some
uh what's the word when when something's
the same on both
sides
oh could already make some more H some
ingots if I wanted to but I don't think
I have an immediate need for it symmetry
yes
yes hi by the way uh I can already
enhance capture
power and and the pals I don't know if I
want to enhance these in
particular let's
go damn I like the light that's coming
out of my
[Music]
home more beds okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
K they're fine they don't all need to
sleep at the same time but okay I'll
make them I might come some beds straw
beds o
o
nice oh I ran out of
[Music]
fiber
la
fiber I wonder if uh there's any
oh any fiber lying
around uh what what am I doing
[Music]
see oh convert the crusher H okay I'm
still going to check what I I can pick
up what is
that milk oh
yeah why is this one crying and why is
it flying I don't think they're supposed
to be like flying right are they
stuck oh I think they're
stuck yeah
I can't help
them they're going to be stuck until
Iris logs
in yeah I've had that happen quite a few
times with my first
base in my first power world
stream they would get stuck on the roof
of my
house knock
knock who's there your wife for life oh
wo oh my God so many P
speres it
m
[Music]
yeah
nice what this ore nice I'll take it
I'll take it any got any fiber going
here any fiber lying around I guess
not I think it's fine if you don't got
any I got some other cool
stuff yeah Vixie is
crazy
ooh damn this looks really
nice what on the second floor
oh nicely
organized good
inspiration ah considering that later
you can get stone
walls maybe I didn't need to make my
house
like two oh those are nice pal
beds the one's over there in the
corner uh a
fer I'll I'll rebuild my whole home I
guess
eventually M for better sanity of course
of course once I can make that I'll make
it for you guys too is this a better
Farm oh no maybe it's like a self egg
breeder okay I've seen
enough I've seen
enough no fiber for me but that's okay
got some
bowls I sure got some bosss to walk in
here and just like take whatever is in
front of
me yeah yeah one
fiber I got one
fiber and a lot of
balls I've got some
balls
eggs I
take
is this problematic am I being
problematic guys tell me if I'm being
problematic can I teleport with this one
no oh but with
this no not in the
slightest yeah that's yeah that stuff is
going to despawn and and when I pick it
up by the time IIs would ever log in
again there will be like the same amount
lying there anyway
so
yeah I'm being
silly I'm just uh helping the economy
what uh what did I do I need to I guess
I need to check the trees for some
Fiber
nice okay I'll chop this tree
give me some
Fiber oh I got fiber oh I got fiber oh I
got fiber oh I got fiber oh I got
fiber oh I got
fiber I got a lot of fiber you just
checked Twitter I got canceled oh my God
like I legit would actually believe
you I wouldn't even be
surprised that's a terrifying
thing yeah high fiber diet what's a high
fiber diet what do you
eat
cery although celery in like m in some
dishes I think it's
okay fruit oh fruit okay I'm I'm up for
that I do
D dity Diggity
dity dity Family Guy brain rot
digity freaking Diggity she
says
oopsie a giggity not
SK I have to say though I never actually
heard beu say
skibidi I know like I I guess kind of
like she she started it but
um I only picked it up cuz I saw it in
the
chat and I thought it's a cute
word I have it's
strange oh oh no oh okay that's that's
fine if it's just that uh wait oh my God
uh
usual okay what are we doing what are we
doing what are we going to do what's the
next
step a high quality workbench a medieval
medicine workbench and deploy a work pal
to the base 7 out of eight 7 out of
eight easy
um the
presso yeah why
not medieval medicine workbench high
quality workbench I don't think I have
the recipe right
now I need another level high quality
workbench and ah these two I need two
levels I'm behind on the levels I'm too
fast with the
tech
and Leal head should I do I have
something on my head no I could make
that the Press so really
sad um
let's do this and oh ah free shot bow is
nice if I didn't already have
the the thing that I'm using now besides
that I don't know about the rest I mean
eventually I might need a repair bench
right free shot you think it's
better pick up nails but build building
various facilities
okay but I guess we got to go explore
and catch more you know what I need to
make some ah yeah what the was that
need to build some
spheres well first let's build
this okay well I did use the free shot
bow a lot on my private time need a
mount too yeah yeah yeah yeah
I made the
melpa or did I not make it yet I just
got the recipe and I didn't make
it okay it's
on I was going to get the pum fragments
right and this one needs more fiber M
well since
um
since the sweet sweet waa gave it to me
I'll I'll get the I'll use the the the
the the where the
trees I I will use
the wolf even though you know I love
alpacas and I
collect
like not figurines like plushies
dolls yeah that's like the one thing I
still kind of collect and like the only
kind of like so to say
plushy that I still tolerate in my
living
space cuz I threw out all pretty much
almost all of my other
plushies I have H somebody I don't
actually know when I get gift like these
I eventually like kind of forget like
who made this but I still have it so
forgive me but like somebody made like
chunky wonky and um smoothie plushies
handmade um not like with like fur all
over it uh just normal fabric but
they're really cute that was me that's
you I have them uh like chilling under
my
TV those are cute yeah those are really
cute wait did I get some Fiber from that
at all fiber fiber 14 I think I need a
bit more let me get some let me actually
wait you guys said I can probably what
for the crusher get
uh also some
[Music]
fiber yeah okay good good good good good
wait I I have
9,800 wood
still damn yeah let's just get like 23
for now oh my God wait can I help do do
we need a water pal I
think thank you wiissa
thank you so so much over
9,000 yeah what H this there uh you want
to oh anybody you wait you no no
no I need
you
cute oh oh not a ranch no no no no no no
no no no no no no
no misunderstanding
[Music]
corner now it say no work available in
immediate visit
bugged this pal needs high level
level no water
what
[Music]
um does it need to be a water two water
not one but two like this one's
one I don't think I have a water that's
two I feel like that's not necessary is
it it it is is
that then I can't make it now what what
about you one
noack has water
one what's a palet has water
too that I can maybe go look for chillet
maybe no chill at this icing
right
damn panking ah yeah
paning panking isn't
panking like
like on the map usually maybe not
pinking oh bu I I I know like pinking
isn't he like here I saw I remember
getting him in my private playr it's a
bus right top left of me a here
is Northwest on side okay like here okay
okay let's get a little little little
short
wait I
need am I happy with my pal
team I could wait can I make the saddle
now okay at least I can make the saddle
and then we can bring the dire
how
mm
[Music]
are you going to name Pals after members
maybe I
will maybe I
won't maybe I
will oh my God this one's taking a lot
of
[Music]
time what they look like they look alike
they look like just color variations of
each
other they belong to me
right look at all those
stones okay uh
Aire wait I want to make some
spars make
them
and let me pick this up you belong to me
no
whoa oh that one is also
gone need balls we need more Spanish wa
oh Spanish Vita
he I got you I got
you
okay
s me I got so many names in
spanish
okay
um level 20 should I get the I can't if
I take the level 22 one with me now he's
going to one hit everything although it
might be useful against the
panking and like just for writing
generally let's just use him for writing
I don't know how strong level 10 how
strong is
the oh did he ah he syned his level okay
never mind never mind forget everything
that I just
said uh okay did it like do I have to
put it on him I forgot
uh wait uh I don't think I have to put
it on him
right wait how to what
there it
is come
on
OHA let's
go Northwest we shall March
uh actually let me drop some
food k
I like c Flower I like the idea of
that ah you guys can have some
egg and uh oh yeah the more
egg actually those eggs we should we
should Grill them they can't go can they
no okay not on the furnace okay no
furnace
eggs
maybe not Max cuz maybe you need eggs
for other dishes too is that a
thing maybe just like this
amount but I know I guess I have no one
out who can do this right
now perhaps I
understand it is what it
is I need it for cake
eventually
oh
that sounds
amazing we can also go into one of these
caves but I want to go get the
pinking I need the pinking for
productivity
uh once I get closer it shows it on the
map right once I see the
area uh how to get
there chillet Toco I should get the
chillet too I really like chillet
level 11 it's not a good level maybe
I'll get it
now
oopsie it's up there is
it huh is it
here no wait
huh
mountain
wolf is that chill up there am I going
the right way and there's like a bridge
here
right the jumps are so funny to me yo
what's this what's this
circle oh who's base is
this you who built a base here I'm I
don't even want to pick up things right
now cuz like I don't want my inventory
to be
filled that's Iris no that's not Iris
Iris had her base somewhere else unless
she has two
bases oh Iris she has a second base for
ore farming ah yeah okay yeah this place
has a lot of ore like what by Nature
just naturally so much ore ah no
no
the the bridge was right
there
no I can I can fix
this at least I didn't take damage I
thought I would take damage there is
fall damage right generally I think I
remember there was fall
damage maybe the lag
not one
mounted
okay
okay I took that already
okay okay second try oh God this turning
nights though oh I don't like it ah I
should go back it's so close so I'll go
back I'll go
back
eat
okay me and uh nissa's favorite Insider
our
Insider I think narissa loves to do it
because I always laugh at it when she
does
it I always make her say okay with a
cute smile can I jump through the
window no
okay okay and she does it so well
narissa does it so well a
F
okay I love hearing her say that
K everybody the
ceremony the Kik
ceremony thank you thank you say
Kiki you're a chicken you have to say it
it's in your
blood
thank you nice good job good job guys
you are a proper
chicken K this time we reach the top of
the
mountain I would hope so come
on oh stamina
no come
on come
on you can do
it you can do it yeah I believe in
you good wolf who's a good boy always a
good boy yeah you a good
boy a good
boy ah there it is not again I will will
not fall down again
oh that chillet doesn't know what's
coming hi tet
oh get off let's
go
oh what's that
sound what's that
sound
shiny
what's that sound is this the shiny are
you the shiny you don't look
shiny shiny nearby
right wa don't get
it
sh I need to learn to like take back my
pal oh yeah first boss kill okay shiny I
hear the shiny so apparently in my very
first pal World stream I missed a shiny
like I didn't realize it was a
shiny oh
oh but that's okay cuz like it was going
to you know not continue
anyway
oh H down here or
what you think it's that that one no
right
oh oh it's pretty strong here I think
it's down
there is it
that it's a shiny
monkey wait there's two that ones
they're shiny though don't kill
it y yeah yay but the shinies aren't
better right they're just bigger but
they're not better right
yay
lucky they are better let's
go how they have skills they have lucky
yeah I saw that does have a lucky
stat hello uh little L Monk Is there is
there a LOF monk Effigy somewhere here
that you would like to tell me about no
I'm sure you're hiding
one somewhere around here secretly but I
want to go back up to where the chillet
was because I feel like there was a
chest that I didn't pick up
right I'm close to Good's base
[Music]
oh it's in his
bucket we have to steal
it I want all the LIF monk figs
please
that's kind of
sus but nothing here uh what the hell is
that is that so shiny what's that tree
what is that
tree and there's an
effigy hey y I never saw this kind of
tree before how did I miss this tree in
my previous first
playthrough yo oh can I chop the
tree fancy fancy tree skill
tree skill tree speaking of
skills what do you
recommend they have fruits
no more
weight okay
ah I thought you could eat them bubble
blast and ignis blast and stone blast uh
and then can I chop you or
what oh I guess nothing comes
out
okay oh Nissa
Bas oh I'm looking at Nissa base from
the top
up
oh everything's
connected okay chill it was
here pretty uh quickly I just want to go
back and check there was a chest I
think Mark Tree on map
[Music]
M maybe
bread
yeah you think I I want more of that
later
on heuse
[Music]
Wolf wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
wow wow
wow ah there it
is I don't know why I didn't take it
right away I was like I got to go
there're shiny they're shiny they're
shiny can't miss out on the
shiny shiny things take priority all
right next
paning somewhere around
there so
[Music]
give me give me the Big Penguin of my
dreams go west
mhm tant produced 40 wait tant's Doing
It tant produced 46
fiber he's doing
it wait I think he just I don't know he
was just like messing around
and I I also thought yeah it's kind of
weird if you need like level two when
the thing itself is pretty a pretty low
level item to produce or like equip not
equ Machinery to produce he's doing it
y guard what are you
guarding what are you guarding don't
shoot me
please level two just makes it faster
yeah but I thought cuz it just wasn't
doing anything I thought we really
needed
it thought it was a
necessity turns out that was not
true I guess we can try anyway there
there he is level 15
[Music]
pinking how to get up
there is
there does is there an elevation here
does it go higher
yeah yeah all right got to got to
Dismount
oh Lord that I will never read let's go
let's go let's
go so rainy's diary I only care about
Way's diary excuse me
yep yep yep
yep yep yep yep oh wait there was a path
here okay I'll take
it zo story is pretty good
well I only care about her looks she's
cute though
really cute extremely
cute sealed real real Realm of the
Frozen W so why is this
oh I think in my private playr I just
had a random panking from somewhere else
but this one isn't a
dungeon why is this one not just outside
like the
chillet I hope it's not too difficult
this looks like Elden ring
ah
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
easy
[Laughter]
ah ah ah ah Kos do
something oh he defeated he defeated
him y y oh God oh
God
take the small ones
down little she's sniping from up
there he's got The High
Ground
OMG
no
damn uh what the wait why can I not
did I not activate
the or can you ah can you only go back
to your base in this case the base in
this case base in this case base in this
case first
respawn okay I'll go like
this TP teleport ah oh
oh I'm what what what what went wrong I
maybe should bring different
Pals do I have any pal that would be
good against pinking it's water so
anything that's grassy
right I know I'll get my pals back when
I'm there but what if I bring uh like a
LIF
monk yeah I forgot about Dodge
rolling level up yeah but now all my
stuff is there I have to pick it up not
grass only electric oh I don't have
Sparks that little
didn't want to be with
me damn
it it's outside oh okay
but now that we figured that I don't
need pinking
necessarily I don't
mind not getting it right away oh yeah
The Shield I know I want the
shield ow okay
ah do it at night when the smaller ones
are sleeping they sleep inside there at
night
and you can just have them ignore
you
hey for
real give
all take
all TI Hall is
dead guess I should go back once put him
into the base
right but before that I I will take
revenge on you little
and take your fluids while I'm at
it hey what's Stone this this is what I
want I know how to roll I just forgot
like that you should you should do it I
used to do
it
back in the good old
days I want this
FG hey hey
[Music]
hey ah
no
no if this one pretty much took two hits
and I thought this one could have at
least survive
one oh man respawn
please why why why oh nice
chest cloth outfit
schematic anything else
here any other Sparks who want to maybe
join my
team no no there's a pig a rush or in
the rush
hour uh-oh
uh-oh I killed it no oh did I I didn't
all
right
nice I was going to go back to heal d
how but look at me look at me running
around without a single care in the
world I can't help it feathered hair
band okay gold coin
arrows where am
[Music]
I quack quack
shba you don't look like
shba okay let's let's let's teleport
let's
teleport we shouldn't keep the wolf dead
too long it will start
stinking a platypus ah
[Music]
yeah do platypus also make quack quack
sounds like a
duck and
Platypus no well this one kind of does
though maybe it's a mix of a platypus
and a
duck can't hold love back guys it's
natural what did they say it was the
recommended level for uh the boss the
first
boss
was it like 20 or
so
YouTube
YouTube I'm asking them questions 12 to
15 really so
low oh can I first B around level 11 oh
damn oh my God like getting all these
materials from narusa
really like sped everything up so
much like normally this like getting to
this point took me so
long
dude
H maybe worth making one of these
weapons
maybe and I'll make the free shot bow
[Music]
oh
oops perhaps oh I don't have I don't
have fiber what how's this
possible how
how that cannot be I just need to
acquire and I I'll make some
more yeah and now the T Fant was
automatically assigned
so a how you doing AA how was your
day how you
feeling ah let's make the The Shield as
well while we're at it a
duck ah did you see uh I at first didn't
even know where it was coming from
because like I think I saw on Twitter
just like screenshots from those horo
tonies the I guess it was meme M Nissa
and then some impostor
bird and I was like H that's cute I
wonder where that's from some was was
that was that in my own video cuz like
the video the the art style was
recognizable that will take a while
until they're here
right uh the art was definitely
recognizable as like from that
song and then today hey I I watched the
a little bit of the iris version and I
was like
ah literally
ah the gyus
pigeon you guys are slow be
faster oh wait I need to
bring
uh put you in here and then how about we
bring a different one with
us and they're still not here
OHA they may be
stuck no I think they're moving they're
moving
[Applause]
attack head shot oh oh yeah don't do
disturb my pals they have to work so I I
literally one hit
everybody I'm too
[Music]
strong it's okay guys no need for you
guys to lift the finger I am here to
protect
you
damn easy
clap easy clap
mhm tant is taking a break huh how dare
you you didn't even do it he didn't do
it at all where's my oh is he bringing
it actually wait he might be bringing it
is no maybe he didn't I thought he would
actually bring it bring it to a box as
well but I guess he doesn't have the
skill wa which is okay that's
fine build let's build the high quality
workbench cuz I can indeed do
that
ah ingots and Nails
aha
yeah we need kindling we don't have
anything out of kind Ling right kindling
kindling no
then sheep switch with
Fox good Fox good
Fox night time you can spawn FAL there
to the
water yeah okay I will do when we wakey
wakey wakey in the NY M yummy fried eggs
keep
goa's dead goa's also dead
oh I'm
sorry did you guys see on my Twitter
yesterday I okay I was actually looking
up that artist again I was like ah what
was the name again what was the name
again of that artist it's like a Korean
artist who drew that sexy version of
that pal and and so I was like looking
uh cuz I didn't know their Twitter I was
looking on
Instagram and then I finally find it and
then I see on their Instagram there's
like a link tree and then I see the on
the link Tre I see the Twitter so I go
to the
Twitter do it thanks and on the Twitter
I saw that apparently they saw a clip
from some one kfp who thought they knew
who I was talking about with that very
very vague explanation of the artist
yeah the
lavander uh
gijinka and that one kfp who fought they
knew what I was talking about posted a
clip and and uh tagged
the artist I was like I think this is
about this artist and then the artist
sorry cuz the artist seems to be very
very active when looking at uh
replies and I didn't see that however
cuz I don't think I was that
I didn't see that but the artist was
like oh I I think this might be about me
and they seemed kind of happy that I
talked about the artist but I didn't see
it until today or yesterday today it was
kind of today I was like oh my God yes
it's you I didn't know you had a Twitter
oh yeah so now I followed the artist on
Twitter and they followed me
back and now I have the blessing to see
that those like sexy
not only pal world ginkas but like
generally I love how they shade skin how
they Rend their skin it's really really
beautiful and like kind of realistic
too uh I really like it I really like it
[Music]
a it's so
nice yeah you guys should check it
out I'm just looking
just trying to not be brain empty
toate I think I'll put some stuff in a
chest cuz I feel like I'm carrying too
much random stuff waa Is So based for
this this the artist is so good though
the thing is I wanted to um I was like
thinking about artists with like unique
art
styles maybe even something somewhat
realistic looking more realistic looking
than like the
usual kind of typical animu art style
and then I was thinking of this
artist yeah so I was looking for them
because of that reason what should I put
in here I just put like all of this all
of
[Music]
this
egg the
fruit yeah
M the milk I guess also will be used for
the cake sometime
right but that'll take a while until I
get that recipe maybe I'll just make the
warm milk with it I don't know what's
the artist's name one bean Lee I think
if you go to my Twitter and look at the
people I follow he should be the most
recent one that I followed and also in
my replies one of my most recent replies
should be to the artist
so you can probably find it that
way yeah there it is that's ntp just
posted it w is a type I don't know I
like all kinds of art Stars really like
I I just find every art style
fascinating wouldn't say I have a type
but for what I'm looking for right
now um when I want to
commission I don't know no promise that
I'll commission them if they're too
expensive if I I
won't I just want to check the the price
and then we see if I can work with this
artist
yeah some
artists have way higher prices than
others especially when they're I've
noticed when they're kind of like
seemingly in some kind of like artist
agency some artists are in like some
kind of artist agency my the artist that
did my my Al alter kiata outfit also
belongs to some kind of artist agency
and those artist agency artists are a
lot more
expensive I've
noticed
yeah good for them get that
bag yeah slave
mhm oh thank you for helping me I'm just
trying to get rid of my
materials yeah it's a
thing it's it do be a
[Music]
thing thank you you're so cute you you
like you like smooy no like I mean
color-wise you're like chunky wonky but
your body type says smoothie to
me oh all of these are just like one
ingredient
hi welcome
back together we're strong together
we're hot yeah yes burn that floor burn
down my
house really appreciate it thank you oh
wait I had one
more sorry come
back
chin on
fire and flip it and flip it that's not
a rash or that's an that's egg fried egg
and
uh a chicken
leg false
advertisement you do that and
I shall feed myself
and
okay artists to set their own prices
regularly undervalue themselves and set
their prices far lower than they
actually should be so it's different
when an artist is part of an agency yeah
but um I will say that also causes some
issues uh being in an agency as an
artist it seems to make things a lot
more complicated
and yeah like even if the artist wants
to gift something to
me
um they're not allowed
to in certain
cases
so that's very
complicated
yeah you're so hungry you're sitting in
the food that's so cute that's so cute
uh eggs and you can have you can have
the no you can have the milk how about
that o yeah the price of being corporate
yeah but in in exchange you get maybe
maybe you get good jobs I don't even
know maybe maybe it's not like that but
I would assume you get good jobs good
connections they take care of all the
paperwork and this and that
yeah okay uh where are we at I would
like a level up so I can learn or did I
already get the right level no I want to
learn this level 12 so I'm going to go
and explore
[Music]
unrealistic would you guys say I'm ready
for the boss I would say
no hi Ki
hi ah how about we like walk into one of
those uh dungeons so to say I mean
they're they don't really feel like
Dungeons but uh oops wait who do I want
to who do I want to
bring let's bring you and let's bring my
shiny
tany and I never had you with me but ah
you both ice that's not so
interesting let's ring y nice thank you
for the pinky let's go I appreciate it
very nice of
you let's go find some caves
basically wait I forgot to make a
shield got to go
back I want to make the shield uh
and I was going to make the bow as well
I did I
did
okay okay nobody saw that nobody saw
anything that was not weird that was
normal
TST
I think I chose a good place for my base
it's like a lot of space very
flat pretty good oh I was going to get
like nails as well I have to make nails
where am I making Nails where would I
make nails on the maybe on the high
quality
workbench T I'm like t
o that's a different kind of TT is not
about te posing I know
that ah I need nails for the high
quality workbench so there's no way that
it will need Nails uh uh that I need to
make nails on there where do I make
nails twice ah wait I didn't see it oh
my God blind W oh and that also needs
ingots H okay let's make the maximum I
think I can make
more ingots too yeah
[Music]
chill a pal is so chill I'm glad I got
back into it but it's like you I feel
like I'm playing solo although Nissa
help me but like I think I need to like
force people to go online for
me but I think um I'll uh when I catch
up a little bit then I'll ask like gooy
B and
others to play with me please at a
certain time on a certain
day not just like count on people
showing up spontaneously cuz that's not
going to work for me that may work for
others at other times but it does not
work for me as we
know are you doing
anything
are Senpai tax time no not necessarily
senpai
tax doky tax you want to know what what
it means uh like myth to me in Japanese
is dolki D
Uki same
generation that's how you call same gen
people cuz you you guys probably know
Senai and you guys probably know kohai
right kohai is the ones who uh
are yeah debuted after me not donkey TX
doy
text
yeah doy doie no d o u k
i nice nongo so gen mate is DOI please
remember repeat after me
doie if you want to say I love my gen
mates do
[Music]
do do
do
doy
SK doy SK I love my
GMAT welcome to Wawa's uh Japanese
class oh my God I really feel like I'm
outside right now touching grass in the
Sun
oh now oh I I really feel I really feel
how the the the the the clouds are
covering the sun right
now cuz like the the light changed oh oh
this feels so realistic to me right now
I need to take my my
meds this feels like I real life yeah
like we're just chilling outside doing
some work together just crafting
[Music]
something yes I'm holding the button to
craft yeah yeah I have to pretty
sure it says hold why' you run away huh
oh there you
are touching grass in
power finally my ocean takes her meds I
will never take my
meds where are you going
kativa huh oh he's taking the egg
bringing it to the food
box chy B you could do that yourself you
know don't freak out
now don't don't make a big drama don't
make a scene now
please nobody going to help me huh I see
how it
is wait could one of my one of my pals
help me oh not
you uh
these don't look like they would help me
but yeah you go you go farm some wood no
I don't need I don't need
wood chill you do something make
yourself
useful oh watering are you going to
water the berries no you're just going
to look at them yeah cuz they look yummy
I know no bye byebye
byebye why am I making so many anyway
I'll leave the rest to kativa to do it
whenever she is free and what was I
going to
make these ah a few more ingots oh
no
okay now I really can't help on this
one look at that big big big squiggle
boy oh he's so
cute this is one of the cutest Pals in
my
opinion I love
it l
squiggle so true so true going to put
these in
here
H
oh oh what what what
oh what you
doing oh chill what are you doing stop
fighting what's wrong with
you picking random fights steal from
Kyla she has lots of stuff I can't steal
I can yeah run like run through the
field and see whatever I can pick up
randomly whatever is on the
ground but that's just like mats just
resources oh depresso thank you
one more please one
more
thanks high quality
workbench oh can you
move
no I'll put it
here she won't
notice yeah I'm sure nobody really will
but I got enough like stones and uh wood
for
sure and I don't even know where her
base is where is
it can you tell
me okay I
think then wait do I even need this one
still I guess I could still keep it for
like working at the same time with
someone
else
oh yes I'm set for a long time I don't
even need these Pals on the wood right
now TBH that is so true what am I doing
I don't need you out here cuz um I don't
need you to be woodworking let's do
something else that we might need just
general maybe another
kativa
H oh the kaas
are well what this is
fine Rock Farm is always good to run and
I have a million rocks too I think but
Kyla is Northeast how far like here cuz
that actually I haven't seen at on that
would be Northeast or like
here yeah I have
99,999 rocks and wood and they're still
locking M 596
can
you I can't pick him up
huh I guess whatever do it
then
fine what am I supposed to
do can enhance
once can enhance Pals if I wanted to but
I don't no I would maybe enhance chill
[Music]
mhm just because I really like
chillet and
um we're missing the medieval medicine
workbench so we got to level up so I was
just
actually thank you was going to say I'm
going to go out and and uh get some
exp but uh that solves my
problem thank you for solving all my
problems and filling my
wishes uh I'm so confused uh
okay I need a I need a
recipe friendship noodle Yes Noodle yeah
I like that more than squiggle in this
case he he do be a noodle for sure
ooh house plants no maybe not now uh o
knif for butchering sumon
piles that's kind of
insane okay we don't have
9,999 Stone we can definitely uh step
back on Gathering wood
though I would
say chillet is a fan favorite pal yeah I
understand
why
okay medieval medicine workbench oh it's
so small can it fit here no not allowed
huh it's so
[Music]
small that poor Cris I think I need an
idol meeting in the moment
not very exciting we did
it build coola box build sphere work
okay that'll probably take a while cuz I
for real need to level up to get those
recipes and thank
you
whoa whoa why so aggressive
huh have a nice meeting go for it should
I should I stay or should I
go I'm not going to Rite to a love
[Music]
song K key once again it's a beautiful
day
bow cuz you had a bad
day o you had a bad day I don't think I
ever sang that in a Koka
before
okay so I think now we can go on level
but uh should I
go okay idle meeting time please
hold uh for
two minutes one
minute I forgot to
m
for
yo what's up guys K Kitty key Welcome to
My Stream chillet is staring at us he's
making sure that you guys are being good
chickens behave
chickens while I'm
gone chicken is a chicken chicken is in
charge of you I shall name you
chick chick
no scatter no no you stay where you are
look at him so
[Music]
cute oh who who who loud loud noise okay
let's go ah
hung I'm so
hungry
mhm union meeting what do I
hear how dare you
guys I give you everything you could
ever ask
for
love stability a
workplace
Community sense of fulfillment
and what's the
word like a reason to
be
pet n you don't need that do you really
are you really that materialistic
huh that's what it's all about for you
huh wow okay I thought we had you know
something
special I thought it was you know about
something bigger than
that something
more
meaningful how how you how can you buy
merch with no pay well that sounds like
a you problem wait this is exactly where
I wanted to
go
EXO and boss level 13 okay it should be
fun money of course I'm treating them
kindly no there's no secret
basement no k k I read kilam
Mori actually that would be a cute name
and I mean cie does like to take lives
right wait I think the other thing is
stronger I oh ah that was my shield H I
think the other weapon is
stronger
ow armor
damaged ow I'm
dying no don't die don't die no no no no
no no don't kill
it
please don't kill me though either Hey
where's your
life a lag I think that's a lag
uh do you
see no no no no no can I die when this
happens
uh
um uh
yeah let me try to
leave
oh
oh damn it I need to repair that that
that sucks ah God damn it I'll go back
to my
base it
K I think it bugged but it felt weird it
was very weird and this is where I'll
need the repair table right which I
didn't build yet repair
bench maybe like
sideways make guns for your shiny
monkey guns what do I have
for a recipe for
that anyway got to repair
this and
this oh and while we add it why not why
not repair this
too perfect CA I don't think I have a
caity in captivity yet
ha if you know what I
mean let's get it this one's alone to
waa oh no oh no don't no don't have
everybody no no no
oh lucky please don't die please don't
kill it no no no
no yeah I'm also surprised I'm already
level 12 that took me ages on my own
thanks to
nista
oh oh
oh there it is I feel like 26 is
pretty
high get in
here
okay cheeky
bastard I wouldn't say it's that
low
okay another
try cuz that was kind of
[Music]
weird should I pull myself down a little
bit yeah let's go L
kids you oh
wait I will switch to this this
seems way stronger like also just attack
uh 200 who said the free shot bow is
stronger did I get one guide or
what thanks for the memberships let's go
you're so
sweet way
easier
okay
oh yeah I had a shiny in one of these
dungeons die just in front of me because
of my pals being too
aggressive
oh
oh and I had one of these fugs
completely bug around like under the
door or something and I kept on hearing
the battle music but I I just couldn't
get to the fug anymore because like he
was like under under the stones or
something like I couldn't reach him
anymore and he was just like forever not
defeated that kind of
sucked but generally I wonder are these
dungeons even worth it cuz like they're
all they look all the
same uh I don't know it doesn't really
feel like a good time
investment there can be some nice items
in the end
okay o o o be a good
keny let me feed you some Kibbles yeah
you like those Kibbles don't you o
o hey I'm helping you I'm helping you
here wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait where's my where's my M where's my
where's my
Mount
oh uh-oh uh-oh okay the cat is
goner yeah just do it just do
it
okay ah
wait got to make sure to pick up the
gold coins I want the
money they do have treasure and bosses
are good and the blue stone okay okay so
I guess they're worth
it this this room is a dead end right
like there's always these free rooms one
has the boss and the others are like
dead ends but they're always like
differently aligned I
think dungeon Palace yeah
[Music]
yeah
let's see what's on this
side is this the boss side a it
is right that's where the boss usually
is it's a cheeky plump and juicy it
says I'll come back later CH
PE KF kfp kfp don't leave e don't what
it will change no
it
changes well I mean it doesn't really
matter right I I don't care what it is
but it was just funny that it was chiy
beas all right then I'll take you
down do I want it to be chicky peas or
do I not
care plump and juicy yes you are yes
that you are certainly plump and
juicy oh one
hit ow I'm so sorry oh wow
oh oh we're so
strong one more hit from him
and ow
ow I don't want to I want to be careful
oh where you
going can you come back
up n you little I can't fly you
know that oh sorry well then
uh I'll give you a
hand no I was going to catch it I didn't
think that one shot would kill
it
no uh I'm not is it
[Music]
uh well I I ended your suffering isn't
that great but like I want to see the
other rooms should I really go there I
guess I'll just open the
chest she hates us just another day give
be no it's not like that it was an
accident every dead chicken is an
accident trust me spark blast let's
[Music]
go you couldn't have just thrown a spar
it wasn't ready yet it wasn't ready to
be
indoctrinated it wasn't ready
oh I feel
guilty what what's with the sandwiches
you remind me I have I brought a
sandwich back
from my idol
meeting that I'm not afraid to
eat I have a sandwich and I'm not afraid
to eat
it it's a BLT sandwich I
think
hello
oh give me your money give me your
spheres give me your everything give me
your
life boys love takanashi sandwich
BLT I love BLT should I put that on a
cap on a
hat
anything here or did I just walk back
I'm
confused why is it so empty these
dungeons are too
empty for real for
real oh it's just mats
here I don't really care about the mats
right now although or is like maybe
worth mining a little
bit
oh what do you think is it worth
it I've been
here damn
it I'll take some ores with
me the blue
ones I already cleared it everything
there was one room that I didn't go to
in the beginning where there's like
three directions the left one I didn't
enter at all
[Music]
oh maybe that room has a
chest pick it up pick it
up
come on be
[Applause]
gone okay but is this really what is
this by the
way what kind of or is
this
sulfur what I've never seen sulfur
before I got to take some of
these don't need that yet
okay well I am out of space soon
so
uh for guns ah I'm not really dare
yet so that was the dead end of that
direction I want to go back to the
middle middle middle middle
beginning which is not
here
let's make this a little bit
faster if you not try to catch the pal
no need to crawl the dungeon again after
boss and treasure he I'm trying to catch
the pals though I'm trying I'm just
overpowered and also I wonder if there's
a treasure chest over there you know cuz
this one I didn't enter yet I think or
did I
I like the tippy tappy sounds too but
that one sounds
weird that doesn't quite fit him wa
there's nothing here okay I I'm confused
that's why I don't know about these
dungeons they're so
confusing wait where did I enter from
where's the
entrance huh
huh did I see this can you mine
these what is
this see I'm so lost I'm so
confused okay I'll just try to find the
exit although this looks really
cool but no
Pals really there were barely any
Pals this is ah this is the
way I know that
way okay
okay
try to left I feel like I went
there I went there I went to all the
lefts is is
[Music]
whatever
yes leave dungeon that was really
underwhelming really
underwhelming maybe I go back to the the
penguin do you think I can take down the
penguin oh sorry I'm trying to open the
sandwich looks so
good wa it's not it's uh oh no yeah it
is it's BLT with chicken I think chicken
and
bacon nice penguin is not that hard the
first time we
tried he
definitely challenged me oh wait no it's
tomato chicken egg salad and bacon
that's not BLT at all where's the
lettuce where's the
[Music]
lettuce
yum
M
protein n n
[Music]
m
excuse me for a
moment while I enjoy the
[Music]
sandwich I dropped some ingredients I
think
mhm
oh oh okay we good we
good
K the tomato is so
small
when will I ever get a
cery
when sorry for making you guys
hungry 86 eggs yo the egg production is
going pretty well I have to give you
that it may not be 100 per day but it's
pretty good
Pizza I might have pizza tonight as
well you had a
seasa how was
it
okay I
finished the one half of my
sandwich o
got
okay
um oh did I get the level up that I
wanted or was that still not
enough yeah no I need I need two more
levels so I'm going to go to the penguin
again
but if only I had that
electricity Sparks
pal but I don't um maybe we'll meet it
on the way but um other than if we don't
then just I guess
um anything that's not water or ice will
at least be oh on fire fire as well we
just let's not bring fire water or
ice I mean I'm going to bring chill
anyway just not going to use it I
think what about
these like
psychic
I don't know who to bring we're not
really prepared for this but just out of
Interest I'll bring you and I'll
bring okay goodbye goodbye chillet I
bringing the Killer
maray
and let me see if I can put away some
stuff
though uhhuh
uhhuh the R button is so useful yo think
I'm going to make another
chest ooh chest
setion I can still reach that chest can
I I think so wait new server well new
for
me it's still the enan server with the
other girls with who already started
before
me I don't know what what Ian server you
were thinking
of is it worth keeping them when I
already like have these
recipes
wait can I activate them right click
right click right click no left click
no sell them okay I'll eventually sell
them
eventually
[Music]
Ruby I don't know where to put these
things so they're just going to go in
here
randomly
yeah Pelt and oh a book that contains s
cool wait I should use
this let's go Tech
point oh what I get a stronger feather
hair Bend for
that
okay ah okay I see I see I
see okay let's go oh you're back again
and wait now that you're here I can sell
you something
right do I want to keep those schematics
or do I want to sell them cuz now I have
the
chance now orever don't kill him this
something well seems like it doesn't
even matter he just keeps on
appearing let's sell I'll sell
it if I need anything narissa can make
it for
me
oh that's good money let's go let's go
thanks
dude that's the
spirit I know right just got to rely on
my oh my mommy
resta who's the mommy
now okay oh wait I could teleport there
why am I not just going
to
a oopsie I just want to press F
press
F
mo catch him he's helpful who
who who let the dogs out wah wah wah who
Let The Dogs Out waha wah wah I did it
was
me okay we have a shield we have a
strong weapon we have this that we
didn't have before I
think M no we just going to go for it
going to have some fried
egg oh W you eat a lot
oh okay
okay for Y and let's go I'm scared no
I'm
[Music]
scared where
it let's get the
tiny tiny gone
first because they were so annoying I
swear to
God
Jesus
Jesus J
shoot
Jesus
Jesus ah right right right
right I
forgot where's the boss
ah H okay okay okay the small ones are
almost
gone ah
wa okay it's okay let's try again try
again this is good practice
for the actual
boss
oh you really want me to do that night I
mean yeah we but we almost had the the
small ones okay you know what I'll pick
up my stuff I'll chill around a little
bit see if I can find Sparks again cuz
there was uh I think a Sparks around
here two actually right before before at
least they may not be here
again
anend just go in and see if the little
ones are dead oh you think they might
still be
dead I don't know about
that stream Sparks yeah let's stream
some
Sparks
ooh oh
oh come with me I must adopt all the
chickens I see in this world all of them
where's my ah okay okay I see I
see might want
the
this okay any sparks flying
here NOP
okay now we'll just we'll just look a
little bit more and wait until night
time
[Music]
let's go this way cuz we haven't checked
it out
yet oh there's a chest a nice looking
chest you drafted yes yes you are
welcome to your new life ooh good
chest I know I know there's a mod I got
to get it I totally forgot about it this
time I don't even know if I need like
like I probably need extra permission
for it if the same person who made the
the goba mod made the Chicken Mod then
it'll probably be
easy yeah the dino goba
mod if that comes from the same person
then it might be uh fast oh by the
way
okay that's what I
wanted did could I use it in a
Solo ah for real I can't use it online a
why
not why
not so
sad I guess I could like show it off for
a moment and like for 5 minutes cuz you
can see them in the beginning and then
go back to the main
World damn there's a lot of uh these
blue stones
here but where are the pals world is
looking a little bit empty right
now you think I might be able to use it
online
oh
hello oh no
reaction
oh it's client base you will oh that's
fine for me if only I see it that's fine
with
me
I assumed so
o why is it don't why is it lower now 35
eh hey you
prick we're so
back H what what's the matter with
you how can you still ES okay o o o yeah
that's what I thought woo level up
okay cheeky bastards you cheeky bastard
where am I right now oh what is this
oh it leads
to a newish
area
feel like there must be an effigy over
there well
well
exploration oh level
16 what's
this small palel
ah level six
16 I am 13 manageable but oh 17 yeah I
think I'm not exactly supposed to be
here just
yet 17
17 I am 16 going on
[Music]
17 oh
you
[Music]
are wait is she 16 going on 17 or was
she 15 going on 16 nah 16 going on 17
and then he was you
are was he was he did did they say an
age was he he wasn't the same age right
what was he 17 going on 18
Sparks oh
you are
17 going on
[Music]
uh-oh uhoh uh-oh uhoh through the tree
no hey no I'm sorry I couldn't save you
what about the other
one I didn't catch it did I I didn't
hear the
sound okay now we got to be careful I'm
not going to kill it
again I hope never mind uh you go away
now don't ruin this for me
again
uh you think my bnk stick is too strong
maybe o getting
here
ow every
time
oh my first Sparks stream Sparks stream
Sparks stream
Sparks also by the
[Music]
way cooler box
right I want the chill saddle I want
chill oh yeah so we have a
an ancient we can get the egg egg
cubor
and so I can't put Sparks on my team now
huh have
to go
back all right that's
fine
chest name it
stream or we had a visitor in the base
the the dude from before
probably
I am 16 going on
[Music]
17 Vixie there's a Vixie up
there and you guys told me how uh useful
Vixie
is yeah showing her age well because I
know that
no I know that movie is old but I uh I'm
not really like when I grew up that
movie was not uh like something we would
watch was old I just watched it because
I went to a like tourism based
school and you know we have a lot of
visitors that love Sound and Music in
Austria that come here just yeah it's a
classic exactly and people come here
just for Sound of Music purposes
especially
Americans they come here in big groups
and they do like Sound and Music
tours Americans love Sound of
Music like it's crazy like so many
austrians wouldn't have even seen sound
of
music but like I feel like every
American
Boomer at least has seen it maybe not
Millennials
but
yeah it's a
classic those are a few of my favorite
things and then we watched it in school
just to understand what the hype is all
about and I really liked it and then uh
we went as far as to was it just us uhoh
my stamina
uhoh damn it took some damage we went as
far as to do a Sound of Music Tour
that's meant to be for
tourists and it was fun the tour guide
when we were in the bus just driving to
the next location like we were playing
Sound and Music music and the toy guy
was singing and we were also singing it
was
fun
yay saving the I only have one of them
it's just like I use it whenever I feel
like it you
know probably need some more
Health
oopsie nothing wrong with being old yeah
no but like I'm just saying like it's
not
really me knowing Sound of Music
shouldn't say anything about my age it's
just a
classic what is that oh that's a base
was like that looks unnatural over there
Effigy I want to reach the top of this
because I'm sure there's something up
there the hills are alive at the sound
of
chicken what's the sound it's a not it's
not the life of the sound of chickens
it's the life of the sound of
pigs
I love s
music K is over 60 confirmed
hey hey hey hey hey
hey you just feel it you get a you get a
Vibe you know exactly where these things
are
placed oh you know Mard yeah I know him
personally
oh yeah I am over 200 years old yeah way
more than 200 years old oh you don't
even know you don't even understand
where was this Vixie that I saw I
totally lost track of it I don't think
we'll be seeing
it I don't I don't think we'll see
it again but uh
interesting somebody built their base
right next to that broken Castle whose
base is
this I love your stories Kaba granny
waaba voice please Kaba so true
hey kab I doesn't want to be disturbed
right now okay let her let her rest let
her
sleep that's Callie's that's Callie's
BAS damn that's a
ah really random far
location K we so Nik yo K
Doo Where Are You
K
Mor I love how this Sparks it just walks
with so much
confidence
[Music]
damn give me more give me more give me
that exp
bonus looking good yay yay yay yay oh
fixy oh there we go
what was mixit doing again like digging
up pal speres
right
ow wait will let kill it
no nice eh 92 come on
ow I'll get another
one arrows and spheres
nice I should have killed ah ah sorry I
I
just brain empty
moment oh
well oh is there a teleportation
point the desolate
Church okay I should activate that uh is
there an actual path yeah
ah
I just wanted to kill I wouldn't I
wouldn't say
so oh combat
[Music]
H I guess I'll catch
you
ooh very strong this oh very strong this
n
strong oh 12 is
low
no are you sure it's dead it looks very
much
alive okay I will not do the same
mistake for the owl because we need
another horory
member cannot make mistakes with the BBS
sometimes it's just better to not have
your
P that wasn't me the the the bird had an
existing condition pre-existing
condition that killed it I didn't know
it had a pre-existing condition how
could I have known what the is that
jol talk killed another electricity
Sanic I think that's another
Sanic CH the mother I I'm kind of uh off
path
now um if I go there then I'm going to
go away from the
church oh misty eye from the mountain
below of my
brother level
three m
[Music]
fire and
so keep watching
over during
[Music]
[Applause]
Sun
[Music]
the mountain side
W
Des come across
SK and I See
Fire Inside the mountain I see
far it hurt so
[Music]
much
inside so
nice another watch
along you guys can never get enough load
of the Rings or Hobbit watch alongs huh
it's so dark I need a uh why did I never
make myself a
freaking fire
stick F you Amazon for taking that word
away from me
a torch yeah but in Wawa typical classic
oaba language it's a fire
stick okay maybe we can try to get back
on track but I kind
of I would have to like walk around here
I guess unless I want to
climb it's hard to see right
now hey
is this
dungeon
uhoh
uhoh abandoned
Minecraft did I read that wrong huh it's
a dungeon
right what I can't
see too bad I can't see oh
heie don't talk wait did I get the last
one did I successfully catch it or did I
kill it I think I killed
it did
I I did okay this one shall
survive it's cute it's literally like
the Sparky version of the the the the
blue one wait do they have them in all
colors oh they can provide some light oh
that's interesting but I guess I don't
have them in my team right
now
uh-oh
whoa
the way he jumped at
me did you just hit the Sheep attack
Lambo attack don't hurt this wild Lambo
you know what I'll make you uh
um I wasn't going to say anything what
what so
angry
a chest what the is
this the sun is back
guys sun is
[Music]
shining wow soy 433 gold coins that's
pretty dope oh another
one oh wait yeah wait there's a lamb
ball
tutorial
oh when okay wait wait there's some more
lalls here maybe with my
oh yeah low damage low damage I can do
it what but they suddenly I suddenly
throw out these crits yo it's
crazy D what was that why did
I why do I have such a high crit
rate oh my God
was that a head shot
maybe okay three out of five lamb
balls where am I damn it I keep on going
the wrong way okay turn
around I got to
go that
way and let's bring up my
amount oh not you what the
hell did you
did you guys see it was supposed
it h okay
bug uh oopsie what if
I switch to the deer oh it skipped the
deer oh no okay so deer deer
how how weol not dead no no no no
no
I will not take such
excuses oh what the
hell
oh I love opening chest hi guys I'm not
going to waste my time with you now okay
wow there's so many wolves here and
there's a need
[Music]
J
don't
run wait
kute you I had I had 83% y'all why
would't you just deal with the freaking
fugs am I the only one struggling with
this I'm helping yeah yeah
so you know what for doing that I'm
going to make you watch as I murder your
[Music]
friends how does that
feel how does that feel to you you like
seeing animals that look exactly like
you die or even me forcing you
to give me a hand with
that oh my God confus ah no not the mega
spere just shut up just go back now
you're confusing me too many wolves
here whoa why the meas spere wait wait
wait how do I switch it again how do I
ah how do I switch H
uh uh cck two oh okay okay okay okay w w
w w
oh
wow thank
you
[Music]
T oh no not the jol
Hogs oh there's so much going
on be bey bey bey beyy wa oh oh
my shiny monkey is
helping oh
no
quick no not you this
one guys everything's so chaotic with me
always I need to monkey I need
to uh uh repair my armor
soon uh
oopsie
W very
dramatic it's
alive oh no a dead one couldn't save
this one
yo the monkey is like out for blood
today
woo got to catch them
all get him get him get him good job
monkey oh why did I just
shoot I'm pretty good I'm getting like
I'm level 15 now I'm getting so
many Pals so many
exp oh look at the celery celery
[Music]
celer a cute they're so pretty I'm not
going to go and catch them now
but good to
know name the monkey Jill
Jill what
Jill cuz he needs to chill oh what
why is Jil
and oh pick piora up pick up what
monkey no no no no no no no monkey
monkey has to be J
monkey am I finally no I'm somewhere
completely different but oh what is this
level 17 as a robe P has a monkey I can
you actually it's not a monkey it's not
like in a monkey category right of
animals pretty sure it's not a
monkey
uh it's not it's considered a monkey
really it's like a yeah like a bush
baby a primate of sorts
aha so it kind of is a
monkey a
monkey okay come on I'm going to go
there then teleport to but first i'm
going to get the teleportation point
this one and then we teleport here no
then we teleport home then we fix my
armor then we beat the freaking
banking one and for all and
forever stupid pinking man
where where am I going is this
correct I will not take this
disrespect
anymore rude as
hell no don't
let
this way this
way off with P so I can see the monkey
um yeah yeah I don't know I I don't
really feel like I want
to force
myself onto her it's
[Music]
okay there's always a chance as long as
she has the monkey and the monkey is
still alive so no need to
worry wait I still I didn't go
there this side this side this side this
side this side don't get lost again
wa I'm hungry
too such a good hack
uh let's eat something that's not
raw Gordon Ramsey wouldn't like it if it
was
raw wait I'm going wrong again wrong
wrong wrong wrong wrong maybe up
here yeah I
know I know there
something that makes me eat it
automatically I think it's the like bag
the food bag that you can carry or
something like
that uh Callie's
base I
think
finally there's light at the end of the
tunnel
yo what what am I going to
yo so this is important this is very
important
hooray ah and in here I think it's also
yeah yep yep yep yep yep I
remember the
effigy
and oops it sorry sorry sorry I totally
respect you okay I don't have enough
yeah
whatever what do you want I'm going to
bring you over to Callie's Pals wait
they're all gone oh did she all put them
all away so that they don't like get
like
sad
yummy I can't take these can
I not that I want to but like you say
like steal stuff but like I don't think
I can steal anything that's not lying
around oh all the beds she got over at
the top here what the hell is
this oh I like how she has it like open
like this pretty
chill but yeah because she doesn't have
her her Pal's working oh there's no
nothing lying around so
abandoned no worries that's not really
what I came here for
anyway
okay let's go oh it's already 10: p.m. I
stream for 5 hours which to me still I
know I have such a weird sense of time
now of like streaming time 5 hours I
feel like I owe you more
guys but we did actually like so much
crazy
progress actually
oopsie maybe what about we just end it
by uh taking
down at least panking and maybe even the
main
boss that would be
crazy that'd be kind of
crazy
wouldn't
it I think it
would eight more hours of stream got it
sounds
good battle zo way to end it on that
would be good I don't know if I'm strong
enough though I don't know I mean if you
have to ride Pokemon pal sorry you have
to ride
pal 10 my
God why
[Music]
then I to lose so much force yeah cuz I
I
feel very very stressed out about
it all here's some food enjoy okay
M I want to grill
the the raw
meat okay let's do
mushrooms I'm Miss said it a lot to I
know it's like ah it just
slips it's crazy cuz like I it's
obviously not I know it's not that game
but also mean that they both start with
P yeah it's hard not to say
it more hot cakes on The
Griddle yeah true yesterday I watched
the the P Direct
M so that's fresh on my
mind well I haven't even given them guns
so I wouldn't even call it
that so far I never experienced that and
I don't I don't really care about giving
them guns it's kind of weird wouldn't it
be nice to just have them attack with
their own skills why give them guns make
them into guns yeah give them guns I
don't really get
that oh oh my God there's so many eggs
a you got got to get the harness for the
fox I I know I had it
before I know it's pretty cool
flamethrower
Fox God why are we so slow even together
huh how
come oopsie let me see
something I should be able to get the
spar
workbench let's
go very very good ooh I think in my solo
playr on that one day where I played on
my
[Music]
own yeah I think I got like pretty much
up to
here cuz I don't remember getting these
things I think this is where I ended it
on in terms of the tech
tree yeah
yeah good morning wa
hello Callie walked out to help Rissa
with a fight and it was this massive
Canon pal that just stagger
locked the p with massive explosions
whoa already up to level 15 good
progress for real for real yeah I think
I I can maybe soon play with the girls
also have 29
Points I could get my own recipe for the
crossbow but but right now makes no
sense I kind of want the chillet
saddle wheat Plantation will be good
meal will be probably
necessary I guess we'll get the
monitoring
stand Nightwing saddle will be necessary
do I have a Nightwing yet though I must
have otherwise I wouldn't have the
saddle and of course the meas sphere
recipe metal spare
I could I should make
one an yay back to work take care good
luck and have
fun enjoy coola box
workbench all right ah damn it Ingot oh
no you know what I think I'll bring
another Fox into the
party also I need more
ore more or more or or no more okay
we need another one with the fire at
least oh my God there's like so
little no one no
one that's actually one of the rarest
ones
then holy moly the fire pals are
rare
H let's bring in the Vixie though we
wanted the
Vixie and for our upcoming fight our
highest level
electricity
pal maybe this I would love to bring
another one but they're so low level
maybe this one and then try to level it
fast somewhere
quickly you guys say that one's
effective against the water pal right
bad missing yeah okay okay okay
okay at night I don't need I guess
so uh a nice big fire boy if you check
the enemy camp cages
oh I see see
h ah 20 20
ingots
Bo that's a bit
crazy wonder if I have more ore to make
that H I
don't I
don't oh God to be kidding
me uh wait and I can't get in uh ore
within my
own uh within my base huh I got
[Music]
a okay I'll
check m
Callie's base has
ore okay I might go
there nice I love seeing it disappear
look at all that there they
uh
transported I got to help him it's too
[Music]
much that's a little bit much you know
what they keep on like um getting it
from
here I'll make a
chest here right
here yeah egg incubator
I I don't know if I have the
materials
[Music]
anyway
Stone and
yeah
mhm I can make
that let's put
it ah no that was
accident
ouch what's a good
place I'll just put it in front of my
house it looks
nice
inside
oh does it have to be near fire okay
okay
yeah I remember they wanted to be like
but does every egg want it to be the
same temperature cuz I feel like they
were eggs that were more comfortable in
in different temperatures
no clever name yeah I so love you I'll
never forget
you thank
you clever
name clever
name thank
you
clever
clever yeah I don't I'm just going to
sit on them no just kidding here Rocky
egg let's
[Music]
go clever name clever
name okay it's dark now I guess we can
take the chance and go to the
penguin bastard
Penguin Ice and want to take cold and
let literally in running water
oo you can make another base of lots of
iron ore there's one near the chill boss
Northwest isn't that where IIs has the
base her uh or
base I think that one's that spot's
already
taken why did I not take that
teleportation Point what the
hell was that teleportation point where
Iris has the or base because then I
guess I just didn't see it
really feel like I need to
level
those Pals that I have with me right
now
oh anything
here oh yeah oh tomat okay ooh I'm going
to
help ouch
ouch shoot
more ah oh no ah
ah God damn
it get it get it it doesn't get much
better than
this has like 5 HP come on Yahoo and
level app for our
[Music]
sparket tomat is a great level two
Miner I
see I want to get spark it a little bit
higher still but it would probably be
daytime by the time I have it
higher
ah this is the thing with pad world you
want to do one thing and then you get
like kind of like not distracted but
like
you stall by doing other
things then you want to go back to do
the thing and you keep on thinking of so
many things that you could connect with
doing that
[Music]
thing
right and it does bring some nice light
this
spikes
[Music]
pal I see nothing I could fight but I
see I think an effigy and then
electricity EG
go I know I haven't been picking up the
normal
eggs they just don't spark my interest
but this electricity egg surely
does I hear so many animal
sounds you think I one shot the sleeping
pengle that's at the
crossbow well that surely would be nice
but when I when I kill one don't all the
others wake up too and then it's chaotic
again you think it's time to
try
no uh where was where oh I don't see the
green thing anymore what is that oh oh
oh guard and a Wandering
Merchant let's not attack
them same stuff as always right oh wait
this
is ooh teacher
implode that one I don't think I've seen
it before
but I can't see the green thing anymore
I swear I saw something oh what's that
oh that's the Moon
H
whatever well you guys should be used to
me talking about hatching eggs I mean I
even hatched an egg in my
3DW oh feel like I see a green
Reflection In The
Water
imagination
yeah but I swear there was an effigy
there
I'll get it one
day but not
[Music]
today the dark howling
sounds ner
h have oh something we can find let's
go come here cute owl cute fat owl or
else I'm going to grill
you okay good choice good choice cuz I'm
not sure about owl meat probably tastes
like
chicken
probably
but
not going to go for
it are we ready it's almost daytime
let's go let's go I'm so
scared are they
sleeping oh they're not
sleeping
I'm already too late
Mo just got to get them head
shots
yum and don't go for
me
oh SP
level seven don't talk let's
[Music]
go take the little
down
no this
panking it's not even him it's his Mini
I okay we're just going to like go at
night time for real for
real but uh
oopsie that's ridiculous that is just
ridiculous uh wait
[Music]
no do I need a better weapon no my
weapon is fine
oh hey M puga you are going to be my
helper in a
moment could I go like together with
narissa for example in into these
dungeons can we like go together is that
possible oh wait I can't level them cuz
they're both
dead yeah h i see
[Music]
spicy she got carried by Kyla rocket
launcher okay well you got to keep it to
a certain extent cuz I obviously like
you know getting carried for
everything oh is not idren is
not not a fun way of playing the game
not the fun it is a fun way but not the
way
okay you go and recover and
recover very very
[Music]
unfortunate
n
uh what else uh let's build a monitoring
stand I'll put it up here on the stone
because it doesn't
matter
right
eh I mean if I Wouldn't Die I could just
use the electric Pals for even if
they're low level for the the small
Penguins that's what I was thinking and
then bring out even if oh even if the
smaller ones are
dead I can bring the um like one of my
higher leveled ones
in I didn't build that I think it
drained sanity just by having it
built did I build
this didn't build it
right no when you use okay then I'll
just have it
built Jo talk died in two hits and
didn't do anything
oh
well
[Music]
okay I'll see what I can do but I want
to bring at least spark it maybe bring
him give him one more level or so you
know
where are they coming
from
there oh they're taking their sweet
time oh I should go grab
some ore that's ore over
there o
wo
wo and again I did it all without my
pals
nice shows you how strong I am on my
own I don't need a pal to protect me I'm
protecting the
pals that's how it is nice shooting
there thank you you can catch and I
don't want to why would I why would I do
that now do it without the
crossbow
[Music]
no and I did it while was way tell me
why
me and the crossbow we're meant to
be m
for tomorrow guys I'm thinking members
only stream by the
way
um late evening 8:00 p.m. wa time maybe
something like
that don't know what to do yet uh I
don't necessarily want to watch a movie
because we just did
that oh I need to see if I find the game
that I have have members permission for
that I like that looks
interesting yeah how about we help plan
is ah yeah remind me of that just like a
we can do besides playing a game we can
like plan out some things for
sure
um
mhm riding Rush Bo is great below level
20 Boulders you mean like those stones I
can break them with the rush board
fast
EG yes light the SP I was thinking about
it recently but not just playing it
members only just even playing it
publicly but yeah we can play members
only it's been a
while we'll see though I I'll check what
uh is in the members only list maybe
some new games were
added if you have the saddle okay oh you
again
oh
ow
you're you're pretty
defensive
okay let's not give it a head shot uh
[Music]
don't no
wait bring out the Bonk stick
uh now
okay can we do it believe
no wait I can take um
maybe not gigas spare I only have gigas
spare oh God oh God
please let me catch
you 20 new members thank you so much ah
water
child you little
ah you're going to kill
me 19% I can't get it higher than that
you going to force me I'm just going
to I'm just going to use
it it
91% join
me I take no no for an
answer took me a freaking G
spere ooh learned dark
ball
ooh are you having
fun
oopsie oopsie oh
M I don't know what I want
here he looks depressed they're all in
good condition I
think we need the stupid cooler box do I
have enough Ingot by now or
what I know one
more woo cooler box cooler box where do
I put it maybe
home for like yummy food that I cooked
for
myself also yeah I need to
eat that looks like watermelon the capry
meat I need an nice
Pokmon but you wrote p o k e m o n why
would you do that why would you write it
like
that what a freaking
bait although I I will give you the
benefit of the doubt I I can imagine you
didn't like realize either what you were
writing you sabotaged
me it was a trap usual room who was
that it's been a while since I've sent
people to the usual mental
Jenny I believe that you had no ill
intent and it was probably a mistake on
your side too
sorry one month usual
room it's you know it is what it
is what a deal
that's pretty light
yeah I
mean he said
sorry and I'm I'm in the good mood who
am I
to ruin your life how's this e goinging
oh oh oh e
oh what is
that dum looks dumb whoa whoa whoa what
is that it looks
funny it's like a slow pole
C I mean not really who knows who knows
really I I'll
check it's level
one oh my God look at me look over here
where are you going I want to look at
you oh you want to work oh he's such a
good baby I look at him the way he moves
bounce bounce bounce bounce bounce
bounce it's like a fish but
also like something else I don't know
it's bounce
boun me is so cute I love
him fascinating and like a
seal but oh my God I want to give him a
hug
choco bee what I don't know what that is
you mean the Final Fantasy
thing that's a that's
CH okay what was I doing I made the
coola box so are we done
here
yes I can now make a second base too
let's go let's go let's go cooking pot
wheat Plantation mil hey I already have
I think some of these
recipes and wheat seeds e what do you
mean I don't have wheat seeds I mean
somewhere I must have them oh wait wheat
seeds okay wait wheat seeds I don't have
where do I get wheat seeds from
narissa G got to go to work oh no
goodbye have a nice
day good luck at work FAL hello hello
little
friend from the merchant oh okay I don't
want to do it
now the mill I can make for Milling
wheat to produce flour requires P of
watering
trait uh I'll put it next to this thing
cuz they look very
similar
[Music]
it's me oh you're being cabon guys you
like it here
cabon and a little bit bonked but ignore
that just enjoy the
cabon we just I I'm just grabbing your
face
just the middle front of your face I'm
just grabbing it because I'm like you
pissing me
off
nice casting a SP can't breathe help
well should have thought about your
actions
earlier oh oh look at the
spars yo do you guys need a chest or so
here
here I think they need a chest even
though they could put it like in here
too I just not going to bring it there
anyway they don't have hands yeah even
if they don't do it isn't there like
others who will like take care of the
transportation or do I not have them out
here at the moment
oh well
anyway
uh follow me
guys follow
me wait I don't have my
mount
follow
me actually
uh March or first teleport and then we
March this stupid penguin my nemeses we
will spend our time here leveling our
sparket and our jolt hog
until we can until it's night and we can
beat its
ass if only there were more Pals
around this kind of
sucks
nothing oh she an
[Music]
effigy they do they get as much
XP uh by just being in my
team as they would if they're out
fighting ooh D and D have fun next time
chicken wizard you can be anything you
could ever
imagine
XP is shared for the whole team okay I
just wonder if it's like
equal x sure depending on the level
difference
mod Pals where are you where am I oh
where am
I oh I could get that uh
teleportation Point
hello there we go I
know catching would be e uh more exp but
they just keep on running away so
[Music]
fast that's a lot of mobs
oopsie good base
nearby
oh
oh oh
ah I don't want to eat tan meat
okay it only dropped fluids I
think elephant
meat
oh hey you
strong oh buba I anticipated you to move
a bit more
ow
no
I know you can also zoom in with a bow
hey with a bow
oh I don't know if I know that maybe I
knew maybe I
forgot my armor is damaged
again God damn
it
right click oh look at you look at you
little Lum ball no sorry guys wait did I
catch
it I think I
did
okay oh wait was that was that one still
alive
actually oh it was I think oh there's
another
one it Escape that one escaped
oh the lambo too no they don't want
to come
on do I need to use a mega sphere on
you I hope
not oh I think that's said
100% spark it defeated Lambo but I also
caught it
[Music]
he that is
incredible when they're dead like this
out out in the open then then you can't
get
them
ah
oh oh oh
oh all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right all
right
and
beautiful sparket is nine and J talk is
eight let's go
oh look at this
[Music]
Nightwing du catch yeah t is still
trying to defeat tanking yes I am cuz
I'm
salty and it's so me oh oh uh go
don't
go
uhoh ah uh
okay fine
50% we'll take it oh is this gooda
B is that GAA base wait it says the dead
beat what we're still a GAA base Goa
base
hello go oh I don't want to pick that up
knock knock
oh
[Music]
ooh oh from moment I thought it was good
no it's like uh I guess captured human
they also work or what like how do they
work in what
capacity what or they just run
around they can
craft
H
okay damn she's got some a nice location
here cuz like she can actually
always catch these nice water
Pals yo you're so far can you please
you're only level four why are you
resisting
everything oh no no the ball the
ball please come
here oh nice nice aim SP get
uh-oh I
no
no I'm too far I can't throw like this
can I oh I God
what
Sonic wait this is
bad yes
a oh
finally I got it this is really hard to
do while
swimming yah what are you doing oh you
sleeping you're actually
sleeping wait you catch it while it's
sleeping and from the
[Music]
back don't drown I'm
trying
oh nice okay woolbert and
woolbert cute how they're working
together did she have like a problem
with her uh caps lock when she played
this because they're
all big big
G okay okay
GA okay
good got a lot of um stuff here
just uh would be a waste if it despawned
you
know would be such a
waste how many space is next door hey
yo I see oh wait I was going to pick
this
up
hi sorry I know I know that was
upsetting to
watch ah no I'm not going to pay for
your
therapy
but just being by my side is a healing
experience so you're welcome to join me
yooo
they
accepted it's the only good
choice I'm going to get jol talk up to
10 now it's
nine to B I see
you no n n what
why they all got it out for me oh
no oh no maybe it is time for the better
weapon uh-oh that one
dead six oh my God that's so
low
what why is it so
low oh oh oh no no a oh do dog oh oh
isn't this beautiful what a beautiful
sight while catching up to everyone
that's what I'm trying to do yeah
finally done with that part oh my God I
did it yeah and now the next step is
just you know taking down the boss which
of course I think is understandable that
I haven't gotten to
yet wake
up a man that felt evil that felt
evil I'm so
mean now that other Li monk is going to
wake up in the
morning and be like where the hell is my
sister what has transpired while I was
sleeping
call route
Awakening okay we got to the base jol
got level 10 I think spark it is also
10 it's night
time if we're
fast
okay okay okay
okay I'm nervous I'm
nervous I need food okay
wait
uh okay let's
go go go are you freaking stupid why
can't can't you walk over some
stairs okay
[Music]
go are they sleeping
okay
murder are they all dead well shouldn't
there be one more what the is with
this one didn't you wake up for a
moment good
morning attack
sparket
oh
ah yeah yeah yeah yeah now we're finally
doing it and he's seems kind of
stuck oh never mind
uh
nice we like to see
it D oh okay that's fine I have a shield
and the shield recovers too very nice
and wait I'm supposed to catch him right
oh mother go
away 5% is like
nothing I don't know if I can
[Music]
seeing
whatever whatever oh suddenly Free level
ups for like spark it and so
on it's okay it's okay I thought okay
maybe a little bit more damage but of
course he does it's
fine we can get them wild they'll be
just as big
and okay no Treasure
Chest
fine so very very
good cooking pot probably will be
necessary mhm what's a heater aha
probably for the incubator for
example do the metal chests have more uh
space than the other
ones
I'm sure they do right and then Mega
Shield Mega Shield would be pretty
good for the boss
fight uh what what's what's the kind of
element you want to bring to the boss
fight was it ground like Earth or
whatever or stone something like that
was
it gotta go Fe in thank you for
[Music]
watching ground
okay U so it was was it fire
then the element of the boss I don't
remember i i i f it
[Music]
before elect ah
yeah should I upgrade my crossbow to
like a poison arrow crossbow maybe give
it some dot
damage I can still use normal arrows
right no poison arrow toal poison
arrow poison I don't know if I can make
that
[Music]
many
mhm bring lots of arrrows yeah I know I
know I mean I feel
like what happened with my arrows I only
have three
left I had so many okay I don't know if
we're really going
to get to kill the boss cuz like I need
to prep for
it
h yeah know I've been spamming them cuz
why not I love using the
um
crossbow but finally we took the stupid
cocky penguin down
The Audacity Of that penguin I
swear more arrows ah yeah cuz like they
the Vixie would
um produce it right let's
see Justice
served mhm yeah the free shot bow I know
it uses um one Arrow
per pew
[Music]
pew there Iris doesn't seem to have a
Vixie
out look at this cute single solo
[Music]
chicken I have to rescue
it come with me oh
hey hey oh a feisty
one come
here do not
res it wants to show me how strong it
is okay 100% you can't say no to that
there you
go yeah I still only have seven out of
really that's
surprising yeah I got
like 13 13
arrows
M oh no not that oh no I kind of need
the or actually I appreciate that
is there some some wheat on the ground
no
no ah yeah I got the wait so with the
wheat even though I don't have the seeds
can I can I get seeds from the
wheat go up to bi base yeah let's check
does she have a Vixie out we need some
arrows
you can buy
yeah but I don't want to go to the shop
um that's so far
away uh be base W house w box W in the
Box actually there's so many places
taken they did not not take the one
space that I used to use in my solo play
throw so we could have taken it oh dear
yeah no I'm not going to walk into
that oh that's not what I need oh look
at all these juicy plump eggs
damn wow what are
you pretty blue eyes white dragon great
I will never know the name
oh more eggs she's got so many eggs what
with this dude what
happened starving yo beu your body is
starving is that how you treat your
buddies oh oh look at the no the grenata
is not grinning
anymore I should
adoped this one's also crying everybody
oh my god look they all feel like
a sorry I'm so sorry so sorry so soor
sorry sorry that's by
accident but they look so
sad get
[Music]
him oopsie sorry
uh
[Music]
no
cute
cute mine my chicken will you be
[Music]
my chicken
employee
yes oh my God I'm so
happy one more yeah then we got
10 anyway I should go back and put some
arrows into the
[Music]
queue
oh
Spears
[Music]
arrows
okay I could make a spare too let me
make that really
quick not enough beds
ah don't
worry
going to
extend
the
mat
Paradise mattress
[Music]
Paradise
maybe it's not a good idea
to go fight the boss I don't know what
do you think can I manage the boss now
that I fought the I fought it before but
I don't remember what level I
was
easily with the right uh Pals for sure
you can set ground like Earth or
whatever it's called
here yeah okay also that that that fish
would be
perfect but it's only level three and I
don't want to level it
now big monkey can do it give me my
Green
Monkey D how and gumos could help yeah
yeah in case that one dies yeah for sure
I'll bring him back
up
[Music]
mhm okay who can make this for
me
uh
kativa
help
anyway uh let's see you guys are
officially retired for
now tany can stay wait that's uh okay he
has sand blast but it's
not the right element just the attack is
but the the pal itself isn't but we'll
bring the dire
how no wait that's
normal oh you you'll come anyway I guess
and the rash
or monkey is
good uh here level 12
[Music]
goomas sh by
level
what I
have I have two pretty
high wolves
okay ice I used to also bring
chillet I think it's chill is pretty
strong to I I'll just bring it along cuz
why not there's no nobody going to work
on this who who do I need to throw out
here to work on
it wouldn't kativa work on it come
here help
me
thanks
nice
buil the other ones chill has a Chase of
chance of freezing yeah that's uh also
what I remember it's pretty
good oh any pal of handcraft yeah now
they're doing it but it's going to take
a while I'll help
to acquire yeah let me can I ah can I
not
help
scare
me don't be so
noisy yeah I defeated the
Pengalin we're going to
try
the real
boss h
yeah let's put a new egg in the Hatcher
for
sure which one guys any preferences oh
God I'm
Burning uh I
say electric egg go go go
ow
just going to put it in there because
it's something like
food close
enough
okay how about
this oh two points how
about health and
attack strengthening myself even
further oh the presso wants to work on
it no
no okay I'll do I'll do something so
guys
[Music]
meow I
think today was very very productive in
power
world I overprepared too much no no
no did you see how much I failed with
the penguin
King cuz I wasn't
prepared
lots of progress yeah it was fun getting
back into it 6
hours I think we should end
it and I hope today I can sleep earlier
because like these past days is getting
later and later and later and later and
later oh my
God it's not
normal you can One V one I I'll give it
a try I just want a couple more arrows
how many do I have
now 25
19 here couple
more sleep schedule good boy
yeah I
think what was I even up for last night
so so long what was
I
I don't even know what what I'm
doing yeah I mean I watched D tendle
afterwards and then I chilled with my
cats a little
bit and then I mean at the very end
right before I slept I I found out you
know the artist thing yeah I was I was
trying to get some work
done you know planning some
things I I had some discussions like
work related
discussions
[Music]
yeah yeah time just went by and I I felt
like I I don't want to just dip on the
conversations understand understandable
yeah so tomorrow I'm going to start late
and since it's a member stream it won't
be this
long so I'm hoping I can maybe get
something
done also I mean yesterday again I had
the problem with
like not getting enough sleep then
yesterday I went to the doctor and then
I went to take a nap after that and the
nap was just so oh
good I napped so
long I had such a good nap with my cats
and even when I woke up I like I was so
tired but I forced myself to wake up but
the cats were so
cuddly that we cuddled for like another
hour yeah cat
therapy yeah okay I think I um I will I
will
attempt just want some
Clarity
mm
egg
so going to drop my ore by
putting some into
this and yeah time for victory if we can
actually do this then damn are you guys
enemies oh
no oh so so so sorry that dad had to go
down like this need poison oh yeah did I
not H yeah I got the recipe I wanted to
make a PO
poison
crossbow oh but
[Music]
no I can't do it now cuz it's all
taken you don't need that don't worry
yeah I probably
don't I probably
[Music]
don't okay then let's see if we fail
then they might be done with the
arrows and then we can give it a try
again it's a was it around the corner or
was it that
way was it this way ah up
here
[Music]
y so dire how is my strongest pound out
cuz it's um downgraded to level
damn it I wanted to catch
it I was going to catch
[Music]
it whatever survives you know we can
start with the monkey um yeah 16 is good
too big
monkey big ass monkey let's
go let's
go
wait I didn't uh renew the
shield but it's okay as long as
everything is
repaired if we fail we're going to make
the new Shield as well
but I I just had the basic Shield as
well and the first time I did
this ow wait
[Music]
pal easy easy this is going to be so
easy it's going to be so
easy what if I head shot the
girl
uh-oh Tan's attack is highly effective
oh yeah this is this one I remember
this easy I'm I'm
chill it's not my first time in this
rodal oh
[Music]
H nice oh yeah he's doing that again oh
nice
blast you're blinding him
beautifully oh but yeah the thing is
there's also a time
limit you really got to have a big
damage
output keeping it cool though yeah
oh I think I also had like the
flamethrower going for me the first
time that was pretty
helpful but we'll see was there uh-oh
what a freaking
stalker
oops ooh did it just turned night damn
it's so dark you're doing great thank
you you can do it that you win for your
sleep
yeah do it for me not for her can I hit
the
arm I'm not don't want to risk it oh
he's stuck ooh stay stuck I I'll gladly
have you stay
stuck oh yeah oh I think it's
stuck
uhoh
a
oh got to just always keep uh The
Shield up give it time to recharge uh-oh
oh she's so wet e
woo T still doing super well oh
oh
let's go
pansy oh he's so aggressive he's so
aggro on
me just like Dark
Souls nice Pink
superjet Monkey screams
you and me are very alike Mr
tany Nice we're oh we're past half let's
go ah first damage didn't have enough
time to recover The
Shield too bad but we're
good
yeah he's busy with the monkey are you
uh-oh he's got it out for
me monkey
beam
Tiara Tiara In Action
Baby
Woo uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh tany got his argro do
something
thank you Shield oh he was he really
wanted me to have that
one sharing is scaring we share the
damage we share the pain we share the
EXP don't look at me like that don't
look at me like
that 5 minutes
left
y y help me Dy oh okay yeah that's fine
that gives me some time to
[Music]
escape
uh
run run run r
[Music]
y
don't want to look back he's surely
behind me oh no he's in ah
okay nice shot from behind nice mud
shot almost
[Music]
there where is he
okay oh
what are you doing here
KY oh did did he just do the red laser
thing he didn't even aim for
me
oh yeah boss eliminated
easy good job Monkey Business let's
go
y first
try I didn't no
chest
okay was there no chest
reward
[Music]
defeated cheers for ra sleep schedule
tutorial done open oh check the survival
guide
okay
thanks y'all we did the tutorial as
[Music]
well everybody's
sleeping while I just did the coolest
thing
ever 6our
tutorial oh how's this
going what do we want to get something
new oh this one yeah I know this one
New
Egg verdant
egg okay depress is still awake well
that pretty suitable that matches the
presso the darkness inside of him keeps
him
awake understandable what the is
going on here nobody taking care of this
mess o o o o
o
okay
y God that was so much fun even honestly
even when I don't get much from the
online um aspect I still really really
really really really like playing this
even
solo so I think I'll I'll do it again
next
week maybe until next week I can also do
something off screen and
then maybe I'll get up to level 20 and
then we can do some stuff with narissa
or goba and whoever is up for
it how's that
sound Maybe not maybe not the ingots are
too
precious oh nice those are
done
not a
hold sounds
good okay that was really
fun I had so much
fun
y SK so much food they'll never run out
of
food membership renewal let's go
I'm glad you had fun I hope you guys had
fun
too and tomorrow we're going to have a
little private session just you and me
guys members
only the is that
no hey y new pal let's go that one looks
so cool what the hell why do you look so
cool don't
run
wow don't kill it I'm trying to not kill
it don't worry uh I'll take I'll take
out my
bat just like
Ichibon oh the merchant is
here okay
44 oh they're looking at me so
angry oh we got it if you find nox here
in your bedding you should leave it
where it lays and leave immediately
picking it up is a one way ticket to a
never- Ending
night what it uh under the assumption
that that KNX does not belong to me or
what nice
lore okay okay I have have this problem
again I can't even stop playing the
game I had this spare animation why it's
fine you know what I'm just going to I'm
just going to um
[Music]
quickly oh just um a little bit
of or
collection yeah we're super caught up
with super chatos so I think I'm going
to leave you guys just like this
yeah feels very awkward to me H the
animation H is that not how you would
use a
spare that's fine go to bed yeah I'm
going to make a pizza and then hopefully
I'll be tired soon
enough if I keep playing yeah I think
generally just me putting it on my
schedule uh just you know playing on my
own will maybe
no alert others that the server is still
being used and they are welcome to also
use it it's just like a little bit of a
mind
manipulation thanks for the membership
welcome try melatonin oh I haven't taken
melatonin in a long time I don't even
know if I still have
them oh it's almost done we should check
it out last thing for today check what
that is
let have it six five four three two one
Miracle of Life and
de floppy a new one I know this one too
though floppy floppy
floppy eh did I pick it up eh eh where
did it
go huh I can't see
it where' the back
go wait never mind it just
automatically like yeah
yeah
okay oh there it
goes am my dad
hungry okay there goes my
food
ah oh what are you doing in my home
hey get out of
here do you have some wheat
seeds wait why why do I have no
money I used still have more
money it doesn't have seeds anyway
where's my money did he steal it catch
him
um I don't
know uhoh
uhoh guys I never learn I never like I
mean that
yeah the moment I hit him I was like
wait a moment if I do this
then one day one day I will catch a
human uh yeah
one
day today is not the
day not today not
[Music]
today okay I I I I I have to end
this I could play this forever there's
like no end to it
[Music]
man your Mone is in the chest next to
the Rocks why did it go
there oh
well but K you've already caught me but
no you're a chicken you're not a human
it's almost 2: a.m. here k please well
this is
normal this is just
normal yeah this is I mean what I
explored today I kind of already saw
before so I really am curious about like
the rest of the world world and the rest
of the
pals no I want to catch them
all what is this why did I put that
there I don't remember that must have
been an
accident okay my mouth and my jaw and my
cheekbones hurt from talking
so thank you so much for watching and en
jman we say
suspense what do we say guys oh you
already
know how do you
know damn you know everything don't
you don't you wish your girlfriend was
hot like me don't you wish your
girlfriend was a freak like me don't
you a
nothing remember to raid what do you
mean what I what raid what
[Music]
home Oh I thought you meant RA in the
game I'll see what I can do have a nice
day
bye-bye
[Music]
R
Legends can I just uh log out yeah right
Al let
me maybe
some
[Music]
attack return to
title wing
YouTube is acting up
again
[Music]
what oh her thumbnail is so
cute he no
start
[Music]