I wonder if I'll become a big soul someday. I'm
drawing the outline of myself strongly and strongly. Everyone
jumps out and
shows me the mighty water in the daytime.
Together with today's tears, I've
come out many times and talked about the future with you. Let
's go together.  Let's walk next to each other
10 times 8 times 000 times I
'll keep trying I still have something I can't read I'll keep
thinking, thinking, thinking and finding it I
want to prove that I'm unique,
right?  Now, in this place where there is no hope, I
still want to believe in hope, even if I won't win even if the song is small.There's
no meaning in me meeting you here, right?
Before I feel like I'm about to do something dark and gloomy, I
'll just keep wandering around.  I'm
playing the rhythm with you who never sleeps. I'm enjoying the reversal. Even if I stumble or
get hurt, I'll start again from here. Even
if I'm clumsy or small, I'll sing the song and
keep going. It's a clear,
cloudy sky. I pictured
your
smile now as if it were a canvas.  Even if I say it in words, I'm sure it's
not true.I'm shy, but I'm flirting.I
don't want to hide my feelings.It's
not like that anymore.
[Music]It's
not vague.These feelings are wrong.
No, cut your fingers.
[Music
] Hello, hello, meow. [Music]
Hello, hello, hello. Hahaha. Chaos.
Hello, everyone. In other words, what's going on
here? I don't know what's going on here.
Thank you very much for planning to attend the Hololive Sports Festival 2023 eve today.
No, there are a lot of people. It's a huge number.
Today, I'd
like to enjoy the all-night festival with you all.  This is a
gathering where we can have fun while also practicing,
so please
take care of us. Thank you very much. Thank you
very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very
much. Okay. Well, I'm going to say hello one by one.
Okay, I'm going to say hello today.  It'll
take about 30 minutes. Is it okay to have a dog?
Yes, it's okay. I'm going to go ahead. There are a lot of people today,
so those who are participating today are the
flyers. If you press the tab key, you'll see the members who are participating.  That's
amazing.
31211414+14
means 27 people gathered together.
So, today we're
going to play with the new implementations for the first time,
do Holmen hunting, and have a little
fun with 27 people.  I've been thinking about doing a lot of things, but
today I'm going to talk to all the listeners who have
n't seen me playing, so I'm
thinking of doing a little hunting.  Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it,
yes, please. This is the best. I'm sorry that it took so long to finish. I feel like I'm sorry, but no, no, let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Jami-chan,
please follow me here.
[Music]
Look at me, look at this
Subaru. Is this Subaru cancer? I get
it. We should get along
after all. We shouldn't get along. No, it's not you. It's you. You
look like Soda, you're beautiful.  Hey,
Sakura
's, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I do
n't want to use it.
Erase it. Erase it. That's great
. It's
amazing, but Saba-chan left it in a state where it could be erased. I don't want to erase it. I was
worried that if I erased something like this, it would affect the system, so I couldn't erase it.
Even if it was incorporated into the system.  Okay, there's a button, so what are you going to
do? Miko-san, put out the button.
Hey, everyone. This time, we'll start with the red team. Let's
play with the red team. Well, let's try to
balance each of them. The
number of people gathered together.  I don't think so, but I think there are
too few whites,
too few yellows, too few reds, etc. It
doesn't really look like it, so I guess it's fine.If that's the
case, then there are people who go home hunting for the red team.  Yes, it's
coming out. Yes, it's coming out. I
forgot to mention that it's not red. By the way, I'm sure some of you
have already gotten it, but there's a book on the
desk. Let's
go back to where we were before.
Yes, this is it.Here it
is, everyone.Please stand there and head towards the school.I
made this file, so I'm
sorry that the en version is not yet available, but I hope the GT members will
support it.
Okay, okay, see you Holmen. The
hunting rules are that each team will select 6 people.
Yes,
it's a 2nd game, so there will be 3 people, so there
will be 6 people. Yes,
ok, then the red team will be the first hunters.  I think we'll
just decide on a group of six people and get them together.Okay, okay,
what's up with Boychat?Let's say goodbye.I
think we'll be a little divided between red, white, and yellow.I'm
sure it'll be crowded.The red group will stay like this for a
while.  I want you to stay and go to Bochit, who has been designated as a yellow year.
Naime
Hello
Ede
Kinpika's yellow Kinpika Nene's yellow Katsu yo
Yellow Who is the one who will do his
best Abelbebe-chan is that right?  Mr.
Kado Makiwatari,
potty polka, Mr. Anya.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. All other
people, please enter once.
All other people, please wait outside the venue.
Yes, yes, this is it, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, we
have entered. We will go with these three people who entered,
let's go, do our best, do our best. This is Holo. It will test how
well you know the live members. It's exciting.
If you use your head, you have bread, you
have bread, you don't use your head, you have bread, I think it's more passion than head,
right? It's
yellow, so it's passion,
right? It's yellow, so it's passion, right?
It's mental and physical passion. It's mental
and physical passion.  So,
is it mental and physical passion? I've always wanted to ask
Menpassion. Last year, Hua
said it was mental and physical passion,
but yeah, it's not a plagiarism.
Noisy. What you mean by
noisy is that they're trying to take back mental and physical passion. I see.  It's so
true that the people who try to make people understand things like this have to try to understand. By the way, do you understand the rules? Everyone, the rules are completely false.
When the game starts, the
person who turned into a demon will be warped to a point in front of that friendly white statue over there.
Those who follow the theme will be O Yellow.The
first match will be Okay,
sorry Yellow.I did it, but it's okay.
Oh
, yellow, 6 people have already entered.
3 yellow. This is the first one, so 3 is fine.
Okay, 3 people have entered. I'm sorry. I
just came to ask where it starts with hunter. Yes, that yellow one.
Okay, let's make it look like yellow, yellow, and then white.Okay, let's go ahead.Asasu is going to
be a fugitive.Here's a fugitive.Everyone is
going to press a little hole to put in the fugitive.I'm going to wait a little while.
Yes, please, please, ah, yellow member here. Do you want to
wait in the audience seats? No
, here, here
, here,
Paki-sama-chan.
Neither Sawa nor Polka nor I are here. Both cottons are flying polka pigeons, so if we
start, we'll start.  Then it is
automatically Ouro, yes, yes, yes,
but this is what I sometimes become an escape.  That's
right, sometimes I'm the one on the run.Oh, yeah, yeah, that's right.The only members I have decided on are the members who will be on the run, but all of them participate.Yes, the participants themselves are on the run.At the beginning, I'm on the run.
Yes, the initial volume is the initial volume check, the high initial volume, the initial volume check, the initial volume check, the initial volume is 200%.  You're the one who's going to
catch it, so you do
n't have to enter. Yes, you
know what it's like to catch it? If you
touch it, it's going to catch it.
There's this. This person's lead is given to them,
so this person who catches it has to hold the lead.  For example,
if you see something that looks like a praising ear, you can
go to the place that says it's got ears, hit this leash,
pull it, pull it to that friendly white statue,
press the sign, and you
can contain it.  My cousin Rick,
do your best, try your best, try hard, start, try hard,
start, it's starting, it's going to start,
we're on the side of running away, okay, we're going to
catch the red guy.
Nice, nice, take me, take me.
Hey, it was
n't red. I guess Aki wasn't red.
That one failed. I'm going to catch one of you. I'll
catch you. There
were two people standing there.
My name.  is the person whose name is red, the person whose name is red,
that's it, the name is red, the name is red, the white and white
group is now the white group, the white and white group, the white group, the white group, the white
person is white.
Push the sign, right, then you
should be able to
expropriate it.The white one is okay, the yellow one, the white one.  It's all
over because I'm a red person, right now, because I'm a white person. I'm coming over here. I
'm on top of a yellow and white pillar. I'm
missing someone from my group.  If we catch our friends, we'll catch them, right?
Wait a minute,
there's a good chance this is a one-shot mistake.  I
want to enter, but yeah, I
think it's okay. It's fun if you catch a lot of people. They
say it's a story. Oh,
stop it. I can't catch a polka.
Okay, this is over. I just wanted to try it out. But the topic is temporary.  There's a possibility that you might touch it. That's the
clothes you caught Nofu in. Hehe, I
was looking at you from above, and it
seems like if you pull the leash too hard, it will
come off. It seems like you can run away. Ririka, you should run away
as fast as you can.  Let's run to the other side.
Reverse this or redo this. This
is practice, so let's
move on to the next one. Okay, so let's move on to the next one.
Next time, Subaru and the others will be on the run, so
please turn to the fugitives.  A fugitive, a fugitive, but the white group has
n't entered. That's it, the white team is
red. Not all of them. All of them. Next, red is
on the catcher side. I
see. I see. I see. I'm getting beaten up.
Please stop it. If you hold the rope well,
go left, right, left, right.  Right and left,
maybe Pol, maybe I'll participate as a runaway, that's right, that's
right, that's
right, that's right.
Thank you for your hard work.I'm
tired and tired, so I
don't have a yellow team for now, but I can do something.However, I'm tentative, and I'll
say how many centimeters it will be tomorrow, or something like that.  I heard that
there are times when you can catch the wrong person, but
the point is, if you catch the wrong person, you can't catch it.The point is, if you catch the wrong person
and touch the signboard, you'll say, ``No,
it's not the same thing, but it's ``Yeah, yeah, yeah!''.  I
can't get into that situation.Is it okay to lie and say that
I'm not like that when someone is chasing me
?Oh, I
can't lie anymore.2000What
year did you debut as that data?  Now that I
'm still here, I
can't say a lie to confuse the person in question.I
can't even tell a lie, but that's probably why the voice chat is
n't connected, right? It's likely to provoke the enemy.That's right, I
can't connect, so my voice won't reach you.  Good
evening, it's about time to start Yes,
run away, run away, let's
go, I'll do my best to make sure I don't get caught, I survived.  Do
n't be afraid, don't do it anymore, do
n't take
it. Hold on and catch this fish.
Run to the other side.
All the catchers, the safety guys, all the guys. It's better to get in the way and run into the other side.
Okay, Kaori, aren't you too smart?
Let's go hit the window. White is
trying to catch me right now. Oh, that's right. It's
not red, it's red. I got caught by red. Seriously,
I'm yellow.  Good money, money, are you serious? It's true, money. It's too
expensive just now.
Why did you get arrested?
[Music]
Hey, money. I got arrested too. I'm
holding you up. The whole store can see it, but you've got big, smiling legs. Oh, I'm wandering around, and Ari Iris is also kind of sexy.
If I'm squatting down the window, I
can't hear anything sexy on the other side. It's okay to play sexy, or
wait a minute. I've
realized that the festival is genius. If I catch it and squat down, I can't hear it anymore,
so it's gone.
Yeah,
what, what, what, shift,
shift, crazy time.  It's dangerous, it's dangerous,
run away, run away, run away, run away, run away, run away
, run away, it's dangerous,
run away, it's red and red, so we won't catch you, Sora-
chan, it's okay, Sora-chan, you're so bold! What's this?  Teru Teru Koko Ake
ran away. It's
okay. Everyone survived.
Survivors are the only survivors. But they
haven't been able to catch them at all. They're not very good. They're not very good. They're pretty
tough. Kanae,
this is going to be difficult.  Hey, Sui-
chan, hey, I guess he was a
genius. I don't care if he's a genius. It's true that he
hit it repeatedly. The polka wasn't good because he hit it repeatedly. Hey, he
hit it repeatedly. Don't you
miss it? He didn't, he hit it repeatedly.  I
didn't get it right, right? I don't know. I'll
definitely try it again. Enter the escapee. I understand. Did you get it? It'll
come out right away. I thought I pressed it, but I'll
press it again. Yeah, I'll see.  Oh, it's here, it's done, it's
done, it's done, Sora-chan was really bold and ran all the way to the center, right? It's totally okay, I can
afford it. Seriously, I can afford it. I'm not feeling
passionate.  If you did that,
people wouldn't think you're an idiot. No, it's
probably just the money.
That's the only thing that caught everyone.
[Laughs]
Hey, what's going on? Seriously,
put me in charge of the idiots.
Please do your best.  Makoto is also like a cat, yes,
but when that shift happens, I can't see the colors.
Makchan did a genius. It's banned.
It's not a prohibited card. No, there's a chance that I won't be able to do it tomorrow. Let's
go, Iris. It's really anti here.  It
's really safe here, it's the red team, so let's
go and take a nap.Let's erase the colors.Let's erase the colors.Everyone
squats down.You'll
get caught.As you walk, you'll be near the bridge.You're
really squatting down, everyone is like that,
Sora-chan.  It's okay if it's hard to understand. It's hard to understand when you
crouch. If you're messing up, you're wrong. You're doing something really, really, really good. You're so beautiful. Which one was doing something good? What's that? When I was catching you, I was like, oh, here.
Squatting
down, squatting down, my senpai was in a lot of pain. I was squatting down. I
'm behind that one in the crowd, but what is this? What
do you call this white one
? White one,
white, yeah, yeah, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here,
right here, clouds.  When I was using a string,
I got caught and did what Mi-chan did.It's hard to get
caught.I mean, it's hard to get caught, or rather, if you're used, no matter how much you pull or pull, I was
taught to be very stubborn, so I
got caught.Stop it!
Oh, but Sara-chan is running away So-chan,
this is amazing, I thought this is
it, but this is it! This is amazing, she's running away. It's amazing, but she hasn't found out. Maybe she hasn't
found out. It's dangerous, it's dangerous, no one should move. It's
okay, Rika, please help me.  Wow, it's
a fever, run away, it
's hot, yoshi, yoshi, you're caught too, Mr.
Polka. It looks like you've managed to escape.
This is what Mr. Polka has devised, a sure-fire way to win.
Please go and do it yourself, Mr. Polka, in the clouds.  I just
had to get in there, right? I crouched down and waited.
That guy was too troublesome, so I got put off
and the other guys got caught,
so it might not be a good idea after all.
Oh, I see. The yellow group is the one with all the clouds.  It's because of Noito It's
so confusing, Ririka.
If you say things like paying money, you're lying. It's dangerous. It's
like an in-cap play.
Kiplay is pretending to play. I think I'm going to be played,
so I hide and sneak.
About the play, Miasu-
chan, I'm sorry.
No, it's totally fine.  Yes, it
was fun, it was fun, it was
fun, and I went home okay. Sora-chan and I were okay. We ran away, yeah, we got caught. He
ran away once, right? He's been drinking. Sora-chan has
been eating and drinking since a while ago.  I'm enjoying it.
Normally, you're eating this much ice. It's like you're always eating ice and then
eating ice again. I was already
on my way, but next time I was on my
way. Sorry, I went to number 2. Let's
get together.  Do you want it?
Yes, I'll move.
Move, wow, wow.  Yes,
the topic is the
same, but in the actual production it feels
like we're going to go through this one more time.Yes,
yes.Ah, the topic is completely different, so we
decided to think about it, so the three of us worked together a little.1
If you want to catch someone, try it with teamwork.Yes,
that's okay later.If you
look at the current balance,
there's a possibility that that tall building might be cut down a little.As you can see,
[music]  I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oro, I'm going to do something with
my partner.Okay, let's do this for now, everyone.I'm
sure you'd like to practice with someone who
has a partner, right?If you have a partner, that's true.Listeners, you're
always listening.  I've already decided on my partner, and that
's right.Yes, I've already
decided, so I'm letting each team decide.Well, I
'd like to do that with that partner, so if I'm the partner, and I'm
the fang, I'll touch that signboard.  Please,
please. No, thank you very much.
Only the seniors are here.
Yes, who am I? Touch the signboard on the polka. I'll
make an announcement on the polka.
How about our team?
First, are the Hasbells team ready?
Well, you see, it's the entry on the left.
Okay, then go ahead and say Black, we're off today.
So Ririka and Sui-chan,
let's go. Let's go up, please. Now, let's go down.  The
people at the bottom who have to touch the sign, the
people at the bottom who don't have to touch it, the people at the top who don't have to touch it.  I
wonder if it can't be undone, wait a minute, I'll ask you.Yeah, I
said that about everyone.Only Shonin
touched it, so Sora-chan should touch it.For
me, I'd like Matsuri and Ani-san to team up.Iris,
isn't it?  Iris, I'm
teaming up with Iris, what should I do?
If I touch it, it's
teaming up with Iris, Pol. I'm teaming up with Iris, and this is it. I'm
sorry, Iris. How do I ride this?
If Sora-chan presses it, it's Col.  There's
someone on top of me, so I think I can ride.Sora
-chan is riding me.I'm going to
ride her.I'm going to touch that horse.There's a horse.Next
time, Sora-chan, I'm going to ride her.
Now, even if I click to enter, I
want to go to this, this, that, that, and that.Who
else is Iris who is not on the team?Iris IrisI
think it would be better to experience it, so
can I ask you to play General Iris today?
I  Wait a minute, so you're on top of Watari-senpai
? That's right, so let me ride on top of a sheep. Well,
this Jigisuka is fast. Whoever is the Jigisuka
did this.
Yes, yes, there is, Iris, Iris, you
can enter the general by
pressing the book.You can open the book and have something in your hand.Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I can
enter the general, but I can enter the general
by pressing the book.
Press the yellow block That's right,
Anya-san, that's it
Anya, that's the
general.  Is it
okay if I ask you to explain
?Yes, I can't see it, so I ask you.Ah,
then Tuvalu can explain it to me.Please,
please, I'll go to the jami.Yes,
this is it.  It's a
game about how many times you can kill an enemy within a few seconds.The
only people you can attack are those on top of you, the ones on the bottom can only move,
and this is the number of people you killed.  Rather, the
team with the most kills comes first, and how many points do you get?It's a
kill point where points are given to the wind.That's
right, but the general is glowing yellow.In
this case, Iris is the general.If the general is
defeated, there will be no king.
So, for example, if the red team
kills a lot and gets 10 points per red team,
but if they
kill Iris twice, they'll add 2 points and
get 12 points, which is crazy.
Whether Iris will come forward and kill them
or not is a matter of strategy.In
this game, even if you die once, you can immediately respawn,
so everyone, it's a game that asks you to come forward and
kill as many as you can.Yes, I
understand.  Please leave
it to me.Also, you have 3 hearts, so
if you are on the verge of death, it would
be more advantageous to go and kill the person with 1 heart.Yes,
there are such things, too.  It
's better to be protected, right? The general has 5 hearts,
so he can withstand it fairly well. I think it's
better to protect the two of us. What's the strategy?
What should we do? Yeah, Rika. At least we're alive.  It
feels like this, but the general
doesn't want to move. I wonder if it's okay if he sticks around with people or something. I keep
asking the general if I should stay behind,
but it's so
hot that it's okay. What's with the heart guy? Sora-chan.
chan, take a screenshot and send it to me.The heart
shouldn't be there.It's
too heart.If I start wrong, the
heart will be small.Maybe now.Oh,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
right.I see.You can change your perspective.Change your perspective.Okay,
change your perspective.  How do I change it? It
's F5. Oh, let's go, let's
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's
hit anything other than yellow. We should hit yellow. I
wonder if there is one. I wonder if there's a combination of yellow. I wonder
if the yellow will decrease.  You can't touch the bottom of each other,
so you can't hit the bottom, or you
can't hit the bottom, so you shouldn't be able to hit the bottom,
so let
's get started, everyone,
do your best.  Attack,
attack, please, attack, attack
[Music] I'm so scared [Music]
Yo
yo
Kekekekekeke It's
scary, scary
[Music] It's
scary There are only 2 left, 2 left There are a lot of people, maybe there are
a lot of people,
where are you?
1 more 1 Hey, there
's only 1 yellow left. I'm
strong. I can't do it now.
That's great. Nice. I
was hitting you with my strong force. Is it
possible that you're strong? I should also say sorry with my bare
fists.
That's great. There's a sword and a shield. That's right. Is the sword stronger? The one with the
longer reach. The reach is
really long. It's true that everyone was
using punches instead of swords, but they were still this strong.
Amazing.  Yoshiru Yorokode Yuu He
really defeated the first one,
but he definitely has the talent of Minecraft,
so it was
n't just Moda, no, he used the sword.Yo,
that house's Lyrica
[laughing]
That's amazing. It's yellow and it's something.  At first, the red and white ones
froze and didn't move at all, but now I'm
going to kill just the yellow one.The
mackerel above is moving, and that's
amazing.There's probably one yellow one,
too.But Subaru is there.  I'm going to support you today,
so is it okay if I come to the red hair?
Yes, please, yes, please, please. If you're
preparing for that, it's a little different from that day.
Yeah,
not at all. I asked if I could do it. Yes, yes. Yes, yes. Yes, yes. Yes, yes. Yes, I'll do it again in 3. Yes, I'll do it one more time, but I guess I'll do 1. I haven't played Soba-chan yet.
So next time I'll be under you? No,
then it's better to have it fixed. I'm sure it'll be good practice.
But if you borrow it, you're already the enemy. Subaru is a lie.
There's no point in saying something like that.
Chana, you're gone, you're an
old man. Ah, Nyaaaa, yes, I'm going to enter. I'm
definitely going to do it. I'm sorry, that viewpoint
was a bit messed up. Yes, it's
okay, it's okay, I'm going to go. I'm going to go.  It's the
most powerful place.
What was the distance? Is it too close or too far?
Hey, kill da killa, I understand. Is
this like playing the general again?
Or is it someone else? That's
fine. Who is the general?  Who
is Su-chan Susuba-senpai? Senpai-ni
Isn't it Senpai Jin-senpai? Yes, I
see. Yeah, I see. Another person who will do it
will try it. What, what, that general, General vs. I will
do it.  I'm sorry, I fell down for a bit. I'll be
with you now, so it's okay to
go home. Then I'll go. OK, OK. OK, OK. OK, OK. OK, OK. Well, I'm
going to freeze up, like before.
This time, I'm going to use a sword. Yes, it
's definitely a sword and a sword. Swords are all swords.  Equipment: I
'm holding a Glade, and I'm saying, "Oh, I
see. It's the first time I've heard of it, so I ca
n't help it. I can't help it. Today is a practice session, right?
Well, which way should we go first?
That's not really the case. I'm going to
cut in. Captain, I'm coming. As expected,
please."  Let's attack and take the back.The
attack red is going red is going red is going red is going red are you
going red oh
ok sha
oh oh oh
oh
[Music]
Danger
Still 1 more to go 1 more to
go 1 more to go at the beginning It's hard to guess
Back  It's really coming.
Red is aiming for me.
Nice. Maybe we should hit him. He's being beaten. He's a
low-ranking guy.
His HP is low.
It
was a shame.
Sora-chan is the strongest. Everyone's strong.
Hey, Red is strong. Even if they're strong.
Sokie.  Tayoshou's general is using a shield, and when he
walks backwards, he grows up again and falls
down.I see, I can't defeat him.I
see.I see, there's no way he's
more arrogant than the general.
Well, it seems like there's no cooldown time for the respawn,
so it'll be respawned right away, so
maybe it's
okay to target it only when the general is scraped by white or red and red.  It's
low, it might be important to look at the HP. It
might be fishing. Everyone from behind the fishing school.
[Music] Is it
going to be a place or has it changed? It's
Nemiko Kohane. I understand.
Thank you very much. Thank you
for not running away.  I can do it with Nieru and Co. I'm
kidding, and it's fun to practice with different teams. If you
want, you can always practice and listen to Harumi, who plays the
role.
Well, today I can press the start button, so it's not at all.
After this, we will practice with different teams.  Even so, it's
okay if you do it. I
think I understand it pretty well. I just have one question. I
had no idea how many kills the general had to kill and whether there was any benefit or not.
But, uh, if the general is defeated once, you'll
get 1 point, right?
Poi, it doesn't matter in the team points from earlier,
but the number of times the general dies will
be added to that overall specific number.  In the final stage, the points that are
added are the same as the victory points for the first match.That
means that the bonus points are
added regardless of the points from the first match.In the
special final, the first place person wins that sushi.  The
team in 2nd place in points will get 10 points, and the
team in 3rd place will get 5 points.
For example, if the team in 3rd place
gets 5 points for the grand prize and kills it 5 times, it's
like 3rd place gets 10 points. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I see. I
see. I see. I see. That's right.
It's interesting. Why is this going to be a little scary? If you can't keep up with it and it's time for the rest of the time, then I'll turn to Gamla. It's not worth it. Yes, that's right, General. Please be careful. Yes, I understand.
So, what should we do next?
Isn't it a good idea to check it once after you do it
? Do you want to
go to the debaku debaku? Yes, I'm going to do it. Or better
yet, I'm English. What are
you talking about?
Hmmm
[Music]
Oh, we're divided into teams. We
still have the equipment,
but I'm sure we have it. We're
still fighting each other. This
is the entry. Split into teams.
[Music]
Please.  Kao isn't doing this event,
but it
doesn't matter which one you want.I don't care about the
festival either.He's a great escort.We're all
here today.We're all here today.We're all
here.Who's the princess?
Who's the princess?Who's the princess?  It doesn't matter who you are, it's
anyone's festival. Iris
is a princess-like Iris, so it's
okay for you.
Iris' friends are definitely going to do their best to kill each other.
But I started practicing properly with that Ririka-chan.
At the beginning, in this part, I
changed the camera to the knights, and if I
walk in a crouched position, they won't fall, so they
won't fall from the back, right? I understand.
Well,
as expected, you said yes, and you
are allowed to change your point of view.Oh, that's okay, too.I've
confirmed it.I
think it's better to change it.Thank you,
but I mean, do your best, do your best, do your best, princess.  Is it
better to do that? Is it
better for the princess to change her point of view? Maybe it's better to change her point of view.
Yeah, I don't know if that's the case,
but Subaru is easy to do,
so I guess I'll change it. Yeah, I see.  It's fun to try this by people
What should I do to equip the Subaru line? Well then,
let's get Subaru. The middle part of the game. That's probably the middle part of the game. It probably won't disappear. Please take this with you. I'll take whatever you want, so Subaru,
please keep it.  I ca
n't drop it.I can't throw it.I can't throw it.I can't throw it.I'll
tell you later.Do your
best, work hard,
but also,
princess, princess, do your best, there's a block on the book.
Yes, yes, even if I log out, I
can't hear it. I can't hear it. I can't hear it. Do your best.
Get off, get
off, get off, get off.
Here it is. One more time.
Oh, red, pink,
pink, pickle,
repiredo.
Redna That's good. Hurry up. Hurry up here. Well,
knights shouldn't talk. Knights shouldn't talk. Oh,
but it's okay to be there or something.
Princesses can talk. Princesses can talk.
I'm talking, so everyone nods.  I do
n't have that or that, but I can just shake it.Uh,
press the E button.I
see, it says this, so it's a refrigerator.I wonder if that's
what I mean.Is it a refrigerator?
Click on it.  Click
on the book and it's nice, nice, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, ok, what's the other one?It starts with white again, do your best, ok, lyrica, ok,
this is ok, tomato, that's ok,
tomato, apple, paprika.
What's that? Matsuri Matsuri Senpai is amazing. He's
nodding. Oh, but it's a little strange to nod.
So I'll check until the actual performance.
Nice paprika. Ah, I'm hungry.
Um, yakitori and, uh, Subaru's fried chicken.  I
want to eat yakitori Subaru's fried chicken Suru
's fried chicken The way to make fried chicken is written in an ice cream book.
Grilled chicken Subaru's fried chicken is raw chicken,
Kako Subaru-senpai, and uhm, flour
and oil, so it's really Subaru's fried chicken.No, no, stop
it, stop it, stop it, how many pieces of chicken, I
didn't write down how many pieces I wanted to eat.  I cut
each fried piece one by one on a chopping board.Well, I
also cut the flour.I
watched it like a director on the cutting board.After that, I
put the chicken and flour oil in the chicken and I
want to eat it.Now, I want to eat the pieces I
just cut and the rest.  I
don't have all the oil in it.It should be sold as oil.I'm
sure someone has it.Someone has it.I'm
going to put it in the pot.  Okay, you can drink oil. I
drank it somewhere and it
disappeared, but please go ahead, Mori
Mochi. Maybe that's what I dropped, and that's
it. Other than that, I haven't written anything else.
Then I'll eat it.  My name and name are
Suru, and it's fried chicken.
It's true. It's true. It's really true.
Thank you very much. Eat it. I'm
not kidding. Eat another one. Yes, it's
okay.  Okay, okay, uh,
tell me the color. The upper right is
red. The upper left is pink. The lower left is also
pink. I don't know the lower left, the lower right.
Please tell me the color. Yellow. I think it's yellow. It's yellow.
Yes.  Early yellow, uh, yellow, yes, no, no, no, no,
no, it's time for killing, killing. It's time for time to kill. Let's do it.
Press the button button. Yes, yes, okay. Let's go. Let's
do our best. We'll
defeat you. Do
n't kill us that long.
Iris, Iris, try blowing that horn,
that horn, I'm forcing you to blow that horn, no matter
where you went now, you're hiding here and there.If you
need to recover, please go.  It's
coming out, it's finally coming out, be
careful, be careful, hide nicely,
do your best, stop it, it's close, hit it, hit it, show it you're good.I said that my
HP hasn't decreased at all.Where is that?
Is this on the top left?  Yes, yes, yes, yes, no, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's do our best, let's beat it.
Princess Isu-Princess is so overbearing Why is
this the first princess? Oh wait, this is a princess and Iris-Princess Princess
I just heard it.
Princess What do you mean? Princess? This princess is the
Japanese of the warlords.  That's the Japanese princess. Is
there really a Japanese princess? Yes, I
thought it was good or bad,
but it was amazing. There really is a princess with a strong fever.
That's what I mean.  Just
keep it up, the princess is really good. That's
right, that's the princess. She feels strong and
different. Wow, the time is 5 minutes. There's quite a difference
. Look, the yellow team still has room to grow.
So, here it is, practice.  I did, I can shrink it even more, I think I
can color it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's
practice, so I'm only going to practice after this, so I'm going to
change the server to 2 again.  I'm
here!
Iris was a princess and was in a good mood,
so she started being called the Netsuhime, and everyone was
hot. I think each of them had
added that new cooking menu,
but Subaru's fried
chicken.  I was surprised that it wasn't fried, right? There were
pancakes that looked like special hamburgers. Yeah, that's nice. Oh, I want to eat that. I'm
going to cover everyone up.
The voice is
like this, yes, it's okay to do it at all,
but yeah,
everyone is doing a lot of follow-up now, so I want to take a
look at it.
There's
only one person, and now there's someone flying really fast. I'm
going to Chocochi.
What's wrong with Chocochi? What's wrong? It's
okay. It's okay. I
wonder if they'll suddenly make me [ __ ] again. I
suddenly say, Wait, wait.
Sorry, I'm sorry, there are
people who want to practice, and I
also want to practice, and I
want to practice.  It's
okay,
I saw that you can do it once with no limit to the number of players.I
want to give it a try and try it once.I
think there's only one red player.I can't do it today.I ca
n't do it today.  There are three of us, yeah, there are three of us, who are we?
Chiara
Let's Go now and Tsui-chan. It's the
same as the actual performance. Maybe, but the actual performance
is the same.  I
went to a different server,
but I think it's okay to split up into groups. I
feel like if I cheer for them, it'll get messy, so I guess it's okay to
split them up into groups and go to that match. The
members who are going to play are number 1. I think it's
okay to call them number 1.  Please move to your turn. I
can't hear everyone's cheers. I
want to do it while listening. It's
okay for me to play as a team. It's okay. Let's play as a team. Yes,
yellow, yellow, yellow,
do your best. Yellow, I'll
do my best. I'll do my best.
Sora-chan is staring into space for a long time. Is it
okay? Sora-chan's intensity is like Su-chan from earlier, and she wants to watch it with me. Sora-chan is acting like a contagion. If you do that, you'll become better.  I'm going to be an infected person,
and I'm going to take it.
Do your best, star, do your best, do your best, do your best, hurry up.
[Music]
Hurry up, everyone, go ahead, senpai
Do your best, don't let God look at me,
and do your best in the water 20  It's really fast, but
it got interrupted for some reason. I
can't do it all over again. I can
play again and again. I'm
starting to have enough energy. I'll play with you first, after all. Nasui-chan.
Yeah, I was using my legs until just now, so I'm
sorry, I
'm sorry, I don't know what you're talking about, but I'm going to use my fingers.Maybe
someone pushed me, or maybe I did something.
Do your best, Mizu-senpai, do your best, do your
best, yes, do your best, go up like Mercury, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up, go up like Mercury.If you want to see how it is,
go to the cat's spectator mode.Press on the cat's purple
board.Are
you okay?  Good luck, nice, nice,
good, good, this is fast, it's going well, it's
fast, it's fast, no, no, it's
okay not yet, I'm still on my feet, that's it, not yet, there's no problem with my shoulder,
okay, Kiara-senpai, did the a go up because everyone fell down?
Kiara-senpai is good, but this  Finally,
where are you? Yeah, finally, where are you
? It's
okay, tomorrow. It's okay, Su-chan, first one. Let's
go to the checkpoint. First of all, let's have a stumbling block. Ha,
Ceci. Let's have a chat. Everyone is right
.
So, what did you eat today?  Hey, I'm
sure it's good. I ate a hamburger. What did you
eat?
I ate mackerel. Let's
go calmly. Let's
go calmly. Who should we go to? A-senpai is stable. Oh
, okay. But we're catching up, so
yeah, there's not that much of a difference.  There's no difference.
This isn't a competition. That's right.
Where is this? Which one is last? By the way,
Sui-chan, if you touch the Bet
on the right side, hey, that's it. If you touch the right side, yeah, yeah, if you touch that, you'll
be able to respawn.
By the way, the play time is about 6 minutes, so you
don't have to worry about it. It's good, it's only 6 minutes. Did Piala fall? Yeah, it's been a
long time.
In spectator mode, everyone's faces are
floating like death.  It's true that my head is
floating, my head is floating. It's scary. I've
caught up. I've
caught
up
.  Don't
go on the bad route. Nice. It feels good. It's almost there. It's almost there. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's amazing. It's you. It's okay. It's okay. It's important.  It's
okay, it's stopped. How long have you been? I came to the bar. I'm so excited. I just grabbed an Uber. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's
amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing. It's amazing.  It's a lot of pressure, is
n't it? When the two of us score, no, Korehi-chan did a lot of work too, but yeah, he's going to score. It's scary. Ordinarily, he didn't do a great job. It's scary. He did a little bit of that. Yeah, yeah, that's because we have those six minutes.  In
Kyoto, Trident's cooldown time is quite short,
so that's right.I'll have to wait
until today.Okay, can I do it all today?Yes, I
might be able to do it all today.However, there is a
possibility that some adjustments will be made.
Yes, it seems
like it's time to adjust now.Everyone has reached the goal.It's good, it's good, it's long, it's
six minutes long, it's long, it's humid.It's
six minutes long, even I can understand it.It's difficult
without doing this.It's quite unpleasant.  Wow, that's amazing.
Nice, thank you. Nice, nice. I'm nice and nice. Thank you for your hard work. Nice. But it's amazing how much the yellow team likes it. Not everyone. U-chan was amazing. Is this the winner? The
winner, the winner?  There's a lot of pressure,
everyone gather at Anya's place, gather around Anya,
where's this, where's this, do your best, where's it
, do your best,
everyone, do your best, everyone, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best.  Let's do our
best, right? Yes, I
have the equipment of the Fang line. Yes, I have the equipment of the Fang line. I have it for the
rest of my life. Fuwa-senpai, please
do it. Why are you
doing it now? Is it okay to do it
like this?  Don't
do it. Don't do it. Take your hand. Don't do it right away.
Why did you think to do it
?
Hakosu, please help me. It's already just me.
What's scary is that there aren't that many Subaru Yellows
on the team that day.  That's true. That's
true. I
said it, but it looks like it's going to be fun. Looks like
Luff is going with the yellow team. I see. Luff is going with the yellow team. I'm
sorry. There
's still a follow-up person for the yellow team.  I'm sorry, I have
n't entered. Yes,
I'm not in red or white, so I'll
put someone in as a substitute and try again.
Oh,
okay, wait a minute. Then I'll enter. Oh,
then, nya.  Please give me a touch of the soul here. I've
already entered another game. I'm
afraid I
won't be able to enter in that world. I'm
sorry, I'll
wait a moment to see if I can enter.  Well then, I can't do it as an envoy. I'm
playing a game. Ah,
items don't disappear. Items don't disappear. Ah, I
tried entering and exiting. That's right. I
tried entering and exiting once. But I did it earlier. It didn't enter,
right?  I was able to eat without it.
Kaanya doesn't have a horse. Tame-a is the only one trapped in the world of fangs.
Annie and A-san haven't fought yet. It's too
bad. I can't disappear. Help me, but I can't.
If you click on the color signboard, you
can cancel your entry.It's been done.I just tried that.I wonder
if Kiba should go touch the signboard on the line.Yellow.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait, this is the game star. There are no
entries for this or that, but there are
no entries.
Wait a minute, I
mean, I have to enter these three teams,
right? Yeah, yeah, yeah.  That's
what I mean, this is Lyrica Red,
try it, Red, yes, Red, this is probably
Mercury-senpai's entry again, but I don't have a horse,
so I see, so I interrupt the game.I see, but I
can't do it.I
have a trident.  It
was the same thing yesterday. I still have
some tools left. I
still have a hunting lead left.
This is what I did when I was practicing with Ririka in the morning.  That's right, let's
check. This
entry is here. Yes, I entered, and
now I've seen it, so I'm going to press the middle row. I
can't do this. How about this? There are still
books left, though.  It's okay now that it's in the book,
right? Yeah, it's okay, it's
okay, it's that one from Ruhrbok, so it's
okay.  Subaru also
has 41, so I've got 41, okay? I
have 41, 41 of my friends. That statue is already
coming. It's going to come in the middle of the night, and it's going to ask me to
get along with it. It's going to come with my nipples exposed.
This is all pink poop.
Beautiful aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  There aren't too
many tridents. Are you
going to let them point at you? Don't do that. A white statue is coming.
In the middle of the night, there's a white statue. Stop it,
it's angry. It says the game master is angry. The
game master is angry. At least it's coming in the middle of the night.  You're
so scary, do your best, do your best, do your
best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best,
don't do your best.
Ani-san entered once, ok, I won't make it okay, it's scary,
Neka, please get along with me. Scary, Neka, youkai has come, let's
get along. I'm Nakaamaru-chan, but I'm Areru-chan, but that's
not right. There are all kinds of people, so now there are
juniors too.  Were you a senpai? No, it's
okay, do your best, you're good, do your best,
do your best,
do your best. There's a face on the ice cream. I'm glad you
conveyed that it's ice cream. It's nice to be able to tell that it's ice cream.
It's got a ki in it. Still, it's a
face, Nico.  But no, it's
not going to work. I was making it while saying, ``I'm
not trying my best.'' I'm not sorry. Please
do your best with dirty talk. Please
do your best. Do your best with an open heart. ``This is good.'' It's like
when we were practicing.  It's a completely different layout.
Oh, it might have changed. It's changed quite a bit
. There are updates every day. It
's okay. I have
n't lost that much. I have a lot of time. That
's right, it's a cat game. The one I went to the top of earlier is
still strong.  I wonder if it was a person, yes, that's changed,
so I'm confused.In
that case, it doesn't really matter who crossed the finish line first.It
doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.In the end, it's about where you were at the end.I
see.  That's right, the
goal doesn't matter, yeah, it doesn't matter, then the goal is reached, Tarama points, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I see, I see, I
don't see, I see, I don't
have to worry about it, I don't have to rush this game, as long
as I can play it, it's okay to take it slow, my own pace 2, Anisan-ah  Ni-san was
practicing so hard that day.
[Music]
Suwaa-chan and meters are coming out.
That's amazing, that's right, Ni-san is really good.
But, you have that bed, bed, bed,
touch the bed, bed.  I've
already touched it, ok, I should be able to go quickly from the middle, that's
good, that's
right, that's right, that
's right.  It's
going to be in slow motion. That's
what I'm saying. It's slow. It's slow. It looks like it's
out. It's so
weird. I practiced, I practiced, I practiced. Go for it, you'll be fine. Yosui, wow, what's going on now? It's like, wow, it's like now. It's too fast.
That's really good, everyone. By the way,
Chiara is really stable this time. That
's amazing. She got 1 point for the 10m, so I guess that's right. You get a lot of points. That
means you get 20 points.  Oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah 20 points 10m 1
point so yeah 200m is the top right now
20 points is the maximum yeah that's awesome Oh
yeah okay okay we should have a chat or something then
let me know
okay okay don't talk you can say it Not at all not
at all  Please speak
already, what's wrong with you
? I'm listening to you. It's
completely wrong. It
's a complaint. You should practice. I'm
making some adjustments. In fact, I'm doing it.
This is a mess.  I'm
surprised that it's changed, and I'm not looking at the try.
But Anya-san can do it. Thank
you. A-san has already won.
By the way,
Miko
threw a good shot yesterday.  That's why it's so high.
There are a lot of choices around here, right? It's
like adjusting a little when you fall. It's
about 20 seconds after the goal, so it seems like it's
better to go to the highest point.
But on the next bed, too.  The course is different,
so I'm going to make some adjustments. It
's the final one, so
if you can practice this, it'll be as good as the actual one. That's great.
321 So that part is
on the way down.
[Applause]
It's on the way down.  Yesterday I
felt like it was easier to do yesterday,
but maybe it's just that it's more difficult.Here,
if you like,
let's practice together like this.Yes, let's practice.Alright, let's
all go.  After getting that gathering, I think I'll do the
replay once and then do it pretty freely.
[Music]
Well then, I'll leave the voice server as it is.
Either way, I'll go to the rele. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Lille This year, the system is amazing,
and if you are a big deal, it
seems that you will be warp on your own if you are in the order of it,
so it's a bit confusing.  Let's
do our best, it's ticking, it's over there, it's over there, it's the order of the relay.Everyone will be participating
in the relay today.Ah,
not all of them.Well, wait a minute.I
want to give you a name, so let's all
run once.That's good.  Alright, Iris, I
'm here, Iris number 1.Enter,
and Kuro is taking a break, so it's Aako,
Kuro.Ai-chan, Sui-chan, and Kuro will save me.Next, Sora
-chan, sora-chan, please touch me.Where,
wait a second, where is this done
?  Here it is, Sora-chan, there's Sora-chan,
where are you?
Wait a minute,
press this erotic.  So I'm
doing it, then next Lily? Yes,
I haven't pressed it yet. It's okay. This is
the order. It's always okay.  There's no
need to be scared if you have a lot of things. It's
okay. It's difficult because it's practice. It's
harder to do it in the half
without Subaru Shiori. So, okay then, Aji-san, you
can join in with Gran. It's okay. It
's number 8, so it's my first time.  With the glasses anchor,
do your best, try your best, try your best, at first Neuma,
go, go, Hacos, you're amazing, you did the taiko version, Masae-
chan, you're definitely talented at microphones, you keep
saying that, you keep saying that,
the other day, the other day, you practiced the real relay.
Well, it started out really
messed up.It started slow at first, but it started at the end,
but for some reason it ended up being No. 1.It was
amazing, it started so fast.Yano
Kachan-chan is in that book.  Well,
now there are 9 people who have received the book.
Wait a minute,
there are 9 people. There are 9 people.
Entry List I think that the face of the entry list will appear,
but it's amazing, and there it is.
Um, the second operator is Sui-chan,
with a yellow block, and when you open the book, it's like
this. 7 Oh, yeah, yeah.  So I guess it's the
7th, the beginning, the 8th, that's nice.I've been able to
do it to the max now, including for practice, so I see.That
's why it's okay for Ren to ignore it.Hajime will
carry it properly.  Obu
gave me a hug.Once we're all together, we
'll start.Okay, so let's see what's cool.Luca-
san, I'm sorry,
but yeah, it's okay.It turned out the wrong way, but it's
not long enough.
But, you know, seniors and seniors, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, you can ask I-chan 2
to go. Is that what you mean?
After the polka, is it Spar? I
think everyone has entered, so I'll
get the baton.  I think that Iris, that great runner,
has the baton.I do
n't have the baton.All I have is that book.When I start, the baton
appears.I don't have it.Oh yeah, when I
start, Iris will be the first to
hold the baton, so I'll hold that baton.  If you hit the next wheel, you'll
be able to pass. That
means you can just click that left button. Left,
click left,
click. Where is the second person on standby?
Well, this is this. This is here. Now
Subaru can't be seen. I can't see it.  Where is
this?
This is the start, this is the first half, half the bell. Okay, okay, oh, it's here, it's
coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's going to go, it's
going to go to
Eris.  Let's go over there, man
. Okay, it's probably just the beginning.
Jean, it would be faster to jump. Fine, fine, nice, nice.
Show them how cool you are, Alice.
Princess
Tasu-chan is
not a princess.  Isn't it
yet? The
second princess is here. The second papan is
better. The second
princess is waiting. The second princess is
waiting. I can see the princess for about 3 minutes. Jump Jump
Jump Nice. The last jump.
Do your best. Ok. You
're here.  Do your best, it's okay, it's okay
Yes, teacher, it's really fast, Su-chan, do your
best, hurry up, hurry up, yoshiyoshi, 3rd party, do your best.  I'm really
not good at
it. I'm star. Nice star. No, wait in the pool zone. What do you mean? I can't do that. I'm the one who got that wave. Good thing. Okay, okay. Where is No. 7? Do your best, No. 7, do your best. Next time, Lyrica won't be here.  It
's Ririka, but with this steering order, I'm sorry to tell Polka-senpai next time,
but it seems like it's the other way around.I'm really hungry after all this,
but I'm hungry on the way, so I think I'd better eat some bread.  I see,
so I was
n't running. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Eating bread is pretty big. Is it left click
or right click? Well, left left.
Click o. Take it with the right and eat with the left. Oh
yeah. That's right. Nice with the left.  Good lucky
-chan lie quickly, fast, fast,
fast, it's
amazing, I'm really looking at you. I'm seeing the next one. I'm looking good.
Do it, Mentajujika,
dive, dive, dive, the waves are coming, so
Passion,
do your best, I think you're good to go, let's go Mel
Physical Passion Mentally Passionate Mental Passion Passion
Passion Passion Passion
Mental
Funai Passion Nice Passion
Nice Passion  I
can win this, I can win this, I can win
[Applause]
Lili who has been turned down is
okay, OK, OK, stubborn,
OK OK OK.
Seriously,
Rika is good, good, good, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay here, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay here
[Music] It's
already so nice, it's so nice, it's so good, it's so nice, it's so good, it's so good, it's so
good, it's so
good, it's still 1, it's
mental and physical passion, it's
Number One Full Passion  Mental
Physical Passion Mental Full
Passion Mental Physical Passion
Ya, do your best.The
waves of people are amazing, just like in the times.The
narration came from a polka.Okay,
do your best, it's One Piece.One Piece.That's what
One Piece is.Let's go.Tsurerua-san, do your best.Nice, nice,
nice.  I
can eat the bread that's lined up, it's okay, I got the
bread, I got the bread, I don't have it,
papa, papa, I don't have to eat it, I push this, it
's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, I have to eat the bread, but I see,
even if I have the bread.  You can go, you can go, you
can dodge. Okay, do your best, do your best. [Music] I wasn't trying to be nice. Click left and right right now. It's amazing. [Music] Do your best, try your best, calm down. You're good. Fall. Calm down.
Climb. It's up to you.
Ame, you can do it, master.
Ada, it's easy to do it.
Dakayayi, you're so good at it, you've done it. Hey,
what's up with the yellow? There's
finally a chance of winning. There's yellow.
Oh no, there's a chance of winning.
Stop flagging.  I'm sure you're
right, I'm wrong, and I'm
only giving out 20% of the time, so I'll
finish the game from now on. Yellow
team, that's yellow. I'm looking at you, I'm
watching you.  Aso-senpai Ah, this was Sora-senpai
By the way, Mikochi is
doing her best right now. She's doing her best. Looking at her, she's like, Wow, this is amazing. The
waves are working really well. Miko.
Chiminami. I'm listening to the waves.
Oh nice, nice,
na.  It's going to last for a few seconds, so it's going to show
up. It's going to be a long time coming. It's going to be rewarding, isn't it? It's
amazing. Ririka and Sora-chan are fighting each other.
What is this space? It's
too
hot. Youkai Niko.
Tomorrow will be better, isn't it?
What time is it? Yes, we're meeting tomorrow. It's
a little early, at 3 o'clock,
so I'm going to go to the studio at 3 o'clock in Suva, so I'm
afraid I'll be in trouble. Oh, and I'm sorry, I
'm at work.
Around 5:30 p.m.  We'll meet up.Okay,
okay.Okay, okay.It looks like you're already ready for the follow-up.Thank
you in advance.You
can do it tomorrow.Alright, we'll have some
time for that later.Let's chat.
After practice, there are some people who want to practice something. I
thought it would be great if I had a voice or something like that, so I'd like to do it.
There's something I'd like to teach you, so let's
all do a relay together.  Let's master
it, let's master it.First of all,
there's no one who says that the first half is better or the second half is better.But this is it.I already submitted this, right?I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, which one is it?  This is today
's one. Yes, it's today's one. It's not today.
This is the one I posted in the chat. Well, it
changes after all. Even and odd numbers
. Well, that's right. 1 is Ririka 2 Kuni 3 Sora-
chan 4 Ririka Ajau 1 is Iris I'm
sorry.  1 Lyrica,
uh, 5 is polka, 6 is bookmark, 7 is
gram, and 8 is starting. Those who
can go are black, yes, yes, that's right.
Iris Iris, there is a way to go to the place where it falls.  I
want to hear the ice bomb.I want to check it out from the ice bomb.Here,
on the ice.Here, on the ice, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, that's it.He
should run right now.I hit the space as
fast as I can.Wow, I thought he was going to run already.  I
slept a lot with yellow, but I'll do it if I have all of them. Ice is blue, but I'm
practicing
right now, and I've been hitting it so many times. It's
amazing, and I can't even remember what I was practicing just now without even starting.  But
if there's one more race, I'll definitely do it, but I wonder
how different it is from walking normally. Well, it's a bit different, but
it's a bit different from that system. Is it
okay if I don't use it? It's all okay. Okay, I
didn't eat bread just now.  There's a
rule that says you can't eat bread if you don't
eat it.I
didn't eat it either.I don't have to eat it either, but if I don't eat it, I won't be able to recover my physical strength, so I'll
be late.I don't have to eat bread,
but I'm full.  In that case, I
want you to take the pas that you couldn't eat.As for the pas, I think it's
probably better to take them.Yes, I want them.I
can reach the goal even if I don't take them.Yes, yes, that's what I
want.  Well, it's quite difficult.
So you don't have to take it and eat it. You do
n't have to eat it, but it's okay if it's late. I
guess it's a violation of the rules if you
don't eat it. Japan always doesn't take it.  Well,
that's the rule. Yeah, okay, Miko. I'd
like to make it feel like each team is together, but maybe it's a competition that uses a system.
Since I can't move, I
guess I'll just gather the people who want to do it.
Ah, okay, then yeah, that yellow.
If we're doing it here and there's a competition, I'll
ask you to chat and then I'll go over there.
Yeah, okay,
sorry. Please, please, I'll reach you. I'll
do it again. Do you feel like doing this?  Ah, I'm
sorry, I'm just
taking the bread of Lille right now, but I
can't eat it right now. I can't eat it unless I
start that game I can't eat it.
There's snow after that ice spot.
If you do it right, you'll be able to jump over it. Yes, you
can jump over it, you can jump over it.
If your timing is right,
press and hold just the last line. It's like this. It's almost
amazing.  It's so important, that's so important
, so hurry, so, so Iris, it's
true, so if you keep hitting it like I'm told, you'll be in trouble.
That's amazing, the
power of the creative god is this. It's going to
change a lot. I'm sure other teams will
do it.  It's like a spider's nest, and it
's all popping out. It's
amazing.
Maybe a spider's nest is in the middle because it's going to hit you. Where's the best place for a spider's nest?
Tell me, tell me. Where's the cloud nest in the middle?
But, I
But it's fine anywhere, but the
trick to not getting caught is to not go for that
. It's better to go straight at an angle.
Yes, it's straight.
Even when you really turn, it's like turning sideways. Straight.
You see, the cloud nest on the far right
doesn't obstruct it diagonally, so I think you
can just push it straight on the far right.Well, I
think the outer one is better.The inner
one will come in quite a bit, but that's right.  It's
easier to do it on the right side because it's not complicated, but it's faster on the left side.There are
clouds on the left side,
so it might be easier to do it.
In the middle of the day,
which one should I take? Can you please take a look? Please take a video. Who shared the last video?  chan made a real video
and shared it with me.It would be amazing if it turned like this and that.I
thought it would be possible to pass at that diagonal after all, so I
went with the diagonal that worked 100%.  If you
try to pass like this, you'll get caught. You
have to do it like this. You
have to go straight. In Japan, you can
see a moth's web in front of you. If you don't move, you'll get hit. I
see. It's true. After all, they
judge things based on mass.  Minecraft doesn't have any slants.
[Music]
Someone came to help me. Someone please record it and
record it later.
Actually, there is a way to almost get there without bumping into anything.  Is
there a way to avoid hitting the pool pool?
There are three lines here, but if you
go below the bottom, you'll never hit
anything.That's amazing, but the
top and the middle are easy to collide with, so
anyway, go below.  It's sinking and only rises when the bottom comes.If you
go up, it's not that bad.As long as you're at the bottom, it's fine.If you're at the bottom, you just
have to go up.I see, the
sea stone team has come to the sky.This is
amazing.It's amazing, but it's basically anything other than the bottom.  Even if you
don't hit it and hit it at the bottom, if you
push the pace just a little, you can go
up. So I think you can go a little further forward without hitting that much.
Wow, this is great, so based on this one time, it's
stable and safe. It's coming, but it's coming.  But it
's stable. It's true that it's faster to jump at the timing instead of running in the cherry blossom area.
That's a character complex, isn't it? It's
better not to worry too much about jumping.
Maybe the jump dash is the best.  It's fast,
but when I do a camp dash, I often fail.
That's right, I don't know the timing.
Well, I guess when I get to the
stairs, I jump first. After that, I think I can press and hold to continue. Jump. I
think I can press and hold jump to jump to the next one. I'm
doing something like that.  Team, Ron
King, Rohant Hunting. Is
there anyone who wants to go hunting? Hunting is the same for me. Well, yes,
hunting is true, but to be honest, the
problem that day was quite amazing. I see, but the
character of the polka that can be missed by hitting it repeatedly.  I'm a little worried so I
'd like to do it later Ooooooooo Hunting, okay?
I've never done it, but I'm a member,
right? Well, yeah, that's cute. I'm Hunty. I
want to play. Do you want to do it? Alright, Hunting. I
guess I'll give it a try.  I'll
do the yellow one, and then I'll do the yellow one.
This means you can do both. You can catch it, you can do it, you can do it.
Wait a minute. There should be a turn.
Ok, have you
learned how to do it in order?  Once
you decide
who you want to do it, enter
Who will do the hunting? Well then, yellow, I've done it once, so who's going to do the grouping? It's
ok, Hiro hunting, or Hero
hunting. Do you want to go hunting?
Me, I want to come just once, right now.
Wait a minute.  Yes, yellow is good for hunting.
Well, I'll wait for you to answer.
Let's do some yellow hunting. The
other members of yellow, the red team was
quick. I understand. It's
okay. So what should I do?  Okay, first of
all, it's a fugitive. Yes, please press this fugitive. Oh yeah, okay, okay
, let's run as fast as we can. But the color of that name might
be quite important. Don't let it get in the way.  Hidden, you
can tell by the jersey, can you tell?
I don't know, I don't know if it's the upper jersey.
People who don't have the upper jersey might not be able to tell. It's true that if it's short sleeves,
then tomorrow, I'll wear short sleeves and a different jersey. Jersey. I think I'm
weaker without the sleeves. Let's do that. It's
cute.  However, the jersey
is really easy to understand.It's true that it's a jersey, but it's
cute, but it's easy to understand.The one with the
blue on it and the shoulders sticking out.But
that kind of appearance is important, and it looks heavy.  It's
certainly fashionable, so it
might have been a title for the second half that wasn't changed.It's a one-shot, which is really
bad.However, it's not red that gets in the way of red, so if you were behind the scenes that red did in the first place, you'd be found out.  It's not like I'm
becoming a genius or anything,
but I can outwit someone who can open up to me. It's true. There was someone hiding in there. No way, I was caught, but it's normal. Well, I was
arrested, but it's not true.
Yesterday, I played a polka and was very strong.Here I was, crouching down in the clouds.We were all there.We all got along, and this cloud on the right side of the statue was very strong.  Even though the group was doing it, they had
to catch the red group, so it was zero.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, what's with the yellow group? It's cute. It's cute. That's nice. There's no white group,
but there's no white group.  So, I do
n't think it's a group, right? I
guess it's a princess, and it's definitely a princess. How long will I keep calling her a princess
?
Look at my brother. Next, I want the yellow person to get caught on
purpose. I'd like to try it out. I'll see
how hard it is to get caught.  It's
probably the cage on the side,
but I can't stand it, so I
think it's better to be in the back, and the string of clouds in the back is
better, so it's in front of the cage.  But it's
not okay, because I'm so close here on
purpose, here in the back, here in the back, yeah, are you
practicing?
Hey, I
'm in a
crazy place. It's like a constellation. Everyone's like a cloud. They're
only doing data. I'm
so sorry.
Oh, it's okay, I'm sorry.
Thank you,
Akio. Please. See you tomorrow.
Please. Thank you. I'm sorry. Passion
power, passion babae.
Passion power mental and physical. Passionate mental and
physical. Mental and physical passion. One more
time. Red.  I wonder if it's better to do that
. Well, one more time, please use the yellow fugitive entry.
Yes, yes, yes, entry. Okay, entry. Okay, tomorrow.
Excuse me.
Everyone on the white team, it's yellow.
Sorry, my red
team is still here.  I still don't understand the action of touching with a rope,
so can I just interrupt the first half and practice just the first half
?
Oh, right-click, then left-click.  It's the one that
excludes on the left, right? It's all
rope. Touch the rope on the right. Maybe touch the
left. Wait a minute. Touch the left.
Tap the sign. Touch the left. Touch the sign. Touch the left. Touch the sign. It's a little
confusing to the left. It's too complicated
to click on the left.  There was an explanation for how to release the rope,
but it's really a bit ok, I guess I'll
try it once,
but that's what I'm curious about.I want to
try it.When it's your turn, catch it with the right hand.It
's in the rule book.  It was written that it was not
written that it was caught on the right and turned left and released,
but oh well, maybe
that's it, I'll try it once.Yes, the sign is right, right,
caught on the right, turned left and put it in.  I
think so, but I don't think it can be canceled.Yes, I don't
think it can be canceled, but there are only
two people left.It looks like there are
two people running now, so it's already a festival.There must
be a mistake.People who don't have the theme.  I guess that's
what it would be like if someone was caught, right? That's not the point. When a
person gets caught, they get fired and
turn into a venue. Or maybe it becomes a venue or an auto venue.
Oh yeah, it's not like if they go all the way to Ao.
If
you try to put me in the cage, you'll probably be like
that.  I was
having sex with her. It's over.
Oh, it's over. I love you,
I love you. What? You're in trouble, stop. I'm not being picky about you. Why? Oh, that's it. I
can't stop thinking about it.
I love that.  Maybe Sora-chan moves quite boldly in
this game.I
wonder if it's better for everyone to run, even if I'm running.  It's true
that if we all run together, it's
better not to stick to one place.That's
true.That's right.It's true.It's
like a stack kill.If you're
chased like that, there's definitely someone.  It's going to
be a festival, and even if it comes, this is still
going on. It's practice, so let's get you caught.
So, how did you get into the prison for the first time? It's
cramped and
painful. It's the first time I've been forced to go in. I'm not good at it, but I
want to get caught.  Catch me,
somebody, catch
me! I've been kicked out
so much that I've been chased out and I've been caught.
But it's true, there are probably too many people,
so I'm being chased out. I've been hunted, I've been hunted, I've
been hunted.
But it's added up properly in the numbers, right?
Maybe it's the hunted owl that came here. Maybe it
got caught.
Wait, it's suffocating. It's really narrow. It's really
narrow. It's so narrow. It's okay. I was running around, and I was
running around with a string.  It's melting, Senkyu is melting,
yeah, that's right, when I run in the opposite direction, I get that nice feeling.It's melting, and it's
blue because it's melting, and I couldn't catch it.What does
it mean to turn around?I
keep running towards the queen's whip.  It seems like he didn't go into the cage, so let's
run wild. So, let's see if
Hunter Sora-chan escaped from the yellow team.
I didn't do it. I didn't want to do it. So, right-
click
with Sora-chan and pan left. Right-click and pan left. Looks
delicious.
If I don't have enough left, I want to
enter Polka, so I can become a cat fugitive, so
let's take a look.Maybe I should catch everyone in yellow.That's
right, that's okay, Pol-chan, let's go, I'm going to
enter Polka.  That's why you're practicing, you
're desperate, you look anxious, you're
crying. Right click, left click, right click.
When you see someone, right click and o.
Right click on the target. Yellow. At first, you smile a little.
Nice. You're not a hunter from the yellow team.  People,
too, please enter as a fugitive. I'm
looking for the entry signboard.
Where is it? The signboard. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's here. It's
really this. By the day of the day,
somehow, I'll have to erase this button. Click here on the left.
It's too late, it's not too late, I
want to leave it on the Internet like this. No
one's watching. It's okay. No one's looking at it. It's
okay to look at it. It's okay to
look at this. I
think it's wonderful, completely
naked.  It's a wonderful naked art, isn't it?
Iris, this is not art.
I think it's art. Okay, that's
it. I've been kicked out already. One more time. One more
time. One more three. One more. One more. One more. One more. One more. One more. One more. One more.  I do
n't know what you're talking about, but it's a bird, so I don't think it's okay because it's not Suba-chan, so there might be an arrest.  It's
not, I know.
After all, it's about me,
so no, no, no, stop it, stop it. There's really nothing wrong with it. It's
scary, but it's okay to just
get along and be white. You're becoming cute, so you can't be nice to each other.
I don't know what it is about this statue being in Florive.It's
not enough, it's not
enough, I thought I'd answer it.I
thought it was Asa-san holding Sora-chan's shoulders, but for now.
Because I want to catch it,
that's it, it's
Subaru. I want to catch it. I'm not doing it. I want to
catch it. I'm not doing it. It's okay just to be close. I want to catch it. I'm going to
get caught. Oh, left click, then right.
Furka. Now, I want to catch it.  It was rejected because it was different.
Oh, then it's okay. Even if it's a festival,
grab the people from the red team. There are people from the red team.
Even if it's on the other side, everyone shifts. It's true. It's on the other side. It
's white now.  Yoaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaafoot you tell you
there you are you I see that I see.  You
can
cancel it if you think it's wrong. Yes, no one is
gone. No one is lying. It's not white. It's normal. In
the first place, there are no white people, so why are you
bashing this place?  Something's right
Hey, I know there's plenty of room, so yellow is
here. Yellow is here. Look, Pol or Luka. They
put me in here, and Nirewa is running really
hard. Well, I was able to run away. If I dash, I
can escape.  It's
fun to run away when I'm jumping around. It's pretty crowded inside. It's getting
more and more crowded inside, and the
smell of sweat keeps coming. Excuse me, Princess. It's a little
scary. It's a bit sweaty here, Princess.  It's a
lot of places I'm
sorry for a little princess. Hunting is not enough. I
understand I
understand I understand I understand
[Music]
Click right.
Turn around,
please enter the fugitive.Fugitive. Hey,
try running away next time. Let's run away once. It's
definitely better to be white. Don't
scrape it off. Don't scrape it off. It's
dangerous. It's dangerous. It's dangerous.  It's crazy,
it's true, it's almost impossible to suddenly
disappear because there are so many strong antis,
but it's just the antis that have disappeared, after all.But it might
be possible to make it lower.It's
true.
After all, maybe it would be better for us to run around in Sora-chan's style.It's
true that it's
fun to run.
Look inside the yellow building. This cat is inside. It's
very strong honey. It's very strong. It's
starting to get started.
Please call me by your name. Honey position is
open. There's one person. Two people can ride. By the way.  It's
open for two people. I
want to go in. The clouds are caught, they're caught, they
're caught! I can
hear the slimy sounds of the octopus. This place is amazing. It looks like
two people can go. It's only two people. It's
nice to have a swing. Bra
too.
The two of us, the fence, are so unpopular
that it's dangerous.
Oh, what's that smell of hair?
Yellow and white are fine.
If it was Lyrica, I'd say I don't like it.
If it was, I wouldn't say anything about it in the book.  I wo
n't stop. I'm yelling. Asara was staring at me. It's
okay. It's
embarrassing to be separated from you, Senpai.
Our turn will come in 1010 seconds. I
don't know. I'll do it here, I'll do it there.
How long will it drag?  It's hard, right? It's an
experiment, sure, but regardless of what
happened earlier, I wonder if you were able to do it normally. Everyone,
don't hide it, it's dangerous, it's Noel.
[laughing]
That's it. It's Su-senpai. You're
serious here.
It's strong, I don't like that, I was warped to something,
and suddenly I was in this area.  It seems
like the end of the story.I see.It's
hard to hook it to something, but it's probably easier to catch it and
take it with me.Because it
can't move, after all.Even though I
like the running style, I don't see how it looks.  I
was running around this time,
right? I was running around,
but I got caught. I was able to escape once, but I was also
caught, so as long as I
didn't go for it, I'd be fine
. I see. Who's the demon?  If I don't know where to go and head towards it, I'll
get caught, but since I'm running around, I can't tell
who the demon is right now.I do
n't know at all, so I just
went right sideways.Oh, right sideways, that's too much.That's why I
met Noel's eyes.  At that moment, I was prepared to die
. I thought it was
over. Yes, I was captured. Yes, I was
standing. That's right. I was prepared. I
can't get out of here anymore. This is probably my first time
hunting.
That's right, I want to do the voice. I want to do it again. I
want to be quick. Wait a moment.
I'll add it in the chat once. Next Hime's voice
is good. Sukete. Next person's voice is good. Who's the voice?
Who is the voice? The voice is Nemii Hime.
Princess, I can't let that take hold. I've
got a feverish feeling. I
can't believe it. Even the letters are starting from the beginning, so that's all I can
say. I came to read it, but something was gone. That
senior, I ca
n't hear it. I can't hear it.  No,
hey, but
wait a minute. The
vines aren't like that either. They just have a long start, and they're
definitely not going to fall. That's right, even if I press the vines for a long time, I got
a little relaxed at the end. At the end, I
moved to the right.  It's
okay to go that way, but I can't run that way.That's
probably the easiest way to go.That's probably the easiest way to go.It's
different from you guys who haven't put Miko here in the wrong
place.I can hear the laughter of the birds.That's Mikomi
Kochiko.  I'm back to 2nd,
so I'm going to
cut off the streaming frame soon.I'm
going to practice, but I've been streaming, so I'm
going to stream too, and then I'll cut it off.It's about time I cut that frame and
practice.  In that case, I'm going to practice a little
differently.Okay, I'll give you the answer first.No
, those who want to do it can do it, and
those who want to do it
can do it at all.The framework that I think is okay is still here.
Maybe I'll go for a while.Okay, then I guess I'll just leave it there.Okay,
this is it.It's the one from Unteshi, and
it's pretty good.Yeah, it was
going strong.Which
part of it is going to get drunk earlier?Minecraft is probably going to get drunk.  That's
what I think of the knight.There's a lot of
fang line, fang line, fang line, fang line.It's
true that the screen shakes quite a bit.On
the other hand, the screen is bouncing
up and down, so it's all the better.  Hey, it's not my intention, it's just too much
movement.
It's
okay. It's not okay. It's okay
. It's okay. I feel like I'm feeling worse than before. I'll practice after this. I don't
mind doing it at all, but it seems like I'm going to close it all once, so I'm
bored.  Can I have your permission?
I'm sorry, I heard that, but I was
thinking of closing that whole thing for now, but
yes, yes, I'm going to continue, but I'm thinking of closing it for now,
uhm.  Is it okay if I ask you to join me in
the room where everyone is? Yes, that's fine. I'll close it when I get home.
Those who will do it as they are, I'll ask them to do that.
Then I'll close it for now. Yes, I
wonder if everyone has gathered together.  Is
n't it okay? It's Sporu. I'm
back, so it's okay for the first time. Okay,
okay. Thank you everyone for today.
Thank you very much. I'm really
happy that you really put your head forward and practiced like crazy.  I
hope we can all have fun together while occasionally supporting the members who couldn't make it. Thank you
very much for your support.
From now on, I'll just call out to the cat, regardless of the team,
but it's okay.  I'm
going to call out to someone like I want to play with them, so
can I ask them to come at that timing? It's a
little bit like that, and it's the same with the Fukuga line that starts up,
and the same with the floor-up, and the same with Higo. I
can't do everything at once, so I'll have to do it now.  I'm
thinking of doing this, and I'm going to gather only the people who want to do it, and
ask them to come, and I'm
going to do it, so I'm going to give it a go, and then I can
close the slot after this, or I can
leave that slot open, but thank you very much.  Thank you very much for your
hard work. Thank you again for your hard work tomorrow.
Thank you for your continued support. Yes, thank you
very much. Thank you very
much. We
apologize for the inconvenience. Yellow will be
number 5 for now.  Then, in number 5,
[Music]
Okay, so by the way, there are still people who are still in the slot.
What should I do if I keep going? It's the voice. What are we going to do about it?
If you want to cut it off, you can cut it off completely.
That's it. I'll
leave it to you.  Shioi, you're flirting, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, don't say that, it's fine.By
the way, Subaru won't be there tomorrow.
The voice here, the voice here, it's
okay, where is it? Um, it's not the
school building, it's the gymnasium. It's the gymnasium.
Yes, yellow, I'll participate.
Thank you. Chat. Ah, that's helpful.
By the way, Matsumachi has some kind of plan. Please wait.  But
when the princess said it out loud, I think we probably got along pretty well. She
said it like red, yellow, and pink earlier, and she said it when she was making that road, so
when she said that, it
was pretty easy to understand that she was going to move.  I get the impression that it's a
continuation, so it's better to crouch down as much as possible.It
's said that if you crouch down and plant something, it will never fall.Oh, that's
right, that's amazing.Now then, Princess Iris, I'd like to
ask you a favor in one voice, Princess.  I
feel like it's not even just one voice, but it's definitely fun.If I
don't do at least 50 voices, I'll probably get
sick, but even if it gets a little harsh.
It's okay if you let me down. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's my
first time. I wonder if it's okay. It's my first
time. It's okay. It's okay if everyone closes their doors.
Only Miz and Matsui-senpai won't
enter.  Is it okay to do that
? That's right, 01 is gathering. Please use
voice chat 01.
Yes, please, please, please, please,
please. In the meantime, Mikochi's broadcast is still
ongoing.  So yeah,
I hope all the yellow members are there, but
yeah, what should we do? The yellow members
can be divided into 444. I wonder if they're there, at all. It's
okay, who's there now?
[Music]
1234567888 There are 8.
Then we can be divided into two teams.  Hey, Team 2, we
can do it. Subaru is watching how things are
going. Everyone, if anyone wants to team up with us,
please do so. Wait a minute, wait a minute. Please go ahead and proceed. I'll
ask you a few questions. Oh, sorry, I
have one more question.  But what's that about? You
make things and you guess what they are.
Well, knights are not supposed to talk,
you know. Basically, it's okay to make a voice that sounds like ``U'' or something like that.
Even with words, things like ``This is that, this is the
usual'' will probably
get the message across, so there are no words like ``Yes, yes, yes, put a green here.''
In that case, the princess can just talk, and the princess is also like, ``Oh.''
If it were the other way around, the princess would
say something like, ``Is that a refrigerator?'' and the
knight would shake his head or nod up and down,
and the words would be wrong.
It's fine as long as it's not that kind of
thing.By the way, it's like that princess's theme, which
can change on the day of the day.In
terms of theme, it's about cooking.Yeah, yeah.
The first half of the game isn't exactly the same,
after all, it's random, so if you
do it with the Red Team, for example, there will always be
a lot of paprika, or a lot of refrigerators, etc.
Miko also thinks that,
but yeah, that's right.  Even so, it
seems like it's all random,
so I don't really understand, but it seems like some random person is
getting angry, so the topic for that day is that the
one that's on the topic right now won't change, and
there's a chance that the same one will come out again.  That's
right, that's right.The
first half of the creative process
doesn't change that much, but the second question will
be a special question on the day of the day.Yes,
it might be that theme.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, it's
like that.What's the orchestra?There
are some changes, but they don't interfere with that.Yes,
yes, I can go with 44.We
haven't broken up yet yesterday.
Yes, how do you feel now? Okay,
now it's yellow. It looks like there will be 44 yellow members, so yellow. Are we
going to do it now? Then,
should we enter as white? White, right. Change the entry to that white.
The same team that will be on the day
remains.  We're going to form a separate team with people, and there's going to be a red
team, and there's going to be a white team. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I
want to cut things off. A lot of them have
disbanded. Yeah, I want to do that. They're pretty disbanded. But even if
those three teams aren't all together, we can still practice. So we
can do it.  It's up to you,
let's do it, let's do it, everyone.If only Eto can do it, we
can do it.Okay, okay, I'll do it as a
princess.I'd like a knight.If I yell, I'll do it
as a
princess, no, no.Why?I want to do it.
Princess
Oh please, I want to see the princess.Then you
can have Mio-chan come as a knight.That's
dead.She's dead.She's dead.So
please be that Mikochi knight.Oh princess, protect me.I'll protect you.Then
press the start button.Ah, let's start.
Where's the button? Come here. Button. Yes, let's
divide the voice servers. Oh, sure,
yes. Let's go to the actual show. Let's start with team number 2,
please. Yes,
yes.
Can I ask you to protect me? You're
in my
turn. You're a bit too quick and your legs aren't strong enough. You're a
strong princess.
Don't move, don't move, you're in danger. You're in danger.  I'm
playing white, white, white, pinpink,
right, right, white, pink, red, right,
white, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, princess, I'm sorry, the
princess is already in tatters, the red is out.Next, white,
pinpin, white, pink, red, please.  Yes, white, pink,
pink, red, please, yes,
pin,
pin, don't move, don't move, oh,
okay, it's going well, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
[music],
oh, what's this?
No, no, no
[Music]
This is it, this is it, yeah, what is this, oh, oh,
the subject
has changed Yes, that's
it, what's this, why can't I cut it like that
But wait, what's that? There's
no white lump.
Okay, so I've already started playing.  The
grilled rabbit meat and the characteristics of the viewer are amazing.I
have a hamburger with a rabbit.How can I
make the grilled rabbit meat by grilling raw rabbit meat?
Get some beef, potatoes and carrots.
Potatoes, rainbows,
potatoes, carrots. Okay, that's raw garlic, raw beef, beef, beef,
garlic.  Nomame lysine
Yes, I used a chopping board to remove the dirt. What should I do with the beef?
Cut it with the board you use to cut potatoes.
Cut the potatoes and carrots. Same goes for the potatoes and carrots. I
cut them with ground beef.  Please roast the potatoes and carrots together.It
's minced meat.It's minced meat.I just want to say it's minced meat.Please
do that.I should be able to roast it with this.It's done tomorrow.It's
done.It's done.Nice
look, take a look.
Where did you go? The
rice you smoked. The grilled rabbit meat is charred. I'm
sorry. Miko, Sanmi-san, this is also charred. It's
okay, it's okay, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's nice, it's
nice, it's nice, it's nice, it's nice.
And the
left side is red.The upper left side is
red.The upper left side is orange.The upper right side is yellow.Orange A
Orange Yellow Yes, red orange yellow
red orange yellow
red.  Okay, the bottom is red, top orange, right yellow,
yellow, red, yellow, come on, okay, nice, I
didn't understand it at all, nice,
nice, the dream is a battle, it's coming, it's
coming, it's coming, it's coming,
it's slipping through, it's slipping through, it's just
a little messy and that's me
Please protect me, nice old man, do your best as an ancient weapon.
[Music]
It's so hot! Wait, everyone's on fire,
everyone's on fire,
right? It's so
big! It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming.  I'm tired, I'm exhausted, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm tired, I'm
yellow, I've
cleared the team, seriously, it's not that fast
Why?Who's to blame?  I
don't have one here, I'm
not doing it at all By the way, Miko isn't doing it at all I'm already
looking at Sui-chan and she's getting irritated
and stabbing me so much It's a trident, you can't
give me a weapon Hey, wait
a minute.Would you like to share the server?Yes.
[Music]
Yes, pon,
pon, pon, pon, pon, that's fast. Praise
me. I want to collaborate with you. I'm looking forward to the book. I'm also
looking forward to the golden one. I
guess it's success when something like a
star appears on the other person's body.  When the brown star came out, I
even learned how to do a critical hit.It
's amazing, but when the brown star comes out, the person with the bow ends up
defeating the demon king.I
wonder if I should make it into a festival.It's like that from last year.
Last year's sports day was really
critical.I remember what happened last year.There
was mob subjugation and fencing.
Teneran -san's stuffy is
that there is
something else I want to practice in the way. It's
okay to follow up OK. There are people who participate in follow -up.  Yeah, the
image I got
was really fast, and Anya too, Anya-senpai.
Ah, that's right. Let's collect the follow-up. Let's follow up.
Okay, after the follow-
up, we'll have one yellow
break up. Yes, yes.
Oh, when's the next practice?  So, the 12th
practice is tomorrow, uh, tomorrow.Yellow 1
o'clock to noon.I
think I can go.I might not be able to do it at first.It's
okay.It's okay.On the contrary, if there's
something you want to practice.  After this, let's
practice together for a bit.That's the first time.It
's going to be an hour from now, but if you're doing it,
please join us.It's totally fine.Then it's a good
time to start.You can drop out as you like.It's
okay.  Thank you,
thank you, I'm so tired. Thank you very much.
That's right. There's still one more person to pull up.
But who's coming next? I've been practicing.
That's why Nemiko's stomach is sticking out. Shut it up. I'm
surprised. Shut it up. I'm really hungry.  Come on
out, let's
move. Don't mess around there,
move. We're already there. What are we
here? We've arrived. Don't say that.
Don't say that. Are you out?
By the way, your stomach is coming out in the morning.
Your stomach is coming out.
I messed up, I'm sorry,
but it turned out to be the moment when everyone's hearts became one, and it
turned into a blink of an eye
. Please touch me.
Oh, I'm late. Oh, Ani-san, please
enter too.  Sensei-senpai is yellow.If you want to
make it white, you should make it yellow.If
you make it red, then you can enter in yellow.I'm sorry, I made it red.I made it red.I'm sorry, I made it red.I'm sorry, I made it
red.I'm sorry, I made it red.The book is open.I can
do it.  Red, red, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I
guess, right? Who is
going to go? The fight
has already begun. Will Miko, the amazing creator, win?
Or will she
win? A battle that can't be won is here. A battle that can't be fought is
here. Good luck, Ani-san, do your best.  A
new word called nya has been
created.Today, I'm going to go to Gaba to
Gaba.Isn't it?  That's
not true, that's
not true,
everyone is amazing, that's right, but everyone is good, is
n't it? You're not doing something like that, that's wrong. Aji, Nemi, you're really good, you're really
good, you're amazing, I
can hear you right now.  [
Music]
That's amazing, that
's
not it. Well, that's the chorus. Let's get along. It
's impossible. You're retaliating too fast. You're coming
back while you're falling. Let's go
to the second checkpoint.  It's impossible,
I'm going to come back
as soon as possible.  It's a joke,
right? It's another team and team. This is another source. So, do
your best, Akuo, Oishio, Ichisui-
chan. It's amazing. It's super stable. It's stable.
This didn't go well tomorrow. Stop killing me.
Stop, stop.  That's it, Subaru isn't here in Yellow, so I ca
n't stop him. Seriously, he won't be there tomorrow. Don't stop him, just die. I'm
really begging you to come in. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
tomorrow the voice
channel will be separated, so I'm sorry.  Chan,
who are you? Yes, I'm with you. Lyrica, please
stop. If something happens, I'll take your place.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop Lyrica. Stop it,
Lily, stop it. I wonder if I'll be here too.  Do
n't worry, I'm serious
No, I'm also a follow-up, so my passion
will be messed up
Hey, everyone's going to be destroyed by the follow-up,
come back, come here, come here, Chiara, there
are still people streaming here, there's
a lot of people, there's a lot of people  It
's currently on air It's currently on air That's right.
Why did it fall? We
're all watching the follow-up. We're all watching the final, last
try hollow up. Tomorrow is the actual performance.
That's right. Tomorrow, the
actual performance is today's practice.
Oh, but
I can't reach another route.
Good luck. It's not a big deal, but if you
can get to the top, it'll probably be almost the same as yesterday's layout. Well, I
made it to the top, but the bottom is the
bottom.  It's pretty messed up,
haha, 3rd checkpoint is reached, that's great,
hey
, it's alright, you stupid idiot, are you okay? It's okay, do your best, A-san, it's
okay, there's still time, go slowly, it's
alright, I fell, it's okay.  Ani-san, please
leave me with the speed of revenge
Please leave me with the speed of revenge Please
leave me with the speed of ki Please leave me with peace of mind
That's right. What should I do now?
19 seconds left. Bad, bad, bad.
15 seconds left.  I can't see it for a second, you're an
idiot, you're an idiot, I want to die
[Music]
[Applause]
On the contrary, it's amazing, but you
also did a great job and you didn't touch it, you won.
No, it
's over for once, so no, no, it's over for now. Now, after this, practice behind the scenes. It
hurts. It hurts, so do
n't hit it like that. Yes, it's a hit. Yes, it's okay. For those who close the frame, please
close it for me. Hichim, please
stay.  Thank you very much
Thank you
very much
Thank you very much for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.  There were
quite a lot of people,
so I think it was a little hard to hear or it was loud,
but I wonder if it was okay.  I do
n't know who or what team will come out on top.I'm
looking forward to tomorrow.Thank you very much.I'm glad that Ame looks like she's having fun.It
was a lot of fun.But tomorrow I
won't see Swa-chan's tsukko, so I do
n't know what to do.But I'm
feeling today.  I'm so glad that Ewatame is going to
be Subaru-chan's boss in the mahoro hunting and the real battle, and
even more so, I'll be fighting with a general on my back.I'll do
my best, so please support me.The
real show will be on today's 6th.  I think it's about 6 o'clock at night,
and it starts. I heard that
before practice, Neko and I had a one-on-one session with Nesuma-chan, and she
taught me a little bit. It's
not like I'm calling her and my heart is pounding.  We were
doing a little bit of back and forth, and I
said, ``Oh, right now, today.'' I usually say ``Oh, right now, today.'' I usually stream until midnight, so I
usually end up saying ``Today.'' But it's a
habit.
Hey, tomorrow, tomorrow at 6:00 pm, we'll have a live performance. I'm looking
forward to seeing you. I'm starting to say "Today" in my mouth. I'm
scared. I'm scared. I
'm thinking, "Thank you very much.  I'd be
happy if you could take a look at the cotton frame as well.Thank
you.After this, I'll practice a little and then go to
bed early.The yellow team will do their best to wake up at 1 o'clock.Thank
you
[Music]
Hey, good luck in your practice.  Good
night, thank you for your hard work. I should try not to oversleep.
Everyone called me.
Thank you very much. See you tomorrow.
Good night.
Senkyu. Those who are feeling now.
[Music]
Good night.
T.
Yesterday's broadcast  But the point of being a general is
different, and I remember talking to everyone about how it's a big responsibility,
but then I
looked at the hero team's chat, and the pair of Fang Lines saw that
written there, and I said, Wow, Subaru, wow, this is
serious.  I was all alone. It
was a bit of a shock. It was a shocking morning.
Now that I'm here, I'm going to do my best. It's a
big responsibility to collect the flag, but it's a start.
If I can, I'll practice in Ekka.Thank
you
very much.