[Music]
foreign
and welcome to the main event of rainy
bird
and birthday oh my goodness it's crowded
today hello everyone
welcome
to the stream
um this is the birthday stream of avalia
Rainey I am Rainey the People Princess
of hololive Indonesia generation two
whether you're looking around or a long
time you're you're all invited to the
party I hope you enjoy your stay happy
birthday thank you thank you thank you
thank you
and um before so actually before the
stream started yeah when I Was preparing
the stream I was a little bit little bit
watching were you guys watching the
re-gloss
I was actually watching what I Was
preparing
I couldn't really watch much because I
was oh stress preparing for the stream
but so far there's three people debuting
right
yeah there's owl right there's oh and
there's Canada and also I'm very very
excited to see them and I think there's
still more coming right
fan of death games just like you she
speaks so fast though um
yes I think like there will be more
coming right uh tomorrow so I'm looking
forward after the birthday I can watch
in peace so I'm very very excited for
that I'm really really excited
Machine Gun Talk
they're very very interesting and I'm
very very
um
very happy to see them
they wish you happy birthday too thank
you
foreign I'm I'm English I'm English
Indonesia Maine
okay but nervous
no because nervous
[Laughter]
thank you
yes yes yes
they can speak English that's good
that's good we can speak English but
even if even if no English it's fun
because I can speak Japanese it's just
not happening right now because I'm
somehow very nervous right now passion
English so Sudan communication with his
name
Um passion passion
it's fine yes
then they can speak anything easy peasy
Japan English
I will teach the regos members Japan
English
I will teach them Japan English and
Japan knowledge
yes the regulars in rainy Channel they
are very very good
in Rain
streams Japan
everybody is mixing Japanese Indonesian
and English together so I think whenever
there's anybody uh anybody new debuting
I feel like that should be my goal to
teach them Japan bullish
I think that should be What Separates Me
from like the other people goals like oh
I want to stream with them I'm my in my
heart is education you know education
number one I have to teach them Japan do
list very nice speaking of Japan dollars
at 9 00 PM rainy will be releasing an
original song
called sip something original song is
giving birth
yes
original song and we are going to be
having a watch along together in this
stream and the song is a mix of
Indonesian and English so I hope you
enjoy it the song is giving birth no no
we are giving birth giving birth is what
in Japanese in I don't know brojo is
Indonesian
yes so
I'm very very excited for that and
so the rundown of today's
Atara of today's event is first we have
a lot of hollow members that have
already sent their videos I asked them
some questions related to birthday and
they have answered so we can know a
little bit of their inside mind what do
they think about birthday what is their
perfect gift
hmm right by the way these videos me
personally I haven't watched so I gave
it to the staff and the stuff is like
and then okay so we can react together
to the videos okay
and second we are going to do a watch
along of the Simpson original
music video produced by Mario
and be prepared to open another tab of
course and the third one we are going to
have a little little reveal what is it I
wonder
what is it I wonder
and of course there's gonna be
don't tell anyone I said there's March
but there's gonna be
yeah it's that's the stream if anybody
asks where the merch where the merch
it's the stream but technically you know
pretend you guys don't know that
anyways
but yes
well I guess we could keep the bgm on if
you guys desire so
so the questions that I'm asking the
members who are there are three
questions actually let me just um
uh okay first what is your memorable
birthday memory
foreign
and third a birthday celebration you
would like to do but haven't had the
chance to
so if you want to celebrate something
but Blanc sampen you know you still
don't have the chance to do it thank you
so what is it
between let me count one two three four
five six seven eight eight
nine ten eleven twelve one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven
twelve twelve Holo members have answered
the questions okay
so who is it
and
shall we start by watching the first one
mmm
let's see
it's not a quiz it's like asking them
the first one who is it drum roll please
and let's play it
happy birthday
baby
[Applause]
from here we love it zombie
wow can't believe time flies so fast and
you know what else flew you me um
yeah I'm so glad that you got
transported to this side of the world
because if not I wouldn't have met such
an amazing awesome Den mate so from the
bottom of my heart thank you for always
being so caring to me and everyone else
I would never forget this how kind you
are or when we were in Japan when we
were sharing uh the apartment together
you're such an amazing person to be
around with and I'm really wishing you
the best of birthdays today next year
and forevermore I love you so much
yeah and anyways I'm here to answer some
questions that you got for us the first
question being what is your most
memorable birthday memory so um a little
backstory okay because there was this
one birthday party that lives rent free
in my head back then when I was still a
tiny human I would hold like birthday
parties in like fast food chains like or
Burger yeah uh at those places and I
would like invite all my friends and
that would include their parents so
there's this one birthday party I think
I was still in elementary school we were
just vibing we were having fun we were
knocking pinatas down and then suddenly
there was this one woman who came
crashing to my party she started
screaming at this one dad and started
like pulling on another woman's hair and
it turns out that uh one of my friend's
dad had an affair and he decided to
bring his mistress
his daughter to my birthday party
and the wife knew about it drove to the
said restaurant and decided to cause a
commotion you won yeah
it was quite a sight the employees
eventually kicked them out
they said friend
from the dad who's having an affair she
sighed and then patted me on the back
she said listen I'm so sorry for this
and you know what I think I gotta go I
gotta take care of my parents so see you
at school and so she gave me like this
present I remember so vividly she gave
me a Barbie doll and then she just
walked out of the restaurants
I don't know how she is right now but
that happened
yeah I wasn't ready for that anyways
next what would be the perfect birthday
gift for you
actually I do have one it's like the the
thing that I want the most an adventure
so so listen I once watched Neil Patrick
Harris going on about his 14th birthday
if I remember exactly so by his friend
he was gifted a week long scavenger hunt
party where he had to solve Clues do
missions go do fun stuff before his
birthday and I got jealous I thought
that would be fun like an ARD yeah
that's something that I'd want on my
birthday
the last question is what's the birthday
celebration that you would like to do
but haven't had the chance to
I've always wanted to do a ball-like
birthday party yeah just like the Royals
back then I want to actually be the
princess of the ball watch everyone in
ball games and prints like suits just
Waltzing around with classical music and
have big buffets oh that'd be a dream
Once I'm successful enough I really want
to do that and of course I'll invite you
yeah it's so fun anyway
um thanks so much for having me I don't
want to take too much of your time I
hope you're having a lovely birthday and
we'll continue to have a lovely rest of
your birthday
love you
[Applause]
oh that's so sweet
okay okay that I was not prepared for
that to be the first story okay like I
said like I said I did not screen uh I'm
I was not the one who screened this it
was like it was tough so okay
cool interesting it's a very Ollie story
but also the fact that she wanted a um
the fact that she wanted a a ball like
birthday that's so I can see her like
that like she's she's very she's like a
very sweet girl you know she likes all
these like cute sweet stuff you know and
you know and when you look at her in
first glance she was like oh the crazy
one but she has that really like super
sweet girl side of her oh my gosh thank
you for your story
um that was a very um that first story
uh made an impression truly
you think you'd enjoy a ball uh as long
as I'm not alone I feel like yeah
um well uh I don't know who the second
one is because these are all marked
media Source four five six seven eight
um well let's check out the next one
let's see if the other stories can beat
this one okay
let's see who is this
[Music]
happy birthday
I miss you later what are you doing
birthdays so you have a question for me
my most memorable birthday memory yeah
the first thing that comes to mind is
actually not really a good memory oh
okay I had when I was a child I had this
like birthday that was like happening
outside in the park and it was in summer
time
summer birthday and because it was hot
and you know you know we were gonna have
an ice cream cake and I was really young
at this time right so I had I invited a
lot of friends as you usually do when
you're still younger and then somebody
came who wasn't invited it was like this
girl from the city that I didn't really
like
probably like around preschool by the
way
and she just like decided to be there
and I remember her stealing my cake and
then running away with it being just
like smashed I guess what we were
chasing after her I I don't know why she
would steal the cake that's so crazy
like like pretty much melting from the
heat anyway but that was not cool and I
don't think I ever forgave her for that
that's crazy what the hell perfect
birthday gift for me the perfect
birthday gift would be a free day
birthday stream on time when it's
actually my birthday
oh geez all right celebration I would
like to do but I haven't had the chance
to I feel like in the recent years I
just generally haven't had any like
proper birthday parties at all like I
feel like it's normal for people to fade
out at some point and just don't really
celebrate it anymore but I really like I
haven't celebrated in a long time while
still visiting my friend's celebrations
uh me on the other hand I'm I'm like I
don't know so honestly just any any
celebration really I just I need to
celebrate myself
maybe next year how about you
what about me
I love you
mama
oh that's very sweet of her
okay listen see when I asked this
question when I asked this question and
said oh what is your memorable most
memorable birthday party I was expecting
stories like say this morning you know
like I did send I did ask like
marshmallow right I did you know oh like
my most memorable birthday was like when
I ate dinner with my parents and so and
so on so and instead we got a um
well it's good well I guess it's a good
story it's a good story it's just that I
wasn't expecting it but it's it's very
entertaining stories in I guess that's
nice we have here trauma dumping
the trauma dumping
but that's crazy that's the that's the
second story and I'm still saying that's
crazy you know will it calm down or will
it get even crazier I don't know but
yeah you know I hope she gets to
celebrate birthdays properly maybe like
you know I think a lot of us need to um
just celebrate birthdays nicely just uh
you know
be free hmm
trauma dumping on rainy birthday is more
likely than you think
all right
that's great that was Kiara
um
and then
one more the next one let's see let's
see let's see who this is
and what kind of story they can offer
happy birthday awareness
I love you first question I forget what
it was around six or eight or ninth
birthday with English bought me a
keyboard it was the first time I started
music I learned to play the keyboard to
play it on my birthday celebration and
that was also the first time I performed
in front of many many people
cute profession first
clothes
because I can wear it till I die
especially the interactive one because
I'm not really into the display toy
loads
because I can wear it oh close
the gun toys especially the interactive
ones I'm not really into the display toy
a birthday Royal them
dressed
[Music]
as my arm
my arms with white horse and have a
bodyguard a dog and have my own ball
oons
where
boy
so uh okay coming from Kobo that was
actually a very um that was one of that
was more of what I expected from
everybody you know like what's your
Unforgettable memory oh yeah I got a
keyboard it was my first time playing
music with the keyboard that's great
right
foreign
toys interactive toys I think right
and then her dream is actually she wants
to be oh like a princess like a tiara
and uh with a bodyguard with a white
horse I guess that's very Kobo very very
cool princess Kobo Indonesian change
people yeah that's why you guys also
said like Indonesian raining and English
rain is so different
[Laughter]
Japanese writing also different
yes yes yes yes very very cool
though that's the least scene that we
got so far I think I mean not the most
sane one sorry force of habit
um
yeah like alter universe is
and then next one
next one is
force of habit exactly next one is OMG
this is like this is my birthday party
but we're like
it's like it's like my birthday party
but I'm like digging everybody's
everybody's crazy story like we gossip
about excuse me what I'm not even
telling anything about my my
Unforgettable birthday experience I'm
just like let's see if you got some tea
all right
next one here we go
ssip International
foreign
company in Japan I try to take last day
for my birthday but my boss angry me he
said this year you don't have the
birthday your birthday like that and I
had to work all day long on my birthday
oh scary second question what would be
the perfect birthday gift for me love
a birthday celebration you would like to
do but haven't had the chance to if I
have the chance to do birthday
celebration I wanna do a Luis produce
live all her member live
yeah very very brief interview style
yo trauma dumping the Stream
but
oh man that sucked though that sucked
though yeah like imagine you're working
and then you're like oh I want to take a
Dale for my birthday and boss is like no
no birthday work
that sucks
yeah
but I hope now I hope now Louie can
celebrate her birthday freely
um
yes very relatable oh yeah evil evil
evil company
yeah not just work and all day oh my
gosh
but now she can celebrate her birthday
with many many friends so yay
and
and yes she needs love I'll give her
love the Louis rizz she just gotta like
sneak it in like what is the perfect
birthday gift for you love
that was nice thank you so much Louie
for sharing oh my gosh
yes I'm very very happy now Louie is
also part of holotori yes
so we can always spend time together we
can spend birthdays together and
hopefully Louis will get to have her
dream come true with special produce
Louis live or Hollow mem live yes
hi and next one
we have uh who is this the next next
drama please the next drama
okay okay let's go let's go wait waiting
right now happy birthday
okay
what is your memorable birthday memory
oh is that the way this year definitely
this year did it um
I'd like to do I would like to do but
haven't had the chance to do it I don't
know I really wanted to celebrate my
birthday offline I mean have a real
party with you guys and I already did it
this year so maybe just doing a girls
night and a party again with you guys
like with you guys I just really really
want to bonding night a girls night or
maybe just go anywhere with you guys
that would be pretty good happy birthday
thank you so much for being my friend
and have a great birthday I love you and
if you have or if you need something
else you can just always contact me okay
you know that thank you I love you
foreign
oh my God that's radiating brightness
[Music]
oh that was like no drama
oh
oh so basically eofi says that uh you
know she's had three birthdays and so
far
[Laughter]
and oh what did she say I already forgot
because I'm so touched
but she really appreciates like remember
last time we also had a uh we also had a
you know eating cake together and stuff
so next year yeah she really likes to do
things together and I'm very very happy
to join her with the celebrations of
course I still remember the first time
we met we watched Barbie
we watched Barbie
like Ramirez I don't know I forgot if we
ever like told the story but
um we watched Barbie like a bunch of us
uh yeah and then I don't know
I would definitely love to hang out with
her or participate in you know if she
has any like events or like Hangouts
she's a very fun person to be around
thank you so much
so cool
um no one tops only birthday trauma so
far yeah yeah the the the old the older
one not the new one not the new one not
not the not the live action one it's
like one of the
um older old movies
yes
oh man all these was crazy we're keeping
trauma score well I leave it to you it's
not for me to just it's not um it's not
my uh you know to judge their trauma
random birthday party is trauma
simulator 2023
happy birthday oh thanks
all right next one hopefully
not traumatic or not uh depends okay
let's see this
rainy happy birthday
I hope all your dreams come true and I
hope all you're preparing on a lot of
things for example like original song
recover songs space faster than you ever
talk
so okay I got I got a cushions
um yes from rainy okay Reina just gave
me the questions what is your most
memorable birthday memory my mom's
memorable birthday memory is
when I was on my birthday a lot of
people comes to my birthday yes and they
even prepared for like a really long
time for making a gift for me yes for
example my Luna fate who've been
preparing a lot of things
book and original songs like it was so
wonderful and also they even that I love
here
it makes me like I've been loved by a
lot of people
what would be the perfect birthday gift
for you ah
the pocket for me
know maybe a lifetime posture of
cheeseburger
so I can I can eat cheeseburger uh
without even paying it because I have a
free lifetime culture yes
again a birthday celebration you will
like to do but haven't had the chance to
yes I really really really want to have
3D life birthday party just like other
girls do and I really I really want to
have this kind of things life birthday
party where everyone where I can invite
a lot of people to come and sing and
dance with me yeah
are
will come to the place to the world
where I make a party yes yes kind of
thing like that yeah yeah I would like
to do that
that's all thank you Randy for the all
the questions and happy birthday happy
birthday happy birthday
to you you're getting old you're getting
old you're getting older all day
the last part wasn't really necessary
wasn't it
but anyways we do have Muna thank you so
much Muna for answering the question so
very wholesome one no trauma detected
we're just gonna we have the trauma oh
meter trauma meter
yeah let me um Let me let me let me
measure that with the trauma meter Maybe
no traumas detected yeah
tried to give me the trauma jeez nah man
it's fun I'm young and free
10 on the trauma scale excellent
[Laughter]
but anyway that's good no you're you
guys are the one that expecting trauma
not me I was normal right but okay let's
see I was just glancing at the time it's
nice because like we're gonna do some
promo shots but don't tell them don't
don't tell them I told you already yes
oh wow so what's the tally so far guys
we have Ollie
we have Ollie with the uh traumatic
story
we have Wawa with the traumatic I guess
yofino trauma Kobo no trauma Muna no
trauma
and Louis trauma so three out of three
so three so three by three
stroma meter okay
three three the score is side right now
I don't know man like I did not plan
this to happen I was just gonna be like
okay guys let's listen to some stories
you know well if you guys wanted to hear
more about me um it was in the morning
stream right now we're like reviewing
this and very nice I can try to answer
the questions as well later on
I don't think only was that traumatizing
I don't think it was traumatized it was
just like a very crazy story but like
you know we'll we'll pass that off as
yeah
who will win find out by watching the
stream is it team trauma or team no
drama
three dark three wholesome nice
anyway it's just a normal day for Ollie
okay
so three three so far
six we have fourteen
so maybe one more
no one okay next story whose is this
oh hi
hi
I am here to answer some questions we're
matching you have you're watching me and
other members shall I go right into it I
shall okay what is your most memorable
birthday memory I was younger when I was
a very small owl once upon a time I went
to my favorite restaurant to have a
family birthday dinner and before going
I said to my family I said please don't
tell them it's my birthday I know
getting free dessert is cool but I
really don't want them to sing Happy
Birthday to me and I don't want the rest
of the restaurant to you know watch and
also sing happy birthday I don't know
what to do when people sing Happy
Birthday to me please don't do that
listen yeah yeah of course May of course
of course it's your birthday so of
course they um told the restaurant and
this was a pretty nice restaurant it was
a sushi restaurant for sure they had a
lot of the staff come out uh singing
happy birthday as if it was a Chuck E
cheese it was a kid's birthday venue and
I just remember being in this dimly lit
restaurant with very good food dying
inside at this Birthday song being sang
to me and
um the of course the rest of the
restaurant stopping what they're doing
to listen to this ridiculous birthday
singing and it will never leave my
memory ever oh never ever I forgot a lot
of things but I'll never forget that
okay I got free ice cream though the ice
cream oh yeah it was good it was worth
it in the end it was great first
question what would be the perfect
birthday gift for you nowadays the
perfect birthday gift for me would be
having people to hang out with and spend
time with on my birthday so people to
take me to dinner and pay for the dinner
and I don't know maybe take me to a
movie and to pay for the movie The
Perfect Gift is to have have a group of
people spend money on me nice so we can
do fun activities that's cool I'm here
to ask me this uh years ago I I would
have said Webkinz at Webkinz were the
perfect birthday gift for me and the
last question like it is asking about a
birthday celebration I would want to do
but I haven't had it the chance to do I
have a weird one I would like to have a
group of people go with me into the
woods or somewhere out in nature maybe
to a lake over to a beach or on a
mountain somewhere in the middle of the
night and I want to look at stars with
people because I I was too scared that's
so sweet I don't have a group of people
do that with me and we can look at the
sky and the stars and think about the
universe and how little how little
meaning everything has a great birthday
celebration in my opinion anyways thank
you for having
evening I hope you've been having a good
birthday
and yeah happy birthday happy birthday
happy birthday
bye bye and she's so cute web feels like
the uh the plush right am I wrong or I
don't know or I don't know what she
meant if it was wrong okay well okay
listen it's very funny we uh so far we
have um three Hollow birds and they all
have very um interesting stories oh is
it just the bird thing is it just a
birthday okay well uh keep yeah keep the
tally keep the tally going
Tori Tori mataised
torimatized
that's cool
well um cool
[Laughter]
oh my gosh
Jessa
just uh yeah
traumatory
I don't know that could be a game title
or something or a skit title that would
be great
nice
well we still have one more we also have
one more bird and I think she goes kind
of last so um you're not you're not
really about to see it until it's gonna
be like one of those like ooh
Cliffhangers you'll only find out the
reason I mean the result if you watch it
to the end you know
laughs
yes
well I I guess we can go to the next one
I'm having fun with these stories so far
well I can share you um
I can share you off the top of my head
maybe like a memory a birthday memory
birthday memory you know it's not okay
it's not interesting I remember this off
the top of my head though my birthday
um by birthday nine nine when I was
still in the egg my birthday it was well
I don't have you guys yet so I have to
celebrate my birthday with family or
like
um IRL friends and then it just so
happens that it was like um a test no a
test week a test month or something it's
weird it's pretty common actually so my
birthdays haven't been eventful because
it was normally like there's a test you
know and usually on my birthday it's not
really something to look forward to
because it would I would have to like
study and like wake up and do the exam
or something and I was so sad because
one time I asked people Mama you're like
yo can I go uh with my friends in the
weekend maybe eat and then my people
mama just said like no you know
you have to go like you have to go at
the end at the end of the month at the
end of the month or even like the
beginning of I forgot what it was but I
got so upset like basically if it's like
so many weeks ahead then it's already
too late the occasion like oh when when
all the exams are done you know next
month and I'm like I got so sad over
that like am I just gonna experience
this for the rest of my life
okay sorry for the trauma dump but if
you ask me that was one memory that
stuck out off the top of my head
but I'm fine I'm fine
but okay I guess I don't get that but I
guess I don't experience that for for
the rest of my life but still at that
time I was really sad hmm
like am I just gonna have to deal with
this every single time every year you
know
sheesh but anyways let's um
check out the next one see Rainy answer
one unlocked
mm-hmm
yeah save us from the trauma train uh
well okay let's uh check out check out
the next one
most memorable birthday memory was that
my parents made a huge Spandau oh I'm
saying happy birthday and put it on the
wall for my birthday party ones nice but
effective birthday gift for me is
definitely a sack of nuts even better
you sack of nuts two sacks of nuts you
hurt her guys I just wanted to celebrate
my birthday in famous food chain
restaurant
I want to experience it firsthand and
take pictures with the mascot yes that's
my dream
actually you know what I've never done
that either I have never been I've never
uh celebrated a birthday like in a fast
food restaurant with the mascot like
because you know like kids you can uh
you can go to the for example like Mac
YouTube or like KF yeah or something
like that and then book a birthday party
for kids and then oh invite your friends
and then there's gonna be like a section
for you in the shop just for your
birthday party and there's gonna be a
mascot and then all the kids are gonna
get gifts you know I've come to uh other
kids birthday parties like that but I've
never actually experienced one myself
so I don't know
maybe I could get a picture with Grimace
you're so right do they still leave
Grimace like on parties like that can I
do it now it's literally my birthday if
I phone up my nearest Mac you know can I
just be like yo I want birthday can I
have Grimace right
no
you should try it it's fun I know I've
gotten a hat before because I went but
not as the birthday person no it's the
birthday boy birthday girl
yeah too late for Grandma's oh shucks
but okay
okay
that is okay it is fine
um
I guess it's time for maracia to dress
up as Grimace well
so right it's all right
and well we have
the next one
what do we have here for the next one so
what's the tally right now oh this dude
was uh this dude was not traumatic this
dude was just cute
right
um
five four let's see if this changes it's
raining thank you so much for inviting
me thank you so much for having me here
so you want me to answer several
questions okay let's see what's the
first questions what is your
I am actually not a patient that really
considered birthday as a fairy special
day because you know every day is
special in its own way right but if you
really want me to answer this I can say
maybe it's the latest one oh that one
time when I could play games the whole
day 24 hours friends and just do
anything that I want to do with the
sensors support coming from all of the
viewers that's so wholesome warms my
heart in so many ways so
next question what will be the perfect
birthday gifts for you
[Music]
meditations too
about this I can say that I wanna do
what
you cannot hear anything
well
my laptop considered that as a spoiler
so it just got Auto muted
automated I see how but anyways happy
birthday one more time rainy I'm so
happy for you and have a blast
thank you bye-bye
oh that is very sweet hold on I think we
should have more
blast
ERS yeah
we're missing one so we're gonna change
that right now
we're gonna change that right now so
that was I think very wholesome no
trauma no trauma foreign
[Music]
before this I want to remind you guys
that the original song of rainy link on
the pin message AKA sip something is
premiering at 9 00 p.m which is in less
than
minutes so once the premiere starts
we're gonna do a watch along there so
ooh get ready
and then also after that the stream is
still not done so you guys go back here
and then we talk again okay
yay
new song High produced by mardiya
bintani
and then
I want to show you some Goods
and then because the goods will be on
sale also so be fast guys the goods will
be sold when it's ding
[Music]
so when it's ding ding ding nine you are
waiting for the premiere right but
there's still countdown so the strategy
is I will show you the item now and then
you will prepare so when the countdown
start you hurry up you buy the merch and
then after you buy the merch you can sit
and watch the MV
[Music]
yes
um
optimize flash sale yeah
hot
um
promo for birthday celebration 2023 on
sale September 9 GST
three special items OMG
what are you waiting for first it's an
acrylic stand and then we have a spicy
night towel I don't know why I named it
that but it's spicy you know and
murakia's hydration check will also give
Tumblr so it's a perfect package for you
if you want to exercise because listen I
heard you guys like to listen to my
songs when you guys are you know working
out or something so I made this special
for you guys who like to maybe run on
the treadmill or just like I don't know
do some sports maybe the acrylic stand
to you put on the treadmill so you're
more uh you know spirit Spirit
yes and then
let's go next
wait
hey yourself
nah
here is the birthday merch set what are
you waiting for acrylic stand
and spicy night towel which is a
minimalistic design uh you guys will see
the bigger image later and bonus
postcard for you guys who uh uh buy
everything and morata's hydration check
tumbler with a More minimalistic Design
I personally am a fan of minimalistic
design so for those of you who like it I
think this is perfect for you
tada
and birthday merch set purchase bonus by
funasensei a postcard with a duplicated
foil stamp autograph oh very cutesy gold
it matches very nice and look at that
hair you know oh so oh so nice I don't
know if you can zoom in but I don't
think you can zoom in but I think the
info will be on the website and then you
can see the bigger image it's very
manaoan picture of rainy wearing uh
wearing pants long pants and then the
undo is showing the midriff is showing
which is the point which is very cool
um
you're using the chair well it's for
photography purposes so it's okay
and then
sure
and then the acrylic stand look at that
very nice right the size is
approximately
150 times 95 millimeters so nine
centimeter times 15 centimeter which is
pretty big oh really
I think pretty big ish
what do you think
and the base is seven six times seven
six millimeters so that's seven point
six yeah so I think it's uh I think it's
pretty big you know not not very small
so I think it's good the bigger the
better right
um
yes and the material is of course it's
an acrylic stand it's acrylic
pretty big Disney and then the spicy
night towel which has the big windows
and has pavolia rain attacks and
Feathers I think it's really good
especially for people who don't really
who prefer more like discrete designs I
think it's very elegant while also being
able to support your Oshi and if
somebody looks at you and she's also a
rainy fan they'll immediately recognize
like oh that's pump it says football
you're raining you're also a fan or
something I think it's perfect spicy
night I think you know look at that
details it's so nice right the flooring
and the yeah I feel like it's very
elegant it's good I would use it
uh also background illustration by futa
Sensei uh size approximately 84 times 34
cm and the material is polyester and
nylon good for your body I'm sure
it'll make a cool background yeah of
course it is a very cool background it's
a long towel
[Laughter]
yes anyways that's cool
and then oh I also have real pictures by
the way
um later I will show you and morata's
hydration check tumbler again with the
minimalistic design it has uh
compilations of text nine nine whole
life ID pavolia Arena's birthday
celebration just uh you know so you can
actually bring it to the office without
people thinking like look at this guy
has an anime girl waifu you know for
those who need to be more discreet it's
all right you can bring it to the office
and nobody will bat an eye
and we have size approximately seven
nine times one four five mm and volume
is 350 milliliter uh for those of you
who have dispenser it would be great I
guess and material is from stainless
steel and the As and the lid is for from
polypropylene and silicone rubber so I
guess it's great you know
I guess it's great of course right
why wouldn't I be part of my wife well
listen sometimes there's just like a
regulation maybe you work in a company
that says no anime tumblers what are you
gonna do about it then well if you have
the pavolia hydration check tumbler no
need to worry you can show off that oh
I'm a big portfolio Arena fan while
still not breaking company's terms
right oh and then
okay basically bundled sales birthday
merch set and basically that and then
individual sales would be acrylic stand
towel and tumbler and these are some
real pictures and I guess there's
nothing to scale but this is what it
looks like pretty much
the acrylic stand
and this is what the
tumbler looks like look it looks nice
right I know where they take this
picture
and this
is the
Town wall and everything nice
I think it's very nice personally what I
think I think is very fashionable
acrylic stand for the Rainy the towel
not and not to anime the Tumblr not to
anime you know so it's very good for
like the people who are like uh you know
I want discreet and it's very
fashionable as well yep and by the way
Premiere is almost starting and sales is
almost starting as well so
the link if you refresh is already in
the description box yes apparently very
cool
premium item one minute to the premiere
so
if you guys want
please check the description box and
sales is already you know you can buy
hmm anyways one minute for the premiere
so we can already stand by on the room
in the room room Premiere will begin
shortly it says let's go
let's freaking go
and I think I need to
download some stuff
oh my God it's so loud the premiere
sound
[Laughter]
it's premiere time
it's premiere time it's premiere time
I want to download stuff
okay
I need to write that we're watching the
premiere now
watching the premiere now
watching the premiere Now link on pinned
comments I'm just gonna repeat that I'm
just gonna keep repeating that watching
the premiere now watching Premiere now
okay I'm writing it
watching Premiere now
link on
Lich okay link on pinned message
let's see I have I have it I have it
let's go
uh
okay we're ready
we're ready
let's go
yeah so guys what's the 12th what's the
twice speed trick that you guys are
telling me
does it help with like delays or what I
don't know
order complete let's get it let's
freaking oh March secure let's go now
let's enjoy the premiere
birthday set or it shows the latency oh
really it works on desktop only okay
next time I will do it
[Music]
uh subtitles will be added after the
stream by the way
yes
hmm
okay yeah Oh My Healthcare I have the
bgm on the whole time but I trust you
guys muted me anyways
[Laughter]
nice so yeah rainy original song is
called sip some tea Lenny
tada
sip some tea is now really I mean not
really released original song sip some
tea vocal by pavolia Rainey produced by
mardial and lyric by afia atalia and
martial September 10th
local time release and it will be
available on iTunes Apple music Apple
music Spotify and Etc and you can
celebrate the release by posting
sipsumpty rainy let's go
thank you very much thank you for your
Harvard no thank you for always
listening to Wayne a anyways tips and
see here is uh you know it's like I said
before with sun small it's more of an
uplifting song actually but it's kind of
like
like friend differently I feel like you
know just in a more cool way you know I
hope you can listen to sip something
when maybe you know when you're working
out when you're starting your day when
you're driving when you're working you
know when or when you feel some things
when you think like oh life is hard or
something and maybe if you hear
something and uh if you hear something
like this song and it will make you feel
better it would make me really really
happy
um
oh
yes yes yes yes yes
[Laughter]
Let It Go doesn't mean letting go of the
wheel if you're driving okay no don't
don't just drive safe okay it was great
thank you thank you thank you uh please
listen to it lots I'm actually you know
what as we speak I'm gonna add the
subtitle now
I'm gonna add the subtitle now as we
speak so you guys can refresh and the
subtitles are gonna be there
give me a second
[Music]
love
yeah I'm very very happy with this song
you know I had a great time recording
this so we can know the full translation
because this is my first time this is my
first time singing uh Indonesian and
English at the same time
yes
so there is the uh there's the
Indonesian version the whole pre-chorus
is uh
the whole pre-chorus is
Indonesian I can translate it Loosely
for you it's like
um
it's like
just just like a winged uh P foul I will
conquer the night with
the wind magic and I will
guys
[Laughter]
oh let's wait for the translation
hey come on I'll invite yeah I like it
I'll I'll bring and invite like everyone
who's asleep to fight against the world
or something a little bit dramatic right
[Music]
don't forget and I'm like of course I
didn't forget well after we go after we
upload the subtitles
after we upload the subtitles we still
have more entries and of course we don't
we need the Cliffhanger we need the
Cliffhanger to be you know
laughs
we need to we need to sit to the end
right the trauma the trauma and the no
trauma
give me give me a second
[Music]
Indonesian subtitle Japanese subtitle
and Javanese subtitle you guys's
favorite I love how Javanese and
Japanese is next to each other what did
you guys think about the song At first
listen because apparently I guess this
Premiere is your first listen right what
did you guys think about the song nice
wait yeah guys
oh wait guys
did you bang or something thank you a
great driving beat I'm glad I'm glad
because a lot of people like say like oh
I listen to your song while I go to the
gym or driving so I'm glad that it can
help
as well let's upload the Japanese
subtitle guys OMG
Japanese
okay
publish okay and then Japanese
Japanese
okay publish
and then upload Indonesian
Indonesian
you guys already understand Indonesian
yeah
yes
thank you
[Music]
oh what is this subtitles
and upload the English
publish okay I think it should all be
good
I think it should all be good and
everything should be published and you
guys will see subtitles of English
Japanese and Japanese and remember the
song isn't released yet at the moment
but as soon as it hits September 10th
2023000 you guys will be able to listen
to it at iTunes Apple music Spotify and
Etc and buy the song digitally thank you
so much guys for the support
yes and then let's continue
let's continue with initiative
let's continue with
this one wait there give me a second
hmm
let's add this
[Music]
okay
this one
is
okay
let me see this and immediately pass
this oh that's Shuba
oh not this one it's the other one sorry
sorry
it's this one I think
huh
not Shuba
guys
[Music]
um
I think it's this one it might be this
one
it might be this one
okay okay okay
it's not this one but it's this one
okay
yes next one is our beloved not cat
Shuba will be last yes
because I think I accidentally pressed
undo and remove
okay and then sorry boss first and then
I resize thank you
and then I will do this too okay
okay should be good let's start with
Jetta
happy birthday rainy
yes
happy birthday
okay I I have uh questions what is your
most memorable birthday memory I don't
remember
I don't remember I'm a time traveler
okay it's pretty tough my most memorable
memorable birthday memories when I when
bustle offered basil and secretary
offered to be part of the ingredient for
my birthday cake nice that was cool yeah
I totally happened yeah
happened yet uh what would be the
perfect birthday gift for you I want to
receive maximum power
from raining maybe she wants to be
tonjour the birthday celebration you
would like to do but you haven't had the
chance to oh I want to re-enact this
scenario where a bunch of people like a
lot of people would Gather in one place
and all of us would have the same
birthday and then we can be like hey
happy birthday oh thanks you too happy
birthday okay let's Thunder each other
and see who will be the last birthday
person standing who will she thinking
like the title who will be the only one
who could celebrate their birthday we
love that yeah I I don't know what do
you think
that's brilliant I love this girl can I
just like marry her or something and
then we could be like the the kind of
evil couple you see in like dramas you
know like oh you know like haha of
course we can concoct such as this kind
of evil plan because there's two of us
you know I think that would be great you
guys support that right
yes
yeah scheming couple
my Reverb is on yes it is on was it not
on before okay anyways
but that's great
truly interesting we love it
so what was that that was I think
wholesome because it's not really
traumatic for her it's just traumatic
for
um the basos right
well let's see the next one
[Music]
happy birthday
oh my gosh happy birthday
okay okay I am speaking into your soul
right now to wish you a happy birthday
anyways
um so you have some questions for me yes
I do you have some questions for me to
answer
the first question will be
what is your most memorable birthday
memory
I guess okay so um here's a little story
um before I entered Holo life before I
became a part of hollow life yes yes I
didn't really
um I didn't really celebrate my birthday
so
my my birthday celebration
was the first time I had my birthday
celebration was my first birthday in
whole life no
it was it was pretty memorable
my first birthday celebration will be
the most memorable birthday celebration
for me
[Music]
the second question
what would be the perfect birthday gift
for you
the world
[Music]
um I mean your love you're my love I
would give you the world my love is mine
too the perfect present for me
your love baby yes I Need Your Love or
else I will I will trust well no well no
ancient weapons don't trust they don't
rush anyways yeah
totally not totally not something says
like the world or sacrifices
and the last question
a birthday celebration you would like to
do but haven't had the chance to oh so
dismissed
I guess
um I want to have I want to have my
birthday celebration in the outer space
yeah that would be really cool even for
Yago
is fine somewhere that is not earth oh
somewhere that is not earth I guess I
should ask
him
we got some famous people well that's it
yeah yeah thank you so much for having
me Rainey and happy birthday happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you
[Music]
this is so cute it's so cursed but she's
so cute well
what's the judgment on that one guys
cute I feel like we're learning more
about the other people I mean the other
Holo mems instead of me but I think I'm
learning a valuable lesson to hear I'm
very entertained right now it's like
they're giving me gifts and I'm like
what is this this is so Priceless no
trauma detected okay
yeah well I guess it's not really trauma
but it's good that she finally can
celebrate her birthday and whole life
surrounded by lovely lovely people like
the lovely person she is
traumatic for viewers
but it's it's wholesome I think you know
like ignore the nature of the um to Anya
or dark Anya or the content itself is
very very wholesome I think
but well
this will be the next one will be
the last one are you guys ready
so far we have had three holotoris uh me
not included and they all have
a traumatic birthday experience
but let's see and even me off the top of
my head I told you guys something pretty
sad and let's see if this last one will
break the curse
are you guys ready can ozora Subaru
the holotori save the other holotori's
reputation for being promotory let's see
what the trauma meter says and here we
go now Shuba birthday story
I want to celebrate your birthday so
from now I
you are three crystals okay fast
that is your most memorable birthday
memory okay
okay my most memorable birthday memory
is my first birthday after showing her
life
because I was so happy to receive
many many many passive presents I have
to pass the message from wait this is so
wholesome and the horrible member
what would be the perfect boss they give
to for you okay
my perfect birthday present is
break the English record English lesson
for real
for always teaching me English kind kind
reason thank you
no
glitch on YouTube
but haven't had that chance too
hey I want to do
the Doodles
because remember
cannot meet
each other usually ah yes so I want to
do the special birthday cakey party with
all heart remember
baby happy happy birthday next time I
want
I cannot
I cannot wait
me for you yeah yay okay okay see you
next time
happy birthday
oh that's so awesome well you can count
on her for being the most wholesome
well that's it that's the mystery solved
Subaru the trouble meter says
no trauma detected Sue bottle breaks the
curse
hola Tony happy Holo Tony wholesome oh I
would love to teach her more English
and I want the whole otori birthday cake
party to be a reality yeah yeah I think
it's gonna be so amazing because then
normally like we're so International
it's hard for us to like get together
it's like a miracle you know it's like a
miracle but I want to do holotori you
know party
that would be nice under normal
circumstances we have to arrange if we
want to meet you know
in Tori National
[Laughter]
it's four out of eight for a trauma
non-trauma by the way but I guess like
dama wins generally the experiences were
mostly wholesome and great yeah
some
I think you know what it's been a great
it's been a greater
stream right we did uh we did um well
you know this is supposed to be a
birthday you know interview thing in the
format of a video but I don't know how
we ended up having a another mini game
of Our Own in the middle well I can
answer some of my own questions
um second what is the perfect gift for
me the perfect gift for me is a very
nice work-life balance
that's a very boring answer but that's
what I could think of off the top of my
head
um
three what's a birthday party you've
always wanted to do but you haven't
really had the chance to I just want to
have like a very cool
I want to have a very cool birthday live
um where I can eat okay I can do
everything basically like one day you
know like one of those like a big
brother shows like not really big
brother because that seems like you have
no freedom but like 24 hours of rainy
party till from Midnight until another
midnight and then it's just like a
documentation of it of me like doing
different parties with friends and maybe
make like something
um a video out of it I think it would be
a cool project you know
yeah like it's not really 24 hours 24
hours but just like picking the
highlights but it was just like from
okay 24 hours what does rainy do but
from Midnight to midnight again but it's
full of like parties and stuff like that
I think it would be really really cool
and we can yeah of course like inviting
friends like
and everybody you know right that sounds
amazing but please make it real well see
fingers crossed you know
bungee jumping in skydiving one day rain
is dollhouse what
yes
remember and remember uh good sales are
available you can access you can access
now
I can give you this yes hello hello
everybody you can check birthday
celebration
2017 three special items or buy them
individually and but if you buy the
birthday merch set you will get a bonus
postcard illustration by funasensei
thank you so much and you also have sips
and tea which is which will be available
after midnight uh in your local time
available for listen and while you wait
you can watch the MV even more I feel
like the subtitle should be updated
right now in case you want the meaning
of the song because it's the first time
rain has been raining doing English and
Indonesian at the same time so maybe you
guys need the translation and you will
have it
they are in but anyways before we end
the stream I want to show you guys a
little something
just look inside the subtitles that's
great
um drum roll please so uh
so the reason I um I'm wearing this
outfit today which by the way looks
really good right below the whole
lighting and stuff because I've been
using the other one the other one but
I'm using this one today the reason why
I'm using this outfit today is because I
really really want to show you something
from this outfit yes
are you guys ready
so you know how I can actually you know
hello check check mic check how I can do
this right
I can also um and I can also maybe
do this I know I can do this
don't do this right but I think you know
but
if I
do this well you guys don't really see
me do this much
but if I do this
somehow I get denied the use of a mic
have you guys ever seen me use a mic
when I'm not wearing a jacket
that's right because they don't allow me
to do that
but
not anymore
now
I have received special from
to hold the mic while I'm wearing
this jacket not wearing this jacket I
mean just like not wearing the jacket
hello hello everybody
and that is an improvement of my rights
as a p-file in whole alive as the P fell
in hole I just want to say thank you for
everybody who let me use the mic when
I'm not wearing a jacket to truly fully
gratitude I love you and then I will
make you some opportunity
um the best that I can thank you all
and um also I guess
well okay I'm just gonna wear this again
um and also
um you know you know sometimes I feel
like I feel kind of bald you know when I
wear this I mean not really bald
um I kind of feel like you know
sometimes maybe I need a hat I mean I do
already have a hood you know I do
already have a hood but when I'm not
wearing this
kind of feel like
kind of empty no
you know I thought like maybe I need
some accessories right
so I'm just thinking what what would be
good
so I told myself
what if I just go to the store
and
get this pair of glasses
I think it would be great and sunglasses
is great because you can pair them with
anything so like even even when I'm like
maybe uh you know like maybe when I'm
wearing this I can still have it on
Hello like hey I'm wearing glass and
there's there's the little heart there's
like little um I don't know if it's a
broken heart or just like a heart but
it's it's there let's go
sunglasses my eyes are not blocked but
I've wanted I see like I've wanted the
sunglasses ever ever ever ever ever ever
since I had this outfit and I finally
got my dreams come true I got my
sunglasses thank you so much and I can
wear it like this too
sunglasses that's nice yay
that's all right
glasses are very versatile I agree yes
and well I guess that's not all can
oh my goodness can you believe that is
not all aren't you still bald then no
you get my points
can you believe that is not all well
so I was just thinking right
I'm thinking
I feel like
this outfit maybe needs some uh changing
you know maybe like I like this but
maybe needs some variation you know I
mean like we can take off the we can
take off the hood we can take off the
jacket but being humans agree as greedy
as we are I mean I'm a p foul but still
pretty similar I'm just like we always
want more more more and more right we
always want more we never have enough so
I was just thinking even though I can
you know dress up so many different ways
with this outfit I still think you know
what maybe would be it would be great if
I could switch up something else
and you know so I asked well can I and
their answer is yes so you know I told
myself okay it's time to reveal it to
you guys this
this new thing about me
and that is a
instant hair changing exclusive to Idols
I think this looks especially good if
I'm like doing this face
yay so it's a little bit of a different
look
um
you hair wig confirmed now
hey it's a different feel definitely I
uh
on purpose I wanted to go for a more
different feel so that it's more
interchangeable if I want a different
look maybe I like this one maybe I'm in
the mood for like the other wavy hair
maybe I'm in the mood for the straight
ponytail I think it's great yes is it
compatible with the glasses well let's
find out it is oh my God maybe it is
yay with glasses and without jacket of
course
I think this looks nice
hello hello hello
and do you guys want to know how long
the hair is I think I can show you guys
to do
I think I can show you guys how wait it
it goes on forever what the okay it goes
on oh okay it's this long
it's this long wow it's so long actually
what
that's crazy
it's as long as it's thigh it's knee
length
it's kneeling
that's crazy
we love it interesting whoa okay
so I like I actually quite like this
look you know just like this I think
it's great
yay
in love with that ponytail thank you
what do you guys think oh what's the
what's the what's a good look here
should I wear oh maybe I should just
take it off or maybe yeah
um
should I wear the sunglasses I think I
should I think the sunglasses looks good
okay cool
yeah
yay
spiky scrunchie I like it's a very nice
detail I feel like
the shoulders must show yes I have a
showing my shoulders right now
ah I'm gonna be using this room a lot I
guess so it's my room now so I don't see
why not
but anyways it makes me look very idly
okay thank you well in case you guys
wanna do a little um screenshot I can I
can do this
shoe I don't I don't do the green screen
because okay you know what
maybe like this
huh
yay
[Music]
I think this face looks better with some
Combos and
I got these upgrades oh my you know
you know oh this looks perfect oh nice
this looks good I like it
this looks sad I'm sad
this looks haha not sad and this looks
wow
insane is great
like the angry smiling
it's great there will be more
opportunities where you can screenshot
oh shoot oh anyways yeah I didn't show
you guys this but I can also wear the
hood with this personally not a big fan
though
or maybe I am a big fan but I prefer
this one I prefer why I'm not wearing
this
for this one I prefer this hair
who yes I think different hairstyles
shines in different uh different
occasions they used to look fabulous
though
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
we confirmed thank you
perfect for ring fit yeah it's very
Sports exactly
yes and I think um we have reached the
end of our achara today
I'm gonna
um so in summary we have
we have received info from other Holo
members some crazy crazy stories thank
you very much for the Holo members who
have spared their time to record a video
for me this wouldn't have been the same
without you thank you for making this
program possible I had a lot of fun and
I'm sure everybody had the had a lot of
fun as well
yes and um the craziest story there's a
lot of crazy stories but a lot of it was
wholesome as well it's amazing thank you
and thank you for all the kind birthday
wishes and also a birthday celebration
2023 you can get the birthday merch set
and also individually remember if you
get the birthday merch set you get a
bonus though and the link is available
under the description box so you guys
can check it out and also Rainey has
released through an original song linked
on the pinned comment which is called
Civ 17 produced by mardial and it will
officially release on a music platform
such as iTunes Apple music and Spotify
on September 10 midnight in your local
time and you can post your thoughts are
celebratedly released by posting hashtag
sip some tyranny and posting it on
social media thank you so much guys yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah extreme sip some tea
I'm very glad you guys like it please
stream it a lot and wow but this is the
end of rainy
stream this is the end of rain and
birthday stream that's it oh my goodness
I was like preparing I Was preparing for
this and I was like oh feeling so oh how
am I gonna do it but then wow
today starting from the countdown
everything turned out to be a blast
thank you guys for celebrating it with
me I really really really enjoyed it
what was your favorite part from the
whole rundown of the Rainy birthday
um
it was an amazing day yeah
thank you for organizing this whole
celebration no thank you the trauma dump
I think this one's my favorite part okay
the song and the hair the model stories
were awesome
nice new hair cake yeah yeah I think I'm
glad that you guys have different
answers because that means like each
part of the birthday celebration is uh
you know good in their own way fits your
tastes maybe different people have
different preferences and I'm glad that
people like different things
I still have the cake and I'm gonna eat
them I'm gonna finish them in a week I
guess I'm gonna share with my friends if
um yeah if we have time to hang out
laughs
cake was funny
yeah thanks
um I really really can't wait to have
this chance to celebrate more with you
guys well it's not just birthday that we
can't celebrate there's a lot of things
that we can celebrate celebrate every
day and also we just hit some Milestone
last time 777 I think we could make
something out of that thank you so much
guys and um
any last words I don't know
there's pretty much no announcement from
me uh but I have released a ton of stuff
and I just reveal new hair as well so
you guys will probably be seeing this
hair quite a bit
just you know when you just you know
upload not upload when you just like
revealed something you just want to like
wear it wear it all the time you know so
I'm just gonna like okay maybe I'll wear
this
okay
[Music]
have a great rest of your birthday
thanks so much yes and that's it I can't
believe it's coming to an end but I
really really thank you for the bottom
of my heart let's celebrate more
together okay and let's just have even
more fun next year okay
thank you very much for your attention I
hope you guys have a great day and
everybody really don't want to end the
stream but it's his time
let's end it I'll see you guys very very
soon
everybody and bye
bye you next time
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]