[Music]
what else is
NS my
Tail so Yeah I would like to say thank
you guys for joining and uh we're still
kind of in the beginning so First thing
first please group with your team
[Applause]
[Music]
[Clap  hands]
once Za Hello and
[Applause]
Za ye
pleas
for back twice
[Music]
i i you guys are ready
yeah are you guys ready Are you guys
posi
[Music]
you do is what is your team name What is
your
[  Music]
team next te de
te
l
Ma good for
the GR May
r
r better
than do
now Where's your
partner i
to i TR to cont
[Music]
Okay gu late now
Hello let's go oh wait no no Just go
around
he I'm going  to what materials we can
use
for a while
Um as you guys can see that uh today is
the day of H ID Um
but we are still waiting for like one person
left But There will
be R already start for the introduction
for each member
so actually  pretty
nervous but let
Justin
requ you during Simon can you please
speak
slowly i can do
that back and forth
left okay jump jump
Okay thank
you Thank
you next
is
[Music]
next haiikokai
[Music] [
Music]
yeah okay
congratulations
[Music]
Malam
Indones
sa Indonesia
[Musik]
Can you introduce your
team you
guys wow
team that our team name should be team
not H JP
s j okay
okay Inside bracket not and then Ho JP
okay okay
okay the not  is really
important part of our team i see
Yes Yeah I hope you enjoy today and Um
There will be a Treasure Hunt game So
your teamwork will be uh tested
yeah teamwk don't your
[Music]
[Applause]
team teeh gambat  t So I guess
[Music]
what Co cobboy left Hello Kobo Hello Kobo
Hello kobo kobo have you eaten Have you
eaten yet Kobo eat first
Kobo have you eaten this,
Jeta also gave me herbs earlier ah great
cool cool cool cool cool
cool k Yes  be enthusiastic, be enthusiastic, yes, that's
right, if there's something that
might be troublesome because you have to
carry it yourself, ma'am, for
a while, be enthusiastic,
ma'am, we're like Kobo, don't you
know if you like eating,
this is an introduction to everyone,
okay
[Music]
Mina atttion please
[Music  ]
ATT
OK, the committee is all three, oh oh,
three of them,
okay, guys, E,
because maybe we're one less, but that's
okay, first of all, we'll reply
First e game will be Treasure hunts them
There will be around 10 spots of
Treasure  it can be in a chest it can be
in a shelker it can be in a dropble it
can be in Anywhere Um So
your mission is to find it every
chest has around three
emeralds you can use for the Ma later
is a hint around the area  that you can
[Music]
check Okay so before we started Let's
sleep first again
Is there enough BS I don't know Survival
for the is it
enough everyone It's okay I i can
Oh than
you thank you
[Music]
the time the time for hunting  The
Treasure will
be 10 minutes after 10 minutes We gather
here again we will we will ask you to
gather Here by
chat wait where is The
Treasure
around on the first floor it's on the
very first floor with the many grass
[Music]
we don'  t break anything right we don't
Break The Stones don't
need my RPG senses are
tingling Where the treas
are everybody ready
ready everyone I'm going to count the
timer So Are you guys
ready
Okay everyone stand
by yes okay I'  m going to it
in we need to Two and then we find go
Find your Treasure
[Music]
I
can't
[Music]
it can be up here too k k k
k are we allow to destroy anything
yeah yeah you guys allow to droy anything
Don'  t
Wor come here here this What is
this get it get it get it I got it I got
it
got Oh yeah
most of the content
we need to find
need now they came over
here don't
know Why should I help
you ureate I don't  know I don't know
but what's what's with the
buttons doesn't do anything What's with
the
buttons i i see it do I have to dig do I
have to dig if
you Fine never never mind That's just
me find it Where is it Muna did  they
find it and and I don't have to look
here anymore I don't know you have to
[Applause]
every what
what Maybe you can go to another place
if you feel like they already search it
I know No they would have  reacted they
would have reacted if they found it I
have no idea I'm looking here for like
five minutes now and I have you already
checked the book
Yeah it says like Among Flowers BRI
great chest Hi from side
so maybe they did find it I  don't know
among the
Flowers I'm trying I'm also trying try
hard I'm going
toers wait this one
Can we destroy the
bo oh
oh is this one gone
yet in the first with to open it you
need in
mana  did he accidentally destroy it
ouch
oh Li
Naon Li did someone destroy the flowers or not
[Music]
I don't know if I destroyed the flowers I don't
know Oh
no the one
whose hat was inside
coy isn't there behind it his brother b was
destroyed by Bu coy Anjir what's wrong  Eh,
you can get those flowers
anywhere in
[Music]
here and then you just leave
like that
[Laughs]
Yes, ara
descendu sor Soror, don't steal it,
coycurin,
ouch, what a shame,
Ouch, there's nothing underneath, Coy, is
n't he?  it's not
destroyed,
it's destroyed,
it's destroyed, it's not
taken, it's not taken, it's destroyed, it's not taken,
gosh, I want another one,
this team
Oh they didn't hear
me SH one
stand This is the
team This is the Hardest One
that way Heeh that's actually where you forgot to
take it Oh
yeah that means you put four
yeah
ah yeah that's okay that's free real
estate Oh yeah that's okay hint for
[Music]
good kids
and to find CH  Where are to
anything he's just observing but he's just silent
like that's how it should be
yeah yeah
eh
where is this
one Oh
okay Oh okay I looked once and
found it straight away how is this oh my god oh my
god Oh there
is one oh no oh yes it's gone there's something
wrong with it
while taking it Wow  If you
look at this, it looks like
this is the behavior of the students,
how about
this, this, this, this is easy, actually, this is
easy, that's it. Oh yes, yes, it's been taken, it's been
taken, which means it's done,
what's that?
Is this there or is
n't this already destroyed?
Hah, it
was destroyed. There was something stuck earlier,
hah, it's been 10 minutes, okay, let's
go back, already finished we go
[Music]
back already finished, go back go
back the
b go back go
[Music]
back
n n
[Music  ]
dat how many do you have I have EMP Wow
that's great you have
EMP Wow that means you lost two
yeah You should be able to get en
You should be able to get en
[Music]
nice I got four
emeralds
every wait Who found Who found whato
Kobo found four and I  don't know how
what I want to check her POV after this
Yeah I don't even know so you guys did
you guys find any No I know what to
search for no no did you guys know that
there's actually one really close by
yeah  probably right here ah what the
hell that's what it's supposed to look
likeers and chest and H see i would i
would recognize
[Music]
that everyone comes here everyone
everyone
[Music]
down Found A got three emeralds but it's
Who's got the Emerald Who's got  the
Emerald How
many How many How many Emeralds you have
Um in total nine wow
wow nine emeralds that's me that's me
like CH treasures if treasures yeah fre
treasures How many emerals you got
That's
awesome I
know so you guys understand understand
the puzzle That's
[Music  ]
nice oh I gu I guess it's
F How many emerals you got
Have you got the
oneish
that's
finished but she found the time
Fin That's not [ __ ]
fair did you get that one all right then
I'll cheat in the other
games wait for someone
cheating  I'm not taking anything
now
everyone everyone
hello
hello Hi Attention
please ok thank you thank you for the
attention since we already done The
Treasure Hun so we have to go back and
the B to continue the Simon
[Music]
[Applause]
let  if we're in mame
[Music]
every Please go and let's go
It's okay you do pretty well what Simon
[Music]
says it's all
okay it's really like holding an elementary school child
[Laughs]
[Music]
i al
[Music  ]
Why list Toon
say why does it matter to
us Hello everybody are you guys all
[Music]
here 10 basically until they can
keep going okay
First I think based on the discord I
think so
[Music]
more we have like
demonst because is the top so goes First
[Music]
Okay
stand how
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Laughs]
basic is given Prom level 1 2 3 4 until
[Music]
so on then e if it's wrong it means
stop
already per level got
S
[Music]
ang ban
wait hold on hold on hold on hold
on
i i that's right, we made a group for
them
OK,
go ahead, use GR for the
participants螢ｰ okay okay
okay Hi Ma
[Music]
ha
hau OK
l
throw away three two
one throw away I throw away throw away oh ang it seems
like that's the way it is ma'am not throw away not
throw away
throw it again yes repeat
okay
throw it Hi
throw it don't give me a
committee bonus
Sal B it's better just leave it
again it's okay There will be later  two, we
repeat, we repeat, OK, it's
okay, just two, okay, throw two,
throw two
squats, two
one
R jkak
[Music]
go throw,
squat,
jump, three two
one, jump, squat, jump,
jump,
nice three
emeralds Emal sengi throw, throw,
squat, jump, jump, J forward
twice forward two times okay okay okay okay three
three two one w throw throw throw
squat jump jump
forward two forward two
UI ah
wow o o
SEG
throw
squat
jump forward
twice facing left left Oh
three two one
throw y
kok jump jump forward forward two left
left shrunk shrunk W ci ci ci
Yos Yos Yos Yos Yos Yos Yos ja sengwa throw
throw squat squat
jump forward two times two times face
left left face right right okay okay okay okay okay
three two one place
forge squat squat jump
forward jump two left  left
right
eh y sorry I didn't see Antoni Antoni
Antoniuh
left left right
okay I I saw it looks like
Yopi is wrong,
right, he should be facing right, but Yopi
should turn around, Yi ngap keuna pasadap
right
Al Oh, that means it's wrong, Heeh
Koko Bera
S eh i l  Yes en is wrong l okay
[Music]
okay go go
[Applause]
this is the emerald yeah Oh okay
okay thank you thank
[Music]
youk
any any
please oh okay
Nice
Hello guys
[Music]
Ready The R I think I think it's better
to stand  in the R for the
beginning than
face Ma there face me I'm here
Hello here here here in
I'm blind apparently Ok so The rule
is like explained during the practice so
you guys will be given
Progressive
Commands
Commands and the more  you can do
it the better more emerals you get yes
and if one of you eh failed question
yeah do we do it at the same time or do
we Yes at the same time
because There will be th two one hmm okay
okay  okay Are you ready now okay okay okay
start from the first one okay the first
one ready yes
throw three two one let's go how
thisame ok
Okay there is no sound there So this is okay
Or not
okay sor can't see it from the plv I
think you have to  in my place de
let it look
Okay okay okay you you can take your item
back Okay Okay
next next you guys are right so next one is
throw
J th two one
okay
ye Okay Ok we're going we're going fast
we're  going fast next throw squat
jump three two
one oh
getting hot getting hot next is throw
squat jump forward twice
OK three three two one
you
for what
you so you were supposed to throw and
then you J and then jump but you throw
and then you
jump
sry She's h
j
understandable
So that's what you guys mean uh pass three
rounds Then I will give you not bad
three emeralds
here Thank you Thank
you I shouldn't be the one studying You
should have studied You
should I just forgot the order It's not
like  I forgot the
meaning uh you guys
cany now Thank you wait H on Oh hello
hello
Please speak slowly
Ma okay slowly everyone stand by in the
red
area beat jongkong jump
throw it's forward left right
okay stand on the on the red area Please
am i on  the red ya ya
stand in the red
[Music]
area thank are ready are ready
It will ey
Ok R ready k ready yeah
Ok ak
two one
go so scared You're starting off a
difficult one because Sounds like So
that's like l three stu  or is it just
and one one
ST ah Okay
okay
me so next is l
J two one have a question have a
question okay no question Just do
it Wa Okay l if they don't say it maybe
it's only one time
you want to  stay J That's also fine
don't worry you got it you got it ah OK
but you know Eh Yes that's it next next is
getting harder
throw
squat jump
throw jkok
jump OK throw squat
jump let's
go OK next next next
throw
squat jump forward twice  okay
squat jump forward two
De that was F times already right next
next next Em Okay OK Okay next
throw
squat
jump forward twice facing left
[Music]
eh
lempkok
jump forward
twice please left face Hi see
name How Kis continues already continues
Okay next  OK next eh
throw
squat lom four forward twice face
left face right face right three two
one
conkok lempau
eh LP and right and here and here and
then after that forg one forg I forg and
then if turn and then If I Turn Right do
I  Turn like 45 De right oh well I mean
yeah As long as you turn right right
what I'm confused about no As long as
you turn right I think so I guess That's
correct okay yeah can we he no what who
was
wrong What did I  do wrong No You should
you should end it with meaning that
the other way
so first faing to re and then faing to
me what I faced right you don't say How
many Degrees right yeah no No that's 90
degrees Yeah but you didn't  say How many
Degrees I think it's just like
it's a misunderstanding it's H
up means only like kind of liking here
and then because this is KITT and then
right is like to the right of this
position So you have to face here
yeah so that means four emeralds  five
was it five right five five five
emeralds five
emeralds
yeah there you go Okay thank you That's
f you guys actually did great Don't
Worry yeah still the highest so
far no no I think got five right but
anyway still the
same
over It's Not  it's not over Hello are
you
ready We have a question yes oh So if you
say like kitty
uh KITT forward does that mean I Turn first
and then i i go forward Yep yep
front side facing at the moment ok
Okay Ok So if Hadan I just Run
like if facing right face right just
face
right face right
Run no worry it's not as complicated as
you guys think it is
ok your position you can stand on the red
dots here red block Thank you stop
Ok Are you ready for the first one yeah
yeah
OK the first one I'm going to tell you
is throw
Zeta ngadap front dong Zeta ngadap there
zetaapadap same muna ngadap muna ngadap
muna but that was right how come that was right
next no no facing the right way don't
Wor back item
OK moving  on moving on the second
is throw squat three two
one
Okay sry take take backem
so nervous in my life
before relax relax the third one
throw
squat jump
two
one gettingot here next is throw
squat jump forward two times three two
one
okay you can get back  to your
position strong
thank going strong next
throw
squat jump forward twice facing left
three two one
more ID
you can get back to position get back
to going strong next one
is
throw
squat jump twice facing left face
right
3 two
one Oh
W  wow wow wow I didn't
expect the first one to get this far
yeah
okayay going strong going even stronger
next
one l
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times three two
one
Wow ye
ye wowow
okay okay Oh my God Okay  even even
Harder next one next one Let's go it
never
I'll start again
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right back five times hit three times
three two
one crazy chat that was crazy
are for the
next go go go Before I Forget
next time next time get into position
Okay red block please Za thank you okay
okay next one
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left
face right back five times hit three
times jump four times three two one
[Music]
one the last
round let's go the  last one Are you
ready here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right backward Li times Pul three times
jump four times run to the red block
three two
one Al crouch by accident
so apparently eh
am forgotten to eh backwards five
times
only only  f you are the highest so far
yeah the highest so
far than
[Applause]
on the back on the
back That's nine emeralds it would have
been 10 right if we got it I Yeah Yeah I
mean That's one less yeah yeah you
go  Thank you Thank you than you thank
you that is so well okay Where is
skyla
anjai okay okay okay okay I have faith in you guys Where should we face Oh face Muna face Muna face Muna face Muna okay thank you
yes you got a face face Muna
Ok  where
m The entrance entrance entry Look up
look
up I'm hereon
[Music]
Where is she here in the green
Okay okay Are you ready Can I just give
you the command now yes okay okay so
every time the command finish you
guys get  back to the red block Al right
and pick up any item you've thrown
the first one throw
three two one
OK that was easy moving on moving on
next throw squat three two one
OK next one
uh
throw squat jump three two one
I have Fa in you
next
throw squat jump forward twice
three two one
okay OK OK
next
throw
squat
jump forward twice facing left
three two one
we have to be patient okay yeah OK okay okay
you made it you made it don't
worry believe in yourself
yeah next one next  One OK here we go
throw
squat
jump forward twice face left face
right three two
[Music]
[Laughs]
one
apparently I don't know should I say
bot B yeah guys face left face right
face left face right yes face  left
face right not face left turn right
okay Wi had is left and the hadon is
right yeah oh I was like I was like
stopping here a bit and then I did that
okay okay okay That's
great you guys are great got F
[Music]
on up
thank you
[Music]
okay hello
helloo
hai yeah
yeah
[Music]
ha J
zomb
I Haj
Maru Haju Haju okay okay first
one
throw three two one go
throw
throw die
[Music]
die ad throw right
throw t Ti  throw
Ti
tor throw
throw
lemp
e okay
take the item again
Bu okay
sengwa
throw
squat three two one
go take lag
okaygiii
throw squat jump three two one go
uh
Wow ci-ji
Okay
throw
squat
jump forward twice three two one
go ye
that's
throwing
squat
jump forward twice face left three
two one
go k
k Don't die
yet I'm sorry but I just laughed
when I heard it okay okay
throw
squat jump forward twice face left
face
right three two one
go Oh together with them Heh kuku
k
He tu
face right face
left face left face right
Hidari  Migi Eh
migak or not, you guys turned right,
didn't you
turn right, turn
right, turn right, turn
right y
[Music] [Music]
Al
ak and
S
finish let's go to the
exit i will try to be
smart ye
don't confuse me with your Mask What  the
hell Oh
S like is talking to me but I see's face
[Music]
What Hi come on come on
downstairs come on go downair let go
downstairs W if you said that with Anya
voice then I would have really Fallen
for it
[Music]
also you should have
picked
yours or not, can't this already match
the place here
[Music]
y here
Thank
you
Minut yeah because we wait for one Minut
[Music]
anywayol just Open it
Yes
better better Who made it
okay okay
good how come you can't hear it How come
you can't
hear it What's up
[Music]
okaybody has each and will
howan apa h
[Music]
this so for the builders you guys will
go to the corner over
here and  you guys will see the Them for
yourselves so we made a room over here
and then will come in and see
it at the very corner don't don't come
in don't come in
this Are All To prevent anyone from
cheating so when  you know the answer do
n't come out
[Music]
Oh and Chat please don't spoil the like
what you see in the
builders side the
gu only just press like the right Okay
there you go go ahead Can I try and I
guess  when we're building it's best to
mute right
yeah also I think better ideas
with
both
see which one round do
come
pleases
Builder
[Music]
Okay This all of the builders for the
yeah yeah on
[Music]
the How to write
I have to sign the book and then Put
It's obviously just one
Guess
how do you write it
[Music]
Bu Go b b
Ok
guys you
guys
Yes hold on please
Run
one it's it's the time  girls again
fighting in a timely manner
[Music]
manner
in this is just like
we need to the round One
Okay
[Music]
the is round One
already
okay okay okay okay okay okay
Za Za
[Music] [
Music]
Ar your voice
I'll  face this way then okay yeah i
[Music]
guessakak in
group Thank you I appreci
itbody ready
[Music]
CH the committee is also leaving
Okay for the book
Ok time to count
[Music]
on tired ya iekak
anyway Okay let's count It
okay count it one
Minut one
Minut
Okay game start
in
three two
one
go go go go go go anj embarrassed Anji
embarrassed go go go go ho hoi hoi au
au
ipakes Aju Aju
oh
nice
man I I heard that sound
no it's
okay it's us  t
they are in
each
Ops
Jan teh
answer Ind what is it
called What is it called teh
eh even kapus
ah
please
the in the
[Music]
k WR down your answer and put it here
[Laughs]
okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
Oh Se
okay  okay Guys,
how do you
make the committee make two mistakes,
where does the sound disappear,
next round,
just let them do it for
a moment, this
sounds like hi, okay,
okay, Builder check, wait,
not yet, wait, wait, Bang
no
Bang No there,
OK I
[Music  ]
[Music]
yeah next
round How much
[Music]
let's go
oh no oh
no I want to put things away
Thank you than
youar right
sears I
forgot
no
here what the
[ __ ] we can't have sheers
yeah no you know what you can you can
you can I'm sorry
here Sorry Here's your shear Oh thank
you thank you and there ok
Oh Next
round are we ready should I check the
book and
it's ready
start
in one wait Three two
one
and
go one minute uh
it's pretty hard it's pretty  hard so
far who was this
R this
[Music]
jetta Giving It Giving It Giving It
Giving
It Call gru Me ni kinginging
before
forget it
[Music]
okay and this one is the attempted 2D
drawing and this one Wow super Massive
[Music]
is  like the closest one so
far this is this is like the closest
answer I
think the imagination is pretty much
Please put down the answer
okay okay thank you for the answer Thank
you for the answer I know you guys
can't hear me but Thank you  you for the
[Music]
answer Okay okay
in w w wow
wow yeah We should have Put Temple yeah
see Canada is the closest one Oh really
So Ju
please clean the W for the next round
Why is the writing small so the
writing is big
[Music]
let me let me  looks like screaming guys
eh
wrong like
this
This is yes oh sherku eh
sherker you hold it Oh this is a
dog thank you
Oh
okay ready
Okay game start
in
three two one
go what was that tea oh yes
Oh my
[Music]
God ouch k
[Music  ]
tu thiss
[Music]
egg ed Um SH this looks
like this looks like a gate What is
this I don't know we cannot see the
shape yet Yeah but we see
[Music]
oh
over done
Please put the answer in Black turnomom
[Music]
that's all
What's important is
everybody Ready
waitah lah don't take
it  you
Ops
[Music]
okay
oh
this picture is right
[Music]
okay
okay okay k this is here
or there I forget e who
was
this this is
switch time switch time oh switch time
If It's switch time it's a time not
switch time  For
me they are switching
[Music]
Indonesia
like
Impossible I gu pretty much
Impossible give it
Another 15 seconds gu
uh this is cool
anyway
i 5 seconds
more over
wrong
Please this is
already the last
okay
okay Oh not yet
[Music]
okay Okay Okay Okay Eh yeah this is
n't
enoughara ehka
[Music]
OK, who's the winner
then?
[Music]
ur supposed
to be k
[Laughs]
kakiii Shouldn't be this right?
Shouldn't there be another word? Is there another word?
Lag
answer correct answer
Oh my God it should be No, how come there's no sound OL?
Mute, OK?
Kam
eh no Kamer no no
Kamer
J okay
[Music]
from earlier ak
okay okay okay
okay where is it Oh I okay
okay
last easy easy Yes
easy eh the book is taken
[Music]
who's taking it  book
Hey wrong Hey bo who's taking it bo
okayo next Okay has everybody seen the
book
[Music]
z z taking it again or not
Z taking it again no Z afraid to take it again
here
[Music]
guys what donon are you
donon who took the book sokap
already oh
Are you ready to sing?
[Music]
laguwan oh
go
on, which glass is sharp,
which one is there?
nice oh oh this is nice oh
k oh
[Laughs]
[Music]
that is to
obvious that is to obvious no his name
tho But whether he can read or not that's all
Yes, yes, yes, that's true, Whether he's
anjir or not, that's
actually true  I can do it because I
don't understand it myself. Once you look at it, I'll
support you. Sis, I can read it. I ca
n't
[Laughs]
[Music] I
have too much of a brain,
but the answer is right,
ma'am. Ouch, not very specific. Ma'am, not very
specific. Yes, ma'am. He wrote what
you wrote.  write, ma'am,
hah, why is that like that?
How
come he wrote what I
wrote, yes, but the Japanese is also
true, yes, this is true, the
Japanese is yes, the Japanese is Japanese.
Yes, the literal Japanese is
this. Yes, the Japanese is this.
Oh yes, isn't it?  I forgot
Cuk
k what the heck
eh Wani this has been written yet I
think Yobi you've written it yet
[Music]
Eh tamzap great bro
H have another
glasses where's the
book
rakuda rakuda that's
dong perkuda that was
doubtful De who's
I'm
anjirah Oh this is there Wow  what is this
guys ak
[Music]
k good J
eh
cor cor
everyone ho hello hello oh no need oh
oh J please
[Music]
OK everyone De
mute mute don't i i mute mute everyone
mute Z I think
[Laughs]
deh nyaameame [
Music]
[Music  ]
There will be like three rounds So let's
go to the wrong together Shall We
Come on Come here Come here follow us
let's let's
go I Think first you guys need
to you know Click the bed just in
so you W spa outside
[  Music]
[Music]
again Come on up here
Come on up
here everyone
[Music]
Pa how many rounds will there be
ak
[Music]
G It's A Battle Royale
basically we're not going by groups
we're not going Solo everybody going at the
time and for the wool cutters You
are you are to press F1 the game
and for the
for you cannot
[Music]
crouch okay
well if if hitting is allowed then is
eating also allowed or like  what if you
die and don't fall i guess you're also
hitting is only for like you know make
people fall don't kill people
you're not allowed to kill you can hit
but you don't
kill but what if  like You've Been hit so
many times You're about to die from just
not eating I
think there is food there There is food
outside
in the
middle
here in
here
okay pleas
for
my le now Thank you Thank
you
bye bye and The Purple  box here
[Music]
[Music] hai hai hai okay okay
Green is
[Music]
pink
where ok
not there is no orange You Take Two or
three
shes only Brown Pink
Green yellow blue and red because that is
the obvious
color as you guys
requested  you guys want like colors choose
to each other We even like to use one fly I
think
so What color should I take
for the
color should we have Green If It's
not
taken go
Upstairs for the forem who has taken
their colors Please go Upstairs because
ITL  be easier for us to
monitor I'm
Brown Okay got got
[Musik]
so Green Pink and yellow is out Green
pink yellow and red Okay let's go with
orange There is no
orange yellow R green and pink is
already out so the is
Brown Okay  Ina
Brown blue Okay now go up
please How many stacks Can we take sry
two please two oh oh only two two should
be enough two should be enough two or
Three is okay I brought a lot I'll bring
some
down but I
think Okay okay  I'm going to say it
again okay
uh is everyone here one two th
]
yeah Don't forget to F1 for the lower
level
[Music]
pink
Well I think like even if I fall
down you can still keep
using Oh
focus on not falling
down we'll Cut our
F1 gladiat match
[Music]
Who's the one who cleans it?
Let it be
L Oh yeah, I'm going to lose it, OK? Oh
yeah, that's it
[Music]
okay, I've already finished it
[Music] [
Music]
out Yes, I'm out
my
[Music]
heart
[Laughs]
out
[Music]
And I don't know
on there's there's a time
limit
right Yes there's a time limit Minutes okay
so
you're careful it's I'll Be More
care
and
gu take more
[Music]
persp How
right but it's it's it's probably
because only this and then one  more game
Right Round Oh my
God
ah like two rounds then
right Don't forget to take more STS
everyone
Okay okay
nice
ure Oh okay
okaying
[Music]
thech everyone already
in we have to accept it
[Music] it's
time we have to hurry up he said
they have to go in a minute
soeng minute times yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
r
in can't see i
[Music]
[Laughter]
really nice art guys
[Music]
Ok everyone stop in right now stop
doing me okay I'll count the green first one
two f f si
[Music]
most Green is
24 mostly Green
24 1 2 3  4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 13 14 15 16
17 18
[Music]
19 Oh
you okay tap there isn't one
Dr pink pink It's been destroyed Oh it's been
destroyed it's been okay 26 okay okay
[Music]
blue blue only
four wow
[  Music]
W here's the one that
Emal
took earlier, that's the yellow one that's got it when it's
ripe
[Music]
Why our
yellow Oh I think it's because They're
trying to get Through It
fast I think
CR Come here Come here Come
here this this is  for you from the
previous
Thank you
[Musik]
you no explanation necessary is
good come back
Tiger
Okay okay we
start got to the corner
[Musik]
oh oh yeah F1
please guys I'm sorry but if we have one
and you only say go in  the Chat We can't
see
it count down f f
f two one
go Already.
nice nice left two person
[Music]
left
F two
[Music]
OK oli oli k the pink one I'm red K
yes 8 9 10 11 12 1 15 1657
3 3 33
[Music]
hello there's one difference please
no
[Music]
P
In In In Please come
here hold on
okay okay okay thank
[Music]
you OK now everyone It's time to
combine
everyone ATT
[Music]
please It's time to combine all your
Emeralds and
[Music]
exchangeit you can take my emeralds
right to buy
[Music]
stuff
[Laughs]
[Music]
First I that was free
was if free since Everyone Is
now what I'm
just we can only
really for one of
Us how
how Ar and
[Music]
my
empty pill I'm new  This is the first time you've heard
e or
watched Buong Jempa Majestic in
Aceh Ma'am,
what's more Indah lag
lam moonlight lam moonlight the wind tu
ayonungsi
Ul
[Music]
indahl men c
l check check live par endari C
[Music]
Ar si  canganganger ar siangang ar
jasanganger ar
[Music]
amanganger open the door open the
door here Kobo got this song open the
door do you want to come in do you want to
loot or not
[Music] do you
want to freing right
[Music]
yes don't
answer don't want to be
there Don't kiss me Say if
you kiss two or three and
it's four and six and it's gone
if you get a new friend darling
old friend gets a new friend darling friend
[Music]
old yit disappears then
whose voice it is I don't know
[Music]
yeah
watch
your history Since the beginning of
time you've
been
[Music]
abused by seasons of
anger
[Music  ]
originally in the rainy season the water overflowed until
far away your spring from Solo
was trapped by a mountain
a thousand flowing waters until
[Music]
far away it was born
if it was
[Music] the
boat
of your past,
Pak's people always rode
[Music]
a
you know
Eh nice nice nice AC
as  cute yeah guys
wow
wow wow I
like it yeah
that's it Man Ho live
Indonesia thank you
[Music]
okay now the medle is already done thank
you so much everyone for watching and
listening to the medle Ho live Indonesia
and I don't know if they are already done
with
the shopping shopping shopping
hosina shopping Mada Des Mada Des mada mada Des
shopping
H Which Tower should we all go Um okay
OK y
yur
Red
E anyanya Ina
y
Know
Ni
likara blue
[Music]
right you have more range
not super chat Thank
[Music  ]
you there is a blue yes
next Put in every
temples Click bat
first When I was playing like navigator
I couldn't really hit anyone with the
arrows to be honest It's like really
difficult Yeah it's really difficult so
And if we buy wait How  many is it I
guess 10 arrows I feel like it just be
gone in the first round R One te ready
for the
game everyone is already there
ok
[Musik]
Solo no b
Ho Hello Thank you everyone for coming I
want to check it first okay  okay perfect
perfect
ha So the first one Will Be
in Red FL In Yellow FL You are In Blue Flag
everyone is already on the
temples
Ok
so I'm just going Say The
Rules a
minutok so as you guys can see There
will be three rounds but  this time you
guys in the round one team
There will be a fighter and navigator if
the fighter De
Can i hai thank you
so a fighter De That's mean game over
for your team if navigator De that means
the game still must go on but navigator
cannot  help at
all cannot shoot cannot
navigate all you
can all you can do is depends on your
Fighters team
and Wait
H if navigator navigator cannot be
outside of the
Temple but can fight with bow and arrow
So if you have a bow and arrow you  can
you can use it if you kill the enemy
and the items fall you can take it oh
Ok the bed is outside as you guys as you
guys can see the
outside if you guys date then Dead
That's
game over quickly item
not giving me the weapon  yeah come here
Okay okay A Bed near the
[Music]
Temp you not even if you die Once you
can't do anything either as a navigator
or Fighter bad doesn't have to be close
yeah
right It's
okay Are we good to  go he guys
guys nervous ready I'm nervous use of the
time yeah do we go back into our own
vcs yeah please Okay
byee let's go back
[Music]
to go back to your on okay
Okay
Nice I'm going to the place first  hold
on please wait
here
Okay
ready looks like ready looks like ready
Okay the game starts
in how many minutes By the way eh because it
should be 30 minutes that means a total of 10
minutes 10 minutes too long too yeah the
easiest way
to die is also true three two one go
Where did you  fall
to Where's zomy I don't know I I didn't
see
it is that Oh that's
rainy and Y Is
there and In The
Rat any In The Rat in kyla's
place She's Waiting for The Doors to
open I guess Oh no she does
n't I wonder  if she wants to
jump She can jump whenever she
wants Where your other
Ok good
thank you, have you pressed F1 yet? How come it
seems like you're going to the save place
and you don't want to
move far to the save place and then you go
to the place where they think it's
this?  No, their strategy is
they want Nit, they're the ones who come,
maybe maybe maybe, maybe,
Hm Why Everyone Is just like so scared,
but Reny is the one who goes
everywhere, he's the one who explores,
really explores.
Wow,
Rene is brave, if for example he meets you.
he can really press the piston and then
jump
towards it, kanata falls down eh Kanata
kanade kanade falls down Yes yes
hang on Sorry Ta and D are near
guys and D is near guys so it's
a bit Taipo a bit
huh
eh ah iovi has come out iovi to the
place
Finally finally War  started between
Anya and iovi Will R follow? You can
see Ina trying
to shoot
her arrow ah
OK Anyanya in
out Oh any that's the fighter yes yes oh
now
r oh she uses
jump she's a piston here SL she's easy to go
anywhere that's aunty  I'm looking for a victim, it's so
scary, right? I'm like a shark, do
n't
you think?
Wow, with the sound of help, he's like right
there, right there, he's wrong, hehe,
but I'm actually waiting,
waiting for Iovi to be hit by the piston,
actually, is it jir or is this member like that, he's
been hit by the piston, like that?  but how come no
one wants to beat
them hah yeah it's just fun to see
Oh
alsuina wait that means because Anya lost
Anya didn't play in the final yeah Yes no oh
okay oh
out OK
r
k hah yes vote out never mind vote out
already
already already already already all three
teams already  that was
just now
okay okay
next round
two
team round two team
Okay Z
Ame
z z
yell can be the same too
hai
[Music]
hai oh wait No Oh I think youain you
have like
[Music]
hair to
y Ok
risu risu accompany this yeah Kar
there's
pink  pink there's no red Oh pink
sorry sorry red
I
forgot I haven't had any water I've run out I haven't
taken it yet I'm sorry Ar Again we're done
streaming I
can
wa is G naig me I can
navigate coincidentally there's Anya tooose
from one yeah
oh just the committee or not  so that's fair, that's fine,
thank you
Space
Can thege Oh
there ready ready Ready okay okay e game
start
and
three two one
go go go go go
go I'm curious AD Oh risu who is the
fighter for risu kanadi and
[Music]
yangniper oh
teone
[Music  ]
now are
[Music]
areing but it's not bad ru ru use
Stone tuh k pakone Ma'am oh also Mr Stone
deh
Oh
okay
Kani
[Music]
kla I I missed ame keegprek ame
Earlier he said kegeprek I missed it oh what a
shame viewers oh tuh tu tu
That's it, that's it, even though it's like
this, that's it, that's it, that's it, they're already looking at each other, you
have to be careful, because
the sniping is
falling there, it's falling, but it's
there, it's there, I don't know why it's still ST
there, even though it's just going up
Ok, pretty tight
everyone I  wonder Who's the
winner am
orisu Oh a close
Battle they have sword versus AX
Oh looking at them from Up closest
One Who's gna be the winner it's
really funny if you go back and forth get
crushed Come on, get crushed dong I
want to see the squirrel smashed
eh
uh but
it's useless for you
to hide  but the tools are still there,
tools
that were a funny way to be Invisible
actually You have to get Rid of your
weapon
[Laughs]
okay
yeah It is it is
it
was J Yes
Wow this looks like the power of
this committee mah
ouch
H wait for this  I'll break it first,
here, there,
go, this
[Music]
here,
okay,
wow, how
naig, so he's like telling people
positions and then he's like telling you
don't come here because there's something like that, like that,
and then like, if we can't
see too far, that's it, so yeah  I
also can't get to a place that's
really far away, you know
[Music]
if
I have a lot of substitutes,
today it's the same in yellow,
yes, in Green,
gre gre,
each other, that's how the dog is
Enderman Hi tbl
Anjir hai hai hai hai
wi
wi wi I
think so  Earlier, Muna, there were
two bars, you know, two
bars, what are there two that haven't been
raised yet, but I forgot where, OK, that's
okay, this is a fight between admin,
committee versus
committee, committee versus committee, no way,
okay, I'll look for a position first,
okay?  game start
in
three two one
[Music]
how come risu risu is so fast
he uh
where's his ren Oh his ren over
there trying to
peek jump around
peek peek where on
earth re going to get out of
his way
Oh still peeking
B fast because
orda come on come on come on fight against
opponent  come on come on Oh that's all there is
to it, come on, come
on, where are
they trying to find a
way try to find a
way looking for
looking for it, you can just increase it
if
you want to move
okay okay meeting with each other Okay Nice
Nice verus Who G be the  winner
[Music]
andn pleas
congratulations Wow, what are the strengths of the people in
each other?
[Applause]
[Music] [
Music]
next This is I will give
you hold
[Music]
on
kk, let's gather first, let's
gather first in one  same place
no oh
no
think everyone thank you so much for
joining the HID Cup for this
year I Really appreciate it that
you took the time to play with us
toing the
and also Thank you for the ID for
helping me toilding finishing
[Musik]
the it  was an honor for me to make
this be one of your mor
[Music]
and
and after this after this for the ID
there's another stream I believe
[Music]
for
the
so gamej
theood pleas
let's take a together
guys where
ya let's  go outside
[Music]
committee
already hai
[Music]
SP SP
SP okay
[
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
I'm
really high nihangong
[Music]
the others are
in Anjay Okay wait where
Here I am
[Music  ]
Meni Hai
k k
[Music]
high
guys Where are you guys
[Music]
a plus one lag bottom bottom can't be
seen from anywhere i
akuou Okay Ah looks looks looks OK okay
ah Yi Yupi Okay OK this is okay th two
one
ye eh  hang on guys
guys hang on guys it's not good nija it's not
good it's
not good hang on B it's not really good hang on oh hang on oh take a
photo so I don't take
a break why fing B Oh B it
's more or less bad it's
worse
I
think it's really funny yeah Wait a minute yeah hang on a minute  yeah
nah Thank you
[Music]
thankk Patience Patience cuy
okay okay th two one
[Music]
[Applause]
go Thank you everyone thank you so much
[Music]