[Music]
hello again K
everyone snail is here on my lap and
he's already getting
agitated I started talking at my screen
but he was he was loving it he was
loving the pets he was purring and
drooling instantly wants to leave we'll
see I might have to oh no he is leaving
instantly well I feel like it's actually
for the best If
he if he leaves not cuz I don't want him
here but because I feel like he's going
to want to leave and I'm going to be
focused on playing the game and talking
to people oh he's so fuzzy though he's
my little fuzzy
baby
oh he knows the three plus hours of
yapping are coming by the way I made
this little
timer at the top I don't know if it's
annoying to look at it's also probably
not 100%
accurate right now but it should be
approximate I'll adjust it
later it's spooky even I don't know
about the
color is that better it could also
be oh mean that looks kind of
spooky that's harder to read but maybe
be
less
obstructive red for the
immersion I'm going to put it in the
corner now it looks like it's part of
the UI is this is this adding to the
experience of s days to
die wait we might we might be having a
problem on the server
it's day 15
um actually I think that means my timer
is
wrong it's day
15 someone forgot to leave I don't think
it was me I mean my computer has been
off since
yesterday so it couldn't be me
[Music]
right been see really playing and then
and then I open up my inventory and my
stats I'm like level 20 it wasn't me
guys I swear it wasn't
me I think they didn't end up playing
this
morning because I don't think enough
people would have been
online a hord knight has been missed
full plate armor
somehow no I promise I'm still I'm still
Luffy well what happened then are the
spikes still intact did everything just
die to the
spikes well maybe my timer is somewhat
accurate still since it's like an
exact week has
passed we're just getting a difficulty
difficulty Spike that should be
fine next raid on day 21
went okay enough I guess so well maybe
if there's only one person on then you
know there weren't too many zombies and
they just died to the
spikes a week behind for next raid I
think it'll be fine based on how we
handled this one we could we could use
difficulty Spike actually oh snail snail
has finally decided to
leave hold on I
that's perfect because believe it or not
the stream is has just started 7 minutes
ago and I have to go to an ID
meeting oh there's bi Boo's
bike so I'll be right back pretend like
pretend like nothing
started yet he he be right back
[Music]
K I'm back okay I wanted to make pumpkin
bread I actually got all the ingredients
cuz this game made me want to make
pumpkin bread but I didn't have time to
make it yet I might make it tonight but
then I'm going to be staying up so late
making pumpkin bread or I could make it
tomorrow pumpkin bread is in my future
and I'm
excited in game or IRL I mean certainly
in game but but IRL well let me let me
join the the
call day 15
hello
hello F why are we on day 15 I I noticed
that it seems someone forgot to leave
the server perhaps I I had a feeling
last night I when I logged out I was
like H like I was one of the last people
to log out but I was like I feel like I
saw someone afking there will it be okay
but
uhoh but wouldn't the base be totally
messed up now then because that means
another Rush happened maybe the spikes
were enough to hold it off right and the
second R well I think if only one person
so lame if only one person is there
maybe only like a few zombies spawned
a no isn't that exactly where she logged
out last or didn't log out last night I
don't know did she
die I I just saw a pink-haired woman
standing on the car being the last
person when I logged
out wait should we ask go up and ask
they notic
okay okay
hello it's don't worry hello hello if
anything this is good because now we
know you know what happened yeah now we
know what happened what happened then uh
apparently R stayed AFK I knew it I knew
it I knew it
saw I was the no I saw I was the second
as I was the last one before ra to log
out and when I logged out I even said to
my chat oh isn't there someone's isn't
Raa still AFK like in the server cuz I
saw her standing on the car Lo out next
to her I was wondering is she she looks
AFK but I'm sure she'll remember 7 hours
oh my
God something else wait so did a raid
come I wonder I think it did it probably
destroyed R over and over
again destroyed by the hord multiple
times
no unable to move but then we missed the
raid what does this mean for us that the
next raid will be super strong we're
ready we're going to do it we're going
to destroy okay we together I think that
it also has to do with our levels and
stuff so since no one L I think so
that's how it was in the better at least
so
F we are we are so well fortified but
that means today there is going to be a
raid
then right
no no seven days so 721 so that was
yesterday yeah the next one is 21 so
we're still on track right just
about do the
same just plus one week it's it it was
calculated guys calculated um yeah oh my
God yeah can you guys give me like some
wood if you don't mind uh there there's
a bunch of stuff in the house go ahead
and feel free to take whatever there
there's weapons in there too as well so
you can do
weapon I even I even double
like I when I ended my stream I was
still worried about l so I checked like
if I could see if she's online on
Discord or on Steam friends and so on
and on Discord it just said that she's
like playing Monster Hunter or so so was
like oh I guess that's fine but no
that's
crazy but hey R you collected some water
for us cuz you kept it oh yeah thank you
for collecting water for us no I'm not
going God a you already did oh my God
how much water was there it only
unfortunally it caps at three
so well great welcome that was
calculated as
a all three people
here and then but hey I made some coffee
and some
tea large Tower I can't find wo
okay CeCe here's your tea oh thank you
you're welcome it's level my God bless
you can't do it welcome that is so
funny here's your
coffee thank
you
yummy B can I get some of that tea oh
okay I'll make another
tea sorry Chef you're working overtime
today give you the
XP penalty I I thought we don't have an
XP penalty what level are you there is a
pen how do I find out tab second
tab penalty was four it's
okay okay my beautiful no
hesitation oh my my
beautiful has 23 deaths
what 20 what 233 deaths you had so far
but I think yeah says deaths
15 wait where do you see or Dev
first I think she probably just died
once and then just was in the respawn
screen probably and then yeah because
and then probably back you dying a lot
sorry I understand why people have to
die is you know you restore your health
and I have eight player
kills eight player you murderer
[Music]
wow well thank you I'm not thirsty or
hungry anymore it's
so let's start preparing for the third
grade yeah okay yeah I'm I'm still
trying to to to find my well not it will
not happen today but yeah we can take it
relatively easy I guess boo can you cook
me uh some corn or something yeah do you
have
any yeah I do I'm cooking up some
cornbread oh no I'm coming home popping
off I'm coming
home yeah the cooks are going to to work
guys the the toil the the some of the
boxes here res spawned so like the
toilet was empty right oh because
because it's it's the ra CU it
respawn it respawn
everything yay I so I have some more Ki
if you wanted game oh because she was
online well some positive
effects
huh oh here I was standing where you and
who were standing I'm I'm behind
you oh stairs here
thank
you nice all so far if if you grow the
corn does it give you more Health back
or
more whatam call it more hunger back
lack of hunger yeah pretty sure it's
more efficient as a food to eat it
grilled yeah maybe we should try and
search for food
too I know but we have like we have 60
steaks at home from the Big Green boar
oh wait did do we did we cook this
not yet but you know I feel like we
might have cooked them all really I
think so I mean the steak conversion
ratio is so bad five raw steaks to make
one grilled steak wait wait a
minute I wonder if the green boar
responds oh I wonder food farming place
I
think uh I would hope that he wouldn't
respawn cuz he's already already in my
nightmares true that guy sucks yeah it
was too strong and too big I was pretty
satisfied yeah a big
[Music]
achievement wonderful you never know
yeah oh yeah if anyone wants to come
with me to grab the treasure chest
treasure hunting I want to Oh you mean
the loot no I have a treasure map oh I
see oh it just hold on a sec what wait I
see a drop is is it the yellow thing bi
boo no you the aop though yeah we should
get the drop first before it goes away
oh okay and then we can get the buried
treasure wait where did the treasure go
the where my map I know I only ever saw
the drop on the screen I saw the
treasure chest oh it might be the drop
maybe
H that must be it okay well let's let's
go over and grab
it yeah already I'm going to head that
way I am home oh if anybody wants to
come let's party them up yeah get in the
yeah can you invite
me yeah well I'll invite you me too I
want to do the treasure chest thing you
it sounds fun
okay oh yeah I see the icon the treasure
icon on the map okay I think only you
can see that then bi so you're going to
have to lead the way to that good okay
let's get the D the air DW the
d uh if you guys have a stone
axe um and get some wood for me because
by hands it takes too long oh I have a
spare axe if you want it oh thank you
I'll take
it siip siip zip
quietly sipping from the river with my
straw hat not even tea just river
water hey as long as it's flooding FL FL
how do you say that flowing oh no
flowing as long as it's flowing it's
healthy oh I made I made the ax ohpp you
made one okay yeah I made one why are
some of the zombies super
hot with their dresses because because
some people are super hot yeah turn into
hot zombies hot people become hot
zombies the
[Laughter]
streamer wait can we go into the snow
area don't we freeze to death or
something oh we have clothes it should
be okay I love snowy area yeah ah it's
too bright my eyes
flashbang why would they why would they
put the drop here they don't even care
AR you the one who uses light mode
yeah hello yeah she
does hello what are you guys planning on
doing
there preparing be careful are we just
balling yeah we're balling right now
okay yes my we're doing class increasing
our skills Loot and loots yeah we going
to build a little house together oh gosh
oh people coming
in um
you are the farmer you if you have some
time today can you try to plant our
super
corn yeah yeah I would love to plant
some super crops super super
corn okay um if you uh the the super
corn seeds are in the new house next to
the fireplace in the food and Medicine
Chest um there is free uh ears of super
corn don't take those just the super
corn seeds there's five of them and if
we need more with more grown ears of
supern I can produce more seeds because
I have some recipe but for now it's just
five seeds here you can take a
look the at the new place nothing cool
in here um anywhere is fine I think I
got I got some magazines
though oh BL crafting I need that nice
guy I I have I've heard that the second
wave has already been finished
[Music]
yeah we're so good we survived the
second
wave unbelievable are we this house for
another wave or are we doing a different
house now well we might this house
because it's it's well reinforced right
very well reinforced okay got to
continue using what's good
still make the most of it oh my gosh
dude are those lions or Tigers what are
those what big cat a mountain lions big
cat big cat big cat means big
trouble oh big cat hurts oh that was a
bad idea mhm yeah dangerous better be
you guys question right now are you
doing stuff at a new location
um bble has like a treasure chest and we
want to go yeah I have a treasure map
that I'm looking
for um where did you guys go I left but
I'm waiting for you somewhere close by
okay well I'm going to go to the other
home so I'll stick in a a different VC
I'll see you guys
later okay treasure is can you kill me
oh H because I see the big cats guys I
found a like
radio
hello f are you following the the
treasure people or I will quest with you
yes awesome but before we do that can I
tell you a story of um my cat yes okay
so um one of my cats has this really
interesting way of forcing me to feed
her I wonder if you can relate
so like when she when she's really like
losing her patience with me oh my sweet
G G you have to listen to my cat story
really quickly okay okay so smoovie one
of my cats when she loses her patience
with me and really wants food and then
wants to show me she wants food she will
purpose wherever I can see and hear it
look for plastic because she knows she
can't eat it she's not allowed to and
then she will like nibble on it and lick
it and make these noises these plastic
noises
forever and I push her away and she goes
back to it she does it again and again
and she will not stop until I even leave
the room and then she follows me and she
finds a new thing to nibble and eat or
until I give her food relatable very
relatable really oh my God
what I relate to the cat you relate to
the cat snail also plastic when he wants
my attention a oh no I didn't know that
was a common thing they definitely know
when they're not supposed to yeah that's
so bad so so bad
mhm but it also makes me think
maybe then she knows also since she
knows she's not supposed to and she's
just like kind of
like annoying me with that she knows at
least that she's not supposed to swallow
it and then you know at least she St she
knows where where the the line is I
guess it's not like she actually wants
the plastic she just wants your
attention cute so
wise yeah I would eat plastic for your
attention
too no no you already got it you already
got it now we understand the meaning
behind feather should I put it
down oh the feathers no
no you you all have my attention we're
going to do quests it seems the
Clementine okay yes CL is is cute cute
name yeah right the
Clementine is there any food I am so
starving also starving I feel like we
might need to figure out a food
situation 60 me if you can cookat you
have the 60 meat I will cook I have 60
meat okay I'm on my way to the house
that's what the B meat went no oh no I
found it where find it I killed two pigs
and I took it off their bodies oh wow
okay okay nice we need that yeah we do
all right send that to the to the slow
cooker
okay um and do you need seed crafting
farming
magazine um I think yeah I already I
feel like I ate
one okay I will put it should make a
Farm by our house because we're
struggling with food
yeah well I did tell Shi to take the
Super corn and and and play uh plant it
sometime today uh but if she doesn't get
to it I don't know I so making seeds and
farming are two separate skills right
are they it it seems to me like it I'll
put the meat in here and I have an egg
oops okay oh I am oh I am on zero oh I
am striving to death right now I'm going
to make a bunch of bacon and eggs how
fast yum does that finish um Takes a
Minute 20 each okay I'm coming over
because it's death or life situation
right now
I can make some grilled
corn okay anything I didn't know it was
why does it go down so
fast and the apocalypse are just so
hungry I
know they don't know that we have to
parkour for
food uh how long usually until you
starve for real for real I don't know
why are we all starving how did this
happen so hungry
maybe because the we loged we all logged
out right of the apocalypse and we were
just so so exhausted from the
apocalypse you're cooking at our home
right yeah yeah yeah okay good good good
good I'm home
heyat oh thought you were eating the
food that I was supposed to eat I'm
welcoming you home ah one corn is that
grilled m yum yum yum yum um yum
yum
salvation a little
bit okay we'll fill our tummies and then
we'll go questing
okay yesterday without you we were quite
efficient too but I think with you we we
are even more efficient we will be three
times a fish I missed you to my
beautiful wies I feel like I've been in
a coma for 2 weeks
yeah I think you have
been fauna got so distracted so often
gigy but she's also so motiv motivated
she runs off into random houses all the
time and punches things I'm
strong yeah my fisting has gotten much
better I've been I I'm gone for a week
and a half and you're the strongest
Fister it's true it's
true she definitely is oh I did some
research into armor by the way like I
watched this whole video on every armor
set and so I think I found out which
armor set will be best for you fauna oh
which one is that it's like there's I
think there's two heavy armor sets and
one of them the one that's like that
looks the most hardcore that's the one
you need ooh the tank armor yeah I found
you already like tanking I
do I found this Assassin outfit
either of you want
this a whole is it just the top
sure I guess do you want a
Chihuahua um I mean I uh I think you can
have it too okay what does it do it
gives sneak Effectiveness plus 5% medium
armor rating uh something something
stamina it lowers stamina a little bit
and it lowers Mobility a little bit but
not starving
why do I have a backpack over here did I
die did you
die don't remember dying why is there a
backpack
icon and not know why maybe I did not
die yesterday on the way did you no I
didn't why why am I why there a
mysterious backpack harvesting
harvesting how do these how do these
magazines keep on appearing in these
chests so
magically we're so good at finding them
they just appear it looks like
everything respawns so we should have
like a bunch more nice loot nice yeah I
see loot in these
cars
uh ah Salvage five repair
five cook
faster eat one right in front of your
face eat
a oh this is rough maybe maybe when we
do quests we'll get a Lot
[Music]
F
farmer hi everyone Welcome to our home
our bod it's very comfy we've got bacon
and eggs cooking you you're hungry oh
thank
God oh you guys have searched a
toilet oh it must have
respawned oh they respawn I see yeah all
these cars are um unsearched again all
right uh this is the new base for
protecting right so we should put spikes
here I think we're still going to
protect the old one keep the old one as
the base for the next ra until it's
completely run
over okay the farm is still at the old
base as well okay um it has not grown
despite it being a week
later oh actually well in while you're
here maybe maybe you could grow the
super corn next to this house I don't
know is that like difficult I need to
get Rotting Flesh nitrate powder and
clay soil so rotting flash is also in
there
and other stuff yeah maybe okay I'll
I'll work on it then awesome thank you
so much
no a spear Stu I'll take
that take what you want it's fine
anything
yeah but I think we really got to go
questing soon to get like to find food
and stuff almost night time so we can
wait I should have just accepted the a
quest while I was out there there is a
quest is it GG's it might be mine yes is
my name tier one clear I feel like we
could we could do that we should oh can
you guys invite me to the party so I may
PX I'll on the farm in the meantime okay
wait thank
you oh you are in a party I think oh I
sent the invite I think I'm the party
leader today oh thank you
this so confusing oh okay I see all
right I'll set up the farm here since
like I'm already
here nice thank you no problem hopefully
this grows within the next week
apparently it needs
water have you been watering
it uh I have not been watering it I
don't have a watering
can oh that's also something you need oh
no yeah I thought I was hoping the rain
would be enough you know Mother Nature
at its finest I would think so too how
can the rain why why doesn't the rain
water our plants cuz it's Arizona the
rain is
[Laughter]
alive
Twilight if only this was the Pacific
Northwest if only there was
vampires who could protect us I know
I fot I was looking for Stones I was
talking about this with Nissa yesterday
um about Twilight in Arizona do you
think that Bella's first time seeing
grass is when she went when she moved to
Forks do they not have any grass in
Arizona they are we I don't I don't
believe it there's some grass right if
they do I don't believe
it maybe fake
grass I just remember she took a little
Cactus with
her I thought that was so cute not
grass it's
planed do some Stone Arizona plant I
have stone please share I will come and
give the stone after I hit the tree
timber
timber all right here's hoping that the
grow uh the corn grows
yes pray for the super corn I put it in
the chest put ins side of the
house I heard that super corn is not a
food but rather a
fuel no no no no most of the high-end
food is made of super corn is it like
super corn
meal uh no like several Foods also just
grilled super corn is fine too I guess
but yeah I don't know they they listed
me a couple of things in before that you
can
make maybe we can't use it yet your
cooking might not be good enough yet but
it it will be good enough at some point
no no your cooking's great though I
appreciate your cooking these bacon and
eggs are delicious thank you yeah better
than
Char thank you I've been working
hard chat what else do I need all right
you guys want to prioritize super corn
right what about like Yuka and hops
whatever that is yes Yuka I heard is
good too I forgot for what but Yuka is
good okay I'll take like two yucas then
[Music]
mhm all right seven days to grow let's
go seven days days to grow
coin yeah yeah once I can make armor I'm
going to make you an a farmer outfit
there's a farmer outfit for Farmer buff
oh yeaw yeaw I like how the farm plots
kind of hovering
well it works pip pip pip pip pipe pipe
pipe Peter Pipe piper pepper
pickles oh we got one more
slot I bet we can do the quest even
though it's night
time of course dangerous strong no we
will do it oh yeah we're strong enough
good luck you guys I'm going stay here
and farm like a that just spawned right
in front of me I wasn't ready for it
I'll protect you you're so good at F
it's like the shown in anime Arc where I
time skipped and like got so much
stronger how much did I
miss I've been
reading reading the Ws of the Fist I'm
going where you girls are let's go to
the quest oh okay I don't think I'm
anywhere near the quest I just went to
this house okay yeah
okay anywhere is there more food that's
done cooked there might be I would like
a little bite to
eat one more just a
little I'm also still hungry and thirsty
but what can you do this egg in this
economy I'm don't raw eggs do we have
any
water you can wear my hat a collector oh
you're right as long as you're Rivers we
can just drink from the the sea that's
wonderful thank God for your hat from
the
river yeah with her hat if you put it on
oh oh can you make more hats with that
then no I found a special part that lets
me do it I see I see it see fa because
of that hat is actual the real reason
why I'm sticking with you it's just the
Hat why just kidding all along it was
only for the Hat yeah sorry it's all
about you know materialism and and using
people for you
know my
advantage it's not true it's not true
it's not true I can't believe this after
everything L of
zombies nice die potato seed let's go
nice all right the farm all
expand okay should we yeah go to the
quest Point yeah yeah yeah yeah maybe
we'll find food on the way yes I believe
so zombies zombies
yippe yippe
exp yummy I made it to level 10 I need a
better ball oh you're powerful okay okay
I'm going to Club it in the head
die wait I think you're lower level than
me now aren't you don't worry I can
still protect you
D all right I'm Going H I'll hop to a
different VC since I'll be focusing on
this stuff I'll see you guys in bit
[Applause]
okay all right giggy lead the way um I
believe it is this way 1 km way West oh
okay gigy have you seen bio's bicycle
yet no I want it yeah I was thinking of
you and she got it like you would love
that bicycle the way you're dooming once
we do our Quest we're going to have the
coolest bikes too we'll be a biker
family ooh oh yeah we can have matching
outfits matching jackets the
Clements yeah
embroidered bedazzled on the bag like
those families at Disney World wearing
matching
shirts a we're Disney
Family oh no
careful never mind you don't need
to oh my God you're so strong I'll put
him on
fire thank you I get strong to impress
you guys that's my whole reason for
getting strong tank consider me
impressed
I want your attention so bad I want to
eat microplastics no
no spit it out spit it
out show me what you have in your mouth
what is in your mouth show me role
playing as a throw throwing cat throwing
up I've noticed actually my cat doesn't
only do that with plastics she also like
when I'm still in bed and I'm just not
coming out of bed to give her food and
there's no no plastics around then she
will like sniff on the mattress and find
all these little like fur balls that
have accumulated and accidentally get
them stuck on her no nose and then she
like accidentally eats it and she can't
like get it out of her mouth and then
she forces me to pull like pull the hair
out and then I'm like this is so
annoying okay I'll make you food I think
it's an
accident yeah yeah it's definitely on
purpose she only does when she's
hungry they're too
smart
yeah is this a fetch Quest or a clear a
clear Quest this a clear Quest okay okay
get the punch
stuff yay
exp let's see if it's like a repeated
Quest once again or if it's something
new oh yeah probably repeat it looks to
me it looks new it's not on an area of
my map I've been to oh you at least for
me
true and also remember that neighborhood
that we found yesterday
fauna we should go loot yeah we should
we should look in the
mailboxes
especially cuz that was a lot of nice
looking houses there
[Music]
mhm steal their books I heard there are
book stores oh that guy's scary that
guy's got red eyes and he's fast
likeing deer just now you literally one
shot I thought he was going to be
scary you're a scary maybe maybe the
enemies got weaker because OFA being
server oh flying over and over and then
they're like it's time to
be oh level up I'm level nine oo nice
ypp I'm getting addicted to this game I
just want to level
up
books where is parkour parkour there I
heard parkour was good got to get one
point in
parkour parkour what is that
under um the the foot
icon so I one one like life hack quality
of life hack that pakour gives you is
that you can jump high
and then you can for example you could
put down two building blocks on top of
each other and now you can jump that
high so you jump up there and the
zombies can't jump up there but they
will go towards you and you just stand
up there they can't reach you but you
can reach them with a spare or so and
yeah you just killed him like that that
does sound a snake a
snake I'm sorry he went into my
sledgehammer the way you just run up and
punch it and dies snake meat no it's
just normal Ste I meat yeah but it's
just normal steak home it's all the
same ow a nope
rope never seen a nope rope before in
this
game nope nope nope nope
nope we are almost there 80 M away let's
go I see it oh oh this looks familiar
but I guess they all just look the same
kind of looks familiar in this game oh
my God Golem house is from the same
company follow there's Golem is Lally
Golem ow give me your ring give me your
ring he thought you had
it okay the quest Roo is this you yeah
I've got the ring that's why I'm so
strong my prees
my
shots in
German have you watched the German
version of course that's like the first
time I watched it it was always in
German like growing up mhm that's cool
yeah nowadays I would watch everything
in English but when I was younger the
First Choice was still uh German German
oh god oh dear oh
SM a
[Music]
stamina there's more upstairs of course
there
is my stamina I need to eat I know my
stamina soup I found no no no
no help help
oh my God they're coming in from outside
too
no oh I'm eing I'm going to die no no no
yeah I have also kind
of broken arm I was trying to use my
band and I died oh God oh God oh God oh
God it's so over no I'm stay alive we
can't fail this still alive this I'm
still
alive long
a oh my God the last hit saved me 8
HP I'm about to went so fast oh God this
is one did it get harder because it's
day 16 it might have yeah but it's still
just one
skull
yeah maybe we just ran in too
fast I have food by
anybody needs
food I guess
yeah like one pieces
is already a
start there's some bacon and eggs oh
yeah thank you but did you actually die
hold I died yeah no that found the
cooking
magazine
all yeah although it's not there's still
zombies in here right cuz it's not
cleared yeah I think upstairs still
probably in a
closet I'm too I'm I can't go up
there
where are we downstairs too I still have
downstairs area which one was the one to
heal naturally again this
one
just ouch ouch a
bird a out of all things now the birds
are coming and joining to kill us yes
please are you downstairs or upstairs or
outside upstairs I went downstairs but
there's nothing down here
H Tech
junkie takech junky a farmer outfit Farm
outfit yeah oh we going to give that to
Shian awesome too much junk in my
inventory
so much junk in your trunk really empty
bookcase empty oh I found the zombies
they're downstairs and chilling okay are
you ready to fight
them yeah as ready as I can be right now
come down
there okay if only I had
ammo he I still have ammo I can stay
behind oh they're right in this okay you
ready yeah
oh my
God you came from
outside she dead there's one on me uh
I'm coming you blind it's just so dark
in
here I thought that was a debuff too
fast I know so fast
I oh you're so strong I some bandaids
here take a take a
Band-Aid thank you you do you have
another one yes here you go oh let's go
wrapping myself
up oh I have shot like a
present oh
yay we are also I it okay but let's take
a look if we missed
anything there's an ammo pile here
random
Shotgun If you see 7.62 let me know okay
[Music]
not that much cool stuff was there a a
mail boox do you need armor crafting yes
yes okay it's crazy I already have so
much in armor
crafting where are you I will drop it
outside I have
24 oh my God you're almost at 25 here
you go 25 now
hell yeah let's
go yippe okay then back to Trader Chan
yep yay and if we see shii sometime we
got to give her the farmer out oh yeah
we should drop it off I have too much
stuff I should drop stuff
off okay me too me
too I'm piing up everything off the
ground on the
way
okay oh I'm I'm infected oh yeah got to
find some honey a there's St do you guys
have an axe cuz I didn't bring an axe I
have honey in my inventory all right I
have an axe like not a a spare but I
have one do you need something where you
oh I'm
with okay there you are you look like a
zombie can you do something about that I
can't I can't I need new outfit and we
all
need
the h anybody put on the Assassin's
outfit oh I haven't put it on I put it
in the chest in our house and I was
thinking giggy would put it
on once we get back I'll put it
on I found that just for you you
know for all the sneaking I do
MH but I will say the Assassin hats
together with the nerd hat are the top
tier hats in the game there's a nerd hat
yeah the nerd hat gives you exp buff fre
I want a nerd hat but but the thing is
like the nerd hat is best to to use
during the raids cuz that's when you get
all the XP oh yeah and the Assassin hat
is good because I think it's got
something with
looting and that's better for like
everyday life in the
[Music]
game I'm going inside this creepy
building this Three Star
Building yeah there's a zombie
yes Will Survive that we will survive I
will survive that car look like
car look how strong FAA is oh thank
you our dear
wife such a Demir wife punching
everything a Demir patient kind
wife oh
you're breaking
everything up here oh the floor is not
very
[Music]
strong be careful you'll get stuck with
just your
leg are you up there yeah nothing's up
here just
[Music]
trash some
snacks how to go down a there you go why
are we the animations man they no
climbing animation at all they're
running oh we going in think there's a
dead person in here yes oh there is a
dead two of them even
oopsie there's two dead
people why is it why am I weak does that
mean my armor broken yeah I think
[Music]
so I hope I can make some armor soon
need a work band
this other one just fell down on the
ground after breaking those things on
the
Shelf he's dead no he's
not I no to fall down
tce books
please they got to have some good stuff
here come on yeah this is a three star
area
oh oh foggy in
here in here out here everywhere foggy
in my mind too a
dog can't Rel faster than oh it's oh
no I tried my best you so good want to
just take two dogs biting her legs like
oh they only have Rotting Flesh there
zombie
dogs zombie
dogs that's why I'm a cat person you
know
yeah
H exp dep let's go I know I have a Deb
too actually I might have recovered mine
already I'm not
sure it does say beware of dog right
here C what is that debuff the 1 hour 39
what is
that it looks weird I've never seen it
before it was so foggy how are we
supposed to read that
far fatigue need Vitamin oh oh we have
vitamins at home I think yeah I have one
vitamin on me too oh I'll put it next to
your bat one
vitamin I need I think we go inside from
the window oh
H there's somebody in
here you putting them out of their
misery let me
in do you want Sledgehammer crafting
skill yes okay I will drop it when you
join here it's right by the
window
doctor the doctor is out
um almost there anything else in
here some glue yummy does anyone want a
blade crafting
skill I think bi Boo likes
those okay what just happened this
B
oh popping
pills popping bottles I vitamins
too okay oh my God I have a book for you
do you see this you should take
that I drop it see
it thank you wait where are you girls we
went inside just to go through the
window 20% extra damage to knocked down
and stunned
opponents I'm getting so
strong which
window can you show me
yes maybe I just ate a potato a that one
found it
okay
wao is this a hospital
mhm hospital at the golf place I guess
it's the ranger
station a armor oh an armor book oh
there's one in here too oh watch
out die zombie
[Music]
it takes me
like the whole time kill him until I
reload I thought he was
[Music]
[Laughter]
dead there's
a
armored oh let's
go more more more more oh my gosh
there's two armored books here
too there's so many is going on that's
the fourth in this room cuz I found one
too busing let us through oh you got the
keys yes yay 29 baby dead in here
29 oh okay okay
okay almost
sh I'm always up in the
action what do we got a dog
again but this time not evil dog
anybody in here for sure definitely in
the
toilet
defin oh let's go okay I want to I want
to uh wear that what you find let's go I
think that is the Assassin Rog Hood the
good one of the loot bonus
ooh let's
go that is one of the top here head now
nowly finding so many armor things what
the what is
that this person is dressed differently
than others
yeah I'm I don't want to accidentally
shoot you
guys I don't want to L of bullets either
much exp from
him no why did I drink it a that was
accidentally nice Community Kitchen
about to eat these two pumpkins in here
oh wait don't eat them oh I just ate all
the pumpkins pump don't eat pumpkins eat
this eat
this sold your D we're past eating raw
ingredients so hungry
[Music]
open
eggs anything else in here um no dead
end guess we can leave
[Music]
then now to head back home oh we can
open this door oh what it was you have
to touch the key rack I've just gone in
a gigantic Circle oh you can go up there
yeah think there's zombies up here nah
they can't
climb oh they can they can climb stairs
at least they they have no idea what
they're doing there's a parkour
situation up
here I just skilled into
parkour it's just like parkour
civilization
can you explain to me what that is cuz I
don't
know um it's a world where parkour is
the main currency yeah it's a Minecraft
world it's a Minecraft world and then
they only Exchange in parkour and then
you start off as a parkour Noob and uh
when you're a parkour Noob you
either or you go for the
bee kill
kill be for chck
chicken yeah chicken gives you two
hearts of health and then beef gives you
three hearts of health and you go for
the chicken every day you can never rank
up to be a parkour Pro so you either
live in complacency of being a parkour n
your entire
life or you try and become a parkour
Pro you're so strong
die run is low on stamina though ouch
ouch ouch I missed the point BL
[Music]
Arrow
wa we did it we did it
oh
ow not
me my
club there's probably good stuff in here
though it looks like
it passing gas sealed chipping
crate I actually need that my pockets
are so full I know me too mine too but I
don't want to skill
into the pack me tra cuz I have there's
some good armor that um like gives you
more inventory and
stuff lot of medical
stuff there's a magazine
[Music]
medicine um yeah two people I
think does anybody scale into bow
crafting I will do it okay wait then
I'll leave it in this uh chest here this
one oh there's a reinforced chest should
we break it open it only takes a bunch
of hits I guess yes yes yes no one knows
lock picking
huh oh no I'm sorry it's okay justy just
trying to find a good
spot is this a good spot
yeah ow we're almost
there I'll let you I'll let you do the
thing I don't want to die not by your
hands you would feel too
guilty
oh there's some 9 mm ammo and bullet
casing here on the table stamina I'm
going to drink beer this will help
will help are you drinking again GG yeah
I can't help it 8 a.m. is the best time
to
drink we need to have a
discussion about
this no I I just ever since we I lost my
job because of the apocalypse really
hitting me
hard oh no same same we're holding the
same boat girl yeah I found this
lifestyle to be really fulfilling you
know yeah grow our own food it brings us
back to Our Roots you know I'm just so
sad I can't provide for my wives anymore
I what do you mean you
provide I'm not providing the lifestyle
you deserve Gucci prod bags every
weekend I don't get a bonus anymore
sometimes a simple life is better means
more than all that
stuff as long as we have bacon and eggs
to eat that's all we really
need you're right I found a new
perspective on life I'm no longer
drunk I see the light that was fast just
a quick 20 minute 20 minute drunken
session just was just feeling the buzz a
little bit
I'm still out of stamina though I know
me too I'm fatigued too I need
vitamins what I'm I have vitamins I have
one vitamin you vitamin can I have it
yes I'm just trying toour right now
would you do you think you would be able
to build a building
block
perhaps I want to go on the roof okay
and I'm trying it with this chair here
but what we have vehicle Adventures does
anyone vehicle
crafting I'm going to scrap and there's
ammo for you yeah let's go and some B
here you can look inside
yes vehicle crafting let's go nice ammo
I can help again oh I don't have any
wood what's time I have some wood oh
it's a bomb here take
this okay uh else I shall take because I
want the
block
building building
building uh uh here take this armor
crafting oh thank another one another
one okay I'm putting down the wood again
because I can't carry this much but
thank you okay I will take my wood back
my 1,000 Woods
oh actually I guess I need one more
block Uh Wood lady can you build one
more block and put it up there
[Music]
okay and
vitamin thank you vitamins are very
important they are thank
you okay there was nothing up here good
good we just had to
no
yes all right then we shall not get too
distracted and go back home I guess yeah
I could got to drop off all our items
yeah and then do another Quest yes
another fa this
one uh-oh broken
leg how did I not break my leg careful
careful ladies maybe it was your
parkour the same you could be it could
be I knew there was a parkour God out
there she protects us parkour goddess so
so
thirsty oh we could go to a lake and
drink oh yeah there one there's not
really it's behind us should we
behind how thirsty are you 30y I'm quite
thirsty it's okay I'll make it
okay e but what about a nice picnic by
the lake you know we make it to the one
right next to the trader that'll be
beautiful
okay I love picnics but my stamina is
quite low because I am
dehydrated take it
slow you can drink my molotop
cocktail no no more alcohol I thought we
discussed this that's why you're thirsty
you're dehydrated
alcoholism the 9:00 a.m.
beer I can't help it life is so rough
but my wives are here to make sure I
don't fall back to bad behaviors that's
right even though I just offered the
molotov
cocktail the devil and the angel on my
shoulder I just tested you and I'm
impressed by the results of you
resisting thank you that's my man I can
have uppies later
uppies you're into uppies I didn't know
can I have uppies
later J flatter I love
uppies I've been here before let's in
here there's another zombie I'll punch
him two stamina oh L you're so good at
doing
that I just leled up my punches this
zombie was just a van life YouTuber and
this is what you do to him van life
YouTuber all his subscribers will now be
wondering why is he not making any more
bad life videos they can subscribe to my
channel instead it's life but are you
going to bring out the same content I
doubt
it oh I just had this feeling I heard sh
what the
hell oh voices voices in my head she's
been soaking up our XP this whole time
yeah it's okay we'll
share the masterroom mining company our
favorite led to many broken legs
here I saw a clip a perfectly cut clip
from your POV fauna when I was falling
down
no that was
nice and giggy you miss the most
dramatic fight ever yesterday with the
boar yeah the boar have you fought
Thea I it I looked at it yeah you want
to go back I know no for maybe not for
now so much meat from it we died a
million times but we kept on coming back
we're stronger now you think got super
stronger yeah we
did Super corn super corn I doubt it's
stronger it wouldn't learn from its
mistakes yeah doesn't have the
capabilities of
learning I don't want to see grace
anymore no no no no yeah is the B's name
Grace that's kind of AOL name I named it
I think so experiment Grace Bob from
Bob's
bores Bob your Bor she's
massive experiment
successful successful but also failed
like I guess that they didn't want it to
be that big and aggressive but the tiny
boards I felt so bad for the tiny boards
we kept accidentally punching them when
they were just minding their own
business they were so exhausted I'm
[Music]
sad you're so
thirsty here where the says y I also
thirsty you're pretty thirsty on Twitter
as well the Hat it when you show us your
your your I I can't say my butto yes
where am I supposed to look when you
show us your butts I must Dro My
Hat it's okay you can you can look at my
buttocks all you want your hood is
getting washed away into the river she's
following her
youing oh what happening do you have
empty hand there you go oh here we go is
there strings attached to you
yes strings
attached so
thirsty you spam balls under that hat I
feel like I've never seen your face and
all the time we've been
together you have a mustache too that
looks Shake not bald I like it oh Kiara
your your mask is so cool too oh really
yeah I think I've have drinking enough
do you need some Kiara um the blue one
is the the first right your okay I'm
fine I'm fine it seems I don't know how
but I
am all right
continue oh you can finally move
normally again Gigi yeah I regening
normally oh what that'ss or St no I'm
not looking at the stamina bar I'm
looking at the other blue
bar that one right
[Music]
there have a lot of bars bacon and
eggs you know who else has lots of bars
fa spitting them yeah I haven't heard
her spitting
them you didn't see
her my track oh
oh I guess she spits
occasionally when I'm feeling passionate
about something when she does then she
really she really spits those
bars no joking with her that's right all
right
traitor hello traitor wrecked
even a dumbass Like You magazine
gotcha I wonder maybe now he's selling
the magazines that I
want oh level up level up level up oh
thank you my invent is so full goodbye
sewing kit mine too wait a sewing kit
I'll take that oh it's on the ground
now I'm too much of a loot Goblin I'll
just crawl home if I need
[Music]
to there's a buried supplies 400 m each
he's selling workstation crafting skills
books o three of them that's good have
money e
not enough I can only buy one right
now but I'll sell some
stuff hey girls when you look into his
um in his shop does he sell Forge ahead
by any chance for
you that's me I will
check my shop my rules you follow oh
look
stumbling into my shop can only one
person shop at a time I don't know what
no I thought that was
debunked oh well he's not opening his
shop to me I think you just have to
stand like in the right way so evil for
that
um oh I might need that actually oh
well I don't know what to sell oh wait
maybe this gets me some good stuff too
oh
okay all
right unlock to get rid of
[Music]
everything he can you bring some
money okay like maybe 500 so I can buy
his workstation magazine Store look you
decided to show willing oh he does have
for head he has two do you have the
money no wait two for you and two for me
maybe we have the same like maybe has
the same inventory oh so if I buy it out
he won't have any more for you too
okay how many do I still need I think
let's see
um I still
need uh
uh
six I think right where am I
going 10 in order to make one right yeah
okay okay six I need six more so these
two and maybe he'll restock while we're
playing the next Quest is really close
to our house yeah it is
awesome I want to make some
snack bir bird supplies chest uh quests
are often bugged it seems yesterday we
just failed one when we started it yeah
really yeah this one will be better
H it's not too far so it will be okay
okay all
right I should also go home and drop
something off but I want to buy the
magazines well gigy are you coming back
to the trader I can come back with the
money okay can you just buy the two
magazines and then give them to me um it
looks like there's
only oh there's 2,000 I have
400 oh my God okay we're
rich so
rich of course we
are We Are Born to Be
Rich we're supposed to be rich we look
rich the richness is calling for
us it's our destiny to be rich very
aspirational thinking I like
it putting water in here
come on
[Music]
stamina come
on if you play this game for seven
in-game
nights uh oh no never mind where pass
that is there no there's no maximum
right this is like endless yeah I think
so oo
you can keep going until you get tired
tired of playing this
[Music]
game oh I wonder know where shy
is oh she left our
party oh she wants no more XP huhuh I
see I'm going to put her outfit in
should yeah we should tell her there's a
farming outfit she can Farm way more
efficiently with that now
[Music]
M wow farmer outfit looking good I'm
going to I'm just going to go tell her
in voice chat yes I'll be right back
okay
delighted with Blake sh sh I have an
outfit for you a farmer outfit it's in
the armor weapons ammo chest in our
house okay I I will go equip uh your new
fashion thing then got just for you okay
okay
bye okay I told her was she happy yes
she was delighted oh we love to make
people happy
yes okay I'm going to buy the the items
yes it's
okay I'm running
off you go you go do
that
uh is there
glue there should be I just put some in
there oh I just want to like add on to
it is it in the bottom chest oh yeah
what is there like a theme between these
two chest I was I was just thinking
there should be
[Music]
maybe well that will be difficult to
achieve at this
point yeah we got so many bones can we
make something with the bones I don't
know actually can make a bone knife oh
yeah many bone knives
mhm potato seed corn
seed pumpkin seed okay
purchasing which one Southern farno B
Mak blue and the what was it the the
workstation
magazine I feel like someone might have
purchased it hey there should be she
Callie just bought it Forge ahead wrong
chat wrong
chat just I need this sech Le snip it
right from under my no yeah yeah I walk
past then I only need four more then we
can have a workbench
finally I feel like it's taking forever
to get a workbench like this crazy like
a workbench is like the most basic thing
in like rust and Minecraft and all these
other games but here it's like
apocalyse it's like my life mission mhm
crazy is she going to come over to us I
wonder she is at the Traer oh I'll come
to
you Traer where are
you I never know when we leave our house
is it left or
right it's up up wait yeah it's it's up
from our house when you exit our home
it's us oh yeah it's where you coming
from right now right yeah yeah yeah okay
how do you name a box
again I think it has a button and then
you can click on
it oh what oh e hold e I'm going to try
digging the
thing wait wait wait for have to do it
us okay I will wait where is it is on
the way kill someone oh no it's just
over here it's oh okay uh right here is
where it's at wait V can you come over
quickly yes I'll see what's
around oh we're really low on
food wait is this the farm okay hold on
don't don't get
distracted
distracted just quickly going to dig
this and I'll go over to
[Music]
Cali get in this
tree yeah this area this biomi is
scary okay I'm wait I'm not here I'm
here okay dig dig dig I'm digging do I
have yes I
have show me where you're
good is it usually like at the very
center of
the you just randomly down oh I found it
oh that was fast yay did you get out of
there wait is this a thing where we all
have to find our own it seems like we
all have to find am okay yeah it was
like that with the owl oh no they Z I'll
try I'll try killing them there a big
one there's a big
one oh
there he's at us
wait is that the car zombie yes he's
sitting
ow what's
happening oh I'm dying don't don't don't
don't don't don't die don't die you
behind you behind you he just
exploded
ouch is this because we're digging right
now I don't know we're too good yeah
it's probably the quest
kind of crazy let us dig in peace
please I think you might have the same
one k if you search down there is there
the supply oh yeah it was yeah
oh looks like butter
okay then what the hell
another many
no are we running or fighing I'm running
we can run okay goodbye
run I want to turn in the quest
yes I feel like digging Quest would
probably be like not such a big reward
could it
be hello oh hello hello Callie told me
that you you're very far on Forge Forge
thingy K in the old house if you go to
the second floor there's two magazines
in the box if you want them is it the
ones that Cali just bought or SE
separate ones from the ones that cie has
or no those are they were mine I told
you yesterday I think that you could
have them but I don't think you heard
me oh ah so there's four in total
there's four in total maybe maybe that's
the one Callie is talking about I'm not
sure but at least two in the old house
okay I'll see I'll see if yeah we'll see
if the trainer still has two yeah hey
gigy didn't you check oh it's the Traer
doesn't have anymore goodbye byebye
because cie bought them from under my
nose yeah right yeah so I don't nice
that she was like looking for it though
okay now I'll check in the um main house
or I'll check later I guess your hand
but cuz we can just go do a quest now
the way you SM oh so there is two extra
four in
total I don't want to just get bacon and
eggs from him but but I'm so hungry no
resist take something more
special okay how difficult is it to make
ammo has anyone learned how to make ammo
yet uh no I don't think so I can get you
I don't know should I get this shotgun
shell but I don't know how to make am
for are you out of your godamn re a work
just a job I've had enough of your
[\h__\h] you better take this job I'm
not in the mood for any please with the
you don't mind getting your hands dirty
no no
not goddamn mind we I know we can't be
there okay I've taken the Malone
residence as well did you yeah should I
take a different one can we get multiple
quests try taking one and see I like I'm
going to take Sean sh up your ass he's
giving me 109 mm ammo but that's not the
one I want oh I have some ammo for you
I'll just take the 9mm ammo and
hopefully someone will make use of it I
guess make up your mind or make your way
out
Qui I want to buy these
maybe all right later thank you birdie
let's go I'm so H should we drop stuff
off and then go okay
I oh I have some food for
you your food watch yourself stranger I
know some soup stock and can of chili o
I'll eat that actually maybe they have
food in the main house I got to go there
anyway we're going to take some of their
food oh the the main house is kind of
like where the like on the way no the
fetch Quest is on the way to the main
house won anyone think about the CL
we're hungry too we are well we got the
super corn
growing yeah it will it will one day it
will serve us well and everybody will
want it we should try to get a du
collector too
maybe yeah I guess so I think it's not
that expensive we just need what is the
duct tape pipes and plastic oh easy we
have that stuff yeah maybe we should
make one
wait someone's saying I can already make
a forge now a forge yeah but not a
workstation right what can I do with a
forge maybe I should make a forge yeah
maybe you can make some stuff with the
forge I don't
know it seems I can make it with the
right
ingredients maybe with that you ah I
smelled stuff with it okay and with the
ingredients that I smell I guess I can
make the armor too perhaps I put the
food in the food
chest thank
you I'm coming to our house too I would
also love some
[Music]
food hungry by
default on how do you make
the do
collector duct tape iron
pipe we only have one duct tape
nah oh we have more I'm sure we have
more it's just not
organized yeah I have two duct tape I
think I also need for the forge oh yeah
for the forge I need free duct tape and
free Iron pipes Etc we can make the the
forge yeah then then I need yeah one
more duct tape here's duct tape and this
you can make duct tape
somehow oh wait I can make duct tape oh
so
talented what else I keep on forgetting
uh one woodlock how do we get a whole
woodlock because I've only
seen that we can Harvest like wood um
like boards
oh I can make one oh okay yeah it's 10
wood for wood log oh
[Music]
ah do you need to right
now yeah let's just make it now do you
have any more cloths
kiaha clo here's my wood if you if you
see something in my chest you can take
it okay I don't see
any I'm just missing Cobblestone rocks
okay if there's nothing in there and I
don't think I
has that's okay I will find it is it for
the water
thing yes
H oh we have stuff up
here a
forge Forge
ahead wait can I actually cut up our
couch to get cloth well maybe I
shouldn't put up our couch sounds
possible maybe somebody else couch yeah
we can go to their house and take their
couch oh this thing is
huge should I put it inside or outside
maybe inside put it upstairs if there's
not room downstairs I'll get rid of this
I'll get rid of the kitchen table
yeah this is a good space for
it
woo
here
wow where is
that redeem the Harrison have to have a
couch right can rip
apart this house next door must is this
the Pig house oh it's Bob's house house
Bob's house is kind of
scary this house is so nice though I
don't want to destroy their stuff wait
let's just destroy Bob's house I'll make
sure it's Bob's house safe over
here section turn on the forge oh it's a
leather couch they're too fancy they
have a leather couch
not uh
do we have
something got ceiling zombies
here expected of such a bougie home I
know you can afford ceiling zombies
too where' It Go
what is
around pile of books fisting
book wait where are
you I'm in um the Harrison's house oh
okay just raiding yeah I'm looking for
cloth how do you take apart their couch
do you need a tool for it I don't know I
just smacked it with my uh my axe but it
didn't give me cloth only leather
may maybe this one's made of
cloth okay I'm at Bob's house looking
for a
couch ter why are we so desperate for
cloth right now we need duct tape to
make a de collector
yeah it is true it is true Bob I am
going to kill your pigs for
food sorry Bob curtains are also good
holy cow I just one shot it oh I'm so
hungry ah don't worry I just killed a
pig if I can oh no oh
no what is this room for oh my gosh
there's just a folding chair in the
closet it's the timeout
Corner let's see I'm starving IR
oh I better get home I'm starving come
back home F your presence is missed is
there any food in oh I already searched
in here I think there's in our home
there's one can of chili okay and one
sham
sandwich maybe I'll if I could just get
this pig you'll have so much
food it's true he died in
and I can't kill it why are raw eggs in
the output of the cooking
pot shouldn't it be cooked
eggs you can put them back in the food
chest uh I just put them in there for
storing
oh can we not just make boiled eggs I
apparently they're
bad it water I guess it's better to just
make bacon and eggs a a Ain BS Ain BS
aing and
[Music]
bgy bacon bacon you put clay in the
Forge smelter then you can forge it put
clay in the Forge
smelter I got you clay clay clay clay
clay clay clay I saw it
somewhere clay clay clay there clay in
the Forge
smelter in the ah oh is that why
nothing's
happening oh wait do we not have micr
Plastics I have some do you have some
it's in my tummy no no macro Plastics
sorry so is this number that
1945 and so on is that um like the iron
being smelted and like possible to
use I see
so if I fill all these oh I can only put
two at a time in right so I can't have
like brass lead Sandstone all at the
same time
M but I could make some forged iron for
now right that would be
good I have 60 meat again
W we're so you are
providing once I let go of the alcohol
that was limiting me I can finally
provide for my
wives I dismantled our
car I hope we weren to use
that okay uh I want to Quest I want to
go
questing we can go to the area do you
want me to come back so you can make
food first still yeah I really want food
I think if we have food and then um if I
can get just a little more plastic I can
make the water
collector okay okay and then the quest
I'm going to is um the their house is on
the way to it so we get your your
Workshop books once we do it yeah
yes it's more like the quest is on the
way I feel
like depends on how you see it I guess
[Laughter]
then I don't know I feels like I feel
like I'm not doing anything on my way
back can you get
plastic plastic from just a random house
I don't know anything okay let's see
what I you can dismantle cars or
tires all right
um we might have barely enough let me
see check my chest again chest the chest
more Plastics wait is there some
upstairs trash has plastic
okay we need we need two more
Plastics that would have been good oh I
see I just went to their house on
accident I was not following the correct
Arrow oh oh I was like who are these
people are they raiding or questing yeah
they're going in a house together I
thought it was a bunch of really
intelligent
zombies oh I'm so
hungry were we not
Princess where is
that I thought we were above eating Rock
I didn't need we're growing pumpkins
I found one duct
tape that's
good I'm scared there weird sounds yeah
yeah why what is this
atmosphere oh I just want
some is this
plastic no my thing broke my axe broke
weird sounds in the
forests I have enough okay I can make
the do
collector I think oh really I think so
all
right what's this place
again sker
place ma
Box
egg I'm so scared to go into things Al
am I
getting wait this would be such a good
uh base because it has a water source
right in front of the house like its own
little Pond oh that would I know we
probably should have been nearer to a
water source but we're also pretty close
to the trader
though yeah I'll I'll should I go the
lake is right behind the
traitor
yeah why is this so scary out
here I'm back with the
meat yay I will put it in the food chest
here is 60 meat and six eggs go thank
you okay I will be right back real quick
okay
[Music]
I'm scared
mommy come home come
home no I must provide too okay you must
provide we've got a lot of bacon and
eggs
[Music]
now you okay no I don't have to confid
and right
alone I'm scared I'm going
back I can come with with you now in a
minute okay it's just like there's some
kind of Boral audio going on in there
when you suddenly hear the zombies in
your both of your ears it's like ASMR
but the worst type of ASMR I don't like
it I have way more confidence with you
girls
around I'm running it's so like time for
me to get a workstation cuz
my armor needs to be replaced ASAP yeah
we do have repair kits if you want to
fix it oh I don't think it's even worth
it I just need two more magazines if you
think about it two it's nothing we can
just luckily get those
maybe maybe maybe if we get
lucky two
of this chest and
then another two randomly oh I see the
water collector wonderful
yeah we are so good at this
m what did I come over here for ah
food it's
cooking food and the sense of
safety okay are we no longer hungry
welome back it's cooking okay there's
one one is ready
here while we're cooking do you want to
hear one more cat incident I have yes
always okay so I feel like this happens
to any cat at some point but chunky
wonky she was like sniffing stuff and
touching stuff and she touched something
that had a sticky surface some kind of
sticker and she got it stuck on her uh
tail and the moment she had it stuck
there she freaked out and
like zoomed for the
all the hallways and back and forth she
was
like and I was like running after to her
like stop stop let me just like rip it
off when she would just freak out and
not
stop it's so funny they freak out when
they have something stuck to the fur
immediately they're so silly they're so
silly
silly they lose their
minds microplastic eating Rascals
it's so cute
though I'm cleaning up the
place all this this trash on the light
no we don't need all this stuff there in
no way but giggy did you see the forge
here look at this Forge oh my God in our
kitchen like a pizza
oven yeah it is we could already in
there to make a pizza what if I put this
in there would you put pineapple on your
pizza yeah always I love pineapple pizza
I do like pineapple pizza this is our
pineapple pizza residence yeah we're all
in
inred let's
go does this make sense guys what I'm
doing here Stone as well what happens
with
[Music]
stone ah I still have all the iron in
here ah it took it all the meat got used
so
fast I don't understand why it cost so
much meat for two bacon strips and one
egg it shrinks a lot in the
pan especially cuz they don't
differentiate the staks we get from the
Big Boar versus the vulture for example
or even the snake didn't the snake give
us the same
meat crazy
[Music]
oh whole first aid
kit I'll take one vitamin just in case
sometimes it's handy to have one at
hand handy to have one at hand an armor
book here
too in there oh there we have a book
chest I didn't realiz yeah I wanted to
make a bookshelf but I didn't know
how so time to get
reading think
I seed gra
not robotic didn't I have something in
robotic harvesting
tool
free Salvage 11
armor
33 I can real good armor already like
the I bet that's the highest skill
anybody has in
anything so yeah just aert of dominance
I said give me all you got Senpai tax
you cannot say no to me I am the most
Senpai out of all of you except for
Callie cuz she's she is 2 hours older
than me
she was pushing real hard to get out of
that
stomach yeah it was like we were a twin
bth okay I'm pretty much ready two
hours okay those two hours make the
difference I have three bacon and eggs
for people who are
hungry
okay I think I'll survive for now but
it's good to have it think I am good
right now all right so one of you has a
quest right or do we I have a
[Music]
quest got two
quests then we shall March oh somebody
fell a tree me I'm a Timber
deforestation
hey no deforestation are you punching a
boulder getting rid of everything in
this Forest I feel like the content not
safe the content the videos that I
consumed today on YouTube will change my
algorithm completely for a while because
I watched a 2hour video of like jungle
survival alone with no tools and then
another one I watched today was um some
guy uh building uh like his his own
office under his stairs and when I watch
that
video the one where where like he made
the chair corner right yeah yeah yeah
but then he was so happy about the brass
detail why did you watch them I don't
know it looked intriguing but then I was
getting
frustrated amazing was so interesting he
used chat GPT to do math for him and it
did it wrong can't trust chat GPT with
everything I really liked it because
like a lot of these like videos where
like people build stuff they're like
only successful but he had so many
failures and I learned a lot of stuff
too just by watching them yeah it did
kind of make me want to like make
something right me too I felt so
confident watching that yeah it's like
oh even if you mess up you can just slap
some bronze on top of it and it'll look
good but then again then again that guy
he has his whole like workstation room
and everything he has a lot of
experience with that so I don't think we
could do it that easily huh no we could
we should have a woodworking Club
yeah Wile a horse for each other
yeah what you know it's a wood carving
and we make little statues for each
other
oh statues off each
other what if they turn out really un
yeah oh I've been Malone resident Malone
leave meone
oh they doing the yeah we can't do it at
the same time we can't they're TW we
can't well
upop it'll probably be done soon right
are you guys almost
[Music]
done it seems like they're pretty done
they're all swarming out
yeah or are
they got un maybe they just
started other one your quest yeah it's a
little bit far but it's
over there we have to kill it it's so
active though a deer yeah we kill it we
can have meat I punch it it's going into
the Frozen lands it
runs
[Music]
[Applause]
oh can punch him I think I feel like the
Frozen lands are still dangerous because
of the mountain
lines should not go Lions oh it's the
national forest the you're just go the
water and
drown that is
like a zombie I've never seen before oh
yeah
e i where's question CeCe has a forged
ahead
magazine she
said what more I think so
whoa no so that's funny I haven't used
yet why haven't you used them a to the
yo he to the yo oh wait do you want to
go pick up the other magazines oh yeah
we can oh wait are they done oh are they
done now no they said they can't oh no
okay now they
can I can't hit this deer it's so good
yay
yay yay yay did they already clear it
out
too I
[Music]
guess are you still fighting the
deal I'll get it I'll hit it soon
soon I I'm missing I missed 10 arrows on
it oh no no it's running
away run dear
run oh me so s they left so much a
potato oh isn't the like cuz when you
start the quest the enemies inside and
uh respawn respawn too I have a feeling
it does if I loot it now we can get
double
loot no there's a zombie get away from
my deer stop that's my it's my deer
KY come on the zombie eating my deer I
killed the deer the zombie is trying to
kill my deer that's my deer for my
wives get off that deer help she's crazy
no no it's okay don't don't worry I got
it I got it there's a wolf over there
you better be careful there's a wolf
with red eyes
scary oh God I hear something really
really terrifying next to me it's a
zombie leave de alone you better get out
of there I need this
deer it's eating my deer there's a wolf
walking towards you with glowing red
eyes isn't that the one I want to make
for sing
across I think I found the the helmet
that belongs to the heavy armor that I
want to make for you fauna oh really
it's very terrifying looking it's not
very Charming good good but the crazy is
this it's literally in an in a house
that has no skulls no
zombies why why is something so for
ahead another one yeah I found it
randomly go what then after I pick up
the CC ones we literally have a
workstation anyway here's the Raider hel
helmet funa your prettiness will still
be underneath there somewhere Quest not
available until
4:33 what what time is it 345 oh they
need to restock the
insides they need to put more zombies
inside they're all just loot everything
around they're all paid
actors it's not real zombies AR
real h i look scary you look very
scary I will miss your green hair it
made you so easy to
recognize can we go get your books then
yeah let's do it let's do
it um where is it where's that
way uh do you think if I hit the wolf it
will kill me do you want me to help you
find it what does it
drop
meat it has red eyes though doesn't that
mean it's like really
dangerous nah I missed three of my
arrows on it he looks really dangerous
I hit it I hit it oh that was so
[Music]
sad what about now is it sad now now
about to kill you is sad oh my God it's
really large oh I'm so
thirsty I'm sorry I'll find one of there
maybe oh it died oh we even get oh oh my
God
did you resurrect it did you just use
necromancy it broke my arm I'm about to
die I have to run not dead
yet it's still L he running out I have
to leave my arm
broke no no no don't worry he's a on me
now my leg oh no how am I going to punch
with a broken arm oh I just realized is
that that my party h p on the top left
he's not dead you're so
dead what will you
die oh my god oh
no why why does it have so much HP I
don't
know oh my I have I died I died you're X
speed up you girls got to be more
careful oh no it's kind ofing up the
he's really
tanky I told you the cold lands are
dangerous I want to kill him I want him
dead I want to know what's on his body
you know what you can still kill him one
day when you're stronger you just have
to strength yourself I'm today today is
that day oh gosh he's the bag he's still
there he's eating your dead
body he's still mad he's still mad but
I'm
Healed uh-oh no he broke my arm
instantly he's so strong I can't do this
don't worry don't worry I'm alive now
I'm going to shoot my my leg and my
arm you'll die a second time paa look at
your HP
he's too
strong okay okay okay I'll C him I'll K
him I'll distract him we have to find
him together if we're going to
find oh no I'm staying out of this I'm
just going to go get my books and get
smarter what meanwhile the girl if only
I had shotgun
ammo that' be nice huh he scaring
me I'm running out of ammo oh
no is he still there yeah don't worry
I'm King him over these still
broken no it's
not let's get some water and some
food my XP dead
though I'm sure he'll give you so much
xp you won't have any debt anymore will
ow he broke my leg
is it worth it is it worth
it we so cost fallacy
kill I'm having a feast here it's like
Thanksgiving meanwhile you girls don't
worry he's resetting our he really
hurts M oh I feel so good here he broke
my leg
he's dead he's
dead maybe some more of bacon eggs M so
easy what did he drop um
steroids um do you want tea I have
shotgun ammo and
7.62 ammo I'll take that and
Mining I will take the art of mining do
it here do you want whatever's here
chest take the
steroids my poor leg let's go is your
leg broken
too what a shame at least we have broken
legs together two broken legs between
the two of us
yeah is this real time I 1 hour4
minutes please no we need a splint yeah
huh kiaha you can come back and we can
start the quest oh to you girls okay
yeah
[Music]
yeah okay and then when after the quest
maybe I'll uh or oh later it's fine too
sometime during the night when we are
not doing any Quest I'll make the
workbench or when we got when we're like
reloading stuff or so whatever when we
have time and then I can make armor o
what do I need for making a work bench
anyway
workbench I will need mechanical Parts
duct tape nails woods and forged iron
perfect I think we perfect oh is our our
doctor left wait did she
leave CE the doctor our
doctor she's still in a VC but m is she
offline m
why do you need something from her I
need a splint
doctor well I'm also a doctor in
training if I could get a few more books
call
911 mhy
Moshi could probably infiltrate
hery I'm worri she logged off for the
day I don't know I don't want to bother
her if she's not streaming oh yeah why
is she alone in there yeah
maybe she just needs a moment this job
is
stressful it's true he smoke break on
the
job wait maybe I can make a
splint if I have wood and duct tape I
think you can do everything fauna that
you set your mind to people say Cece's
done for the day we have broken legs I
think I can make I'll die with wood and
duct
tape doctors have two duct tap
do you have wood can I have your dust I
have 1,000 wood here for you wood I have
another thousand in my inventory don't
worry oh do you have any CL she's always
chopping those trees I have five cloth
fragments I'll make you a splint I'm
glad we could at least have broken legs
together why do I have this there you go
thank you for try try that out
doctor I'm Healed I have a 40 minute
ailment now to I'm healing recovering
wait let me give you your wood
back that was worth it I would say yeah
we got so much xp
steroids yeah a a
book
yeah um
soup soup
[Music]
so much barwell extender mod
schematic I don't know what that is do
you want that I have no idea I'll carry
it for now that sounds like something
for a
shotgun increases damage range and aimed
accuracy for my
shotgun I'm typing the Bible no no no
barely
barely what's in
here CH going to disassemble their
car anymore who's I'm almost there 100 m
[Music]
okay what does Callie mean I should make
the ammo or is she saying she's going to
make the ammo
um how do I interpret that think she's
going to make ammo oh sick I don't know
that's how I interpret it I'll get real
busy with the armor making
probably all right I'm here where are
you here
okay let's begin wait wait wait okay
okay in oh we changed it's blue
now that happened
oh I'm trying to get up here to search
this pile of garbage I wish they would
give us different quests we're always
going to the same
places yeah maybe we need to it's not
locked anymore better oh there's a guy
up
here I can take him why did I why did I
why did I do that wor wait this there
more guys I can take them even with a
broken
leg healing leg Yeah I need to distance
myself from these toxic
interactions no no no no I said distance
distance distance
distance dead dead
okay soon to be dead nice shot in the
neck gigy oh yeah he's dead now he's
will be dead
soon sounds like there's some stuff
going on down there I'm just looting the
no it's calm it's
calm y
yum yum babying my
leg I'm going into the basement Who's
down
here
anybody
beautiful somebody I hear someone me too
oh I see him
now
meow there's two of them somebody there
kitty kitty there no there's just like
pictures of cats oh really who's cat
finally pictures I thought they were
only dog pictures and bird pictures but
finally some
justice oh I found a
stash o I forgot we were doing a
[Laughter]
quest you just get so into your blood
lust I know I'm just here to punch
things
oh I know I like how it explodes once
you're done looking at
them the pictures are photos of the
dev's pads oh we have the confirmation I
knew it I knew
it thank you don't are
cute
NY where the rest of them W my cier S oh
someone else's I think it's really badly
like hidden in a way that I would
normally never find it no I found it by
accident is this someone
else's it's not mine oh yeah I forgot
what to find supplies I forgot you were
on a quest too I thought it was a clear
Quest oh
I got meow meow oh they're cute two of
them two of
them oh I have a medical journal for you
soon to be doctor thank
you got to look dangerous hey have you
been to the attic yet yes I don't think
there's anything left up there you can
go if you want maybe there's a curious
Satchel though oh true there might
be I can wait you you forgot an
important thing for oh you didn't open
the shipping crate there's a shipping
crate I'll take
it oh that was just ammo that I can't
use this is a different attic than the
one I was in this is not my attic it's
not my I wouldn't ever miss something
important like
that get Amed cat I will thank you for
their cat yeah for us
now tuna I'm going to cry if we have to
see a zombie cat
sat where is my career
Satchel is it
downstairs I'm also very
cucumber does somebody want to take some
of my
stuff I am also wearing cucumber
I we could try to consolidate
though uh how heavy I wonder our
magazines one
space Oh Oh It's about spaces not the
weight oh wa then F read my cooking
magazine oh I would love
to it's about as heavy as 1,000 pieces
of wood okay in this cooking magazine
you will learn how to make Austrian
schit pumpin pie
[Music]
no or kaash man how about
kaisman
P I learned pumpkin pie in
Kaiser
yes what is this shotgun Messiah volume
free oh shotgun I don't use
shotgun giggy use shotgun I use shotgun
then I think this magazine might be good
for you ooh
and then have haven't I already given
you a bow magazine before then take this
one too build onto it yes more bows wow
sharing is caring because we care so
much about each other in the Clementine
family so
beautiful and there's a wait I still
haven't found found my okay is it in the
garage it should be maybe behind here I
don't know it's it's like does it show
up on your map oh uh yeah I just tried
to follow it now but could it be
outside maybe
not no wait it's that way it's moving
maybe a zombie is carrying it is
upstairs or
downstairs
M well it must be right above me I guess
if it's moving around like that yeah it
might be right above you or or below
me cuz I checked the Attic but I didn't
check the fauna attic oh yeah there's
another Attic in the garage oh but yeah
it wasn't in the garage yet let me check
out the garage the garage
attic um so many why does this house
need two attics I know save some for the
rest of us yeah my house doesn't even
have one attic that's a good though
attics are kind of scary it feels like
Monsters could be up there oh is this
naturel up here kiaha oh I I found
another one that doesn't belong to me so
I found two that don't belong to me this
the one that you found is is it on a
shelf no is it over there oh okay wait
then it must be the one you living room
living room upstairs or come to the
garage and go up the
ladder the garage and up up the
ladder I broke their sofa and got cloth
do you need that mhm
M just break all their
stuff that's a living
room through here through here damn
zombies you live like
that across you
see they're hidden so
me what if I break my
leg you'll be just like us yeah we can
make you a splint what like I saw that
one over there but this one you kidding
me we can match
[Music]
yeah okay we're done ladies
okay we can go back to the Traer how far
is your quest
fa I don't like the
ladders come on now we're not amateurs
anymore I have a broken leg
we have to walk back our poor legs I
know oh oh still oh
no we're 21 more
minutes oh yeah not so bad I have 28 I
don't know if I jumped maybe I did is is
all of that all those broken legs are
from your little Adventure out there in
the
snow no we were in the snow we were we
were at the we on the street oh yeah
we were in the street yeah not in the
snow well since you girls are walking so
slow I'll check out this house good good
I'm going straight for this
car murky water iing you probably got a
decent amount of XP too kiaha for our
our adventure I'm not sure I wasn't
paying attention did I get any XP chat
it was 1,000 for killing that wolf yeah
really I I hope I got some I feel like
even if you're in a party when you're
not participating in the battle or
you're not even close then I don't think
you I don't think yeah
oh can I be sneaky I heard there being
sneaky it's daytime what is there to be
why is it playing scary
music only got beautiful birds the sky
wow
legs mhm
you look like a zombie G just
walking I'm shambling cucumber when you
see a zombie in the distance and it
starts hitting a tree a lot of
money all right I got I I killed one
zombie in that house and I got 300 coins
from that really Dam that Z's Rich that
was the only person in there wow this
walking slow
too I mean how bad is
sprinting it just makes it go back up
what happens I'm going to hover over
splinted
lay oh your max health is lowered by
13.5 so we keep sprinting we are missing
13 Health well I'm still at
100 yeah yeah it's not too bad Rich
zombie all that money is not going to
help you after you're a zombie what are
you going to
buy do you notice how we spawned in like
completely naked with no belongings
isn't that
weird that is weird what were we doing
before the
apocalypse don't ask questions you don't
want the answer to I think this is
protagonist syndrome
protagonists always kind of start like
that don't they it's mysterious but you
know scientists are still doing studies
about it and just not figuring it out
yet but they're getting there we're
slowly Gathering more information I have
caught up to you oh
No
Just
minutes this is so cute you two seem
like like two old married like
90-year-old people we taking a a really
slow hike a really slow
hike no
no it we're
cucumber carry anything although I would
love to check find Salvation there I I
do wonder if the boards respawned oh I
killed a few so they might not have
respawned but the big one probably did
right the big one oh yeah the big one is
down
there I have not I did not try touching
it I just
left that is quite the
cliff we're just making our way one step
at a time why is there a cliff when I
have a broken leg you're rude
inconsiderate maybe maybe somebody did a
digging Quest right here and they just
couldn't find
it looks like it dig up a whole
Mountain yeah
I can't believe it's like 30 minutes of
real Lifetime and then you don't he it's
two hours of your
lifetime will you now maybe rethink your
choices and regret your actions I'm
happy we killed that me too it was so
worth
it it made me feel really accomplished
like I achieved something yeah I see I
would do it again if I saw one I'm
shooting me to I'm punching next time
maybe I'll help you so that you don't
have to suffer so
much oh wait wait you have some shot
some some sh some 7.62 or whatever for
me right maybe when you catch up with me
you can give it to
me I have
26 awesome I also got 66 9 mm but you
don't use those oh no
I think so yeah I saw some using it mhm
but I never get shotgun ammo drops never
yeah where the shotguns
at crafting
skill I know I wanted to make you a nice
shotgun when you came back but I I I
couldn't I
failed I wanted a gift for you welcome
my beautiful sweet angel all I have
finally
have a workshop 17 days
in well can we minus seven from that 10
days in oh
crafting have you also been reading
Knuckles crafting books or there's
Knuckles crafting yeah I guess I should
you should I have two oh thank you
oh let's go armor and I got handgun
crafting this for you thank
you well F I'll drop you the Furious
Fists
books three Rand cting skills awesome
thank
you I can get new
weapons
yeah let me talk to him
to I'm going home
okay see you at home open these three
random crafting
books man now he's giving me like good
stuff like too much good
stuff here's two armor
crafting bye thank
you I'll also buy one just for
fun he's selling medical
journals oh do I have money
I have $100 only we have 2,000 at home
oh
wow
nice
um um bad news the fetch Quest is in our
house so hopefully those zombies don't
break our stuff
no we can maybe cancel that Quest and go
so
easy I wanted to go home anyway
happen why would that happened that's no
that's crazy it might not be maybe it's
no I lied it's the house next to our
house I guess it can only happen at
houses that have skulls to begin with
right and ours didn't have a skull yeah
yeah yeah we just have a random house
okay you shocked me gigy you shocked me
you scared me
all right I'm also on my way back I took
a quest by the way just in case we need
one later after yours okay I have mine
too it's a little far though okay it's
always good by that big lake to the West
oh also oh wait the fetch Quest maybe I
Quest if it's so closed and I'll make a
workstation after the fetch Quest yeah
M you're still so slow I'm over cucumber
and I have a broken leg and nothing is
going right wait what's wrong what's
wrong I don't I don't know let's talk
about it scary about this cruel world is
your midlife
crisis I just don't understand why when
we loot a house and we think we're doing
so good that everyone respawns and then
the door gets magically fixed right in
front of us how does you know what would
help you and fulfill you probably
alcohol no
alcohol no no no in our house build your
own office Under the Stairs will that
help me that will surely fulfill you I
feel like God is Playing Tricks on us
though do I need brass for that we can
we have brass we can use brass we can
cover up the
mistakes it's going to be fine geky it's
going to be okay
I guess I'll build my own office Under
the Stairs yeah when when you're like
sick of our yapping you can hide down I
would never be sick of your yapping a
I'm sick of what God has done to us no
we could have had a beautiful wonderful
life without zombies and starving why
did he put us here this is true but it
is a challenge and we we have to go
through it we'll get stronger out of it
we be strong connect in this
world we don't have to worry about
co-workers and
bosses
and um
offices except for the one
sters yeah except the one that we robbed
and we don't have to worry about the
HOA
yeah that's true I haven't paid our
water bill in like 17 days so wait we're
here now let's let's make the
workstation okay do you want to help me
gather things together cuz I forget I
can only remember one thing at a time
what do you need how about four duct
tape do we have that I can make that and
Nails we have that's a lot of nails yeah
91 Nails oh wait I have maybe some in my
chest
too
I'm I have five nails so we have 96
Nails wait how many f
H hey can you make I have one
nail okay then we have 97 out of 100
nails so
close well give me give me the ones you
got for now oh yeah maybe try tracking
the recipe then it will show up on your
screen
oh amazing you can make nails and Forge
all right I wait why does the DU
collector make dirty water
oh wants you to boil it yourself why is
the do
dirty W it's has also been doing that
the whole time don't ask questions God
is testing us the acid do oh
no Co where are the
nails they're in the bottom chest bottom
chest thanks dropping stuff sorry if I'm
putting them all in the wrong chest oh
do you know about the deposit
button it keeps taking my five billion
Stone stop taking my 5 billion
Stones I do need my 5 billion
Stones what else uh this
[Music]
and I need a few more of
those Weir these ones okay four duct
tape four Nails
more we're so close to a workstation oh
my God I'm so
excited it's very expensive I have an
engine for our car
yeah and the
headlight for our car yeah I've been uh
like collecting some carings and
throwing them in there because I also
have the vehicle crafting skill
relatively High oops so we can be the
first ones with a car on This Server
oo yeah like a minivan for our family
yes would be so cute how much duct tape
do we need four okay I will craft
[Music]
it yum y
y I'm sorry I'm very excited we've been
working towards this for a while yeah
[Music]
oh I need to look up what armor was
supposed to might be able to make nails
oh I already got Nails I can make them
in the Forge okay good I already made
them like the forge can make all kinds
of stuff can forged iron yes I've been
forging a lot of iron do you have some
oh yeah how much do you need um I
need 12 easy
take in front of
Forge thank you I'm going to get brass
knuckles so strong duct
tape what about the duct tape duct tape
go this is the
moment work table
workbench oh bunch of girls already
logged out huh what did they it's only
Cali and a up there
oh I need
food do we have some food for
shoting we have
some come and get
some it's so
slow okay which one's the Sorting button
I get this one
items to
fill
hey
[Music]
hey we need to be a little bit more
organized it's hard to find we
do sorry I'm just working so hard
getting us all the wood that we could
possibly need to start our life
together wa why are you I saw even your
title says wood why are you so focused
on wood I just love hitting trees then I
go you a lumberjack
armor oh I am a
beaver you know cute Timber I have 3,000
wood if you need any wood that's that's
a lot for sure where did some more don't
worry where did my workstation
go did in your
inventory no no
where did it
go
where where did it
go it was down
here oh
wait did you find
it I was looking in the for for the
workstation crafting thing but it was
just in the normal crafting thing in the
normal crafting window I'm so
confused I'm so
confused it's like as if you're looking
for your building block in your cooking
pot I would find a block in there in my
cooking pot just got to dig deep
M
glue let me put some
glue it's it's already been almost 3
hours we're supposed to end it at 4
hours I wish it was
longer even though it's so
late I
know I'm making my iron knuckles
wait if you're Gathering so much
wood uh yeah wait wait sorry do you need
it for something specific no okay good I
I just like having it good it's it's
useful for the forge cuz I need a lot of
burning material okay I have
3,700 right now no no right now it's
fine there's still plenty in there but
good good to have wood at hand
anytime oh oh
oh I can make a
GL bed potato is that
good IRL baked potato is amazing that's
true I would like a baked potato
[Music]
IRL I wish I could like type when I'm
looking into a crate I wish I could type
in like the name of what I'm looking for
you can't right oh no I'm just drinking
drink the murky water it's
fine what did I need
again I always forget CH how do I
know pipe
thanks it's always the
pipe did y'all find your supplies what
does she mean what supplies does she
mean I don't
know I guess she's talking to us right
oh in the quest that we did
maybe you mean our
[Music]
Quest repair there we
go yeah we did do you want to kick us
off the
server yeah are you trying to kick us
off right now one more hour please
[Music]
[Laughter]
yay yay thank you boss can't I make a a
baked
potato do I not have the skills to make
a baked
potato it's ridiculous oh I don't have
fuel GG can you put some of your your
wood into
cooking here my sweet
1,000 oh thank you so
much don't worry stand back kitten I
have so much wood you're the
best I have to go to an idle meeting
I'll be right back oh okay
okay G hi I'm going to get more wood
your thumbnail is so cute by the way I
know the person who drew me as a beer so
cute it's so cute oh to be a little
Beaver oh I got the
workbench yay this is a glorious moment
workbench achiev best moment of my
life oh you're a
sweep no what happened I placed it
wrongly
now it will stay here uh oh cool hey get
your hands off of that than I'm curious
what's in there yeah I can make armor
can
I all right I oh I'll need a one two
armor crafting kits for every every
single thing I want to make that's crazy
I think I had a couple already acquired
one there must be more elsewhere
like what else would people be using
those
for uh
what
what does some does the old town have
any spare armor crafting
kits I make
those h
never
mind never mind you got
it just got to remember the basics
sometimes um okay armor part seing kit
duct
tape all right we'll be needing a lot
more duct tape and swings
oh nice my leg is going to be healed in
minutes finally it's been so long glue
and cloth glue GL GL GL glue glue glue
glue glue glue
glue
cloth I feel like yeah I saw
[Music]
oh one second maybe whenever somebody
wants specific hi whenever somebody
wants a specific armor they shall
provide me with two armor crafting kits
for each piece they want and then I can
make it for what's going on
Gamers
hello yeah hello hello hi the
workstation
yeah it has been completed but uh oh
good you should let me craft things
because I have the highest skill ah yeah
you're the one that can do it but every
piece of armor needs two armor crafting
kits and then 10 claw frag fragments I
have a couple of these things but barely
enough right now I see especially like
armor crafting kits and I can make armor
crafting kits but then I would need uh
like more duct tape for for example I
need a lot more duct tape oh I see so if
you guys have either duct tape or I
think I had some duct tape in my uh
chest need of duct tape though to make a
baseball bat or just the armor
crafting
the Ser so we know what to give you and
we'll just put in your box if you could
label it okay you were doing vehicle too
I have four vehicle magazines ooh nice
we can make car
there are some legendary Parts in here
you actually need those to craft the
strongest version of whatever weapon you
have so the strongest version of the
club level six you need one legendary
part and then basic Club just so you
guys know what that's for I'm going to
make a baseball bat so I don't
necessarily need a legendary Club but
I'm just letting you know that's what
the parts are for okay
okay yeah o shotgun weekly let's go
where are you in the house there ah yeah
take magazines if you need you want to
go together to base again to drop our C
or do you want yeah I'm going I want to
go to I want to go back to the quest
Quest or not the quest Quest the new
house I want to go to the new house I
have oh am I muted no here hi you here
yeah I have uh something for you I think
want oh you do oh well I give it to you
now that you're here before I leave oh
oh I am not I am not at the house yet
you can put it in a chest though and
then I'll grab it if you if you go says
that you right there next to oh no wait
no no sorry that's wor never mind yeah
I'm pretty far but you can put in a
chest or something okay okay what is
it h no it's nothing it's just like a
night guy the magazine and oh yes she's
going to shank even harder people where
are you right now I have a I have some
we at like the the desert or something
I'm coming to we're coming to the the
the new house though we're coming I got
stuff for you too Kiara hold up uh you
in the house oh yes oh good gosh why is
it so hard to control a
bike by the way how does the bike take
damage is it like if you fall or
something no I it's it um it gradually
reduces its durability as you use it so
you're going to have to the main thing I
wanted to give you I think I don't know
thank you oh no that's awesome I know
you you like I've never taken care of a
bike
before oh wait give that I'll press
x what was that yeah I hear scream scre
screaming ladies are coming watch out oh
small
rain baby yeah looks like a small board
is coming oh
already I'm
F there are a lot of them you I will
help
you I'm punching let's go let's do
it hi BS
hello look at us having a nice romantic
bike ride together yeah in the forest oh
you're riding together yeah yeah these
screamers these ones
[Music]
reloading oh yeah I it's a peaceful
peaceful existence in Canada and uh she
just killed
someone so
peaceful
peaceful yeah I wonder if these guys
drop a ton of loot I got one they're not
really dropping much I
except exp which is good something you
fools bike behind here yeah hit him cie
yeah I got him with the
bnk I'll park my bike next to your here
we go oh
okay hello uni wa that lady looks like
she falls out of T all right
okay I lock
mine I think I need to go now
everyone thanks for playing thanks for
playing byebye w
w see you next
time okay you made everything respawn so
it's awesome yeah yeah
really
yeah byebye everyone see you
byebye oh KY you got a bicycle too yeah
I got a bike and we met the new Traer
how TR bicycle oh yeah there she's too
as she kisses you what says that she
could kiss you if you if you um what is
it if you get bike and tier 2 quest uh
you can talk to the guy and he'll give
you a special dialogue to say like
special Quest and then he'll give you a
quest to visit the new trador oh ooh
yeah and she's got more stuff I made a
bunch of bandages you're blocking the uh
the
entrance you want to do this Quest FAA
yes okay I'm at the start Point okay
should we go a failed Quest took long I
guess looking do we not have any leather
at home a leather maybe I have to make
it craft
one you're so smart but
no I have stuff for you okay here's
vehicle leather we do have leather right
here we do thank
you I have 100 leather there you go nice
100 yes please
I'll give it to you in just a moment I
have to run to the old house really
quick to get duct tape I'll bring my
duct tape too you have a uh in here
Kiara yes mine's over here uh in the
living room ceiling okay I'll just try
find it as long as it's named over here
here here it's not named all right how
you I'll name it for you it's okay oh
thank
you problem wow the archiv are doing
archiving things he is archiving
ooh by the way we did um plant the super
corn o yeah it's planted it should be
growing or done growing
hopefully I think I might have messed it
up cuz I punched it and I only got a
couple seeds back I
think I think she supposed to punch it
though right you get it or not but you
should punch it
right I you're the farmer
yeah I mean you don't seeds aren't
guaranteed it's like 50% depending on
your level
probably so punch away as long as it
says it's not
growing for now should we all get into
the same party do you think okay yeah
there's less than six of us I think
maybe about you're leader right now so I
think you can do that oh yeah a
lantern do we have a crafting table down
yet or no yes yes it's in the kitchen in
the kitchen
okay but yeah if you want to make armor
then you should probably leave it to me
I think I can make weapons with it too
is it scary outside yes probably it's a
little gloomy it's night time it's seems
scary ah she's
running oh wait I was going to put more
iron oh yes our spiky house spiky house
it's very
powerful very hard to get in too for
zombies and
r no sh is already wearing the farmer
outfit as far as are you yeah yeah I'm
wearing it good it's scary in here when
it's dark here I'm coming I have candles
here I'll put in the mood lighting I can
I can make ammo wait are you girls doing
the fetch Quest right now I I can supply
Quest I'm coming over
okay the clear the area Quest do I but I
can't I can't the supplies Quest
oh well I'll just go where you are I can
make I can make all types of ammo
now really how did you do that put uh I
I have the skill for it I
guess oh
ammo for
[Music]
everybody oh look at
some owie guess you only put on
surfaces but you didn't start the close
yet did you no just killing them in here
okay
okay almost
there so
easy when I have such a strong Fister on
my side that's
right
oops pumpkins there's some good stuff in
these
cabinets I can make pumpkin bread
pumpkin bread looks so good in the game
that I went out and bought ingredients
to make pumpkin bread in real life and
I'm going to make pumpkin bread oh this
is the guy with it made you so hungry it
did I had to have it in real life can we
come over and have some that sounds so
good
yay send a photo of your pumpkin
bread pH you guys sorry I was
T he's fast are you doing a quest here I
can join you yeah yeah I see um most of
them there too by the way um don't you
have to add everyone to the same party
I'm
trying okay or we can just SP and doing
their whichever works
we in a in a quest right now so you'd
have to wait yeah okay I'll just join
that then yeah let's merge and Quest
together since I think there's five of
us 1 2 oh crap I I buil a quest oh it's
cuz we dropped the party I guess yeah
uhoh oh that's fine that's fine happen
the fin supplies I found also one not
mine there's a biker G in here uh oh I'm
already running they're all
upstairs W I'm hungry so anyway I
started
laughting
get party me too please I think
M you mean should we wait until after
the yeah cuz you as I am okay you're
sker Place yeah yeah oh what you a sexy
zombie
yeah the red a red one hey you pretty
lady go around the corner there's a
courier Satchel here one of yours it
might be
mine not mine okay I think mine upstairs
iot we were on a quest again I was just
and
punching I think there must be an attic
cuz I think mine's
down all right I'll wait for you beibs
okay I'm
coming yeah you still got to get the the
invite
anyway is it in here look at you and
your bike I had a walk here just
like I thought you had a bike was that
a oh it's just
there accident what oh okay already
started wait let me something went Splat
in there yeah
oh sor
shipping crate oh mky water nice a kitty
Ki there's a cat picture in here a
different one is it the same as before
one a orange cats
[Music]
Behavior oh New Stone spear
oh okay found
mine oh my God what a cute cat I know
is there an attic I'm so upset we can't
take the cat pictures and decorate our
house I was going to steal some
lovecraftian
thing I'm not sure if yours is up here
too but in the Attic that where we were
the dead person there's a um not
the I
meant downstairs oh a basement yes sure
oh but I'll Che upstairs again maybe
yeah it's like on a really high shelf
you might have missed it oh weren't we
merging since there like no I think they
already started so we have to do Wai for
them to finish their Quest okay okay it
there's like a respawn time when we were
trying to do your quest it made us wait
like 2 hours 2 hours in game yeah that's
rough should we do something else then
besides this
one
um you see I don't have I don't have one
oh I see yours okay yeah I see yours I
don't think maybe I have to break it
what where are you I just do this one I
have to break the kitchen to get my
statue oh but you found it okay yeah
found it yeah we can we can do this one
for you after they finish and then we
can merge yeah okay how about we do
yours yours is like right there and near
myy oh true we are pretty close yeah F
do you still do you still have the Hat
fauna for drinking
yes please let me drink some here you go
we can also join you guys on your quest
now we just finished ours I didn't even
oh you guys have you turned in the quest
to the trader yet no not yet that or
else I think you gave me your ra hat you
i s how they invite us that way they
still have the
quest oh I want I still think that might
affect it
will
yeah okay we can
wait okay I'm at the Harrison residence
if you want to do all
[Music]
just that's my it's my bik it's my bik
it's my pink bik what a cute bike thank
you ah empty hand
[Laughter]
forgot don't look okay now you can look
I'm watching I'm
watching I'm watching I'm
watching pretty good pretty good pretty
the drive skill yes watch watching me
drift I'm drifting I'm drifting look I'm
drifting wow watching I'm watching
watching I'm drifting around the course
I'm drifting my go she's crazy I'm so
crazy look at that W she's driving on
the inside yeah she's um uh R
tracing Ray tracing great Tracy it's so
long she's not disgracing us I'm
intimidating should I just wait I think
you just wait swag cuz it goes up
okay no no no this wrong
way the green
one I you can't wait no you do have I do
have my hair out I should be yeah I know
I was just I don't know I thought you
were behind G or so
all right let's give back the quest
should we yeah and then we can combine M
we can
back well we'll wait to start any Quest
until we combine so that way we can all
do our Quest together
yeah I'll head
to by the way Kelly did you like wait
was it tap you wanted to give to me I
I'm it here so I'll see
you byebye byee
byee see you next
time byebye where did you say you
brought it to Kelly it's in the chest in
the new house the ones that aren't
labeled I put leather and duct tape it's
only six duct tape though that's
F thank you you're
welcome do we have any food I'm starving
yes where are
you um in the forest I'm coming to
you I'm inviting you do you want a level
five St what oh a stone stone who uses
who uses 44 guns me or I will be using
now this Stone EG I have a funny
magazine that if
you go to the shop with your gun you
will get cheaper prices oh that's so
funny yeah
it's funny like you're threatening
[Music]
them I'll keep magines for Kiara and Y
yo magazine stalks are
[Music]
rising Fist and R love
reading is good for you reading and
fisting
yeah mostly fisting but also reading
about FIS just sounds wrong it just
sounds it's a deep deep
there's so much to know I don't think it
sounds wrong you should embrace
it okay okay I too love reading about
fisting not only the act of fisting but
reading about it watching it I love
watching you
fist than you oh my Lord and the chest
inside the unlabeled ones should have
leather and duct tape duct
tap oh nice lots of leather here's your
f magazine thank you waiter waiter more
fishing
please I'm getting so
[Music]
smart okay I'm going to go make my nerd
hat my baseball bat looks so strong oh
my gosh I can't wait to kill things with
this they for the
win and
then I have two skill points huh I don't
remember what the other stuff was that I
wanted got to look it up again
later
was ah the pre-child fit was are like
the best
uh Prater yeah the preacher the preacher
you have the Hat of that I think yeah
the preacher outfit is the best um
what's not heavy not medium what's that
light armor light armor the best light
armor
set out there
so Raider scent football I want maybe
like I don't want to just make stuff
with my own for people and force it on
to them they should tell me what
somebody screaming out there we got to
deal with her a glad down where is she
now
now ra that'll be no more screaming out
of
you oh there's a bird chasing you watch
out a bird there's a bird out
here is it the bird that's screaming I
think it's a bird that's
screaming so loud
the dang Birds put it away from me for
now I keep telling them to do something
oh there he
is andot just start shooting at it
Bird's
dead it won't bother us
anymore how do I take
back here's my bike
[Music]
okay what you making me yeah I made oh I
made a nerd hat which I will wear I I
feel like I might want to make nerd hats
for everybody because if you wear the
nerd hats during the raid you will get
so much
exp that would be
nice we could all use that
tomorrow yeah what oh Oh there's uh
shotgun shells and stuff in the output
oh yeah I was making those ah I
accidentally took the 7.6 to2 did you
make those for me
yes so nice so nice you're
welcome you're welcome how far am I from
making love free stuff
chat and how funny do I look
now so funny
nerd look at me wait I want to see nerd
K you can see my orange hair at
least nerd my gosh
nerd give you
wedgie give you a swirly K oh you why
can't chat not
chat if you want to see how it looks
like because chat is covering myself
just look at me I don't I look like a
nerd my life today looks like a nerd
right come on just like
you wait I'll show you
chat what a inconvenient place to be for
you here can I turn this
no wonder what I look like from the side
do I have like a ponytail or still Kelly
tell me let me see hold it uh Pony uh
let's see yeah you got a ponytail I got
a ponytail ponytail kind of boy looking
frazzled like you don't take care of
your hair I you know some busy studing I
can't find my brush yeah she's reading
up on those
books and like the side of your hair is
like growing out of like the side of
your glasses and like above it it's like
a big bald spot it's kind of weird bald
spot no there is kind of a bald spot I
don't believe it you're messing with me
bald no
bald bald there's nothing wrong with
being bald it's true yeah there's
nothing wrong there's nothing wrong with
being bald I just don't want to be oh
Trader is opening up so let's go give
the quest back
yeah B to
one day we'll all be bald okay never my
head will be full of hair forever do you
need wood I have 6,000
6,000 that's the max stat stack it's
6,000 for my wood another stack yeah I'm
making another stack I think I can
consolidate my wood now what is it you
need wood just tell
Gigi I have so much wood don't even
worry
man that's a lot of wood I heard if
you're wood you have wood for more than
6 hours you should see a
doctor good thing you're training doctor
doctor can you see my wood
please are freaking
menaces my God sweet Jesus Joseph and
Mary nurse nurse I have so much wood can
you come count my wood I don't know
I'm quitting I'm getting my medical
license revoked I'm turning it back
in when you get fired from malpractice
so you don't have to look at my
wood um change of topic does the other
Trader have like better quests yes yes
the the other Trader has tier two quests
as well so the quest you guys got going
on right now that you want us to join is
that a tier two yes no oh let's go
finally oh I have I have I have two tier
two uh quests going on at the moment
bioo would you like a tempered blade
schematic a tampered blade yes okay
might be
good all the Traders will give you the
max tier Quest you're eligible for oh
okay I'll get tier two here too once I'm
there okay all Traders show tier two
okay
um what's happening Quest started oh
here do you want armor crafting right
here oh you guys aren't on my party yet
oh yeah one sec one sec
um let me see let me
see fun now yes do you have um 200 coins
yes I actually how do you know know
exactly how many coins I
have wait did you drop those magazines
for me too oh that was from someone else
oh oh I'm getting all these donations
from these
magazines all right I'm just buying the
last magazine he
has oh well thank you sir I'm
42 level 42 armor now nice when can I
make the next tier I want
there all right I'll uh leave
the group and then I'll uh be open to
being invited okay how to leave okay me
me too leave all right I am single and
ready to mingle
okay let's mingle I'll mingle with you
I'm ready to invited as well yeah I
invited you you buy it wait Crest failed
oh is it the sh Quest you just accepted
yeah it'll come back when you when the
person rejoins the party don't worry all
right all
right
okay doing me a
concern oh go I joined as well tier two
Quest let's go inite please I'm starving
thank you you might need to go accept it
in your menu there we there you go oh I
have two workstation magazines I'll
bring them to you kiaha
nice oh we're meeting up anyway aren't
we
yeah towards the quest I'll just go
towards the quest and then which Quest
are we going towards I don't know
there's one being shown to me okay I
think it's the same I am
[Music]
following yeah we got to climb the
mountain but we can do
it we just got to Skyrim horse it you
know EAS it
yeah I'm pretty goat like oh we go clear
to G that's for sure oh
really you really don't have to make
those
noises well you're pretty good at
that are crazy it makes me happy nuzzles
into your hand and licks your finger
looking for some I don't know if that's
necessary I'm just emulating goat
Behavior
is that not what goats do she's you went
to a petting
zoo do something
scary um flashes you my demon goat
eyes I I have passed out onto my back as
goats do out of I began eating your
liver oh wow asteris asteris Asis they
rping with words Barn Fe
Fields oh
no we got this
wait it's on the other side of the
board thank god let's run it
ladies all right let's go big
[Music]
party we can take them oh boy oh they're
s Snak too snakes there's so
many danger
noodle don't worry
Guys these guys will be easy small
potatoes what's wrong with oh never mind
I got like the angle on
it happening so fast steing zom worry
not guys I am skinning this war while
you are
fighting yeah get his
goodies there's a lot of them falling
from the sky
wrecked he's dead they jump so
high I want to fight too but there's no
zombies in my way yeah
so they're lurking they're lurking about
they're falling from the sky
oh even another ladder to
climb oh can we get much higher can we
higher oh I didn't die I didn't break my
leg I was so
scared again for 2 hours Golem
[Applause]
cooling mesh mod there's some goodies
over here guys if you guys want this
stuff Kiara and B let's go yeah I I
failed I just took going to where you
were so I'm giving up on that cigars
boost what cigars boost your strength
increase your but ability and make you
look like a sexual
tyrannosaurus what that's what it say
ever
W okay I I want to be a sexual
tyrannosaurus I learned it
Tyrannosaurus what even is that I don't
know Ty
T that is definitely what I
want you sure
yeah
it I want to be that that
person I'm
okay I'm
fine I also found a ton of gas cans full
of gas for when we get
cars so I'll hold on to him for
now at least I said it for you
guys I muted myself uh oh
why because not everybody has to hear
such things what things now I'm
curious of plays of words I see I think
that's just what the game was getting at
so well uh are we done with this Quest
we're done how is this tier two it was
too easy I agree it was very easy want
to find the big boar
[Music]
again you want to fight him again maybe
that wol again we lose our we should we
should the quests yeah in the quest
first quests are are better oh for this
do you want to do you want to do my
quest that's like right nearby sure mhm
yes I see it yeah maybe I don't know wa
where I'll just go I'll just follow
you what's this one also a clear Quest I
believe so clear are easiest cuz you
don't have to look around forever for
things just kill kill all the zombies
how did I have to turn in our current
Quest first right no it'll St you can
turn in multiple at the same time don't
die oh this is so pretty on my way
hopefully I break my leg again I I think
if you've cleared the quest and you die
you can still turn it in oh really yeah
as long as you cleared it I think I
don't know I might be lying I hope so I
think as long as you clear it yeah as
long as you clear
it yes no I wasn't lying I was not lying
oh G are you joining us yeah okay I'm
headed over okay I'll
wait this is a nice residence I hope the
B
respawn are those BS your source of meat
this whole time you getting the bacon
from I get some all Bs I have 16 meat
right now I need another boar oh wait
that's pretty good though that's a good
handful of
meat okay we let me see let me make sure
think we're
complete okay we are complete let's
go let's run
it
[Music]
Yi just run start
shooting he's
blasting
oh B I have a magazine for you I'm going
to stand right here while I'm dropping
it you thank
[Music]
you a so flow you look good I'm sorry ow
that was not my intention looking
ladies go up I wonder hey hey hey hey oh
we already in there
a sham
sandwich don't eat it it's a
sham
I my tummy is
fine oh there's an upstairs oh
H let's
go oh she was working out wow respect
when she turn into a zombie yeah so that
tells us no working out working out not
good for you you found a nerd me sorry I
ended up
cing please be nice to my ner friend ow
the club the club it hurts this baseball
bat is so
overpowered kind of laggy I can make
iron tools now oh we did it
Hunter's Journal Barrel extender I want
these gloves I'm taking them for
me what gloves SE shipping crate no oh
here's some
shotgun stuff
shot yeah there GG do you also use
shotgun yeah but I am using my bow
mostly right now so if you have a good
shotgun you can take
it ok
H thank you there's um what did I find
here oh I have some bullets for
Kiara thank you some what what bullet
does anyone use knife magazines I do I
use knife
here thank
you and here's the ledge Hammer if
someone wants to use the hammer cooking
magazine oh I do I do the hammer I found
I do the haming in this
household what you revolvers right B yes
I will be using revolvers later f okay
I'll leave these for you thank you I'll
keep it it's chaotic I'll put it in our
home later
okay good job team yeah that's it it's
so fast when we're big group it
is it's good we all get the reward yeah
not fighting for my life
I they have a pool I like steamrolling
enemies a pool this is a nice house is
this good to drink sip sip let's see
really
nice oh no it is it is not good to not
clean you need my hat what it's too late
for me I lost I'm going to get I'm going
to get beep and diarrhea do you need you
need tea I have tea oh there's more
zombies here I'm
[Music]
hung oh wait I have a food oh
no thank you Kell I love how you just
come in from
inside this guy looks like he's an
Outlast
yeah look like he's going to
explode
scary okay I think yeah let's return the
yeah go turn in some
quests good job team good job job that
good good job team no casualties I feel
like we could take the boar we could
probably I mean we we finished the quest
now so you want to take the boore let's
take the
boore all right we've definitely leveled
up a lot since then thanks to the W and
we have stronger weapons
partially and more people
people if we go in all at
once yeah I guess we could be
strategical about
it or we can all just hit each other
until something happens we can all hit
each
other wait um somehow we're close to our
home I'm just going to drop off some
things really quickly cuz I'm cucumber
me too cucumber
I have so much stuff in my
inventory oh you're here already same fa
yes H cooking magazine in magazine chest
thank
you did I just learn all these is
anybody hey chefs you guys making
anything delicious for us yes you know
how to make the H yet or what H do you
really want that hobo Ste huh how to
make hobo Ste one day we we'll get get a
delicious pumpkin
pie that's what I'm talking about fauna
makes the best pumpkin pie in this land
the most
delicious oh I'm going to get you a home
cooking
weekly thank
[Music]
you oh I can I can get a bicycle now oh
yes bike join the bike game yay so now
we we can go meet the
girl I want a
bike me too oh I got to go to the quest
to give it back and do you have to give
back the other quests at the like right
uh Quest person or can we give back both
at the same person
myc I'm going to go back give
Quest I will get
if you girls are going to the board let
me know okay going home first okay step
by step good why is there a hole outside
who who dug this yeah that's kind not
very nice them to do that my bike keeps
getting locked in there
yeah I swear this is not a natural hole
I think someone did this spend it all in
one place yeah know someone did that on
purpose to be mean
he's not a feeling you know who did that
he's not giving me a
bike he give you a bike oh he's giving
me a bike never mind y
[Applause]
yay oo I leveled up
too my
bike watch out for the hole
outside Fists
I have armor magazines for
you behind you oh sorry sorry a sorry I
was muted I was like talking to my
chat what's what's going on problem I
feel like my server is lagging where is
it maybe I haveed running for you oh
thank you the be is just endlessly
running for me oh I'm in the I'm in the
Traer yeah but you're like running on
oh I don't know
why did you buy those for me
FAA um I got them as a reward and gave
them to you okay okay I don't have wait
actually I do have money now he gave a
lot for that
one uh does anybody use like uh bows
even nowadays in our uh I think you do I
think and Cecilia also do I believe and
I'm also going to drop some magazines by
your oh but is this magazine Chad is
this a magazine that you only learn once
and then that's it because this doesn't
seem like
a yeah yeah okay then I wonder if she
had this before so if it's a one time
thing I don't know I'll take it for now
oh wait oh another
one wo burn
use the
bike uh you have to you can't place it
in here you have to leave the the Traer
area and then you can just place it down
and then press e to ride it and then
hold e to pick it back up again oh oh
I'm in the
hole I immediately went into the hole
watch out for the
hole oh dear I someone is this to us on
purpose I want them arrested
whoever of a
bike the bike the world is my o press x
x to ding ding X ding oh wait bicycle I
didn't see the bicycle I got a bicycle
too special jobs he gives special jobs
now yeah that's the trader that's a
Trader tra we need to ask for that I
urge you all to accept it so that we can
go meet her if you'd like
yes okay let me show you where she is
yes please I wonder then she the special
job we can go she would have a different
stock for magazines I
suppose she has a different stoping the
guy such Scholars
here big readers
ouch my bicycle is red oh now it's green
ah oh oh never mind but once we find
this new Trader maybe we want to get a
new house you the new TR yeah
maybe you can see
look disappoint so you'll find yourself
on the WR are we all going to the trader
gen yeah yeah uh that' be cool which
direction uh That Way Southeast right
yep only about a kilometer
away with my propeller hat and the
bicycle I feel like I can take off
anytime I'm a
helicopter this is the only helicopter
we're going to be able to get in this
game truly no we'll be we'll be able to
get a helicopter after by the end of be
able to take off in the sky yeah yeah
and then shoot them from the
helicopter is that supply drop Supply
oh I hear it I hear it I hear it a only
400 me away I'm going for
it okay let us know what's in it oh wait
it's in the scary Forest I'm still going
for it oh the Traer the trader is in the
scary Forest anyway
yeah y the supply crates are kind of
underwhelming though I'm not going to
lie there's not a lot of great stuff in
there maybe they get better also
depending on how far we are with the
race
I hope so after each stage maybe better
drop I hope fingers
crossed who are these Supply crates from
anyway yeah um Trader Jen doing it for
us cuz she wants to kiss us so bad
there's a big oh she did want to kiss me
earlier I'm on my way to watch
you oh there's a bigle
back up there is a big
hole Yeah I don't know where it's going
to drop you think it'll drop in the hole
no it did it did disappear from the map
did you collect it no no it's coming
down oh maybe it is going in the
hole it's coming in the
hole what's in there it sure is shotgun
shells that's all I wanted there's a
baked potato there's magazines too if
you want to take the magazines H I'll
take the
coffee what kind of magazines let's
let's open these and see what magazines
it has um it has handgun and armor
crafting assault rifle and workstation o
workstation for you oh yes I need both
armor and okay I'll bring those to you
thank you is the Traer lady like on a
weird path up a
mountain yes oh yeah you got to take a
swirly a a swirly path yeah I'm on it
right now it's not hard though it's fun
yeah I'm on my way over to Judy
witch Judy witch that sounds familiar
Judy witch um I'm going to her house by
accident this is a dead
end what does Judy want from you I don't
know it's kind of ominous
oh why is her last name witch do you
think I mean something
that's why it's
ominous it does the swirly Road go down
again weirdly like yeah it doesn't go
straight a bit up in the mountains this
is
confusing yeah that's why we need a
helicopter am I going back
helicop I missed there is a
snake oh you guys should have seen we
went to go find bio's treasure and then
it was that went into a snow place and
everything was super overleveled M and
we died a million times I can probably
saw the messages of be would die C died
die die it was intense it was crazy oh
oh I'm tracking the wrong
Quest how do you can you change which
quest Quest girl you're tracking I'll
just go to you you can you can uh set a
waypoint with right
click oh
fast what is this
path yeah it circles through the
mountains a bit but then afterward I
just went down very steep I just kind of
mountain goed it all the way down they
could totally place a uh roller coaster
here this is the perfect place it is
very
swirly I think
I did I make
it goating our way up here yeah we could
do that or we take the biking path there
is
one I got lot my legs are not strong
enough to bike up here my Cals pedal
pedal work those I'm trying working
harder I am a mountain biker
to put down some signs I keep on taking
the wrong
turns but now I think I got
it yeah it's just a little confusing I
went the total wrong way but I'm on my
way now you got this we should have gone
together I know yeah I could have showed
you guys the way sorry about that we got
distracted by the air
drop Six shotgun shells woo I'm almost
there on my bike wait how do you get off
a bike
e e and if I leave my bike somewhere
does it ever despawn or something uh so
hold e and drag to the hand symbol to
pick it up into your inventory
[Music]
okay H okay
noise
wow the lovely in here ah hi hi you made
it just in time this is her oh it's a
church oh so you took the bike path and
you're already there you're so fast I'm
I'm on the
mountain get lost two times just jump
down do M down the de
incline W closeup of her upper body
okay that's what I said you just you
just like have a front view over her
chest
[Music]
your health is my
priority now I'm motivated to get there
fast I got to see this dang she's
flirting with me she was like glad to
see your face
oh what I want her to FLIR with
me I want we have like 15 more minutes
before today's shift
ends I'm so sad our sh fun isn't it it's
so
[Music]
fun maybe it would be good to accept
some quests she has so that I don't have
to come here all the time I guess no
never mind we got two tier two quests at
the other guy too still yeah yeah she
only gives you one Quest at a
time okay I think I'll bicycle my way
home so that I can maybe in the last
minutes figure out where to put my skill
points and if I can make one more armor
piece
sure sounds
good head off for tonight thanks for
playing guys yeah thank you okay thank
you thank you at the same time tomorrow
I guess yeah same time I think okay okay
and then we have the raid too so we'll
have to get ready for that o the raid
the raid's going to happen like pretty
early right cuz it's already day
whatever M like free it's on the 21st
just get ready two or three hours I
think yeah we can play a little after
though so it's
fine yes I want to let's do it for sure
okay see you later have fun see thank
you so much byebye byebye care of
yourself oh she's already
gone I may have taken the wrong way
again I'm in the
mountains oh no are you biking through
the mountain through the mountains are
you biking directly up the mountain wait
kiaha is here no not directly up if you
you see me
uh if
you go that way here around here right
side then you should you should get
there wait where did you go gosh I think
I'm going up the mountain she down
[Music]
there is that
g no I don't know how to get out here I
get down here I can climb
this is it necessary to go through the
mountain no seems very difficult she has
a really nice
place
yeah she does how do you repair your
bike is your bike
Dam she's a little damage did you
destroy it no I just fell down the
mountain oh yeah you just need a repair
a repair click okay
congratulations I make my payment to the
Duke now BS when was night 14 uh we
missed it chat we missed
it it happened while we were all gone
but that's
okay people probably keep on coming into
our streams like and they missed the
beginning where we explained what
happened and they'll be like what did I
miss like did I sleep through it what
happened I must did you guys take a
Quest from her her I no I didn't I
should have you can um just always need
someone to handle the tough jobs oh I
would kiss you but oh do want me to help
you with your leg hygiene and all oh my
leg is okay right now my bike is not
very okay she'll be fine
though don't worry I'll go up the
mountain
again well I don't think you need to go
up the mountain to bike I you should
just I did say
is this view of her I don't even see her
face you don't see her face you just you
just stare right into
the it's a very welcome
bug we don't want to I don't think I
don't think it's a bug I think it's
[Laughter]
intended it intended learn an
Elixir
okay chat do you know what video I was
watching actually the liit I have it in
my
history thanks for letting me take care
of you and be sure to tell your friends
the quest I got so close I don't know if
I want to do it
though how long do we have I can I can
do it if you want with you oh I can do
it too where are
you
Northeast it's the tier 2 Clear G right
yeah yeah you you going to do a quest
yeah so let me go
where the one tier two GG okay I'm going
to try to get there ASAP is it up the
mountain or no no it's not up the
mountain don't break your legs that
way we don't have to like end exactly at
the 4our Mark right cuz I just want to
spend some time looking at my skill
points no just don't AFK for 7 hours
yeah yeah I will
not I'm just picking up stuff on the way
there's a lot of on the way okay I need
command one a nomad chest
yeah oh oats brother may I have some
oats zoom zoom zoom this place is
scary I know lives here dead people so
scary that dead people live
here oh we have two quests do we we have
a lot there's like three around they
next to each other who's Quest is it
it's two of mine okay we can do all
three of these actually oh okay we fast
yeah I'm almost there
[Music]
okay fours
I am really
thirsty is there
a here take my coffee thank you does
show and all that on your
bike
huh I could be dying right
now 250 M almost
there please
wait no
problem Wawa is on the way
soon I'm there oh the signs are telling
me to go
slow don't listen to them it's an
apocalypse who's going to enforce them
this looks like Fallout New Vegas yeah
does look like New
Vegas I can't
believe and me we're all playing New
Vegas
yeah funny danger noodles okay I am so
here
for you I have stuff for
you me too I have lots of stuff what all
for me yeah it's Christmas die orange
die watch out there's a zombie you can
die your bike or whatever else snake I
will die my cloes yo so many magazines
you guys are
amazing it is good that the whole server
knows what
all of that do you want this knife
thing oh I would like a knife thing
thank you scary scary welcome snake
o for
G
yes oh I have armor magazines
too does anyone
like or explosives yes Sledgehammer
thingies I do I do okay there you go yes
yes yes
yes
lovely I love how you girls keep on
getting magazines that I
need okay what's up hello
bues eating a can of pears it starts
blasting
everywhere oh I can buy something all
right Let's help out a little
bit I will help by opening
things oh we just started
blasting I will regret this but I will
go upstairs well I'm behind you oh
there's another upstairs
too
ow she got yellow eyes m orange
eyes
spicy it's getting spicier here in this
area things are getting a little bit
more difficult dangerous
danger that's good I was kind of getting
sick of all the same places yeah it was
too
easy sorry guys am I giving you guys
motion sickness is upstairs
there's a
box oh a forge ah
head let's
go more more more magazines you
go yummy yummy books I
am I like to eat
boogs oh there's some
here he's on fire
waa s loses you
oh
one
y we still haven't finished what's left
there there's more somewhere maybe
there's
more on the
roof
here us
careful don't fall how do I get up here
un
un did he not die from the fall he did
not he was
chilling
damn okay good job level 13 W Commando
outfit excuse me and what's outfit
commit oh that's I think a pretty good
one
Yeah medium
armor oh no but you my little pretty
lady will get a heavy armor set oh I use
uh medium okay I don't know if that's
good or not but but there's many
different medium
ones do you have any cool armor right
now bi boo I just have the god scavenger
outfit right now you can try this one
craft something better
my armor is critically broken right now
uhoh it's getting a little bit
yby well wait do you have a good good
outfit not yet here one day I'll hit
these arrows I'll just wear it for now
and then once I got the one I really
want I'll put this back into the armor
chest and somebody else can have
it okay thank you thank you oh I have
ammo for you
does anybody use assault
rifle uh no I use machine gun okaya ammo
for you over here where are you where
are you fauna
fauna where are you
oh behind
you I'm jumping up and
down we got to do like hot hot cold
cold oh thank you oh what is that
armor parts ah armor parts that's smart
that's what I need too all right second
Quest okay let's go oh this one's harder
right this is fetch so got find an item
okay be so much easier but everybody's
got their own item Brea SP oh god oh
it's
behind oh they're twins
I feel like we're ping them uhoh there's
a cop in
here he
[Music]
boming wow juicy how does he have so
much
rain yeah boom head goes
crazy is this a developer
himself painting
oh blue baby I'm not sure if this is one
of the developers
though
hello oh
wow I think they're in the
closet okay okay
okay oh woing
accidentally stab
you oh no AC stab her you you killed
me going to die as a anyway no no no no
no
[Music]
no wait I failed the question no oh I
think I did too it's okay no but the
other one's still there but you guys you
guys are still okay so keep going W okay
I'm feeling hot are you okay without
clothes apparently you feel
hot it says You must find a shelter
where am I going this
way Arizona
baby is this does this all look like
this because of forest fires I think so
unless the
[Music]
zombie everyone's dying
what did what did I
T oh it's the spikes it's the spikes Why
didn't it make
noise I didn't hear
it that was mine R I have survivor's
guilt now don't feel guilty get that
reward get that bread also there's two
up here
I
stairs maybe that would have been my CER
Satchel who I thought zombie but like a
really pretty one watch out for the
spikes I'll protect you I'm a Zombie
coming back to life Quest
Limit Oh yeah you Daily's uh Quest have
a daily limit oh ah
oh so I guess we can go back to give
back the
quest right is it are we are we done in
here yeah can lo here
yeah I have a medical
journal oh I I have some ammo for you
Kiara and oh I got a brawling for
fun thank you oh we forgot
this so scary oh here you go there you
go thank you oh my goodness
sick oh I can drink beer
now don't do it but it helps me punch
better did you go go into the uh attic
and found crates yes okay okay okay good
good oh now you can you can be like
drunken fist you know like the kung fu
people drunken
fist the medical journal than some
steroids too
thank
wow wow my armor level is at 54 now my
gosh that's half of the
maximum wait I accidentally got a
medical Journey Journal I dropped it
again I think I can make first aid
bandages
now our second doctor yeah doctor are
you lied now I am I didn't give up on my
dreams after all even though even though
I wanted to can you please check
something
[Laughter]
what was
it
um yeah let's go back I quickly want to
you know take care of everything make
some
Sho do we have to talk to the same
Trader that we got the quest from or is
it any TR the three of us failed uh the
quest let's do this one right here
that's mine so it fails the last one
that we did too trffic so we can
complete this one maybe okay I'm so far
I just was biking oh you were fast huh
yeah I just closed my eyes and started
biking she's in the hurry I'm on my way
back there's a quest here people yeah I
have a clear Quest
here
what I don't see it I don't either but
I'll take you don't see that you don't
see the bouncy exclamation Point yeah
normally we would see it sweet maybe we
can't do it together for some reason
hopefully we maybe maybe we can't cuz I
can't even press f on it CU we reached
the daily Quest limit is that why no I
don't think so cuz we failed we failed
ours so I don't have a it should say if
you have a limit but do you have at the
bottom left do you have a exclamation
mark a red
one no
is that the one that says you're done
with questing FAA do you have it I have
it yeah yeah we're done with questing
for
today I don't have it yeah you're not
done we can help I guess I can't start
no I can't start it I think it's bugged
so we can go maybe you can start it
because we're in a group maybe alone you
can do it maybe well I don't even see it
for myself okay so it's okay let's go
home
and end our days slowly
yes turn the quest first go to the Traer
yeah I follow you girls I don't know
where to
go I feel like I actually have to learn
the maps
now like before I just run around but
now there's like roads and terrain wait
do we go do we go up this road we go we
go down we go down go up we go we go up
we go up you right you right
C on them what are you
saying and then I started
biking yeah I think learning the roads
is good because now biking cuz it
Doesn't you can't just cut through
really easily with a bike
yeah this place is nice yeah Nice
Landscaping she just closed
now closed have a good
night there oh no she your bike she
stole your she stole my
bike what about this one did she Chuck
it outside this pink one did she throw
it oh did she did she Chuck it outside
that yeah she might have thrown her bike
out I oh my go go it does it not work oh
I guess that was nice of her to
do she's
no yeah just just cuz she's closed
doesn't mean she's
heartless
nice we'll figure it out later chat all
right well I guess this is where I will
stop for today okay okay yeah me too
goodbye bye bye I will stay in game just
to quickly skill points and stuff but I
won't stay too long and not stay
AFK don't AFK I
want wait where's Home where's home
byebye that way byebye byebye
[Music]
byee okay I'm going to get a skill point
really quick too I think I want this one
[Music]
though pain
tolerance I
think finish bra ER but I can't I have
to have
to I have to get so high into
fortitude finding hands wait does this
help oh this does help doesn't it
oh quick jab is it all
punching enemies will quickly be
overwhelmed by your Relentless onslaught
of
punches and that does sound pretty good
I love
punching I failed my quest that's fine
let me let me
leave
[Music]
game thank you again for watching and
thank you for for wait can I pause
this thank you for 900k I do want to do
well I don't know it's not so watch a
celebration as it is a stupid bit a
stupid dumb bit
that is not even anything but I
appreciate it very much thank you thank
you thank you thank
you do it anyway okay I probably will
I'll do the bit at some point it might
be late though cuz I'm kind of just
playing Seven Days to Die all week I'm
getting into it I don't really I don't
want to miss any I might have to but I
don't I will try my best not to miss any
days well I will probably miss the ones
that are in the middle of the night or
super early if there is one but I don't
want to miss the other
sessions so once again thank you very
much for watching thank you for 900k
appreciate it that's a lot of saplings
this a insane amount of saplings I
cannot even begin to imagine that number
it's unfathomed
so thank you very much I really
appreciate your support and you being
here this has been a lot of fun all
right I'm going to take off I need to
make my pumpkin bread I need to make
this dang pumpkin bread I don't know if
I'm going to make it tonight
CU it's late well maybe nothing wrong
with some midnight pumpkin bread
right but anyway thank you for hanging
out byebye fun well
[Music]
bye e