[Music]
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello
where should i put you where do you want
to be
i'm thinking of playing in
full screen today
you know
what you're
going to be a bit more stretched like
that right
yes
age of
empires finally
i'm so sorry to keep you guys waiting
it's been
uh
a long time since the first one i mean
not a long time since the third week but
third time is the charm
yeah yeah yeah third time is the charm
today today it's happening
oh
it's not
it's not really fully filling out the
screen whatever let me
just do it in obs
come on
[Music]
okay
yeah yeah yeah
that's a bit too big but
oh well i i i hope you guys don't
miss um or don't don't uh
i hope you guys see everything that you
need to see um i played the tutorial
uh
[Music]
like completely
a game sound should be oh wait
game sound should be there
[Music]
now
very quietly though
uh i played the whole tutorial
you know including david wallace coming
to
rescue me at the very end
wait what do you need to what's what's
on lower right oh me oh
i somehow thought you said lower left
and then there's something really
dangerous here these numbers are fine
right
[Laughter]
oh the famous song
is pretty nice
yeah
found this on yeah
okay
ah sorry
i moved the microphone
so we're finally going to play this
today
sorry sorry sorry for waiting
for letting you guys wait too much i
guess since we don't have anyone to play
with yet we're gonna play single player
uh what campaign you wanna try i don't
know
i
um don't know that's me by the way
that then that one's me
that looks like me
i know i'm carrying a flag for fish but
that's me
wait is that fish on its helmet
i thought it was like feathers or
something but when i look closer that's
fish what the [\h__\h] why does he have
what does he have
fish stuck like that to his helmet
how much does he love fish
okay that's not me forget it never mind
i thought that was me you know it's kind
of it looks like the feathers
that i have on my ears right now
[Laughter]
that's so weird sign of stat status nah
it's ridiculous
what country did [\h__\h] like that huh
never seen something like that before
never and i've watched a lot of medieval
tv shows and movies
okay so
single player
what do you mean i've i've done i've
played the turn what do you mean
you should know that game or did you for
some reason delete my history
should i have saved no
uh wait what is this difference
associated with or against computer
players play for the official campaigns
based on real-life historical events
which one should i do
campaign story
okay
okay let's do it
oh this is um
ah does this randomly assign me some uh
oh wait never mind
europe
oh
there you go so i can choose
one of these
william well see i did it for some
reason it only gave me bronze but i
think all i did was gold and
[\h__\h] this bronze sign [\h__\h] that
um
oh dosio oh my god
where are the tutors
i guess there's no tutors in here
it sucks
but i remember the joan of alc
campaign i think
for some reason
um
maybe i should be somewhere else on the
screen
should i be like wait
should i be here
let's read this
uh oh [\h__\h] i i chose it
go back
the age of king's campaign
joan of arc 14 28 1453 and that's get
that gets pretty close to you there's
like a thousand no 100 years
100 years more and we're at the tudors
almost war has raced for 100 years and
the exhausted french army has lost
nearly every battle the heir to the
french monarchy is too cowardly to
ascend to the throne soon the english
enter burgundian allies will conquer all
of france but in the darkest hour a
young peasant girl declares that she
intends to save france in this campaign
you will play as the franks
i like that cool
um
honestly i'm gonna be very honest
these are apparently all real people but
joan of arc is the only person i've
heard of in my whole life
who the [\h__\h] is barbarossa
can the will of one man forge an empire
frederick barbarossa attempts to unify
the squabbling german fiefdoms into his
holy roman empire and then expanded into
poland and italy should he accomplish
these feats will he dare to take the
cross and lead his army to the third
crusade
titans attila
ah
now you say it yeah a little bit maybe
heard of it before
and i mean dracula what the [\h__\h] why
dracula
history forged an incredible legend
around the man who held 15th century
wallachia against the vast armies of the
ottoman empire his cruel tactics and
sharp mind made him the most feared man
in all of eastern europe but will they
be enough to parry the turkish onslaught
400 years after the fall of rome italy
remains viciously contested as
byzantines lombards normans and muslims
covet the southern italian port of bali
experience this chaos for the eyes of a
byzantine family rising from the common
soldiery to the nobility and preserve
the legend of the romans
interesting
ah dossier but somebody in the chat said
that jonah of arc is like a good
starting campaign
are they like kind of like different and
difficulty wait there are
oh wait um these ones are red is it
because of the time period because these
ones are blue but i guess it's like
thousand years before is that why
i'm green no this is around the same
time
oh this one's green
is that the difficulty
[Music]
that's the difficulty swords show the
difficulty swords
swords i don't see any swords here it's
just to call it
oh
that expansion do i have do i have to
buy an expansion for this
but they all they all have colors
this is purple
the swords next to the name
[Music]
ah on here i was looking at the
description
oh
that one has a lot of swords
okay these
these four
are apparently on my level
mm-hmm
okay
um
you know what we will go for joe
and of arc
an unlikely messiah
oh
okay wait why does it say de why does it
say german
i have it in english everything's
english should be fine
okay and then maybe uh i can go back
down now
can i come back down i'm getting like
dizzy my all the blood is
accumulating in my
in my brain
[Music]
this morning i walk to visions of fire
and steel we leave
i wandered through camp ignoring the new
snowfall but observing the wounds and
wariness of every soldier under my
command observing the desperation in
their eyes
it was then that i first saw the girl
that's me she told us that her name was
joke
she was but a peasant who did not know
how to ride or fight
she told us that she intended to rescue
that's actually crazy what the [\h__\h] the
darkness lifted from the men's why does
she think she can save france
and we drank in her everything normal i
may have lost my faith
but joan has not lost hers and that is
enough for me
what happens
what's wrong with that
where the rightful ruler of foss the
hides from his foes
the war-torn land in between is infested
with enemy marauders
and we will lose many men oh no
death is by now an old companion
but for jude why we will face it
what did she get you under her spell or
what
it honestly why no i'm curious
[Music]
i think i've heard of history of her
before but
why did they choose to follow her
joe and must survive
she's the power of god
john was the original idol
she says that god's like well of course
he did of course you did
as he usually does
yeah because god god is um her papa
yeah yeah yeah he drew her he's her
artist
and now she's everyone's oshi
she's the og
not beethoven but i don't
a french idol
what the [\h__\h] honestly wait is there
like a is there anything like good movie
about joan
of arc maybe i already saw it but is
there a good movie i want to watch
because like i like watching um movies
and tv shows of around that period
yeah which one
and what's it called not nothing
no
i mean like a real live movie
the one with mila jovich is great
maria the virgin witch oh i watched that
anime
um fully
bill and ted are you guys for real that
doesn't sound like in like a movie or tv
show that's focused on that topic
the messenger story of joan of arc is
good great okay thank you that actually
sounds like a proper
recommendation for once
oh
villain where the [\h__\h] is villain
[Music]
anyway okay i look it up
villains ted is time traveled oh i see
oh well i'll think about it it already
sounds like it's not really
you know proper
faith
oh man
oh yeah
i love reading wikipedia articles yeah i
am
anyway well escort joan from the camp
and
vocular
francis enemies are england and burgundy
be on the lookout for their forces do
not expect much assistance from the
demoralized army of friends
but they would i thought i thought i
motivated them but to be alert for any
soldiers who might be inspired to join
your army once they see joan oh
protect your two knights they are your
best fighters and know the lay of the
land my two knights you mean the ones on
the horsies it is not necessary to
eliminate all enemy forces just focus on
bringing joan to her destination
uh-huh oh okay
keep an eye on jon's health if it gets
too low keep her away from the
interested
i have a bad feeling
joan the maid one blue has reached the
french army camp of vogue where several
men have plans to escort her safely to
shinon she know
uh
one blue for orange the road to chino is
dangerous if english soldiers and bands
scrolling over the countryside
oh no however there are many frenchmen
who are willing to help the joan the
maid
reach her destination okay
so
uh we bring her to camp okay
i'm scared it's it's been a week since
our last bonjour
my colleague and i will escort you to
the chateau of the dorfan or else we
will die trying i am john demetz and i
will protect you with my life
we we oh this is joan okay okay uh okay
or should i wait do we just go or do i
start by um
building some [\h__\h] wait i can't i can't
i can't build it
wait what how does this work do we just
go
okay
keep
which it
this one
we are somewhere right now do you have
not guys
yes
i have heard your claims and believe
what you say
we will follow you to shin
you're gonna follow me okay good i
inspired them come on
youtube
you don't wanna come
what about wait i saw someone here
yeah yeah yeah
come on
i guess they did say don't expect too
much from them
leave it [\h__\h] come on
join me
i'm inspiring i'm a waifu
come on
no
leave it oh okay i guess we're gonna go
can i not like build more like in a
tutorial i like build stuff can i not be
weary also hold ahead our enemies the
english are out in force and their
burgundian allies are thick as rats this
question is the better part of valor
wait wait wait
wait wait wait indeed
ah
can't build on this map oh i wanted to
make myself stronger do i have to go
with what they give me
and like i mean don't i need like wood
and stuff food
oh hello wolf
theft do i do i need
let's kill him let's kill them
okay
go away
[Music]
you're a big attacker
do i get the wood the rocks
no
don't even get the wood
mama mia anyway can i do like a
formation where joan stays in the back
please can she do that or is she
not caped there we go that's relatively
that's a good formation
am i going the right way
no heart look out a battle rages ahead
stay back let's be caught in the
crossfire
okay stay back
let's let's leave okay okay should we
another glorious loss for france
glorious i hope you really can turn the
tide of this war joan of arc
okay um
can we go now
seems to
well we can feast on the dead bodies
nah
there's some english among them oh no
they're they're fastly turning into
speedy specially turning into ground uh
earth soil we don't want that we want
only the freshest
glorious loss wonderful that sounds so
positive
france suffered another glorious loss
let's go
um am i
am i
is this little patch here
where i need to arrive at
that's really far and i'm going in the
wrong direction perhaps
i got to sleep already i've been
streaming for like five minutes
good night i guess
oh
i really like the way water looks in
this game it it looks absolutely
beautiful
um as if
we're in the maldives can we i guess we
cannot pass this bridge
but if it's shallow water we couldn't
theory pass
i'm just guessing this this is where
they want me to go
hopefully
math is not that big so
[Music]
uh
ah hello uh are you nice
friendly for oh okay uh oh oh
[Music]
what has become of our homeland yeah
what the [\h__\h] man no you can you don't
have to destroy
but can can jonah list heal or something
okay
can you heal
no what can she do
away we don't have to kill the house
it's a house guys
chill
ah
where where's the lion formation
when wow why do you go back
hurting the house what did it do to you
she can regenerate health okay but what
about the others
we're gonna we're gonna die
i need even more
um people to join me
bonjour a box formation there we go oh
yeah that works too no no it doesn't i
don't like it
oh [\h__\h] no
purple
we're like free people i don't think we
can attack
whoever's behind that
theft
[Music]
no
no no no
trigger the event first okay
um
please don't kill me i'm holy a
burgundian in campaign we'll never get
through that wall without cj that's what
i'm saying
that's what i'm saying
all right then we just walk around i'm
glad they don't have arches and they're
shooting me
leave it liebe
oh yeah oh yeah oh no
leave it
just walk around yeah um i guess yeah
they did say in the description i don't
have to battle these people just run
leave it
try to stay out of their way
as much as possible is this bridge
intact yes
how do we tell her tell me what
wait what
how do i quickly get back to my people
they're there okay
[Music]
click on the mini map
stop wait um somebody once told me
to use the knights
uh can i how do i click them
to use the knights to scout the area
through that through that
what do we have here two
two wolves
[Music]
leave it
okay
it's just a bit annoying to switch
between them all the time because you
always have to like select them like
this what is this
what is this
it's yellow why is this something
something yeah okay wait yellow was our
color right like the
our english people at
least think yellow was
on our side
[Music]
ctrl number to group them
city only
one
oh
thank you
amazing
okay um
a village is here so i think we're safe
here
i'll also assign all of them to
oh [\h__\h] what oh i can't do that
i can't do them also as a group okay
oh you're sure
gather your belongings men we follow
jonah thank you we'll carry that along
with us it may yet be of use yeah you
better um in that case
these are maladams these are also many
times okay you
and you
and
you
you go to
ctrl
too
you are wait you're not you're pacman oh
well still fine
okay
thank you for joining this this village
is actually like on on my side and
they're not [\h__\h] cowards like
everybody else beautiful
beautiful
ah
can we just walk through here oh no
that's where the map the map ends okay
how about downwards
um
hi the dying man in the ram
oh
interesting so for example how do i hide
him like this no okay
this one
also
do they
heal inside
three out of
45.
now he's in
no
okay but um the ram
like
what's the use of putting people inside
they make the run faster
or because they like um
what's that sound because there they
like move it from inside
it attacks and moves faster cool okay
um
good uh
let's go oh wait i already tried to go
there
uh can i go through
oh
over here maybe
casey hux
relax
oh
no i guess not
i don't see a path here i guess i have
to go a different way wait no they want
me to attack the
the purple place now
no way no [\h__\h] way
no way
not ready for that fox
oh no can i get some more people maybe
there's some
what is what what's over here
and i want more people oh nothing
i'm not a hodor
don't forget siege web ben
what the siege weapon
what
nanny you say no i didn't
uh
there you go
oh there's auto safe
or
french idol
is my
oh she
okay
save
the ram is a siege weapon okay
oh wait i guess it doesn't count
no no it's oh it's coming with me
obviously what the [\h__\h] okay
oil
oil indeed sleep it
they're not very fast can i hide joanne
inside the ram too
is that a good idea
yeah should i should i
leap it
feels relatively safe wait wait wait
she's like wait for me stop rolling away
i want to answer please
all right
oh is she in i think she's in yeah okay
nice um
from where
from where should we attack
and where should we try to enter
what about what about here
i don't see the wall here
we need a manganese ram to get suzy's
walls oh here is navigate okay
so this ram
kill this yes oh yeah
and have the people ready as well oh
there you go they keep on
going together okay
wall is weaker than gate that's what i
thought you know but okay oh dear oh
dear archers oh no
[Music]
wait a second wait a second let me let
me rethink this
[Laughter]
they can shoot through the
gate but can they shoot through the
other wall
if we go for here maybe instead
oh my god
oh they can okay well well well well
wait what about the [\h__\h] ram rabbit
right
never mind
um
bad idea bad idea only oh [\h__\h] only
sense the ram
maybe
god damn it i've lost so many people
already
do it
good job
come on come on you can do it
oh oh great stress
okay let's go
back
oh you can stop no you can stop rambling
or should i wrap something else should i
ramble my friends don't know when to
give up
i'm gonna wrap the are that's it they
only had a few arches no way
there must be more oh oh oh there we go
yeah now we have the upper hand
do they have like a relic or something
here
you guys get distracted so fast can they
actually do something smart for once
anyone else left
we have like
no concentration on the task okay i
think we're done
ram why are they gonna rebuild [\h__\h]
oh they better not
micromanage
[Music]
as long as the the fire doesn't do any
damage to my people
that fell down wonderful
okay cool
now everybody okay all right oh yeah
go go
over here
change your bathtub to make them less
aggressive
i don't know wait i can't no hello
oh you can't
wait what the [\h__\h]
what what why are you going that way no
just go that way
oh because when i press it uh when i
click at something that's dark
they go a different way
okay it makes sense
then let's send to garrison to kill this
wall
they're not very smart at path finding
you no juice
if they keep on
wasting their time at these houses their
weapons are going to be like
what's the word really um
black
because
that's a good towel
[Music]
everybody
let's keep on moving is that actually a
pack or
uh oh oh yeah
so a little bit of a hill
maybe not the most ideal path for the
ram
defensive
thank you mmm
venison um
you want to eat
[Laughter]
when i killed the wolves i couldn't eat
them
bonjour
can we no oh yeah okay
okay
maybe i shouldn't
i'm using i'm using a weird path i know
uh can i
walk over here
no
okay you will find your way your way
away
eventually guys let's go here
oh [\h__\h]
yeah yeah
[Music]
you can walk on the water in in certain
places some some
some waters are more
shallow leave it
wrong way mon ami no i i was i thought
so this didn't feel like the right way
wait
ah can i walk across these waters or
like here
[Music]
i can walk over these waters
and god damn it
[Music]
see
i thought so cause like there must be a
reason why we walked for the purple base
for [\h__\h] sake
uh
i knew it
i know it they wouldn't send us fruit
all these woods and hills
makes no sense
yeah
lots of big cities were founded next to
challenge that is passable by foot and
cart are you joking that's irony right
because like obviously they would build
it where you can't pass if you're smart
yeah yeah yeah the venison voice line
was important it was a secret event that
i just wanted to show you guys
urgently
oh oh they want to trade oh well well
they have to build
a bridge then i don't know
oh wow wonderful
wait wait no i want to do it differently
oh god damn it okay
um
no
how about
the pikeman
[Music]
one no how can i get more than one
pikeman
[\h__\h]
hold down shift and click to select like
there we go
the pikeman might be better at dealing
with wolves
what do you think
i thought you know because they have a
long weapon they want hello kill kill
the wolf
remind them
you know keep the wolf away from their
bodies but
click on any of them twice ah okay okay
okay oh yeah
[Music]
lovely fun thank you
glad you guys like it um
what awaits us here
there are burgundian soldiers everywhere
hurry west to the river where we can
make our escape where's me on the side
of russian
west is left we are in west oh god are
you coming for me
oh [\h__\h]
away go away
they're just
going into position and which way then
this is west there's a boat for me
what
that's my boat what the [\h__\h]
we're just gonna look we're just gonna
walk past and what about my ram can my
ram join
what about my rapture like should i get
joan out of the ram
ram ram can get on boats okay cool cool
uh can we go faster can we run perhaps
why don't they run
no no no
yes yes yes yes
and also here other ship
um [\h__\h] go go go go
go booty
no
oh [\h__\h] what do i do it doesn't work
[Music]
why did it suddenly stop okay okay okay
i never tried getting into a boat before
in this game i wasn't sure what was
happening
full capacity in one of them but
they wouldn't walk to the boat
i thought i could only control the boat
if i have people inside oh well okay
is this the right way no
okay then this way
or do we just go do we just stop here
i wonder
oh
maybe
[Music]
i should save
okay
oh how about here
oh no lots of trees
[Music]
here baby
oh here looks good here looks very good
i can go up here
how do i get them out of the boat here
unload
huh
oh
uh
unload height
wait
is this gonna work
can i get through
yes but i think i'm missing my ram
click to un-garrison this capped ram
um
these chips are so stupid
okay
do we have everything
outside no yeah i think so
cafe
okay oh yeah
so where the [\h__\h] are we
this this again doesn't feel like the
right path
let's let the knights find out
yeah no i'm missing the mini map
um
[\h__\h]
i think i think i need to go here but
i'm like oh oh watch it
ah right
maybe maybe this way
is the first time i see someone take
this
well oh hello
i'm i'm original this is yellow this is
our color right
i don't like to copy
we have maybe
[Music]
cook me long
enough
quest accomplished
joan is healthy
and living her best life
yes
i made it
but now
but she did
no she's she's there click to anderson
okay
no no evil wait
no evil surprise right
is this is this place occupied by
evil people
whoa
across the bridge okay
i like this place with the flags here
it's quite pretty
uh-huh
i have no good sense of where to go in
this game apparently
oh
okay
oh but this seems fine
yes let me in hello
[Music]
thank you took you long enough to open
the door where's the red carpet
[Music]
oh we keep on going this is a big place
huh
hey oh
nice catapult or whatever that is called
again
oil
oh
come on
come on oh is he trying to heal us that
cleric
that'd be very nice of him
we'll see you now
[Music]
uh-huh he will see me
where is he
pray
[\h__\h] jump scared pig
frankie's victory
i mean it didn't feel like a victory we
just escaped basically and ran to a
different um base like the cowards we
are
victory jump scare
okay next door
as joan's footsteps echoed down the
marbled hole of the chateau
the fat and whispering dukes did not but
snare
the duffer himself seemed afraid
as she kissed his
that's feet got him she demanded
why does england claim what is ours
why are you not crowned king of france
as is your right wow okay you know
exactly what she's doing there the
chamberlain was stroking his ego
at the door kind of kind of provoking
him by kind of positively undermining
him he stands only to the shoulder of
the shortest man
but all of us must look up to speak to
her
i know not what silent conversation
passed between the door fair and his
would-be savior hmm
but it was obvious that his majesty was
in the same thrall as we mm-hmm
yay
i did pretty badly but anyway next level
march 26th shino it is one thing for a
band of dispirited soldiers to put their
trust in a teenage girl
it is entirely another for that girl to
be given command of the army yeah why
what the [\h__\h] like
what did you do filled with pride
and we heard the dolphins heralds
pronounced i joke i don't get it i don't
this sounds like some kind of fantasy
blood
so that she may look like a general the
dolphin presented joan
i was skeptical
but not only did the man unearth a
rusted blade
but we found that the sword had belonged
to charlemagne
grandfather i'm still confused
i shall not doubt her word again
still visible on the hilt
was the fleur-de-lis
adopted the fleur-de-lis she looks so
sick now oh cool
wherever joan goes
i think this is kind of a fake hit until
you make it kind of folio story the city
of hollyoak is one of the finest
when it
is about to fall definitely this war has
dragged on for 100 years with precious
few french victories
the people of orleans need a savior yo i
love the sound of receive jonah horse
stepping tip
okay joe and must survive that is
reasonable the cafeteria and orleans
must remain standing escort joan to
blows
blow blue so that she may command the
french army how do i say that blue blue
[Laughter]
ah
okay
the french army is limited to the castle
age oh and a population of 125 hurry to
orleans
that sounds so
english
before the english can cause much damage
be wary of english force yourself of the
river but do not forget the rendezvous
of your army and blah
blah ease
bl bluis or leon
uh once the supplies arrive and only on
you will be able to build up your forces
frankish knights are useful uh for
taking care of english longbow men
french knights and siege weapons
frankish castles are inexpensive and
provide excellent defense
use your market to trade for resources
until you can venture outside of the
city the english castles have large
garrisons it is best to assemble a large
attack first before attempting to storm
them
yes yes that's my plan but we can't wait
too long right
rich farmland is located west of oleon
but outside of the city walls it is one
outside of the city walls and vulnerable
oh
[Music]
i see
jonathan her escort is leaving for only
all reinforcements and supplies are
waiting for her in blah blah
finally the army must reach the city of
ollyong across the river and relief the
english siege of the city the english
have divided their army surrounding
early all from the both sides and
occupying several castles to the north
is the northern english army
you think i'll remember all of this
you will need siege equipment to destroy
their castles the burgundy burgundians
camp to the east
they are not a real threat at first but
left alone they will train the size of
[Music]
this is timing is important here i am
the duke bill
milady
i will proudly ride with you uh-huh
you and
you is
one
no wait you and you
is one
so the snare
should we let them go already
to um
i can't see but my map should i go where
should i go
there's no good space for me to be on
the map maybe the ride sign oh city
needs help the english are coming oh
[\h__\h] hell mate
uh
[Laughter]
chat
you go maybe here how maybe this is
better you prefer do you prefer to be on
this side
the english are
coming the angles are coming
the control group i'm so attached me to
me too
in the middle oh the middle ah true i
guess i'm usually never in the middle
it's kind of unusual but okay
oh yeah here's good
chat can be in that box there
where what do i do first
wait what did i do first
what did i do first
ah
[Music]
why do germans like aoe too so i don't
know german's austrians are like rts
games i don't know why
follow the roads but there's two paths
which one is the right one i guess um
but only only with these two right
um
can you guys do something useful in the
meantime
please
john oh
hi monk wanna come with me no
why not
take everyone
okay
light color color light cavalry right
the ones on the horses no oh wait this
one maybe scout cavalry you mean scout
cavalry
go go go
i'll put you on free
yeah yeah
check it out what is this place all the
bags let's check it out let's check it
out
nothing so far oh oh oh purple i hate
purple
you're supposed to fight against that
um
[Music]
oh no
okay my light cavalry
maybe i should have walked around them
who should have walked around them
oh
[Music]
well we only lost one dude and a lot of
hp
oh we can send them back to heal well
not the dead one right
so if the wounded ones
you got them in right
if the wounded ones
maybe you should maybe we should send
all of them
and the rest are fine
how how how how how how i don't even i
don't even see him anymore
yeah so he got killed so he's dead okay
[Applause]
okay can you heal the other one thank
you
why don't you just come with me
okay
and people die when they're killed what
the [\h__\h] chat
leave it
okay
so um i wish i still had a scout but uh
okay we don't talks
so i'm just gonna send the protagonist
okay
this doesn't seem like a perfectly safe
path but oh well ah
is this friends
i'm scared
hey box
they're they're light blue
lines blue
ah she's not important anyway yeah
[Music]
thank you oh yeah with my white horse
and my white armor i look so much more
convincing now so they all joined me
beautiful okay so but they did say do
not go immediately we want to be as
strong as possible um
can a trading card go trading how do i
do this again
where where would i send them to the
to to the very bottom
here
is there something to trade i didn't ah
right click on the ally market
oh they just go in there
no but where do they go now
i need to just find it first okay that's
what i thought okay so this is ours now
no
i still can't like do [\h__\h] here why the
[\h__\h] okay leave it
we need to get your supplies pass the
english onto only all we need to get
those supplies past the english okay
where the [\h__\h] are you guys going
with all of
them also with the trade cards
okay yeah i mean they could start
trading immediately when we reach only
oh yeah
maybe
no no can i
uh
how do i
i said double click but that's not quite
it
no those are super oh those
the trade cards are the supplies oh
wait
wait me do one thing um
what was it again shift
there you go
[\h__\h] my breasts don't can you guys like
kill him what is he doing
be faster
the eye is gone
kill him kill him
archers [\h__\h] i am oh yeah
bonjour no we can't let them go up
oh what a [\h__\h] waste of time
but is he not gonna attack like my oh
what is he where is he going what's his
plan
oh man cafe
everybody oh yeah get your ass back here
oh he's just a scout okay okay okay
that's not ideal either though um
where was the city
no i want to i want to select
but no no what's the right button
yeah and then um this okay
[Music]
but i want i also want them all as a
group except for
you and you and
all of the trade cards
are gonna be
two there you go finally
okay
now
we must go to
oleon
oh look at all those
materials
is this the right path or am i taking
the wrong path once again
okay faith
[Music]
don't think that would fit all of us but
wait
should i be particularly happy about
this can we like take you
um can we join um
we join boats
nope nope not looking good
no we wouldn't fit all of them
uh take turns ah that's so smart
you're fred oh yeah that is so smart
leave it so we can cross the river
uh oh wait that's uh those are trees
[Music]
how about here
yeah that looks good
unload
yeah okay
both go back both go back
huh
where did you see burgundy
over there wait what
okay
my safe
okay this boat go here
okay
is this is this smart check map yeah i
see some purple on the map
oh finally
but they're not i don't see them maybe
are they attacking here
we're here
no
like here i guess we just saw like a
glimpse of it
okay
unload and
unload please
here
okay
that takes a little bit too much time
for my
taste but okay okay relax it goes on
[Music]
oh okay he's dead was that a scout
but that's that's my home i've arrived
already yo this place is huge
oh
[Music]
i heard shots
what why am i hearing shots is it the
are they train the archers big hugs
look i should work
now we are
saved wow
yes you're saved of course indeed and uh
where do i do it do i send the card
somewhere here now wait a second
oh
for that one guy
stop it
oh but that's what's happening they're
like
ah now that's what the shots are
ah
they're trying to defend well how about
you just um chill
just chill inside
and then stand ground okay just just
chill
um
what are we to do now
do i wait
where do i deliver the
clark's not here
is this not my town
the cat town center oh was this the town
center
yes okay
they all look so similar they need to
like make it more and look more
different like the ones with the horse
box is obvious
brought us supplies now we can masters
of forces we need to raise one of the
english cases
[Music]
okay
destroy one english castle okay but
first you want me to um have more
have more of an army perhaps
oh upgrade to man at arms you didn't do
that here yet one
[Music]
what
research wheelbarrow hell yeah
research town lunch food
why don't we have food 650.
but obviously we need more villagers
we only have one free villagers
cafe
only have three villages my dad let's
make that
okay free
okay
i'll make more people
get busy oh i'm being attacked by two
burgundy
we're fine we're fine
so these are all normal houses for
everybody to live in right
oh
okay
make more make more how many though
oh
maybe a few
one scout cavalry because we lost one
but then i want these ones but we need
now we really need food okay so where is
the farm did we not have a farm here
uh
like a not not a farm but like a win
nothing nothing
how's this work again
build a farm should we just do it inside
i wanna build it outside
that's scary
the hints at the beginning to be fast
yes
i remember
and also they were yeah there was a hit
that like there's
farmlands we even saw them didn't they
were they
what oh
that's the castle that we're taking
right
i don't know where the farmlands are
anymore
i saw something
near it
farms near town center
oh you want me to build them near the
town center
bestie so
that they don't have to go so far
[Music]
i'm confused
because they have to drag it back mm-hmm
farming simulator for now
chopped trees okay but that i will have
to do outside
uh where do i see like all of my other
dude that was the button that was the
button okay you chop trick wait
you chopped three
you chopped three and then
we built wasn't there something yeah a
lumber camp
wait i saw that somewhere inside no
no okay but we can should we build a
lumber camp inside or outside
[Music]
near the wood line
um
oh the couple ones next to the town
center
okay
ah can i undo what i just told them to
do
you guys just go here
[Music]
what
you guys are confusing me
press delete on the building to cancel
or destroy them
anyway now nobody's [\h__\h] farming
farm go go
[Music]
uh
military buildings
another watchtower is that the same
thing yeah
um
i mean maybe we don't there's a lot of
watchtowers around i hope they're doing
their job properly
they're not
what the
[\h__\h]
i'm stressed out this is stressing me
out this is stressing me out already
what the actual [\h__\h]
hello can you guys like kill them
[Music]
repair that [\h__\h] immediately
defensive maybe
wait why the [\h__\h] are you inside
can you kill them
[Music]
wow
leave gates with cake units on your
gates they will keep them open
okay perhaps
did you fix that
not properly yet
oh what the [\h__\h]
wait i want food
where do i go for food should i just
make more and more farms endless amounts
of farms i'm not sure if that's really
like
what they want me to do
cafe
huh
okay
[Music]
there we go
oh that's here i guess
[Applause]
um i've got one here
there's not much space
[Music]
we don't have any
stones in here though to mine
the ones near my this one
[Music]
hey
last year
[Music]
did i do it wrong
okay
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
english stop attacking me
as please as it's just one that's okay i
think i don't know oh my god
how many how many
um
like army people
should i
have until i'm ready to go
i need
more food though also i want to like um
[Music]
research everything i can
okay
we don't
we're not close to 200 yet
why why was the oh god
it was the
this one
oh no that's not it that's not what i
was looking for where
is the
this one
research scale armor
the blacksmith because they make my army
stronger
max population is 150 okay yeah yeah
we're also still at the feudal age we
want to go to the castle age that would
be nice but i need 800 foods for that
200 gold gold is okay but um
still need more foods
okay
ah research complete beautiful
research
[Music]
you can sail villagers to blow to get
lumber
but that's so far
they need to bring it here now
build your farm near an ally town make a
mill there
there's no space here
research mill
uh
where was research mill
farm research heavy plow you mean
[Music]
why can i not
why can't i
i get it for free
oh let's go okay it's all ready i'm
already doing it huh
i already have it by default
noise
okay um besides that
[Music]
okay i should save i should save food
now to get up to 800.
that's gonna take a while uh maybe
let me look around oh dear
um
well everything's so far ah ah there it
was
there's some stuff here but
it's relatively far won't i get like
attacked
while i'm gathering that
[Music]
i can't they will right
but
why are you just sending unit or two
with them oh okay
but when even when they gather it like
here
don't they have to bring it all the way
over here
or if i build a camp there and they put
it into the camp it counts as my
materials
okay okay okay
then
you
[Music]
and you go here
and
a knight comes with you
how about that
and then and then one more i just want
to get them into a group first
maybe a second night or or an art shirt
one or two archers
[Music]
is that a big enough group
how about this i know i'm on the attack
i hear it but they're taking care of it
fine
that's that's that looks like a safe
group to me like there being plenty
protected
okay so you guys
oh
he's waiting at my ship you guys want to
go
is that food
you have a wood to give a wood uh wait
food resources i would prefer
i didn't see any food resources
and that's gold
i know like i'm moving the mouth what do
you mean
a maybe a fishing dock
i did that in a tutorial fishing dog
would be nice there's a lot of fish in
the sea
okay then let's go here and then kill
that dude and then build although they
all come from this bridge don't they
i mean that's not the safest maybe over
here
we go here and you also become
group four
and then the
the villagers built
the
dock here
and then
another villager
builds uh
a watchtower
oh
here
okay yeah
yeah
wait
i don't even need lumberjacks or i don't
need i need them i don't need villagers
for the fishing doctor fishing dog does
it on its own
fishing ship
rebuild fish trap maybe maybe free ships
a four
movie good morning maria
and i don't i don't even need to are
people gonna attack my my fishing port
fishing great for food yeah
um
okay well then you go
and then you guys hmm what'd i do with
you
[Music]
i mean
i guess you could you could build
another watch though but it's not a
waste it's not just your waist
don't stop making villagers
i'll make another one
wait we're at 400 at least 400
foods that's something
a wooden fence should surprise put tower
noodle bridge
okay i i didn't want to necessarily
bring all of these people but
i should no no no no no no
no
[Music]
i want to build the watchtower
no
i can't i don't have it now i don't have
enough stone but now i really need
materials i need to send like my scout
um
you're my scout right
do you want to go somewhere with me
let's go on a trip
it's scouting time
maybe that way
you guys where are you
you guys i guess just go back for now
do the fish traps have to be where the
fish are
no i can't put it put it there okay good
okay
[Music]
this is work
these straps are water forms
nice nice
where's my scout where's my
scout yeah
this is what they were talking about
different english [\h__\h] them this is it
okay
then four
they all come here
all of four comes here
it's the farm but i already built so
many [\h__\h] farms
i'll come over here
and build
a farm
uh
we have some
[Music]
wood here too but oh dear we
cafe
[\h__\h]
okay there they're taking care of them
good good good good good
stone don't go
oh oh dear
can we kill that
you work on that you work on that you
work on that you work on that
you see you like
here
hey
you're like here
great you are
[Music]
you guys chill here
actually i need maybe
yeah i wanted to build a watchtower but
where where is that
no dark she's chilling she's chilling
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
there's not so much going on on the left
side so
you can protect from here okay we may
come
no no no no we make a few more peeps
are you joan of work of course i am
ah i've got no people here um
[Music]
i'm [\h__\h] hell i'm so bad at this
the tutorial was nicer on me
no
i guess i don't need a watch wait no i i
don't need they're going to attack my
[Music]
would they attack my fishing point
i felt like um
[Music]
offense
just want to build a fence
but it only says stonewall and ah that
palestine well that's
that's maybe good
time can i not make like a [\h__\h] ton of
them
that's so weird
i want to build it like
oh i can't
never mind
[Applause]
[Music]
a few of you guys should go back inside
oh maybe a bit more
do i have um
oh i can't since i don't have a castle
age yet i can't do
uh clerics yet huh
where they can go to castles now
[Music]
castle ace let's go
so much food suddenly
go inside
my people go inside
on
your
please
this was not a good idea
um go here
okay um you also
go here
[Music]
you
is there any field that's not being
worked on this one
oh no that looks like someone's working
on them
wait they they didn't leave their stuff
yet actually
wait
me too
okay how's it looking here how's it
looking here
uh
you got one buddy one two-handed
swordsman left to protect this place
uh
okay
you and
you
come down here
and
okay
oh are you
not you're done building well not quite
is that protected oh can they enter they
probably can enter from here
economy isn't fun i would say so too
we're doing the franks yes
this ship ain't doing [\h__\h]
research gill nets
okay
how's it going here um
preferably
someone needs to build
a mining camp
because i don't see one here
and i'm curious what's over here is
there something else hidden from me
gill nets research complete
oh wait now we're in cass lights we want
to build um like a church thingy
for clerics
oh oh would you look at that we can um
use that as a food source as well
is there more of those where those came
from
oh [\h__\h]
well the pig is not doing so bad
against my knight
that's actually kind of ridiculous but
okay can you oh it's gone i finally
could use the meat of the pig
oh the villager has to do it
oh i thought i could like protect
uh
protect them ah i need one more villager
to fix this tower
and
[Music]
no one's working here
already english
i don't even see them
why is it happening
we're fine
okay
nine nine nine okay so now now now now
now
uh research hand cart how about dad
um
[Music]
what was i gonna do oh yeah oh yeah
build
and
a monastery yes
wait is this not a monastery what the
[\h__\h] is this
can i like
it's a cathedral
but i can't i can't like a cathedral i
guess
does not count as a monastery
they're coming they're coming
you mean they're coming no it's they're
always on their way
someone died
i'll put it here
um
[Music]
yo guys
can you please
help
here
[Music]
they left they left okay we have one
once again asserted our dominance
can more than
one person um
work on a building because i see like
usually
only one person can work on the farm
which is kind of annoying
unless i've seen something
uh
wrong
it speeds it up okay okay
so let's create some monsters research
whatever the hell that was again
research fever
box feed yes
[Music]
herbal medicine
oh garrison units heal six times faster
gary songs garry zones can i build
garrisons
gary sons gary suns can i build garry's
songs upgrade to longswords man upgrade
to pikeman
research squires
infantry do more damage
i said yes let's go
water where's my water whoosh
what
foot soldiers in towers and castles
garrison is when you put units in towers
and castles ah yeah i learned that in
the tutorial
ah
i was thinking of for some reason now i
was thinking
of the the
cart where we had a joan inside
oh well yeah now we need gold huh
is this the only piece of gold on this
map
do we have no choice
i mean at least it's like you know here
where
we have friendly people i mean they also
seem pretty safe down there
let's send some people there and see how
it goes
yeah you could trade food for gold ah
okay
that i can do that sounds like a good
and relatively safe idea um
okay
sell 100 food
yeah
wait how does this work again
ah there you go
oh
wait that's so easy
okay never mind we're not gonna farm any
gold
[Music]
h
sure why not whatever that means
are you guys done here
uh
question anyone here who needs healing
go here and they shall heal
hey
cafe
okay
oh you know what i'll send one monk over
here oh [\h__\h] wait oops i pushed the
wrong [\h__\h]
no no no no not you guys no no no no no
no
no you guys just work you guys work work
no no
i need more defense over here
but earlier finally cleared everything
um i will send a monk did i is he on his
way
i can't see
i don't think so okay
okay one of you
[Music]
protect this camp please
and
uh
anyone who's not working
not the ships
oh what do i do with the trade card now
um do i send it to
here
how does this work
[Music]
oh yeah it's gonna go now
oh
oh um i hope you don't die on your way
[Music]
that was a friendly market right
seven
oh they're they're building more and
more they're gone when can we go they're
building more and more of an army
um
[Music]
protective route to it okay that's not
gonna happen i'm pretty sure that's not
gonna happen
oh no oh no no they can't no
they killed my oh my oh no i'm not gonna
make it in time where are we people oh
they're all just chilling here having a
[\h__\h] party
my god
they're all just having a [\h__\h] party
drinking some alien [\h__\h] they're gonna
kill all my villagers
cause everybody's [\h__\h] slow as [\h__\h]
oh my god oh wait now he's at least
attacking the farm
the stupid farm plot and the stupid
house instead of uh attacking my
villagers which would be such a smarter
thing to do to do permanent damage to me
what what what oh no
okay you know what i should send all of
them
not all of them
i guess i'm sending all of the horses
um you know what this means guys
as it gets stronger
we have to get stronger
i've lost too many people already
cavalry archer beautiful
i'm lacking gold
need to sell more
[Music]
oh god i'm i'm like freaking out upgrade
to light calvary
uh husbandry
scout night
night there you go what's going on here
did we
did we save it
oh yes
they're fine relatively uh
you'll heal when people need it
can you heal the building
no he cannot
[Music]
wouldn't it be so much better if you
were able to build the bill to heal the
building
are we ready to go now i'm guessing we
have to attack this
how much of an army do i have
cafe
[Music]
not even close
research squires whatever
[Music]
i need to make ramps why do i make ramps
i didn't see them
where do i make them
where do i make the rounds
oh my god please stop please stop
okay fine
looking okay
siege
spill
a siege workshop
oh
[Music]
space
it's like right here
um maybe here maybe here
[Music]
max sample
do you perhaps want to
repair something do we need something
repaired no
you can help
if he's not already done by the time
you're there
more cavalry archers i love cavalry
archers
they're the superior way of moving
around
oopsie
[Music]
can i stop to wait am i out of fish
hey what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
where the fish
ah here's some fish
oh thank god
you found them okay good good
good okay
uh
what
the fish traps next to the dog is out of
fish
oh
next to the dog here
here
fish traps make fish
okay
now you can continue
ah okay okay
okay okay okay
uh
cafe
uh you guys you guys you guys you guys
you guys watch tyler
bestie soap
and you
oh can we not repair the farm it's kind
of on fire villa
oh well
do you have a big army
have a good size of an
army oh wait so i built this thing
where is it
where did i fill it
where did i build the thing
what's the thing
where is the siege thing and this this
is it
build a scorpion but we want all of this
right probably we just need more wood
now okay
[Music]
maybe
send more
of these peeps
to the shoe
hey
just need a lot more wood now
yeah yeah yeah
okay
you as well
lots more wood
rams mostly okay
let's see
how many will suffice
for
[Music]
once again i'm not surprised
now leave the woman alone leave the
woman alone for god's sake
oh
oh they are leaving the woman alone wait
wait wait don't don't you dare
you
[Music]
i'll make them aggressive hopefully that
helps oh we have a healer and there's
that it was so smart to bring a monk
it was so smart
is there any way to select
or like see
all of the army that i created
because i have some badges but like i
have way more now and i would need a
like
box can convert oh yeah right
no
oh
that's probably wrong because of the
keyboard
which one
which one is that
click the sunset
sunset
shift ctrl play ah shift
shift comma is the way to do it
okay
and
wait wow we have we have
in total
thanks chad yeah thank you
[Music]
so pretty itself in english it's a
pretty decent
amount of army i think
no gold again
we can afford to sell some
maybe
[Music]
even oh wait [\h__\h] no i sold wood i
wanted to sell i wanted to buy wood oh
[\h__\h]
okay well we'll get it back we'll get it
back
you can put units and rams mm-hmm
i just need 160 freaking oh wait now
it's building up they have
finally gotten to work wait no what
where
hmm
you got nothing to do you might as well
go grab someone
faster
94 why is it so slow
research search for gold mine you think
there's one somewhere
i need it to be close by
pray
that needs fixing
this feels a little bit like sims yeah
it does
am i ready now can i build it now yes
back to ring rum one
okay
oh [\h__\h] no no no no what
[Music]
let's gather here i guess
but where did that one ram just go
other now it's finished one round how
many do we want
i forgot if you guys said something i'm
just gonna build
a couple
a couple five more
three four to five okay
okay okay okay okay
okay
you guys
you guys go here because i'm scared of
being attacked
right a couple of you guys go there too
[Music]
army wise do you think i'm ready besides
the rams not being ready
[Music]
more nights
uh nights
good idea i like nights like me some
nights
are you norfolk in english
ah it's fine it's fine
work faster
[Music]
faster please
can then like upgrade this ah research
goal oh
oh stop 15
oh
research double oh
i did never do in the tutorial nice
bosa
20 wood chopping speed
[Music]
all good here
sheesh
[Music]
and then last one we want is chain
boarding aub
hmm
maybe
buy wood for gold i don't know if it's a
weapon at least at least
wood is something we can still easily
acquire here so i'm not gonna waste
my gold on that now
hold mine
and
i mean i saw this but
that would that would mean that we need
a gold mine here and i don't i don't see
one
unless maybe there's one here i don't
know
i can check it out
no
no just more oh hello
let's kill you
[Music]
isn't that a beautiful sound
yeah no i don't i don't think there's
any gold close by
unfortunately
oh [\h__\h] my farms
they're restating right it's fine
okay you
[Music]
help
oh oh us done with the fish again
[Music]
i'm busy
uh rams
one two three okay then we should have
like five or or six even that's that's
enough right
oh there we go found some fish in the
sea
[Music]
really far away
maybe you'll find some more
explore
[Music]
battering ram
created yes i'm still in chapter 2
it's an rts it can't be dead fast
it's it's real time you know
it takes some time
[Music]
yeah but now i think wait besides one
more thing that we can research
um
here oh i need gold
so
these games take time i want to do it
proper
of course i've heard of starcraft before
never played starcraft though
i played like some rts games when i was
younger i think like this
not much but you know as a child i just
kind of like dabbled
deeply dabbled a little bit this time
they have no work anymore there's no
more stone
well then we better go and kill the
burgundians and so on now
oh hello oh dear
[Music]
can we go now
uh we have now
let me see
i'll build i'll build i will build
well i can't oh i will build
anything else we need so i wonder
kevlar archer
skirmisher crossbowman
high command swordsman pacman swordsman
first man prize man
and gather them
here
you guys
okay over here you guys over here
by the way yeah we're gonna i'm gonna
save
ah
you think you think you have enough i
think
yes
[Music]
honestly a scorpion sounds fun
let's make one i don't know what exactly
it is
are we're safe before attacking yeah
the new you buddies also come here
and what was it
okay
48.
you can't tell me out i can't win with
that
elite screaming [\h__\h] elite scream you
should know let's scrimmage [\h__\h]
skirmish overkill
[Music]
we're gonna go now no more time to waste
when i save i'll save one more time
[Laughter]
[Music]
to where we go
okay
um just one question we they want us to
kill this this
this castle right this is a castle let's
go let's [\h__\h] go all of ya
all of you yeah yeah this doesn't
include my
normal workers right come come come come
come everybody come
yeah wait maybe maybe once gather here
don't go too crazy yet
[Music]
kill the red cat that oh that was uh
oh wait
hmm it's a yellow castle
oh where are the
or maybe up there because they keep on
coming from there oh yeah yeah
okay
indeed indeed then we go up there we
shall go okay
56 of us
my people are a little bit dorky they
don't know quite what they're doing
they're a little bit confused but they
got the spirit this will probably all
burn down while i'm trying to kill the
english but that's fine
it's fine they're so slow
wait why are these horses just walking
so they stay together or what
we're gonna go aggressive stance
kill them kill them all with fire
oh they're saying information okay
[Music]
oh god that's fine that's that's fine i
guess yeah
what are you doing what what are you
doing
oh now you're facing an army
okay
oh they're not they don't even care
about him
oh it's because i'm [\h__\h] monsters and
stuff wait a second chill guys chill can
i look um is there something else else i
can research
converted units
die
what
a thousand
[Music]
nothing i can make to make them faster
oh well
oh don't waste your time on that don't
don't don't even don't don't don't don't
don't don't no don't waste your time on
that
walk faster towards the goal
okay so
so far
it's still doing fine
okay wait you are you're not doing
anything
you build a farm
buoy
you know also build build a freaking
farm bestie soap
there we go
[Music]
[Applause]
let's look at the number we already lost
two units i think
where
wait where where the rams
where am i [\h__\h]
what
where are they
miss ramp
rounds
by the mop
huh i don't see them am i blind
i sent them here
what the [\h__\h] are they doing they look
like houses
oh
come on you [\h__\h] idiots you had one
job
you had one job
no you had one job done
huh
what stopped you
what stopped you from coming to help me
this is going to be a disaster now
pull back retreat oh the scorpion came
of course the scorpion came
falling back
oh god
where the [\h__\h] are my monks
okay
it's not okay
it's not okay did my monks die
but like i always selected them as a
group
and told them to go there why did that
not include them my i think monks i know
here monk
are you healing
[Music]
okay they're just having fun until they
arrive nice
can you like work on this now please you
gotta chill the [\h__\h] out
oh my god
ah unit scary song okay um you
you like go in there
cafe
can it be any of them
[Music]
right
man
[Music]
i mean them being faster now probably
doesn't do [\h__\h] oh god
for everyone except these [\h__\h]
chill
[Music]
because they're aggressive but i want to
kind of keep them aggressive oh well
yeah yeah do it do it do it
go in
you are all such [\h__\h] idiots
[Laughter]
wonks really only heal anything that's
within one meter of them huh
oh my god
okay i think we're like pretty much
ready it's going great
almost almost
oh wait they are already in what the
[\h__\h] are you guys doing
oh they're okay
i guess we're in but how did they get in
oh they just entered when the door was
open
we're not done we're not done
oh we are done we are done
don't lose your way
[Music]
monks are gonna die
huh
do something
what are you
[Music]
doing we're done
they have the roof to attack yeah
[Music]
everyone chill
okay i'll go get
[Applause]
france belongs to england now never
forget that what do you mean
wait what
why why do we belong to england
no no no no we just won we killed an
english castle
[Music]
[Applause]
we won we won
we won
this is salty yeah
oh man this
took me so long
carry she wasn't wounded she was always
at full hp
was free
the entire population cheered us on for
windows
so actually the only piece of history
that i know
that i've consumed
of
um jean duck i think is
um
[Music]
a cute musical
uh that i've watched in tokyo
performed by
none other than my favorite hello
project idols
from uh betty's cobalt
cute smileage and so on
they actually
had like a musical future musical thing
in tokyo many years ago where they
several times performed this and
actually it was really cool i did not
know what was going on at the time but
yeah they were singing and dancing
and i remember them yelling out la
priscilla la purcell actually let me let
me look something like that uh um
actually some songs were so pretty
how do i find it that's not that's not
how i find it
that is
oh yes
[Music]
don't play it i just want to send it to
you guys so you guys can watch it
it was smiling to make this cold but
yeah my favorite idol groups
where that one uh
give it a
quick
listen
yeah should i should i pin it for you
guys
they had like two different groups that
performed different
in different combinations of idols
there's mama t
we've heard twin tails she stands out so
much but they're saying that we are john
we're done
oh my favorite isako is
there with the short hair it's a wig
though
it's so long ago
yeah okay you guys watch that okay um
i'll continue playing
[Laughter]
it
[Music]
on
homework after watching you okay okay
nearly a decade ago yeah
it to be like that
i think i wonder it was their dvd with
the full musical because i want to
re-watch it
that's not period-appropriate clothes
well you know
it's it was a cheap production i think
very cheap it's more about the cute
idols
only oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh get muted oops ah
there's
he drives man on with curses and fists
there will be plenty of english necks
for leia to break
a taste the gateway to the loire river
valley the english hotel in a grip of
steel was the huge army and the sergeant
fast of devastates the countryside
john leads us to pate to capture the
english castles however we must avoid
fast of sami until we are strong enough
to face it yeah that will take me about
five years please wait
[Laughter]
all right
you guys ready for more chaos
and
boring building of my army that will
take five years
[Music]
john must survive destroy free of the
four english castles oh dear okay
and time is still confined to the castle
age and the population
make sure you have ample siege weapons
before salting the english castles okay
okay
the area across the river and to the
east should have plenty of resources
with which to establish a crown a town
east
across the river and to the east
okay austin
scott's report the french army on the
joan of arc has reached the lower river
to take the region back from the english
the english are in control of many
castles in the lower valley although
they will not be very aggressive their
army is not to be trifled with the
burgundians the [\h__\h] are the closest
to the river and will quickly field an
army of infantry
it may be a good idea to deal with them
early
uh-huh
okay purple first
the english are general the english
general faustov is said to leave the
english army orange be on your guard as
he is said to make use of heavy calvary
units
okay i'm scared
scared
rush northeast kill fest off his base
has decent resources and easy to defend
really focus on one at a time you could
you tell me to go to festool first
but the game tells me to go to
burgundians first
could you read it all out in the french
accent i don't know if i can
the french orbee under jean of oak i
don't know
has has reached the lord river
to take
the region back from
english sounds like a mix of german and
french
[Laughter]
okay who wants me to go to the festival
first and who wants the burgundy and say
purple or say orange
purple orange purple orange tell me
purple
green orange orange purple purple orange
purple orange purple
[Music]
yeah we'll go wiggle purple first sounds
more reasonable
um hello
i'm scared let me look first okay
where did we go first
cafe cafe
we shall do so yeah
la hill wishes to kill something
[Laughter]
lahia wishes to kill something and chill
the [\h__\h] out you will kill plenty of
people
but first you have to uh we have to
strategize you know and build a bigger
army we're too small at the moment
you're good guys
go in
it's a
boat nice boat nice boat
[Applause]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] off
no no no no isn't it
where the [\h__\h] did he come from
they
have no time to chill huh
over the river and east they say how
much east though
wait wait wait can i look at my the
notes again where where did where the
ear
okay area crosstalk
establish my town are we building from
scratch
uh
the blood only sword is almost dry i had
to
get out of there again got it
huh
i'm garrison there we go
oh sorry ships you guys um i don't need
you anymore
yeah you guys you guys can chill there i
guess
gold oil
hmm
we're built from the start now okay well
i see gold
oh wait let me let me you guys can you
guys just chill lex chillax here for a
second should i build here
should i just
sorry yeah this doesn't seem most ideal
let me see
oh
yeah yeah
okay
the burgundies are there okay but here
we can have fish
fish gold woods where's stone
here's some berries
i just need stone
ah stone is some some stone is here
shall we go over that river too
[Music]
wait that's difficult oh yeah
what the [\h__\h] wait now i'm confused
should i build here or should i go
around the water and build a little more
here even more east
i think even more east is safe
cafe
holy [\h__\h]
instant kill
uh
okay
practical retreat that area did not seem
safe
wait
no no
uh please ignore us
kindly why are you guys not in the
[\h__\h] ship
that's all get into the other ship then
bonjour
[Music]
you gotta be so complicated
oh thank god they did not uh attack me
just now
okay what about here please tell me this
is good
[Music]
where is my
okay i'll just unload everything
oh
scout cavalry go go
what do we have
just some wood gold
yes
sheep
yup
[Music]
yeah she found
stone okay i think this area is good so
we build it right here
okay um
this
this feels like the place that the game
intended me to use
villager
let's build
a town center
cafe another one
build a house
wait can i not build a house until i
have a town center
i'll build a farm dog
warship nice
oh oh oh oh oh okay uh red red
is it good that we're so close to them
but you just have to be fast and kill uh
and build some some walls i guess
more sheep
sushi plus what do you mean
that is that is dangerously close um
move my sheep
oh i can move them
oh what
oh
they turned blue for me
what just happened wha what the [\h__\h]
just happened
what's going on
oh you know what you should better help
that we make this
we finish this faster
come on come on
my both attacked the enemy ship no
my boat blew up the red chip what
nice
okay nice okay
so far
so good uh you keep on doing that and
now
we create villagers oh we need to build
a house
i like starting from scratch because
then at least i know where i put
everything
build the house
[Music]
at least the map ends here so i can
safely build some stuff there i think
well let my sheep do the scouting i
wonder if that works properly huh
okay we need houses enough houses for
the people currently we have
um
only so many houses that we can afford
having
15 people
obviously not enough because then now we
can't uh we can't create more
holy [\h__\h] we can't create more
villagers and so on
we can't create more
you know what you guys you guys chill
here
some of you guys chill here
i'm gonna do this right
high command too okay just have them at
the edges where something might attack
us for now
cafe okay you build another house
you also build a house
buster store
you can set the scout so that he roams
what
where is my where's my scout currently
thank you
oh should we build a couple more
are you guys able to deal with that dude
[Music]
yeah they're gonna be fine
okay
you guys go back here
you guys you're gonna be back here
now
can we build a
watchtower
maybe here
bestie soap
actually i need stone
[\h__\h] a stone
stone
and one more you build
you build
a mining cow
here
this i don't like this we will have to
destroy that
can we like already just right now
do it
um
[Music]
there's only two there no problem
uh
a lumber count
on the count
cafe build
uh wait what uh
gold camp not the end wait gold camping
oh my god
they do be dying there though
oh but we took it down yeah they won't
be watching us no more
okay okay okay
now
let's build some villagers
research that [\h__\h]
build as many as possible
and
we
you
build another house
okay how are we doing so far
we need someone in the watchtower right
right oh yeah
really
no
does the watchtower work on its own
okay
okay we need some more wood so let's
help you sure
it will shoot automatically okay cool
nice
okay
you helped us
too
okay okay okay
some city building places yeah i like it
to be organized
can you build you're just a house
builder keep on building we need to be
more and more and more and more great
you can help
scout oh he's chilling he's chilling
good job or oh i thought he would be
dead by now
oh
continue you saw everything you needed
to see
i'm being attacked with the scout door
ah yeah let's go okay okay
no need to worry
i think
okay okay you
um
should we build walls
you might want to help with the stone
though
uh also
fishing
fishing dock oh need some more wood
i need some more farms
okay
this is fun this is fun
my favorite way to be playing one of my
favorite games nice i'm happy for you
great i'm happy for you
another watch tower
[Music]
this will last forever i'll need more
well there ain't [\h__\h] around here
let me see they said
we're so close to red but we will have
to attack purple first
purple
had a watchtower here but i don't know
where they actually are
maybe maybe in this corner no wait it
probably said so it said where they are
probably
closest to the river will quickly fill
an army of infantry it may be a good
idea to deal with them early closest to
the river
didn't say anywhere exactly though right
oh well
is sound much good
wait are we capped to castle h
did is that what they said
confined
what we can't even advance if we wanted
to
we were already castle h in in the
previous thing that makes no sense
logically thinking
um
[Music]
rusty soap
oh dear okay okay
then we can't have monks
oh man
okay
[Music]
oh dear
rusty so
yeah monks are castles that's what i'm
saying yeah
we are in the feudal age right
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay
well
um
oh dear is that ever gonna like shoot us
directly from the water
hope not
i can't get food in castle age okay
so i can't get to cos ledge okay cause i
was just wondering it doesn't tell me
how many materials i need
[Music]
no okay kill him kill him i changed my
mind
is that a scout
what what are they doing why are they so
stupid
[Music]
why are they so stupid
i wanna build my dog please i can't
why not
[Music]
why does it
does it why does that work move the
boats
okay
it doesn't work here
i want dark stucco
i'm trying to make it half of water
hopping land but it doesn't
it doesn't work
it was a valid spot really
can't i can't i can't
oh ah here
besties
[Music]
maybe it may be better to build garrison
because i don't i'm gonna run out of
i'm gonna run out of um stones now
unless when i have traders hmm
what do you think stonewood use what
i agree
what's yummy what are you eating where
the sheep where am i where are my sheep
did they kill my sheep
[Music]
oh dear oh oh no don't attack the ship
you idiots
you [\h__\h] idiots
why did the ship disappear
they're lucky to have ship stereo
okay uh continue making more people
and
okay who's got nowhere
you wow you're so fast with that damn
feeling that is great not as slow as i
thought it would be
who the [\h__\h] died
i guess i guess that works so
we don't need to go past that point
okay
then a little bit more here i think
[Music]
okay looks good looks good
and cheese can start gathering the fish
down yay
i think it's my
scout dead
i think he's dead
map is looking the same oh what are you
doing
why are you even there
my god
oh here
so aggressive
[Music]
okay
build gate
guess i guess we're building it here i
mean huh
can i just replace it
and replace this let's see so
i guess
eyes it's not really smart on the to do
it on the water is it
use the wood gate oh
well it's gonna be stronger you'll use
wait i almost want to cancel it is it
fine okay because i feel like the the
ship will go by and shoot through the
gate
hey
[Music]
cafe
can i just connect it to the wood i hope
musty still i think that should be
protected properly okay now you go back
oh you can't
how are you gonna go inside through the
wood
[\h__\h] she doesn't know
walk through here
be hot go here go here
and uh
[Music]
yeah now let's see what else we can do
a market
a good space here
yeah yeah yeah so far
new farm
you have to destroy free i know
just don't stress me out i have to build
an army
i also have to build
the barracks it's about [\h__\h] time um
let's build the barracks close to the
gate
wait
build
archery
do you think you'll be able to beat
other young members i don't know but it
actually sounds like fun but then we
would have to convince everyone to play
why did they open
where the [\h__\h] did they why why the
gates open go away
[\h__\h] we keep on letting people in how's
that possible
and we would have to convince
um ian to start playing this i saw you
know id playing it and that moon i
wanted to
[Music]
um
i wanted to
do some kind of
tournament
so i wanted to
[Music]
oh
can i build like a double wall
is it time to take down burgundy
this is freaking me out
um
free english again
i'm gonna build another wall
oh oh no
no we're fine
we're fine um
i think we're fine
we're fine we're fine we're gonna we're
gonna we're gonna we're gonna we're
gonna we're gonna build the stables soon
soon soon
take more wood
need more and more wood
okay everybody
get the wood
wait
on the farm oh my you know what never
mind how about not a farm but this
[Music]
no it's a transport ship uh did i have
like some kind of
military ship no
no
stop it where where are my good ships
[Music]
no
i have to protect myself
what's a
of these are ships to attack people with
right
a war gallery galley is this a war
galley
galley okay it didn't say war galleys i
wasn't sure
upgrade to war galley
and demolition ships
um
ah they walk such a weird path no
way
repair it repair it while they're
attacking it
yes we can we can work against it
ah
800 meats 800 meats
800 oh we're almost there we're almost
at castle age okay
[Music]
when when the farms look like this do
they
do do i just build another one on top
what is this thing about reese's seating
what's better
no water controls best water control
oh
um
[Music]
i might
oh
did they stop no they didn't oh but
wait
can this ship attack
[Music]
cafe
i'm not sure if it will be really uh
effective
oh oh
oh
our train
tactical retreat for a second oh it's
coming closer though
i'll get it done eventually
[Music]
what was i doing
what am i doing
oh
god these people are so stupid
he's not the watchtower isn't even
hitting them
you guys also always just have these
randoms running around
not doing what you want them to do
or it's just me
i need this i need this
okay
focus on good everybody
[Music]
[\h__\h]
but the dock is standing its ground it's
doing quite well
you have them stand their ground
[Music]
but i'm not sure like even when they
stand their ground and they just like
attack the walls and
then i have to send them out to i always
have to micromanage to
actually get them to do [\h__\h] so i'd
prefer to always have them regress on
aggressive so they automatically right
away attack them enough
maybe i should have just not built
anything in the water um because it's
kind of a waste of resources huh
to keep on trying to defend myself here
on the water well if i had nothing on
the water they would just like mind
their own business
[Music]
they might bring the third ship
[Laughter]
please no
okay i'm gonna ignore them um sorry guys
you gotta die
just don't get
hit oh
oh that that one just went five oh it's
just chilly
oh
interesting
what was i doing
it was free of them but they didn't
necessarily come to help it seems
wait how come i
200 gold oh oh oh oh
wait we have gold right here
did i never
why did i
why did i not um
cafe
hey
[Music]
mining camp does that work on the gold
mine too
are they gonna bring it over there
or if i just build another mining camp
they'll bring it there right
i forgot about it yeah i think so too
[Music]
foreign
besides that everything seems fine i
just don't want them to
kill all the trees so that we don't have
any
any trees left at all i use
oh i thought it was like a horse there a
knight but it's just a
flag
okay
oui
okay we make one more
uh what was i gonna
what's it gonna do oh
[Music]
i'm so proud the other ship is dead too
how the [\h__\h] did we do that
wow
actually impressed we got him
so bad
you could close it on air
wow
um did i build a blacksmith
i don't think i did
that's uh
horsey
what that scooped an eye on that corner
yes i did
oh yes i did like how do i cancel how do
i cancel how do i cancel
can i cancel
i didn't see it
delete
no
click and delete
okay thank you that worked it was i was
just paused okay
actually maybe you guys stopped working
on the wood there and start working on
the wood there
oh
yes uh it probably worked better because
my arches were standing right there
and they don't even stop to fight with
me no creatures
they just go on a little a little trip
research forging research scale mail
research fletching research
kind of
research
skill whatever
[Music]
let's go let's go
right
you want to fight you want to fight you
want to fight
you sure
that one's kind of stuck let's get him
he's good
let's
[Music]
uh upgrade galley
i can't yet i need a bit more
more food
burgundy 14 research complete
why did i tell me that that makes me
nervous
is that bad
yeah
so oh that that's what they meant
they're just um chilling there oh dear
um cafe army
a bit faster
just a little bit faster
[Music]
did anyone important die right do we
still have the important people yeah
yeah okay okay
okay
um
[Music]
okay okay i have too much wood
more farm
let's see no uh
what exactly does the mill do again
besides
them being able to bring the food there
i'm not gonna build a trade card i think
because i don't know where where i would
send it now
who's that okay
castle h
cavalry archer
reach research squires
okay we need um now now now we are gonna
sell some wood
it's always good to have extra supplies
guys
always good
but as i told you we ran out of a normal
stone
oh there is gold right that's gold
ran out of normal [\h__\h] stone
my stone for the castle
yeah okay uh
that costs a lot though
900 how much do i even need
i can already build it
all right
[Music]
i'll i'll build it just here i guess
you guys thank you so sweet
you know they over there on the on the
lake on the river they're just playing
their own little game you know
they're just having fun
oh wait those are those are fishing
ships oh i thought my galas are gone oh
my galley's dead
[Music]
oh my galleys are dead
oh wow that's okay
that's fine
now we want to also build a
church can we
monastery yeah
you help as well
castle belt
school i never built a school before
university
what does that do is it's okay if i just
build here besties so it's not easily
reachable but
why must they always chop that one they
should chop this one you should
[Music]
be sure
some some meat okay
but just in case that bestie soap we
can't fish anymore
oh yeah
now let's see can we upgrade upgrade to
the long swordsman upgrade to pikeman
[Music]
upgrade to elite skirmisher upgrade to
cro crossbowmen
okay
university build so what does that do
research
murder holes
what
masonry
fortified wall guard tower ballistics
was that worth it do i need all of this
make monk convert the ship
can i convert ships
ballistic
masonry
okay i'll wait for this i'll wait for it
[Music]
oh god
did you search that thought away let's
see can we
oh yeah
right click the converted ship to
control and is it that easy
is he gonna like go outside he can't do
it from there can he where is he
oh is he gonna try
i still can't uh
all right i guess i continue trying to
defend myself here
oh
wait wait where's my mom going to go
ah he's gonna walk all the way around
no how about you just enter this ship
go to the other side
oh dear
you're free why don't you do it
[Music]
is he in the ship
yes
okay
so if we break but won't he be like
one-shotted to death
i'm scared did you did you unload him
cave
[Music]
we need to do this in a different way
oh i'm going to work ellie
nice nice guys can we hold can we
continue holding
i almost had it really empty does it not
take so long
wait okay if it doesn't take so long
um
[Music]
a new monk please
more monks
need more monks
[Music]
oh man
more galley research
uh build war galley
are we like focusing too much on this
[Music]
what about burgundians what are we gonna
do about them
[Music]
are they still fighting okay they're
done right
oh yeah
okay
oh wait never mind
is that scout
mom complained now we will send one monk
here
oh there you go
and he will heal
oh
is that my walk alley no or this kill
someone stand anywhere no wait not kill
don't kill because then we can't
[Music]
then we can't convert it but my dock is
on fire
ship to distract
just kayla okay
can the monk heal a ship or does it need
to be repaired
[Music]
well in another case we'll have a
cafe some people uh right here the dock
oh and yeah they have to repair
good good good
okay now anyway um
[Music]
we wanted to research something here
ballistics
[Music]
okay and now we also have to focus a bit
more
on my army
okay
okay okay
ah seats workshop
[Music]
seats workshop
uh
okay
i think that's pretty much the last
thing we will need
bestie soap i'll build it here
for the wraps for the rams yes
[Music]
gold gold
okay
[Music]
oh
done
[Music]
um
after kill first castle orange would
sell an army of scary cavalry towards my
base so build your defense up first oh
so i should leave some here anyway i
have to
orange will send an army okay um but
before we kill english castles
uh the burgundy don't count as english
right so we have to first uh
i'll build another scout because i have
to find the burgundy base
uh scalp
scout cavalry
my walls are
perhaps not the best yes
oh no did i tell you to kill him that's
not what i meant
oh it's your repair seahawks
[Music]
okay there's a lot of people there i
have to do it
archery
in the tower
crossbow man okay
hold down garrison hold down out and
right click
those are purple no
where's this
sculpture that i just built
[Music]
scout
um
and find him
where the [\h__\h] is this girl does he not
count as army
wouldn't he spawn here
oh wait is this you that's a cavalry
archer
use defense zone
um
you mean
[Music]
defensive stance
wow my scalp is now a live cavalry
oh
oh okay
which one which one
it's it's kind of hard to find the right
thing
here light cavalry
um
where could they be
it didn't say which direction right
top left
red
look at an achievement
out of their element oh i think i found
them
or they died is this just a little
outpost oh oh that i found them
okay
[Music]
back we go
everything fine here
yeah
oh why are you standing here
um
where would i build the the
rams thing again
more wood
nice yeah take it down yo yo yeah
we are weakening the english army as we
speak everybody
let me let me take one more look at the
hints
and besiege weapons
[Music]
should have plenty of yup yup
and controllers
not very aggressive they keep on
attacking me
i'm closer to the river and will quickly
feel an army of infantry maybe without
you
okay okay
[Music]
oh yeah take this one down too
yeah yeah to keep going
so what do you recommend me what else i
need i have
uh
people in my army now
making some more rams if possible
more rams just nights and rams
wait nights nice
[Music]
nice night's nights
what about these axeman and the
petard p card
are they worth it
one more ram now i should have like
three rams
what are they doing
shooting bomb
suicidal sequence wow okay
[Music]
x-men good okay i made like one or two
oh yeah
training towards the next area too much
kind of i guess yeah
so so we want some people to be in there
right so for example
wait which one did i eat yeah there's
one in there right
and there's one in there yeah i'm going
to put one in there maybe not the crust
what are you what are you what are you
doing
skirmisher
[Music]
oh archery units aren't as good oh [\h__\h]
well
um
[Music]
kind of ready
41 now
and i keep on taking that [\h__\h] we'll see
how your knights fare against english
longbows yeah
but you guys did say i should keep some
for defense
so
let's have
a defense squad and a
a fighting squad um
right you guys go here how about that
your friends go here
[Music]
you guys come here this is fighting
squad these are
oh yeah
you can go here
how many would i need
two nights
yes why not
not good
go full force
[Music]
no you guys just stay here that's fine
yeah yeah john of course john will
survive yes yes yes
cave are you we make one more monk
one will stay one will come
with me
maybe should we take no that makes no
sense because we have to go over here
safe before attacking you know what i'll
save right now
yes
put john on the cat ow
i didn't quite realize i could do that
john okay
the other dude know right and he can in
theory die
this one why is he not even on the horse
he needs a horse
build wall this this is a ball
ball this is a wall
oh but oh dear
destroy my
my
my my my
my my farming wall
okay then we have to build a proper wall
uh
wait
[Music]
i keep on building
what was the problem with having
uh
of having nights to protect the
city lock their gate with your wall
this one
i should build a wall there
okay
[Music]
english
oh here
[Music]
is he gonna walk all the way around
there to build that stupid
ah
ew
[Music]
why can't you just build it from outside
look from inside i guess
what a dummy here
[Music]
they're just gonna village
but he's relatively fast he's almost
there
would block his way yeah
i could just walk up i mean now now it
probably wouldn't even block it
now the trees are completely gone
okay
okay okay i think it's time to move
but i have to make up my mind with how
many people i'm gonna leave
here okay yeah cafe
we can um
out
send one of these dudes in here
and one of them in here
maybe build one more
of those
towers
another watchtower um
most of the time they kind of come from
here
you guys
are 19.
a couple more
and i guess two
[Music]
leave it
just trying to find all my people but i
think wait
that's pretty much it uh they're done
here too
okay
go back to get some wood
don't die while you're at it
okay
these people these people are one team
we make them
oh this is right again
yeah defense team seven
apparently
and these ones
well does that add up
7 and 27
great
i should have 48.
oh these ones too cafe libre
this one
okay
44 plus
seven
seems about right some someone's missing
though
some
oh
oh hey cafe no
ah ah the ones who are inside there's uh
jean john is inside
i'm house capped oh yeah
okay yeah
build house
probably gonna lose plenty of people
anyway but yeah oh and then i guess i
have some of them inside the towers
yeah okay
like one each
okay okay team
oopsie
yeah sure why not save
team
team two
um
[Music]
are we gonna have another disaster with
the rams who knows who knows
wait what are you gonna do hmm what do
we do with you guys more more wood
chopping more wood chopping
no lazing around more wood chop chop
chopped up
[Music]
keep making military
okay
[Music]
okay okay
should i send them also the same way
you need more houses
cccc
oh hey
oh [\h__\h] what did i do
[Music]
leave it
shift clip back to build multiple times
oh cute buildings oh
mercy
[Music]
cafe
oh i did it wrong
oh well i don't need so many i think
it's fine
okay can you guys not
attack
everything you see just let me go for
the castle right if they have a castle
they don't even have walls why am i
bringing my rams
why am i bringing my rams
those are for the english no
maybe maybe they have a castle i can i
can destroy the castle with the rams
town hall town hall okay okay
mental support yes
hello just visiting um you don't by any
chance wanna join
the french people
now is your last chance
if i see anything else to attack i'm
gonna send another ram
[Music]
what's shooting me
oh they have something funny here
is that is that no that's not it oh god
no wait oh oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
we killed the thing that hurt me really
badly
um
they got catapults and what
they told me to be careful
[Music]
you work on
that didn't see another k is this is
this that's town center i'm so stupid
attack where are their armies
[Music]
you're such an idiot
you're such an idiot everybody's here
these are all idiots
[Music]
at least he's not losing hbm
wait
how's it going
everything cool yeah they're cool
they're cool they're cool they're cool
i'm not even gonna send reinforcements i
think
i think they're fine
they're gonna make it we're just gonna
have a lot of casualties
right
oops
right you guys are fine
[Music]
you're not gonna rebuild it right
uh should we just go back are we done
here
can they rebuild it
i guess we're not done we're going to
continue this oh [\h__\h]
they can rebuild oh
and we better kill everything
[Music]
i'm being attacked really yeah
let's do aggressive stance let's destroy
everything
power which power oh that
one dad
okay
[Music]
where did you hear that something was
going on here that was supposed to be a
secret
they left i think they were scared of me
i'm asserting dominance
[Music]
okay okay
now is it really work attacking the
farmland
this is all they have
diet farm style diet grass diet
[Music]
we can attack this thing
we might have rebuilt something in the
north
so scared
that's red territory
i'll go
i i'm completely out of gold what the
[\h__\h]
but here everything is in control at
least that's good
and we have a [\h__\h] ton of food that's
great as well
okay okay
recreating my army
uh where is that dude oh
are you having fun there no
that's the top of the map i think
it's fine
[Music]
okay
really you want me to farm the gold here
gold gets expensive
oh all right all right
cafe
charlotte i built a gold mine here as
well
but then we even have something in
between actually there's some stone
[Music]
i guess not
okay then we'll build
a mining cap
here
so
okay
just don't forget about them remind me
that they exist
yeah i feel like they were
closer spots but oh well oh wait there's
more here too okay that's good that's
good once we're done with that little
um space of gold then we can continue we
can continue here now
do we retreat once now is it good
do we keep some people here maybe even
maybe
right
that makes no sense you stay here
you stay here
and you stay here
and the rest
um
yeah the rest you guys would go back
[Music]
we go all the way back
you guys go here to heal them
and then we attack the english castles
meanwhile
meanwhile meanwhile
of course
[Music]
never enough
okay
is that's all we have left of people
you're afraid
wow
okay we lost
we lost a lot of them
kind of sad but oh
oh he's following us
yeah
the gal is
the kelly's are the mvp
of this play friends
[Music]
right now
okay so we go here to get some healing
now where are
the farmers ah they're already on it
they're so fast right like you guys stay
you guys are supposed to stay you guys
are gonna be
uh
here protection group
maybe i even send
a few more
[Music]
they're all busy let's see
what are we not lacking food
you too
help with
[Music]
oh i'm not good to protect okay leave it
okie dokie
i'm getting healing
or what
seems like they were totally fine as
well
this is the protection unit
okay
are we all together
40 people now
40 people
oh
41.
i will am i ready do i need more
what do you think guys 41 plus my
my cute
rams
that's probably not enough
probably not enough
a few more rams
oh god i'm dizzy oh god
x-men
[Music]
also tomorrow 12 hour marathon don't
forget we're gonna start early you don't
have to be there from the beginning of
course of course i know it's that would
be
a lot
um but yeah
we're gonna have a lot of fun i uploaded
the schedule
yesterday evening
in case you didn't see it
uh we even have collabs
one with id members and one with
some
english live english members
what about cavalry archer
hell yeah
oh no i'm actually back to 90.
[Music]
i need to build more houses that makes
sense that makes sense
and playing some games i haven't played
before like actually only one maybe the
um
what was it oink games
seems like
uh
jackpots
but with board games
pretty much
okay
um
i think it looked fun so and i wanted to
try something new because i figured you
guys
want to see something new as well
could be wrong but you know
what was i doing
what was
wait what happened with
what happened with the wall i supposedly
built
on it
was it destroyed
okay
what the [\h__\h] didn't i built ah no they
just i didn't build it all around it i
thought it i did but it didn't build it
in between
what
[Music]
free english
where
oh all the ship
yeah the forest
and now now after i built that wait
it should be fine
okay
back inside why can't you be like him
and build it from the outside hmm
oh they still they still didn't do it
properly
wait girl wait
[Music]
rusty soap
can you just do this correctly
for once
okay
now now she's filling it
i'm going for overkill
that's my goal
caroline archer
[Music]
so
i think i can
search bearded axe
i think i'm
pretty much
done with researching where's my
blacksmith here ooh
get all that
how about now can i go now
frankly your civilization is looking
pretty good there really
thank you i like your jokes
i want to go
upgrades yeah i totally forgot about
those
eliminates the minimum range of volt
tower as customers when they can fire
enemies attacking your base
oh
cool
drinking old buildings by providing
10 more hit points
upgrade your watch towers and lets you
build guard towers which is stronger to
have more textbooks
it's not worth it in this play for it
i'm making you feel young again
noise
that's a good feeling to have
i want to feel young again too
says this eternal phoenix
i think if that's not enough then i
don't know man
i think
[Applause]
how do you feel
the wall is still not complete
they're going through here to collect
the one wait stop guys
stop
rusty so please
endless life time to be young you gotta
continue to die able to
yeah yeah yeah diablo too
i guess that's something that makes me
feel young yeah yeah
all right um we're gonna go here maybe
go in here
is there or is there a good spot
they're like everywhere though
so we have to go for the whole city
wait where are they where exactly are
they going now oh maybe instead here
then
they have to do such a stupid path
um where do we enter
closest to you first the next it means a
good start okay oh i have to walk like a
really weird path though unfortunately
well then i'll i'll enter through maybe
here
ram attack
wait okay everybody stay accept the rest
how about that
it has begun guys
it has begun
just rams please rhymes only
oh there it's right there nice
this is good because otherwise a lot of
my army would be um having trouble now
[Music]
i think there is oh yeah a lumberjack in
here
you
go here
besides that cafe
oh because they walk further with the
wood they're accidentally
joining my army
they have asparagus you know what zombie
jacks are [\h__\h] strong i'm pretty sure
of that
i'm sure they're really [\h__\h] strong
so
in in dire situations i wouldn't mind
them joining my army
can the monk like heal rams please
that one's not doing so well the other
ones are fun
no he can't okay that's fine
we're going in
bank we're going in
[Music]
yes
we also destroyed everything here
i think so
oh you're joining the party welcome
welcome
no problem
[Music]
enough of this
she's in the castle though what you
gonna do what you gonna do huh
what you going to do
what are you going to do
oh oh that is that is that him the scout
cavalry
yeah
well what what's happening here you're
chilling
i come for you
[Music]
where
where trouble do your worst you english
damn you english peeps
don't undermine me i've taken down
everything successfully when it's time
to go back
wait wait the [\h__\h] am i here
although or do we go straight to the
next place
it's right to the next place or we still
have 40 people
we press on
or yeah wait for fast 12 to be dead
maybe and then go for the other two
castles
is
[Music]
gotta fix the rams oh yeah
oh i lost i think i lost one
[Music]
oh how are they doing they're still
alive i'm so proud although where's
those army people
did they die or did they join my other
army somehow
[Music]
yo i have so much food
also i'm here where where is
where's he he said he would come i don't
see him he's slow as [\h__\h]
it's kuruno maternity
oh you have a headache i hope it gets
better
check for burgundy and survivors
i would see them right i don't see any
one of them
[Music]
where
oh
this
why are they not coming to me
am i supposed to fight them there
[Music]
no
it's okay
[Music]
ambush
oh they killed my rams first oh
oh that's fine
that's fine
oh they should come for me now oh let's
go kill them kill those [\h__\h] why
aren't you going around there
oh okay ignore him
[Music]
is that him
it didn't tell me that i killed him
though
cafe
ah
he's that dude okay
[Music]
[Applause]
god curses you
i shall feast on your body no go back oh
should we kill them well if it's worth
it they
move relatively fast somehow
i'm walking after them is kind of mad
the the dude is dead
no need to
really
they might they might attack my base
okay okay
everyone
join
join me in the attack
we'll take them down
what's up what's up
yeah
we will we will get golden no more of
those stupid stuff that keep on running
around my face
it's an eyesore
easy very easy
focus on building wraps
okay
[Music]
oh
yeah this could be easier with wraps huh
oh oh oh
maybe retreat
we killed their rams i think
maybe time to go
what do you think
yeah
i'm gonna go
go
oh i mean we can kill you guys sure if
you're asking for it literally
[Music]
now their army should be dead
oh never mind
there's even more
yeah the castle is the objective
go for it okay my cutie patootie ramsays
good job great good friend no need to
heal them because those are all new
uh
you guys go here
we need more rams maybe maybe one more
[Music]
or two more okay okay okay
uh
all right uh i think
i think everyone's here
um you guys
wait yo
man up please
[Music]
right
i'll bring these along too
okay
ready or not i'm coming
this is my new
rams unit oh yeah kuzo
and all of these no wait not all of them
can the rams move past him past them
wait there's one more here
[Music]
more houses yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah we're gonna have some people die
anyway don't worry believe it
rip minus it did they die
oh
that's fine
we got what we wanted we have more than
enough food that we can sell for gold
we're on our way now we're on our way to
victory
okay
um
well this is 45.
hopefully
enough
oh wait one more
oh yep
oh wow wow they're sending some
reinforcements here that looks pretty
strong
hopefully that won't be an issue when
i'm gone
[Music]
orange market if you want free gold
cafe
[Music]
in here there should be a castle
these people really need to stop
farming those trees outside
you also you can go back home
let me build a house or still
bust yourself hey
[Music]
which
side
which side should i go
look around a little bit
oh yeah
the way keanu plays the game is so cute
why
why why why
that's a lot of freaking wraps i don't
even
need so many
maybe i'll leave uh some behind oh
my rams kill it kill the fire
wait one here
one here oh it's right there okay and
then go for it
do you think
oh it's down nice nice um i think it's
already time
yeah
oh wait not yet not yet
[Music]
i mean that kind of pisses me off that
they're out there
my characters
[Music]
this cage is a toughie
okay
[Music]
yes
attack the castle
people attack the people
beautiful i thought um that all of these
castles were connected behind the same
wall but they're just
small castles behind a small
peritoneal
so this is easy to deal with
[Music]
how's it going here oh so peaceful
it's war however
not peaceful
then english can't make a castle
stronger
than yes nothing stronger than lehigh
oh [\h__\h] i shouldn't have salt of wood
oops
uh what was i gonna do
yeah
all right
uh
question is if we can go straight to the
next
castle oopsy should i save i should save
can i go straight to the next one
[Music]
i'll go i don't have so many
i don't have that many
and what i need gold
ah
nani
okay
a couple more of those
at least they're being healed back up
you guys chill here for a little bit
[Music]
old you get the what oh you get gets
less every time you sell
oh
[Music]
sold it there all right no no no you
will not
no i will not let you
can you join this army
well done maybe yeah
i will send some more
[Music]
they might die but that's okay
mineo
okay okay okay
i have joined forces
wonderful
then the
the rams tried to get in but they
couldn't those poor right
that's all four little ramps oh man
they tried their best
and you try your best but you don't
succeed
oh yeah when you get what you want but
not what you need
the next one looks huge though i wonder
where the castle is um
it would be good to know
but
you guys
it's okay don't tell me
we move
make some reinforced reinforcements
maybe
if only i had more gold
oh [\h__\h] i barely get gold from that
but we're almost done it's fun it's fun
it's fun
we're almost done we just can't lose now
oh wait we should farm that
wait wait what the [\h__\h]
oh my people should just farm that oh
well
about [\h__\h] time
right
oh yeah can we like make you a team
again
okay 47 how much did i have when i tried
to kill that castle
[Music]
run in with the rams first eh fast stop
laughing oh i fought
i'm being attacked by myself
no you actually you have to help here
um what the [\h__\h]
but it's good that we upgraded the
towers here
that's good
[Music]
oh i have to upgrade them manually no no
i think that was like what i mean is
there was an upgrade that meant um they
can
there's no minimum range
that they have to um you know there's
there's no minimum range for the towers
that's what i mean
wonder if there's anything else useful
that just upgrades the stone walls and i
don't have stonewalls
i've greatly watched house lets you
build guard towers
you know that that might be useful but
oh well yeah murder holes that's what i
mean
sounded very wrong but uh seems to be
the way to go
[Music]
okay
do i have enough people i'm just scared
because this area looks much bigger
than what we've faced before but i'm i'm
gonna try to enter from the right side
maybe
cafe scepter
maybe from here
then the watchtowers can't unless
there's one inside but
on horse scout
okay wait
i guess
let me see first maybe i can see the
castle from here although that would be
a stupid decision from them
like game wise they should make it
difficult for me to see the castle from
outside
i see nothing ah there's just uh
wood here okay just a forest
[Music]
maybe it is like here in this corner
um
[Music]
i don't know where the best place to
attack is
i
will i will
i will stand
right one here
okay
one here i think these walls are weaker
right
that's all
[Music]
good
probably
exactly wait is that what they're saying
that is incidentally what we're doing
maybe you join i'm scared one more will
help me surely
body ramp
[Music]
yes
oh there's a cat why why do they build
it right in front of the cage that's not
very logical in my opinion
but okay
[Music]
that was fast
oh
all right almost in
are you gonna come outside sure sure go
ahead go attack go ahead
you can let us enter tools
thanks very much appreciate it
[Music]
think i have the situational control
no no go here go here
you guys go here you guys
all of you guys go here
faster victory are my mom's dead oh no
also this rap is not getting inside oh
oh nice they have a good last of them
[Music]
[Applause]
that was fun
quite the challenge and so much
preparation
you might one might wonder if that was
too much preparation but
it was a good victory
now
[Music]
way better than most beginners really
against because i have that austrian rts
blood in me
hell yeah
all right
well guys um i really need to go to an
idol meeting and we have to read super
chat i don't want to end too too late
today because tomorrow i have a 12 hour
stream
um
you know
so
uh i want to go relatively early to bed
today which means like at the latest 3
a.m
yeah
and get as much sleep as possible but i
will read super chats i just have to go
to an idol meeting first
so you're welcome to stay
i'm gonna probably read a super chats
for an hour or so
and then i'll cook and then i'll sleep
and then i'll stream for 12 hours so if
you want more kiwawa tomorrow will be
more kiwawa
thank you for helping me getting into
aoe2
i'm still a little bit um like lost here
and there i guess but um i think i'll
i'll get used to it i'll get into the
groove and then i'll i'll know by heart
what i need and i mean most things i
already know like oh i need i need
these and these mines i need a market i
need a castle
first i need to advance to this age and
so on blue buba
upgrade everything
yeah
yeah all you need is ramps oh yeah if
they actually
do their job
it was very enjoyable thank you
it can get a bit complex but it's not
that hard um
oh overwhelming since these games
were designed with rts players in mind
but that's
perfectly understandable
thank you for watching this game gave me
used to playing the line my childhood so
it gave me nostalgia yeah yeah yeah it
gives me nostalgia too like i've
definitely seen it when i was younger
so i even i either played it a little
bit myself or i saw my my mom or my
brother played i'm not 100 sure but i
was i'm definitely i definitely know the
game
hmm
also wait is
is what what was the name
wait a second
no that was not it
ah
was black and white on rts too
yes it is yes it is
black and white one or two i'm not sure
which one
but i loved i love black and white
sort of a
wait i want to play black and white
with the ridiculously huge
god animals or whatever that was
hearing your keyboard is a joy
yeah yeah it is isn't it
um
i might consider stronghold or
stronghold crusader
get to build castles
i got to build castles here too but you
mean probably more like
like it's more about castles and they're
bigger and they're cooler
maybe
disappointing what's so awesome what do
you mean
they don't oh yeah yeah that's another
one of those problems i have a problem
with quite a few games that i like
really
um hold cherish daily in my memories
um from my childhood games that just
don't are not being sold anymore it's so
sad
um
so sad
vaporwave is that considered vaporwave
oh my god thank you cyrex
i'll definitely play aoe2 again i don't
know how soon i kind of want to play it
close to
the tournament but i don't know when
exactly that's happening
um
so
when when i know the date i'll be
playing more and more aoe too coming
leading up to that
yes yes
okay i'll go to our meeting now um and
then you know we get the super chats
behind us because i actually i still
have to actually maybe
record something perhaps um
if i got time but i probably don't have
time
big super chat oh thank you so much
hopefully i'll get to it otherwise i'll
get to it eventually
i really need to go to an island meeting
can we watch a cutscene oh yeah wait
right i guess they tell us a little bit
after pate the myth of english
invulnerability of english emilia watson
now our army knows it is possible to win
but only if we are resolute and cunning
english are a most deadly enemy
they don't look so deadly in that
drawing
they need to
get their bellies big
to make matters worse we now face
enemies on both sides
the dolphins advise i spend more and
more time wrangling
jealous of joan's influence of court oh
i pray that joan can complete her divine
mission divine mission dolphins envious
advisors
[\h__\h] dolphins just kill the dolphins
shitty dolphins
shut up what do you guys know about any
of this huh
well well well
well well well look at us clearing
everything
is there only one more mission
oh
but they take so long i wish i could
finish them now for completion's sake
but
yeah no oh there's three more okay that
feels better then
okay i'll see you in a minute
tomorrow
see you
[Music]
don't go
just wait just wait for me
[Music]
nice
me she is
[Music]
is
ahoy
[Music]
[Applause]
let me unpin that now
there must be a lot of new comments here
[Music]
all right let's go to my office
hello
where's me
[Music]
am i not like on the side
ah
that's where i left my body
[Laughter]
mmm i remember now
in another castle no no no i'm here i'm
here
oh okay
[Music]
man i cannot only
hold big armies
but also
a lot of water in my body it seems
i i thought of that while i was on my
idol meeting and i thought i need to
tell you guys that
i thought that was a smart way of of
describing that
strong armies and strong idol meetings
thanks for sharing you're welcome yeah i
know you know
i'm a very open person and um
you and me
me and you we we guys have a certain
connection and and we've been through so
much i feel like these kind of things
you yeah you need to know
good to know i know
you're welcome
i did say hi to chunky and smoothie as
well
while i was at it
oh yeah i definitely have to record
something after the stream
[Music]
let's look i have a lot of uh a lot of
messages again
damn
but i'm looking fine okay
chihuahua yes that's me
yeah recording before my marathon but
but that um
i have two things to record but um i'll
have to spread it out a little bit but
um my voice will be dead tomorrow unless
i record it before
before the microphone but
i don't think i'll get up that early
tonight's the 10th
11th
mama bring pineapple juice i don't think
pineapple juice really helped but i'll
have tea
and
um
yeah my fruit candies and
yeah no bc sometimes is cozy but i will
bring out some bgm now
today
what should we listen to
um
i have one one track that's called
relatively upbeat jazz
what was that again
ah yeah that one
i like the pris description
oh anything new here which ones are new
wait i can't sort them after
neil
that's weird
very specific yeah i'm trying to
name them in a way that i will later on
find them
easily when i need something
specifically
oh yeah why not
yeah let's go with this one
done oh maybe not maybe for a while i'll
go first as well for a while
[Music]
i think i have to read super chats from
today and yesterday
only
[Music]
i think
oh wait don't do not distract
[Music]
did you guys watch lena's birthday
streams plural because i was in
i was in a concert featured a little bit
by singing
a firebird
mostly like backup vocals
but it was still pretty cool
now i'm in the mood of for singing
firebird
um completely alone
i've always felt some kind of connection
to that song for whatever reason i'm not
sure why
my sword yeah yeah yeah
all right
you see the bottom left is where my all
my weapons are stored at
um
[Music]
yeah i did i did also call in
into her calling stream
and i was tired
actually
i woke i woke up a little bit too early
anyway like half an hour before my
actual calls i was just dozing hoping to
fall asleep again but i didn't so i just
was like half asleep until my call
and then i'm like
i love you
my tweet
that was with half an eye
one eye opened one eye closed because it
was bright and the screen was bright and
i wasn't sleepy
[Music]
she called in last into my birthday
stream and i called and last into hers i
think
that has some
deep
meaning i like
it russia
[Music]
okay i'm gonna start now
thanks for the pinky
your mk stream
okay
mario kart
when the [\h__\h] did i play mario kart
[Music]
i'm a little sad i couldn't participate
but i enjoyed it a lot because it's one
of my favorite content of yours i love
when you lose and rage but also when you
win and get super smug so cute thanks
for organizing
organizing
[Music]
when did i organize a mario kart club
what was that
is that just a reference to something
really really really long ago
[Music]
what
i mean i know i organized it before but
that's like a million years ago
uh well thank you
i'm confused jeff started
it's pretty old the enid one is pretty
old
jeff starr thank you thank you thank you
thanks for the rest of the chat test
what are you testing
your credit card
thank you so much
for the red super chat
maybe that's slowpoke
oh yeah internet explorer that might
have been the reason
[Music]
mortal kombat i never did
don't cast like me
i'm sick and tired of being gaslighted i
did not do a mortal combat collab never
played mortal kombat in my life
[Music]
stop it
thank you so much for the support so
generous
but don't don't waste so much money on a
test
[Music]
i corrected that spelling for you
i need advice back when you were an
active idol fan if you ever have a group
or idol you followed change direction or
start making content you found this
tasteful
were you able to reconcile yourself to
the new style or did you move on
no i don't i don't think so
like
if i think back to like betty scobo and
q and so on
the idol group said i had followed
the only thing that you know i think i
told you guys before but baby scope of
my favorite idol group
um
they
made a lot of really dorky derpy songs i
mean it wasn't their choice but
you know and
i would
they weren't like my favorite songs and
the more time would pass the less i
would like the songs they produced but i
love them as a group and you know it
wouldn't change how much i love them
and
uh
fruit candy
so
that's probably not exactly what you're
asking for but no that didn't bother me
and maybe the only other thing i can
think of that relates to this is
you know there's just one youtuber that
i watch
and i really like it when
i really like the pokemon playthroughs
and then zelda playthroughs and then for
a long time
there were um
no not any videos that i liked on that
person's channel
like for several months even
kind of boring didn't didn't change what
i thought of him
though
i still i just waited until there was
content again that i enjoyed
watching and now now there's more
content like that again
yeah
um so i guess i just waited but i i i
i wouldn't say i found the content
distasteful so it's again not very
fitting i guess
not very fitting
[Music]
yeah
yeah i don't know
i guess i guess i didn't really
experience
anything fitting sorry
first ignite thank you and pepsi
oh
frisbee phoenix called emperor's tantro
kiwawa praise bean
here's my annual birthday gift to you oh
it's your your birthday
in seriousness though thank you always
for working to bring joy to so many
chimpkins and for being a priceless part
of home alive
thank you
happy birthday to you
i need to check out don well he's um
he makes german videos only so if you
don't understand german
don't think you
will enjoy it
um well thank you so much dylan i wish
you a lovely happy birthday wish you all
the best please continue supporting
kiwawa
thanks for singing fever night and don
danke soon write so free
oh what's this name
it's so long
papago
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's too long
with chicken burger bulldog sauce
chicken vocal
[Music]
black
hello thank you
hi kiara thank you for your energy and
charisma on your content i have noise
hypersensitivity and where i'm from the
shouts and top volume on cars
are just too much for me oh
even got socialized anxiety watching you
and homo in general ate me to explain my
issue better and now are actually
helping
you mean because like we improved your
english or what
now you can explain it better
in any case it seems like your situation
improved a bit and i'm happy for that
noise hypersensitive sense
sensitivity i'm not sure how exactly
that feels
i can't relate but i hope it's not too
troublesome
i wish you
lots of health and happiness
thank you for the generous support thank
you
[Music]
yeah i'm surprised that um
my my shouting and all that doesn't
bother you
i'm surprised thank you though i hope my
streams don't make you suffer and only
bring you happiness
blackbeard
downstairs
thank
[Music]
i always praised your skills for a
beginner in a lot uh in a lot of games
now you're telling me you were playing
games with the equivalent of wearing
weighted clothing
wow you must play a bunch of old games
again just to see
honestly i don't think
that i played
all the games recently
all of them in 40 fps it was just
because i think i switched up my
monitors
and the one i had in the middle before i
think was at least set to 16. i think
but i'm not sure now it's hard to say
but i can't i can't guarantee that
that's the reason why i sucked at
certain games
yeah
could just be very recent ones
like tunic for tunic it might have very
much been the case even though it felt
really smooth to me
now especially for speed running
could revisit it and see
how it feels
[Music]
no for some reason i didn't know this
but i don't think there was anything
that i played
um before the monitor switch i also
played after the monitor switch so
that would make sense why i didn't
notice it
anyway thank you so much
uh hildegan thank you very much
a common tip for getting new monitors is
to always input
the setting to the edge set your monitor
supports it's just like how you have to
set your ram speed you did do that too
right
no
what
why do i check that
you don't need to set ram timing that's
silly okay thank god
ram's feet
my rams from aoe2
how do i set their speed they're really
[\h__\h] slow i would like to know
i would like to know
help me set my ram speed
i got you i've got you
language in action
action thank you
oh
interesting
[Music]
it's been almost two years since i
joined kfb but i soon have a job title
yeah what the [\h__\h]
wait i already gave you that yeah yeah
okay now that seems familiar we already
talked about this you now have the
hashtag will catch your guild enforcer
title
make sure everyone loves only quinoa and
listen at all your music on repeat all
day every day
wonderful
[Music]
have you tried downloading my ram that
seems like a joke i don't think that's a
thing right that's that's a joke right
oh wait is that i think that's a joke
yeah that's a joke okay okay okay i got
that one i got that one
[Music]
i'm so proud
thank you for the pinky
oh my god
oh i also answered this one already as
well
i'll skip it then thank you though
techno king 77
[Music]
swata thank you for the pinky hey boss
here's a pinky from me to you it's my
birthday and i want to thank you for
making our days brighter also and early
congratulations for your two years yay
can i ask for an employee number please
as i may have dropped mine in the friar
how how can you drop it and you forgot
what it was
unbelievable
thank you so much first of all for the
sweet generous super chat
um
so your birthday was yesterday huh the
oh no the day before yesterday
at that time
[Music]
yeah i had the day off yesterday
so that must have been the 8th of
september
you see your number
your employee number will be nine
oh
eight
hey
and a happy happy happy birthday to you
i hope you enjoyed it i hope you had a
great day
and many many many more great days to
come
because you deserve it
how convenient yeah i don't know how
that's such a coincidence
that his birthday is his employee number
uh wow that that must be um
it's a miracle
that's destiny
wow
that conduction
all at once oh yes yesterday not the day
before yesterday it was really bad
only intro gamer could do that you're
amazing boss thank you
it was
i don't know more books than usual as
well in that last episode
interestingly i don't know
why we were kind of unlucky i guess they
were trying to
stop me from finishing the game on that
day
[Music]
thanks for playing you're a great player
thank you
too kind too kind
[Music]
they're getting patches
okay
that's fine i finished the game anyway
so as long as i don't get soft lock in a
game all is good
getting soft lock soft locked
on stream would be
quite the problem
quite problematic
hope
[Music]
go to your old school's website and
check their lunch menu then bam balanced
meal schedule
i don't even think my old schools have
their lunch menu
on their website no way
our schools don't do that do you do do
american schools do that or wait you're
from from the great british land
did your schools do that
we don't do that
[Music]
enjoy america oh
italian schools sometimes
do we don't do that here
yeah
that could dunca
crispy cat come on for the pinky
i finally became a bucket i want to hear
your little [\h__\h] can you tell me
i'm looking forward to a year later yes
another year
is about to come upon us
so you better stay you better stay
forever you little [\h__\h]
crispy cat thank you so much
what's the point congratulations on
being a bucket already wow
[Music]
i almost gave you a kiss
my mom was leading up to it but then i
realized wait
wait that's a pink super chat wait wait
oh and then you guys started fighting
over being the last super chat
hobby line
i really
there we go
childish chickens childish so childish
[Music]
yay
i really didn't put much effort into it
though to be honest
but i'm glad you enjoyed it
it wasn't much effort
my best work really
it was so easy i didn't even have to put
the the logo on it because it was
already on there
[Music]
mina konosama is
um
[Music]
you're awesome i can't believe you
played with 30 fps the entire time yet
you still managed to do your part in
the fps games you're way better than you
think
also i think the reason is that your
display doesn't support
okay 60 so when you changed it
uh i don't know
it confuses me again
it's currently
2k oh you mean when it's 4k no
that's it's just because i had it um
switched around before
[Music]
that you agree
no
i signed nothing
robin hood thank you soon thank you for
the rest of the chat hi kendall today is
my 25th birthday which means i can now
why do why does everyone have birthdays
[Music]
i guess because you were born and you
know
being born comes with birthdays
damn
now i can rent a car in the u.s
wait you can't rent it before no way
what
you have to wait until you're 25 no no
[\h__\h] way
what
[Music]
insurance reasons
but so aren't there people who drive
what about the people who have their
sweet sixteen and get uh a car from
their rich [\h__\h] rich parents
[Music]
when they're 16 or 17.
they just don't drive it or what
i think i've seen people
in america
in tv shows drive cars with uh when
they're still under 25.
that's owning another one oh
wait that's so stupid you can buy one
before you can rent one
[Music]
to celebrate such a momentous occasion
could i please have an employee number i
look forward to the stream and your
12-hour marathon
of course you can it's 909
909.
it's like no oh no
german
happy birthday to you
recently i remembered uh another way of
singing happy birthday in german
that's very childish
um
but i forgot the very last line
let me look it up
[Music]
happy birthday to
you
[Music]
here it is
happy birthday to you
[Music]
it basically means happy birthday to you
jam in the shoe
[Music]
apricot in the pants happy birthday to
you
i used to sing it all the time when i
was a child i completely forgot about
that version
but anyway to you
[Music]
yeah haha you got jab in your shoes huh
you got apricots in your pants
yeah cause it rhymes that's the
the only reason
[Music]
but it was converted by a priest
oh how the [\h__\h] did that happen
unbelievable
i didn't even see any priests from the
oh wait our priests i guess because
they're co okay that makes sense
where's one of my monks huh
[\h__\h] those monks
i shouldn't have i should not have let
them join my army if they convert
my red super chats
unbelievable
why are you guys spamming volo lolo
what
why are you guys spamming
[Music]
oh age of empires one joke okay thank
god
it was kind of cringe to be honest
it's a noise monks made converting ah
okay i forgive
i forgive
you
thank you almost a year without catching
a livestream of my ocean but now i can
afford superchat because i have a job
and on top of that you are the first eon
member to play my favorite genre of
games rts nice
nice
i'm glad you guys all enjoyed it so much
really
jargok
gervania
thank you for the pink super chat also
congratulations on stickery for the job
i wanted to say that and jagbox says
versus hedgehog empire series yeah and
finally it happened
sorry i had to move it so many times i
know that was very disappointing
for the people who looked forward to it
yeah i'm sorry well thank you for
waiting jared kyoto
indeed
name thank you
what's up what's up
great to see you playing my favorite
game
your favorite game is aoe too
going to sleep now so a tip sacrificing
your employees by dozens may work for
carefree but not always in aoe too
i think i built a good defense
i was well prepared even though i didn't
know what's to come
how many enemies i would face
but i had a feeling
i'm feeling and i went after that
there's voice commands in aor2
oh i thought it was the other way around
you give the game voice commands
oh
well then huh
[Music]
you will see soon eric mcnaughton thank
no name 55mg oh never happy birthday
congratulations
28th birthday
noise
continue living please
continue
onwards you go
zero kingdom
[Music]
um
you know if it were up to me i would
have probably just gone for like you
know one of the newer ones but uh the id
girls went for this one and i do still
wonder why um aoe 2
still seems like the popular choice
i do wonder why is it just because they
brought out a definitive edition
definitive or is it because it just
always had the best
stuff in it
it's just the best one
[Music]
it held up greatly huh
people still love it
[Music]
but this one's more fleshed out and
balanced
most established
sometimes good games don't age yeah yeah
i have to say the same thing for sims 2.
there is sims one semesters in spray
sims 4 but i think i always enjoyed sims
2 the most
[Music]
i don't have a problem with sims 3 for
sims 4 for that much like although if i
had to say the worst one was probably
sims
for free even though it had so many good
functions that they then dropped with
sims 4
like a big open world and all those
patterns and colors that you could
freely choose
that was pretty damn good i dropped it
for some reason
and there was something about sims 2
maybe it was just that i was in a
certain age
um
and it just
i don't know i was in that age where i
just started gaming more and more i also
played sims 1 before that but when sims
2 came out i think
at that point i started playing more and
more games
i got more and more deeper into it maybe
that's just why i have such deep
memories of sims 2 but i also think it
was a great game and they had great
expansion packs
yeah
[Music]
i remember oh my god
oh my god back then the internet
was not such a
big thing yet
i don't know
about what year i'm talking right now
but when sims 2 was announced
i remember
i was still living in the same room with
my brother
and i had um
not a bunk bed but you know those bunk
beds that have space in the bottom where
you can
put like a table and so on
so i remember um like there was this one
gaming magazine that would bring out the
news of new games and back then i think
most of us just got the information
about new games from that magazine
so i would buy that
and it had this this big issue about
sims 2
and it had this big artwork
with
that's also on the cover of sims 2
spread out over two pages and i i took
out those pages and i remember i
plastered it
onto
the wall of the second floor of my bunk
bed
and i kept on looking
like every i think was it a weekly or a
monthly magazine i'm not sure but i kept
on checking back and back then there
if the magazine had more info
and more like screenshots and all that
of sims 2 because i was just so [\h__\h]
excited about it
and yeah i looked up all the information
beforehand like oh there's a money tree
oh my god there's these
these pink glasses or whatever
ah
and because i was like
even before then
just so excited for it
when it finally came out i played it
endlessly
but i do think i kept on also
continuously making new families again
and again
[Music]
yeah magazines
i haven't touched a magazine
in such a long time
but it was nice that you could take you
could rip something out of a magazine
and then use it as a poster
and some of these magazines would come
with free posters
and some toys too sometimes okay but
those are different kinds of magazines
yeah
there were some girl magazines oh my god
some girl magazines they came with bags
like little bags sometimes or pencil
cases
or something like that
and i would always get them just for the
accessory that they came with
i would say they were usually actually
worth it
[Music]
the other day when i was at the
supermarket
the magazine counter is always at the
counter when you pay
the magazine section and i was eying i
was eyeing what they are like selling
right now but i also felt kind of
embarrassed about looking at the
magazine area in the first place because
i
feel like no one buys magazines anymore
i'm actually surprised that they still
have such a big
selection of magazines anyway
but i was eyeing it especially like the
cute magazines at the bottom that are
meant for children
they still do
the dagger red duck
um
uh taschenberger pocket books
the small books of tacoma duck
but
and i still do like barbie magazines and
[\h__\h] but what i did not see was witch
magazines what the [\h__\h]
where are my witch magazines and those
stickers looks like attachments
so much when i was younger
scrooge mcduck
they had these little books
i i read so many of them when i was
younger
[Music]
i collected them i had mountains of
those
[Music]
this is like looking at the pictures
mostly
partially me too which was really nice i
admired the art so lots of nice things
have stopped i haven't seen it anymore
they don't make wish anymore
oh my god i wonder if i could make
millions of dollars if i still had my
witch magazines now are they worth a lot
probably not
oh no my witch magazines
oh no
oh man
uh no
why do why did they stop just just
resell the old ones remaster them
is this such a thing as remastering
magazines
like um like games
magazines reprint oh
well then [\h__\h] reprint it do it
uh anyway let's continue
uh patsy duncan taxi thanks for the
razor chad victorious
it's not a disney show
i feel like that's a disney show with
ariana grande
it could be wrong though
sounds like it
thank you tai chi mwah a nickelodeon
show
oh wait nickelodeon is not disney
for some reason i thought they were kind
of the same thing
like
nickelodeon is a thing within
disney
no
well they have a very similar style
of cringe um
gm lenny lemmy thank you for the
[Music]
i just wanted to thank you again for
everything you work helped me for a
really rough patch and your display of
genuine kindness replying to a previous
message oh
going as far as saying thanks in my
native language
of course
i like to flex my my obrigada
actually got me a little emotional
nowadays i'm finally at a good place
thank you for all your work and for
being who you are i wish you all the
best and will continue to support you
that's what i'd like to hear thank you
i'm glad you feel better
really happy
you deserve to feel better
so don't let anything drag you down
anymore okay
enjoy
life as it should be enjoyed
which i i i'm
i'm a bad person to say that i guess
because i also
have troubles enjoying life a lot
because there is a lot of
like even
recently especially recently i feel like
a lot of people are
throwing stones in my way and
like using me
undermining me gaslighting me and it's
been
really um tough
on me
having a really tough couple of months
i can't even
explain properly why but yeah
oh and life you know is pretty mean
sometimes we have to stay strong
there's like
just so
so much that life throws against you
trying to make you
stumble and fall over
um
i have to stay strong
don't
give
others the power
to have
power over you
hashtag philosophical phoenix
[Music]
well said
i had that in my mind for months
[Music]
like i i think i've been giving given
people
some rl people so too much power over me
my mom and my best friend they're
telling me that like i need to be more
strict i need to be more [\h__\h]
i need to be more like no [\h__\h] you
but it's hard for me
i'm too nice a lot of the time
um
yeah i don't know
how
how can i be more like that
like i'm i'm very easily intimidated
[Music]
in situations where
i really shouldn't be intimidated that
easily
because if you if you show that if you
also show that you're being intimidated
and the other person they know oh
this person is easily intimidated i can
i can get something out of that person
if i just keep on pushing
more and more
this person will never fight back
[Music]
nah i'll just continue [\h__\h] around with
that girl that little girl that looks
like she's 12
when she acts like she's 12.
damn conquered thank you
sometimes you gotta go full karen
i always in my mind i always do
but what comes out of my mouth is more
like little little tiny baby mouse
[Music]
more but 11 9 21 marks the day i first
mentioned your name and to my friends gc
saying i'm starting to like chihuahua
she feels very genuine and sweet
and wasn't that even pre-debut
[Music]
and five days after
became an egg so you mostly made your
judgment no wait 21 that's one year ago
sometimes i feel like the anniversary
that's coming up is a one year
anniversary not a two-year anniversary
ah that was last year not last last year
i get confused
very confused about time
money
[Music]
um
one year since i officially declared
myself kfb nice
thank you
and you you stayed so long
thank you so much
[Music]
this dream came true my favorite which
you were playing one of my favorite
games of all times well it's always fun
to sing and see an outsider's
perspective you're learning super
quickly and i have no doubt you can get
the hang of it in minimal time oh thank
you very much i'm glad to hear that from
an experienced player
i didn't make you super mad about how i
played the game
thank
you yeah it might take a while until i
played again on my channel but uh it
will definitely show up again so look
forward to it
[Music]
really doesn't feel like two years
already
that's weird
i don't although at the same time i
don't know how long two years should
actually
feel i
i'm confused
how long are two years
[Music]
i think i think i know why it feels like
one year is because
my memory card in my brain it can't save
more memories than from one year ago
so
i mean i know i've been around for
longer than a year
but
my brain is trying to save some memory
space
so
it feels like i've only been around for
a year
yeah everything is just
blurry
good memory to be sharing so many
stories
[Music]
the fact that i reminded myself
remembered some of the the magazine talk
today is a miracle i
i think in those two years of streaming
i've told so many stories about myself
that there is not anything left to talk
about at least things that i can't talk
about
on stream
in terms of that
nothing more in particular that i can
recall
yeah you always find more no i'm like
pretty
i i rely on things that are happening
now
because i'm out of stories from before
also my throat hurts let's finish this
one
kitchen maybelline
five hours i have to be careful tomorrow
but i think i talked a lot and you know
one reason
[Music]
one reason why i decided to get
collaborations this time
is because i i will be able to talk a
little bit less during those collabs
yeah i also
um plan to do some food breaks i i did
go
to the supermarket today
because tomorrow is a sunday i did go
today to buy some snacks for tomorrow
[Music]
i have everything
ready
yeah marshmallows i will set up after
the stream i want you guys to send some
questions
uh
i will let you guys know on twitter
i know
[Music]
is a lot easier
a lot easier for people who are used to
dual stick maybe
i don't know about me and better install
yo you're right
how do you know i don't have it bought
or installed yet
but wait only games is on um i'm
planning to play that on switch right so
it's not steam
the other game uh was um ultimate
chicken horse
yeah yeah
oh my god
[Music]
well
yes
[Music]
i also have to
prepare and see how to enter the new
rest server
i don't i don't know if it's on your
server maybe it's just you know maybe
it's not a new server i just can't enter
with a click
[Music]
my throat hurt
oh no make believe two five four one
thank you for the ransom chat
[Music]
is your name charlemagne because
franklin your civilization looking
pretty good
did charles maine have a good
civilization
glad to see you having fun tanjo thank
you
glad to see you having fun watching me
my beloved maple leaf thank you so much
[Music]
no no no the reason i'm doing it at the
end because it gives you some kind of
hype and celebration feeling it fits
most
at the end
but it's fine i have a collab right
before that so
i think i can rest my throat a little
bit during that and then i might even
take like a
10 minute silence break complete silence
even
no yo yo yo
wow
[Music]
take a break after we're gonna do
another no uh i have something planned
for monday
but it's a short
stream
so
no worries
[Music]
and it's gonna be late so i can sleep in
and also
monday is gonna be the monday night for
me it's gonna be the anniversary collab
as well
it's not what i meant but that's also a
thing
[Music]
i will take tuesday of therefore
oh thank you
okay
uh after the franchise for the pinky
make me feel young again i remember
playing aoe2 like crazy when i was small
boy on my pentium free pc with 42 mb
graphic card and 128 mb ram okay even i
know that that's barely anything that my
dad bought at id to be ready for the
year 2000 and this new thing called
internet
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah surely back then it was like normal
decent
standard
[Music]
for the normal consumer especially
yeah yeah yeah that's funny
oh my god pentium free let me look that
up
pentium free pc
ah
that doesn't look as [\h__\h] as you made it
sound
like from the outside looks decent it
even looks like one of the pcs that i
used to have
but no i think i had something better
because my mom you know she was a gamer
so she made sure that we had somewhat
decent
somewhat
decent pcs like i would get
me and my brother and my sister we would
get like the the old graphic cards from
my mom you know how you know how normal
families
they um like all the sisters and mommies
they give their their daughters
and their younger sisters
um their old clothes that they don't fit
in anymore well mommy would hand us down
graphic cards
[Laughter]
graphic cards and whatever
the hell you need but
pc
honestly usually i wouldn't be the one
who receives them though because
i was not the priority because i was not
the best gamer in the family
normally would go to my brother or my
sister i think
i got the hand-me-downs from the
hand-me-downs from the hand-me-downs
but it was good enough for what i was
playing
which was mostly sims
and you know sometimes gamecube
[Music]
and announcement performance space but
not only that i was the youngest too
so
the game the best game is for the oldest
people in the family the older
they were the best
neighborhood games
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
now i'm the programmer yeah surely now
i'm the best gamer in the whole family
no unfortunately still not
but it depends on the game it depends on
the game you know you know you know
i have my strengths and weaknesses
everybody does
[Music]
no bester tales of sinfonia back then
was my brother you know remember how i i
said i would normally
always ask him to play the boss fights
for me
or we would like play together because
back then tales of symphonia and the
gamecube had a function where you could
um play together but you would only join
the fights
the field exploration and all that would
be controlled by the first player and
the rest you can do together like
fighting
[Music]
you guys help me now
you guys are my my big brother
[Music]
okay
better make myself shut up
in the dancing looking for the top down
true blue clue thank you
raymond
[Music]
is more beginner friendly
like richard duncan
the crazy big red superchat thank you
hope you have a lot of fun playing aoe2
i have been playing it since
release so it's a game close to my heart
still playing it a lot to this day also
aoe2de has co-op campaigns
so you could play it together with
another whole member yeah yeah yeah
that's the plan that's the plan looking
forward to more aoe content in the
future please please please yes yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes
that's literally the reason why i
started playing it
so don't worry i got you fam i got you
[Music]
dana is also playing so we could also
play against reynolds
i think kobo two maybe all of all of id
not all of them
i don't love them i think
thank you so much sirex way too generous
very way too generous thank you so much
thank you thank you thank you i
appreciate it i'll play more aoe too
because i was enjoying it so far
it will stay on my channel for a while a
little while
[Music]
very good
if you're gonna write english
in in korean
then
[Music]
m
keyboard asmr
nice
[Music]
i don't speak english
yes you do yes you do
[Music]
wait who was that what was that um um
too good
[Music]
i used the in the korean that navi mama
told me
do you want to die
[Music]
it's so threatening
we're good now
no more english korean trolling
[Music]
let's see where was it
wait there's so many new super chats
what the [\h__\h]
guys i thought i was almost done and
then i refreshed and you guys went crazy
again
stop
[Music]
not played much rts before but ever
since it showed up on your schedule i
got the urge to play it
and got hooked
with gold to keep good and go compare
them really hope to see fellow kfp and
low elo rankings hello can't wait for
more aoe content thank you wait are you
where's elo are you playing aoe
[Music]
where's elo
matchmaking system for online play okay
but are we talking about
are you talking about aoe don't you pick
up aoe
[Music]
uh-huh
i don't see him specific oh there you go
i'm answering my question okay
well well well have fun
get good but don't get better than me
all right that's my order
[Music]
i am
do i read this in japanese
or
either eva like
kumahara
or
i don't know how you want me to read the
name but
you're welcome glad you enjoyed it space
waterfall thank you
gabriel brandon
mr
[Music]
facts okay everybody listen up
number one one in every eight thousand
one hundred ninety two pretty much
reverse results in the shiny kiwama
number two she's cute number three i
love her number five kiowa
what
now i'm already signing you guys are
lucky
i'm the shiny kiwawa
it won't get much better than this
you're welcome
where's four
oh
[Laughter]
was that on purpose
you missed one
i didn't even notice
if you guys wouldn't have said i
wouldn't even have noticed
[Music]
thank you
uh thank you for the rest of the chat
one year ago i sent my first super chat
oh
since then i've traveled again and met
many great people this wouldn't have
happened without you as my driving force
meeting you at dokomi will be always
something i'll remember fondly
[Music]
oh it's gone
here's another great year i love you my
oc love you too thank you so much
on to the third year hopefully that will
feel like three years not like two years
you better be around
in one year promise me
promise me
thank you so much for the support for
such a long time
glad you're still around
i appreciate the loyalty
and the endurance
[Music]
thanks guys for the reminders by the way
lord thank you so much
thank you
space wonderful thank you thank you
caesar bill thanks for the pinky that's
my first episode for you i just want to
let you know that we kfb chimpkins love
you and hold you very dear to our hearts
you're a very special person to us and
we want to see you well i'm happy hope
you feel better soon
[Music]
sweet
love you guys too
oh we're getting all tacky now aren't we
because the second year anniversary is
coming up everybody is getting like
cheesy and tacky
cute
superhuman blue duncan
[Music]
was king of the franks ruled over europe
like almost all of it was like kind of
the first
holy roman emperor like a sizable
portion of europe but technically here's
the sense you like me how many times are
gonna say like
you like me know him better as
[Music]
there's an american radio host who's
called charlamagne the godwin what the
[\h__\h]
what did i write it
how
what
shallam okay i guess
[Laughter]
[Music]
german wikipedia says that's kind of
yeah i know
so he's the bestie old bestie
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
i'll remember
i remember him
i didn't recognize him because you guys
called him by different name
[Music]
good old buddy haven't talked to him in
a while i wonder where he's at
oh he's dead huh
loser
amen
[Music]
but i guess you did some cool stuff you
know
[Music]
thank you so much for the info for the
lore
thank you
yes it is definitely worth i would say
skydiving
thank you
[Music]
can you tell us something about dinner
with him
and we never had dinner we only had
breakfast
every time we met we only had breakfast
it was kind of our thing yeah
yeah yeah
that's awesome thanks for the pinkies
sorry i missed you reading my super chat
with how confused you were i left a more
detailed explanation and comments of the
cult of
[Music]
right them i'm confused about what i was
confused about what was i confused about
what went what
i was confused about something else that
i remember but i don't remember one
where i went
what
what what
i'm very confused always
[Music]
look at the ring adaption
write me a goddamn tweet
[Music]
pill bug
that should be that person
who drew
some aoe to chihuahua art before i even
played it
oh what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
wait i went on twitter to find the pill
book art but now i found
from christina manzanita
remember that artwork in the beginning
of aoe2 of the main screen
with the with the fish on
the fish on the head
look at this
well that's me
now i understand why i got confused it's
a very similar photo that is actually me
nice
oh
man
beautiful
[Music]
ah
oh that's that's i didn't know you could
draw
like this in this style
look at that beautiful chicken at the
bottom though it looks so fluffy
[Music]
[\h__\h] nice
okay
found the actual thing
i'm going to show you guys pill bugs
aoe 2
chihuahua fan art if twitter loads it
there we go it's so cool
[Music]
i got a sick hat
this is so cool
thank you
no no what comes i need that
i retweeted it once um
yeah it's so cool
also my shield
my shield is on top of her shield
i'm making shield love so cute
and the chicken the chicken look at that
chicken there right there right there
it's so cute
that's so cute
the sword though the handle of the sword
yo
that's so sick
nice
[Music]
please draw more more more
more
so thank you for the pinky i really
enjoyed watching goddess aoe too i'm a
goddess it's chuseok in korea just
the goddess second anniversary is
tomorrow
what's chuseok
it's a public holiday in korea oh
chuseok is a public holiday
i'm going to have fun watching but
that's perfect timing nice you guys can
watch my stream all day
i mean it's a sunday anyway but
[Music]
oh like thanksgiving
oh
wait monday or sunday
cause for you guys now it's sunday so
tomorrow maybe means monday
[Music]
is it monday
friday too monday oh
well nice and you really can watch all
of the 12 hours okay you better
and
now you have to watch
the whole
[Music]
foreign
what do you mean they need to sleep they
sleep before and they sleep after 12
hours doesn't you know it's not 24 hours
just organize your sleep schedule
oh it's not easy
anyway thank you so much pilbang
you're really talented artist so i'm
looking forward to seeing more
squid thank you soon if you hear it here
then i'll be here in a year attention
always informal oh romantic
thank you
[Music]
i'll count on you
looney duncan
john dark was mostly a face
but she said it wasn't she eventually
grew out of it and went back to being
joan of light
we're making that joke we are making
that joke right yeah yeah
no no boo i like it
i like it so so i just thank you thank
you soon ah the film rights oh oh oh oh
don't worry thank you thank you for
catching up
it's funny it's funny
[Music]
no i haven't the new season is starting
next week oh [\h__\h] no i can't i can't i
mentally can't
no
oh
yeah i heard it was renewed and i guess
new season is starting oh
[Music]
i'm going to go now and cook a little
bit i cooked yesterday
i'm so proud of myself
uh because it turned out really well
i'm gonna make part two
of that because i still have some
leftovers that i i didn't even cook yet
what did you cook well well well
wouldn't you like to know that any
superheroes are coming now i'm not gonna
read them in exchange i'll tell you what
i cooked
i wanted to show you a picture actually
now the dish itself is nothing special
but i'm quite excited because it was
real so easy actually oh [\h__\h] my phone's
dead
[Music]
i can't show you the picture my phone is
dead
[Music]
maybe i'll upload
it's not special enough to be on my
twitter where i feel like
well maybe i will
okay
well uh one of my recipes that i ordered
from hell fresh for this week was um
german
currywurst
curry sausage if you have a visit
germany
a really really really popular street
food is curry wurst
um now this is more of a dinner version
because it had a salad and it had fries
self-made fries
and and the sauce for the sausage
was self-made they didn't bring a
finished
sauce but sausage was really easy to add
a sausage
sauce was really easy to make
[Music]
so i'm really fascinated
it was really good
so i made that and the sausage yum yum
yum yum i actually made too much sausage
today i'll make a little bit less
sausage i mean i'll make what i have
left over but yeah
curry what's yum yum yum yum yum now i
know how to make that currywurst sauce
if i ever cancel my hellofresh
subscription i think this will be
a recipe that i'll be
using quite a lot
even the french fries weren't normal
french fries because
um according to the recipe i
uh
before putting them into the oven
when they were still raw
i had to
kind of
like
put some
not parmesan cheese but similar cheese
all over it
so they had a really nice
like
color
colored really nice colored cheese on
top of it at the end after getting them
out of the oven i never did that before
putting cheese
on the fries beforehand but not like
really cheesy like
creamy cheese no no
just like it was um
it was
kind of parmesan cheese you would top
your pasta with at the end
[Music]
yeah yeah
shredded yeah not not even shredded even
smaller than that just like powdered
yeah just a little not too much so it
doesn't overpower
yeah
oh yeah it worked so well oh and i did
when it said salt put salt on your
potatoes
in the recipe but i didn't put normal
salt i went a little a little bit
rebellious i did the unthinkable
i put the chicken salt seasoning that i
got from veils
on the potatoes
[Music]
yeah i used it i tried to use it
sometimes when it works but it seems
like i could use it
it was good it was good but i feel like
i put a little bit too much for summer
some of the fries
tasted a little bit too salty
surprisingly
but it's good i want to make it i want
to use it more
somebody stop this woman
heresy
it worked pretty well together
chicken salt
yeah
yeah yeah now uh i shall go
and
save some energy for tomorrow
and tangents too save some tangent
[Music]
also remind me one thing i wanted to do
tomorrow is every time i change the game
or the activity that we're doing i want
to change my outfit because i have so
many
so we can get some variety
[Music]
and we have 50 shades of kimono
not 50. how many outfits do i have
normal
casual but i count casuals two because i
can be a kitty cat or i can be like a
vacation girl
and then i have this one
and then we have the kimono
and then we have the dandel and we have
the wolfy wow that's like seven
odile has variations too but i'm gonna
count it as one
it's at least seven
ah kimono kimono also has some good
variations
[Music]
but still let's say 7.5 or 8 let's say
8.
[Music]
yeah i could pin some outfits too but
it's fine i have i have more than enough
outfits
yeah okay i will go now thank you so
much everybody for your sweet support
and your love
yeah
thanks for enjoying an old game
and you on my channel
[Music]
are you are you are you guys ready
you better get some good sleep and wake
up early for kiwawa and get some snacks
snacks next you guys have snacks ready
for
it will be less um exhausting for you
guys because i actually have to
entertain for 12 hours and talk for 12
hours but you guys can just watch
quietly
but stay until the end and even if you
can't watch the whole thing then
definitely be there at the end you
should be
[Music]
yeah okay
let's celebrate because this will be
that will be my main
um
anniversary stream
i know it's a day early but this will be
the main thing for me
so i hope you guys will all be there
and more
no you cannot watch and you cannot sleep
during your watching no no
okay and in german we say
[Music]
[Applause]
i love kfp
[Music]
do
why you're still here
[Music]