[Music]
hmm
on the last episode of
holo rust
the hello everybody it's me the sheriff
cowboy tanaka domo konichiwa
hello hello senpai domo
yeah watson this is a pretty nice derby
that you built here ah god shut down
[\h__\h] no sorry sorry i know how to drive
shut up chad stop bullying me it all
ends tonight
on the final episode of
season two
polo rust
who will live
who will be spared
shall we find out
together
[Music]
hi
play game i can't let you guys see where
i'm playing 14 players
[Music]
14 players okay well my hands are
looking a little big there looking a
little chunky a little meaty hold on a
second
[Laughter]
evening hello hello
hi guys how are you guys doing today you
guys ready to finish this this rust
party i heard from watson the pool's
gone that's fine i pretty much expected
as much um this is going to be
interesting
i really just i want to like i mean i
scrapped most everything of importance
um so i think i kind of just want to
witness the chaos today but if i can i
might still you know grab as much little
scrap as i can and throw it into the
workbench just one more time
pretty sure houses decayed
um that's fine
i actually i think the pool is gone
because the house decayed
um last time i checked i think i only
had enough wood in there for 24 hours so
um
ah
whatever fight people with water guns
well that was that was a thought that i
had and i was thinking i might actually
stand a chance if i make myself one of
those fancy water guns that i made for
watson yeah
so uh yeah we'll see we'll see how i'm
feeling
we'll see we'll see how i'm feeling
shove peace up their tail pipes
you're really teaching what what peace
stands for
the true meaning of peace
pieces of human
oh man this is exciting i wonder who's
on don't tell me i want to be surprised
i want gonna be surprised
i want to randomly run into people and
be like oh hey we haven't encountered
each other until today
now this this particular server is
important to me because this was my
tutorial server this is where i kind of
like learned the big basics um of rust
and from here on out i think things will
get a little more intense i want to do
like more electrical stuff and like cool
cool [\h__\h] like what watson did with the
demolition derby right
um i want to try and do stuff like that
i still really want to try and make some
kind of race track some kind of like
really shitty race track but i think
it's possible i think you can do it the
peace palace needs to be big and
grand you guys believe i can do it
say yes
yes
you believe right
all i'm saying is give war a chance
no
no shout outs to everyone in chat saying
i got a nice uh large bottle of sake
here to enjoy the night um recently
these days i've been like drinking apple
juice and water but tonight
tonight's a little different you guys
tonight we celebrate the end of a world
the end of a life with some sake
it's the backwards shinigami sake that i
got
um
for um as like a
a celebration gift from the production
team of new underworld order so
put the scythe down please
i have had the scythe down and i will
continue to i might shoot some people in
the head with my shotgun it depends on
how i feel
i might go a little crazy now
the reason for that is because i don't i
don't like being a punching bag you guys
punching bag is what i'm gonna be though
if i uh
if i let myself be one
and i'm not i'm not gonna allow that
so if a water gun doesn't work out in
the end i might use my shotgun
shoot everyone especially the shark guru
might be the only one i definitely
actively try to kill but
you know that doesn't sound too peaceful
well the time for peace is over i i mean
you guys saw me yesterday playing guitar
and a horsey
is this where my house was
i wonder if i got killed oh i did
but how
i wonder who did it i wonder who killed
my body without contacting me to tell me
that they were going to do a
let's see where am i
let's go home
ah
oh [\h__\h]
you can tell right off the bat some
nasty stuff's going on
i can hear it already
gara took your base she's supposed to
report that to me
she's supposed to tell me hey callie i'm
about to raise your hand
i'm at the edge of v10 this is where the
shop is
yeah whatever
huh
your base was degrading
yeah but i still had [\h__\h] i wanted there
like my guitar and my horn what am i
supposed to do without my guitar my horn
oh who's that running over there
oh it's a [\h__\h] storm
maybe a helicopter took your home out
that might be kind of believable i was
chilling in the pool i think
oh they are really [\h__\h] each other up
what
who the [\h__\h]
senpai
just take me to my unnamed bag
you know she technically did me a favor
what we got here
all right
let's see
this give me this
i just want my horn
let's see
where the glass is at
oh this looks fun
[Music]
my gun's gone
someone definitely took my gun
i got my guitar and i got my horn but
where's my electric guitar
damn it you sons of [\h__\h] all right
my shotgun
there's my damn shotgun
gotta be around where the pool was
where's my damn shotgun
i really like that shotgun
shouldn't have scrapped the other one
all right well
don't need any of this [\h__\h] anymore hey
with my high quality metal i wonder if i
can make a trade for my life
now let's see what i can make over here
a shitty pistol
water pipe
shotgun oh
oh nice water gun
a shotgun fires a single round
there's nothing
who's there
let's see what else we got here
simple handmade sight
fire shells
i want to make a good pistol
revolver
a cloth on a metal pipe
metal pipe
double barrel shotgun with two metal
pipes
uh
whatever
i'd rather bash people's head ins
head-ins heads in
got any mail
i knew it no one around here lacks me
all right how much water do we have
take all the water
steal everybody's water
[\h__\h] those guys
all right
let me get my sheriff gear on
i just wish i had my sunglasses with me
but wait there may still be time for
sunglasses yet
just a moment this is important
this is important
let's say crafting clothing
yeah
i like these red ones
else can we make
campfire grill
tools
with some tools
i really need an axe flashlight i need
i think i lost mine
big weapons popping off
what if i leave these around yeah
i can put these all around me and i'm
gonna play my horn the lure people over
to me
oh it's just too good of an idea
what's this this is a trumpet
social phone
megaphone
give me that
scrap of paper for leaving notes
flame turret
i can fight one of these guys
no worries with my guitar
little piggy coming over for slaughter
or you can just [\h__\h] off that's cool too
let's see i do like this empty propane
tank wood
gears
really want some gears
find some of those
and what if i put all those wooden
spikes around me become a one-man band
but i'm still a recycler at heart
[Music]
it's a metal pipe yes
it's a little ingenious
hear me out
it's kind of a smart idea just a little
bit kind of
i'm gonna go find out where the war is
and then i'm gonna set up a bunch of
traps and play a ton of music
these gears i can use those
all right
let's see what we got here
wars everywhere
i don't see anyone here about my place
for now
i wonder if people will be either by
that locked crate
got a couple gears to expand the tree
let's go see what i can make
wait a mate
what is this
ah this is an instrument for me
sheriff's looking good
looking like a savage
all right what do you got here
let's take a look shall we
traps
oh yes
fire turret i do like those
i need rope and wood for this one the
shotgun trap
make two of these
now there was something with metal pipes
i could make
aha double barrel shotgun
we can get two shots out of that one
yeah
i need 25 cloth for this little revolver
here pretty sure that we have cloth
yes we do
all right
make a revolver
i'm gonna put some of this stuff away
because
i will die
maybe we'll take my stuff i'll make two
of these just in case
let me put one with a lock on it
all right
a precious metal to trade
stones
some metal pipes for making more of that
more of that stuff
water gun
what else
put that away for now
got all my favorite instruments
i'm still making the pistol
now then
let's go ahead and upgrade that tech
tree real quick before it all goes to
see it
all right
[Music]
can't afford can't afford
not for long though not for long
oh
hey pig
come over to play
i want your meat
i have a grill though
could make campfire
what are you doing there get off my
property
oh yeah you saw my he saw my big knife
didn't like that
did you now
we need more wood for this bad boy
a box repair bench just not enough wood
i'm pretty sure i had wood in here
somewhere
there we go
all right all right i'll make a grill
barbecue
all right my gun's almost done
i'll put one gun away for safe keeping
and one to actually use on people
and then we'll have my water gun of
course which i can refill easily
and oh
let's see
this
you'll see
this is a shitty one
yeah this is the only this is the one
that can only hold one
away with
you all right
oh hell yeah shadow pencil thank you
if you
loot this body you
will be cursed
for
the next
month
also [\h__\h] you
all right that should be good
what
is this one not the one that can shoot
two what am i doing here right what is
this that i'm holding
water pipe shotgun fires a single round
before reloading this one can hold two
ah but the problem is i'm not holding
the ammo all right hold on
i'm at a shotgun ammo
that's a shame
you have gunpowder charcoal
make anything with that
ammo
nah looks like no that's fine more
bullets
[Music]
got a lot of bullets
i have a lot of i have a lot of gun ammo
all right let's see i'm gonna store it
away um
let's put like
48 back
only the pistol gets reloads
[\h__\h]
all right boys
well that's okay because you know what
i'm here to play my instruments
and dupe my little horn
[Music]
now let's go find out where the fun's
happening because i think i got a clue
[Music]
i'd prefer to find the fun
um
before i die
now let's see
let me check real quick 105. jesus put
some of that [\h__\h] back you ain't gonna
use all that
bring peace to the land
yeah my way
serving up peace the sheriff's way all
right now let's see look at my map where
does girl live
was a lot of bs going on down here
if i remember correctly
a girl lives at e10
i just want to see what's up with her
not yet not yet not yet not yet
there will be a time
the time is not now
you met scrap
ah shut them on day
[Music]
let's just see what's going on
just looking over the horizon you know
minding my business
i too do not hear any shots but i could
use some mushrooms
it take all the mushrooms
well that ain't fair
hold on hold on short little mushroom
grab and break
real quick
did not really embark on this journey
with a full stomach
there may be repercussions for that
just a moment
hang on hang on
everybody has to eat well before going
into battle
damn it
how could you see me from that far i
just don't i just don't buy it
just don't [\h__\h] buy it
oh wait no come back come back little
dear
mom back
that son of a [\h__\h]
i could really use some steaks right now
well you know what guys
why go to the slaughter right away
i see no reason to do that there could
be a mighty fine brawl happening down by
the uh supermarket
we got here food market
that's where we'll go
but it's also it's also getting a little
dark
i don't want to repeat the last time you
know bears and [\h__\h]
forget that
no surrey
i don't think so
[Music]
it's the final day of rust
season two
[Music]
it's got a soft feeling just a little
blue
[Music]
it's the final day of rust
season two
we're all feeling hold on
so i can purchase food
i don't buy that nobody cares about this
crate
[Music]
should be fine right
but i will fire on anyone i see
[Music]
[\h__\h] 29 haha that's scary
head to the supermarket now
[Music]
rama
flashlight may be a bit of a dead
giveaway
better to travel in the darkness
[Music]
i don't know if we're gonna make it in
time
[Music]
any mushrooms
any uh mushrooms
around here
there is no more fruit of the land left
over
they've taken everything
[Music]
all right let me just find a quiet place
to die away from people
[Music]
so
this is weird
[Music]
it's not letting me go the way i want to
go
oh your health will just keep going down
oh
i see
i mean i can't move like oh
i'm literally such a [\h__\h] idiot
i was uh
my hands were not on wasd
oh okay
it's a safe zone but of course
well it means i can't get killed here
right
stuck on a twig
we're in an area of peace
[Music]
who the [\h__\h] is making fun of me out
there
howdy
oh
yeah yes
okay doko
dokodeska
kochi kochi
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
okay i
uh turn on scrap ichi
okay yeah okay
yeah yeah yeah
mochi
[Applause]
[Laughter]
hey
[Music]
is
so
raise the roof
wow
yeah
yeah come on it
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
psycho
[Music]
it is
let's
[Laughter]
[Music]
is
let's go
[Music]
what
give me
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
nice job
come
[Music]
let's go
come on come on let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
do you like
oh good taste good good taste taste
[Music]
[\h__\h]
it
is
[Music]
it's
oh god oh god
senpai
oh no
[Applause]
ok
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah let's go
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
i mean yes i have food one second here
have two tunas
they're on the ground for you
i died twice oh i'm sorry
you grabbed the tuna no it was fun all
right
[Laughter]
here's here's zettachan there you go
tuna
ah nande why can't i drop it hold on a
sec
here i'll give it to you
i'll give you some tuna
here
yeah here you go
it's for you
oh
[Music]
i know
see you
bye bye
[Music]
let's go
is
[Music]
party time
it's okay don't cry not goodnight there
not goodnight there
it's gonna be daijoubu
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
crazy
[Applause]
[Music]
fire
senpai
oh
[Music]
drinking and gambling together [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
please god please
breathe please
[Music]
yes
is
oh
[Music]
please give me full
this
[Music]
it's okay
yes
[Music]
let's go
me
washington
is
gave me a present do you need scraps i
have 200 oh okay you're going to need
more than that for me i always take
scraps
i'm gonna here let me give you
you can ask some more i got a present
from fubuki so you can have half of what
she gave me
here
here let me toss them out to you
here you go president from fubuki i'm
just going to return it to her
afterwards anyway and just keep my
waiting
[Music]
very aggressive today
yeah towards the casino this is how i am
in russ casino i'm betting on one then
because you said so yeah
i have a i'm a very good guesser
i've made a couple scraps here
let's go
[Applause]
[Laughter]
this time
is that fauna in the cow thing
fauna
oh i thought you were fine because
you're wearing a cow thing
it makes sense
[Music]
if you think it's five i'll put a little
in five
[Music]
i'll put a little in five i trust you
here
five
five guys
[Music]
yeah i know it god told me oh yeah
kamisama
so shoes
come on
[Music]
come back i can give you scrap
we're just having fun here yeah yeah
yeah
yeah join in here from fubuki senpai
she gave me like a [\h__\h] ton of
scriptures enabling my 200. you're
enabling my gambling addiction yes make
more money
[Music]
let's go
oh my god
please
[Music]
yeah i just wanted to shove this horn
directly onto your wolf snouts
[Music]
give me one
yeah do whatever you want they're from
fubuki senpai i just wanted to share the
world
[Music]
likelihood of winning to be hired
shut the [\h__\h] up out there shut up
quit making noise shut up
shut your damn guns up stop with the
bomb
shut up
all right sorry i had to tell them to be
quiet
they are quiet now
yeah give me this yeah all right both
wars ended yeah
thanks to gambling and drinking together
even if you have some iced tea and water
fubuki senpai and i are getting lit
though let's go
[Music]
yes
oh
shot out of all of you i swear to god
hold on
[Music]
shut your asses up shut your asses up
shut the [\h__\h] up shut the [\h__\h] up
shut up
stop shooting stop shooting no one
[\h__\h] wants no one [\h__\h] wants you
here
[Applause]
oh my god kiara your audio
place to be
yo i know
the european thing you're not funny oh
no way that's insane
oh my god
you get a call
are you shooting at the casino can you
stop please
[Laughter]
yeah we're just having a peaceful time
kill that person yeah kill him
[Music]
oh yeah that's a good point other people
are streaming i probably shouldn't use
the f word excuse me i'm sorry everybody
else's audience i sincerely apologize
that was not very cash money of me i
will i will behave myself right i think
i might have that in my inventory let's
see
all right let's see
internet just crashed let's go
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
i'll go with one one one one a little
one a little three one
one please
[Music]
[\h__\h] about me out here
what
yay
again again
again again again again again
fubuki senpai mochi deska
[Music]
yeah give it back to you
how much did you give me earlier i want
to give it back oh sure 200 and uh wait
hold on um i gave you 207 scrap
okay 207 okay yep you want to give it to
fubuki senpai because he gave it to me
[Music]
yes
foreign
this is the real peace party right here
[Music]
let's go
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
who are you
hello i'm here
sure i'll use it i'd love some more
scraps oh yeah
[Music]
can you play blackjack in this game
is
okay
here play
more players needed add more crap to
your table story
you know
for the minimum buy-in do you need more
scraps we don't have enough for the
minimum buy-in do you need more scraps
[Music]
i wonder how many players are necessary
maybe
mom how much we're trying oh not all
caps hold on okay invite people you're
trying
yeah more players need a story game okay
i'm just coming
maybe
let me see okay
[Music]
there is
oh
[Laughter]
love peace
[Music]
um
i'm having fun gambling here
[Music]
what if i say that to her
[Laughter]
wow
going to come kill me
to protect you too if she does that oh
thanks appreciate that kiara
don't you have some cards to count
sheriff
actually
i'm
too busy getting rich
[Music]
you're welcome to use this
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
get down
we're kicking ass today guys
yeah three three three please
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah it's awesome isn't it cool
let's go
i made it myself
it's gorgeous
i got a lot of money yeah
i just made my money back
i made my money back yay
um
[Music]
i can go back and make another one
flower kindness
yeah
how do you make other sounds sharing is
scary to switch to all
yeah you can play it like with different
numbers
you do sound like the ship
another band member yeah
i want this one
[Music]
and then it cuts to this
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is important
do you need some more i can give you
some
only if you don't need that i'm just
still trying to build my tech tree yeah
sure here let me see i can throw you a
couple to keep gambling oh my gosh i'll
give you 100. how far are you
i'm almost done with workbench one but
that's it
let's see
oh yeah i live right next to a recycling
plan
oh yeah i'll do that next season here we
go
yeah i just want you to keep gambling
with us please
i just i immediately got them back
anyways
[Laughter]
nice
yeah if you want to use the recycling
then you get rid of some stuff
like i might recycle my bear traps my
original plan was to like leave bear
traps around and then play an instrument
and lure people to come and die but i
think i'd rather gamble
oh
especially guru oh sorry mostly guys
[Music]
get the shark
my new favorite band yeah good
[Music]
dude
do
[Laughter]
[Music]
how can this game be so silly but also
so brutal at the same time
whoever's out there shut up
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
oh
it's only special nights
[Music]
it's a special night
is
please
let's go
[Music]
now make sure you don't get killed don't
lose that beautiful horn i don't know
i won't lose them
[Music]
you drink a lot of beer that happens
oh
[Laughter]
from our
peace
yes
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
outside the casino
aka
peace palace
hey hot dog yeah this is a peace
challenge
yeah it is a peace palace right i'm
gonna make my own someday but for now
this is perfect
global chat though is there a way we can
do not global chat
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
i'm only talking [\h__\h] about them because
they can't hurt us in here
[Music]
on them
energy
oh
[Music]
uh yeah it's pretty rare for anything
besides one and three
[Music]
maybe next time at the end of the season
we can roll the stage and make a big
concert oh fun i like that idea let's
start a band kiara
start a band i'll play the trumpet
is
[Music]
because no one ever chooses
not this time you know you can split
your winnings yeah like so you can
choose one and two or one and three and
you know but i did that last time
everybody told me that's a stupid idea
yeah it is
[Music]
there's an accident it's all good
oh no kiara
almost 7 000
[Music]
but then i gave away
707 of it so technically
i'll be able to pay her off
yeah
yeah i just want people to gamble with
us
[Music]
gambling means peace in this game
gambling is the only piece
hey what is
this
[Music]
so you cannot convince me to pick
anything besides one and three
yes
[Music]
right here
there is a table back here with four
seats
if you want to play
[Music]
it's tough blackjack needs a dealer so
like i think both of them need a dealer
i don't know what game is here god damn
it
let's see
[Music]
okay
all right chiara fubuki senpai and i
will just gamble here
i ain't leaving tonight
[Music]
see you later kiara bye-bye be careful
don't lose your horns
[Music]
[Laughter]
a
[Music]
mama
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go
[Music]
is
thanks
oh
[Music]
thank you friends
[Laughter]
no
it's okay mama
it's
okay
[Music]
is please
please please please
please
oh
[Music]
i'm gonna miss her
well now comes the scary part which is
returning home
let's see well i'm here
there's the last crate we don't want to
[\h__\h] with there
i know they're gonna hurt me if they
find me so
i'm gonna run around this way
uh-oh
the wheel just keeps spinning don't it
the wheel just keeps on turning
i'm gonna sneak away now
[Music]
shut up don't do that
keyboard capture how do i make it not do
that
[Music]
stop
stop with the keyboard capture i don't
want it
stop i don't want it
stop
okay i'm done i'm done playing
we're stuck now escape duh okay
i will protect myself if i have to
i'm about to get quiet guys because i
don't feel like hey man thank you for
everything you've done
okay
because i don't feel like turning off
the
touch to speak
also just real quick
no i should not wait till morning
morning is when people can see me i'd
rather get killed by animals than by
people who will loot my [\h__\h]
um
oh my
god now
i just want to finish the first tech
tree
like what's this mixing table that's
freaking sick
i want that
and i can make a real bed next time
and a real fireplace
that's amazing
right now to do some electric stuff like
solar panels
this is going to be important for the
next wipe you guys we're gonna need
solar panels
electricity this will be important
let's see what we got here
flasher light electric heater
that's gonna be helpful
one of these one of these
ooh speakers
give me that
door controller
a real telephone
igniter i don't know what any of these
do but we're gonna use all of them
button
and target
nice
and we're almost completely done with
the first bench
that one's oh
i like that it's good
okay it's just dear
oh that's cute kiara accepted my
invitation to team you don't need to do
that kiara
it's very nice
can't afford all right so
this is basically kind of where it ends
for me
um which is fine
i would like to get this last
this last little one
right there
kiara wants to do the derby
ah sorry caps
[Music]
all right
i might be able to finish it up actually
if
i find a little scrap here
my favorite place i'm gonna miss it i'm
gonna miss this place a lot
it's done me very well it has served me
so so very well
all right i 13 down the street from your
house location gotcha
5 13 hey
right we'll head over there in just a
sec
by 13.
okay
let's go
let me go quickly make a little scrap
and then we're gonna go drive
how about that you guys
how about that
i do really like the derby a lot i think
that'll be fun
i also need to find some things to kill
at some point
yup the map gets reset every month so
i'm gonna miss this little place
yeah
i mean i'm sure i can build my own
recycler as well but
and then i can actually put one in my
house you know
that would be nice
ah
[Music]
i think that's enough to finish the tech
tree i think so too and then we got work
bench number two i think we'll get
through two and three next time if we
really put our nose to the grindstone
because i really did only start playing
rust after like what the
18th i forget exactly when it was but
it was pretty recent so
okay
oh jesus christ
all right uh and this is it
tree's done
the first workbench is complete everyone
we did it
i'm happy
all right i'm going to go meet up with
kiara now
i don't really care about losing stuff
anymore at this point all i really
wanted to do was finish that tech tree
so
i have 13. i it's super close to me
there's one left i missed one hold on
no way
are you guys [\h__\h] with me there's no
way i missed one there is
can't afford [\h__\h]
okay well
well let's just see if we get any more
scrap
let's just see if we get any more scrap
maybe i can steal some from ama
i'm just kidding i'd never steal from
her she's a partner in peace
let's see might be done this way
jesus christ
was that from over there hopefully
they're not fighting over it on his
super peaceful demolition derby
cause that'll make me mad
that would not make me very pleased
day isn't over yet though so let's see
what happens
i'm going to steal some food right now
how does she like how she able to put
the cars back so quick
i say steal food but i know that she
wants me to have some of this
i'll get the tunes popping too
thank you ame
what a legend
there we go
feeling good
let's get the tunes popping off
play
high pitch low
howdy
howdy howdy i can't hear anything
howdy turn the power
is the power on it might be off
oh
howdy turn it on i don't think
oh shoot hold on i need to
hang on my phone's about to die hold on
a second hold on
hold on there it is
[Music]
something weird is going on there i
don't know
do
do do
i'll just wait for kiara here
i just wait for kiara
there we go
[Music]
hey windows it should be on then i don't
oh
maybe i'll just play my trumpet
where is everyone
[Music]
i'm going to shoot kiara with a water
pistol when i see her
in here
i wonder what's for dinner
okay
what is guru doing what the gu doing
i wonder if i can get some onigiri from
the convenience store oh yeah da i can
but do i want onigiri or do i want taco
rice taco rice is so good don't you guys
agree taco rice is really good
i'm a big taco rice fan
taco rice is just my jam
i don't think do they have taco rice
everywhere else in the world i wonder
you know like rice with taco stuff what
is that it's rice with um
like a bunch of like taco stuff on it
instead of the um
the uh
the taco shell
like the taco tortilla
you eat it with uh you just put all the
taco contents on rice and then in japan
a lot of times they put like an egg on
it or something like that but in in
japan eating raw eggs is fine because
it's like not bad for you or anything
they're like
treated well and stuff like that to the
point where like you can't get sick from
it
so you like a lot of people just like
crack that egg over the taco rice and
it's like really good
it's on your regular rotation yeah it's
super good it's the best i think it
might be kind of a japan thing to be
completely honest but now i love taco
rice whenever it's available i
i get some of it
now let's see i'm low on water bottles
so i'm gonna get some water bottles
[Music]
[Laughter]
actually tries to sing well
it's actually more of a
japanese-american thing i can see that
yeah definitely
[Music]
well if i eat coffee jelly now i'm in
trouble
wouldn't it be hilarious though to play
rust until the sun comes up
wouldn't it just be hilarious
for my health
i'll buy some but i'm putting it in the
fridge
i'm putting it straight in the fridge
or else can i grab
[Music]
no thank you i think i'd rather die
that's a rust night but i have my nihon
shoe already so
i'm happy
what's in the fridge nothing condiments
the contents of what you would assume is
somebody
out of college but not a full adult
would have in their fridge especially in
japan
alcohol and
condiments but in this case no alcohol
because i'm not really doing that right
now so
human meat ketchup
is
when does the reset happen um i think
tomorrow at 10 am
but when i say goodbye to russ tonight
i'm saying goodbye for
the the entire wipe so
i'm not getting up at 9am to play rest
another time
i need to i need a break before valhalla
because i'm not giving myself enough
breaks so
yeah there's still time to gamble
if i really wanted to
but
as much as i'd love to also kill guru
once i just don't think it's gonna
happen
it would be super funny though if i went
to where she was at and i just lured her
with music and then i'd set off a bear
trap
it would be funny
you still got four hours then oh okay
gotcha
i see i see
i just need a good sniper next season
for sure
we'll get her next season
break me off a piece of that kick cap
bar
put your hands up says the sheriff
why are you hungry over there i can
actually see er on my map
she's on the way
i hope she's all right i hope no one's
messing with her she's going the wrong
way
well i'm not going to backseat her and
tell her
tell her to come over here but i hope
she's all right
maybe she's hungry
oh she's on my taxi right now i'm gonna
let them do their thing then i'm just
gonna mess around here what do we got
here
it's lost it's locked it's locked yeah
well no [\h__\h] sherlock probably should be
otherwise the thieves could get into it
i'm not gonna mess with the cars yet
i will certainly break everything so
this is cool
large furnace so if i wanted to like
cook some food maybe maybe i'll hunt
some animals while i wait
oh nice car maybe ame could fix this bad
boy up wait hold on a second
this one on his cars
oh no
would be cool though she should fix it
up
needs a full set of components
i see so this is how amelia gets the
cars working
that's kind of cool lucky her
she got a car right there
bails
is baeon
wanna join me ahmed kelly for demolition
derby i hope that bae isn't too like
[Music]
disillusioned
after all the all the bullying from iris
i see deer
skirt around here
see if they cross her out
oh he's mad
nice
oh i'm out
oh no he run now
that was kind of sick i'm glad that you
actually came to fight me
that is until i started hurting you
i won't let you get away
i'm gonna treat my friends to some deer
meat
he's not gonna run far
he'll stop
why are you running the deer thought it
could win
he made a big [\h__\h] mistake
he's heading for the hills i'm not gonna
let him
yeah it's cold here isn't it buddy you
wanna return back to the forest don't ya
that's how fun i'm doing this
oh
oh he's just chilling
this really does not shoot very far does
it
okay
again that was just uh
some interesting timing
i thought that was pekko to senpai but
it wasn't
that was um an npc
well
them is just the break saying it oh my
god kiara arrives where's cali
dead
i'll be back though
hi an npc hi an npc killed me i need to
go what the [\h__\h] is on your head
oh no
it's okay i'm gonna go grab my body mama
i'm a pumpkin girl very cool i'm gonna
go grab my body and be right back get
your body
yeah
that little laugh
that's pretty funny
i just seen [\h__\h] and then just
dead
it was a little funny
i just wanted the deer come on
scientists we could have shared
we could have shared
but no
he's not still there i'll be annoying oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] no
stop shooting me
oh i don't know where they came from oh
it's a century so it's like a
what you may call it
well
oh well
sad on this
turd has my number oh well
happy for the better
that's rough
might be inaccessible now what a shame
yeah let me see
body
thanks mengs
might need a little help there
i am weaponless you know aside from a
rock oh and some [\h__\h] tune in water i
guess
ward
let's see where was it
let's see
a little dangerous to use the global
chat because who knows who's gonna head
over there and start some bs but
i gotta believe in people you know i
gotta have faith
that's what i'm supposed to do as the
sheriff right
just have a little faith you know
right guys
right
what a
nice job dummy
excellent word
oh yeah five scrap that could be helpful
it's good to have faith yeah
hope is really important these days we
just we don't have enough of it
i wonder what iris is doing here
i don't know if she's playing anymore or
not i feel like everybody's playing
roster right now
or at least most folks but
i don't know
most folks are taking a peek
you could just have i may get you with a
car i don't want to ask her to do that
right now because she's having fun with
kiara so
i'll make it back on my own i can
i can be a responsible adult and kill
wolves with rocks you know
hope descended then promptly left i
don't blame her this place is insane
that's the house of someone
everyone is meeting up at age 14. that's
a fake spoiler right
there's no
it's way
hope gave up and started killing people
herself but why
what's the reason you take their scrap
sure but it's just a stupid tech tree
once you get all the tech trees full
what does it matter
what's the point
i don't get it
maybe that comes as me being a reaper
death isn't fun it's a job
it's about sending a message
it sounds pretty edgy
gambling money oh that's a little easier
to understand
just just a little though
supermarket
i am hungry
probably cleaned out though oh
no we got some stuff
dang it i was so ready for some derby
fun i just had to go and
do something else
[Music]
damn it oh well
plenty of water though
looks kind of nice
oh well
curiosity always gets me killed but it
is always interesting that's for sure
hate scrap
hey scrap
yeah that's all dog that's about all i
want
chocolate bar
blueberries wait no i wanted to eat that
doesn't matter
[Music]
yeah that'll hold me over for a little
bit
carrying more water than the water boy
uh-huh
captain is saying no shows no moisty
maybe that's what i should rp does
captain insano instead of cowboy tanaka
as captain and say no i could at least
you know
stand up for myself not be a punching
bag that's an animal
i'm not [\h__\h] with it
i wonder if there are people that can
kill like a bear with a rock
probably really good at it too
damn i am far from where they are
this is quite the track
a new role each season
yeah the peace palace just sounds too
fun to make
uh-oh
i hate the sound of whatever that was
oh hello
are you
pinto
who's that
i mean i can't take it
as much as i want to
it looks like somebody else's horse
how do i take them
ride horse
okay
all right
now i'm a real cowboy
oh hey there buddy hold on there you go
let's go up here
ah you can't jump can you now buddy
well this might be a little rough for us
ha ho pinto away
all right let's go around the cliff side
oh [\h__\h] run
pinto you gotta [\h__\h] run man
pinto i need you to run
pinto
we gotta go we gotta get out of here
it might be near a rage [\h__\h] let's go
this way pinto jajo pinto
horse is feeling lazy today
i see he's got an energy bar
all right buddy you can just walk for a
little bit
potential got my stuff oh heck yeah
kiwawa
she's the best yeah i did give her a
real nice horn
oh lordy
it'll be interesting
run
come on pinto let's go
come on buddy
come on mind the trees
you'll be just fine
i know it
let's keep on moving along
we gotta don't worry about those bombs
we'll just ignore them
it's all fine
hey look we're almost back
now we're just gonna make our way
downtown
back to the derby
let's go pinto let's go
something is running too
i'm gonna ignore it
it's a derby
[Music]
i wonder if a horse can be brought to a
demolition derby
hello
konichiwa pinto and i are here to party
[Music]
there are two cars missing
oh
whoopsie doodle excuse me
[Music]
all right
excuse me
i'm back
[Music]
um however i do wonder where everybody
is
hey pinto let's turn around
riding horses is a little tough
well he'll be fine
[Music]
oh there they are howdy
hey guys all of your stuff is in this
truck bed thanks a lot i appreciate it
all right
thanks for the help you can uh you can
get into the back thank you so much i
appreciate the help
thank you
thank you thank you can we
i appreciate you guys
light up here to fire up here
you guys got a lot of stuff
what is this a note if you lose this
someone's in your inventory
i do i do have a couple things
i wanted to surprise you with my water
gun told me to pick up the stuff
but now i'm encouraged
no no that wasn't for you kiara i
promise it's it's different it's you
were actually helping me you were
helping me
you're good you're good thank you thank
you that doesn't count no it only counts
if you kill me like if it's a girl or
something
i'll keep these in here these are all
miss things
i'm going to take this cap though
oh
oh yeah i found a horse by the way his
name is pinto i brought him over
yeah his name is pinto why is he he's uh
right where all the cars should be
my flashlight's gone oopsie doodle
that's fine oh
he's cute you can use him as a car too
for the car yeah for the car derby sure
sounds fine to me i just found him
you might want to be nice to him though
if it hurts the horse maybe not but
isn't he a cutie he's a pretty horse
okay
he shall be the he will be the
commentator he'll look at us yeah each
other that's right good pinto pinto's a
cute name
this place is so sick i know right
hey kiara check this out
people need to see
hey check this out
hold on
hold on oh yeah
water pistol why can't i shoot you with
it
because we're on the same team
now it's just not working oh really yeah
just broken
oh well let me see maybe i can put some
water in it
come tool
you come hang out
let's see oh there we go yay a water
pistol
is that water yes water
gun yeah it's just water
yeah this is piercing this is how pink
no why would it be milk what the heck
[Laughter]
oh my gosh this is a strawberry oh yeah
yeah like a splash yes splash
hey pinto do you like water guys
oh
he's taking a shower
come on
okay
well then let me reload it
okay hold on i got you
are you stuck
i'm gonna get you i'm gonna get you whoa
headshot
okay oh you come send me dogs
come on
don't speak korean at me
i know what you're saying i know a
little bit of korean
oh pinto did you like your little bath
buddy you can drop everything off here
and we could go find apparently there's
a big war happening against
nice
[Music]
i have some bear traps i was gonna set
him around myself oh yeah i have a
pistol let's see oh let's see have some
not anymore drop off some stuff
let's see okay cool
i'm gonna go back to my house and grab
bullets um
because yeah
you guys did grab my stuff but i think
you might not have gotten the pistol
which is fine because i was holding it
just don't worry about it what what kind
it was just a regular pistol but oh the
pistol itself yeah yeah it was on the
floor back there
oh got the bullets from you i think oh
cool 69 bullets of course there are six
okay
i'll grab those if you don't mind and
then i'm going to
go yeah i guess so wait i think these
are are these from you too though
100 pieces of high quality metal yes
those are mine
okay
yeah
i'll just go make another one there's
two
is that is it
let's see it's yours bandana mask nope
that's not mine
i wouldn't i haven't held any of those
but i'm gonna go grab some stuff from my
house and then we can go meet up you can
take this car right here you just have
to back it up okay sure um
question uh what's the chords what are
the chords for the big war that's
happening is it where they live
you're in peccara
here like your plumber's trumpet
oh oh kelly can i have my key back my
cargo oh yeah sure
one sec
hey let me get out of here um
you know this car is super nice and
whatnot i think i'm gonna take pinto
i think i'm going to take it
yeah just because you know i'm a cowboy
riding on in with a pistol it just makes
sense here i'll give you your key real
quick then can i ride with you um here's
your break another car
there's your key right there and i'm
gonna go grab some weapons and uh what's
what are the cords can you remind me one
more time
uh i don't know actually okay it's fine
kiara's on my team actually it's the
award you know kiara's on my team so i'm
just going to go to where you guys are
it's here oh it's here the revolver
you found it yeah it's on the floor by
all this stuff oh thank you hold on a
sec let me go grab it uh hold on
to the team oh you can just click on her
uh if you hover over her it says like
invite to team and it's got like a plus
sign
i think that's how it should be but my
horse is stuck
let me through hold on
yeah
you should be able to join but
maybe let me do it oh yeah i'm the
leader so let me invite you
invite this you have a gun kiara
i have one with five shots
all right i sent you an invite oh what
kind of game
you said the pistol was down here here's
i dropped some more bullets for it and
then i think you have some of cali's
elbow
all right i think yeah i i put the 69
ammo into the box into the
oh thanks so it's in the box gotcha in
here and then let's see i got a roadside
kill water jug is this the pistol no
that's not it uh let's see
there it is i see it thank you
thank you guys
all right i'll see you guys soon
okay
i'll we'll type the chord into the team
chat all right cool that's fine you guys
are on my team so i'll just follow you
see ya
okay
yeah i'll follow you guys don't worry
you're good
all right grab some ammo
and we're gonna ride on pinto
well this will be interesting you guys
it kind of seems like it's a bit of a
how do i say this
a struggle of peace versus war
there it is there's my ammo
all right now what do we got here this
tool
i have a shotgun too
i'll need to lay some bear traps and
these spikes
the spikes that'll slow down and hurt
anyone that walks over them we like that
we love to hear that oh it's nice of her
to give me my horn back
actually this is her [\h__\h]
no it's for her
all right pinto
pinto
there you are buddy hey buddy
you ready to go
holy [\h__\h]
that doesn't sound good
where's my revolver hold on
[Music]
that doesn't sound good did i not pick
up the [\h__\h]
oh pinto i don't know what i'm gonna do
with myself really hold on a sec
well the later we go to the war the
better to be honest
i guess i just freaking left it on the
ground okay
go grab it
[Music]
i could have sworn i picked it up you
dropped it of course i did
of course i dropped it but where is the
question
i wish i was not so stupid
next to the other stuff
i wish it wasn't so hard to see
see a revolver there we go jesus
that took me a second but we got it all
right revolver
which is gonna do us a whole lot of good
in this war i tell you what
oh god
oh god you guys
i got a bad feeling that's fine we're
gonna bring it
all right fine pinto let's go
pinto can you move
i really really want to use you to get
out of here to
go
go go go anywhere pinto i beg of you all
right
now
where is everyone at can you move pinto
pinto i really need you to work with me
here buddy
hey pinto
pinto
pinto please
all right
good boy
now
go back up
and we ride into battle
we gotta go off this way
now let's see where everyone else is at
oh yeah where are they
oh they separated i wonder why
i'll meet up with kiara
all right turn around buddy let's go
kaye
i hope she's all right
hi ho pinto away
onto the tree
where is everyone
howdy
howdy howdy i'm here
howdy i'm here your your pumpkin head's
looking real nice i accidentally broke
amma's car oh dang it how'd you do that
yeah
[Music]
i accidentally shot the car while i was
sitting inside oh that's okay it happens
to the best of us
it's fine you got a gun on you yeah
yes nice i put it away
all right i'll put it away i got a
guitar
do you
yeah
for me and my horse just telling kiara
because she actually shot
car uh yeah i'm on my wall i'm shooting
anywhere on the move again all right
let's go let's ride please don't hit my
horse though sorry i'm in your way
i get you i get you i'm getting out of
the way
oh you guys are heading this way i got
you i'm sorry i'm just voice
brilliantly yeah pinto's really in the
way right all right i'm coming let's go
hi ho
off to one second
road trip
[Music]
of course you're probably faster going
up the hills oh yeah to be honest i want
to doodle i'm sorry i'm in your way now
wanna hit your heart that's all right i
know you don't want to hurt pinto just
don't worry about him and i we'll just
be skirting around y'all
i had to name him pinkle oh that was his
name when i found it when i found him
maybe i can rename him at some point i
don't know
i don't know much about horses so
oh
what a rash name it is also the name of
a bean oh cool maybe i'll i'll name him
mr steeds oh god oh god oh god oh god
cliff
hurt ro don't walk behind the car sorry
sorry
can't help myself i love being with you
guys
[Music]
i do too war's happening
we're going towards them amelia says
with great confidence
oh lordy
i don't know what is going on down there
i think we should go by the foot now
yeah i don't want pinto to get hurt in
the crossfire
all right pinto you stay with the car
all right
oh [\h__\h]
you're cute
[Music]
if you have stuff you don't want to lose
you can put it in here all right cool
there's room by the way i'm going to put
spikes around the cars you guys so if
anything run around the car to the back
and it's a safe area because i'm putting
spikes around it okay
[Music]
just don't you know get caught in the
spike i can't put it i'll wait until you
guys leave before i put it in there
oh yeah it's locked didn't it okay
you're gonna go in and fire no i'll i'll
go ahead and come in i'll follow you
guys
do a few shots
yeah take a few shots
let's see
all right i'm putting these right in
front of the car
we going
all right and next to my freaking horse
don't you hurt my horse
[Music]
is
anybody have claws do you have any claws
um
sorry taco rice anyway i'm back
oh [\h__\h]
had my binoculars
or the other two at
zama yeah there
what's up mommy
you putting your important stuff down
just burying something okay
i'll go with you because i'm i'm scared
to go alone i know i'm the sheriff and
everything but
it's better to have a friend
oh what is that is that a bomb
no no no it's just that my car keys oh
nice i can go in and die oh nice idea
all right okay
are you gonna you ready yeah i might as
well i don't really have anything i'm
attached to tiara
okay i can see her too let's go
this is like a cliff so be careful all
right
oh there's stones right here ooh
i don't think i can do anything with 100
stones
i can't find trees let's see i got a
high quality metal i got high quality
metal
metal fragments some bars
um that's about it to be honest right
here
yeah we can use this tree for hiding
and put a bear trap if we wait here for
if we bait people to come over here bear
trap will kill him instantly
oh yeah you can just break down the tree
break down break down
but it wouldn't give me any resources
when i was breaking it down because i
don't have an axe if you have a rock it
should still work
[\h__\h] i don't even have a rock
yeah sorry whoopsie doodle
there's a wolf over there i'll keep an
eye on it
can i have some some wood galley i don't
have any wood on me right now actually
sadly
oh i thought i did remember
well then i just got weapons
and bear traps
there you go use that we should probably
put it on like a hill or something
though yeah so we have good uh view
nice idea
maybe one of these higher ones up here
oh [\h__\h]
oh
i made three barricades but
cool any questions i want to
place them right here kiara wherever you
place or wherever we place the
barricades i'll put bear traps in front
of them or around them so when people
try and come behind okay
[Music]
over here okay
okay
over here by this tree nice facing the
base that's a good idea
oh [\h__\h]
who was that
a sniper
um like uh
wait i'll give you the barricades
because maybe you know how to place them
there's one there's more coming
another one
so let's go down there okay
did you drop it already
okay i'll pick it up
this is yeah
i can't believe i'm participating in a
war
i never thought i'd do something like
this
okay okay
one more
all right they're traps yeah i think
they're going in the face you could try
going in
all right people are just running
towards the side
oh my god
yeah
if anybody has cloth you can build a bed
i don't have any nice ideas
i think or do i know i have leather
[\h__\h]
okay
now in this little this patch of grass
right here i'm putting a bear trap guys
don't run into it
oh [\h__\h]
sounds so close
yeah
but my my shotgun won't even reach that
far will it i don't know anything about
guns
you have to go in
yeah
i guess peace is no longer an option
guys
might as well
they're running it naked meaning they
like just died at the long range oh man
what beautiful calming music yeah before
war if you guys want to go to someone
running there
on your enemy
enemy
friend no no enemy friend
oh is that another horse oh lord it's
getting loud oh who's that
yo oh they're all walking oh
oh my god that is insane what is going
on down there
oh geez
yeah i'm kind of curious it'll take me
ages to come back if i die yeah we'll
definitely die if we go down there but
still it seems fun
if we find if we find cloth we can make
uh beds i can go grab some actually and
come back
in you guys want me to go make some and
come back okay
you live closer i live like i do a
million miles away but we could make it
sure all right i'll go grab some find
some hemp
yeah i got some cloth i'll be our bee
let's see oh my god there are naked
people here
out good luck
[Music]
say
it's [\h__\h] funny
someone's horse
poker senpai
[Music]
no come back horse
all right let's go
i don't think this is pinto but it's a
horse
pocahontas naked i mean everyone's naked
because they're dying over and over
again
did not really prepare for this war very
well i mean
at least for me personally i
could have brought some cloth but that's
okay i live close by
so it's really no big deal oh lordy
riding a horse is a little tough
actually i think i might be better on
foot
oh my god it's literally so loud
this horse uh does not like the elements
oh this horse's weight has way less
energy than pinto does this is
definitely not my pinto
this horse sucks this horse socks
sorry horse and you're probably a good
horse i just uh i don't have time for
you
[Music]
this horse ain't no pinto
that's for sure my pinto could run real
quick real fast
all right i'll make some good [\h__\h] for
the team
with all that i have left
i can't believe i'm resorting to war but
to be honest if you think about it this
way guys if you think about it this way
them them folks causing war
they're the reason we can't have peace
so for that reason we must take them
down
that's it that's all there is to it
oh
i guess that that's fair
uh most of my items are gone now
oh well
i suppose that's fair
there's got to be some cloth somewhere i
got leather
well
i guess that's the end of that maybe i
don't have cloth anymore
but i did have hemp
just don't know if it ever grew
my bench is gone too
man
that's a shame
the timing
well
let's see
phew
what can i make
make flashlight
what else
dammit
so sad
can't even look out for my teammates
come on sheriff you can't be useless
like this
come on
don't be useless like this
how do we make a sleeping bag we need
cloth
how do we make a bed
i don't know i need to find some hemp
well
well folks it is what it is and to be
honest i think the best thing i can do
is just grab anything that could be
useful like gunpowder i don't even i
don't even have any gun but i got i got
tarps
tarps are good
you know what
sometimes you gotta give a little to get
a little
when you care about your friends
you sacrifice things
and me
i'm willing to sacrifice for my friends
to close off my own back
what else we got here
that's the true sheriff way
i don't even really need these to
respond i think it's kind of over
a jacket's even
godspeed sheriff
god speed
rifle spear gun
nothing i need
let's see how much cloth we get
that's all i needed why'd you throw it
[\h__\h]
hold on
i still want the leather all right
let's go back to them
all right folks
the journey must continue
i'm gonna make some more bullets a
workbench level when required the game
says
well that's not gonna happen
let's go
i have sacrifice oh boy kiara went in
all right well let's just get back to
the homies
good enough
kiara just flew in she's like nah forget
it
props
[\h__\h]
starving
mushrooms
maybe watson has some food but i don't
want to bother her
i'll ask her
but
i really have anything to eat there
anyway so
howdy watson you would nap and have some
mushrooms on you would you
i have a grill you can set that down
put some raw animal meat on the grill
kind of like to get attacked by
something now so i can shoot it kill it
eat it
but
oh lordy
tuna
son of a son of a gun
[Music]
right
there is always horse
where is everyone
oh amelia
amer
i'm there
oh fire
oh man i'm hungry
oh thanks i'm dying here
thanks
i have a sleeping bag
yeah i made one
here
all right i wonder where we should put
it hold on where is it
huh
what the [\h__\h] i just made it where is it
did i drop i dropped it oh my god hold
on a second
you got to be kidding me it must have
been up there
you dropped it why did i drop it
why did i drop it
come on
you gotta be kidding me
why do you keep dropping stuff i don't
know
ah
we'll find it we'll find it
your inventory was full when you made it
of course it was put oh there goes kiara
well she gave it her best
classic mori i mean you're not incorrect
all right now i do recall i dropped i
threw something when i changed clothes
but
glue stuff to your hands
was it near my house i wonder
hey pinto
backtrack
bro
i might as well just go make a [\h__\h]
new one to be honest
and i'm starving again yeah let's go
all right i'm just gonna go make a new
one
i'm gonna make a new one a search for
mushrooms
freaking classic
all right
fine
fine fine game i understand now
this is the way that this is the way the
game goes my inventory is full i'll just
drop things
got it
yes
okay
you're
right it
understood game understood
no um is down ah
dang it my sleeping bag could have
helped
that's fine though it will help from
here on out
from here on out it will be helpful
is peace still going on nah not really
takata
anande trader
traitor
oh boy both my team's down yikes
it's got to be something i can find to
eat in here too
something that'll give me cloth
sacrifices own shoes off back
own clothing off back
i think this will give me tarp but
that's about it
i just need five more
come on
let me cloth something
yes all right that's it that's all i
needed
all right hold on
um i'm not gonna let's just get out of
my inventory all right
i'm gonna make
this sleeping bag when i get over to
them
it is nighttime however
i don't know maybe it'll be kind of nice
you know at night
with the friends
i have a grill i should have offered
that over to boston
oh man
can i leave the game
everyone's gone
i don't even know where we where we were
was it here
internet died
yikes
they took over the rabbit hole
not surprised
the war is coming to an end
go kill now very little time left
two minutes left till the server's
bye-bye
no way
two minutes left go kill
i thought it was 10 a.m come on now
promote that piece all right well let's
see who i can get who i can get with
this gun here
all right don't run into the traps i set
why at 11 pm js i have no clue
i was not informed of that i was told
that 10 a.m was the reset
but you know what it's cool
i'm coming
might as well go out with a bang huh
what am i down there
oh yeah
oh
oh that person's dead
he did
eh
no
who's on who's damn it girl
damn it girl
why is it always gura why can't it be so
i gotta be someone else
why can't it be someone else see what
the server's still here
game was rigged from the start
it indeed ended with a bang
died exactly at the hour
oh yeah the sleeping bag is there
they were all there for you on a gold
platter i thought we were all working
together against one person
damn it
there are some things that the sheriff
still doesn't understand
will never understand
it's a war yes but a war has sides
the girl was confused
no i don't think she was i think she
knew exactly what she was doing
girl wants you to be her why why does
she want me to be her rival i literally
am not a fighter in this game i suck
konnichiwa
show
konichiwa
yeah konichi konichiwa cowboy tanaka
this is
[Music]
oh
oh my god nice
[Music]
i have everything i need
okay
[Music]
is
you can turn names on i think
oh i see
gotcha i can't leave it
i'm not sure i think i have to turn them
on
hold on a second
all right rust
take me to options
go chat show hud show name tags on
all right
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
mine
she get girl
oh wait i still left some things on here
i'll give it back to her she just needs
to come and get it for me to apologize
she has to come say sorry callipe mori
you're the best sheriff on the planet
and then i'll give it back to her
bye
just come give it back she has to come
say sorry and i'll give everything back
to her
get rotated
bye
she's coming with a gun
she'll never find
me eat something oh [\h__\h] yeah you're
right
i think i had some steaks but i threw
them out
well i have this for now
hold on
it'll be fine
she has to come say sorry to me
i'll be fine i have a ton of med kits
but let me go find some mushrooms
away from here
away from her girl can find me
she put a bounty on me
[Applause]
sounds about right
i will give her her stuff back but she
needs to say sorry
and she needs to call me the best
sheriff in the world
[\h__\h] why'd i do that
i should have known
i'm back here
come on back here
there's got to be some food somewhere
they'll stop running eventually
it does she will well then she's not
getting her scrap bag and she had a lot
of scrap
she had a lot i felt really bad taking
it but i need i need to hear sorry and
then i'll give it back
then i'll give it back to her
here maybe if i approach without holding
a weapon
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] can i use a rock to harvest this
guy [\h__\h]
boy
is not perfect this is not great
didn't really think this one through
guys
yikes
can i kill his body like this i can't i
can't we're done for we're finished
this maybe wasn't the smartest idea in
the world
you'll starve before she can kill you
now i'm going to the supermarket oh oh
[\h__\h]
no weapons here
only nice things
and friendship
i want to hear a sorry
loppy maury i didn't mean to hurt your
feelings
oh wow you really just kind of [\h__\h]
everywhere huh
white thoroughbred oh so that is the
name of the horse huh
hey buddy you want to take me to the
supermarket so i can get some food
my man
you want to take me to the supermarket
just real quick
thanks man
let's see
the food's over here and it's a safe
place if i do head over to the safe
place she'll be forced
to
ally what
what
it's stuck
you barbecue my ducky knife
it's a trick
there will be no peace
oh [\h__\h] hold on
oh boy
all right use this
i'm in trouble
i'm in trouble all right
but i have mushrooms
for that we might just be fine
i will get to the safe zone
almost 1v1 to a pig why
oh my god
peace was never real sounds like
hardcore copium right there
hardcore copium
[Music]
i have everything i need for peace now
a peaceful apology
from you know who
now off we go to the safe zone mushrooms
need to let me gather these
all right horsey we can go again
okay
off i go
peace is all around us everyone you just
can't see it
not all the time but it wins in the end
peace wins in the end
he's coming for you now cool meet me in
the safe zone
we can do a fair trade all i ask for is
an exchange of words
i was gunning that board down that's a
boar it's different
it's not like you know my fellow
teammates
it's just it's not the same
eat the mushrooms
all right let's
move get a move on they're going to be
hot on our tail
oh boy
oh boy oh boy
i know that attack helicopter isn't gura
but it still spooks
me and welcome to the safe zone
can you imagine if i didn't go to the
safe zone how silly that would be
come on now
i wouldn't be that foolish
if they want a barbecue though i mean go
for it
see
picture time e11 oh that's cute
i will not be participating however
because it is too dangerous i'm wanted
i'm on the run
what if i just gambled all of gerda's
scrap
that wouldn't be all right that's not
okay
come on now i'd never do that
i'm not that messed up come on
too much fun it's a little too much fun
hey man
hello
hey can you help me with something sure
why not
i can't right now
come back later if you can help me out
all right where is the food
come on i remember there was a food
place nearby
don't you lie to me
was it here i wonder
hi do you have food yes
i need this i need the tuna
for tuna
babaroo
it actually is group photo time though
you're missing out
why does it have to be outside of the
safe zone
[Music]
get in the picture
if i get in that picture hold on
e11
if i get in that [\h__\h] picture
let's see
one sec
um
hide the money maybe
hold on
i will
and then i'll go
do not tell gura where the money is
please
okay i'll hide it at the roulette hold
on i'm trying to remember where it is
it's up there isn't it yeah
little box i could put it in i wish they
had a box here
if i put it in the recycling machine
will it despawn
hide it all on the 20 oh god
time to gamble
gonna have to just drop it and go
all right
let's see
go to e11 for the damn photo
all right um
at this point guys i'm gonna stop
streaming so um thank you very much for
coming today
uh i appreciate it um i'm gonna get off
the stream now and um i'll go i'll go
talk to them myself later and uh yeah so
thanks um
awesome
so see you later bye guys
you