foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
oh
nice nice uh transition yeah thank you
thank you thank you thank you
I think clean this room oh it's um
it's Eden
Eden
Eden's also the one who made your room
yeah it's been looking so much for
others now he's got the time for me oh
you're ready Stephen
it's so nice here I like the light and
all
so pretty
yeah wait can you can you move your head
a little bit like to the side there's
like a window thing
like a window thing at the center
[Music]
wow p-files everywhere oh yes it's
gorgeous thank you so much
and welcome Kiara did you say yet
yeah there we go yay
yeah you know guys we wanted to do this
classroom since a very long time
and
Kiara low what do you mean here alone
oh
no honey it doesn't sell she doesn't
sound low I don't think maybe I'm maybe
I'm maybe maybe he means my height oh
maybe
how tall do you want to be I'll Grant
your wish
do you want to be as tall how do you how
tall you want to be
it looks like I'm standing up for
something
bring me down okay I'm ascending or
decent now I'm descending yes lower
lower lower lower lower lower
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yes well I'm
watching it on YouTube so my reaction is
a little bit late okay okay okay okay
okay if people are saying you sound kind
of low that's so weird though
I think it I'm just thinking
[Music]
let me um
hard to hear Kiara oh my God for real oh
Maybe
try meowing again
[Music]
okay I think that's enough
yay and Cat
Nana can I just say before we start yeah
how gorgeous you look thank you you know
I had a feeling uh before you know I
told you right you know I have a feeling
that this tree is going to be a little
bit tangenty you know just a little bit
of feeling you know
we're gonna talk about your kimono so
pretty and your hair I love the it's
such a strong contrast not only in your
hair but your overlord outfit has so
much contrast and the black black
streaks they're so cool I've seen like
I've seen some girls doing
um they dye their hair like only the
tips of it make it they make it black
and the rest is like a bright color it
looks so cool
and I love the braids and then you know
they're like a little bit not messy but
you know when I make braids like that on
my hair then I pull out a little bit the
streaks so that it gives this like messy
look now really messy but like volume
you know it's so nice and I really like
the hat and I really like the the p-file
feather on there it's so pretty yeah and
then I like the Tonto necklace and I
also really like your your fluffy scarf
and like your gloves and I like the
whole color theme going on because it's
like so unusual but it's so cool it
gives me like a retro but also modern
Vibe and you look like a like a really
rich lady I like it
thank you you know I really really love
kimono I really like your twin tail I
really you know you know I was I was
watching I was watching your showcase
like I was just skimming through like I
watched it again before before this
collab yeah you know what no no no like
just now just now just now like I can
lift I can lift you like I like the
pattern I like the pattern that you have
under actually yeah I can't I can't I
can't pull up anymore because uh it's
gonna you have no legs here but is that
is
okay I can put you down
so now we have a matching outfit I know
do you guys see like you know actually
we had a little talk about like hey KR
like actually brought it up like hey uh
like because when I'm like having my
kimono and stuff like hey like would you
think it would be cute if we had like
something matching or something she was
like yeah I think they're pretty cool
you know
but you didn't match anything to me
The Joker it kind of matches it kinda
incidents did you even ask for a choker
or did you just get it I think like it's
a
telepathy like I forgot if I asked
because it's been like a while but and
then listen and then the twin Tails we
have I have braids and a red circle next
one Tails I have braids in my other
outfit in my casual ones yeah then I can
match that one as well
that makes no sense that matches not at
all shush so picky nah nah okay listen
guys you had an opportunity to match
with me and you missed it
[Music]
like I don't know
wait look at that face right now what
what
I think there's some bug because
on your side on the stream I see I have
Angry Eyebrows but a happy mouth and
I've never had this before because on my
side my eyebrows are angry and my mouth
is angry
you know you know what I had like I was
like so happy because uh you know I have
the sad face right I have the sad face
like okay I'm gonna I'm gonna look sad
now I'm gonna send it
[Music]
oh
look at this I have sad eyes but I
said nice but like I'm smiling
look at this
but that's normal for you no no it's not
normally I shouldn't be able to do this
and then like
yeah it only happens when I uh you know
when I do certain things but I I guess
this is like a sweet secret emote
accessible to everybody
I love this expression though right now
I think I want to keep it for the whole
screen because I undo it then I'll never
get this face back me too I'm gonna be
like hey
[Laughter]
it's
foxy expression I feel like what I have
right now
[Music]
okay
you know you know a lot of Indonesian
right you know tonjo
um
really for real I haven't been teaching
you see that's why I'm here to make up
with makeup to it is that what it's
called yeah make it up to you
makeup
make it up to you that's what it's
called gosh I can't English see that's
why I'm teaching Indonesia instead of
English I'm gonna teach you um since we
are already like both in kimono I think
it would be nice if we both like learned
some uh travel related words first is
because you know maybe you want to go on
a kimono trip together and second maybe
if you want to take a little vacation
somewhere I don't know oh yes oh yes I'm
wanting to visit you girls over there
forever I need to do it you please
please please please
do they like in Indonesia would I have
problems if I don't speak Indonesian and
it depends where you are I think like
not really like for example if you're
like in the city area or something I
don't think you will have problems at
all okay so they speak some English
there yes yes they do speak they do
speak so it's no problem
so in like touristy areas yeah in like
touristy areas and like in general I
guess if you're in the city you know we
have this sub language called daxel in
which you like mix English and
Indonesian so if you know if a country
has that kind of thing you'll be fine
speaking English I guess
okay okay hopefully I can learn some
words so they can be like oh Indonesian
Jose Indonesia
thank you okay in that case I actually
don't feel insulted because it's really
not Jose but in Japanese you know when
they tell me nihongo Jose and I feel a
little bit like insulted because because
it's like uh
everybody you say Joseph to people who
are not Joseph at all that's the thing
yeah like I'm not special you know you
want that special treatment right
yeah okay anyways one thing to kfp if
you're here please take many screenshots
of this face because you'll never see it
again yeah
[Music]
okay so
Indonesian class
ring thank you I like I like writing I
don't know that's that's a really weird
thing to say I like writing
but you like drawing too I do I do we
did that drawing club last time right we
took us together
yeah what you need to draw us together
in kimono sure I can do it right now and
we're never gonna have the class we have
one we have one hour guys we have one
hour and this is what we're doing longer
than an hour don't worry I guess so I
guess so dying it's not a classroom it's
an art room
[Music]
yeah I really enjoyed our dry oh my God
I'm gonna stop looking sad because like
wait oh shoot hold on face
look at this cute oh cute cute that
feather it looks like you have like a
fox ear okay let's see let's make it
more uh let's make it more feathery than
like this yeah
and then we have fur
ther
[Music]
dude yeah the fan right you have the fan
right
yeah but mine doesn't move mine's not as
fancy as yours
[Music]
mine mine just is still but it has a
funny pattern yeah I guess so
it's okay it's too I think it's too
cluttered we don't need to show the fat
I like your hands though it looks like
you're about to like steal the
watermelon
I don't like my hands but I can at least
uh do my hands only one hand I can oh
bring in like this it's like well what
pose is that what pose is that it's like
I guess
um so uh when I introduce myself I'm
like I
said
I thought it was like when you see
something really cute on the internet on
the street and you're like ah donkey's
cute you know
okay I guess it's also a pledge of
allegiance a pledge of allegiance my
allegiance
[Music]
I swear
banana and yet she will cheat on me what
oh
huh
what she said no he's cheat on me no
when
mention all the times I cheat on you
didn't you talk about feet with Gouda
yeah well do you want to talk about feet
with me
oh
okay we're gonna start it's been 20
minutes do you know okay something I
can't wait to learn something yeah we're
now here okay okay um first I'm Gonna
Make You Pick how to refer to yourself I
right Kiara
um there's actually a lot of food
okay that's fast
I can't hear that all the time
especially when I listen to Kobo because
she speaks so much Indonesian she's
always like yeah
like
um so it's the Dynamics kind of
different but it's um
it's kind of cute but not very it's not
so gendered I guess like Saya is the
most formal Aku is like informal kind of
cute if girls say it but if guys say it
it's kind of weird I don't know Norms
are weird like that and gue is like the
most casual you know
[Music]
just because I hear it so much which one
do you use
uh it depends I feel like when I talk to
people like I say Aku but there are some
moments where I say but like I think Aku
is cuter definitely oh okay I I say when
I act like antagonist yeah
I'm happy that for once I'm not the one
mispronouncing words like what's the
difference just saying I always ask
stuff like hey yeah how do you pronounce
this this or that like pacifist and
pacifist like because it's Pacific Ocean
but it's pacifist like cows
I guess because it's a Pacific Ocean
yeah but Pacific
means that is all on on the English
language for being stupid
yeah this is very important
[Music]
means not
or like no
and I am means
chicken
very important important phrase for you
I think
I am
ready
I am oh
yeah and then what's your hobby I want
to like give you like three sentences to
introduce yourself or something
watching Netflix
okay Aku
[Music]
Suka is like Suki you know like
I remember them yeah
is watch
Netflix
[Music]
Netflix yeah so this is like if you can
replace this with like anime or whatever
like an anime
you just censor Netflix yeah
but only in writing not insane because
they gotta they gotta pay me for more
marketing you know
they will never I know
I like um playing well I like cuddling
with my cats ah oh my gosh this is
improper Indonesia but this is how I say
all the time uh mine is like play
yes
[Music]
it is like cats this is not proper
Indonesian but Kuching is cat yeah good
thing why is it not proper Indonesian
because it's like if you want to say
playing with cats you somehow need to
say like mine Sama Kuching or something
Sama is with you know I like playing
with cats and then but like sometimes I
say it's improper like
yeah okay
[Music]
yeah I also like
I guess is more proper yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yes yes yes yes
yeah we bonded through our love for cats
[Music]
with a
okay
did you take notes we can take
screenshot yeah very efficient you know
like in classrooms yeah like just face
it you know it's more efficient to take
the whole like photo of the Whiteboard
and study at home yeah
your writing is better than mine anyway
so okay you prefer your writing okay
clean the board
and then next toe I'm gonna if we're
traveling we're gonna have to be
interacting with people I think right so
we're gonna uh teach you about how to
say excuse me oh yes okay like Sunni
message sorry
it's um as you see in Japanese
are kind of different usage but in
Indonesian is it the same or also very
different
um there is the same word like that
that's like same word but different
meaning for Gomez
but uh wait what I don't know you can
say either uh maaf
math is also means uh it also can mean
but it's used interchangeably and there
is also this word permisi
now let me see it's like a permission
yeah yeah permission yeah permission
like and then math is like sorry you
know when you say like English hey sorry
but you know right
[Music]
let me see I'll remember because it's so
close to like permission okay okay yeah
it almost sounds like I say yeah
I usually teach you super casual but uh
can I uh can I may I ask a question a
boy
it's like ham
um
ask
oh yeah yeah
put the power in yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
nanya and then what do you want to ask
for example
[Music]
oh many things
where is
and then everything where is Hotel
oh yeah yeah okay maybe uh question mark
question mark question mark
mama
yeah where ah
oh okay so Hotel dimana yeah Hotel uh
for example uh Rainey where is
the toilet yeah
perfect yeah it's literally the you know
rainy doco if you guys see me not
starting the stream I swear guys I was
like starting the stream and then like I
was just like chilling and Cara was like
yo you haven't started the trailer one
for real because you have to like press
two buttons and I'm like I almost forget
sometimes
yeah for me it's
um also a problem like I press both
buttons but then when I switch out of
the YouTube tab too quick then it
doesn't work I doesn't register okay
okay yeah
some they're always like okay
yeah oh my God always happens and then
when like some chat to say oh yeah rain
is downloading the game right now I'm
like oh [\h__\h] that means
earlier too they were saying yeah rain
is still downloading Kiara
it's like an ongoing meme like you know
when I'm doing that I'm still like not
you know I'm still downloading the game
okay yeah where for example toilet Kiara
or like raining anything
by the way this torrent is like
restaurant it's very easy yeah
[Music]
here's the order if you want a chicken
restaurant uh chicken restaurant right
chicken restaurant all right and then
it's actually restaurant I am so you
kind of switch it yeah
on chicken yeah
yes and then
if somebody watch and if somebody says
like that you can answer like d hatiku
it means in my in my heart
it's a really crappy answer it's a
secret yeah but yes in my heart
Nina that was very cute so it's not the
toilet is in your car yes
because sometimes like because sometimes
like people yeah I think if you can know
this people would be like oh my God she
knows it
um
yes
and then oh uh uh what else what else
maybe
um
yes it's like shorts it's like my heart
uh-huh in my heart exactly and then or
maybe uh you want to go somewhere
um
uh I don't know that yeah wait can does
the same thing work for like
[Music]
I Sayang is like love and care like love
care my cats
[Music]
let me take a screenshot yes okay okay
chocolate
all right all right
okay I got it let's go oh someone's like
Indonesia
I don't feel insulted being told that at
this stage I'm happy being told that
yeah
now it's like do you know yeah yeah like
a lip service yes now it's just sit
there just trying to kiss my ass
uh and do you want to go shopping do you
do a lot of shopping
foreign
would you recommend me to go shopping in
Indonesia is there a good stuff in
Indonesia I don't know I think like
there's like a bunch of like local stuff
maybe at least for local stuff that you
only you know that's only available in
Indonesia and then maybe like souvenirs
ah yeah souvenir souvenirs
what's the population souvenir I don't
know
like
yeah it's like actually a pattern and
there's like a lot of patterns yeah
right yeah remember you girls talking
about it or like
um when there was like a outfit reveal
for Indonesian girls outfits you all had
like batik pattern on your outfits I
remember that yeah yeah
yeah yeah like this
[Laughter]
you know uh I think like it's called
something else in other places but it's
like this you know like you use the head
and they're like oh
it's this thing and then you can also do
like
think I don't even think it's Indonesian
it's like clackers clackers
yeah but like so it's gained popularity
in Indonesia like all of a sudden I even
like bought one just because you know I
like why not
I mean suddenly your handwriting is from
a different person
not too sure
okay well if you want to buy souvenir or
batik or lato whatever you ask them you
point that the thing is sometimes like
uh you don't have the price attached
right for example if you go to like a
more special store yeah you can say how
much is this is
but
[Music]
again yeah
yeah
the suffix yeah is like the yeah so like
how much
is how much like foreign
[Music]
yeah
and then uh you can say
you can say this
[Music]
but not recommended
[Laughter]
I can hear it from your tone
yeah yeah yeah like hey bro how much is
this but maybe if you need to like
establish like a buddy buddy feel like
sometimes they like it right so yeah
Choi is like hey buddy you know and then
like yo how much
but like not very recommended
if you're in a polite setting but you
know I think like it could be nice you
know when you talk to the ID girls and
then they're like uh showing you stuff
to shop and you can say and they will be
like oh
[Laughter]
blown that they'll end up paying for it
yeah of course you should use this
yeah okay let me okay save this okay I
got it I got it
am I getting a test at the end or am I
safe and you're safe you're safe okay
because I don't think I I need some time
to practice you know yeah sure sure
you can maybe I'll ask you to like
construct the sentences but you can take
a look at your notes it's all right
something about my cat
yeah
it was
[Music]
toy
yeah so the letter c we usually say like
the chi CH you know
um like just like that
um
did you take a screenshot
thank you
what's thank you in Indonesian again
thanks Bry
this is not see like you already know so
I'm teaching you the the maybe the more
casual one
it's you say it's uh so fast
[Music]
a few words I've heard before
you can save this this wait sorry can I
I want to be canceled but was that also
Indonesian
yeah is Indonesian
was that the hello uh that's good
morning
good morning okay so
[Music]
it's if it's night time here you say
islamath malam
[Music]
is like uh it's like evening Bros you
know
[Music]
what's up Bros
[Laughter]
I need this on a new slide greetings
okay greetings goodbyes and stuff like
that okay oh
mm-hmm
okay
greeting right good
morning
[Music]
good morning
I think I know that from nity Joel yeah
even this is your one of my favorite
animals oh so much good taste uh evening
in the night night is like oyasumi right
okay okay good morning afternoon evening
night good morning is
Salama
buggy
[Music]
um
but I have the feeling
yeah yeah yeah yeah she does she does
afternoon or more like noon starts like
two I mean 12.
um
and good evening is like
[Music]
so there's like two types of evenings I
think like uh because like evening is
kind of more like closer to night right
but for us if it's like already like
four to six p.m there's like an
in-between here
four to six you say sorry
[Music]
can I not just say the whole day said
I'm a buggy
I think like it's acceptable because
like you know what they say like if you
wake up everything every time it's buggy
you know I know I know people who always
say Ohio in Japanese what time it is
right for real
yes
[Music]
good night Mama missed uh my mom is good
evening okay night is this is weird
because like means like sleep cause like
good night is just like oh yes to me
right you know
foreign
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
and then except for tea door you can
even like omit the mat and then as long
as you know people know the context and
it's like nice I can be like yo BAGI
Kiara or something and it would yeah yes
[Music]
it's like if you yeah
yeah and this is nice word
[Music]
um
yeah
different
it's it's the same it's just like a turu
it's like a regional language but these
days in the internet a lot of people say
turu if they say sleep
door
time for sleep
riding while I close my eyes
yes I am going down
I accidentally I accidentally said uh
like a bad word
no no bad word out of context it's just
like uh you know just you know when you
say like the f word or something but
it's not really it's not really the f
word but if you say like the f word to
like emphasize something you know you
don't need to be rude yeah that's what I
just said
I I forgot I was laughing and I said it
didn't forget
is dog
ah hunting yeah so it's like you like
cats but you also like dogsing
[Music]
I love cats and dogs I can teach you the
eyes and
I wouldn't say that I wouldn't say that
do you not like dogs
I don't hate them but I would not go out
of my way to say
maybe if you're in a conversation with
like some some person like you're you're
shopping and like oh yeah I like dogs
I am I mean what I only like big dogs
[Music]
big Angie
the sun is big
is small
dislike
[Music]
why
because
they are too hyperactive and they go
like
yeah and they look like they I know some
of them their eyes are too big for their
body
you're so judgey you can't just say that
you're gonna get canceled
canceled by the dog
you don't know if the dog is watching
vtubers you don't know if the dogs
watching the classroom like you know
they will ever know yeah you know maybe
we have dogs in the chat we don't know
I think I mean I mean some small dogs
can be cute too yeah yeah yeah yeah but
normally I feel like they're two
um too active too aggressive like
aggressive and like them you know they
really just push and push and push you
don't like it aggressive
if a cat goes like you know
[Music]
I'm happy but if a dog does it no no ah
okay okay well well well well well I
guess uh if you want to be compatible
with Chihuahua and you're a dog you just
have to be less noisy I think
or or be more like
yes yes yes yes very nice oh kanapa is
also nice
is why if you want to be
curious and somebody you know just like
makes a statement you can be like why
but why
you know
what does that mean I don't know
[Laughter]
tell me
yeah yeah
tell me why
did you um take a screenshot I'm gonna
erase this yeah
what's yes yeah
or
[Music]
you can choose God
yes yeah yeah okay all right yes
cooking because in Japanese it's no yeah
yeah yeah right right right
wait it's just G alone no it's so rude
though if you text someone this they
will understand but it's so rude but I
think it's funny you should use it you
should use it on the ID girls
or like yay
it's just Y and jeans yeah you are NG
you should use it on the ID girl
sometimes okay okay I'm trying to
remember yeah assorted yes and no guys
guys guys guys do you have any like if
if Kiara talks to ID Girls what do you
think I should teach her
like
what do you think if Molly ever asks me
if I want to marry her I say just get
thank you I've only ever asked me if I
want to marry her I just say get get
yeah
yeah yeah but like if it's like if it's
like through um uh if it's through like
verbal voice you just say Gap but like
if you're by text you just like capital
G is fine
okay
the the k for okay in English too I mean
it's not rude but unless it's in the
root context when someone you know tells
you something and you're just like okay
whatever okay whatever it's true yeah
yeah yeah yeah
all right I'm not really listening I
don't really care okay and I want to
teach you numbers but do you really want
to study numbers no okay let's skip that
I don't know what we can study then
basic phrases maybe
if you wanna do you wanna do you wanna
say haggle like for example if
something's too expensive
yeah I think generally I don't have the
the personality to haggle because I'm
like too scared and that's so weird if I
go there as a tourist I feel like maybe
I should be haggling because maybe they
want to wrap me up yeah yeah I don't
know I don't want to like
you know yeah yeah it's like I get it I
get it but I will give you if I'm not
alone if I'm with someone from the area
then maybe I have more confidence but
then I just let that person do it yeah
for me yeah yeah yeah so you like um
just so you know
you doing no I'm also really bad at it
I'm also really bad I'm just like oh
like I know like it takes you know like
is it pretty normal though
um in certain settings yes like of
course if you're like in the department
store you can't haggle but like in like
some you know in some other places like
even like online marketplaces
oh my God you say you little [\h__\h] a lot
so I can say
yeah you little shits like
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
see guys I'm not teaching her like bad
words because she's she's already like
saying you little [\h__\h] all the time so I
thought say that many times to my
viewers yeah she she says that all the
time you want me to say it
maybe okay
for legal reasons and so I don't get in
trouble this is rude
don't don't say unless
unless your Chihuahua your Chihuahua
yeah so you can say
um
was chicken right yeah yeah yeah I am
chicken I am chicken I am not Siam yeah
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
I hope will not see this stream and
smiling it's okay it's okay we need a
little sprinkle of spice you know
yeah yeah
I don't mind yeah you know like I have a
story like I was a you never remember
that uh was it the I don't remember if
it was like the sports best silver or
something uh but I was like practicing
with like oh it was the ID thing and
then I was practicing with like Mikko
Senpai and stuff and then I didn't know
that they were streaming so I was just
like teaching them bad words and then I
only knew like a lot later that they
were streaming I think I've heard of
that yeah
click
they're gonna be like oh they know where
are you teaching everyone bad words
I didn't mean to it was off it was off
stream to me but I guess not to them
yeah but I guess yeah I also thought
like the other uh the other girls like
if it's like related I will teach like
for example like you little [\h__\h] you say
that a lot so I will give you like an ID
equivalent
yes yes yes
this literally means this literally
means anjing like you dog you know
yeah yeah like dog is like uh an insult
in here even the dogs are so cute right
hmm
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
no no I like I like like big fluffy dogs
so yes
big fluffy dogs are cute you like them
[Laughter]
[Music]
what other words do you study when
you're do you learn when you're
traveling
um maybe if you're in the airport I
think dimana is already good oh
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
um
you're thinking it's like a filler word
what is it I wonder
oh yeah it's kind of like a filler word
like if you're thinking of something
what was it again
and then oh oh you you can say if you're
in trouble you can say
[Music]
come on
I was gonna I was gonna teach you to say
I'm not guilty
I don't need that I wouldn't get myself
in such a situation no you never know
perfect huh
[Music]
no no no and no good and then we can uh
Aku h
I'm not guilty no I don't need that I'm
gonna teach you anyways uh guilty
.com yeah this is not yeah
I'm not guilty
in case I end up in court yeah
just in case I'll help you with my
gaming knowledge I will be your attorney
[Music]
if you want to go to the ah to the beach
Maybe
yes [\h__\h] maybe you want to go
snorkeling in the future again
yeah so nice right
um
I I uh
um remember I think I told you you know
I want to go to Bali right yeah yeah
yeah and and I think we said that like
you can come with me right yeah yeah
yeah uh no
um I have a problem why why why
a couple days ago
um
Kelly was you know she was supposed to
go to
yeah yeah just traveling and I think she
was supposed to go to Bali and then she
kind of had to cancel her whole rest of
her whole vacation and then I I was
trying to cheer her up like I was
listening to her and all that and then
she was like mama you know what I don't
want to travel alone anymore I realized
traveling alone is boring and so on and
so she was like yeah how about you know
next time we go to Bali and I'm like
yeah yeah yeah yeah of course
say no how can I say no okay so maybe we
have to go together all three of us but
that's fun too that's fun too yeah no
problem but you understand the situation
I am in right I mean we can go separate
times but of course that's kind of weird
too two times to Bali
I assist together that's okay the more
the merrier I can yes okay I like that
no Cali was feeling down because her
whole vacation got messed up and she was
like I don't want to travel alone
anymore
see we can invite Cali to the party yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
it means I want
to go to Bali to go to yeah to go to
Bali Bali you can say
Maldives so that's why I want to go to
the mountains
I really want to go there again too yeah
maybe check out like the you know the
different you know different Resorts and
stuff yeah I was thinking no maybe like
November December
for real we have we can't go again at
the same time we went like yeah
the proper time November December is a
good time apparently oh okay okay okay
but I think it's also most expensive
yeah and it's also really busy
so sad and then Maldives and then for
example it's not only places you can
just say I want to go to the toilet or
like
or something who are like yeah Mao is
one so like
I want to go to the restaurant or say
where do you want to go
[Music]
okay
Indonesia yeah yes
Indonesia yes yes yes yes
like earlier I wanna go to your house
your heart
[Music]
what what
that was so natural again
apparently there's this thing where when
people like say something sweet flirty
to me and I I don't notice on
immediately changed the topic but I I
just realized I need one specific phrase
oh what is that I need I need to ask
um is it spicy
food ah yeah you can't handle it yes yes
yes this is very important for you
or you can be like it but this guy
question mark
is it spicy or no basically is it spicy
or like uh or like ini this is ini what
does
this like this is spicy
[Music]
um
can you say a word again but that's like
the E is like the same as barsala or
like the others
uh you know Indonesian people will say
it's not spicy but it's still spicy so
you need to you need to make sure that
like there's no chili or whatever so be
careful good when they say no can I ask
really oh okay really really
[Music]
thank you
okay
really is it really is no this is if you
want to be like a more up to date with
like the culture the web culture
is
you know like literally means is it yes
but it's like it's like really you know
it's like for real you know for real
okay
okay we can practice like hey Kiara
um okay uh this is the restaurant I
wanna order this uh spicy meatball do
you want the same thing
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
iron
water how about sparkling and
non-sparkling because like when I go to
supermarket or so and I look for the
water and all the water bottles I it
doesn't say in English if it's sparkling
or non-sparkling
we don't I don't think sparkling water
is a is a very common in here and yeah
yeah yeah so I think it will say sparkly
water
yeah like the the right word is is
really long
it's a carbonated
[Music]
I feel like if I read that I could like
even guess it yeah yeah
and this is like butter is like
possession so like carbonated yeah
carbonated carbonara carbonate water and
water is yeah so I guess if it's not
written uh you can assume that it's like
proper I don't know do you like
sparkling water
ah Still Water yeah still water's best I
mean I guess it's not common here for a
reason
carbonated spaghetti if it's like
Coca-Cola also ah of course it should be
carbonated yeah I guess of course of
course of course okay
[Music]
[Applause]
can't wait I need to take another
screenshot now that you wrote some extra
things here yes yes
I
didn't follow you guys
[Music]
who are you talking to Elena I'm talking
to chat while you're taking screenshot
on carbonate circola I'm asking them
what I should teach you because we have
a reflex
[Music]
a movie
who taught you that for Google Google
you're typing something I thought what
are you doing I thought you were gonna
like message me something
means more
[Applause]
but did you take notes
no no you have the pen and the paper no
you take the note I want to change the
new [\h__\h] no you know the notes
okay you can look at the archive it's
fine
yes okay um I mean I took a screenshot
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
uh guys for okay last thing I should
teach her we're gonna do like uh you
know ask the audience kind of thing what
should I teach her before we end this
session
hello oh my God you know
yeah from Hollow here yeah hello
yeah all I well isn't it it's like hello
for hallucinations yeah Halo is like uh
hallucinations it does mean that but
it's kind of like when you're like you
know when you call someone
you're kind of saying like
you know like you're so delusional yeah
and gws is just get well soon yeah get
well soon for like this state of Halo in
know Ah that's just English yes that's
just English but like in this case like
you use it to like support your Halu
accusation like
gws yeah get with s
give us very nice
in German we also like the letter W we
just say V oh yeah
we say it where okay it's way too I know
W is too long gws dude it's like what so
I just say yes yeah nice yes yes yes yes
yes yes
[Music]
you know the bird that always go
no me I'll show you later now okay you
go
yeah okay okay yes yes yes yes okay wait
um okay and then okay this is actually
very important so if you're so excited
and you want to tell me if you have
bought your tickets you say
UDA
ticket
for the concert or what concert or
anything any ticket it means I have have
or already
but
Billy tickets good oh that's that's very
specific yeah no because I want to hear
it from you
when you end up seeing me
yeah
well when I when am I gonna see you
later I don't know see me soon okay
[Laughter]
okay we can go
huh
yeah
are you calling me little [\h__\h] what
because you didn't tell me about coming
to Japan and then all we had is one
evening to see each other no listen
listen like I thought I did yeah yeah
yeah you know what happened I was like
shocked when she doesn't know you know
[Laughter]
arms in karaoke and I also took your
hand when we were like going outside and
stuff I need more yeah more more more I
miss my Lena yeah we can we can we can
link arms more and bite
uh you know what it means
I always say that to everybody like by
the way did you know
instead of language can you like only in
the end like is there anything like
really yabai and G that I'm not supposed
to do
like culture wise or so I don't know
I don't know you should I think it's
like I don't know guys
like I would say pretty standard stuff
but maybe it's not still I don't know
just be just people
don't eat with left hand
though
but how would they know
they don't know no no no no no the same
thing the thing is okay it might be
considered like the right hand it's like
ooh the good hand but honestly
if you're left-handed like what are you
supposed to do is whatever and people
don't judge guys don't scare her
wait so only for eating or for
everything can I like not pick up a
bottle or so with my left hand
guys
Just Fur you're scaring her it's based
okay listen see it's based on like the
you know thing it's like if you like the
right hand is like the good hand and
like the the left hand is maybe like not
so good hand or whatever like so you you
shake people's hand or like you give
it's kind of like you have to give
scissors like this right always with the
right hand though no matter if you left
it it's always the right hand if you
shake hands yeah I guess so yeah but
that's all right
yeah like you're you're left-handed you
know I feel like if it's right-handed
people if they use their left hand
they're gonna like they're doing it on
purpose you know I don't I don't even
pay attention that much you know because
I don't really care about it and it's
rude but if you're left-handed it's okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah if
you're left-handed and people know like
it's okay
um definitely I will have to like put a
Post-It on my forehead that says I'm
laughing like slap it on you know
me how to say it in Indonesian then I'm
left-handed I'll just everywhere I go
before I do something I say Sorry by the
way I'm left-handed so uh now I think
like through your mannerisms people
might be able to tell so that's all
right
[Music]
Indonesia today like when they raise
children do they
um like teach them to do everything with
the right hand like writing and
everything uh nope not really because
like if you're left-handed then what are
you gonna do like um I have a share of
like friends who are left-handed and
like people though to from if you do it
early you can train them right
[Music]
[Applause]
but I wouldn't really do that because I
don't like it either someone said don't
touch people's heads
don't touch it
do you touch random people's hands I
didn't think I had to say that
but like people sometimes you know
they're like uh I wanna pet pet your
head like Inna Ena is currently she said
it herself Ina is currently giving good
out daily head pets
Indonesia head pets would be rude I
don't know but I think it's like no no
CCC is giving like girl a daily hat pass
that means like it's with consent right
and it's like they know each other well
and it's with consent but if you just
like go up to a stranger and be like I
think that's kind of weird now I
wouldn't like it I don't like it even
even from a friend I don't like my head
to be petted you don't like it okay
noted but see it's uh yeah it just
depends you know it's very personal what
about are there like any specific like
hand signs that for example the peace
sign the middle finger
[Music]
puppy like just pointing ah I think in
in for example in Japan it's pretty rude
to point at someone yes yes yes I think
like I don't know I try to avoid
pointing I guess just to be safe because
like
you know but I
um depends on the context I think I
would point
at things I think that's okay but
pointing at people I don't know
like oh obviously none of the bad
context like haha look at that person
they look so stupid haha the more like
oh hey look there's Elena and then I
Point At You
there she is I think uh I I think maybe
you can I don't know it's very the thing
is see Indonesia is very big and I think
like there's a lot of Customs either
even like ones that I'm not aware of and
maybe something is okay here something
is not okay there something is not okay
but in other places it's okay yeah so I
guess don't really worry too much
yeah I think don't worry about it as
long as you
um maybe apply the standard stuff you
should be okay question mark very vague
I know well what about what about uh
blowing my nose
uh I would avoid to do that in public
[Music]
okay in Austria we don't care we just do
it because if it has to leave your nose
then it leaves your nose but yeah but I
mean if you have to that nobody's gonna
be like ew freaking gross nobody's gonna
do that I just avoid it if I can
[Music]
yeah of course if a tissue where else
would I live your clothes
they need to tell her about smiling
culture in Indonesia excuse me smiling
culture what's smiling culture smiling
at people dude what's smiling culture
I think it should be I think it should
be common set not common sense I think
it's normal to smile at everyone right
[Music]
well I would be a little creeped out
maybe if everyone smiles and stares at
me though no no not like that not like
that what is it do I have something on
my face I don't know I don't I don't
know I don't know smiling culture you
guys are telling me things I don't know
I'm so insecure now yeah I think it
depends on the country yeah I guess
smiling is good will you will you smile
at me
happen in there I can not not smile at
you
[Music]
are you are you a real Indonesian Angelo
so that's how you guys know I'm real
oh yes I don't know I just called them
names
[Music]
[Laughter]
just called them names
oh my God Kiara Kiara Kiara look at the
time
what's with crony what's with Chris
where's Chrome wait don't you have a
little bit of something after this
uh
uh chroni di Mana dimana crony
Divana cloney
oh member stream
ing
I miss you too
I felt like you know the stream was like
half studying but we also had like a
little like talk and you know I'm not
gonna lie I'm like I'm I'm like allowing
it because I also wanted to talk to you
it's like you know we're like busy so
it's like when we're together we always
want to talk you know we have to watch
more animal videos
what's the name of the little animal I
don't even remember anymore I don't know
but I'm sure there's plenty of animal
videos on Netflix yeah yeah oh my God I
want to watch animal videos please yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I will come to watch
animal video yeah you will like you will
go and visit me and it's like oh what's
the agenda watch animal videos with me
no but like I want to travel more this
year you know and I need to I need to
see it I need to see Elena's place and
Dana's cat and yes everything you know I
want to see
and please do please do please do we
need to stay in the different places of
the world different cultures and eat
different food yeah yeah yes yes yes I
also want to like go more places I still
haven't visited you uh-huh yes I would
have known if you would have I would
have seen you I think
I'm waiting I will wait for me wait for
me maybe we will have an accidental
exchange you you go to Austria I go to
Indonesia oh no no
Diwana
the Indonesia
now hopefully that will not happen so in
order for that not to happen Dana we
have to communicate clearly okay yes no
more of that you didn't know
yes
okay well it's been a fun talk I hope
you learned we we didn't teach you much
but I'm just really happy that I could
have this opportunity finally you know
and I also teach a lot of people like
English and German in my streams yeah
and
um I feel like it makes no sense to
teach too much because there's no way
they're gonna remember all of it and
also when you travel in the end you're
an either with someone who speaks a
language or you have like Google
translate or whatever or yeah
speak some English anyway over there no
you know most of the time it just needs
to be a few words and yeah and even
those words are so simple that probably
English would suffice too yeah sometimes
you can be like oh yeah toilet toilet
toilet and then they just know yeah yeah
yeah
yeah so I think this is fine but it's
important to know that I can say a
cookie DAL to get out of everything yeah
yeah yeah yes yes okay
[Music]
um that's it by the way when are we
singing again Kiara
[Music]
I think we should revive it
let's revive it let's revive it
[Music]
also because the last one was on my
channel Animado yeah
so if anything it's on you Dana yeah
okay fine I'll do it I'll do it with you
I love you
um yeah wow I never I never said that to
chat and oops now the cat is out of the
bag
okay yeah guys actually that was I was
organizing it but now that she has
worked I want to yeah exactly and then
we never did continue okay you know what
let's do it
[Music]
what about this
okay
I don't wanna I Don't Wanna Stop The
Stream but I have to we'll meet again
soon okay I'll see you
your flower is so cute by the way
um thank you not as cute as your
everything
ah cute thank you for giving me the
opportunity to teach you
available so last minute because I
needed something to do yeah I thought
like you know see I was actually like
sick recently too so like I was all like
okay if I don't say yes I don't know
when we're gonna like have it ever you
know so we're just like okay let's do it
now nice
okay any any any messages you want to
say any message you want to say to Chad
before we leave
um
what are you typing
[Music]
thank you
any last words
okay
Spirit Alive let's go
three Papa
um everybody
thank you very much for your attention
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Music]
foreign