[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
da
m
[Music]
don't
down
[Music]
ah
ticky
[Music]
[Laughter]
stop stop
i get dizzy so quickly i can't do this
spleen well welcome everyone i'm sorry
for uh changing the game last minute
it was inevitable
whoopsie
[Music]
there it is
it was inevitable
uh i mean yeah so i wanted to play
diablo today release day it is
um
but
the servers are
seemingly having issues
and um
um i could if i wanted to i could create
a character character on the offline
uh mode
but i don't want to do that because
i'm planning on to play a diablo to
resurrect it not only as announced with
my family but
well
i've seen certain whole life english
members
show an interest in playing it
as well
uh
[Music]
so
and yeah
as well i think but other whole live
english members as well so i was like
hmm
if i'm gonna play it
i don't want to have two characters and
level them both like one of the offlines
or one on the online server because you
have to in order to play online with
your character you have to create the
server uh to create the character on the
online server you can't make one on the
offline server and then use it on the
online server that doesn't work
yeah
so
yeah i didn't want to play the
the beginning of the game again for a
third time you know what i mean
yeah i wanted to avoid that so we're
playing a different game today i have
literally no idea about this game i just
know it's like a funny game
where
i think it's click clicky a clicky game
where you click things
[Laughter]
it's a
clicky clicky game and
uh the problem is i don't really know
many memes and references i never know
any freaking memes and references when
you guys
uh tell me about things i remember all
the times when
people sent me something in the super
chat and i'm like uh what does that mean
meanwhile the chat is like
funny
and i'm just like
eh
yeah so you guys will maybe need to help
me
and from when i know this game
if you play it fully you can like spend
like six hours or so with it is that
correct but uh i don't know if i want to
play a full six hours
so
maybe just like three hours
er and not more
and then we could do a second a part two
at some point i hope you all are okay
with this change um i did a poll in the
bridge at an emergency poll and made you
guys choose i am aware that uh it was
split between sims 4
and but i feel like you know you guys
know my worries about sims 4 i think
and
i do love sims but whenever i play sims
4 on stream i feel a little bit
pressured
i didn't feel like putting pressure
today
we'll play it another time again
[Music]
okay
so i i guess i'll guess let's get into
it
let's go
tell me if the audio is ever too loud
also my
mouth barely moves huh
when i'm in this form
what do i do shuffle explosives tell
that's minecraft are we playing
minecraft
oh i can choose okay
what even is the goal of this game i
don't even know how about
i came in like a wrecking ball
yes
uh-huh
what
oh oh i want to rob a bank successfully
is
just do everything okay
stumble into the correct option
well that's already my first fail
there's no construction okay so i wanted
to go into the bank and the dude was
like not happening
okay okay what's what's eight h on and
bios what
retry
aha
owl body exclusive exclusive explosives
[Music]
handle with care i handle everything
okay you know how to move how many eggs
i have to deal with every day of course
i handle things with care i don't drop
eggs and they would break
so no way that this would happen this is
an inaccurate depiction of me
i guess it's not me it's henry henry's
stupid henry doesn't know how to handle
eggs not even his own
um
[Music]
okay can we get in
he's stupid never dig straight down okay
that's a rule that you could probably
apply to
er minecraft as well although
digging straight up is more dangerous
than digging straight down i suppose
yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
number one rule
my mother
[Music]
oh it is a minecraft reference oh
embarrassing technology i'm sure it'll
get better okay well we only have two
left
hmm
i wanna get the wrong one
uh the laser seems very very
um
brutal
oh oh i thought i was thinking of a
bigger okay
i was thinking of a bigger
laser like one that you shoot out of
space i don't know i don't know why
penta fail
shut up so it is disguised how does that
happen that that the last one you choose
is the right one how does that happen
oh
do they think i'm a bag of money we lose
i think we should throw it in the back
just to be safe
did you guys hear that well is that so
quiet you ever wonder why there's a bank
out here
no
this is supposed to be like more of a
vault you know it's literally in in the
middle of nowhere
turn on subtitles can i do escape no
way in guys little quiet okay
oh are we
oh
we are uh
was there even a ah this is where it
starts okay okay so now what are we are
we
escaping the prison okay
i've done that before i can do that yep
yeah in one of my previous lives i was
stuck in prison
i'm pretty
not really but you've got a
package package
don't get yourself
we've already checked it for anything
useful jailbird exactly me
yeah yeah of course i checked it i mean
if i didn't check it i'd lose my job not
always my
job idiot
well good for me then they didn't check
what's in the package that's good for me
cake
that's uh
the cake is lying wait a second
gatorade
how would that help me
[Music]
are you okay
i i think he's hallucinating
yeah that's not really happening is it
um
donuts oh yummy sugar coated sugar
glazed donuts so simple yet so divine
west mesa penitentiary
mesa biome i want to find that in
minecraft
oh my god what was what is
nrg side effects include nausea
headaches rapid heart rate um
well folks good to know what oh that's
that's an energy drink it's not like he
drank that much
all right just a classic file
eh oh i can choose what i use it on oh
um i would say the window
because
oh
that building did not look that tall
from the outside before oh wait no that
was the bank this is the prison ah it's
so different okay wait can i turn on the
menu you guys wanted to have
wait is this saved i wanted to turn on
the
subtitles
options
subtitles on there you go
let's go
okay
all those things nice
are you you're free to go yeah shut up
we did the file one way now let's do it
the other way
thank you you're welcome
of course i will do anything for you
guys
no not true
find him
[Music]
wow
hey he's escaping
they didn't subtitle that he's escaping
oh what do i want to do
oh
what would i do with the chair ah just
put it in front of the door and with the
grenade i would just blow up everything
that's not very smart is it
let's try it
throw it at them
yeah i mean that was pretty obviously
that's still gonna go well
oh
i thought you were gonna just put that
in front of the door okay let's go right
dunk dunk
it
oh
now you're on top of that
[Applause]
whoa that's some good choices
i would say parachute or jetpack
actually we can just go very very far
away no
i see so actually i guess this game
could be shorter if you don't try to do
literally every option why didn't we
fail
[Music]
yeah so i just wanted to get some fresh
air you know understandable isn't it
i've been in here for
more than
five minutes it's just unbearable
okay let's uh plunges that's funny that
wait that reminds me of uh
that old old movie that i told you guys
i'm scared of the one with the uh
stop-motion with clay uh loved one you
guys know what i'm talking about
have wallace and gromit but did they
actually have plunges i think they did
[Laughter]
it worked
what
all right guys thanks for watching
bye-bye
just kidding don't leave don't leave
don't leave
don't leave don't leave don't leave
don't leave don't leave but we're still
playing oh wow that was that was very
lucky but okay we're gonna try a few
more things
uh one out of three oh oh
no
can i do more prisons okay no i guess
we're doing the next thing hereby
declare we're doing the next thing
archaeological exhibit
[Music]
that again reminds me of wallace and
gromit
i can go to the menu later i can pick
off
in literally every choice is that it
like i can you go back to any of these
choices
oh i like that explosion
medieval section
[Music]
yes
ah
quick thinking guys quick that's gonna
break yo and after that
i figured that garden is much less
dangerous than driving
[Laughter]
[Music]
police
see i have some practice in this not my
first time riding this rodeo
sir place your hands where i can see
them
do not comply i will be forced to fire
upon you
you leave me no
[Laughter]
place your hands where i can see them if
you do not comply bribing
bribery is a federal fencer and do we
care
what you should be for that
i wasn't really i was just i was just i
was just you don't want that you don't
want to become a magical girl and and
you know
do the maduka meguka sir place your
hands where i can see them
i thought it would be nice
i swear as well office i just wanted you
to make your dream come true
[Music]
interesting wait one of the three
ah one other three endings to stealing
the diamond ah so there's still two
endings for for both of the things i
just played oh
ah a mogus
i saw i saw that there's like some kind
of a mangas reference well well look
can't pin him to any crimes
you'll be going into the airship to
bring him down
i don't need to remind you that we've
got you on several charges attempting
robbery
breaking yourself out of prison
even stealing the tunisian diamond we've
got a lot of counts on you
do this job right and we'll drop all
charges against you oh okay bringing you
close to the airship and leave it to me
it's up to you leave a question
down
in that airship don't worry
where i want to go in uh well how i want
to go in oh
crap grapple crap
[Music]
i think
this would be the most movie-like option
i want to try the sticky handle
what am i even trying to do here right
now zero point energy what is this
i i don't yeah i don't know either
without what i was trying to do
ball and chain
stick it on and oh
[Music]
i'm really good at this
i got the wrong one
no hey hey
i
it
failed but i am a winner what does that
mean you're sending me mixed signals
that was a speed run but it's a fail
but i didn't have any other choices what
do you want me to do
what
oh
do i have to go go to map i am at map
click click huh
is that a dead end
do i have to go like here
and uh let's see where we continue
the empty box
look who finally decided to wake up was
it at that end you've been quite loose
okay
well does that mean that the sticky hand
was not the right choice are you sure
about that because it looked like it was
pretty pretty good
a pretty good way to end it all right
i'll go with
the crapple grapple gun
well well well
what's a joy buzzer
sounds funny
[Music]
remind me to never shake your hand i
sank that a mongol ship no more emotions
ever again
it's dead never happening ever again
let's try a bomb
big bump must work i'm a little bit too
close to myself though
uh
so
is it waiting or is it probably
someone's just going to open the door
for me now
ah
yeah you got a task out here don't you
that's what i thought
no no i'm not letting you in anymore
give me the key
excuse me okay um i'm not really good
with events i'm gonna take a look at
this what
oh i'm doing tasks
yes yes
oh
i want all of it what is that
what am i looking at
no
is that
is that porn
uh
[Laughter]
wait wait a sec
i thought i could choose something else
but this wasn't this was not me choosing
uh the
porn what is that a simple
oh that's a game
ah
okay don't choose the computer i know
i'm addicted but i shall not choose it
anymore let's use this elevator
that was not part of among us
let's go for the event
all right it was always the vent there
was always just one option
what else could it have been ah this
place i know this place
vault cells
uh whoa
yummy
yeah do i want to go over to that side
oh yeah because of the vault i suppose
leaping not gonna work
no magic pencil oh you mean i can draw
myself a bridge i want to see that
oh
why did you draw a nutshell i don't know
what the hell that is
i was hoping it would see me as
its mommy and help me
teleportation that's the key
[Music]
oh oh did it work where am i
i'm in the void
is this the afterlife
well
yeah that was probably not the best
ending let's uh let's sleep because
that's probably gonna fail isn't it
[Music]
that's cute he did he tried his best let
me out of you no
not to kill the ducks that's that's
that's sweet of him oh thank you
oh is he gonna like help me later
because that was optional
wizard magic paper riser retro glove
hack
into the gate
what are you doing that's quite shocking
i'm glad i'm not in your current
situation i bet you can't wait to go to
home i guess that's some kind of
references
[Music]
yes um no more of that
what would i do with a vaporizer
oh my cell phone to paper
oh i'm i'm prettier than that
hey
wait it worked
i'm so smart
[Laughter]
it's right in front of me
oh
gravity manipulator claw pack or shrink
and grow
can i
can i make the diamond smaller wait it's
not a diamond it's a ruby or what
surprised that worked yeah this model is
perfect for this game it isn't
it
simulates again
what's going on it looks like he set off
some sort of alarm on that oopsie
he's going rogue
all right
yeah enforcement to move in
is this going well
[Music]
i hate green shells
umbrella i know my umbrella hmm
yeah that's difficult choice am i am i
am i choosing to fight
[Music]
phoenix
i win the game i win the game
did i win
oh my god i started the one
everyone
am i playing a different character now
prototype deb
what
this one cuz i can't read this one what
is that
attempting data recovery
99 that's exactly where diablo stopped
for me just kidding i it eventually was
able to go through but
server did
what's happening
i thought my game was broken
i thought it was cursed
okay so that broke the game
uh let's try the prototype
i don't even know what the hell is going
on here
anymore there he is it's got the ruby ah
i don't forget about it
that looks like
that looks like cali
mustache gold chain
two fancy top hats
yeah yeah yeah that's what callie wants
to look like
[Laughter]
am i right kelly
don't worry believe in yourself believe
it believe it and you can become
whatever you want to be
let him go what we get what we came if
you believe it trouble you can be
somebody
what are those lyrics honestly
[Music]
i cleared the game
again
easy
[Music]
wait how many
like how long does this go
how many
like
how
fling i did it clean the complex okay it
still continues
ah on the map it tells me
ah hello henry
welcome
to the wall ah thank you some of them
have come a long way victorious
criminals
[Music]
again
you wait here until cell found yeah
cute redhead girl
can i just talk to the girl
ah
is that teamwork
i think
pl i will play dead that's i'm good at
that as a phoenix he's grigori
yeah you know new one henry and then
he's dead
[Music]
okay
i think that was the right choice no
pretty convincing i know i know right
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
you
they speak in germany
[Applause]
yes go ahead yeah it looks like uh henry
stick man stick stick man why are the
things
german when this is like apparently set
in russia
attention we haven't escaped conflict
heading towards the surface do not make
me do this myself
yeah they spoke
german don't question it
what
oh it's cute it's like a cute pokemon
game or something like that
do we fight or do we fight or do we go
into the
let's go into the tank
oh there's someone in there
oh
[Laughter]
gee thanks a lot
you can't do anything without a healer
welly
what is this
a spooky
no no no
no no no that was very scary i don't
want that
[Music]
what are you who are you
taco they're missing the a
okay last
[Music]
did he choice just stick it there did he
really just stick it there
i thought there's some way we cannot let
him get through the skate oh nice hat
they suddenly have a nice accent how why
sandwich costume
or the keys to the truck
first let me have a
[Music]
sandwich i can destroy julie everything
now i'm strong oh so short
and effect was so short this one weird
trick will make you super buff
weightlifters hate him what kind of
reference is that
let's do the costume
why would you
shoot
why would you shoot a snowman
i just came here to escape
you guys really need to chill right now
what is your problem
do you just not have a girlfriend
[Music]
it's okay i'll be your
girlfriend but
only for one day
do you wanna build a snowman
anyway you want to try it out that ain't
happening
[Applause]
go go go go
where
music is this considered
music was that too late
did that count as i chose that or not
[Music]
oh thank you you're the first person to
escape the wall orb start
no way
no
but that was the only option though
henry i'm impressed really i am you're
the kirby
[Music]
back to the complex what's it going to
be henry it's going to be the airbag
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay i will surrender i'll find a
different way out henry i'm impressed
really i am oh yeah thank you very much
possible but this is the end you gotta
be patient here huh
you stay in there
i'll surrender
really
we'll see
oh no
boxing security what an honor
no that's a fail tool
and where does it restart
okay okay
let me out of here i'll i'll do a quick
dive to kirby's planet
don't take it off just wait there's one
more oh really do nothing i thought i
was stuck forever
is this 12 minutes i have to say henry
i'm impressed really i am you're the
first person to escape the wall i
thought we weren't going to play 12
minutes today
you stay in there
or you return with us back to the
complex what's it going to be nothing i
guess very risky
oh
all right everyone back to work i will
not forget about this oh
[Music]
we did it we did it
all right next up completing the mission
can i put on my
oh
oh so i'm i'm done with the game and now
i can't do the extras okay i'm done i'm
okay with that i'm down with that but
for that i must put on my glasses
because i am maximum
gamer now
so that means
i am allowed to wear my glasses
hey guys
where do we start
eh wait what are are these side stories
oh
but are these like do they end with
failures or
[Music]
do they also have a happy end
smug toe
separate endings ah
so i guess we could try to go for the
girl wait do i click how do i do i click
on this one
i know those are my what i got okay
so
what do i do
menu
i guess we start from the beginning
skip intro
uh but we have to get in again so that
was disguise no
second map
oh oopsie
[Music]
need to choose two ah
how did we lose one i think we should
throw it in the back can i sleep
no i can't
oh just wait a moment you ever wonder
why there's a we'll get in there soon
enough well i think it's supposed to be
like more of a vault you know oh that
makes sense
pick the two endings in ctm
and we can pick the part from the map
okay
[Music]
i did not expect that to happen
should i go next now or i'll end up in
the prison no
or should i go to the menu
wouldn't that be
try map
let's go to the menu okay and then what
escaping prison oh no it is
ah i don't understand ctm
play
[Music]
i don't understand
select both
oh
hello yeah can i speak to the chief
please not available
combining i was just wondering if the
rocket platform create the finale whoa
cool a rocket
firing up that space station into orbit
is that me yeah the one where we can
just sit around
there's someone suspicious in the back
you know luxurious lounges
with many meddling governments
yeah right we're leaving from that
jungle base then right
relax mate no it's going to be a bloody
hell mate get it going
an entire rocket you must be mental
you're bloody mental or you dip
four hours before lunch
oh
[Music]
yeah sorry in my wealthy model i really
can't limbo that much
sorry probably putting the fall faults
on my wealthy model come on
come on
no
okay last option let's go stop hey can
you
it could be that easy wait a minute
anything about it he's too fast intruder
who is that can we stop him please no
don't stop me i i have something to do
please oh look you're not allowed to
change heads all right now drop it
this one
i did a trick
[Music]
i've had enough of mario kart for the
rest of the year just kidding i could do
a few times more change heads all right
now drop it
i'm looking
[Music]
should i just do nothing again look
you're not allowed to change heads was
that an option now drop it getting on my
nerves apparently
[Music]
close the main door immediately
he's riding straight up what is this guy
doing trying to steal a rocket no
totally not
oh chief oh it's a pretty rocky yes go
ahead
no
hammer
hmm
which one
did it matter
[Music]
whatever
anything is fine really
for a gamer i can handle literally every
element
and still win
what
told
[Music]
welcome to stickman space resort
built out of a former top at base it's
been refitted for your luxury
green top pets aboard have reformed
that's what i deserve the top pets that
remained on earth were arrested as you
know the resort is run by the man
himself
you may wonder
we may never know but hey you wouldn't
be here if that didn't happen
enjoy your stay oh
i got my own rocket
yeah baby
what now
what did i do now
i can't i need more endings guys
how do i get more endings
[Music]
time to hunt oh so that was though that
was an actual final ending
go to chapter three and four
i'm in episode three and four do all the
things
okay i want to
meet the girl
what's she in here
[Music]
what's in here
we shall find her in here right
uh skip yeah there she is how do i talk
uh boost up
because she's gonna help me right do you
wanna be friends um
let's help one another
and then get married
i can get us a space rocket
just for us too
[Music]
whoa can we bring her
with us
yay
[Music]
ah we're a dream couple you're welcome
look at how much what did you do to get
in here hmm i ended up buffing up my
guys what's your crime being red-headed
australia i mean i'm orange-headed but
people say that's redheaded at the same
time
synchronized take down tall guy
bounce bros
[Music]
why did you guys say this right this one
worked if we can get you up there you
could get in and open this door
that's a
great a
a a plus uh voice acting
uh
judo throw the force i wanna try that
one
are they too nibio is that their crime
for getting in here
let's go for some break
oh
i'm pretty good with all of those i've
got quite the experience one each ah
well let's go with the crossbow and a
sniper raffle
you're stupid mate
let's see that in an instant replay some
that's some reference again isn't it
what about
taser and it's not the raccoon
i mean it worked
why did you use that on me
hey i just grabbed these maybe they'll
come in handy
i thought you
blend in hold the elevator
thanks can you believe this inmate
outbreak crazy huh oh so crazy
are you guys new here
we transferred from the eighth floor oh
don't please don't talk she shouldn't
even
press x for doubt
that's at least one reference i get when
is that guy a detective or something see
we shouldn't let her talk to begin with
she's stupid
i'm ditching her asap maximum security
what do you think that i like
who get the guards
okay i guess this must be this option
then what
there is convict here
what was that
shouldn't you cast your hands i think
they are pretty useful
oh
[Music]
thank you
you can't go mixing fighting game
reference why not
how is that fail
[Applause]
i think that will upset me
yes
i don't know if i want to take you with
me anymore though you kind of ruined it
very early on you know very charming i'm
i'm going to stay with kisara what are
these options hmm
what is that option what does that mean
is that a hole in the ground
i'll try first with this one i don't
think it's gonna work all right
cause it seems too easy
too easy a little bit too easy
[Music]
how isn't this a prison where only the
the the like the people of the worst
worst crimes
get into like the big brain
crime lords right so how are they so
stupid
no
brain hair dudes
[Music]
[Applause]
it was all destined to happen trust me
oh
yes girl okay i'll i'll rethink about
ditching you
i will make it i'll reassess
you
convict ellis we did it and i got the
girlfriend
she's my bond girl
um
okay
completing the mission
uh
should we really do that now should we
now we should first get some other
endings too right let's go to
yeah but i don't know where i would go a
different way
um
i don't remember
three and four
huh
only three and four you can use the map
[Music]
where is the map
still don't understand is only three and
four have the n is okay
three and four when you say three and
four you mean
this
episode three okay
skip intro map oopsie
oopsie
well well skip
okay so we got in previously with
the grapple gun is that okay still to do
what if i do the map ah
two out of three
two the two two three
that's
where do i go
should i go
numbers are the fails
uh-huh
first choice
viewing platform
okay
[Music]
we weighed it last time
we missed one end ending i think once
failed this one i think
okay there we go
now we saw that now we wait again
[Music]
but now from here on i think yeah we got
all of them then we got this one we did
we didn't do the stretch chewies
how did they make
[Music]
that really grinds my gears ha ha ha ha
ha ha okay
so we got that one okay not this one
wizard magic hack
oh the one that we used was a paper
riser and
we tried out hacking i think
mask become wizard
i always wanted to become a wizard
eh
shouldn't shouldn't becoming the wizard
always be the way to go
retrograde wait did we try this one
before
[Laughter]
how insulting you look like an idiot not
me okay we got that down
why is that zero out of two oh because i
immediately chose the right choice oh
that's good
gravity manipulator
yeah someone someone on the earth is
gonna get hit by a huge ruby on on their
head
i hope they don't die from that
what was it
other wrong option must have been claw
pack right
[Music]
take care of your bird did you hear that
guys you got to take care of me
understand
you gotta take care of me okay
are we clear
ah here i also chose the right choice
right away how about umbrella
thank you i'm gonna take care of you
guys too i will try
oh
did we get like blended into a smoothie
and we did armor i think that one worked
so
yeah i don't know what the plan was i
already knew the right option so don't
remind me here i'm just trying some
things out
happy new year
i don't understand that
all right
we're we're clearing through these quite
nicely this is the last one we didn't
look at
we looked at this one in a prototype i
think was this one the one that worked
this one i think definitely uh we didn't
try out
oh
what
i made the planet sana are you proud of
me we'll take our problems and push them
somewhere else i don't understand the
reference guys is this funny are you
laughing yet is that fun yeah you're
laughing are you laughing because of
what
spongebob reference oh dear not even
sponsor spongebob
references i understand
dark energy bump whoa
whoa
oh my god
what is the sad music no
did i just destroy the whole world
there's not even a message for me why
was there no one left to write a message
from me
eh
i'm so sorry
wait but um
but did i i think i did all of them
though now
so we shall go here
and
we did the girl one
we did try to play dead
uh we did try tackle so do i wait for
wait a second
sorry sorry
at the map here
ah there was only
do i go here
i guess
i did the right thing here as well so
let's do a tall guy
play to fail okay facing the same deck
hey wait for the transfer
ah
don't see helping
hey it
i almost wanted to do that i always
watched it in scrubs i wanted to do
something like that too
will i ever become the tall guy
okay so wait for transfer is something i
should try
all right let's go i let's go
ah stop kicking my butt
[Music]
what are these options
ew
yo that sounds like a like a pig's nose
yeah that's disgusting
that's still laser plane
does this does this path lead me to a
new ending oh wait did that choose the
right option again
i'm such a genius
oh
happy birthday you could have
thank you
we'll play diablo 2 uh next week or so
maybe we'll get them next time
what is this missing ending from in
eh
no
no what the hell that sucks
eh
wait so i go here yeah okay
the laser plane would normally be an
option i suppose
i've never seen this all
oh my god
what happened
uh wait were those all like
disgusting people discussing illnesses
yo
that's literally a room where you're
you're like they they want us to die in
there that's disgusting
are they doing that to contain the
illness oh yeah
what is the sonic pose
that's oh that's a cute emoji
teleporter that works before didn't it
[Music]
aliens exist after all i've i've been
saying it all along others
let's game we speak isn't
it cookie
cookie always good
is that an alice in wonderland reference
finally do i understand something
oh wait so ah the only not fail option
would be laser plane but for that i'm
missing uh
aircraft
which which one
what should i do
infiltrating the airship infiltrating
the airship
uso
i need to go to the airship
okay
where yeah i did everything no
is this not the airship
get the other words ah
get the other endings huh
like go
[Music]
earpiece in canada cannonball oh
the aha here what do you think
oh yeah thanks guys
holy go go i'll hold him off
push
come on you sprink oh beautiful accent a
may i join could you teach me tomorrow
vail is gonna teach me how to speak a
beautiful accent
i hope i can impress her can you teach
me some lovely accent words please
have a collab with bails tomorrow
[Music]
first collaborates tacos tomorrow
i really expected you to grow faster
than those frosters
oh how to speak or bloody hell mate oh
only all right
one force is actually two forces and
they uh are the same but they're also
different yes something like that
that's some deep stuff is it the chair
what would i do with the chair
oh
unexpected but it is a solution
good choice thank you it doesn't seem
like it was actually a good choice but i
appreciate the positive words
okay i understand i understand what you
want from me
hurry up now activate the doors activate
the doors quite clean
oh no wait don't activate the doors
it wasn't leaving me
run faster
[Music]
that's disgusting
all right all right all right we did it
though
that's for real now of wallace and
granite
reference right and oh that's that's
that's nostalgic that's very nostalgic
[Laughter]
let's use that one
i don't know about you guys but when i
was watching that when i was younger i
just always thought it was a hella
creepy movie i don't know i don't know
creepy
yes i did not wear the harness and you
know what i don't like those rubber
pants anyway so
you eat them i never want to see them
again
you loved it
i don't know get away
now i've got yeah
i
i was never really able to use a yo-yo
the right-hand man attacked
oh my god what what reference is this
psi defense bash
110 hp damage massive
[Music]
no
you're cheating you're cheating
earthbound oh
what did you expect hitting him with a
yo-yo would do i don't i don't know i
mean i just wanted to be cool you know
i thought at least in a video game i
would be able to use a yo-yo properly
[Music]
it was blitz it's it's thunder in german
that was very effective now
fleet
i i understood that
wait so
did i just use the wrong attack is the
knife the way to go though
how about magic
reflect
[Music]
no don't reflect it on me
i started to fire on myself today no
both work oh okay okay i'm gonna go with
this one i prefer this system
tools chainsaw yeah
baby
oh 7 500 he must be dead come on
how can you survive a chainsaw
[Music]
it's cause i didn't stream spikes god
damn it i got a tent
hey we got some items out of that noise
last reverie
fire always works at the end of the day
interesting choices um let's start by
beefing up
holy
[Laughter]
wow see results in up to eight seconds
oh
impressive i think you should have gone
for spinach
and they don't work
what
jet puts production notes find lighter
material to construct the boots out of
yeah that would have been smart thank
you maybe next time don't ask me to test
them out though
ask someone else
[Music]
i just want the little kitten to the
chain
ah
okay okay oh that's a lot of choices
uh let's start with the tag
you guys wanted me to use that too
was that the right option
oh it was
seemingly seemingly
oh
[Music]
nice this game is fun
i like these kind of simple games i like
them
all right let's we can try to get the
other ending from that point
um
menu
here
map
[Music]
must be here yeah
okay and let's see the pirate ship
because that must be the failed option
really does is that
the what
oh come on you had one job brother are
you saying
i got noodle arms
i'm so sick of people saying that to me
[Laughter]
was this the right option all right
pretty big fall oh i'm sure henry had a
plan ah always i always have a plan
mm-hmm
[Music]
oh i see i see it
i understand i stayed up there
[Music]
i do want to see the failed option there
though
may i please use the missile
bamboozle
on the second floor that might not have
been such a good idea yeah i've realized
that now
okay so
can we do something else here now
i got new ones
i can combine
how about this
and then this
oh no
this one
let's try one more ending there oh
let's see what happens with these
combinations
preparations are nearly complete should
be able to launch within the hour oh
so this is the top hat clan secret base
sign me up whoa what happened to that
nobody
know
okay
uh henry remember that orbital station
idea we were talking about we went ahead
with that plan we've got all of us don't
cry guys don't cry once the final
preparations are complete we'll be ready
to launch into orbit that should keep us
far away from any governments trying to
bring us down oh
should be a jeep
hey what did i tell you about calling me
that henry is the chief remember yes
okay respect the chief under attack
you two get to the rocket henry
escape to space let's
the rocket is launching in five minutes
can we launch faster for glass tank
supervents
falcon bunch
[Music]
[Laughter]
they remember me as a hero well then i
would say that was a success
we have infiltrated the system guys
well we must make sacrifices
abandon just you wait till my friend
gets here yeah sure
[Music]
oops
must be
[Music]
machines
tom's up let's do this who are you
oh my god there's so much going on
let's do
st it's a style on them yeah
i can do that too
[Music]
i forgot how did i do my dab
i used to be able to dab i forgot how to
do it
all right not gonna lie let's breathe oh
thank fair
i summoned i upon this earth
my kfb burbs come here to protect
your savior your queen
you angel and your leader
of the kfb
crickets really that's all you're going
to give me crickets
someone took too long for god's sake for
god's sake wow
impressive huh
one minute we gotta hurry
um
you guys need a ride
hey girl
oh
okay we'll probably need someone uh
okay okay okay okay i get it i get it
this is not how you drive a car man
hey
i chose you
oh
three
two nine
when in doubt always rely on henry yeah
we're leaving the dude behind i suppose
whatever henry's still down there yeah
the door opened up
huh we gotta go
oh
no no i thought that was someone else
they're leaving without me i'll use the
club go go go go go go go go
go go is that dragon ball reference no
no
god damn it
what is this
is this a
special
toy
let's use the tank
[Music]
but why would i do that thank you thank
you thank you thank you
put yourself on the line to save the top
at clan
you've truly earned my respect and you
think i'm a better person to lead us
call me tension
[Music]
unfortunately we lost quite a few
members during the raid
with the station in orbit we were able
to raid any place on earth
ellie was officially recruited into the
tuppet clown and given the rank
right-hand lady right-hand lady me and
my right-hand man went on to become top
operators in the clan performing several
successful operations sounds like a
story straight out of
gatsby
beautiful ending i must say
what
now i was still missing something
here
was that
[Music]
another scene a map
you guys said i was ah
i'm missing some here ah
what
no that was the right one oh god
earpiece wait where was the earpiece
where was the earpiece
who's there
you should have asked they probably
would have let you in if you had girl
scout cookies damn it
vacuum
we're just vacuuming vacuuming everyone
who's in there nice
seems like the right choice so we should
probably look for something cause
otherwise there would be people waiting
down there for me noise
smite no point in this operation
all right gentlemen we've been tasked
with developing new weapons for the clan
oh any ideas that's kind of thinking
stop it guys
stop it chickens
trans dimensionalizer visit us now
dimensions with the flick of a switch
you went to the first dimensions okay to
flip the switch up and to get back to
all right
oh
they won't notice
[Music]
uh
friends
oh
cute looks like
looks like garfield a little bit
a tails get tails on
me take care of this
like a thin version of garfield bone
melt what
what's that mean
how did i do that
is it
magic oh man i remember you got a nice
hat i think nobody knows about this here
we'd be in a lot of trouble
yeah okay well okay you should never let
me throw things i'm not good at writing
things unless when i throw things in a
different kind of way i definitely
through this game
hello mr special you like spiders
all right
wait there's no way you're getting
through there gotta think outside of the
box guys
it
looks like you can get around if you go
through that air duct
all right i've hacked into their power
grid what do you want me to do
oh
i don't need your help i'm sorry i just
thought you needed some help
oh
[Music]
did i roast him did i electrocute him
cargo bay
well that's okay it's the enemy
banana
[Music]
is that what this means
oh
my ear
mimika i can't hear no more
that was louder than crazy ollie
hey there's a
[Music]
this could be a problem
looking good with the sunglasses oh why
thank you
oh
i did it in famous stopper clan has been
apprehended hundreds of arrests made
many still at large
authorities tipped off by anonymous
source
[Music]
endings four out of four
unique fails 4006 wait i got all the
endings
all the endings in the airship right
[Music]
which means
we can combine something again
ah we got all aha we should get all of
the ones from the complex too
now the hodo
[Music]
you need the ones from the complex all
right
oh wait oh
oh
oh wait i can just go there
huh no
no no no that's uh other
let's go here
so
what was i'm missing here a lot of
things
uh
those are for the fails huh
bottom the laser
white boxes
boost abandoned alley mm-hmm
i'm not sure which one to go
little boxes the little ones
uh which one did i choose here
originally
wait nothing well oh wait those are the
ones that i didn't have before right
those are missing options
where are you
both of them oh yeah yeah yeah yeah they
weren't available before yes of course
so well uh we'll be right there
sit tight er
i'll let you know when we're close
one hour later
where exactly are you
cafeteria
okay got the map here
yes there you are all right how do you
want to do this
i don't know
you tell me please
hey henry
it's me yeah i'm i'm undercover i'm here
to break you out yeah and i think i knew
you need to be fired
[Music]
yeah we probably should have gotten a
gas mask beforehand so only choice is
left
[Music]
i was expecting a really cool car what
the hell
but i'm not going to pull you up see
without you i become the leader of the
tuppet plan again
i can offer you many things as i took it
all i can offer you 10 of the kfp income
you will regret that carefree
is the world's
wide bestest fast food chain
wrong choice buddy wrong choice
henry will remember this
kiara will too
but will i survive no
am i dead
that counts as an ending no
next door
next
now in
aha
this one is this the one i just got yeah
i think so
that'll hold up okay no no no no go back
go to the menu go here
skip follow
map boo
and go here again and then do the
government
for now
yeah
oh henry hey
yes yes yes yes oh i see i would like to
have a number nine and then whatever
number 36 and
two burgers two drinks
see dr pepe mission but uh chicken
nuggets time to swing by
[Music]
hey so uh i'm getting pretty close
yeah
just uh try to get outside and i'll uh
you know
hey so uh i see the wall yeah outside
nice
yeah please pick me up mommy
i'm lost and i'm scared i got this yeah
it'll be just like the old times
yeah did i choose the right choice again
oh my god i'm so good at this
mini helicopter how many oh i'm so cute
isn't that a little bit too small i
don't think i can get in that
yeah
and there you go
hey i'm seeing that oh thank you oh i
wasn't even supposed to get in there all
right
it's pretty cute did i choose the right
one again rta let's go
i'm just randomly choosing things
[Music]
sorry sorry sorry uh
jumping down was not the best option i
realized that now
boy mate
what the hell
need some backup here
okay okay okay i understand
this
guy
he's as flat as a pancake now
[Music]
i am
i am born to be a criminal
four out of five what am i missing
what am i missing
here
maintenance spin
which because the small white white one
oh there's one okay i'll cook it
oh i don't remember
i did try this one i think yeah yeah
yeah
oh ellie will remember that
and i'm like look at how much i care and
she has red hair oh my god was that only
small sister
[Laughter]
oh yeah that makes a lot of sense
oh oh no that that's olivia
ah
aha okay
wait that's is that the
is that from wind waka
wait
i got one too
wait a second wait a second where did i
save it let me let me get it let me get
it real quick
[Music]
i have it
i have one too
can't find it
ah
where did i save it
i don't know where it is well i don't
know where it is
i want
i want to use my my my tacto
got them all right i'll just use it here
i love the window
see this game is i guess so much more
fun if you actually
understand these references
too bad you didn't know how to play like
an ocarina
shut up i don't need an ocarina
[Music]
it wasn't me
did i do it
[Laughter]
congress thank you thank you thank you
i'm so proud
i finally feel like a zoomer again
uh
come to think of it those boingers are
kinda loud
power damp
quietly though quietly you're not
supposed to make that mario sound
idiot
idiotica
yet it has worked
we are here now
hmm
how about a balloon
uh
oh
really really
really
i did not expect that to be the right
option again
rca let's go
it's actually pretty good for me because
i'm having insane stomach pain right now
i want to get this over with
[Music]
wait did i choose the right option again
i swear i'm not cheating i'll leave
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is the power of the phoenix and the
power of the stomach egg combined
these are really fun sounds i could like
make a song out of this
[Music]
[Applause]
get callie in here please
this is probably not the right choice
hello
did you think none of the crew would
notice
i mean we should have just killed all
the crew duh
that was my plan why did i not get to do
that
rocket it is
i'm not sure if a rocket really makes
that sound
who built that rocket it's not rocket
science come on
see you runner
someone just leave think of a smith
probably off to see his family
[Music]
um
[Applause]
okay does that mean i have everything
did i get them all
okay
i don't know if i want to combine
literally everything uh because i really
don't feel well but we'll combine some
that we haven't seen yet at all
for example these ones
dun dun dun oh you guys can tell me your
favorite one if you if any of you
remember is your favorite ending
combination you're welcome to tell me
afterwards
the players are hosting
most recent
this is a code 12 broadcast the remnants
of a top hat clan have been seen
mobilizing near the dogo bogo don't go
bongo why they are attempting to launch
an orbital satellite of some kind
unconfirmed reports are telling us they
are shipping their assets by train to
this base in the jungle gotcha forgot to
understand include all treasures and
artifacts they have stolen throughout
the years
now these treasures are worth quite a
lot of money so we gotta make sure
i got to i know that i wrote everything
down
my favorite ending is alpha and we know
it's in ah new oil
this is checkpoint inspection team 5. we
are all clear
now's the time guys now's the time
magic hat
i suppose we should hop in yeah
and once again i chose the right object
[Music]
i
say
i sit
uh excuse me uh i'm saving that seat for
my real friend now hello
hello come on oh hey there you are yeah
no this guy just took us
goddammit
mannequin
whoa check out this crazy coat rack yeah
just hang anything on me i'd hold the
person
you think that's funny i'm gonna kick
your ass after this
i'm gonna kill you hey
no
i was still about to kill you press
after pay respect or i a window it is
oh how did i do that jump how did i
manage to do that jump the way i jumped
out of there impossible
yes i'm skilled in photoshop graphic
design is my passion
let's get everything packed up before it
gets too late
interesting leaf mode
just place these on any object and they
will turn into a leaf transport the
biggest things with relative ease suck
back it will vacuum up anything you aim
at that's a guarantee it certainly does
suck
infinity free
store anything in this cube it's got
virtually limitless storage thanks to
his creative use of pocket dimensions
animal crossing let's go
okay how about the cube it must be the
cube right to the cube
[Music]
making room
i
i will not pay for that
just to let you know that was not me
you cannot prove it
okay in the end you just have to
suck it all up
[Music]
okay you guys will now have to tell me
today's the day your favorite
combination and i'll watch that one in
here
i'm so fast i'm like zooming through
these things here
uh no i don't i don't understand here
here we go here
[Music]
one three four five four five four five
a lot of four fives it
four
like this
is is this five
or is it is that five
yes
okay okay okay
uh
let's go let's see
why you guys like this one so much i'm
curious
let's find out
one and two
a lot of people saying one and two as
well
if i do all of them then i'll end up
doing all of them
that's not necessarily what i want to do
hmm
wait wait
easy you were gone for a bit
i was able to bring you back to life
thank you specializing military grade
organization oh i see i think i was
forced to replace spine and lift arms oh
my god damage you sustained i'm a robot
you had running with topet glenda da
i've encountered them before
you see you're still healing
healing
they went south if you are wondering
about 10 hours ago
wow you're learning so quickly
i'm a transformer now that's what i
always wanted to be and now i shall fly
towards the sun just like papa said i'm
thinking once we arrive we should be
able to
[Music]
he's got that near automata huge ass
sword if you can call it a sword we got
the right noise again oh my god i just
got a feeling
[Music]
you can count on me in this situation
i never miss
oh i took another eye
it's my newest hobby
[Music]
wait did i do it again
i chose the most ridiculous option
pokemon
have i so far ever missed
[Music]
what does that even mean this option um
i'm not sure about these
[Laughter]
you don't have to do this
you chose the wrong enemy anyone
available there's an attacker in the
cockpit
[Music]
the ship yes
oh captain my captain
looks like we'll be sharing this last
ride together
how romantic
well
you got us
what is it
worth
it is this a failure
completely
[Music]
oh don't don't do this to me don't don't
play the piano music no
[Music]
was it all worth it
why are we here
just to suffer
revenge at least at least we got our
revenge
okay
[Laughter]
one and three one and three didn't i oh
okay this one is a new one right okay
let's see oh look at that that one also
seems to be very popular
i'm surprised you guys even remember
which ones you like the most
have you played it so recently
oh wait did i do the wrong one
the orbitals did i show the wrong one
they climbed to easily raid any place on
it or is this one train this should be
one
henry henry i heard you died
ah man
the top back plane has been causing a
bunch of problems for me lately
yeah ever since they got that orbital
station set up they've been suited
now that i think about it you and i made
a pretty good team in the past
i bet we could take them out it's
starting to get personal
well what do you say
wait the game kind of crashed
what the
what
[Laughter]
no way
i just have to you don't see my mouse
anymore do you but i have this loading
thingy
hello
will you come back to me
no
come back to me that part always crashes
what
did you guys this would did you guys
tell me to do one and three because it
crashes you wanted to
oh
it's a common bug did you guys let me
choose that on purpose no
[Laughter]
eh
i think i have to close the game
oh yeah i don't think it's coming back
yeah it's not responding
okay or program schliesen
all right all right all right i'll bring
it back
uh
[Music]
i shall hey do you think it will happen
again
it crashes eight 80
of the time
that's uh
quite the high percentage
[Music]
the odds are pretty high i will give her
the one more try
i'll give it another try
four or five spirit for for home home
okay i'll do that one till then
does that skip the part where it
crashes henry henry hi
how you doing girl haven't seen you in
such a long time a bunch of problems for
me ladies and gentlemen
they got that orbital station set up
they've been super strong
now that i'll be fine okay you and i
made a pretty good team in the past
indeed i thought we could take them out
get personal let's get pregnant what do
you say you want to help me take them
out oh yes
awesome all right follow me i'll take
you out for a nice dinner too if you're
okay with it
[Music]
secret government prototype we did it it
didn't crash
there it is
all right how do you want me to bring
you in
from the back it's just like last time
[Music]
beam aboard sounds so easy almost too
easy
i don't think so i don't think so
hello no no i cannot explain no
[Music]
price
you think it's going to be such a big
deal to get spoiler than henry stickman
collection
see i told you it was a good idea bats
have no clue you're there now
stick back here though so they don't
detect me
get inside from here though don't let me
do this all alone
um
charles what the you know what no
this calls for some bold action
i'm the bold action man
warning critical damage
immediately
i've always wanted to do that morning
anyways
i should probably find a way off the
station before it explodes
yeah i'm not gonna do this alone
child's gonna come with me this is the
only way through
um then this vent leads somewhere on the
other side
now we're just going to end up in space
now
he likes to sing huh
rta what what i'm not reading the chat
[Music]
i don't know how i do it
well okay this time i'll miss what
um
sorry
we should shoot him
shoot him while he's on the toilet
no i don't want to spoil you
okay okay how about the middle one no
one in there right open up
well that was intense
i can't wait to go home
[Music]
don't worry about it i'll find another
way
[Music]
did it though we got
life is not worth living anymore
bring me back my toes
f
i will miss you dude
i'll miss you
it was nice knowing young
all right
what's next guys
four five
four five one two three four five okay
let's look at it
done
it's been a long ride
i've been through a lot of now
hello lady hey easy easy i've seen you
we're gone for a bit
i was forced to replace spine and light
i wish i told to do this again
was beyond repairing
[Music]
oh you want me to choose something
specific there
is it a failure
okay
oh you want to see the mail
oh
my dear chicks
all right all right
skip spirits
[Music]
i didn't watch jojo guys i don't
understand but it looks funny
go go go go go go go
go
um
[Music]
japanese he says
you're kidding me there's no way that i
really say that
shitty
japanese such a shitty japanese
[Music]
okay i don't know enough about anime to
dispute it you don't know this is
this is reality
thank you guys for showing that to me
that was interesting it would probably
be much more interesting if i would have
watched jojo
okay
uh i watch i watch one more one more
ending
which one
we've seen a bunch of them already
which one one and two
one two okay a lot of one twos did i not
do this already no
one three one two one two one two one
two okay
we're with ellie again
you sure this is where he's gonna pick
us up ah there he is
you said you did some work with him in
the past or something if you trust him
then so do i
hey henry hi sweet nice to see you again
who's your friend
i'm ellie well nice to meet you any
friend of henry's is a friend of mine
so uh
this is the best timeline but
well you remember the captain yeah he
had to sanction this pickup in return
we're gonna need your assistance again
the top bats all right again
that's all right
it is the least we could do he is
helping us out
and never catch a break the line tells
when we get into the air
all right all right we're on a mission
now the top egg clan is set up by i need
child to live worst case i'll throw ali
out of the window launching uh some kind
of space station into orbit it'll be
sitting pretty if they pull this off so
we gotta make sure that they don't do
that all right talk to the general he
said he's pulling out all our main
forces
he said that henry and i made a good
team last time so i trust that we can
pull it off thanks
pretty good team too don't count me out
now we're gonna make a great squad three
of us we'll have no problems
completing the mission uh-huh
yeah
what
something smells good
i don't think i can get any closer
without getting shot down no worries we
can get there from here
where are we dropping boys
[Music]
[Applause]
no come on
let's talk
how about this one
that was weirdly smooth
so what's the plan
the rocket will be launching very soon
please get on board immediately i will
not hesitate to leave you behind
okay i'm on my way we gotta be quick
right away i'll be down to help as soon
as i can
looks like it minecraft let's go yes
finally a reference i understand i know
how to build stairs it will take a while
i ran out of blocks
where's my elytra
goddammit can you pick up my items at
least ellie
all right
barely it is tattoo
tunnel
bananas oh this is this donkey kong
funny story this cannon was actually
built to fire humans oh really
funny
how useful oh
direct hit how is the window of a
rocket so so thin and so easy to
break rta again
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
did i do it again did i do it again
you will challenge me
i'll take care of this
you think just cause you fuse you're a
match for me
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm so sorry about that my regular
thing is always
[Music]
wait so much for rta
yo
i thought i was doing it again
oh wait wait i know what this is i know
what this is
turn down for
turn down for what oh
[Music]
all right
we need to come up with a plan quick hmm
okay guys
i'm gonna crash head first into the
cafeteria window what do you mean like
you're gonna jump out and smash it with
your head no no with my helicopter
think i'm ready hold on i don't really
understand it's not to understand it's
simple i agree but i also don't
understand but
how does that help
i don't really think you get it henry
you get it right no i don't understand
anything i've just clicked then
everything randomly not really i think
it's a little bit things haven't been
entering my brain properly oh
it would have been amazing charles it
would have been amazing guys listen up i
got a plan henry and i will overload the
engine room causing the explosion
charles we'll need you to wait outside
the auxiliary exhaust by the forward
left booster you'll only have about 20
seconds to get out before it blows
all right i'll be ready hurry
i don't think this is gonna work
i don't think this is gonna work where
is he of course all
yeah this is a question that we should
have cleared uh in the beginning
of course in the end it's henry's plan
yeah
yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah oh yeah that's a great idea
let me introduce
[Music]
did you set the autopilot
all right then let's fail
[Music]
ah what a move
i can't believe we did it
we kept sending the rocket anyway
oh
that was a lot of fun
you know feel free to call us if you got
any more jobs to do
alive still
at the end of it you're still live
so how do i marry charles how do i have
romance child still
charles
he was a good guy i don't know about
ellie she's kind of lame yeah
yeah but that was fun that was a fun
spontaneous little game
thank you guys thank you i have one four
thousand okay
if you say there's your child's ending
one floor is a child's ending
well okay
okay i must see that is that not the one
where he died
this one
does he not
did i not look at this one yet
i knew this would happen i knew this
would happen when i asked you guys
you're gonna not let go
boys been waiting for you two to get
here
let me just get right to it we've
discovered that the remainders of the
tophat clan have been seen building some
kind of rocket they've been gathering
their remaining members and supplies
here in the jungle
if they're able to get this station into
orbit they'll be impossible no we can't
do a little bit more it's okay no you
don't know us anything henry but we
could really use your help on this one
help us out with this one now i'm so far
that it wouldn't be worth it doing a
part two anyway so you and charlie have
worked well together in the past so we
figured you'd be the perfect man for
this operation
you can count on us
now we're really putting all our
potatoes in one sack on this one so
don't let us down boys okay
leave it to me i'm the queen of rta
hey i know uh we just started and all
but uh i
think i'm getting targeted by a santa
what is that yeah
[Music]
cupcake
sorry priorities dude
i'm hungry
panel let's go
yes
this will help me tomorrow it kind of
looks like the sand turrets shooting all
of it yeah just rip out all of the wires
i need to keep you alive i'm sorry okay
i'll try better i'll i'll do i'll do
i'll do it better now
was that not it are you telling me that
was nothing but uh seems to have done
the trick
nice
the rocket will be launching very soon
please get on board immediately i will
not hesitate to leave you behind
ever that one are you in there i should
be able to get you in there with this
oh
oh invisible bridge really alrighty i've
teleported that platform i don't see it
could you
make your way across then help
yeah
thanks for that charles that was very
useful
oh no no you didn't put it there silly
well thanks guys
i felt that
my uber driver
go ahead and grab onto
the thing and then i'll helicopter you
across
oh
yes okay easy
[Music]
we didn't even notice it looks like
every member of the top clan is on
here looking at a schematic here
um if you get to the engine room you can
shut down the engine and then uh the
rocket won't be able to take off and
then they'll all be stuck
so i'll cause a distraction while you
make a run for it to the engine room
sounds perfect dude
hmm
how about a tv broadcast let's see some
netflix
hey guys come check this out i just
finished watching sick note it was
really funny i can't i can recommend
[Laughter]
[Music]
into
not as sick as my dance moves
just wait for my 3d yeah just uh keep
heading up those stairs and you'll hit
that engine when i hit the dance floor
your jaws will drop my little chickens
manages the electronics or something i
don't know i'm not a rocket doctor
anyways
do you think buddy well that's great
because i'm a rocket doctor
just have you tried turning it off and
on again
oops oh
use their feet ah they're sending
someone from the storage nice
engine is definitely gonna buy you some
extra time now that's the one that i
just finished in uh tales of varieties
then i'll call in the reinforcements and
we'll make these arrests easily
i understand everything you just said
there must be someone really happy now
that i'm playing this game again
this game i'm never picking it up
ever again
that was
short-lived this will turn the user into
a bug
be that kind of one listen to a hot
glass of all right
and that that will work
[Music]
oh my god i've been having so many
mosquitoes in my apartment recently i
think because i got so many mosquito
bites or i got them when i was sleeping
over at my mom's place that's probably
more
more uh
probably is it because my my brother was
complaining about mosquitoes too and i
don't see any mosquitoes in my apartment
the mosquitoes
eh
instantly swap places with anyone i use
this every day it's bad all right
all right
nice i want that tool
the cockpit is coming up all my homies
ain't mosquitoes
mosquitoes did you fix the engine why
hold it right there
so i'm really eating it i know not only
tiana
and now you're here to bring down the
rest of us
henry are you in trouble i'm not just
trying to recreate my ttrbg experiences
no no yeah i still can't tell
oh actually i can see from here yeah it
looks pretty bad this project let the
loner rock i got your back
[Music]
buddy him out from here don't worry this
there's zero chance that i'll hit you
with this
oh boy this is bad
oh boy
[Applause]
i could
[Music]
that was so easy
he must have little arms
unlike me
[Music]
sir hello
thank you for the applause everyone
thank you thank you
henry yeah
nice work man yeah this is uh this is
every last remaining member getting
hauled off fine work indeed boys you two
really do make a fine team
and now we retire
sit together on our front porch well he
is now get all together while cutting
our account a lot more missions together
with charlie yeah
drink some hot chocolate
oh special grover ops oh peace
[Music]
romantic
it's guys love between two
guys yeah
okay that's it i would say no more no
more
uh
i i apologize i will not be reading
super jets uh as i said i don't feel
very well tomorrow however is my first
collaboration with bales hackles from
council whole council so please look
forward to that uh
it will be
i don't know what time i think 5 p.m or
so my time but check out my schedule if
you don't know what time it is and we'll
be streaming on both channels so i'm
looking forward to having you guys there
wait was minecraft tomorrow no no no
fingers crossed with bail
base bales
the rat
yes
yeah yeah yeah i think minecraft was the
day after um
yeah okay then thank you guys for
watching today
hopefully hopefully
we'll be able to communicate properly of
course why wouldn't we we're both
australians uh
you didn't see my wink there but i
totally winked
we're both from the same country totally
so i think communication should be no
issue yeah i'm gonna go make some pasta
now
take a good rescue thank you you guys
too
thank you thank you off collab when yeah
yeah that should be totally possible
after all we live in the same same
country
enjoy your pasta thank you i wish i had
lasagna right now but it's okay i'm
gonna need a different kind of
pasta
yeah yeah
thank you guys thank you yeah i enjoyed
this um i think diablo 2 would have been
great too but we'll we'll play that next
week and then eventually we might gonna
we're going to play some collaborations
we're going to play online with some
whole life girls and perhaps some at
some point with my mom as well
and yeah
yeah yeah it's all right it's all right
i'm not even mad i'm not even mad bro
it's okay
thank you guys i hope you enjoyed it and
in german we say auf wiedersehen
thank you soon everyone
i love you guys
thank you for coming bye
[Music]
wow
do
[Music]
you