[Music]
so
but we're still together even though
we're back how do we do this this is
magic
wow
wow impressive
it's black magic how did they do it
we're in the same room oh my god oh my
goodness it's nice to be next to you
again
wow no more surround sound but i guess
it's okay i'll take what i could get
[Laughter]
sound quality kind of different but oh
well
hello everyone first of all i want to
apologize my voice still is a little bit
blah so
yeah
deal with it and next to me we have
pavoli
[Music]
i'm renee from whole life i degeneration
too i'm here to review some photos yes
9000 pictures because
um well i mean it was totally 9 000
pages but i had to cut it down because
stream length you know guys can't make
it for 9000 pictures how would we do
that impossible especially with all the
talking in between but i do have some
nice big pictures and we're gonna talk
about every single day because i have
14 pages of notes on my phone
um
and okay
elena in between you took some notes too
right
oh i did i did i did yeah yeah yeah yeah
but she was like
can i have your notes can i copy your
homework yeah you can make coffee
because i do haven't yeah i i we're
gonna have another recap over at my
channel
i started doing this like
a few vacations ago
where like after one day i just write
down literally every single detail
because i'm like yo
even the smallest details people enjoy
hearing them so before i forget them i
write everything down
and you guys don't have to take notes
don't worry it's just us you guys are
basically uh the teacher is correcting
the homework i guess
somehow are you trying to eat my hat
again
no no no
no no
no
you don't sound as excited as you were
before the stream
huh what you said you were excited
i was i am excited i am very excited for
the pictures no no no tell them the real
reason
the real reason of what what you told me
what
huh what did i
i'm actually kind of trying to like um
get her build hers a keyboard i was you
know i was
messaging
yeah i was actually messaging her
yesterday too and then she just her only
response like laughing emotion i'm like
why are you laughing at me and she was
like i thought it was gonna be something
about the stream or something but it was
about a question about keyboards i was
asking her like
so what's a deal breaker what do you
absolutely need what do you not need
because originally i said i want the
numpad
even though i don't use it i just feel
like the keyboard needs to be
it needs to have the number otherwise
it's incomplete but she told me that
there's barely any keyboards for like
making your own keyboard that have the
numpad right
yeah kind of
technically you can have a separate
numpad if you want
i don't want a separate number it has to
be one piece but oh well i'll try it i'm
trying to get used to the
the one whatever you call them tkl
[Music]
r75 you said you didn't mind either i
guess because so
there's like there's some that are
missing almost everything i don't know
how you even use the keyboard that
misses almost everything
it depends i guess technically the
function rows you i mean you use for
minecraft but otherwise not really right
yeah yeah yeah yeah the the f key is
like i guess
on my for example on my laptop they
don't even work
i don't know why no no yeah they don't
work
they don't work really why don't they
win you can use layers technically you
know you press something and press one
and it becomes f1 that kind of thing oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah but i don't know on
my laptop i didn't do anything i just
doesn't work you know on laptops usually
on the f keys you have like some things
like turning on sound lower volume and
so on and and and lower the brightness
of the screen and it doesn't work
maybe there's something you need to
press it's just like when you have to
press that thing if i want to press the
add mark on your laptop
oh yeah the chat says i need to press fn
okay i don't know where that button is
but i'll try that sometime
okay okay thank you okay now let's get
started because i think yeah yeah
anyways
we're gonna talk about this
yeah yes we're gonna talk about this
because it's gonna take a long long long
long time probably
um but oh yeah if you guys remember
last time the first stream that we did
from the maldives the supposedly scuffed
one which wasn't even unscrupped is
where we already talked a little bit
about uh the vocation and basically
though we covered the the first day and
maybe half of the second day maybe
partially just a floaty story we didn't
include
floaty
i story include that when uh reyna is
doing her recap tomorrow so yeah and if
you haven't listened to the first part
of the story on that other stream then
you should do that afterwards guys
because we got gonna kind of skippy
doodle that okay
okay so here's uh pictures let's get
started this is however
from the airport travel because i didn't
tell you did i tell you guys there was a
nutella cafe
oh dubai
i've never been to a nutella cafe before
i need to go yeah yeah yeah yeah i was
like um this was during my flight to
like my layover on my way to the
maldives and i was like looking for food
looking for breakfast and i i was on one
side of the airport and i saw like a big
sign that listed all of the restaurants
in the terminal and what is that nutella
cafe and i'm like what the hell
so i went to the absolute other side of
the terminal and found the nutella cafe
and i had high hopes but honestly it was
it was so simple because
it was just a flat ass crap with some
nutella inside i didn't even have fruit
to go with it
i noticed you're curious you're crazy
about your food your fruits yeah i love
love me some fruits on the crap and and
on you know the waffles and everywhere
um but but hey it had nutella on the on
the napkin and on nutella on the wet
wipe and and they have so much
merchandise there you can maybe kind of
see it here like a zoom
they have like
you can make your own nutella glass and
you don't see it here but they had like
uh t-shirts and all kinds of stuff
yeah lots of merchandise i didn't buy it
though because i was worried about my
luggage for the seaplane
um no
okay anyway that's fact super light yes
yes yes my airline allowed like 30
kilogram but then the sea plane allowed
20 kilogram
[Music]
and that was exactly 20 kilogram but
anyway this is just something i wanted
to show uh but here we go here we go for
real
this is on the way to
uh maldives you can already see here
this
is like the main molded islands
um consist of two islands we'll hear
about this later but this is kind of the
airport island that we're flying to
um okay so here we are here we have um
the seaplane
uh
airport seaplane porch
and what do you guys see when you look
at this because me and elena what was
our first spot
irl animal cruiser
animal crossing total
you saw a drone where did you see a
drone oh it's a drone
what are you talking about but yeah this
is dodo airlines like the color and oh
my god this was both of our first time
seeing in a seaplane right
my first time on a sea plane too yeah
yeah yeah yeah so it was we didn't know
what to expect um it was it was on the
water here
and this was a lagoon therefore no waves
here but then later on when we were on
arriving at the
at the
uh
at the hotel resort island there there
were a lot of big waves yeah but what
was there anything that we wanted to
talk about that we didn't talk about yet
from the first day
from the first day what did we do you're
the one with the notes yeah i think i
already said everything like i told you
how to open a bottle you drink a lot
um
water by the way guys water like juice
like fruit juice i feel like i need to
make that clear because some people are
like drink drink what like alcohol no
oh oh i thought that was obvious yeah
elena drinks a lot of juice like unknown
in that simple seaplane
uh
lunge
she merely grabbed like two bottles of
multi-vitamin juice and then
immediately chucked chug
down
yeah
and you you were too busy taking notes
you were looking at me and then you were
like on your phone taking notes and then
you i was like can i see and then you're
like no no
yeah i was writing down things for later
kind of think ahead
and i was like i need to i need to write
down every detail from our first meeting
because later on it will be precious
those details
[Music]
do you have do you have some
some um
last time i don't know when we asked for
your first impression for from takanasi
kiwawa
you didn't come up with much oh
oh
no i thought
i saw your clip about the last day but
that's gonna be like skipping to the
last day so i woke up okay okay
actually so when i was on the plane i
took home notes first impression i
noticed this is like a little bit way
later but i think this is already from
the first day that
you crack your fingers or knuckles a lot
for
not that much
not are you sure you were like oh
like well don't tell the kfps i do this
and then
it's just just the just the knuckles
just the knuckle the fingers the thing
is okay yeah yeah
and and uh and the feetsies the toes
those are okay too
that's okay
anyway so seaplane yeah yeah we already
talked about this look this is the the
the
cockpit is this also called the cockpit
there were two dudes i don't know
and um yeah
this was the shortest flight safety
instruction that i've ever had heard and
i wish they would do it that short in uh
emmy rates can i can i quickly like vent
about this
oh
i tried because you know when you fly
from europe somewhere like there's a
high chance that you're gonna try a
million different european airlines so
you see all kinds of different safety
instructions but
freaking emmy rates yo
they just absolutely overdo it like
their flight instruction starts with a a
video in in um
or
arabic
is that what you call the language
okay and then
yo you could i've seen it in other
flights before they subtitle it so you
don't have to have
several ones okay so they play it in
arabic and then next
after like it was already 10 minutes
long after that they show it 10 minutes
long the same video but in english and
then after that they show the same one
but in [\h__\h] german because the flight
well that was on the flight back because
it was to germany three
with the same videos in three different
languages and then it's not over after
me being absolutely absolutely annoyed
to hell they show the most obnoxious
video that i've seen several times right
now but it's so [\h__\h] obnoxious
it's not even safety instructions they
have maybe you guys know and if you look
it up on youtube you can find it but
they have this video where they they
advertise their stupid tv program do you
guys know what i mean
but it's so annoying because
first of all they also show it in two
languages first in arabic and then in
english and and it's so annoying because
it's so [\h__\h] obnoxious do you guys
know what i mean it's so annoying they
show like oh my god oh my god you you we
have it is such an annoying accent and
english british fake accent we have the
most amazing entertainment well you can
see jason yeah we where we live
[Laughter]
that was more intense than i thought it
would be i'm so pissed off this is one
of the reasons i don't want to fly with
emmy rights anymore oh my god that was a
that loud bunk
did did you
did you fall oh sorry that was me so i
don't know that was me there's my legs
have you ever
flew and flown with emirates before
uh i think so but like once or twice you
should you would remember
huh yeah i remember but then i don't
remember that detail
i thought my experience was like pretty
good it's [\h__\h] torture
you just it is you just feel very
strongly about a lot of things my my
experience was fine
i despise emirates anyway
anyway
so seaplane was really loud right
right yes yes i couldn't hear anything
oh is this the picture i took yeah did i
take this picture yeah you're like you
take it because like i was on the aisle
so yeah
it was really really small so it was
really tight and small and
couldn't move yeah yeah
yeah pretty much
but uh
yeah
we already told you guys last time we
communicated via
notes on the phone
via text yeah
is just a couple that was in front of us
yeah
yeah we were on the second row and then
in front of us was this a couple and
then they were like there was like a
small fan and then i remember the person
in front of us was like getting sick of
it yeah it was blowing around in her
face and that was always a korean couple
there were so many korean couples
everywhere yeah there were so many there
were so many actually yeah
in the in the resort too
yeah yeah yeah okay wait um
you sure let me go back to my notes
the couple's single
i wonder i think they were married most
likely
anyway
so here's just uh you know while we were
on our way to the island some
some pictures these are not so good
because the weather was bad but um
yeah
yeah you can see how there's like a lot
of islands
you're like
don't don't go don't fall asleep i told
her that you know uh whenever i'm on
like a plane ride or something like i
fall asleep so easily and then she's
like raining don't fall asleep don't you
want to see the islands and then like
after a while there was just no islands
it was just the water and i'm like kiara
where's the worst see where's the
where's the
scenery but then there were so many like
look like maybe i just had a better view
because i was able to see like through
the corner and all that like here
there's something yeah maybe you're on
the window i wasn't and you said it was
okay for me to close the window
oh it's true it's true i don't like i
forgot something you talk you talk
what what you forgot something okay
anyways yeah
okay yeah i was in the aisle basically
i'm an aisle person whenever i go in the
plane i'm out and then it turns out that
she likes windows so you know
we don't have to fight it i'll like
do the junk and like oh i'm getting
window nah so i would feel that you know
everybody who travels with me they're
pretty lucky in a way when it comes to
like playing plane rides you know we
don't have to fly it is okay why do you
like windows so much let me ask you
because i hate apple
you hate what
what
thanks for asking me okay i have a cool
video let's just
have a cool video
oh reina you're not gonna see this and
you have to although wait a second okay
i can make you see this
i mean i have the stream window open
anyways
[Music]
here it is i filmed um a speed bruh
video of our landing uh yeah it took a
while man i thought oh we're gonna land
soon but then he flew so so slowly
around the island
when is she gonna be done i don't think
this plane flight is gonna be over
anytime
that's what i was thinking in my head
we're like you know i'll just let her do
her thing okay watch this
[Music]
and then we were like oh that's our
island
oh look oh oh and then we didn't land we
flew around it i'm like but that was our
island right right and it's
the landing was smooth but afterwards it
stopped and then the waves was so
intense i was like i was closing my eyes
because i didn't want to like
reverse drink
just like what she did
but you guys don't even notice from this
footage but like the waves this was the
first day and it was stormy the waves
were so strong and
the plane
once it landed moved really really
really really slowly towards the the
dock so
for a really long time we just had
this bounce
back yeah
the house
yeah
ah it was something yeah we were getting
we were getting kind of
low-key sick
yeah i was i was yeah i was i was
feeling kind of sick and we went down
the airplane i was like oh my gosh do i
feel this dizzy that i felt like there
was a lot of shaking but then it turns
out there was shaking so yeah yeah yeah
but then we
landed and we were welcomed by the whole
hotel stuff basically uh-huh mm-hmm and
and we met our butler as we tell it we
should i should skip for all of this
because we already talked about this i
think um
okay let me read okay so uh
did we talk about
let's skip to the let's skip to the the
the first breakfast joshua
uh but this is how was this
dinner
yeah this was our first dinner but it's
just we ordered
so basically we we each get like one uh
starter one main course and one dessert
so she didn't really know what to order
so i ordered for her so we got like this
uh chicken satay it was yummy this and
this is also chicken wrapped with leaves
so it was like a southeast asian
restaurant so like oh i know this it
looks so cool yeah
uh i like this one and the other one
that you the starters that you ordered
for me i like them very much
that's good that's good so here we are
on our first the day of your first night
we were gonna go to breakfast it was
still
pretty
the wind was really really strong um but
we were like yo they have such nice
tables on the beach so let's eat there
so we sat down there but it was really
hard to eat breakfast because the wind
was so strong
yeah
the wind keeps feeding yeah my hair yeah
but i think like we were thinking we
don't know how the weather is gonna be
all the time so as long as it's not
raining we make use of it and sit
outside
yup
that's what we did i uploaded my
breakfast every day guys so if that's
something you're interested in look on
twitter now
with in between those trees looking at
the most beautiful water it's amazing
yeah yeah it's so nice
i saw the photos on twitter and like uh
the comments like the skies look so
cloudy but i guess it was cloudy but
like a lot of times it was it's not as
cloudy as it looks i guess it's not that
bad it was still
well the first few days
uh even when it stopped raining it was
still so cloudy that i never saw the sun
but
oh yeah it was still it was still kind
of bright and warm
i guess like ah the first few days it
was kind of cold actually it was like
maybe in what
i think it was definitely under 20
degrees even though it said on the
weather report it said like 30 degrees
it felt like 15 degrees celsius guys
celsius yeah yeah
so that was a lie
yeah we kept checking the weather report
and i'm like so the weather effort
report says it's something degrees and
i'm like yeah nah and that's a lie
because we didn't really feel that was
accurate at all but
the water was still
warm enough to
go in every day
and
i did i did go in i did go in and eat uh
oh uh we did
the first thing we did right like back
yeah near our yeah yeah we did and uh
uh i also during the breakfast i just
walked away from the table to check out
like a hermit crab and hermitage yeah
yeah because
i don't know what was i was getting
impatient and i was like yo
it looks so pretty i was just eating and
she was just like oh she went to the
center like what is she doing
i took a picture of her for private use
i took a picture of her just like
looking at her
it's so funny it was cute
but yeah did we did we we already told
you guys right that afterwards we bought
went and bought super expensive floaties
um
and then there's the floaty story
[Music]
oh i'll tell i'll tell the completes yes
tomorrow i'm gonna have comics drawn
yeah
and then after that after the floaty
story um there was i think there was
like it was it started storming again
because like it was storming literally
all the time and then we streamed for
you guys and then elena after the stream
tried on the the daniel dress that i got
her yeah yeah yeah yeah you want to talk
about it
oh yeah so basically like obviously it
was my first time wearing uh their nose
how you pronounce it yeah
she was helping me like put it on and
stuff so i was like yeah and it actually
like fit really well and you know the
fact that you can uh pretty much like
adjust like the you know oh how how
tight things are yeah because there's
like ribbons
yeah yeah there's like ribbons there
were like two right the the blue one and
the pink one
yeah yeah yeah yeah so you can choose
and
i got here like a mostly blue dress she
posted a picture a close-up of the dress
on twitter guys if you haven't seen it
yeah yeah super close-up you can't
really see anything but like you can see
the patterns and clothes
oh
yes yes yes i could probably find it but
uh never mind it's a it's just like a
blue dial with like floral patterns
the main dress is like dark blue and
then there's a light blue apron i think
and then there's like yeah yeah pink
ribbons on the top that's like kind of
like a corset kind of oh yeah that's
cute i told you aina you need to get a
push-up bra because
the diagonal dresses are really meant to
enhance your booba
yeah yeah she told me that i'm like i
don't own any in my um yeah i've never
really owned push-up bras in my entire
life but i guess just for the dirndl
i'll get i'll get one
oh yeah and i also explained to her that
you guys don't know this i suppose but
like for the apron for the dinner dress
um there's a tradition how on which side
you tie the ribbon and depending on if
you tie it on the right side or the left
side or the middle or the back it has
different meanings like for example that
you're taken or that you don't have a
boyfriend or that you're uh that you
that you ha that you're a widow and
there was one more i think i'm not sure
but yeah sorry i thought
then
that's our uh
that was our gift exchange i was really
so relieved to see that it fit because
that was my biggest worry
it's always
it's the dinner single somebody asked
oh yeah anyway yeah because you're
asking it's always really nerve-wracking
to like
get somebody something that requires
measurements like clothes and stuff
i just realized because of the comment
that you read um
and i forgot to say that dandel
the word that is used to
call the dress is
um
a dialect word uh
that means girl
oh
so it's basically the dress is called
girl
girl yeah yeah
it's kind of weird i never really think
about that but uh chad reminded me about
that
it's a it's kind of like a
austrian or like
south germany
um
dialect word because we speak some kind
of dialect um in some parts of germany
and austria
yeah bavarian austrian dialect and
dandel the real word for girl is median
so how i wonder how did it go from
methane to dandelion we will never know
yeah you'll never know
i don't even know that word that's an
old german word isn't it
anyway anyway anyway so yeah i helped
wear the
the uh gentle and then after the stream
i wanted to to go swimming again but it
was already cold and raining
ah but then
on the previous day
on the evening we reserved a massage for
the evening of the second day on on
tuesday yes yes yes yes we were so
excited for that
[Music]
and there was right list of of massages
that we could do and i wanted to do a
thai massage because um yeah i've done
like so many different massages until
now and i kind of like the thai massage
because it kind of they stretch your
body um as well huh so reina went with
the same massage and i think that should
be the next picture this is the next
picture it should be maybe i know oh
that was just oh no that was
a different
yeah you see here
alcohol free
italian fashion drink
yeah italian fashion drink
nice yeah it tasted oh it probably
tasted good i guess
it didn't quite taste so much like
uh
alcohol i don't know it was fine it was
yummy it looked fancy sweet and nice
yeah it looks fancy too yeah so that was
fashion drink that was like a welcome
bottle yeah thank you very much for the
welcome bottle thank you and then yeah
at first you were like oh okay okay yeah
that was a massage
the moment we entered the room and was
like yo
that's the window
oh
you can look at them yeah look at that
yeah cause you you put your you put your
head through here right and when you
look down you could actually see the
waves and
no there were no fish i think uh but
yeah
this was bad weather i don't know if you
can see but holy [\h__\h] during the massage
it was getting so stormy that i was
really worried about the house blowing
away
what i was half asleep
i i even
joked and asked my massage therapist so
you don't you don't remember
no i don't i was too busy sleeping
but it was really really really really
loud
really that's you know the waves for
relaxation to help you
it was really stormy like really a vibe
it got really bad during the massage you
know but anyway we had our massages here
before they start the massage they do
like a dum-dum
and then they walk around your table
singing bowl yeah or something i think
that's what it's called singing singing
ball
singing bowl like a bowl of food um
yeah i think that's what it's called but
anyways yeah singing bowl
really yeah
yeah guys what is it called what is this
called
singing boss that's a weird name it's
cool
i told you
keep it 10 meditation balls see i would
prefer that one that sounds more legit
really i don't know you're just trying
to reject the facts yeah some people say
it's a singing ball but i don't like
that that sounds stupid
what do you mean so stupid you sound
okay stupid next next next next yeah but
it was really nice and then i took one
more after the massage before after
before yeah before and after they even
have like a nice tub over there a round
big tub that but that was even bigger
than our tub that we had yeah yeah is it
wait is it i think it's just more
circular i guess so i guess so that was
really cool i guess because some people
take a bath here after maybe getting
appealing or something
yeah yeah
that was a really really nice massage
but as you can see
uh it's already getting dark here right
but it was before 8 p.m on the later
days it was still very bright at this
time
but because it was so stormy it got dark
really really fast outside
yes yes
yeah
afterwards
actually at this very point of time it
was raining really strongly and we ran
from this building to the next
area
we ran over to the place where there was
the sauna and the jacuzzi
and ah yeah there you go cause they
served and we had our food and drinks
what was this
um walnuts uh walnuts coconut uh some
coconut pieces and then some very
raising like
dried berries
yeah lena was eating a lot of that and
we chose the same tea so we got some tea
here and this was the the jacuzzi but at
this point of time it was ice cold so we
didn't use storming now
but we were chilling we used the sauna
that day
uh no i don't do we i don't know
let me check my name maybe we just ate i
don't remember i don't think so
yeah we might have not
maybe we didn't go in i'm not sure yeah
maybe we didn't maybe we didn't no no i
don't think so i don't think so because
like the next days that's where we were
like hey you want to go sauna
okay
yeah and then we had dinner afterwards
uh we had like a grill grill dinner
it was like a grill restaurant
oh yes yes um
yeah yeah yeah yeah it was just like
your salad
and then she was like are you not eating
this or something i'm like i don't know
[Laughter]
she keeps expecting me to eat all of
like you know i like vegetables but i'm
less used to like this is the salad
yeah she likes her salad
this was really weird because like this
looks like like some kind of sauce to
you guys right but it was like it was um
not liquefied what's the word it was
it was it was solid the solidified um
solidified yeah but basically it's
mozzarella and and tomatoes but it was
really yummy mm-hmm
you seem like you were enjoying your
food yeah that's your salmon my main
course was salmon
bread africa what was it what was the
word whatever and some yummy carrots
and oh i love these uh these thingies
these green thingies and this i think
was a block of potato
potato
no no i guess it was braised maybe it
was braised i don't know
yeah it was yummy yummy very yummy yummy
and dessert and then that's yours
yummy dessert
i don't remember what what that was mmm
just some just some cake it was
something something cake it sounded good
though but what did i order i don't
remember what did you like uh
for the first day oh i don't know that
was the second dinner
in the grill in the grill you remember
the grill
[Music]
yeah i just i remember my main course i
already like surf and turf and then for
the starter i ordered like some um yeah
stuff
the dessert i just don't remember oh
well oh yeah the servants
looked so fancy because they opened up
that
lobster i don't know was it lobster yeah
yeah yeah yeah the the i don't know the
shrimp like thing the beef cream
shrimp
it looked it looked
nice but
yeah was it good yeah it was good it was
good yeah mm-hmm okay
good
i was good this was included uh so we
had like breakfast included and dinner
included that was half bored but there
were some things on the on the menu that
were not included wasn't your surf and
turf was not included i think
um so it's like some i have to pay extra
from for stuff so like my starter in
this restaurant with my startup and my
main course was you know i had to pay
extra but i was like okay i like grill i
like stuff
i just want to splurge a little bit
on the stuff i like and some things were
not included because they were just a
little bit too expensive and fancy i
guess for the hotel to include it in our
half board but generally things are
included and then the drinks were extra
yeah yeah yeah yeah drinks will you have
to pay a hundred percent okay i also
took pictures of my food but maybe i'll
share them
yeah not on this stream maybe later okay
so that was basically
a tuesday evening
and after dinner
we just went to
a bed and i guess i showed you
uh i started showing you animal videos
wait was that the second night i don't
think i think we no we watched i think
we watched last night i showed you
scrubs and then on the second night i
showed you animal videos because i
connected to the wi-fi
and then no animal videos was italian
night i think okay
okay remember because you are like i'm
gonna hit you and i'm like there's
yeah and then i first showed you i guess
half cell
anime prison yeah that
[Laughter]
anime i know
that anyway but she always calls it
anime prison yeah yeah the first night i
showed her scraps because i downloaded
them on disney plus and then on the
second night i guess because i connected
to the wi-fi suddenly it said i can't
use disney plus anymore on my ipad uh
yeah because it recognized that i'm in
the motives even the downloaded ones i
couldn't watch anymore so but it was
really really sad about it because she
really liked that one episode of scratch
i really liked it it was my first time
watching
i liked it i'm glad you like it you
should you should continue watching it
it's really cool
yeah so we started watching some other
stuff on on netflix because at least
netflix was available yeah
yeah yeah and then it was wednesday and
uh i wrote down i woke up early because
i slept early i fall i fell asleep so
early and then i woke up day night oh
yeah and then i was like i looked
outside we finally had decent weather
and shallow water so i woke up with dana
and i was like
wake up we should try going snorkeling
and
ah
oh i wrote we didn't see much but still
fun and motivated and happy first time
too and apparently like uh they provided
the stuff for free
they uh we can rent them for free we
didn't have to pay yeah i bought the you
know
so my setup for taking pictures and
stuff was basically just you know i put
my iphone on the you know the waterproof
case thingy that costed 50 dollars by
the way
i'm still very salty about that i feel
you i kind of i feel like you know i
have to treasure this i will never lose
this because it costed me so much
yeah yeah yeah but i remembered why i
wrote that we didn't see much because um
we first started snorkeling um around
our over water villa
we didn't go to the reef yet in the
morning we went later on
because yeah because we were snorkeling
yeah we were stronger
behind the house and it was just really
i i only saw like like two tiny a
seafood fish and then i called elena
over but when she came to me i couldn't
find them anymore so yeah we didn't
really see anything but we tested out
the snorkeling stuff and then wanted to
use it again later because we were
really really motivated then no
so then uh we had breakfast and then uh
uh
oh yeah after breakfast this was when we
yeah we did a cocktail class
when we walked in here it was like for a
moment it was no rain but once we sat
down
the rain was pouring down so much that
it got really loud we could barely hear
the cocktail guy
remember
yeah i guess you know the weather is
like that that's why we have to you know
every time it's not raining we have to
make the most out of it yeah
with our yeah
yeah
just like the participation in the
cocktail mocktail class was pretty
spontaneous our butler kept on updating
us every day they had like um like a
schedule for rainy day activities which
i thought was really nice they had what
kind of stuff did they have
the hat and the basket weaving class for
example they had that yes yes yes yes
basket weaving
yeah
but the thing was that we reserved it
and then it was actually good weather at
that moment so we didn't go
we were like sorry
we're not going because it's nice
weather for once but anyway first was
the cocktail mocktail class i just was
kind of interested
because i was hoping that he would uh
maybe show us some mocktails too and he
did
[Music]
so first he started out making
margaritas
right
remember and he was a nice guy
he wasn't i do remember
yeah he made it
but then and then that's your drink he
was like
he was putting the the glasses there and
then like he we were like what six
participants i think
not many yeah yeah yeah and then i i
asked uh if he could maybe
make me a mocktail because i don't drink
alcohol and he was like all right one
second what do you like and uh uh he
made me a passion fruit
something something
oh
boy
pineapple
maybe it was pineapple yeah
yeah yeah that's like the only thing
that he had was pineapple i'm pretty
sure yeah yeah yeah
she has a special drink just for her
everybody else gets the same thing yeah
i tried a little bit of that tiny
yeah i know but yeah i tried a little
bit of that was good yeah i got the big
glass and everybody got those small tiny
baby margarita glasses
tiny baby yeah yeah i guess that's not
how you usually serve a margarita
usually it's a bit bigger glass right
but but that he basically served it in
shot glasses
[Music]
but sorry he made me this and then i
asked for a second straw and i said it
and then i forgot which straw was a mine
and hers and then i kept on like mixing
it
i was like no i was trying to help her
like i think mine is this and i'm like i
don't know i might have switched it
around i'm like what
and i was like i i think i switched it
around do you think you switched it
around
oh well
it was good yeah it was good yummy i was
happy i got a whole big ass drink and
then he made a second round
what's the second round of drinks that
he made
ah no he didn't make it there was like a
korean couple and the the girl made it
right
he asked like us like anybody want to
volunteer and try to make you know the
ground and then so this person just be
like yo actually
her husband like she explained her
husband made her do it she was like what
am i doing what why am i why am i
standing here now in front of the mixing
table i don't know what to do my husband
made me do it
yeah but she did a good job yeah
the mixer the mixer guy he told her how
to do it and then she mixed it for
everybody um it was like oh yeah he
asked her like what kind of drink do you
want to make and they just chose some
fruity fruity elements and he said okay
we can make a cocktail out of anything
and then yeah they made a cocktail
delicious
[Music]
okay so after that the weather cleared a
bit and we went back to a hotel room our
house and we streamed
mario kart on dana's channel if you
missed it not mario kart mario kart
mario smash we we we we stream smash
my notes say mario kart what the [\h__\h]
yeah we're streaming smash
before that actually we still had like
some time and then you were actually
trying to unlock like the yeah yeah we
were waiting actually to get uh the
internet fixed because something didn't
work anymore and in the meantime
we prepared and i also yeah i unlocked
some characters and i showed reina what
the game looks like because she didn't
play it before hmm yeah yeah it was
actually the stream on my channel it was
my absolute first time touching the game
so yeah yeah like yeah was actually
really pretty good you know
like unlocking like the thingies and
stuff yeah
but elena when i was playing against you
maybe it was because i was we were
streaming and then i kind of was like
shitty really bad at the game
but it was fun so we streamed and then
um afterwards
now okay here continues i don't think i
really have photos yeah this in between
this is already dinner i don't have
photos from this but uh my notes say
that after the stream i wanted to go
swimming because the weather was okay
um but it was already high tide and it
was pretty
the wind was really strong but i wanted
to use
oh yeah that's that's the floaty
floaty get on two points down
second time
i threw it and then you expected
wait wait wait wait don't spoil it do
you want to draw that one too right
now okay fine yeah it wasn't sad
dude
we were so excited
it had a happy end
[Music]
about no we were so excited about
italian right but then it turned out
yeah yeah italian like but but no wait
wait wait
you we're forgetting a big story here
too
after the floatie 2.0 story um
uh we were like okay
let's let's go to the sauna um in the
jacuzzi so it was actually not raining
and we i was like yo because it's not
raining how about we don't call the
butler for once and we walk on our own
oh my [\h__\h] so
yeah we walk out we take we walk outside
our house and you know there's like this
maybe you guys can imagine there's like
you know all the over water villas are
connected by one long big path
so we started walking that way
maybe like for 10 meters or 20 meters
and then i hear like no i just
no yeah i heard a big thunder and i was
like oh that's the thunder that we were
waiting for
because it was like throughout the thing
everybody keeps saying oh yeah
thunderstorm
we don't even see any thunder yeah and
at this point we were already used to
the cloudy weather and then
we hear lightning it's like thunder oh
that's the thing that we've been waiting
for that's thunderstorm i heard it and
relax
suddenly while we're still walking on
that path it starts pouring down in
buckets and buckets and bubbles a
warning
and and
we
when i say we i mean mostly rainer
starts to panic
and we run we won two teams
and we we
run to take cover under the entrance of
like a different villa which was kind of
it was kind of awkward because like
elena um
panicking and then they opened up the
door and they were like i lost that
it was another korean couple surprise
surprise and they were like
what's up and i'm like sorry sorry we're
just taking cover sorry we're just
taking cover yeah and then they go back
inside it was awkward because they were
having like a huge fight and then yeah i
think they were having a fight and then
they heard it she wasn't cold and i'm
like how can you be not caught and then
she's like and the ac is so cold i'm
like are you serious
oh
it really wasn't that cold it wasn't i
think lena was just like because of the
rain you were you were like
panicking the apparently p-files don't
want to get wet
yeah
that's why you're not a duck you're a
p-file
[Music]
but yeah anyway so we were like do we
walk i was like i'm gonna run back and
then you were like no you wanna like i
don't know we were trying to sort of
like contact our butler but like
i i just like didn't know how to get the
phone because like i think where was my
phone it was somewhere out of reach
because like we were like so we're like
drenched basically
and then
then we were hoping for someone to pick
us up because there was some staff
people driving with their carts on that
path
but they were driving really slow and
didn't go to come to us and then one
drive passed and we were like okay i
guess they're not gonna help us
um
but then
suddenly
our butler drives by
with uh reyna's new floatie
uh on in the back of the cart
trying to bring him out of
like she wanted to like bring it while
we were somewhere else i guess to
surprise us hey it's already in your
room and then we see her and we're like
hey hey hey hey we're literally just 10
meters away from our house but can you
can you quickly pick us up and then we
go in there we go into the car we drive
to an apartment our house and then elena
is like i need to i need to quickly take
a hot shower because i'm freezing so
cold i'm like okay okay
it was a storm
it was a storm it wasn't even like some
rain
okay okay
okay
i think you maybe had like i have this
maybe sometimes like even when it's not
that cold
i have this like cold shock sometimes
maybe you had something like that
maybe when you feel like
you're like even though it's not that
cold you're like shaking and
shivering i have that sometimes
sometimes
maybe
i felt really cold with the rain but
like the ac i was totally fine it was
like even it was only like 21 degrees
celsius why did you think it was cold i
think i think it's because you're out of
uh my mom always says that you're made
out of out of sugar and when it rains on
you
you're gonna fall apart and melt because
you're made out of sugar so that's why
you panicked
what
you're wearing
you're so sweet you're made out of sugar
so the rain hurts you because it makes
you melt
but basically you know i was first i was
also surprised by the big rain i was
like yeah but then i you know i just
tried to think logically this is just
water it's not gonna hurt me so let's
just wait until it calms down
i tried something close body temperature
it hurts my body okay after the hot
shower i was fine though yeah yeah she
quickly took a hot shower and then we
had the butler drive us
because it was still raining we wanted
to walk but then it was still raining so
she drove us to the sauna we went there
we chilled like in the sauna warmed up
in there and
oh what's that um
wait let me read where did you drive
at this point
drive this back
uh
oh yeah lena takes a quick hot shower
because she's freezing like as if it was
the antarctica is what i wrote
what is the stuff that you wrote okay
fine
and then
we then finally dropped the sauna we
kind of got loki third wheeled someone
came into the sauna when we were in
there right yes
and we were in the middle of a
conversation about like something whole
life related so we were like
oh and then we were just like
no cause we were like sort of like lying
down and we had to like sit up yeah
because it was a really small sauna like
it had like two rows you you could lie
down on each row but then there would be
no more space to sit so then we set up
and then we like we didn't want to leave
immediately i think but once that person
entered i think both no it was not the
british guy was a different guy but it
was a different one yeah once he entered
i think both of us were like let's let's
just uh not go out immediately because
that feels like we're leaving because of
that guy and that's kind of awkward
let's just wait like two three minutes
and then
go out saying oh it's so hot did we have
like a small
um
communication for our brains in that
moment because i think we did i think so
and then we were supposed to go to
dinner right but then as we were getting
picked up the guy was like yeah
apparently like they asked if like oh
like is it okay if like the guy
the guy
because the guy was asking for his own
butler yeah and the staff was like is it
okay if the guy joins you
yeah yeah and i'm like
we
said yeah because we're nice
but the guy ended up saying no thank you
yeah yeah so he didn't join us
yeah he can read the room after all
so
yeah
oh yeah but by the way i tried the
jacuzzi again before that but it was
still cold so we still didn't go in
no wait no wait no this is wrong this is
wrong we both get out for after a while
try the water but it's surprisingly
lukewarm and it's already cold because
of the wind so now ah okay it was not
ice cold it was like lukewarm but it was
cold outside so we didn't go
no
and then we went to dinner and finally i
can switch pictures
we were so excited for italian but i
misunderstood something we didn't have
italian we went to the the first
restaurant again yeah we went to the sea
restaurant uh this is your dream this is
your drink my drink this time i ordered
some duck curry
curry
yes
curry how is it it was good
it was really good i took a picture too
oh man
um
i had a starter this tonka guy soup
which was really good um but the one you
spilled
in a second so i was i was trying to i i
was using a spoon because you use a
spoon when you eat a soup and then some
of the chicken pieces in there were so
big and i tried to separate them and
then suddenly because the bowl was so
round like [\h__\h]
it spilled over and it was like so
embarrassed but i was trying to play i
was trying to play it cool though and i
was like oh
you are always saying like oh rain is so
clumsy you might need something really i
this is my only clumsy incident planet
you hit yourself a million times during
this trip
no seniors you are so unnecessarily
observant
necessarily people and people appreciate
my details alright
i guess so but also
yeah also it was really cute and she was
like trying to drink the soup because it
was yeah she has a very severe case of
nikolajita and she kept trying to like
i thought it was cute
yeah she was having such a hard time
eating yeah it was so good but it took
me so long to eat because it was really
really hot in the beginning you know
but but i after i i didn't spill
everything but when they helped me to
clean it up they wanted to take away my
soup but i was like no i'm not done i
want to continue eating
so they left it and i finished eating it
okay and then oh this was my
main it was ah yeah yeah yeah yeah
some kind of noodles
really yummy really yummy but
you don't see it but this is a huge
[\h__\h] serving it was like a mountain
okay
it's a [\h__\h] one yeah it was kind of
yeah i guess it was so much yeah yeah it
was so much it did look good though that
that on top i think it's an omelette
it's a egg they made it look so fancy
yeah
fancy it reminds me of your hat
did spiderman serve this
spot you mean because of this pattern
yeah the food makes me finally of your
hand
oh yeah it's my hat
true true and then
like while we were eating i noticed on
the ceiling i noticed this little friend
hello
and then i got i am happy and i took a
photo
and why are you sighing
no nothing it's cute it's cute excited
yeah we don't really see these much but
elena told me they're really common like
in
also in indonesia
to show up in houses but we only see
them in like forests maybe
i was like asking like you don't have
those and like yeah we have those and
i'm like okay sure and then i started
telling her a story about like how in my
house something something something and
she was like wait you have them in
houston yeah
[Laughter]
that's very very interesting i guess
because of the climate they show up yeah
maybe maybe
i guess so
so then we went back we were very sleepy
or i was very sleepy we watched netflix
show
happily with reyna but immediately fell
asleep raina liked it that's my notes
what what did we watch
that was when we started animal
uh
videos now
wait i thought animal videos was italian
night did we all just watch something
else i don't know i don't remember i
don't know
i think first first night scrub second
night hard sell fortnite heart cell and
animal videos fourth night only animal
videos
all right i think it was maybe like wait
it doesn't matter
but yeah they never
was happy
i always fell asleep
really quickly and she put away the ipad
eventually quickly yeah
it's not normal though
not normal it's not money yeah that's
what i heard like oh you always have
trouble falling asleep you have to watch
netflix for hours
really so you're saying i'm calming
that's good to know
actually no that's not true you you were
really really not calming
but maybe my mind wanted to um
escape that uncalmingness
and then yeah you're my your mind
cooking
anyway we always had like comfy ipad
netflix nights so that was nice uh and
then this was first
thursday just a random picture of the
ocean by the breakfast area we woke up
to good weather um but this was even
better than the previous days actually
yeah starting from wednesday it was
getting better and better
oh yeah right wait let me see better no
yeah yeah yeah yeah no wednesday was
still the
wednesday was the raining incident so
first day was where it got really good
and friday was really good too and
saturday as well yeah it was really good
so three days of shitty weather and
three days of good weather
yeah yeah that's a little bit more
appreciative of the good weather yeah
but look at that clear water it's so
pretty
yeah
so we welcome to good weather it says
this
but this time later yeah yeah
before the breakfast i guess oh after i
think before again
um
we went snorkeling in the morning again
but in a different spot
i guess so but this time like i was like
it's too cold and then rain it motivated
me like she went in first and she was
like it's okay
in my in the house in the house though
first we went uh close to our area to
get wet first and then we walked over to
the to the reef yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and i think
that was the first time
we went to the reef right
yes and then the other there was another
was there another couple on that day
like
or was that the next day i think they
were wearing these
they're the orange floaty like on the
all of the korean couples were wearing
like some safety west vests and stuff
and some special equipment
uh maybe they were scared of drowning
but i always felt like these korean
couples they were like extra secure
while we only had the snorkel equipment
we're cool we don't need those floaty
security vests
like in the first place though i don't
even know where we could get
them and then they were like people with
maybe there were people with shoes too
like but then i also kind of agree
because like remember the the corals
were like kind of sharp
so maybe next time i would consider
getting yeah the shoes the shoes make
sense yeah but i don't know about the
vest like because when you're snorkeling
i'm not a good swimmer but when you
snorkel you always stay
like at the top anyway like you don't
drown it's it's like kind of like
impossible you float on the top
so yeah i guess so
we also use the scuba scuba scuba shoes
too right and if the flippy flippy shoes
down the flip-flops mermaids
yeah mermaid mm-hmm
so yeah we went we went snorkeling and
now i guess i'll show you guys one of
the snorkeling videos that raina took
wait did you did you uh did you download
the newer one with the clear finish i
thought i liked the other one because
the colors are
more uh super blue or turquoise yeah i
like it actually okay okay okay all
right all right you can show that one
okay so lena used her 50 dollar phone
case
[Laughter]
to take some videos of the fish i looked
for the video and
i feel like i saw
a lot more fish but you saw one special
fish one really special yeah
okay let's look it's just kind of hard
if you're like taking videos
but it's so cool that you made this
video because now we can show underwater
footage wow look at this well fish elena
taking fish videos then we have like
striped fish here black and white
zebra fish then we have these typical
all she cut there but here comes the
special fish not these
the things but this one
whoa what is it yeah yeah yeah yeah guys
what is this reyna was asking what is
this
yeah it looked like an eel but it's
probably not an eel but it's like
this was special i didn't see this one
trumpet face yeah trumpet fish really
long feet needle fish
what's that fish trumpet let me look up
trumpets trumpet food [\h__\h] fish let me
look that up too
oh that looks i guess kind of like it
yes but not really it has different
colors oh
yeah what the maybe uh maybe maybe maybe
it looks like it looks like one maybe
it's a younger version because there's
some that look similar and some that
don't look similar
mayhaps no i am yeah it could be that
here
okay wait what's the needle fish then
needle
fish what's needle fish there are also
like some fish uh yeah that looks
dangerous
oh my gosh the first needlefish attacks
indonesian team on a fishing trip
hey but this one looks more like it to
be honest
it could have attacked you
could have attacked it
oh my god
it's good that i blended in with the
fish
are you sure but then they probably knew
that they were dealing with a people
okay but okay that was special i saw oh
yeah the one special thing that i saw um
that i never saw again was a fish with a
long
horn on like a unicorn on its forehead
and the guy in the tourist shop told me
uh
the name of it which was such an obvious
name like horn fish i think
but what was that i also saw like a flat
white fish but that was on the other day
i couldn't get
unicorn fish goldfish no
no i'm not what
now i don't know
no i don't know no not that what the
[\h__\h] no no no
that's what the [\h__\h] is that
that's just
energy with a long unicorn horn
what no no no
no
spiky head fish swordfish um maybe sword
swordfish
it didn't have any special colors it was
just like grayish whitish no not a
swordfish it was not on its mouth it was
on its on its forehead
i'm just looking at pictures of fish
he's scary okay
porn well maybe i'll find out later
again but yeah let's continue watching
this wow yeah fish
oh
see yellow fish so cute wow they were
always in the next one
i had to mute the audio because it was
just like
occasionally i'm like
[Laughter]
there were a lot of those
i think
yeah the strap fish that was cute
oh this one looks funny
i saw that one too i think ah rainbow
this one's the rainbow one it no
that's not the rainbow one the rainbow
one was black there were multiple
rainbow ones yeah yeah okay fine this is
another rainbow
that's one of the parrotfish because
their mouth looks like a parrot mm-hmm
funny period for real
bye-bye bye-bye parrot fish
oh more of these
there was more variety i think but it
was i think they had some problems
filming them all
yeah it was it was real
so the real footage was like 10 minutes
or something and it's like
i don't know
yeah sorry i was really interested in
these because like they were just like
walking and chilling so there was yeah
there's a lot of footage of these little
guys
[Music]
wow wow
wow yeah so cool
wow nina took actually sometimes she got
me on camera
too
that's why i have to cut those
i have to cut those but but hey can you
send me those later too because i want
to see how i'm snorkeling how i look
when i'm snorkeling
no i was just um it wasn't there wasn't
really anything clear i said i sent you
the non-snorkeling stuff but like i'm
gonna re-watch the footage thank god i
felt like i feel like
there were much more colorful ones too
guys don't get this wrong there were a
lot of fish a lot of fish yeah there
were a lot of fish
wow
fish
i see
so many like literally everywhere you
look there were fish
everywhere
well coral as well
a fish
these ones are really nice
striped zebra fish that dipped their
face in
something yellow what's yellow
what's yellow oh these look those those
are nice too there's some kissy fish i
know some of those you call like kissy
fish or something like that oh so pretty
i'm so close they're like yo stop
stalking me get away from me social
distance girl
no it's like i wanted to get away
because they're the ones that won't go
away oh yeah mustard they're dipped in
mustard
yeah
um oh what's this
hello fish
yeah there was like there was like also
like some footage of me like stalking
the blue fish there was like one blue
fish but then yeah i didn't i didn't
give her that because like she only
needed like three minutes anyway so i
was like yeah bye mom
yeah okay
thank you for the precious footage
[Music]
yeah it's really really special that's
so cool i was really worried about your
phone but thank god the the water didn't
go in
yeah i was actually my first time to
taking this kind of video
it was hard i wanted to take pictures
but with the current yeah with that kind
of setup it just wouldn't oh yeah
it wouldn't press in underwater so yeah
oh yeah you were struggling a lot
like sometimes you said that the waves
turned like pushed the the photo button
and took photos
[Applause]
i had like some several like zero zero
videos too because of the stupid waves
thai hand
apparently like there would be sometimes
some baby sharks and depending on the
season there could be like mountains and
all that but we really didn't see
anything we were mostly satisfied
satisfied with the fish that we saw but
i think in the future when we go
snorkeling again we want to look for
like even more
special
fish and sharks and mantas and all kinds
of stuff yeah but there's someone we
were happy with what we saw but
apparently you can see even more special
um water fish there
we didn't meet baby gouda no no no no no
no
yeah sad sad
they said they show up there but i don't
know
wow maybe
maybe they didn't want to see us maybe
they were shy
or you like actually like um you know be
because we were snorkeling or staying
mostly like on the um
how to explain this
like there's this reef right and then
there's like a cliff where it gets
really deep deep deep but we stayed uh
yeah on the on the side before it goes
really deep so if if you go
deeper i suppose you can see some more
special ones yeah we stayed pretty
pretty close to the dock and to the
um shallow area mm-hmm but i don't know
i went there there wasn't really
anything the fish were like mostly
chilling like right here
anyway and when it gets so deep it was
really hard to see as a snorkeler we
need to like go deeper because it gets
like really dark there
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh maybe we can
dive next time i don't know that sounds
exciting but i also want to snorkel yeah
snorkeling
really i'm i'm so happy about that
that was my first time ever snorkeling
and i'm like i'm already so excited
are there any more snorkeling spots
maybe in indonesia or something i want
to go
yeah yeah
yeah so
then what what's here wasn't it and then
yeah weather getting better
uh wait what's my tropical amazing fish
super cool we were happy went to
breakfast
where the weather getting even better
after breakfast so we sat by the beach
again yeah we had breakfast by the beach
again and then um
yeah yeah and then we got oh yeah
afterwards after breakfast we
immediately got ready for swimming we
got our
towels did our even our makeup to look
cute a little bit
and then we went to the shore even there
lots of oh yeah a lot now when the
weather was good even by the shore we
saw lots of lots of fishies
know
yeah that turquoise fish that's a
different that's a different one that's
already the evening i have some photos
later
where i show how clearly you can see a
lot of like white and turquoise fish
yeah right at the shore like in the
shallow
area where you can walk right at the
beach it was really cool
so they needed some more videos on the
water and i uh we're using our floaties
now by the beach is way safer
oh thank goodness yeah yeah we're just
floating around for ages and i taught
her how to properly like get into the
floaty and let your legs stick out if
you know what i mean
yeah
but also if you do that then you can't
fight back when the waves try to get you
back to the yeah
i don't know
one at one point like elena um was like
already like she had her leg sticking
out so she couldn't move anymore and and
then she was
moved all the way to the shore pretty
quickly to the beach so i pushed her
like a mommy does mommy do what mommy
does i push her back into the water
really far and then like you go girl
[Laughter]
she did and then i got back into my
floating after i pushed her back into
the water
and then we chilled in the water
yeah and then just laid on the water
with our faces up like floating without
the floaties then we found some weird
trash i already talked about this like
uh i got the bottle i have a picture of
that oh gosh
yeah you should uh you should show show
me the picture
okay
i found out what those things were the
day before yesterday i talked about it
on my stream
yeah uh the barnacles
barnacles yeah they're called barnacles
and they're [\h__\h] disgusting
okay i'm
who didn't see the stream the day before
yesterday i just want to say the like
everything was really clean and all that
but sometimes from the ocean some things
would like um come to the beach from
outside the ocean and and then i think
every day staff members would like pick
it up because every next morning you
wouldn't really see it anymore and new
stuff would sometimes
come to the beach
but it wasn't that bad yeah mostly it
was like really really old stuff coming
there's from the ocean
how did you stand on this corn
oh sorry not discord because i'm lazy
okay well
then i can't show you guys
it's okay it's okay it was just some
disgusting looking trash you guys don't
want to see it
i can't yeah yeah you guys really don't
want to see it honestly
yeah
yeah but oh i i actually can uh real
quick i can't do that actually do you
guys want to see the trash with the
barnacles
do you guys want to see it i mean you
know we can like as soon as i get it
like you can show it
i want to see
now i'm even more interested all right
all right they want to see it right now
oh i'm sure oh my god
okay um i'll send it on your to your
discord okay
there we go yes but also no understand
you asked for it
like i also sent it to you a video but
like non-discord oh my god
oh my god okay i i got it
there it is um she was trying to like
flip it with like some some straight
coral and i'm like dude why why are you
doing it but we saw it first in the
water and then there was still like a
crab on it chilling and then it come
came to the face
of the crab when run away
yeah you disgusting
some transparent crabs
so not hermit crabs but actually
so these things they were breathing they
were coming in and out and in and out it
was really [\h__\h] disgusting
why are you trying to flip it yeah
that's that looks like a hand soap
bottle yeah it's the sad reality of the
ocean pollution
it may make me a little bit more aware
of it so that's something i guess
yeah
yeah anyway
[Music]
okay so oh yeah but then i i cut i cut
my foot
we both cut our foot several times but i
have this like one pretty
big cut on my on the uh sole of my foot
and i kept on getting sand in it and at
one point like when we were at the in
the room lana was helping me pouring
water over it so i could clean the sand
out it was really annoying
i had to clean it like every day like
two times because yeah it really hurts
even when there's just tiny pieces of
sand in there and i don't want it to
close before i get out the sand you know
[Music]
[\h__\h] sand ah i had abandoned all
right
yes i i kept i was this is one of the
smart things i brought a lot of
band-aids from home
and i kept on switching them because
after going into the water and walking
through the corals on the sand it would
go off and then i put on a new band-aid
because i had so many
yeah it's coarse and rough and it gets
[\h__\h] everywhere [\h__\h] sand
sorry that's the star wars meme do you
know the meme
no
it's close and rather you get it
irritating it gets everywhere [\h__\h] sand
star wars meme nicer uh
yeah so we cut ourselves a few times
and then we chilled on the beach chairs
this is where i got the sunburn the most
i think
until the dark clouds came i charged my
vitamin d
after that we just showered and chilled
in our villa
and then we talked ah and then and then
i
didn't take uh where's the picture
didn't take a picture um
i i brought one more souvenir for dinner
remember the cake
i have the picture i have the picture
show me something
you you look for it so i um in austria
we have this famous cake it's called
sacha torte sakha cake it comes from a
big um famous hotel chain in austria
called sacha hotel and
they have some like normally it's a big
round cake a chocolate cake with some
jam inside apricot jam it's really good
very chocolatey but they sell like they
sell it in small cubes as well to bring
it as a souvenir so
yeah we ate it together and they were
free cubes but i asked elena if i can
eat some too because i really love the
cake even though it was her souvenir but
i ate it too
so we snacked on that on our balcony
[Music]
i will show you guys
number one save
uh oh [\h__\h] this is when it's already
open oh well uh yeah so the three little
cubes with the sakura seal on top when
there's no seal then it's not the
original just so you guys know for
future
it's really yummy but it was very
chocolatey right
yeah yeah yeah it was very chocolatey
and then i i ate one she ate one and
then she's like i was gonna save it for
later but she was like do you want to
eat the other one i'm like oh yeah
sure
i wanted more so we split the third one
because i just wanted more yum yum yum
did you not take a picture wait did you
pass italian night yet no i guess not
i don't think we're there yet not yet
yeah so we ate that and then we
um
there was some
yeah okay uh this was before dinner i
think uh
wait
this was before dinner do you guys see
this hammock
oh my god
there's a there's a big big hammock in
the middle of the water here this is
when it was high tide and i was like
elena can you take a cute picture of me
in there we were
okay and we were on the way yeah to
dinner we were already like on our
dinner clothes and i'm like
where were we i think so no we were on
the way to the spa which was over here
wow because we wanted to go to the spa
before dinner we still had some time
um when was that time where i got my my
whole clothes like drenched because i
had to take a picture
don't know maybe another time oh yeah by
the way yeah continue to continue
continuing
so i was like can you take a picture i
want to try getting up there
um
[Music]
so i tried but the first of all the
waves are strong second of all corals
around here yeah first of all um like
here i i think i was still able to
low-key stand
but it was really hard to get up here
uh yeah especially
did i eventually yeah i tried but now
would you help me yeah so i got you you
had me help you yeah i got you to come
here and you held one side i held the
other side and then went up so because
otherwise it will always flip and flip
and flip and then he went back and then
he took they tried to take some pictures
and i tried to pose cutely but the wire
was so close all the time and i couldn't
pose cutely and you also couldn't get so
close because of the water you stayed
like around here the sun basically the
sun was like
back there so like you know like
problems oh hey son
yeah
it didn't look so good but i still felt
like that was quite the
accomplishment and a big effort it was
like an adventure trying to get up there
so
it was fun still
and we gave up eventually and
yeah
oh yeah yeah then we went to the spa to
the jacuzzi
uh this time this time we did go into
the jacuzzi right
i think so was that where we recorded
the the the
look
yeah exactly yeah later was the one who
started making the sounds on under the
water
i was like
and then and then we went actually we
went back to the room once because we uh
dressed up there and then i wanted to
put on like cute cute uh my cutest dress
but
they came with some pants and they
didn't fit so it changed again yeah
and then it was regretting that she
didn't bring fancy clothes
yeah
i asked you like before like so what
what stuff did you cause like i was also
considering bringing something fancy but
then i was like i don't know maybe if
she's like not bringing anything then i
i don't know and it's also going to be
like on vacation hobo mode
and then she betrayed me she brought a
fancy dress
yeah it was like just in case maybe
there's like one restaurant or one
dinner where we want to dress a bit more
fancy
and i thought you're gonna bring gucci
anyway so
what is it with gucci i don't know man
what do you keep saying gucci i know
this is my go-to brand for fancy fancy
clothes but
they didn't bring any gucci but i
brought this dress but it didn't fit
so sad
so sad man the pants were too small it
was like a dress that had some
see-through parts that's why it came
with some pants but the pants
were like
five sizes too small for me while the
rest of the dress fits
i hate that so much when that happens
[Music]
well then you had another dress and that
looked fine no i'm having a lot of
clothes with me so that's okay now yeah
finally we had italian food for dinner
uh yeah do i have that and that that
should be yes oh
wow it's still bright oh my god
yeah this is what the place because like
the weather was good
yeah
now it's so bright
and the weather's good it looks like
this
this pool this was the main pool that we
never entered
yeah we never did we never went in here
because we preferred the the ocean i
guess also here there's a special
honeymoon table
we wanted to sit there but they said no
because it's reserved for honeymoon
couple
and then i'm like hmm
yes
look at the flower petals there's some
flower petals on there yeah and they got
them yeah
they got the flowers also on the first
night remember we saw a table and we
but that was the first couple i think
oh okay i think that was that they were
also in honeymoon yeah they got a
special table too but those were two
different couples i think
because the first one was uh i think it
was a korean couple and this was not
korean couple
i'm observing i'm observing everything
honeymoon for three people there's three
chairs oh
yeah no no that was just two people
although
i did i did see some
some people
came
with more than one woman last night was
it yeah
but
yeah
a second probably yeah yeah on the grill
yeah and there was a little grill right
there
we had three women with him
but yeah
that was very fascinated by that we
talked about it for a while
yeah
well like
harem yeah it's a world basically a
harem yeah like a real
real-life hiram anime harem yeah
i saw that guys several times uh
throughout the vacation sometimes he was
with with like all of his three women
sometimes he was only with one of them
yeah i wonder what the other ones were
doing
oh well
so
uh we finally had italian food this is
some more this a different view this was
like the front and this is when you look
back
and inside there was a seating area too
which was important for later yeah very
important
very important oh and then this was my
starter my starter was so [\h__\h] good
it was literally just like
a toasted baguette with some prosciutto
some pear a lot of salad
balsamico
uh
and oh yeah some some cream under the
prosciutto [\h__\h] amazing yeah
what was your favorite italian uh mine
was like some really nice shrimp with
like nice garlic something something it
was really good too
i felt like in this italian restaurant
like the starter was kind of better than
what i have for the main course yeah me
too me too me too but maybe my mistake
was ordering a pizza they gave me a huge
[\h__\h] tune of pizza and i feel like i
should have tried something else
did you ever finish it yeah maybe not i
brought it to the room rabbit leg i ate
rabbit leg for wow
you're just eating all of the whole life
senpai's huh
curry
rabbit
italian food
yeah
yeah i guess so i also have my pictures
maybe i'll show it who's gonna be next
lena who are you gonna eat next huh
i don't know it depends what's on the
menu
you continue eliminating your senpais
until no one is left and you are the
senpai
[Music]
that's how it is
no no no no
yeah anyway but anyway it was good right
for the dessert i had to obviously why
did you have some uh lemon cake i think
yeah yeah there it is having lemony with
it was kind of almost like a creme
brulee top thingy um
not quite as crunchy as creme brulee but
it reminded me of it oh
yeah
in the southeast asian restaurant the
dessert that i got i had some pandan
creme brulee right the green one it was
really good yeah special creme brulee
the thing is special pandan cream maybe
guys if you look at the difference of
the table here it is a wooden table here
it's a different table so what happened
is suddenly it started pouring down
again we were under
under one of those thingies but still it
started raining on us as well so we went
inside here and finished our food in
there yeah yeah
oh oh yeah and then
i think um the the waiter we talked to
him on the next day too i think but um
he um like i was getting really curious
about living in the maldives so
yeah
he told us about like how expensive it
is and it was pretty cheap actually and
so we were both considering moving to
the walls
yes
so how are the details like how does
this go yeah
and how do you say like how much are
things around here
yeah but the thing is like
obviously the biggest dream would be to
live in like one of those villas that we
stayed in forever but those are just
good internet
but those are resort villas like i don't
think you can really like if you were to
buy
or rent one for long term
i think that would be insanely expensive
yeah
i think i would prefer like a more
spacious place like if we were to live
it like you live in it like long term
maybe yeah
the only realistic thing is to live on
the main island
and then from there on always take a
seaplane or a boat to one of the nicer
islands
but
obviously the biggest dream would be
just to be to live in that villa but i
think that's impossible oh well yeah
this is a random picture of um i wanted
to show this because the whole island
had these
like it was like a jungle of these paths
that connected to all kinds of
restaurants right
the golf cart
and you can see here on
the tracks of the golf cart for the
first couple days it was always huge
puddles of water
yeah yeah
but what impressed me was that after it
was finally done raining
um we saw when we walked down here we
saw like um
maintenance people with big big thingies
uh fixing the road
right they were flattening it again to
make it easy to drive yeah
very nice i thought that was really cool
because like usually we're like we
always see the beach but when you walk
through here it feels like a jungle
yep and i think like when the day
started you know uh
better weather we don't make use of the
golf carts that much anymore we prefer
kind of to kind of walk
i think it would be like a shame if we
didn't at least at least to the ones
that we the one the place is like the
spa and the red breakfast restaurant
where we knew they were close by
yeah some others when when the butler
was driving around with the cart it felt
like a [\h__\h] maze like where the hell
are we going
yeah yeah yeah yeah but around the end
we just went uh by foot and oh yeah
guys you know something don't say it
don't say it
what do you see that close-up version of
this
i mean of course you see
i wanted to take a picture of the
coconuts but yeah the camera was kind of
like making it look not so natural
but that's not what i mean guys
look closer
i maybe i need to make it closer do you
see it
do you see it
you see it now
now you should see it come on do you see
it
not the
camera you see it i'm gonna send you i'm
gonna send you i can zoom in
you see it guys
there's a gecko on the camera
[Laughter]
and her gekko fascination
this is cute
so there's security footage sometimes
must have like a gecko body on top of it
like no no stalking no no don't watch
these people only watch my body watch my
sexy gekko buddy
there was also like a snail somewhere i
have a picture of it but yeah
yeah one snail that we almost stepped on
oh yeah i was like oh no there's a snail
and then the butler picked up the snail
and put it into the grass
so sweet yeah
sweet be careful
this is finally a picture where i can
show you how clear it is
look at it yeah yeah yeah yeah
so clear it's so clear like this was
right at the beach side like literally
over there would be the beach
and you could see uh once the weather
was clear these fish
were here all the time all the time and
also under the beach villains here under
the shadow there were even more
maybe because it was cooler yeah these
swarms of fish they were protecting
themselves from the hot sun because they
don't want to get sunburned so clear i
love this like
this texture of the water you know
yeah
with the lights these these ah
wow
wow perfect water oh my god it's crystal
clear
crystal clear let me see what does my my
notes say um
oh yeah
wait this is already the next day uh
before that
after dinner i wrote uh
really really really talkative
this is this is the day
where she was so talkative about the
animal videos that i was going crazy
yeah
what do you
i just wanted to share my happiness uh
when it comes to watching animal videos
with you
okay wait have a good example um can you
please try to recreate your commentary
while i show this video again do it be
realistic what video this be a realist
okay um
ooh ambien blah blah
oh no
[Laughter]
basically like that yeah for half an
hour the whole time
i would quiz her like if i see her like
not paying attention i would be like and
then there's the narration like oh yeah
in this like in this region the you know
the seal does this and this like hey
kiara what range in what region did you
listen
um she bumped me i'm so sad yeah
she was like getting um okay it was cute
but i was it was really cute okay but i
was really really tired so
i know she was tired i'm so tired i'm
like
shut up
and then she bonked me
i didn't want to say it i didn't say
shut up i was just thinking shut up
[Laughter]
she was so done yeah like a mom is done
with her child
my child's too too active
mom is just like oh god please save me
yeah
but then then finally
after the one episode we went back to
the hard sell show and then i fell
asleep in five seconds literally
now
but but you were still not able to fall
asleep you were like running around the
room and like running outside the
balcony
you might get some
you make it sound like i was running
like wow
i wasn't i was quiet
i wasn't running i was walking i tried
my best okay
i was wondering
what were you even doing on the on the
night table there was something a little
bit louder
huh nighttime i don't know you were
doing something there were some noises
and then you went to the balcony and
then you went to the ninth oh i was
folding clothes i was holding clothes
i went to the bathroom to fold my
clothes i went to uh the bedside ah and
then i was like rustling through like uh
my my bag i have like multiple pouches
and stuff right yeah maybe that was it
now
i thought it was like 3 a.m but
apparently it was still like around
midnight when you were doing that yeah
it was midnight ish
very active that was the only day you
weren't like that though
i couldn't sleep okay was like no no
actually i was like feeling kind of emo
because i realized that oh no it's you
know we passed like the halfway point
and then like i was like oh no
but then like uh i guess you know yeah
sad but then i guess i'll just get it
try to get it off my mind by folding
clothes i need to anyways and then once
it hit like i guess 2 am i was like all
right we have to do yoga tomorrow which
we spoilers ended up not doing yeah and
then i i i tried going to sleep anyways
yeah we were like hey we're going
we woke up like every day around 8 00
a.m so early anyway and the morning yoga
starts every day at 8 am so we were like
how about we do it today actually like
tomorrow for once just for the
experience even though i don't really
like yoga do you like yoga
i have no opinion really it's not like
oh my god i love yoga so much but it's
like i'm okay
but then this time i don't know when we
were up in the morning i just i just
didn't feel like it uh i don't know
about you ain't them i just wanted to
chill in bed a little bit longer
yeah we ended up like just chilling on
the bed and stuff because oh i don't
feel like yeah we didn't wake up early
though right but then we just decided
not to go we just chilled on the bed for
an hour
yeah and then we finally woke up we had
breakfast first breakfast this was
friday this is friday and then we went
snorkeling again
um
oh this is actually
ah you took the video on the second
snorkeling day not on the first day
according to my notes
oh for real yeah i guess so
um and then
and then after the snorkeling session um
we were like okay let's let's swim
uh all the way back to the villa because
like we can enter the room through the
balcony
um
and then we swam it was really
exhausting and it took us quite it was
really difficult um
there wasn't even any fish on that side
wow so it was kind of like uh and i kept
on having more and more problems with my
uh
with my snorkel thingy
i kept on like getting water in my
goggles and in my breathing tube
and
started swallowing a little bit of sea
water and then one villa
next two hours in the neighboring villa
i stopped for a moment because i felt
really sick and elena was i went over to
her
yeah i went over to her like hey yo
what's up and i'm like yeah linda you
should quickly swim away because i think
i might throw up right now
i was like okay i'm gonna give her some
privacy i'm gonna go up
and she was basically swimming away
slowly slowly slowly so you didn't even
see it right
no i didn't it was embarrassing so i was
hoping that you wouldn't watch and every
time i like you know um first phase of
throwing up i quickly like smooshed it
away the water so that you wouldn't see
my embarrassing throw up accident and i
threw up again and i was like it's just
still not watching thank god quickly
quickly go make the water go away and
then again that was about
five times so my whole breakfast was
gone at that point um so sad
puking in the neighbor's backyard i
can't imagine yeah
thank you
no one else was there i didn't even know
and then you um i was i was up and then
you were like
you you told me uh i threw up and like
okay are you okay
just drink some water
yeah we chilled for a while i tried to
calm down my stomach
brush my teeth drank some water and then
oh yeah oh yeah i just ran my thing i
remembered something now we forgot uh
the thing is yeah we were in the balcony
right of our house but the thing is last
night i locked because every night i
usually we usually lock it anyways and
this one was locked you should do that
so we couldn't get inside it was lucky
that i had my phone with me so i could
immediately contact the butler to open
the balcony door for us imagine if i
didn't have my phone and we forgot the
room key
yeah we forgot the room key too we
forgot the room key we forgot the and
then if we didn't if i didn't have my
phone we would have we would have had to
swim all the way back yeah probably yes
yeah yeah
yeah but thankfully someone opened up
the door and we were able to enter after
a while
yeah but i just remembered this was
actually the day we woke up early um to
call into inna's birthday stream um
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah a little bit early so we wanted to
fall asleep again but then we were
wasn't it saturday no it was a friday
apparently i don't know that chad said
so
no the chat was wrong no it was saturday
it was saturday i was saturday my notes
say saturday but the chat said it's
today no it wasn't no
it's friday it's friday their time but
like for us it was a saturday morning ah
okay okay
all right all right all right that's
that's that no no we just you know
after that yeah we chilled i calmed my
stomach down but hey now we had a good
reason to finally go have lunch for the
first time
exactly we kept skipping lunch because
anyway yeah the lunch wasn't included
anyway so we're kind of min matched
having breakfast
it's not like we eat a lot anyways yeah
like all right don't need it usually
but then yeah and we needed some lunch
because my breakfast was not there
anymore my breakfast was eaten by the
fish in the ocean you're welcome
okay yeah okay and then we went to the
italian place and
aha um okay so first we went to the
no actually okay
so here's the thing
uh yeah
i wanted to
why did we do this like this again first
i i think
i think oh yeah before having lunch
originally i think we wanted to go
swimming
but then we didn't do it we went lunch
first was it because it was raining
for a moment ah
i think so i kind of forgot
oh maybe yeah maybe because of the
weather and then we were basically like
yeah let's do how long i don't remember
yeah because the weather was a little
bit unstable on that day there were like
two times when it rained a little bit so
we had lunch at
the italian place i ate my
35 up wait that's something else i'll go
back here later the 35 dollar lasagna
and then um reina wanted to have some
sushi so then we walked over to the
other place so we had lunch in two
different places
and just watched each other eating how
was this sushi
it was okay
um i would yeah
i mean i guess like i was just curious
but then um if you asked me i would
probably it would be better for me to
like get uh italian lunch anyways yeah
oh
yeah yeah yeah but you wanted to go and
try it out so at least you did it once
um yeah yeah at least like i'm not like
super oh i wish i had tried it or
something so you had like this is unagi
right i remem i remember that and then
salmon and then this thing
the left one was like i think that was
like either like yellow tail or
something i don't really remember
and the unagi was um
grilled or like i don't know yeah it was
grilled
yeah yeah yeah okay so we ate that and
then it started raining again but after
that it didn't rain anymore after that
ah now we got windy when i was eating
sushi yeah yeah yeah yeah but now
remember we wanted on this day after the
lunch we wanted to go
kayaking
but the weather was it was raining yeah
it was so unstable so we were like what
if we're in the middle of the ocean and
it starts pouring down on us
that's not gonna be nice so because we
weren't sure about the weather we just
stopped and cancelled that idea we never
went kayaking
unfortunately sad sad sand yeah what is
the try though when the weather is a
little bit more stable in the future
yeah yeah kayaking is fun in general but
not when it rains
um we just uh my my notes say
we just went swimming with our floaties
because afterwards it actually didn't
rain anymore but we were just like it's
better to be at the beach than being in
the middle of the ocean
when it rains no to take cover
so yeah we went swimming i almost fell
asleep in the lounge chair oh i have a
photo of that look tatan
yeah we made ourselves that's my balloon
that's your new floatie
yeah that's my new floatie and the one
at the back was hers
when you're chilling here after being in
the water for a while
uh
ah
and then it rained a tiny tiny tiny bit
so you woke me up
and then we went to the spot into
jacuzzi but the jacuzzi was dead
there was no water in the jacuzzi
right
and then the one yeah and then the one
there was there were two but then the
one
it was kind of cold yeah there were two
one cold one empty so sad
but we were waiting for our massage so
we spent some time
uh there and waiting in the sauna and
now we had our um bali knees
balinese man oh yeah balinese massage
how was this
how was it
it was good oh the massage was good
though
balinese was also good yeah yeah yeah
yeah here you're just just for just for
the imagination for another reference
yeah
weather was also better too so it wasn't
really yes this time it wasn't storming
so i could relax more for the people who
don't know a balinese massage is with
oil
um
for the first massage thai massages with
cloves but these massages with oil so we
don't uh we're only wearing pant pants
but
we didn't look at each other no no no no
no not looking no looking it's your
massage so massage safe massage and uh
it was a mix of uh swedish massage of a
thai massage and
uh one more
you remember
no it was like a mix of three yeah i
remember yeah yeah yeah that's the
maldivian and not my living balinese
massage it's a mix of free massages yeah
but it was nice they used um
i was i was like sitting uh first before
they gave me the massage they make you
have a foot bath and at this point i had
a really bad sunburn so i couldn't i was
stepping and i'm like [\h__\h] this is too
hot then they added some water some cold
water and i'm like
that's so hard i can't
and then they threw the whole water away
and just gave me a water a cold water
bowl
wait wasn't that the first the first
massage or the second second
the first one i was so funny i remember
me feeling pain too because i think i
it's not because of the sunburn but i
cut my ah
near my ankle i cut myself and it was
like pretty bad too
a lot of cuts yeah it's the best the
battle scar from the maldives like where
did you get your scar i got it in the
ball dude
you have this huge cut over your thigh
look at that
cat scratch
yeah but like the thing is usually like
that this crash is like straight right
but because it was caused by um it was
caused actually by like a metal like on
the ladder near
yeah and then there was like the really
uh strong waves so it looks like a
horizontal s
it wasn't a straight cut because like
look at the waves
wow yeah i mean it's getting better and
okay i don't feel it anymore
yeah okay so after the foot bath uh they
asked both um they mostly asked you they
didn't really ask me much but they asked
us about which oil they we want them to
use but i just got offered the coconut
oil because of my sunburn i didn't even
know there were other options because
they asked you and what did you get
um i apparently yeah there was like
eucalyptus and then something and then
jasmine and then coconut
uh i chose a mix of jasmine and coconut
i think they didn't give you a choice
because you were like so sunburned and
apparently coconut is the best for like
sunburns and stuff yeah yeah
she only asked me is coconut oil okay
and i'm like you know i guess okay
so then vegetable oil
we laid we laid down
and uh they first did the claw
again around our
ears and they walked around with the
sound cool
it vibrated
yeah
and then they started the massage it was
really really really nice it felt really
good with the oil felt nice i like oil
massages i don't know i like oil massage
it's so relaxed
dry massages are good but almost i just
like ah super nice yeah
yeah that's nice and i was looking at
the at the water again this is such a
cool thing like also because like in in
other massage places that are not on an
ocean
often they use like nice ambience sound
like ocean waves and and birds chirping
but the thing is here
the sounds were naturally coming from
outside they didn't use a cd or
something i thought that was really yeah
special natural asmr ambient sounds
we don't even need yeah asmr 100 natural
yeah i was like half asleep if not
asleep
it was amazing and oh oh but
yeah
apparently my notes say that my arms
felt on fire afterwards uh my sunburn
didn't feel so good after the massage
actually
i kept asking you like just yeah like
how is it i remember that like the
dinner sometimes it didn't hurt and
sometimes it would hurt a bit more like
after waking up and after the massage
and and yeah it went something like the
flippers from the snorkel when they
touched my my feet wow the plastic when
it was sticking to my feet that hurts so
much oh my god oh
and at some point my my feet were
getting um swollen i wasn't sure
i was like looking at my feet one
morning and i was like
were my feet always like this or are
they swollen and eventually i found out
that it's pretty noble to have swollen
feet from a sunburn
so yeah
they're not swollen anymore though yeah
yeah and i'm back tomorrow
that's good
yeah
i was like oh but then i thought like i
thought i didn't have a sunburn but
apparently i did have like not as
noticeable not as noticeable not like
nothing was swollen but i still did have
some burns uh it hurt i went to you know
this is post vacation talk but i went to
the you know
i got treated i gotta treat it it's nice
but anyways yeah i went to the salon
and they told you sunburn on your scalp
girl
yeah
[Music]
it hurts yeah i wanted to show these two
pictures just so you guys got a feeling
from for what our balcony was like we
had these mats here
i mean yeah we were like yeah we were
chilling on there but without the towel
it's really uncomfortable
yeah ouch like sometimes like the the
nets would like you know
form a pattern on like your thigh or
something yeah
it's like a hammock basically um some
villas had a pool
but they weren't available when we were
booking the uh they only had the ones on
the beach with the pool but we wanted a
normal water villa so we were like okay
i guess i guess no pool is okay because
we have the ocean and uh yeah we were we
had like a lot of lounging uh um
possibilities and if you look here you
see this on the very right does that
look familiar to you guys that's the
outside shower that you guys saw in the
it's raining many videos yes yes yes yes
yeah yeah yeah
on that day it was raining so much i
took a video here on that side and down
here
down here if you go down here
you can reach the water so you walk down
and you're in the water and during low
tide it was really shallow but during
high tide the water would go all the way
up here
what is it
that's that's where that's
cut herself on the on the left oh yeah
yeah
this ladder where i cut myself so sad
yeah that's all right yeah and these are
our our flippy thingies this is where it
really hurt having my legs and my feet
but they were magical yo
because those make you swim like a
mermaid
uh-huh that's so good so this is
actually my first time wearing those two
it was fun i realized oh
and over here right over here is where i
threw up
oh that's what i had in my mind but i
was doing i was going to let you finish
but oh yeah you said it
the hilarious quickly went away it went
all the way is scattered all over and
there were no other people around no one
saw me no one was in the water besides
me
i didn't even see her it's all right if
you didn't if you didn't tell me you
threw up i wouldn't have known yeah i
was suffering while you were
escaping from the from
yeah
yeah anyways
[Laughter]
most famous tourist spot can you believe
it
but this was really cool like waking up
going outside to your balcony and then
seeing this beautiful beautiful view
that was just the most special thing
this was my dream having an over water
villa
yeah
and it's the specialty of the maldives
there's like a [\h__\h] ton of resorts and
they all have these over water villas
they also usually have some beach bellas
but these are just that's the special
thing you know they're like all
all aligned here
yeah you can't really see though because
they all have like a little wall here so
we can't look over there and they can't
really see us same over here yeah so
there is privacy definitely
it's a dream
yeah okay back to here yes
we're almost done we're almost done
actually pretty fast too
okay yeah
so this is before the dinner or whatever
yeah i guess so
oh
yeah this was this
friday friday
yeah that was friday right yeah friday
night
uh oh it was so nice you can already see
some stars here it was not completely
dug yet but you see the stars
yeah the star story yeah
i when it was completely dark i tried
taking a picture but i couldn't get any
stories on the picture
even though that
my phone wasn't good enough to take
picture anyway i did take a picture but
it didn't look good at all yeah like you
know you need a proper
um
camera another phone to take a picture
of those stars yeah you need a long
shutter speed
yeah yeah
um but we were walking back from our
massage
and i think and we already had a change
of clothes so we changed into a clothes
and then we walked over to our last
dinner which was actually over here and
this was the the grill
restaurant yeah but this time because it
wasn't raining we sat outside for the
first time for the dinner yeah
and it was amazing they had a live
band like singers
live music was pretty cool they had like
their own like mixer
it was so nice they were singing like
really romantic songs partially like fly
me to the moon they sang fly me to the
moon made me so happy yeah they did they
did they sound like a lot of like really
nice oh it was a couple
they had really nice voices and and yeah
so we were uh sitting there eating our
last dinner this was the other side so
this was right view this was the left
field
um yeah it was really dark on the photo
wow oh it was dark on the photo but it
was
a bit easier to see in reality
oh
this was really like already empty
stars yes we saw the stars up here you
guys can't see it
but yeah that was really nice and
actually this group over here they had
someone who had birthday
oh yeah
yeah
at some point
the singers started to sing happy
birthday and i sang along did you sing
along
i think so yeah really just you know be
cooperative yeah maybe don't yeah i
don't i don't remember you hearing you
sing
that's all right
but i was joking like they should
like sometimes they were taking five
minute breaks or ten minute breaks and i
was like yo we should we should go and
sing y'all
if they only knew
they had
the top singers of all alive no just
kidding
yeah yeah
it would have been funny but yeah we
didn't do it of course
there were also like people dancing
right and then then they were like don't
you like we were so looking at them and
then one of the people uh the staff were
like oh do you wanna do you want to join
don't you want to join but then we had
to start
no i just didn't want to join because
i'm too shy i don't know like no
no it's kind of like um
i don't know it was nice watching them
but dancing by myself i don't even know
those dance moves like they were dancing
more like you know as a couple like
hand-in-hand kind of classic
dance low-key
in front of these people there was a
a sitting area right here on the left
side and there was a korean couple
sitting right in front of them and there
was a cute girl
who like she was i think she was getting
a bit drunk so she got up several times
and like just danced around with idol
steps like really happily and had her
husband's boyfriend
film her like he was not dancing with
her he was only taking videos of her and
she was just like
and the staff were really happy
looking at her
yeah it was cute it was super cute kept
on looking uh over to her
yeah
it was really cute but then around the i
didn't want to join though yeah we
didn't want to join but around the end
of the dinner on all of the the birthday
people these ones they joined them and
they did some really
really like they they looked like they
were used to it like they do it more
often like dancing in in couple style
um
yeah
yeah that was nice it was a nice
atmosphere right
yeah
it was really nice and then the music
was so good too oh that was your dessert
that's my dessert i'm just showing the
dessert i guess
you didn't say that
lava cake i even took a video of uh when
i opened it but i'm not gonna show
and then
um
wait
let me check my notes
my notes what did you eat on that day
um for the dessert i just ate i think um
the salt caramel
ice cream and then on that day i ate the
same starter and for the main course
for the main cars what did i get
some oh steak
there was like a choice of steaks most
of them were not included because
they're like the better type of steaks
and you chose the one steak that was
included in the health board yeah
because i felt like i splurged enough
the first day on the uh what was it yeah
but then i ordered the sides that i
ordered they were not included anyway so
i feel like it kind of even
what was the yeah
i i tried a very special like hot sauce
from them it was really spicy
yeah
i wish we had tried them too
no
no no no no no thank you
no thank you
but yeah the dinner was really nice but
we were getting really sad and
sentimental
it was last dinner
uh oh and later
yeah
dana was really really fascinated by the
sparkling stars oh i was when we walked
back when we walked back there were so
much
so many stars and the sky was so
uh you know like mcflurry i said it was
like her first mcflurry
there were so many but actually during
the dinner elena um because we met we
noticed that only elena was showing me
her um
her cat pictures i was like
okay i guess i'll show you my pictures
now so i showed a lot of my cat pictures
and then i was really really excited
about my kitty cats
yeah i was i liked that picture yeah
we showed
each other the pictures that was our
main topic for this dinner
yeah for the dinner we were just like
you know
and after that
yes yes
oh no i was just gonna say like after
the stream we're gonna be like oh yeah
let's continue like looking outside or
something we were gonna i was gonna be
like hey let's watch videos and you're
like no we're gonna look at the stars
and then there were no stars anymore
that's the sad thing like before the
stream there were a lot of stars and we
wanted to look at them but we had to
stream from the balcony from the hammock
net thing
they were gone they were gone guys we
missed them because we were streaming
but the stream was fine we had uh
karaoke and q a stream
uh
maybe you guys watched it did you guys
watch it
um
which one you see
i know i asked the chat i asked the chat
did you watch the stream yes yes yes if
you didn't you have to catch up it's a
it was a great year
singing together for the first time
before the stream um i i i actually i
didn't you know when people do like um
off collab karaokes i
i personally have like high standards
when it comes to that so i don't want to
just sing the whole song
together so i sat down to separate uh
the parts of the songs that we're gonna
sing yeah i didn't want it to just be
together all the time i wanted there to
be like some kind of like
you know
system
yeah
i think i think that makes it
more
professional and and interesting
that was great though i did that before
as well when i had an energy of collab
karaoke
there we also separated the lyrics in
special parts like sometimes sing
together sometimes solo and so on
yeah no i did put extra work into it i
did yeah
yeah awesome oh nice
so spicy nice and after that animal
animal documentary because no stars
yeah after that with the uh uh we will
help yeah and then we found out it was
kind of chronological actually because
like remember we watched the final
episode last time and then
we watched the first episode this time i
was like wait what it's chronological
yeah we watched some animal videos
did you know
people make jokes about us watching
really innocent animal videos because
the
the letters av
stand for something
spicy
stop ruining our say so innocent animal
experience okay stop ruining it i was
like we were watching completely say so
in innocent animal videos
yeah
they were baby cubs okay babies
bubble
and then i forgot about the brothers the
naughty brothers though
[Music]
but it was innocent guys stop stop
making it into something spicy it's not
spicy yeah we did like the our vacation
was very wholesome and yeah some people
are making it
don't know yeah yeah yeah yeah that's
what
is in indonesia and that's why
indonesians will keep laughing which is
also very um similar to the english
titty
ah i guess so
a german word yeah a german word that
also is very similar and also means
booby oh yeah yeah okay
but it's i feel like it sounds more
vulgar than
oh really
breasts for example
[Music]
she said like she read out like an
article in german i'm like wow german's
so nice
and then did they say what was what was
the indonesian word that you know
she knew
and that was what was it i i think i
only said tediously but i also know wait
said i'm sad
that's my greeting
no you said you knew
wangi
because of ollie yeah says
oh
i don't know what it means but i i i saw
it a lot
yeah you said that a million times
during the vacation and then sometimes
you would you would say it while hitting
my pillow
[Music]
[Laughter]
i brought an extra a personal pillow
with me on my travel i have like yeah
the cute one
i have um a pillow that i've been using
for years from don quixote in japan
it's it's not really a pillow it's a
plushie
that's really soft and squishy and it
has an animal face and i use it as my
pillow for so many years because it's
like the only
pillow that
i don't know my if i don't have it then
i feel like something's missing
so i bring it for traveling too because
it's really useful uh in the in the
airplane um i used to try out these neck
pillows but i think they're [\h__\h] they
don't work well for me so i bring just a
normal pillow my favorite pillow and
then i use it also in the hotel yeah
yeah yeah and then it was i keep
punching it yeah you kept on punching my
pillow is it so smart
i can't help but punch soft things
it's very cute no
the face it has the the the face yeah
cute face
okay oh so yeah this is um
we're now on the last day saturday look
we got the butler to take a picture of
us
yes
good
wow that's so cute
[Music]
i'm smaller than you cute
[Laughter]
my sunburn oh i i edited i edited the
legs so the sunburn doesn't come through
it actually was really sunburned yeah
yeah
no well well my notes say on saturday we
woke up early for the call-in for inna
we literally woke up like five minutes
before
um oh yeah and we only slept like five
hours but then we didn't go back to
sleep we just we were pretty awake after
the call yeah because we were watching
the animal video it was kind of late
so we went to breakfast after some
chilling in the bed the last breakfast
was sad like people were asking how are
you and i would say i'm sad because it's
our last day
yes oh yeah
one of them was like oh so i'll see you
at dinner and i'm like actually no
oh yeah yeah there was like this there
was this wine some earlier coming to a
table during breakfast advertising
sometimes they were like staff members
advertising their things and this wine
person came by and he was like yo we
have a wine testing later and we're like
well besides me not liking wine we don't
have time because we're leaving sorry
hmm
so sad so sound
um
ah
we didn't even eat that much on that
breakfast maybe it was the sadness
yeah i was yeah i don't know i just
noticed that i would it's probably
either like because it's the same thing
anyways we we ate everything maybe then
we wanted to
but wasn't the last was it the last
breakfast or the the one before where
you ate the maldivian breakfast
was the one before the last time
yeah they ordered the maldivian
breakfast
yeah curry tuna curry and some other
stuff yeah no not the two the two that
was not in the curry let's just make
that clear
it was like a side
it was
wasn't it
it wasn't the side in the bowl
um that was also tuna
i say okay okay okay
yeah and it came with something that
looked like crepes but it wasn't the
crap it was more like bread right flat
yeah
some eastern something something exactly
some place is pretty good some places
eat like these savory curries and stuff
for breakfast for breakfast but for me
it's like i can't that's that's lunch or
dinner for me i can't eat that for
breakfast that feels so weird oh
you're something lighter like sweet you
always eat your sweet breakfast with a
lot of berries and nutella and i always
i always got fruit from the from the
fruit buffet i always got like the
banana yeah the bananas and the
pineapples and i tried the mangoes but
this is
this confused me i was really excited to
eat fresh mangoes from here but i really
did not like the taste of the mango here
i'm i'm gonna be honest
it was not good for me
did you like it i enjoyed it
um i think you know i uh it's just like
mango different types of mangoes tastes
different i mean mangoes are mangoes i
get it though
i think it was ripe but i think it was
not the sweet type of mango yeah yeah
it's like another time no the less
i think like people when they go
indonesia they're very
crazy about the avocado and the mango
because fruit is too cheap around here
no it wasn't sour chat it was not sour
but it just
tasted just tastes milder it didn't have
much taste and the taste that it had it
was just neither sweet nor sour it was
just weird tasting for me personally
a little mild
but i also tried the dragon fruit for
the first time that was cool
it didn't taste like it looked like it
i'm not really yeah it was just a
it was nothing special but i just at
least i'm happy i tried it
yeah i guess so um yeah let's try
something for you for the first time at
least you tried it yeah
so wait breakfast oh wait friday friday
uh friday friday where's friday i hear
ah
friday friday or saturday
what's up
saturday saturday
i lost track where i was in my notes we
had breakfast and then we went one last
time we went snorkeling but we didn't go
stay for so long because i got really
sick again
yeah yeah yeah you did so yeah i was
like swallowing so much seawater
but anyways it was the exact same spot
anyway so it's not like we had really
anything new plus there was not really
that many fish to see yeah the fish were
like i don't know the same as as the
other days so i wasn't that impressed
anymore and i was swallowing too much
seaweed so i was like um
and i'm going out
sorry
and then right in front of me i was
going out
we we went
back
yeah we said we want to try different
snorkeling spots someday
feet very swollen sunburned hard to take
off the flippers went back and then we
started packing
uh and then somewhere in between
i i started doing the big math because i
was separating our bill we had so many
bills like from the restaurants and from
the seaplane and all that so i sat down
and rana was watching me and calculating
how much
each person spends how much she owes me
because i paid in advance
i did the big mouth yeah uh-huh
yeah
and then then we
quickly took some last-minute pictures
outside but we got a [\h__\h] heat stroke
or something because in that short 10
minutes we were drenched in sweat
outside just for such a short time it
was the sun was boiling it was really
funny
i think that's where you know i got like
the sound burn on my on my stuff head i
don't know i don't know yeah
that's all right it was really really
really really really hot so we ran i i
ran back to the room because i
the the the
ground was so hot
and i was already sunburned on my feet
so i was running and my i couldn't be in
my sandals because my sandals were [\h__\h]
and filled with sand so everything hurt
and i was just running and then taking a
break and running over the hot ground
like it's like lava i'm running running
running finally back to the room we're
just trying to cool down
cool down drink some cold drink from the
mini bar
and then
yeah
chilled on the balcony oh i i uh let out
all the air of our floaties
oh yeah
it took quite some
looks like you saw my floaty right there
were like two parts you know the the cat
the real floaty part and the fancy
cactus part and i was like
why is it so difficult
hey i already told this on monday on my
stream but reina didn't even know how to
open the the tube face
[Music]
i did not know it's like i don't even
use floaties that much i don't even
remember the last time i used them
probably when i was like a little baby i
didn't have to
put some
mommy quick
showed jordana had to open it and then
you have to squeeze it to let the air go
out but after a while my baby raina
wayne yeah he was too tired for
exhausting from from um squeezing the
floatie so she gave up and then later i
just i just let out the air about all of
them
yeah i mean i still had to you just i
still had stuff to pack i i yeah
but we guys are taking a break we ended
up having like a lot of extra time
because um we realized we were getting
picked up one hour later than we thought
we were getting picked up
[Music]
the scenery one last time
this is really random but i read her
like some wiki article of demon cat or
something
and it was i think the night before or
one more night before it was the night
before
wow on that day i showed you some more
weird stuff but that wasn't demon cat
why did you why did we read that
because i wanted to i wanted to read you
a better story
there was some wikipedia article about a
demon cat
yeah
and she was reading the whole thing out
loud for me i'm like uh-huh uh-huh
um
nothing what you're saying is entering
my brain but okay i'm listening
it's all right
it's supposed to be a bedtime story you
don't need to think about it too much
yeah
wow
well so after a while we finally got
picked up
and our butler was driving us to the
reception and she gave us like one last
tour
for the whole jungle maze so she was
driving like a little bit more like
like in the in the center and we saw
like some
how do you call it some
farm yeah like a farm they had some
stuff
that they were planting on the island
apparently
um
some naturally
island grown stuff not naturally but
yeah yeah some stuff that they grow on
the
and then yeah we reached the reception
like we paid the bill and then we went
on this sea plane
you see over here
irl dodo airlines
it was so sad and in the same plane
um
i was trying to hold my tears when he
was crying
like other people were crying we went in
the background this time then you you
kept looking out the window
crying
yeah i kind of noticed like your hand
sometimes goes up to your face a little
bit but then maybe i was like i was like
thinking is she crying but then i don't
know i i don't think it's what like it's
very not delicate to ask
just i just ignored you
but no holding her hand
but no for real like before that even
like i was like trying so hard to like
not cry because like i don't know that i
don't want to be the only one crying
it's like you know she doesn't
it wasn't like crying
it's like it was like it's gonna be like
waves like oh am i am i the only sad one
here and then i was just like trying to
close my eyes trying to like breathe to
not cry and then
she reached out her hand to me and then
i'm like oh
man
yeah so at first uh so at first like i
hold her with like both my hands and
then but then uh it was getting so
difficult like not to cry so i like
looked at the other side and then it was
like basically
there was nothing so i was just like
looking at luggage
and then i used my other hand basically
should have looked out my window
no i don't wanna once
yeah
anyways yeah
i was i was like
for the rest of the day like in the
seaplane and then in the taxi and then
in the
where was it in the lounge in the in the
airport i kept on
uh holding laney's hand queen joy
not gonna see you anymore no
[Music]
yeah
so sad
but so when we left it was around 4 00
[Music]
uh there was only one seaplane leaving
the island on that day
um it was completely full
and then the thing is for 4 p.m was um
the seaplane leaving but
we both of our flights were really
really really really late like around
midnight almost
so we had so much time to spare and the
thing is we didn't even mention this on
this island when we arrived they told us
to
um
put the the the clock one hour forward
right forward right back forward oh yeah
forward
because of the daylight and that we have
more from the from the sun and the
daylight and then when we arrived at the
main island we had to um turn the clock
one hour back so we had even more time
so we had like about i don't know eight
hours of time to fail
yeah which is why we
organized we asked for a tour on the
previous day and this was surprisingly
cheap out of all the things that were so
expensive the tour the private tour was
surprisingly cheap right
we were like what we you're like so
surprised yeah i was kind of like
not hoping i was expecting it to be like
really expensive but then wait what yeah
three hours of a tour a private tour um
it was 120 dollars total and then so we
we split it per person 120 was i think
okay for a private tour we got picked
out by
by um a dude with a car he was really
nice uh born and raised in the maldives
and this actually i also took a lot of
pictures from that and i wrote down a
lot of the info that he gave us so no
really yes now you guys are gonna get
some knowledge about the maldives yeah
yeah some actual knowledge and i'm
actually i'm really glad that we did
this because otherwise we would have
only seen this side of the maldives but
this is not the only side of the
maldives yes yes oh this is just our sea
plane one more time
so there's two islands two main islands
the
island where the airport
is something it's called hulu male
yeah uh
oh yeah yeah ah wait i i put all these
notes in a different one
my notes for that were here okay so he
said that the holoman artist at home
island was like kind of an artist island
i don't know what he meant with that but
okay
um he says that everything built on here
like the grass uh all of the grass all
the plants everything was planted
artificially because the whole island is
basically made artificially
um
it's also
previously it was mostly just the
airport there and no buildings but all
of these buildings that you see here are
built freshly and newly um they weren't
here until long ago until that long ago
until
just a while ago
and um
yeah now they're trying to get all the
like a lot of the people from the main
island over to this island because the
main island got so crowded and they're
still building a lot of new things here
and um oh i was really surprised that
when i and i got into the car i tried to
close my seat belt but i had problems
with it and then the dude said
yeah he said there's no need to put on
the seat belt i'm like dude what you
don't have even a law for it and he said
yeah we don't have to wear seat belts
because there's no accidents and i'm
like are you joking
i wasn't sure how serious he was about
it so i kept on asking like are you sure
are you sure but how are there no
accidents what about you know he said
that oh because there's no highways and
i'm i said okay but even if there's no
highway even on a normal road someone
can crash into you and he said no
because
we don't drink alcohol here there's no
alcohol allowed so i'm like oh well now
it makes sense there's no drunk drivers
so there's barely any accidents also no
highway nadu
it's an island right so they can't drive
fast anyways
i think yeah no highway he said there's
no highway so they don't usually drive
that fast yeah
i ended up not putting on my seat belt i
felt really weird about it one time we
got out of the car and i went back
inside and i out of reflex i wanted to
put on my seat belt again but then i
realized oh yeah right yeah right
it doesn't work yeah mine works though
one more thing i was really surprised
about that i wrote down as well is
um not only in the resorts but also on
this main island
they accept
uh not only my leading currency but usd
euro and pounds all okay in cash and
card no matter what they all accept it
which is crazy to me he said that's kind
of like a main currency for them too
so you guys don't have to bring any you
don't have to change any money to
maldivian yeah currency
yeah yeah i didn't change usd us dollars
though but yeah if you guys already have
the currencies the major currencies you
don't have to yeah do more deviant
dollars more money yeah i'm crazy
so anyway
uh no natural trees all very industrial
oh but
not at all
when we were driving around the island
we saw
um randomly we saw on the beach side
some people with parrots and we're like
oh my god parrots and then he stopped
for us let us go out and we we checked
out the parrots they were so cute
look these were fighting look at you
it's so cute the the small one keeps
trying to like get the attention of the
bigger one yeah he was like annoying him
all the time
sometimes like he was trying to like
step on the lip like go away
but we were so fascinated by it and
screaming and then he told us this story
that he used the driver he used to have
a parrot um but it was stolen because
they're really really valuable and what
did he say how much his i have nine
thousand one of them
one of these big ones costs nine
thousand dollars
because they have to import it from
outside of the maldives and um yeah they
stole it from him like many many years
ago someone broke into his apartment
because the people knew that he had a
parrot stole it and then yeah
unfortunately never came back but
um
he told us also that these people meet
up here um with their parents because
there's like a whole like
like a group of people yeah a community
who loves parrots and they all meet up
here and then they they let them sit on
this
thing for a while and then they let them
all fly away at the same time and then
they just go somewhere and then later a
few hours later all the parents come
back to their owner
and yeah that's their fun activity that
they always do apparently yeah this
one's nice and i asked like if you
didn't look the same like how do you
know it's like how do you know it's
yours and then oh first they have the
tags and also the bird knows who's the
owner so yeah no problem i guess now
yeah
there's yeah the red one's called naruto
this one was so big
it was yeah it was snacking he was
snacking on something
oh yeah
like the guy was feeding yeah
yeah i actually
i was i was thinking he was gonna say no
anyway so i did i didn't ask if we can
touch them but no they bite so you can't
touch them
unless you're an owner
yeah um also
uh
about these apartments i think this
might be this is i think belongs to
these apartments he said something about
blue haven apartments no no i wrote that
down because i saw some advertisement
about fancy apartments being built i'm
like i'm gonna look into that later
these buildings there are like red the
red ones like a complex and then they're
also like different colors like purple
and blue and yeah basically like it's
just like a huge like yeah apartment
complex yeah those are all the new ones
but it's not like the whole island is
filled with these actually these ones
really stood out because the rest of the
area was mostly flat on this island
right yeah they were mostly still
building things and there was still so
much space that was empty and
oh yeah so then we drove to the to the
island to the main main island that was
next to it you we drove over a big
bridge and
uh
yeah uh here this is just some random
pictures this was uh like
a place about something i think yeah
they did something
in the middle of the square they did
something there yeah yeah they did
something so it's like a neutral place
for something something i don't really
remember i wasn't the one taking notes
but um
to be honest like this picture i would
say doesn't represent the main island at
all because this looks so wide and
wide and
um open open yeah mostly it was not like
this it was more like uh
later said it resembles indonesia
yeah like some some parts actually
really remind me of like yeah
yeah this was a
mosque that is not being used that was
their oldest mosque i think and then
they had a new one uh but i was
surprised because like in austria i
don't see so many masks and this looked
this was sand and i was like surprised
that they look like this so i was like
that's just how they remember there were
a lot of birds chirping i am in this
area wow the words are so loud
and throughout the tour too like we kept
seeing like cats with cats yeah a lot of
stray cats actually if you look from
here to the right side there was uh like
a huge
um museum yeah a big big museum on the
right side but they said that ever since
the sea thing started it hasn't been
used for for like two three years it
hasn't reopened
yeah because of the
pandemic unfortunately no no
um oh okay so then
after a while we were really really
hungry so um we asked the driver to
bring us to a place where we can have
maldivian food
then he brought us to a restaurant that
had like maybe one bolivian thing on the
menu the rest was like italian and the
international [\h__\h]
like we were very clear about our intent
but yeah i think i had something
different is my like oh yeah i'll just
take you to a place where there's like a
lot of kind of different food so you can
just i'm like in my mind i'm like no we
want more even food but i don't you know
i didn't want to fight so this was the
only maldivian thing apparently that
they had on the menu that wasn't seafood
so this was a tuna fried noodles tuna
tuna and the fried egg on the top it was
good it was spicy it was good yours was
spicy and mine was not spicy yeah she
was like no spice please for me extra
spice
but
well i mean
i feel like
i'm sure there's more than that actually
our butler recommended us when we asked
about maldivian fuji i recommended us
some kind of chicken dish but they
didn't have this on the menu no chicken
biryani
uh
oh yes yes yes yes
chicken biryani i think like she wanted
to try it but then yeah the restaurant
we went to didn't have that didn't have
it so yeah oh well it was good it was a
bit more than it looks like guys
it was not that
was pretty big actually
but it was nice and then this was our
view
[Laughter]
i was like there was like two like three
stories there was like the second floor
the guy recommended the second floor it
looked pretty okay but like slightly
narrow ceiling
and then i was like okay maybe i want to
see up rooftop and then he's like okay
and then
the rooftop looks like this and then i
asked her uh okay then what do you want
and then she's like i want to eat here
yeah because i mean i mean the inside
was just so quiet and boring outside at
least we have something to say it was
like really yeah that's why i offered
you like do maybe you want to check out
upstairs but but
this at least i think way better
represents the city center of
the the of male island because there
were a million bikes everyone uses these
bikes this is not not like this in
austria
but uh they said this is southeast asia
you said this feels very very familiar
to you
yes it's very southeast asia
welcome
everybody
also
[Music]
for me this was really weird like what
the [\h__\h] so many [\h__\h] bikes man but i
guess it's like taking pictures of the
traffic jam
he did now this explanation made a lot
of sense to me he did say that um
because it's an island
uh and there's no cars being built on
the island impor you have to import the
cars which makes them really really
expensive so most people just opt for
the bikes which makes a lot of sense no
yeah
and i guess it's um more flexible like
you don't have to you can drive around
these cars like i i guess that's like
more useful yeah makes sense
oh oh
i don't know if i if this is something i
should talk about but i personally found
it interesting we asked about because we
were really interested in living in the
maldives so we asked about the security
in the maldives
and he told us that
um there's generally there's no no
pickpocketing but there are ah yeah yeah
yeah yeah crimes like um like he said
there's gangs and i'm like what do you
mean yeah is it like like
no
it's more like uh no right like street
games more like maybe gangs in schools
and something and then they fight but
they fight in the nearby way or
something no no it was not just school
gangs yeah not just
street gangs yeah
yeah
i guess so
but yeah that was apparently a thing and
i was pretty shocked by that because i
never heard about gangs in austria
yeah
me on the other hand not so shocked
hey but you know me having played yakuza
on my stream several times i i was a bit
a little bit
fascinated and wondered if there's an
ichiban running around the streets here
somewhere
normal tuesday morning
elena gracie like really oh my god
that's a bit that's a bit scary that
kind of ruined it a little bit for me
like hearing that that sounds scary i
don't know
but the city was so so so different from
the resort islands so it was a different
world completely
um that's actually the last picture i
have
after that
after the tour we quickly went back to
our launch we repacked some things in
our suitcase then we went to the airport
which was really tiny
it basically only had six gates
six yeah
so yeah we were kind of wondering like
so where do we split up i hope our gates
won't be like too far apart but it turns
out there was only six gates
in the yeah
so i went in like faster and i was like
wait where is she i was looking for her
like did she leave me but apparently she
just
it took some time because my first
airline you know it was like this this
cheap ass fly dubai airline so the cheap
airlines usually have
less staff on the counter and more
people in the lines waiting and it takes
a while it took forever so i was
actually we had because we were staying
in this fancy resort at the airport they
had like a special staff helping us
oh yes yeah i i asked him if this is
normal if he helps everyone and he said
no only some people from some resorts it
was we got special treatment treatment
arena
yeah yeah we did we did we did it was
really nice yeah he helped us get to our
check-in counter i mean it's a small
airport so we probably didn't even
really need it but it was nice anyway
because he was helping us with our
luggage as well yeah um so
while i was waiting forever and ever and
ever i asked him i tried to make small
talk because you guys know i don't like
awkward silences he was just standing
next to me while i was waiting in the
line so i made small talk i asked him
what are the
what are his from his point of view the
top five resorts in maldives that are
like luxurious and nice and he thinks
one should visit so guys listen up
here's the list from a from a maldivian
airport guy
number one deluxe lux
number two
the ozen old set ian
h-u-r-a-w-a-l-h-i uh-huh um number four
the gandelhi
r-a-n-d-h-e-l-i
[Music]
number five was one that i came up by
myself because i saw it on um in like
advertisements and i kind of want to go
there but it was [\h__\h] expensive it's
the there's a red skelton on the
maldives and it looks insane
i showed it to you
you liked it too right
yeah it's like super modern looking
but it's like uh we we checked i think
for like
uh
like wasn't it like six thousand dollars
per night or seven thousand eight
thousand
yeah it's just definitely like uh more
and more on the expensive side
six thousand per night yo but it's
beautiful you guys need to look it up
ritz carlton maldives they have like
these round over water villas they're
round and really modern actually today i
even watched a youtube video from some
influenza who did a room tour
it's so beautiful
[Applause]
i don't think it's like is it six
thousand for i don't know it was i know
it was 14 was it 14 000 per night and
then uh separated by two six thousand
or oh no or was it fourteen thousand for
five nights and then separated it i
don't know anymore i don't know
you guys can check it by yourself it's
fine maybe it was maybe it was uh 14 000
in total for like four or five nights
and then that separated by two was like
six foot
not really though i don't know
i just know i just okay no no no no not
not i just thought it was crazy
expensive
way more expensive than ours
maybe we can
maybe we can ask them maybe maybe we can
say them we have many subscribers on
youtube can you please um give us a
discount like for real though we're
doing good advertisement here for this
hotel even though we're not saying the
name
[Laughter]
[Music]
i can advertise
on youtube on twitter on tick tock and
instagram everywhere um please please
please
honestly um
i i used to
work in a hotel before and i
sometimes i saw emails from like
influencers
and they were like hello i would like to
book a revenue hotel i'm an influencer
can i get some discount because this is
my this is my instagram
and i just deleted them
[Laughter]
[Applause]
yeah i mentioned this before
i don't know that because i looked at
the instagram account it didn't even
like honestly it really didn't have many
followers anyways i'm like yeah what
exposure are you giving our hotel excuse
me
what
[Music]
the last few
oh yeah actually elena's flight was
gonna go before mine so i was prepared
to like sadly say goodbye to her but
then her her check in like her uh
boarding just would not start
yeah
and then it was basically just like six
gates so like they just have to like
keep using the same gates for like
replies so maybe that's why there was a
little funny delay on my part i'm
guessing yeah eventually mine started
boarding before hers so she was standing
in line for a while together with me
[Music]
we were watching animal videos but then
like after 10 minutes i think like both
of us realized that we didn't really
want to watch
yeah we should spend the last few
minutes maybe just trying to talk but i
was so sad i didn't know what to talk
about
[Music]
kind of reluctant to like say like grab
your hand or something like or your arm
because like yeah i know you have like
that sunburn right but then like on the
last day
you you kept like yeah you kept reaching
my arm or like yeah i'm holding my hand
or something so i guess oh maybe she's
okay
yeah
that's good
kept on hand-holding and then until the
very last moment you stood in line and
then i left and then i looked back and
you looked at me and then i looked back
again and you didn't look anymore and i
was like oh
but then then
i got into my plane and i wrote this to
you later on i got into my plane and i
realized oh
because i had a window seat i realized
your airplane thingy is right next to
mine
it was standing right next i was waiting
for you to come around because we were
all transported by the small buses to
the airplane uh you know how it is with
smaller um airports so
i was waiting and waiting and waiting
and waiting and waiting and then i
finally i actually saw you but i was too
slow to take a picture of you walking
into the plane
oh yeah how are you
yeah yes i felt like the guy like
everybody was like going through the
back of the back door but then like
apparently
they told me to take the front door for
no reason i don't know because it
depends on where your scene is
my seat was like at the
oh maybe i don't know it was like really
weird maybe
i got it wrong
but
my plane still took off earlier than
yours because i don't know why they had
so much delay for yours
yeah
well i told the rest of my my airport
story i already told on monday my 12 13
hour um overlay um transit story
hold on
it went well though it was okay it was
just way too long in total 25 hours of
traveling it's just too [\h__\h] long
but yeah hope you're not we did that was
that was basically it do you have like
something you want to add or like a like
a conclusion later
a conclusion i can't talk about a
conclusion yet because they're still my
stream
oh true to mama same time on the channel
um you were asking me about like you
know remember how we still had
the what was it the questions that we
have an answer from the
waldies i think yeah yeah tomorrow too
do you wanna show it yeah of course of
course okay
but uh you will be drawing the drawings
live or did you
are you going to prepare it after all
i'm going to prepare it now or maybe not
now not now maybe maybe like tomorrow in
the yeah maybe tomorrow okay so so no
live drawing you're gonna already have
it ready
yeah i'm gonna have it ready because
like life drawing will take so long
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah you did it before people really
like lena's comics so if you haven't
seen it yet tomorrow i think you'll like
it she has she has really cute drawings
i always know this when we when we play
the guardian phone you make such cute
drawings
no thank you
we also drew on like the hotel
yeah the hotel
doodling on on the on the little memo
pad that was on my bedside night table
she kept on adding doodles like uh first
she drew a p file and a kiwawa and i was
wondering hmm
i hope the housekeeping
people are not whole life no they don't
watch
you never know you never know
anybody
conclusion maybe tomorrow um
yeah no but from my side well
even though like
um we
documented so much and and talked a lot
about work and also where a lot of
social media and streamed i still feel
like i was at least able to
um really
like how could i not enjoy and relax
when you're in a place like that it's
just
let me go back to just give you the
vibes oh this one is good how can you no
matter how much work you try to do on an
island like this you will still uh like
leave being
happy and relaxed i mean we were all so
sad leaving but but still
yeah yeah but i still feel like the the
whole
atmosphere and the beauty of the scenery
like everything was just overpowering
the stress like for example i had a
really
really like sad
um upsetting message on the first day
from work and i was like
ah [\h__\h] this later i was just hold this
and down i was really upset but then
like there's all this oh beauty here
it's just so so so so so amazing and
that overpowered everything so
yeah we're and honestly even like the
streaming and all that that was fun too
like being able to
capture
some some of our time together on stream
i think for me it will be great to look
back on that someday and look at the
archives
more advanced yeah yeah yeah it's it's
special memories and um i'm really glad
that i had a travel partner like yo dana
i was really nervous about it in the
beginning
but
because it's our first time meeting but
but then we got along really well
and and yeah it was so nice meeting you
finally right now
yeah i really want to go on on the
vacation you know it was it's really
funny because um very recently uh after
the vacation uh i had a meeting with my
manager we were just like talking about
like stuff basically like a lot of like
you know long-term stuff and [\h__\h]
stuff and i'm like
and
my manager was like so rainy are you are
you happy and like huh
but then i told but then i told her that
you know like currently like i'm
actually feeling like pretty peaceful
with like what i have and it's like and
then i think it's also because of the
vacation you know i had a lot of fun i
could relax i could um i don't know like
you know talk about a lot of things with
you actually
so yeah
i'm very yeah the vacation really helped
me to you know relax and stuff yeah
that's nice that's good to hear
ah
i'm really glad i asked you to join me
on this trip um i'm glad you asked me i
was also really like oh no what if what
if you know you know because we're going
to be like i mean stuck for like a week
yeah
yeah yeah personally i wasn't going to
worry you of course like of course
anybody would be worried but then i'm
just i'm really glad yeah
i know it all went really well and i
think now we're just like about a
million times closer than before we
already were good friends before but now
even more like we keep on sending each
other cat photos on whatsapp and
we talk much more now so yeah we
we had a big big bonding
experience happy
thank you
i hope you don't uh
i hope the vacation didn't make you
dislike me but i feel like you got along
well
yeah i think yeah um
how about demon cats
no no
a lot of things like i want to say but
it's just like you know really redundant
if i say it like in words i had a lot of
fun basically thank you thank you
it wouldn't be the same if it was the
maldives but without you
of course it wouldn't be the same of
course it's different
of course yeah of course but then you
know what i'm saying right yeah i know
what you mean
i i really want to go back like
as great as the resort was i think we
should go back and try different resorts
like the ritz carlton
please please please please we'll
advertise you a million times completely
as many times as you want us to
that would be amazing but we should
definitely go on the trip again maybe
next time we can bring subaru because
somebody really needs a [\h__\h] vacation
yeah we were also talking about like
bali and stuff too like way back then
she really needs one
i want to go to bali sometime too
yeah
i would be glad to show you around even
though i don't know anything about polly
but you you've been before right
i know yeah i guess i would know more
than you yeah
you're kind of like a
kind of not not really a local but at
least you're like from the country so so
yeah
they can't rip us off too much
[Music]
uh water i talked so much again my
throat is so funny oh yeah let's drink
hydration check everybody hydration
check the only time when elena drinks is
doing a stream or doing dinner
yeah that's what i drink
so
yeah well tomorrow even more details
some of the dramatic stories like the
floaty story and
i don't know what else she's gonna draw
but i'll be there on elena's channel
it's in the description so if you didn't
subscribe yeah subscribe to elena
because you know um even though she's
from whole life indonesia she speaks a
lot of english in her streams she plays
a lot of fun games just like me she
plays also a lot of long games and she
streams a lot so if you like me then
you'll like reina as well i think yeah
[Music]
so check her out guys she's just
just because she's from life indonesia
doesn't mean that she's not interesting
okay
no i just feel like a lot of the whole
life english viewers they don't
they don't check out whole life in
indonesia that much because they think
they because of language
or something
[Music]
for some it maybe is correct some of the
whole life indonesia members speak more
indonesian and some a little bit less so
you're one of the ones that i would say
speak a little bit less i guess so it's
easy to watch you even as an
english-speaking viewer i would say
right
[Laughter]
yeah elena does a lot of really long
karaokes
oh yes i just did a five hour karaoke
where i jumped on our cat hair
yeah that's relatable very relatable for
me
yeah just can't owner's life
yeah i'm just coping you know i'm just
coping like ooh smile because it
happened kind of cope and then i feel
like the night no the night when i
arrived i was like i'm gonna sleep alone
tonight i die and then i brought my cat
to sleep with me
yeah
the after vacation depression hits hard
i wanna go back i mean i'm also you know
i like i like being with my cats it's
comfy being here with my usual setup but
i already want to go back
oh
yeah
well you know we it's not like we even
though we were on a vacation we still
brought up like at least look i put out
so much content besides streams and a
lot of videos every day
so we can always do this and repeat this
it's not it's not like we're gone
completely
yeah
yeah we always yes
okay guys a chat i'll see you tomorrow
on latest channel
i hope you'll be there
and for now
that was our maldives vacation thank you
for
listening and also for um like
hanging out with us during the vacation
and the little streams in between and
enjoying our tweets and our little
videos and all that and then also the
preparation before the vr
stream for example oh yeah yeah
it's all of this is slowly coming to an
end but maybe there will be another
vacation down the road sometime we have
to
reward ourselves with these locations oh
no oh no we're going on a research
island
oh no what can i do i must go
i i can't help it
is calling me he's calling us the waves
the sparkling the fish are calling me
yeah yeah so
what do we say in german in german
germany
[Music]
[Laughter]
don't hit my viewers five times don't do
it
you pronounce it really well too
yes
yeah okay yeah
good german
thanks everybody
thank
see you tomorrow bye bye
bye
yay
[Music]
do
you