[Music]
ah
foreign
[Music]
huh
oh
uh
hello hello
welcome to the collaboration i am
training
amelia today as a kfp employee
yay i'm excited to be an intern
and do work that connection has been
lost you know what i think we can uh do
it without being
in each other's room okay
uh because people are gonna probably
have two windows open anyway
okay no no this has been happening since
uh two days i don't know why but
we'll figure that we don't need it we
don't need it we are connected by our
hearts right
yes our souls
ame is helping me today
to do something important
uh i have been building
a house with some chickens and
i've uh they have um procreated so much
that it's uh been giving me a hard time
to collect all the eggs
so i hired uh watson
industries is that how you say it yeah
industries what's an industries
to work for me also she's my i hired her
once i opened up membership i hired her
anyway against her will
so she has no choice she will help me
build an automatic egg collection
cart underground system and yeah anyway
right
rails are your thing right yeah yeah
yeah yeah we specialize in rails here at
watson industries
and i'm excited too i thought it was
industries
i mean you know this is potato potato
tomato tomato
industries is that british aren't you
british
yeah yeah mate
are you in the server yet i'm trying
yeah i'm
i'm here i'm just gathering materials
okay
uh uh nice viewers have sent me
a references on how to do it
so we will try to copy that there was a
i've often sent
some various uh
ways to do it yeah but um
one person sent me a chicken friendly
way to do it
and of course i wanted to be chicken
friendly hmm
yes i've copied the blueprints uh they
did not copyright their intellectual
property so it's up for grabs
and it's mine now i own it
own it now
spawn in my room but i didn't show my
stream yet what happened in my house
do you want to come over uh okay i'm
just making sticks really quick hold on
okay sticks i have a lot of sticks
though oh
i see i see you in your house like like
through the walls i see you it's creepy
i can see you too
okay okay hold on i'm just building up
the last few things that we need to take
like 30 seconds
okay no problem no problem i'm waiting
i have a bad view here i need to re
re-position my window so i can see you
better uh
okay
nothing i mean you placed your house
there
uh after mine was already placed so it
was almost like
you were asking for me to stalk you yeah
that's true
you got the best spot for a house i
don't know i should have thought of that
beautiful thank you i'm beautiful
all right and oh i see
and do i have a zoom button
no ctrl is not working someone is
telling me
wrong information in the chat
why would you guys lie to her hmm yeah
i'm nice to me
you're gonna be put on santa's bad list
oh my god does that oh
did you emma did she also install
optifine
oh yeah yeah try pressing
uh c c see the button c
wow holy sh
i don't think that i don't think it has
to do with optifine
and they told me uh since since i
installed optifine it's one
zoom ah here she comes here she comes
i don't have my house a little bit
welcome welcome welcome
welcome so um
everyone please look at this room and
read the sign
the one and only
[Music]
and we have today added hookah papa to
our server
yeah i made a room for him wow he
changed it already
damn why did he make it so fancy he's
only been on the stereo for two hours
he has a black bed and i wrote this sign
here
a bit uneven he has a puffer fish why
does he have a puffer fish
oh and he's been collecting some
materials for me what uh orange and red
wool
so that we can build a restaurant isn't
that cool
that's really not one of my flavors now
yeah i'm playing i'm paid employee papa
lives with me
papa has his own room very fancy and i
have a chicken in my house now
and i have many chickens over there i
have too many chickens i'm
in too many we might have to
call the population a little bit
lord take me
some of them
[Applause]
you can't escape it's okay this is just
inevitable
hello i kill you though i will kill you
out kill it i will kill you
sorry what what is this called uh
uh when i win a chicken dinner yeah yeah
yeah
why why does that phrase exist also oh
my god
i i started this i did this today and my
in my
minecraft stream my holy [\h__\h] my papa um
my papa uh
yeah i don't know what he did here
there's a lot
and he made a orange orange sheep
papa this is not hum human how would you
how are you saying
manic human humane
this is not humane this is a very um
disturbing
wow this hurts my heart
but wow this he did all of this in like
two hours
where did he get all the sheep from
maybe they multiplied yeah but not so
fast
why that's um
um i don't know what to say when i look
at this
i think some some renovation has to be
made
yes and then can i hire you for that
that wasn't in the contract
i'll do it myself but i mean we could
kill some of that no no i need the room
i need the room i need it
anyway so basically this
chicken house uh even remove it
or we lift it right right
yeah so the blueprints that i saw
require
uh like a
block down here so the the rail
would be this height where this block is
here but because your floor
is essentially this block we either have
to raise it on the inside by one block
so we can dig this out
and then put it back because we need to
get in there to be able to put the rails
on this level
so that uh it can collect the eggs at
the right height
i am confused i am confused uh what is
the better option mrs amelia watson
um let me let me let me assess the
situation here
um
i think what we could do here is we'll
kill
like half of them okay
i don't have enough eggs why why would
the kill half of them what is that
necessary
we'll split it in half with a fence and
then we'll kill one half
one so that we can fill that half with
dirt
and then bring the other chickens from
the other side onto the raised
dirt and then we can fill it fill the
other half with dirt so that
we fill the whole thing but in in steps
chad would you say that that makes sense
you guys get it right
i feel like i have to make a diagram
can't you just dig down no
ah no
yeah we can do that but then we'd have
to mine the ground under the chickens
that's fine yeah
okay so we'll go down we'll go down
three
yep yep maybe i need maybe we should
bring a shovel
yeah i need a shovel too okay
oh finally the chicken noises are open
my my way would have worked too
oh i believe you look at this chest i
mean look at this big taste
look what i got today do
in the watson shaft in the watson shop
oh
good choice
do i have a hubble i don't even have a
shovel
let's make a shovel i don't have iron i
could make some
maybe we should sleep okay
okay i'm going home out there plus one
adorable oh my god i will never forget
the first time i heard
amelia hick that was
what is that what is that pretty sure
that was your reaction
was it was how do you remember wow you
you're not only smart you also have a
huge
um memory card
[Music]
i just remember really weird things
okay i'll make you a shovel too thank
you
then i'll i'll make a uh egg chest
i have too many eggs all right so
if we dig down three wait hmm
yeah yeah yeah and then we hmm
wait a second hold on my brain is
processing
yes yeah yeah yeah okay i see i get it
okay i trust you
i'm i'm i'm not really planning on using
much of my brain today anymore
because i have uh what's in industries
yeah yeah
this is this is my job
but i was honestly i uh today when i
streamed minecraft
it was the first time for me to see
our server since the last collab that we
did
the five member collab i haven't played
minecraft since then i was shocked
at how how much you have done for our
server
i haven't what that much it has been
there has been a lot done
thank you wait do you have any pickaxes
yes but in my tip
that's really i really like those those
stairs
and when i complimented your stairs
i said uh um something about the shitty
stairs that we had before
and that moment ina was watching and i
didn't know she was watching
she was like oh i made those shitties
[Music]
sorry ina they had to be uh upgraded
now but they were good they were good
while they lost they served its purpose
oh indeed indeed indeed
do you how many do you need uh just one
i think
i learned how to throw items wow thank
you
wow i've learned so much
okay so now
what we're gonna do okay you see how i
put two blocks here
so this first block is originally the
floor already for your
chickens and when we're done we're gonna
dig out this so that they drop onto this
level
we're gonna dig out this one i mean so
they drop on to the bottom level you
know what i mean
sure sure i can totally understand
this is a two by two space and this is
the
level that our rails will be on
can i click on the on the row next to
you
i don't know how long let's see
how long this goes this makes sense
right guys
should make sense
yes chad says yes it makes sense nice
as expected from what's in industries
with her
stolen blueprints uh
the sound of the sheep and the chickens
it's really nice music to my ears
[Laughter]
please everyone flip it thank you
let me see how far we have to go on this
[Music]
side
you know uh it'll be kind of bad
when you have the sound of the chickens
and the sound of the sheep and then the
sound of the uh
the cart going constantly well
i mean whenever i will go there to
collect my eggs i will put on uh
you know those headphones that that that
oh yeah your earmuffs your mufflers no
i mean like more the sturdy ones when
you when you
go like oh yeah yeah
and you like fly a plane or you uh i
know what you're talking about yeah
yeah yeah all right so i have a task for
you yes do you have any iron
yes okay we're gonna need a minecart
and a hopper so i'll start putting the
tracks down
and yeah uh
uh how do i make a hotmail i don't know
i don't have a recipe for a book i'm
sure
that's chat yeah i do i do i do i like
okay okay okay
okay let's see i have lots of iron
you're so quiet what happened uh i'm
just putting the rails down
okay i'm focusing on her work yes
i was just thinking
actually i don't think this should take
too long i think i'm almost done
wait take your time
this is this is the only thing we're
doing today
but i do want to think it hurts my heart
but i do
want to eventually have an automatic
grilling thingy
ah but it just hurts me
to even think about it like that that's
just my chicken
my baby but in the end what else am i
gonna do with those chickens right
just yeah multiply them until there's
like
trillions and billions
yeah just the way of life
wait wait uh i need a minecart with
copper right
[Music]
here
yeah yeah yeah well you can just make
the minecart yeah and then you put the
hopper in the thing
oh wait or i don't know like
no yeah that uh that was yeah a mine
and we need another chance probably uh
yeah yeah yeah unless you already have a
chest for eggs we can just repurpose
that
i got it i got
it mrs watson i have been useful
for once perfect
you're you're usually useful usually
wow it looks exactly like in the picture
yeah you're making the redstone blocks
well i found it in the nether somebody
left it in a chest so it's mine now
it's fine i can make more if they want
it back
i have a lot of redstone too though yeah
that's fine this is good i have enough i
think it's already
i didn't i asked in my in my last stream
i asked
how much time do they think we will need
and some said five minutes and others
said one hour
and sometimes five hours so i'm like
really confused as to how long this
actually takes but maybe it just doesn't
work the first time we're trying it yeah
yeah maybe
yeah pretty much
you can almost testing so uh i actually
miscalculated the roof so i think the
roof we're gonna have to fill this
you know like where our headspace is
we'll fill it with dirt
and then we'll we'll drop the chickens
the two dirt blocks
so that they fall where our head is you
just
i get it i get it okay exactly at the
same time you started talking i saw a
comment in the chat saying the exact
same thing
ah okay nice i think they agree with you
right i think
this looks so professional i think uh
it should be good enough i'll put
another one here just in case where do i
put the part
uh you can put it anywhere i think but
maybe i might need more i might need
more
rails oh i need more more uh
gold rails i mean for like to keep it
going constantly because i don't know oh
that's gold you need a gold to make
those
yeah yeah all right put a card on it and
we'll see
oh there it goes sorry i'll push it
once it goes it should oh let me get a
line
i think i might need some more
dream over goodbye thank you thank you
for your services
yes it already works what the hell
yeah all right now we just fell in the
wall thank you thank you
all right let's let's pick up this cart
if you could
uh how oh i just hit it yeah
you might i mean yep
okay do you have any dirt because i
don't think i have enough
uh probably somewhere yeah i'll pick it
up
and then uh what we can do is uh
i guess we can build it i guess it can
be right here we can build like a little
a little place to collect your stuff
because we'll the chest will have to go
somewhere
how can i how can i give you the whole
64 package
uh go into your inventory and then pick
it up with the mouse and drop it
why did i forget that i am stupid thank
you
do we need torches in here maybe to
brighten it up while we're working
oh hold on hold on i have i have an idea
there we go
does that work for you i'm holding a
torch in my hand and it wrote it
brightens up everything because of the
uh
haters no but it's okay okay i don't see
the light
as long as you see them and don't hurt
yourself while you're
practicing your practices
i think all right we're gonna have to
send the uh my
okay so put the minecart with the hopper
and uh send it on its way and then we'll
we'll follow the rest
why is it it separated chad how do i put
it back together
i think if if you put the minecart on uh
the non actually you can put it on the
red part
and then uh just put the hopper inside
of it and then we'll push it
i have to craft it again i have to like
ah
okay god damn it like if you pick it up
once it's uh
just oh i didn't know i didn't know
okay
okay and i'm back
yeah push it and then when it's on its
way is it going
yep glitches really go endlessly what if
we log out what if
does it still collect when we're all
logged out uh it should
i think so then uh the chest we would
put like here
and then uh we could shorten this to
make it like
two steps instead of three
and then now um
yeah yeah it works yeah but
not gonna work no
well yeah because we have to we have to
finish taking out the rest of the
floor in the chicken house so that that
chicken
apparently oh okay yeah yeah that's what
i was like are you gonna
i'm gonna i'm gonna be there when yeah
yeah i'll wait
should i i can't oh did you forget to
put the hopper in the thing oh wait
no no no it's in there
what's in there you guys open your eyes
guys
should i bring some seats so that we can
distract the chicken
ah that might yeah that might be helpful
so i can dig
uh what did i come here for upper chest
[\h__\h]
my brain forgetting what i came to do
in two seconds
upper direction chest under rails oh
just has to be under the rail okay we
can do that
like under under or just like if we dig
if we dig like there it should be okay
if we put it here
chest oh the chest has to be under the
rail with another hopper
okay poppy
too many
i got it i got it i got it but if i do a
double chest
don't i need two hoppers
uh i don't know i don't know how it
works
no okay apparently no
i got i got one test and
hold on i gotta move this block really
quick
[Music]
ah one hopper shift click to chest okay
this game is like so smart you can do so
many things
yeah there's a lot you can do i wonder
if they
ah wait when do you guys say underneath
you mean like what do you i don't
hey i thought that this can like exist
without the block
no no i don't think so
hey but i feel like i saw that before
ah oh wait what if
put rail on top of hopper okay oh okay
okay okay
okay
first chest
oh wait and then
hopper shift
test down one more level underneath
uh just
one more level down
just under the hop oh
[Music]
did you pick up the chest oh yeah i have
it sorry i you go but we're gonna
make to move no
yeah you can take just take out the
other rail too
all right for now i'll uh do this
do you want to yeah put the chest down
there
oh no i'm just putting this there we go
oh god the chicken noises make them stop
you can turn it down yeah
but it feels like i'm muting my family i
don't want to
do that
you can't open the chest if there's a
block over it what really
have to be placed first oh yeah
so you have you have one chest you want
to put that next to it
and then shift
people lied to me
okay wow
but this is supposed to go
this is supposed to go
the rail
next to it uh but apparently we
mean we don't need another helper
apparently just has
to have one helping
i'm in don't get half the chest
i give it to you yeah no i don't have it
yeah i give it to you
no i don't have it
i dropped it and uh i saw you pick it up
well unintentionally pick it up i'll
make one more
half a block slab okay i'll go make a
slab really quick
in the my chest my chest is in the chest
what is the chest in the chest
no the chest is not in the chest ah you
mean in my other chest
let's see i placed it
i made two chests guys
i'll just make another one okay
side
and this will be placed here
but don't we need a block yeah yeah i
got it i got it yeah
but they said it will not open got it
all right that's open
i put it halfway okay
and what happened to your shovel i don't
have you
yeah get out get out and get out
okay now we can fill
this back up
why do things keep on disappearing
ah the chest might be in the minecart no
no okay
now the chickens we lower them by
two blocks
okay uh ooh no spider
oh no i guess that's the bad thing about
having uh
yep automatic doors on the outside yeah
we haven't seen many issues before
so uh wow there's a huge egg party going
on
but how do we how do we do this um
so you want to lead them away from at
least one block and then i can start
from there
okay one second i'll get in there and uh
actually i can just do it like this
they're just falling in
all right i have to see
oh my god this is okay you know what
i'll just put them all in this
little pit i also fell
okay they're all going in okay we'll dig
around them after they get in there
okay oh my god
oh my god it looks very fluffy in there
like you could fall in there it would be
a really
really comfortable bed
or maybe maybe if you pull out seeds
okay this is
nice okay no they just keep jumping in
the hole
all right is that not what you wanted um
i still going sorry no it's a cut
i have enough i have enough some
sacrifices have to be made well they
keep getting in my way
i'm sorry they i did not raise them
properly i've been too busy you know
there's too many chickens i cannot break
them all at once
i don't know where the father went they
have no father ammon
please understand education is a bit uh
poor on this server
i'm suffocated by my own children
help me do you happy
where are you oh they're giving you
are you saying are you saying i look so
much like them that you can't see me
when i'm in between them
i feel like we could have done this in a
more efficient way
nothing is more efficient than the
what's in the way
all right we're almost done actually
and as i expected i just
have the chicken stare at me while a
weapon is working
all right uh it should be done after
this vlog
yeah get out
all right now it's just stairs
we could put like actual stairs here
oh uh this might this might need to be
modified a bit
i think that's because i was still
carrying the seats
don't look at me go away my children be
free
be free in this one room in this one
tiny room
ah there's already five eggs in here oh
there's
also a chest in the chest yes where the
chest pants yeah
it wasn't there when i looked before
interesting
oh my god eggs it's working
yay we did it oh
the first automatic uh
first automatic system in the server
oh my god and that was so fast we only
had uh it only took us like uh
30 minutes yeah that was really fast
but okay and when it's full then it just
it just doesn't
uh fill it up anymore but the car
probably keeps on driving i guess
yeah i want to see what happens if we
both log out and
this is really still collect uh it
should
so the server is running on its own so
everything should still
do its thing
can i hire you again soon
i mean what are we supposed to do for
the rest of the stream now it only took
40 minutes
that's a good question um is there
anything you would like to do that i can
help you with
uh remember i was telling you i want to
build like a xp farm
oh yeah i do want to build something
like that but
i'm not sure like uh pekura did
she did a upside down pyramid
yeah and i think the way i mean where
all the the enemies spawn up ah yeah
yeah yeah like
it's all dark in there and then i'm
pretty sure the way it works is
there's like different water sources
probably like in each corner of the
pyramid that pushes them down into the
one
hole where they fall down but the thing
i couldn't figure out is uh
how the door opens because they press a
button and then the door opens up top
but i was playing around with the
redstone
and it doesn't it doesn't travel
vertically it only travels on the floor
i wasn't sure how they made it so
you know what i'm saying i
i i have watched the compliance complete
stream that people
did but ken um
probably a redstone torch tower as they
say red red
red stone torch towers ah
you understand that yeah yeah yeah
i get it yeah okay um
well then i i have to i have to think
about how we're gonna make this or where
we're gonna make
it okay let me think about it a bit
because i kind of i guess the pyramid
the upside down pyramid is like the most
it doesn't have to be yeah i guess it
makes sense for it to be an upside-down
pyramid
how would we even start that i feel like
actually um i will um
make some sacrifices right now
it's already collected a ton of eggs
i just killed like 5 million birds oh my
god
this feels so wrong it hurts my heart
i'm so sorry
how could you kill your own children
but i have so many eggs i need to make
more space for the newborn baby
i can't stop it i can't stop myself from
killing my peers
i mean you're getting free xp yeah
that's true
that's this is an exp farm though
oh my god
yeah but okay i have to stop myself this
is too much
for my heart for my soul i feel like
i've killed my family i can't get back
up
well you guys have chosen death
okay he's free go
he decided to go back in
i was trying to free him
i will i will create some new life right
away this is not a sad moment this is a
happy moment some lives have to go to
make space for more
but why because it's just
i don't have so much space and i need
food
gonna have an egg party you want to
watch
how they okay sure one second
[Laughter]
and another generation has been born
wait so what's the point of that uh
well we kill them to get meat but uh
we can't keep on recreating new eggs so
we have endless meat
i see i see i see i see and also we get
feathers for arrows
i just honestly i just wanted cute uh
chickens
and the cape you have is pretty cool
where'd you get that
the what the cape oh
my turn around on this you don't have
one
apparently i got it through uh ah my
shader
for i think my shader not off the phone
like when you install the shader that i
have you get my
cake i didn't get a cape
hey but are you using silver no
[Music]
all right so sleep i think i've made my
choice
i thought about it a little bit okay
pyramid that you made um
it's really high up in the sky but i
don't think we need to do that
is there is there would there be a
reason for it being so high up
maybe just because it looks cool do you
see a reason
is there a reason yes there is a reason
there is
uh the fall damage
okay but we don't have to make it so
high up
um do we not have enough blocks
oh i should have enough blocks yeah i
have i have a ton of cobblestone
um me too i also have a lot of blocks if
we still need more
i don't think we need to make like um
um i'm just trying to think of the
layout for it
i don't want to copy her exactly like
i'd rather come up with it myself you
guys like
why do i have so many eggs what the hell
because of me
when you work with kiara once you go
back home
you cannot get rid of the eggs for the
next seven days
is this my my payment yes
eggs i hope you're satisfied thank you
very much
for your services
i guess it's worth it thank you
you can have your own uh chicken in your
house now oh yeah i can make more
chickens
yeah why would you if you
if you have a chicken farm already in
the neighborhood yeah i could just take
eggs from you and you would you would
never notice
yeah i have so many too many kill like
half your chickens and then you would
never notice
they can only be killed by my own hands
okay brother i
i wouldn't do that i mean i did kill a
few willows uh
you know it was an accident though
okay so i think i've decided the
location
possibly for our xp farm unless it'll
look too ugly here i don't know we can
build something on top of it
when you killed those chickens did you
make a grave for them
at least ah i mean i used my shovel and
i dug a lot so their body might have
gotten buried at some point
okay good enough thank you
you want to say some words to remember
them by
i don't know which one of you it was but
i hope you had a good life
uh with your friends with your family
with your companions
but in chicken heaven at least you will
not be made into a phoenix burger so
it might have been a better life we have
amelia
um only to thank her she
she has given you another chance in some
way please see it positively
yeah like a phoenix you'll be reborn
through your eggs
yeah what the phoenix will be reborn
like a phoenix
they will be reborn through their eggs
ah
like a phoenix yeah yeah pretty much
rest in peace my dear chickens
beautiful i would like to change the the
outside uh design of my
of my chicken house someday though it
must be i actually want to build a huge
chicken on top of it
oh like uh like uh subaru some pies
yeah ah cute
all right so i've decided yes
we will try to build it we have decided
to hike okay
[Laughter]
uh we'll try to build it uh we were
saying we have to build it in the ocean
so
we'll we'll take good as old atlantis
spot because she's not gonna build it
there
and that's really good yeah
because she wants to build it in a coral
reef biome and i tried looking for one
but i couldn't find any and
i'm pretty sure there's one like really
really really really far
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay let's leave that question
unanswered yeah
it's okay it was fun and we have found
uh but we can do something else with
that spot
probably yeah it will be worth
well worth something else also there was
a village there so that's that
there was oh yeah yeah yeah there's a
yeah we could we could put all our
automatic farms there
actually maybe they would be better off
closer yeah it should be closer
but for the xp farm i think it's fine
for it to be
pretty far away yeah yeah because we
don't need it every time just when you
want to like something yeah
or uh yeah get your levels back for
whatever you need it for
don dun
i feel like such a farmer let me play
this game
is this my real purpose to be a farmer
so satisfying
wait sorry i'm almost uh back with you
okay it just feels um a bit wrong if i
leave my
my field without planted seeds
thank you time where are you anyway
i'm in my house just gathering resources
for the next project
okay
amelia not only detective
but also architects is there anything
she cannot do
i doubt it
everyone hire amelia watson
um my schedule is uh booked currently
but you can go through
uh my assistant
have you heard the tragic that has come
upon
ina what happened while i was streaming
i was like oh let's check out
how uh inna's house is looking
and i went over there and
pretty much uh 90 of the cows were
gone you know how she had like millions
of cows there
yeah and they were all gone
and inaud didn't know i thought that she
just like
he ate most but it's very repopulated
what's this
was this my papa again it's really
repopulated now how did this happen
and look oh and sheep's went since when
it cooked
why is there sheeps now
i think she was uh i think she might
have been playing a little bit earlier
got tonight oh it was not my papa anyway
she
we were like okay why did this happen
did someone eat all the
all the uh all the cows because it was
really like
only like four cows or so in the in the
in beside
in inside the fences oh
ina logged in and she checked it out and
she realized that she left like a glass
block
somewhere here and that's how they got
over the fence
they escaped i have only myself to blame
this what you said it was very sad
very sad that's right good so quickly
yeah all right
now you're my intern
okay oh i need a bucket
okay i i have a bucket if you want it
but i don't have it in my hands right
now
okay you get your bucket i'll get my
bucket i think we'll need
like okay yep oogie actually i got that
bucket from you know
i'm sure she doesn't mind well she will
never get it back i'm sorry
it's a very big project it's okay if we
don't finish it
oh yeah i'll i'll stay with you for one
more hour because after that i have to
keep your chest okay that's fine
i need more i need more um
i need more coal damn am i running out
of coal
do i have more coal
you can use your bucket to get lava you
can use the lava
for your furnace what
how does that work uh you just fill your
bucket with lava and then you put in the
furnace so you take your bucket out
and how long does that work i don't know
actually
i think somebody said it's like 15 more
than coal 15 times more
[Music]
amazing the knowledge that that is
inside you does it not
like is it not heavy to have so much
knowledge
well chat chat they like forced the
knowledge on me so
wow wow
well
sorry i've been uh trying to organize
all the stuff
[Music]
just put it all in there more eggs
feathers
if you see a bucket just take it
okay i see a bucket no it's my bucket
oh i see a bucket is that milk
i'll just make a new one otherwise there
should be a bucket
there should be there has to be a bucket
okay
i have the bucket i have the bucket oh i
got the pocket is there anything
anything else i need
uh maybe if you don't have a pickaxe if
you have a pickaxe
africa all right we should sleep now
though
okay let's sleep together
on the other side of the room you gotta
check out what i wrote
i did that after my stream
for whenever she comes back she has a a
bed
next to a chicken which might resemble
me
like she doesn't want to sleep right
next to me but she'll see this chicken
which will hopefully remind her of me
yeah like she'll subconsciously up and
she'll be like wow i miss kiara yeah
[Music]
i feel like that that will work
definitely it's good that you have a bed
for her because uh she always picks up
her bed after she sets the respawn point
ah that's a weird habit yeah
does you still not have a house uh that
hole over there you see that hole
oh that's uh that's callie's house
house she decided to leave my comfy cozy
house
for this
oh she has a bed wow wow
she also dug into my tunnel over here
but it's fine
should i pick up some water here uh yeah
if you want yeah well we have to take
well yeah
no actually because we need the source
we gotta take it from the source
from the source
i got it all right we're gonna take the
minecart all the way
oh yay next
mission experience point farming
power well i don't think we'll finish it
today but we might get pretty far
i have a good idea of how to do it
i trust you i trust you ami okay i
respect you
and you can take those cards for you
okay
[Music]
now you press the video how far do we go
all the way
oh okay we're going all the way
ex atlantis
yeah we'll have to change the signs
since it's not gonna be atlantis anymore
i'm zooming in on you ame oh
it feels much slower when i'm doing ah
it makes me dizzy
oh a cinematic oh my god
like i'm shooting a movie
oh we could shoot i mean we should make
a movie
in minecraft um
episode yeah like laugh or laughter
noises afterwards
yeah okay i like it if you write it i'll
help shoot it
okay i'll write it okay it will be but
we also need
uh enough to co-write it for some bad
puns
that's a genius item come with
all the hololeon members during
minecraft
yeah with jokes i think some people have
already animated some stuff uh
some minecraft stuff about us yeah that
looks so good
i retweeted
yeah if we make it ourselves we can add
like dialogue and stuff
and we can voice it ourselves we'll have
cali do the
soundtrack okay i don't think we
need to so much better
yeah yeah you're right okay
low quality we don't have much of a
budget detective
weapon yeah that's true
well then again well
i mean maybe there will be some
people who want to uh
yeah damn it's it's a long long shaft
huh
we're almost there this is the last part
actually i think okay
yeah when we make a right that's like
yep this last part
okay i remember i remember this draft
that one's pretty big i want to take a
more
bed here oh yeah
emergency bed you made it wow hooray
motivational i like all the signs that
you all
put in here thank you very inspiring
and you have to ask one thing um chapter
chat
yeah this is for uh treasure hunting
this is our dock
whoa i wanna go
sometime soon yeah we should we should
all do treasure hunting if we
we end up doing collabs again soon or we
can
everybody collab or we could just go
just us
oh you want to go there what okay so
we're we're just
uh i'm just uh i think we'll make it
like in the middle of this thing
and i just need to ask chat uh what do
you guys say fall damage
from the zombies uh how many blocks of
fall damage is the
ideal amount for the last hit because
uh the idea is if you're making it high
up
you're doing it because you have more
vertical space so that they drop
and somebody says 20 22 23 okay we'll do
we'll do we'll do 23 blocks okay
i'm gonna start building a bridge here
okay you you boat around
uh you know do whatever and then i'll
let you know
i will need you soon okay okay okay
i'm boating around wow the water looks
so nice with the shaders
yeah it does unfortunately though with
the shaders it makes it harder to
um makes it harder to find
treasure uh treasure because the boats
you can usually see them loading in but
with
the shaders because it's so shiny you
can't really see under the water
for a long distance oh yeah
the enderman looking at me from very far
away
and oh edelman you wanna fight huh it's
just lonely
oh i say i see pool
you wanna come home with me i don't have
any season oh wait
are you okay
i'm not looking at you he looks cute
meh meh
sorry i killed you okay
i'm just uh i'm almost most then i'm
just gonna redo everything that i did
why why why it's not uh it's not even
okay oh my god there's so many and
there's an enderman party
or is that oh only one that just go it
moves really fast
oh i'm at kuda's old house
did she move her house too uh i
think so she mostly has been like at her
underwater cave by us
i think she might have some stuff in
there still but like junk pretty much
it's like an emergency bunker it's like
um
like uh how'd you say like
ruins uh of like an historic
historic building
that was that was pretty funny we spent
all that time
building this i couldn't even use it
yeah oh my god
there's so many sheeps well you know is
the tunnel idea was it was my idea um
but uh yeah didn't work out
emma do you like ice skating i've never
been ice skating before
what yeah ame
one day if we meet in the same country
probably japan
then we will go ice skating
it's fun it's easy and it's fun i mean
in the beginning you fall down a lot
but we should go together yeah but i
don't know how to
i don't i'm not a motorly inclined
yeah me neighborhood it's really easy
you learn it quickly
why don't you know how to ride a bike uh
you don't know how to ride a bike okay
so
i am actually also not good with riding
a bike
uh i'm really bad at it like really
but but ice skating is different
do you know how to rollerskate no i
can't ride a scooter i can't ride a
skateboard i don't know how to
rollerblade
i can't ride a bike driving a car
what how to drive you know how to drive
well i don't have my license
uh-huh how did you learn to drive
it's okay it's okay really ice skating
is not that hard
once you figure it out i will teach you
i will hold your hand and i will
okay and one day
you should come to to my my
my my home my
my other home yeah yeah i'm not named
where many phoenixes live wow every
every winter there's like a really
really crazy
uh uh ice skating ring there
it's really nice i can see the the moon
through the water
wow you can come back if you want to
sleep really quick
and then then i'm going to start i'm
going to start building up now
people are saying hand holding is loot
[Music]
holding it's a little rude
okay no that's you that's you right or
zombies no
what it is hello it's me
am i wearing something purple oh yeah
yeah uh so all i did while you were gone
is make this
bridge okay beautiful the bridge to the
moon
yeah oh
that's so so melancholic
okay come on oh yeah i came to sleep i
forgot
do you have a bed do you have two beds
oh they're inside yeah yeah yeah smart
you guys are so scared
how do you think of these things well
good and i would treasure hunting we
would come back here
and put our stuff back but then we
didn't want
we didn't want our uh
it's the parts driving away from you
wait i could catch up okay i got it
um yeah okay sleep
good night amy good night
[Music]
look at each other in the eyes
okay oh wait i'll take some of that
all right and we're gonna build some
stairs
going up i don't know how high up
we should go actually we don't have to
do that we don't have to do that
okay do you have do you have cobblestone
yes okay we're gonna build you can have
the other block and i'll have this block
and we're gonna build up we're gonna go
i should have brought more how many do
you have
64. okay yeah that's fine we're gonna go
20 up okay
okay wait how many was that
you count uh yep
[Music]
uh
no you guys this is just to go up and
then we're gonna build further up after
we build our platform
how much are we going up this is good
all right now we're gonna start
we're gonna start building our little
platform
okay we might replace i might replace
this with glass but for now we'll do
with cobblestone
good that it's safe here to fall down
because i'm not sure if i
understood how this works now
well uh after we build this then
we're gonna use our water buckets to
make like a little water elevator
so we can go up and down
[Music]
how big should the platform be very big
right ah
it doesn't have to be that big it was
huge uh
with piccola's stream well this
this is just like the base area and then
this will be like where you hit the
monsters
and then further up is where we'll we'll
put the uh
the pyramid oh should i not make it this
long no that's good that's fine
i'll i'll just match what you're doing
okay
oh i know how it works now i can go
until the end i didn't know
you could have saved yourself a lot of
pain no but i did i did press
shift back then i don't know what
happened maybe because you only pressed
it and like
you thought it was toggle but you have
to hold it
i'm not sure what i did bye
oh here i'll build the i'll put the
water elevator
thank you let's see it had to happen
[Music]
you travel up there you dropped
something
okay you dropped some stones
oh with space huh
[Laughter]
i'm sure she would
i think i think this is good how long
have you made it yeah
i ran out of stones no can it be out of
wood
and dirt probably now here you take this
oh
it has to be well i'm gonna replace it
anyway so it really doesn't matter
okay you're gonna replace it
yeah because i'm gonna i'm gonna i think
well pekka does was made out of glass
and i think it looks pretty cool but it
doesn't
it doesn't have to be glass if i start
enderman from here
bye bye-bye taking a swim it's really
hot here so uh yeah yeah yeah
a lot a lot of hard work sweating
yes i need a counter uh
of how how often i fall down from here
you shouldn't fall down
now okay so now from here
we're gonna build up and pretty much do
the same thing
okay all right i'll do it from the
middle i guess
actually from the edge how many should i
count
uh this one is okay we're gonna do 23 on
this
23. okay
i feel some six seven ah
[Music]
i forgot how many did you say 23 i think
i did 23.
i did 28. okay okay that makes sense
yeah
i keep while i'm counting i keep on
forgetting how much i ca
how much i needed to count you're
getting too into it
okay from here we're gonna do the same
thing and build around it
okay uh i don't know i guess we'll
well i'll let you decide
you let me decide okay yeah
don't oops don't fall don't fall kiara
don't fall
don't fall don't fall don't fall maybe
there's a way to turn it on toggle
instead of shift
or uh hold on no it works i just
cannot lift my pinky don't lift your
pinky kiara
all right but how do i stop how do i
stop my tongue
[Music]
are you gonna make another elevator wait
i have the one oh yeah you have the
water
yep oh my god all right you have to
build back up
actually wherever you build back up from
do it from like one of the corners that
we can sort of match it
try to match it
[Music]
okay i reached it i need to count in
german otherwise i can't count well
i like it hello i'm back
so uh you want to match it then i made
it way too long over here
yep let's see if you can fix it without
falling
again i have the bucket right so we'll
put the we'll put the bucket uh
on this corner over here you see where
it ends you can put you put the water
there
you can put the water right there do you
think i can do that
just put the water am i not gonna push
you down when i come over there
no are you gonna give it to me uh yes
i'll please just take it uh um
but what if the water bucket falls down
i don't think it will
i don't think i can push you off
okay we'll put the water here right now
it dragged me down
where is my okay here okay i feel like
all the stones will fall oh wait
well i haven't been drinking oh wait how
do i
oh also remind it it's because i always
forget
reminder for what to eat because i
always
okay oh wait i'm eating raw raw potatoes
goddammit i thought
oh i only have bro i thought those were
done potatoes goddammit
well okay didn't you just like harvest
those
what how are you
i can't do it on it
[Laughter]
don't worry i got it
i i tried to like do it in a way that i
can also collect them
oh it's okay we don't have to keep them
i have a lot
[Music]
okay
amelia i have an important information
for you yes don't
sw yeah yeah yeah yeah
you just gotta let it go
[Music]
let it go let it go i don't think we're
allowed to sing that
here's just three words in the random
melody
let's see if that holds up in court
don't worry uh amelia you're not only a
detective and an architect you're also
my lawyer yeah yeah yeah
yeah after this we can go go sleep
okay oh pretty sunset
right that's what i love about this
shader
and amelia she looks so beautiful in the
sunset
ah your hair reminds me of a sunset
actually like the colors
the orange the blue
i'm just going to stand there not going
to do any work there stop there
oh no and on the golden hour is over i'm
in it's okay
i was working we're almost done
trying to do a show photo shooting here
do you need someone
what nope
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is my reason my purpose my destiny
is to fall
that's what you get for slacking off
don't worry i i almost got it we're
almost done
you can go back go back to bed it's okay
i can be useful sometimes
see i closed almost the hole okay
i just okay now let's go back down and
try not to die
okay well i only have a half a heart
left
you have some do you have some cooked
food or something incredible
make potatoes i can give you raw
potatoes for that uh
oh it's all right thank you though thank
you
if you want to you can cook them here in
the furnace oh
nice well i don't think there's anything
to burn unless you have
ah we can put some of this jungle plants
i have charcoal i have charcoal
okay does that do the trick yeah yeah
[Music]
okay good night ame good night oh yes we
can't forget that i was not very helpful
to wake up with a fresh mind
yeah it's a new day new day new day
and a new hick good day starts with a
good hick
good morning sunshine this looks pretty
cool
so far i think um yeah
beautiful following piccolo
[Music]
you having issues no no no no that's
fine
i got it
i'm gonna take down this extra pillar
that you made here it
water looks so nice
oh why am i why am i dying again
i'm coming i'm coming yeah my chat is
counting down as
a as me falling down that i didn't i
didn't really fall down that that was
not
falling down are you even up here
no i'm just shouldn't fall damage yeah
it did not count but you fell out of the
waterfall
yes and i took fall damage from that is
that isn't that unbelievable that's not
fair
uh when you get up there you can i'm
trying to give you something to do
um
we're gonna be building a upside down
pyramid
so i don't know exactly how to start it
so if you can think of a way to start it
you can do it i think i think all right
you have the brain power
yes totally yeah i believe in you upside
down pyramid okay
but like on uh top
like that from like um
how do i explain my thoughts
uh the base here is that the smallest
point of the tip of the
pyramid or do i build a tiny tip on
on top of that
i'll be right there i'll be right there
uh all done i'm almost i'm almost done
nah i think you you have the right idea
i think you haven't already i just have
to see what
what you're talking about besides
they'll be there uh
just like see your explanation clearly
there's nothing to see though it's just
imagination yeah yeah yeah yeah
hey you can like do a little guide okay
i'm coming up
you know that uh deutsche technology is
best to take a look uh
okay i'm here okay question was
it so if you're feeling an upside down
pyramid
um does is it like the tiny
tip the one block tip of the pyramid
yeah so or is this huge
platform the the smallest uh tip
smallest uh whatever
whatever okay so
there this is this is the tip of the
pyramid you see this
okay so we'll build
this is the perimeter of the tip and
then we build like staircases
up you understand like uh we should be
able to walk up each corner
from the inside oh from the inside you
want to build it
yeah like uh oh that makes sense
we shouldn't be able to do it like that
i think like this
that i think that's but aren't we done
building unnecessary blocks outside like
like
like this one because we have to place
something
underneath every time to build the next
step
[Music]
well that's why we have this platform
here so that we can uh
yeah yeah yeah you got the right idea i
think this is yeah
okay
yeah we could do it from the higher we
get
we get a problem okay so maybe go on the
other corner and then
i guess it doesn't matter oh i see i see
i see
there you go
right
now we do this
oh okay okay okay okay okay i got you
watson
i yeah we got it all right okay okay
let's see
well it doesn't have to be it doesn't
have to be exactly like this like now we
can go out
by two you know what i'm gonna win and
uh i think i finally understand how i
can do the thing okay we'll go up we'll
go out by two this time
okay ah two oh squishy
just to give it more um i want to say
girth but i don't think that's the right
term with with
well with english words i will have to
trust you they're
wetting my british dictionary
watson
why am i doing it differently
uh because you didn't go you didn't go
out on the on this side you put it on
top of the one that's already existing
you got to put it
ah okay okay you you just misunderstood
when i said two
yeah yeah yeah that's fine that's right
okay okay
now you can start out there's one blocks
left though i haven't i have more hair
oh thank you welcome this is all
you need me to run to get more blocks
let me know
okay oh you have more no
at home yeah 10 10 million yeah
say this is the the fruits of our labor
from the uh tunnel digging
it's like that's where that's where all
of our resources came from pretty much
for building i mean aside from wood lots
of stone
lots and lots of stones now you just
extend yours by one
like this extend okay on the same level
you say
yeah oops okay
just so that uh it starts widening out
you know
okay and chad
right i wonder well
you know there's no real right way to do
it i think for this part
as long as as long as we make it a place
where everyone is getting
tell us something should we send super
chat to let them know let them know what
2 2 2 x 2 tip
they need a 2x2 hole oh a two by two
hole
[Music]
what is a two by two hole well
this is the three by three hole
well okay three by three hole okay
[Music]
this should be fine i think
it also works yeah they said it works
wait my freeway okay okay
good i shall continue my
my building am i going up again
um yeah yeah yeah you don't happen to
have a water bucket do you
oh nope i do not
okay jump down freely like a bird
yeah uh so you guys for the exit hole it
has to be
it has to be wide it can't be like just
one
for the hole where the the monsters fall
out
okay has to be white okay okay okay i
got it okay we'll dig that we'll do that
at the end
so we don't fall what are we building we
are building
a tower of death every enemy that will
spawn on top
will fall down a tiny hole a really long
hole
and they will die yep and no we we get
the last
hidden and then we get the xp for it oh
yeah oh yeah right because you can
activate it with a button
and then they all fall down and then
you're gonna explain with the exp you
can do enchanting right
julio i never enchanted something before
but sounds cool
should i widen it again my row or keep
on going up
uh i think widening it by two maybe
maybe this time
okay from where you are go up by two oh
i have no more stones left
should i go home once and pick some
stones up oh if you don't mind
i have i have some but i don't think
it's enough to finish i have
okay i also bring some food
okay enjoy your trip
thank you probably take me like uh 20
minutes and then i'll end the stream
okay okay thanks kidding we can do a bit
of
i can do a bit of overtime you have
helped me so quickly today
i don't know if we'll be able to finish
or test it because we gotta wait for
stuff to spawn so
yeah finishing is probably not possible
but that's all right
oh yeah pretty far work in progress
you're so fast everything i i do with
you it just goes so fast just goes like
zoom
efficient time travel
almost as fast as your mom goes when i
i don't know
not gonna finish that nope
i'm not good with mom jokes okay
oh my mom is watching all my streams by
the way mom i just said that because
ahmed does all the mom jokes it's
because she always does it mom i don't
do mom jokes you know mom that i don't
do it
she really watches all my streams i
think i've heard her say a few
mom jokes before so i wouldn't really
trust her word here
that's not true i've said maybe one mom
joke but only to copy you
like police story my mom jokes if
anything probably just stories about my
mom that weren't even jokes but they're
so funny
but they're not jokes
uh uh well i guess you're in the tunnel
so you can't sleep
but when you get back you let me know
yes i'll instantly sleep
[Music]
amelia would you like to say something
to my
also mom watched like all the other
girls so she also checked out you
ah i remember what she said about you
checks me out huh
i just told her that you're you're very
smart
and very sweet and very helpful
ah thank you
oh if i say something to your mom um
oh you did a good job kiara's really
nice yeah
uh if if i were kiara's mom i would be
proud
that's so cute
well yup mama is very proud
she told me she's very proud i'm very
happy
that's really nice what about um
would you like to mention any any
anything about ground pounds
um uh
no no not today
not to your mom that's only for chad's
mom
okay okay chad's mom okay okay
who is who is chad chad chant
killing i understand
always getting bullied but dad really
just doesn't learn
the lesson they keep on trying to teach
amelia watson but there's nothing to
teach emilia watson
she already knows she's also a time
traveler so everything with
telling her now she already learned in
the future or in the past or whatever
yes nothing you can teach amelia watson
and i shall sleep now okay
hold on i gotta go back
there's there's nothing to teach amelia
watson except the heights you should be
building
i got the right height no i guessed it
myself by
reading chat and inferring what the
correct number was based on how many
people were spamming it
why 128 for best spawn rates
okay 128 blocks
wide everyone's uh why why
the height why 128.
[Music]
120 tall hmm
oh i why because it's the best spawn
rate
alright
what can you say why again
because that's how the game was
programmed
what happened nothing you guys it works
there's a creeper that spawned on top of
my
platform and it almost killed me hooray
well it seems like it works yeah
yeah it's fine even if it's not that
efficient it'll probably be better than
nothing
i agree it should be fine
but the the pyramid can still like grow
bigger now
no they're just saying because the
creeper spawn so successful
oh no yeah with the
pyramid we can still go up a little bit
and there will still be more levels i
don't think it'll be
i don't know if we'll reach 120 i don't
know what we're at we'll see
i'll be able to check once i get back up
there because pyramid
levels are still going up so we might
reach 128 at some point
okay they're saying to put torches
before we are
like actually using yourself so we're
not getting
uh yeah interrupted
yeah stupid creepers
today when i was streaming i was leaving
the watson
shaft with uh in my inventory that was
about to also end the stream so i'm
right at the door of the watson chef
and i'm like answering a question from
the chat and in that moment when i open
the door from the watson shaft
a creeper blows up behind me and kills
me while i'm having diamond
in my hands uh yeah
a lot of the mines i uh had to name them
like
f this mine because that uh happens a
lot yeah
i didn't put enough torches i don't know
why i did that
yes anyway uh because that happened
one uh one glass panel got destroyed in
that window but i replaced it with a
stone because i had no
glass ah that's okay i can fix it at
some point
if you will ever notice i'll find it
usually though i guess something like
that happens and if you have dirt
uh i usually fill it with dirt because
uh i'll definitely notice if it's dirt
like when i go back through it's like oh
yeah
[Music]
hey wait was it really called watson
shaft
was it really called weapon chat yeah
that's the name of the manual
okay because everyone is laughing about
the name in my chat
i don't understand why that isn't so
funny
what's so funny about watson chapped
there she goes laughing you guys say i'm
the lute one
well i didn't name it after all
because i have arrived
and with many stones and many potatoes
oh my gosh
what do you need watson uh now i'm just
going to ask for pickaxe
i only have my own damage
yeah check the y level
[Music]
we're at 112 that's not bad but it'll
it'll be a bit of work to go all the way
up but we don't have to finish so
we'll just go for as long as you said
like uh
we don't have to go over anything yeah
maybe like
20 more minutes yeah that's fine okay
see how high we can get
i am here hello hello
let's see i have i have lots of stones
so let me know if you need stones okay
i think i'm good for a while i had a
decent amount left
wait oh i'm making too wide
[Music]
that's good
it's like
like a little area here it's like a
small lake it could be really nice to
build something there
i don't know what though um you want to
build something in the pyramid
no no no there's like a little lake if
you look behind you
you see over there
oh yeah that's a really pretty area
yeah maybe i like a like a holiday home
oh yeah yeah yeah
vacation house we could build there like
a
hotdog hotel
nice watson
hotel made by watson industries
maybe not maybe not a hotel maybe i'll
build a
banana boat banana but
yeah that'd be cool
okay what what exactly is a banana boat
is it a boat in the shape of a banana
uh yeah we can make it that what is it
actually
i think i think it's a type of boat
yeah let's make a yellow boat in the
shape of a banana yeah
a giant banana in the water
sounds good it'll be sold as a bunch of
yellow stuff
i don't want a banana wait do i know
what a banana hammock is what is the
banana
milk what am i saying oh god
she doesn't know you
i guys no no no no
no no no no i can never get rid of the
bottom left thingy oh god
can i undo what oh god what did i say oh
god
is it like a type of underwear uh
well you could say that because of the
shape yeah okay
this is embarrassing no you didn't know
it's okay
you get a free pass but you know what
what a hammock is where you can like
sleep in like between two trees
yeah i thought it was maybe like
something like that
that's understandable understandably
once i said it i was like wait
wait
this is what i get for that i fell down
headed to the counter
made me too nervous
[Music]
no there's a lot of words like that that
have a
you know a double meaning oh
it's normal oh yep okay
a creeper no no no
don't come closer it fell down nice oh
no it's back
don't don't don't explode don't
just don't is there something there
yep two creepers but i have escaped
on our platform and on the on the
on the lower one on the first one wait
how do i get
wow it's already it's already effective
on there
yeah on the lower level even i'm gonna
get to you
did the water like uh stop oh wait no
no there should be water in the back and
in the middle
okay i'll just have to dig through it
okay replace it again
is this tree really big or is that just
a regular tree
there's like a big tree but i guess it's
just regular it looks big
i want to see the big train it's not i
mean it's not that big but it looks
it looks pretty big from here that tree
you see it
right here in the middle of this horse
field oh
it does look big yeah yeah but i can't
tell because the trees over there look
i guess they do look smaller oh they
said it's big they said it's a big tree
wow
nice um how do you say
[Music]
english
um
[Music]
yeah observation not exactly but nice
observation
ah thank you
talking about the job as a detective
the among us stream
you were just too good of a killer i'm
just thinking about maybe like
changing your your career maybe you
could become a reaper like
assassin oh yeah
oh damn assassins are like really hot
[Laughter]
if you say so that's that's why i like
cali so much you know
oh yeah yeah yeah badass
if we go sleep uh yep
uh jump down okay
i'll use my last two blocks okay
when we come back it's gonna be
dangerous we didn't put any torches down
so
oh yeah that's
oh someone sent a super chat to tell us
something about our thingy
i shall read it in the second
i wish i could have uh done the imposter
thingy one time but
i'm doing a mangas stream with the
viewers
to tomorrow i think oh
yeah hopefully i can beat one posture
but i wonder how it is to
to like play it with the viewers like if
i watched it when when poga
uh played it with her viewers and they
um
they let her win and like really didn't
play it
like like norm like normal people would
yeah
yeah no i don't know i want to play it
normally
otherwise it's not fun tell your
employees that they'll get fired if they
don't yeah
abide by the rules yeah i think we can
communicate and
and yeah tell them how to do it don't
you also want to maybe try that by
playing among us with your viewers
[Music]
why so many creepers why why
okay um you know oh we can go from the
back
are they gonna blow up if i go past them
in the waterfall
um good question i think it's fine
i think the back waterfall goes all the
way up
[Laughter]
is the platform okay yeah
okay nothing that we cannot fix
okay okay how did you get in here
well i went for the middle waterfall
okay let's continue building until the
night uh okay
that's good whatever yeah what do we
have
let's see our y oh we only went up by
two blocks yeah
it's a long long process maybe we can go
up
uh on this one we'll go up by two
instead of out by two
yes i i agree with you
i agree where'd you go
i turned around and you were gone i'm
there i'm there i'm there
i'm there don't you see me you need some
glasses
you need glasses if you don't see me
maybe i'm just going too fast
oh yeah yeah i think my game is
volunteer sometimes the
enemies show up as invisible so maybe
maybe you're also invisible on my screen
yeah does that ever happen to you
because i haven't seen me a lot
no never happened to me it happens to me
like almost every time i play
monsters will be invisible yeah
yeah oh that's weird
spooky i think my game is haunted
okay where did i stop here
don't fall down kiara it's not that hard
we're building up on the first on the
first row and then we'll go
out on the first row yes
oh okay sorry i wasted some of your
blocks
no problem i have enough now but it will
just not look
pretty from the outside are you okay
with that what's in uh i'll fix it i'll
fix it
we're building uh original design
um inspired by uh
senpai yes
and i think now
uh let's build up one more
and then build out
[Music]
i'll probably be nighttime but yeah by
the time we're done with that
maybe actually
are you gonna fail someone was trying to
tell me something
[Music]
uh the mob farm it's better to put the
farm
120 blocks higher than ground not at
y28 it's because maps despawn instantly
when they're at
120 120 plus blocks away okay so it's
not 128 but 120.
okay we're pretty close okay i think i
think
uh as long as the top
the top top level is at 120
it should it should be okay because it's
still
it's still accessible by the mobs all
right now we go
out okay
okey-dokey wow people are like finally
finally i love it when we can make them
crazy like this
finally she read it hallelujah party
funny
but we had the right idea i think didn't
we we were pretty close
wait now they're like no chiara no wait
wait oh well
what now they didn't understand that we
did not understand apparently i said
you want the base to be at 120. does it
really i mean does it really have to be
so
strict on the numbers because we were on
the lower platform and there were
already
how many monsters were there there were
like seven monsters already on the lower
platform which wasn't even at 120 so you
guys
you know there may be a specific way of
doing it but i don't think that's
it has to be you know it's not like the
law it's not like it's not going to work
at all
it's not that strict 128 is efficient
okay well i'm all out i will follow
what what's in this can i have some
blocks
there you go oh wait i'll only give you
one
here have one block each
one thank you wait
you're welcome no you only gave me one
block
no it's down there down here ah
thank you i can give you more no it's
okay i think this is good
okay
hold on almost fell down
they're saying 120 above the ground
well it's too late
too late i'm sure it'll work
yeah it will work
we're we're widening it again right
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
it should be two ideas
it'll work but not be as efficient
well too bad
it feels like i'm falling down in a
second ah
oh no i'm fine i'm done pressing shift
again right
yeah up again okay
[Music]
i'm out of box oh that was fast
yeah you thank you
uh i guess i'm not really a kfp
intern at this moment it's more like
reversed roles now
true yeah well you have already done
your job
yeah you got distracted
you have some good balance we need one
of those signs that they have like
at a factories or like construction
sites it's been
zero days since the last accident
it's never been more than zero days
yeah that's true well i'm speed right
now
i'm speed i'm down
i just i just see your name
oh good too good
it's been in zero days oh yeah we have
to put it in minutes
yeah yeah
okay well everything's good down here
everything's cool
no mobs
wow this is so impressive from inside
yeah it's like a coliseum
[Music]
i got a i got a good number of 10 times
falling down that's a good number i
rounded it
up so just that it would look like a
nicer number
that's why i just fell down
i'll leave some stones here okay so that
they can be used thank you
why is he not closing
oh yeah there we go wow
wow let
[Music]
let me take a screenshot for next
thumbnail
beautiful
better angle
run run run run
thank you for the congratulations on 10
falls i know
impressive but wait the light is
horrible now i cannot work like this
my work is a photographer i cannot do it
like this
okay i'm coming back oh guys
where are you um down there okay
hello hello
i put the stones in inside
ah thank you
continue buildings well amelia
watson it was a pleasure to work with
you today
yes yes yes you have made some nice
progress on my side
and on your side yeah we did a lot today
it's not that i only used you
and uh uh
yep used your uh your
body for working and yeah
i also helped you so everything's cool
[Music]
should we take this back and we can do
our exit as we're going
oh yeah just so next time you start
you're already
at home back at your farm you can take
that one
oh should we sleep what about you what
about you oh i have a minecart here
okay let's go
the ending credits yes roll the credits
roll them my friends roll them oh there
my my chat is trying to be funny by
um you know how number 10
it's uh written as t-e-n you know right
ah yeah yeah yeah
and pencil is one of my nicknames so
they're writing the number ten and then
two
hahaha funny clever
[Music]
respect me i'm your i'm your boss i'll
fire you if you keep on joking about
that
i like it i think it'd make a good
hashtag too
oh yeah
yes thank you don't give them too many
ideas
don't make them feel like they're funny
or something
they can work for the at a better place
with a better salary if you if you
motivate them like that
all right so if you say goodbye yeah
yeah
goodbye i'll continue my stream with
some super jet readings though
yes chris protags
are really nice to listen too thank you
yeah yeah yeah because you like talk
about other stuff
yeah super chat you don't i do sometimes
uh usually i try to get through it
pretty fast
there's a lot to get for you yeah
uh well yeah thank you guys for watching
we made a lot of progress
today hopefully it wasn't too
frustrating for you to watch and if it
was frustrating
uh i hope you could bottle it up and
deal with it in a
healthy way um
uh yeah so thank you for watching and
kara will still be streaming after this
i will not because i'm gonna do super
chat reading sometime tomorrow because i
got a lot to catch up on
so yeah you go watch kiara stream as
soon as we
get to the end here yeah i think
that is the real question am i oh oh yes
uh yeah i'm gonna go to sleep
right now i probably won't sleep that
long since i slept for a little bit
earlier
ah while i was sleeping uh i had a dream
i totally cared i had a dream that kiara
moved the stream
to like two or three hours later and
then but it was like a weird dream it
was like i heard her voice she was like
talking to me saying i'm it i moved the
stream two hours later
and i was like what and then i woke up
and then i checked i checked my
my phone and i got a message from her
and she was like
i'm gonna move the we could move the
stream two hours later
it's really weird it's like my my brain
picked up on on the message you can
uh you can see the future like for real
you're a time traveler
i was yeah to you on discord saw it in
your dream and heard it in your dream
yeah but actually i maybe you just had
my stream open because i also said it
out loud
no no i didn't have used to move inside
another case that must be solved yes
your voice echoed through time
well then amelia if you wanna uh want me
to help you out sometime soon with the
tower again you can call me anytime
ah thank you thank you otherwise
uh if you don't want me to help you with
that next week otherwise i must
challenge you for
a chess rematch next week oh no
good job okay i'll i'll think about it
i'll ask you
what they want to do yes all right
bye bye bye uh thank you
thank you good luck on your super chat
thank you
bye bye thank you for your help what's
in the industries but you're welcome
i'll send you
i'll send you the bill or the other one
you sent me the bill
i'll just take your eggs and we'll call
it even
bye
[Music]
all right kiara it's gone uh
what did you guys think of today's
stream i'm gonna go check her egg chest
because i'm actually curious to see how
many we've gotten
uh since since we finished the
construction of the
automatic railway
i'm just curious
cozy stream good stream i think yeah
thank you
um yeah so thank you wow we had a lot of
big super chats wow
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you
actually not that many i guess because
she killed a lot of them
there weren't as many
can they escape i feel like they can get
out whenever they want
anyways uh thank you for all the big
super chats i'm gonna do
a super chat reading tomorrow at some
point because i have
uh super chats from the minecraft collab
and also the among us collab that i
hadn't read
i think i did i don't think i read the
witcher
i've read the one from witcher today i
don't remember oh 500k
so close woohoo
um yeah so uh i will put out a schedule
probably late tomorrow
um and i will schedule karaoke
probably on monday or tuesday or
wednesday
probably wednesday i like i like
and then um yes
i guess uh hatsuma already talked about
it but
i do have a collab with hachima on
i want to say it's tuesday but i don't
remember exactly
i think it'll be after we'll do the
celebration karaoke after the collab
um i didn't read the last
witcher's super chat okay i will do that
tomorrow then
we'll do super chat reading um i'll try
i try to find some way to make it
kind of exciting
and uh
did you confirm my youtube schedule ah
okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah oh thank you thank you
everybody for watching thank you for
support i will read all the super chats
tomorrow then we'll be all cut up
and i'll try not to uh like usually with
collabs um you know i just end with
everybody else
uh so yeah we'll do super chat reading
to
catch up and then hopefully we don't
fall behind
i'll try to do it after every stream
and yeah 27th yes on the 27th
so i'll see you guys later today or it
might be tomorrow for you
and we'll hang out for a little bit then
i'll work on the schedule
i don't know what time the super chat
reading is going to be because i'm going
to go to sleep now i don't know how long
i'll support
but thank you for all the support a lot
of super chats today too
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you good night oh yes to
me
uh thank you for watching thank you for
support
and yeah uh another week starting
this week is pretty good i think today
was the only day that was like kind of
meh but uh all the rest of the days were
i think everything went really well
hopefully next week we have another good
week thank you for watching
[Music]
goodbye
so
[Music]
bye