a
St
what
[Music]
w
h
[Music]
for
no
[Music]
woo
k
hello hello it going I'm
[Music]
dying die oh yeah you need heal need to
balance out the
orange oh the Orange is we have to our
colors to be
darker or lighter like a darker
urine what what what oh my God because
you're like orange you're both orange
actually you guys are like really really
dark
urine
who piss is
orange well wants to I I think if you're
radioactive maybe speak up who who who
wants to confess I couldn't believe that
I would hear such a thing already like 1
minute into the Stream So I really
thought you we got to set like a record
for
this um yeah so we're back again with
Eden Eternal Yi
yipp um sh is feeling a little bit under
the weather right yeah I'm dying I'll
see you guys in heaven don't
die and and uh so yeah I think today
will be a little bit of a shorter stream
this right
this
yeah but we'll be we'll be efficient
anyway even with less we got to go kill
Charles again that's
how it's okay it's been a while
so that a
recap but before we do that um kfp is
inviting us to visit visit our Guild
City so oh can I visit your city
actually I don't know as a guest can um
but if you can't I was thinking you
could visit Inkwell City if they have
one I heard I I don't know how to get to
my own
City I don't know either yeah how do we
get to the city is it go to base when
you open maybe it's press G oh I can't
go to your city okay I'm going my base
see a
so you're going to Inkwell right yeah
I'm going to Inkwell oh I got a free
outfit o I have a k are you also coming
I go to base okay let's go ink
willion wow so many people again by the
way I'm a Cheerleader today oh my God I
just
left a cheerlead this
guy
r whereit
I walked in and walked out immediately
no come back are you scar they can't
hear me right now be nous backwards are
they too loud I need to be louder than
them I'm here I'm here I can't see you
there's too many people okay wow I'm so
glad you guys chose a desert level if
you chose a desert level I would have
shoved all the all the sand up your here
actually don't know where I am I think I
almost said I was going to shove all the
asses up here but so I guess I could do
that to be honest okay okay okay okaying
master I heard something about oh
they're already here you already made
yeah they made the stat so fast isn't
there supposed to be boss fights in here
maybe I'm thinking of are going to
change when we change outfits or do they
have to be remade also well we have like
free workers they have to be remade I
wonder cuz like I'm not I'm changing my
outfit every single time I log
in wow what other what other options
were there for Guild types is there in
St we got a
church you can I think you can go from
like the G menu and then find town
maybe oh wait did you go maybe it's not
yours I don't know how how do I get to
yours I
[Music]
don't wait are you where are you right
now I'm an Inkwell I don't know how I
got here no no I mean I mean location
not which
Guild the the forest or or aen I'm an
Aven if that's what you're talking about
okay wait oh my God we even got a guild
icon now what a chicken I'm just a
Wandering child in my own
Guild no he but maybe inil has no City
yet oh we have a city apparently we have
H statue uh I don't I don't know if they
made a statue you got to enter so then
they can make one for you like I think
I'm in I'm in the thing I'm just
wandering around while everyone follows
me making sure I don't kill
myself show her the way show her the way
to the Statue oh but it can't show me
the way cuz I'm running out away from
them that won't work got Farm did you
see you open the guild announcements the
kfp made a
guide
oh I'm reading the guide right now these
are the statues I remember Fame Que
guide oh wow you can like Harvest these
here I'll link it thanks for the
information
everyone Consulting gu helpful and
missable info wow oh you're going to
make a statue that's so nice of you
[Music]
guys it' be funny if you just made four
statues no you can you can make statu
anyone you want it doesn't have to be me
unless you do
something there's icons you make a stash
Thursday oh oh the Grands got their own
little wa how do oh you can double jump
what I didn't know could double jump in
this game why are they in the box is
that a The Shoe Box honestly I don't
even know what the purpose of jump ISO
[Laughter]
box per perfect perfect and then you got
some rep why are you guys what can you
guys calm that
Crystal calm down what do you get this
fighting each other I assume this is
oh but I have too many quests I
shouldn't have done that it's too late
I've already done it how do I get a
[Music]
crystal those states are beautiful how
do I give it up you guys can remake them
every single day that I log in okay how
about how about I not do my own gu
Quest it's too much work right now I'm
sick guys I'm sick that was uh nice
thank you guys you worked so hard on I
can sign work to workers nicer thank you
well that's that's should be what they
do by default what a
boss allting she needs to kill Charles
yeah for a third time cuz I hate
Charles let's go Pi a
DA uh wait how do how do I get there uh
how do I not be homeless in the game I
forgot to rent a
house you can rent a house yeah they
said that we have a zero homeless
population for ink
[Laughter]
well oh I need to be level 35 okay oh
I'm I'm watching off of you guys until
then we'll get there ah we should make a
group again oh yeah a
party
party I party party thank you for the
invitation oh thank you all my healer
friends
okay let's meet at the
dungeon
okay BR
rout I have no idea yeah uh was
itona rude how do I want to do a
territory War I would
die what territory are you fighting for
I I don't even
know the heck are these people you can
get statues if you're like the top four
in the server I guess freaking
flexer the one at Beluga Bay
right
what oh actually that's the VK HQ oh I
wasn't the wetlands oops it's okay we
can have Gigi teleport us I won't mess
it up this time I'm
running don't worry teleport away I I
have to run there
first don't don't worry I'm
running maybe I'll be there
first I go do I care about the
St sh
Cavern get
you North oh vile shark yeah
yeah okay uh it's like Nord shark but
it's not a v n is it even Nord shark
actually the VPN oh wait that's just
Nord
VPN you can be double secure so
secure why are you so fast Shori you're
so fast you're slow slow my little
orange
urine what what move speed does your
mouth I have no idea
you're so
fast okay okay I'm going to summon
Chihuahua no I'm summoning
you wait did you did you L your soul oh
thank God thank God summon me I'll
probably end up in the void Vortex or
something like that okay now what if I
summon you
again stop itop it St it no okay now I
summon you again no no I I any need
better casting time I'll end up in a
black hole
okay we're we're good now we're good he
maybe I can pick up a
daily oh me too wait I can't haven't
finish
this got to do the real Quest
first this is again vile shark vile
shark Solo or multiplayer for your quest
I think we can just do solo can't we
hold up solo yeah SOLO going solo oh my
oh why you dying G useless no reason
oh well no
reason um no
reason well K can heal you too I'm just
going to watch I could I could however I
will heal Kiara as
well GG not so much all right you heal
me I he her no
reason a healing uh what do you call a
long long like a healing train no a
healing
centipede
cede sorry I should have laugh seeing
you
die no no I'm not dying I have two
beautiful healers in the centipede who's
if you were in the human centipede which
one do you want to be like which
position I guess the
front yeah the side yeah I don't
remember eating your [\h__\h]
I I I did watch that movie and I
remember there was a Japanese guy and he
speaks in like well naturally Japanese
and I was so proud of myself if I could
understand bits of it but those those
jellies when we kill all of those
Charles you get Charles we only need
Charles to be honest
okay well girls I need to announce found
something what's up yeah I started
watching Breaking Bad oh is my God
finally finally have you guys watched it
of course not I don't know media of
course not of course not what yeah I
only I stay in my own little bubble
under a
rock wait gy have you watched it I've
watched it I've also watched song
what
sa oh Saul I thought you meant
saw play game no that's Lal s is um like
wait I saw part of the universe it's
part of the universe what what universe
is what who the Breaking Bad
Universe it is okay I I'm really not far
so maybe even asking that question would
be a spoiler
it not really related it's about another
character ah he doesn't show up until
season 2 okay I'm like four episodes in
into season one or so and I'm just like
wondering how how are they going to
continue the story for Five Seasons like
they all
die I don't really know I me just making
earlier like what I can't really see the
future it's
concerning I'm excited
I hope you're enjoying it I I really
enjoyed it the first few episodes not
the first the only the first episode
actually I was like oh this is actually
I thought this would be more dramatic
but right now it's more
funny great but yeah after that it
immediately became really dist
disturbingly concerning and
worrying yeah I like Breaking Bad but I
think I prefer Better Call Saul over
Breaking Bad and then Breaking Bad was
just like I had to watch it in order to
watch Saul which was really really
good but I I I'm not saying that by the
way in a in a negative sense that it's
not funny or so it is still funny while
being depressing and that it's fine it's
good I'm not saying it's bad I just was
surprised it was as as depressing all I
know about breaking bad is this about
like drugs probably and and people be
dying
what's the sa version who's Saul you no
idea who's Saul not yet Saul is let I
mean it it has the same Vibes he's a
side character it's like lawyer stuff
instead of drug stuff oh so he does
things
legally so yeah some law drama I see I
see okay shall we go back to the
wetlands now that we did then I think go
back to the wetlands okay okay to
Wetlands Yi I will be there soon do not
teleport
me what you don't want to be teleported
not
yet stop running so fast her own legs or
with her own
Mount her own bunny rabbit yeah it's so
cute I like breaking bed now I have two
addictions Arcane and breaking bed my
[Music]
enemy I can't get that out of my brain
once it's in there why why why did you
have to sing it sorry I want think about
it I sang it
like 30 times in my last Diablo
stream is brainwashed I wake up to the
sound Sil Liv my turn
[Music]
around yeah now that we can perhaps do
English song covers but only by putting
them on Spotify or whatever we should
sing that song My
[Music]
Enemy yeah let's do it let's let's pay
for the expensive
license song
cover no just kidding dad just
kidding what the possibility and then
she surprise you guys with that cover
for eag of edes yeah we're like just
kidding and then a month later we were
just
kidding we never
kid what the heck is demon light cream
where do I get this cream yeah who up
demon light
creaming is that a quest item does it
say quest for the Lost
Palace level
[Music]
32 how are you enjoying enjoin how how
are you enjoying our
cane um so I am currently holding back
to watch all the first couple of
episodes from the second season I want
to save it a little bit cuz I don't want
to end it too
soon but it's so good
really
really gay
and it's beautiful it's a beautiful
maybe I have to kill things for it it is
beautiful I how who do I kill turtles
turtles am I killing
Turtles oh sorry you're not a turtle
you're a
bear sorry you look like an animal so I
immediately
assuming there's no story there it's
like the green envelope in the inventory
don't listen can you tell me which
specific role and
col you can find Le of Legends they put
more story into their game yeah you you
press Fusion for it I
believe okay but I think I need to
combine the two items don't
I it was green now this
one oh this one even like us oh Jesus
Christ where do I get this from
where the F do I get this Wetland
Spirits who's who's a spirit here USD
monst
monster in this
economy who's
W leave there yet no please game is
Frey Oh you mean League of Legends yeah
oh League of Legends is
free I saw you have invited people into
your
chaos everyone you don't want to play it
huh I don't want to play it no what
what's your reason do you not like I got
time for other stuff I don't have time
for Le of
Legends no no I don't know like I I
I it's okay if you play it I won't judge
you you know I mean I'm judging you
but I just kind of want to see like like
I want to play the characters that I saw
in the show just experience it
once cuz like I need to make that
connection oh the attachment you know
they're making like a farming game in
League of Legends or something what
farming the yal one it's some it's some
relaxing cozy League of Legends
game I to make demon light is it not out
yet I I don't think it's out yet I need
Darkness essence now who's emo in here
besides me yeah who
emo go pet
attack how do I
get enough demon Essence I can't
tell I mean Darkness Essence where yeah
I need that too you got to kill Wetland
holding us on our hands anymore what the
spirits yeah they're green little guys
they look like saplings
essentially I'm killing
them
where if you press M and like scroll
down through monsters or just check
where I am at yeah I'm coming over it's
not dropping they drop the other items
too they Dro both of them but I have not
gotten a lot of Darkness Essence yeah I
haven't gotten a single Darkness Essence
these Wetland Spirits sck I got to make
them cry
more Spirit oh I'm already
there I my something
[Music]
Tak please give me my darkness Essence I
just want to be Emo
the Ence of
dark eggy did you watch all the episodes
already for I seen
them I think I got spoiled a little bit
on Twitter No but it's kind of a thing
that I expected anyway to happen so yeah
but people should stop not everyone's
watching all the episodes
[Music]
yeah well it's fine the next set isn't
even out yet I think people should lay
off on the spoilers until the next set
of episodes are
out be courteous please get off the M or
St a few more steps away from me your
big ass feathers are constantly in my
screen and makes me
jealous I want those
feathers you could just PL it off of
them
[Music]
H good idea oh I got two five Darkness
Essence I feel like I'm partially
picking it up oh y I got a
cute
[Music]
crafting oh more dark assessence I don't
need
yeah I don't want it anymore and we can
just throw him out of the that's
true why is this dude like
clear okay I'm talking to
rocks what are they saying to you I
don't know I skipped through their
dialogue did not archive ski a
skipa okay
Quest finish next
Ah that's why you're talking to rocks
you're talking to monuments yeah talking
to the Pebbles what's up
Pebble was a big Pebble that's a pebble
when it grows up
yeah let's see oh
wow wow it's got so much to say I know I
didn't read it
okay cool St oh I see I start I clicked
on another Quest where am I headed o I
should not be going wrong Quest running
back stay on the right path giggy don't
get distracted lost I'm lost it's the
Zoomer
mind too easily
distracted my fingers are so weak my I'm
so excited for this
dungeon oh why yeah you'll see it you'll
see
it my hands
hurt why I've done so much gardening
today oh efficient are you growing like
vegetables or something no no no I just
I mowed my lawn and did the the edges I
trimmed the edges of my lawn but the
edges I did with like some
shears but it was so
exhausting and my hands are in pain a
cuz I I kind of didn't trim the edges so
far cuz I didn't have the the right
equipment for it and so it was it was
quite a quite a lot to
do I wonder the garden I wonder if you
can just replace your lawn with fake
grass
so you never have to deal with
it I can't do that it's got to be real
grass I would replace it with my little
golf
course I'm thinking next year I'll just
uh hire a gardener for the
really annoying
stuff but it's a good workout I
definitely only burned a lot of calories
today CH Cho what's in your
garden not that much yet because I only
have this Garden since this
year but I had some strawberries but
like really a small
amount uh and I
had I planted tomatoes and uh bell
peppers but then I had none of it
because because when it was actually
growing I was in Japan and then I I
couldn't have any of it
no yeah and and then I don't know a lot
of my plants also died because there was
suddenly a huge rain uh attack from the
sky uhhuh and they trying to keep your
garden down yeah they're they are garden
keeping me they're Garden
cake yeah but also I've been growing
some herbs I want to grow more herbs cuz
it's nice to have like fresh ble and
fresh parsley and stuff like that
whenever you need it so I need more of
that I think next year I'm really going
to focus on getting a sick Garden
together but I think I'm actually going
to hire professionals to like style Gard
give you rose
bushes rose bushes why rose bushes
evolving it'll be like the the Alice and
Wonderland Rose
Garden yeah I do want some flower bushes
but I was thinking if I'm going to plant
any bushes then I might as well plant
like bushes that carry fruit oh that
makes
sense you're living the the harvest Mo
life
[Music]
bushing
oo
yeah but I always be careful with what I
planned because I'm always checking if
it's like cat safe even even if they
don't try to like nibble anything I
still want to be
careful make sure everything's cat
safe got to protect the kitties roses
have fruits rose hips rose hips I only
know rose hip tea wait you rose
hips oh wait those are those really Ed
what's that in
German I had a I
saw oh never thought about eating those
like in uh in their not tea form I'd be
scared to eat anything like raw that I
grow what even if it's just like veggies
and fruit a little I mean like my
parents grew stuff but I fear like
something came inside it like a
bug n i what's wrong with eating a
bug if you grow things yourself that's
like maybe the least concerned you got
to be about your food rather than like
when you get it from the supermarket or
so you know they must have sprayed it
with a lot of pesticides and [\h__\h] so if
you grow it yourself you can be I think
less worried about that stuff true but I
could just buy it from the
store it's so expensive and even I was
just so mad every time I buy like
strawberries or so it's just
always they die after one day in my
fridge even and most of them are really
bad quality anyway I got my
modified genetically modified strawberry
stay last a bit
what am I supposed to do with this I'm
clicking on it I don't know what to do
oh wait what do you on the magic key
there's like a stone so you got to you
got to press on that item and then there
should be like a fusion thing click on
that item again and like drag it okay I
was clicking on the on the Rune nothing
happens when I click on the Rune but
yeah it's confusing when I don't want to
pay attention
honestly and the for meame ancient piece
where you get the indented ancient piece
I think you should have gotten in it by
default I
didn't just just keep pressing randomly
but you got to make the item oo why
can't they just give me
stuff okay maybe how do I track me what
I
need no I do not want to track
you don't track all on track I got
it okay okay
okay Yi I'm not yet oh shoot I lost all
my
tracking where do you get the indented
pce uh when you click on collect magic
key it will leave you lead you to the uh
NPC it's like an NPC with
a green exclamation mark above them and
then if you choose the talking option he
gives you shi the thank you sir you
welcome beautiful antique collector Bass
and
kiaha immediately sharing my newly
acquired
knowledge not gatekeeping my knowled no
Garden keeping here
[Music]
mhm okay I found a SLO in my garden by
the way I almost cut it with my Shear
did you know that they like
beer you should like leave a bunch of
beer around like open you know for them
to access yeah yeah there's this video I
saw where someone left a a container of
beer and one slug showed up and then
more slugs showed up and then before you
know it the entire container was full of
slugs e i it and I don't want I don't
like beer with slugs either like that's
just I want I want my drunk slugs
they're
funny really do they behave differently
yeah they party
[Music]
harder I have the
quest the quest Quest for the dungeon oh
oh we have to talk to this thing
okay all right yeah I'm ready too for
the dungeon oh give me give me a bit
it's taking me across the map for
another stupid
daily it's a five player dungeon does
that mean we need two more people you
can still do it solos I think it's fine
yeah it even says choose single player
dungeon still yeah saying go solo we got
to kill double
door double door yeah oh absolutely no
references intended right yeah we only
believe in single doors here
S no I left the slug alone no slugs have
been harmed in in my gardening session
oh but you know if you have one slug you
have tons of slugs I think no no no I
really only saw one slug oh no that's
because they're underneath the the
surface of the dirt they're buried
underneath every time you step under
grass they like M kiaha
feet kiaha feet I'm can't wait for
October Fest when all the beer comes
here all right I have harmed slugs
before did you pour Sal on them or
anything no no wait was it really me or
was it my mom slugs have been in my
presence thrown into a
fireplace but I think it was my mom what
I did on video okay there's video
evidence of me doing it too but because
my mom did it first oh you you learned
her from her huh from her
mistakes I mean to be fair they do look
pretty gross I would just like get the
they're so gross and they were like I
swear everywhere I was camping in my
mom's
Garden because I was making
a surviving in the wilderness
video yeah cuz her Garden is like the
Wilderness and on my camping area I was
like you know making everything nice I
had a fire I was making uh a chicken
soup
legitimately and uh yeah then there were
so many slugs and it was disgusting so
had to get rid of some there there were
I swear there were like in such a small
area there were like 50 of them that was
probably their home base and you invaded
their
home no no no no no that is my mom's
home base and they invaded my mom's home
but but I think your mother could have
been the
Invader this is this is their land
before you guys showed up there's plenty
of slugs in this
world it's fine wow
they didn't pay rent yeah they're not
paying rent well to be fair I don't
think you had any documents to make them
pay
rent they ain't got nothing yeah did you
give them the paperwork maybe they would
have paid rent if you gave them the
chance you know maybe maybe they maybe I
did them a favor maybe like them being a
slug is their bad Incarnation after
having a a Bad Karma Al wow I wonder
what you
no I didn't have a favor they're
reincarnating as a human again now to to
live an interesting and and then they
remember their slug memory like that's
the woman whose mother threw me into the
fire they're like I remember when I was
just
like if only I could go back would you
still love me if I was a war for real
for that actually is a legitimate
question
then the slug person incarnated slug
person 30 years into their life finally
settling down getting married and then
getting a midlife crisis wondering if
their partner would really love them
even if they were a slug so they asked
the question and open up about their
previous life I think I think I would
like not love someone if they were a
slug because they can't talk anymore I
think what I would do is they would be
my specimen and I would take multiple
pictures of them and just post it on
social media you would use kind CL is it
really clout though but then it makes me
wonder am I technically taking like nude
photography of them
y they like would they feel
ashamed if they didn't like being naked
they would become a snail and put a
house on their body also that would lead
me to if they didn't like being homeless
then they would be a snail putting a
house on their body so I think they they
don't own the property that my mom lives
in I
can anyway enough reasoning it could be
like title where it's like I was a
garden slug but a phoenix evicted me
from my home and now I'm a
human death is by fire when a phoenix is
at
your in front of you threatening you of
course it's going to be by fire oh you
in a
fighting I'm in the dungeon
okay I saw people fighting something
outside a solo right just King things
I'm ready how do we enter all I have is
this rock oh you still have to finish
making the
rock oh no no no I see it it just says
enter and then five player and I'm like
why okay I'm inside you do have the
quest that says defeat double door yeah
okay good double
door I'm still a bar
to be barred until 35 maybe I think that
was what I needed to be I shall heal and
then I would like to try my other
glasses ice
Shield o Burning metal oh crap where
where did you go oh you're still right
here
oopsies
oh got a little bit distracted
honestly you should just be like a a
tank Mage or a battle mage
GG I'm going I'm going no you should in
any case you should choose a class that
can tank AOE be like fight with
a GG I need to heal you stop running
away from the Healer don't worry don't
worry I'm so strong
killing destroying you think they're I
know to be fair you're
squishy what the they still they're
still so
tanky they are
mushrooms okay I want to change into
like a different class why were you
excited for this dungeon Chi oh that's
because it took uh I inspiration from
the name of it or something
oh like Oh I like that word that's a
fancy
word malice Palace yeah ah sh I have to
think of you in my M
stream uh on Sunday because I was
watching Once Again Bak um this time we
were watching the
secondar season we're like pretty close
to the end finally yeah but the was it
the opening or the ending song
end song it was called
shii oh shii yeah it was a pretty good
song and about I think um I don't know
something nice
shiori about one shiori
Nolla yeah it it was an O to me do you
know clar c l a r i
s yeah they made that song oh that one I
see but yeah they make many pretty songs
so Shi is also a pretty song just like
you thank you now we have to wait for a
song called
Kiara I would make that
myself make it into my own
hands but you should cover The Shield
song guess we'll have to see if I can
sing it when I'm not dying sound pretty
in your
voice when I'm not dying oh God there's
a frog coming towards
me he's confused she's
confused he come
back I'm not using my sta why' you
hesitate kinky it' be funny if you were
using like an ax all this
time I was using my
guitar
uh is that that I don't know I don't
know the that difference I hope I do
more damage now oh wait you're a mage as
a mage I too want to be a mage heal your
S I will wait uh I can be the
healer okay a while if you want well I
had to level up myself stuff I'll do it
off screen I guess at this point I am
just considering uh preparing a tank
[Laughter]
class it's good to have all kinds of
things when
we we can be everything
die transformed
mushro you will regret living here he's
living his he should have been born a
slug yeah he should have been born a
slug so he can get evicted instead of
killed you didn't kill them right Smiles
at
you oh by the way I finished the the
homicide for game GG did you like it I
did but I had no idea what they were
saying most of the time so homicide for
a game I I probably I don't know but
homicide vers a game where just like
creepy looking uh Creepy Pasta men and
they speak in a language that you can't
understand and you have to decipher what
they're trying to say
context what is this I had no idea what
the heck they said but they were kind of
cute you should start from the beginning
now that you have your dictionary filled
out and then fix your words if any of
them are out of context a lot of them
are out of
context it's like at one point they
would make sense for one situation but
the next uh situation is like it made no
sense I don't know what it
[Laughter]
is I like the this dude named Mr
hood and then uh the
GRE yeah but I didn't get on this r
out I didn't even know you can get on
his route I don't think you can you can
it's just uh like one choice that you
can easily Miss oh boo I want more
information on him he's healing what
the oh maybe he heals when you attack
him there's some characters who do that
so we actually have to think
now die now don't
worry yeah I remember one of the words
is like when you get the tool and then
you don't know it's tool so you have
like I don't know crowbar or
ladder sense anywhere else or like
instrument it's like okay instruments of
torture what the hell costly out of Mana
now this is sucking up my Mana oh hold
up I need to a buff you guys again okay
where are you I need to buff
you oh you're good okay you're good now
oh cleric
Buffs I got B
bus oh my God it's double
door oh
my they really made him a wizard it's
double door oh I think there's something
attacking me
attack it back fight back I'm healing
you guys
though double door you will die oh wait
I think if you lead him out he'll
actually like reset his health are you
trying to stop my
research
yes you just wanted to know about anime
girls
nice what I wasn't even paying attention
so hey I'm going to talk to
B okay me
too good job nice dungeon
yeah on to more good work everyone good
work indeed we are such successful
experien Warriors making good progress
mhm
where is
best oh back in the main
place I'm
hungry you can eat like the mushrooms in
this area I hate
mushrooms I wish I like them cuz they're
like growing in my garden against my
will what is it about I like it when I
musroom T both
both like musroom
sauce oh the size like cream of mushroom
I don't like the texture either
yeah I wish I like them would make life
easier o they got some
nice I like seeing mushrooms grow in
someone's lawn like it's not meant to be
there naturally but I just staring at it
yeah if you like seeing that you should
come visit me
oh and then I can bring beer and get all
your slugs no I want to see your cat I'm
coming over to see your quote unquote
cat no no for real everybody's welcome
though come over you coward you want to
see my cat welome see my cat I'll let
Chi go there first and then she can
teleport me to your
area what am I going to link my soul
to I guess her bed and this quest one
want to become level
33 yeah some other
quests thisy Quest doing my
dieses I I'll buy a book to get
a got to talk to
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] jongo
free there we go more mushrooms will be
killed by my
hands we'll teach them a lesson grab all
these daily Quest I guess I wanted to
ask you girls a
question following question um this is
the context uh yesterday uh I announced
a a cool
collaboration with a company saw yeah
they're going to do some cool stuff you
know and I was wondering yeah uh if you
girls were to have a collaboration with
a company for example like hi to they
make like the PC cases or V to make like
knives and ramen and stuff or anything
really what what would be something you
want to put your name on if you could
make it if not just these companies that
I name just anything in your mind what
would you want to
make like uh what type of sponsorship I
would want yeah essentially I I would
want Lita
close that's cute
yeah I think that's in the realm of
possibility or like accessories would
you want to design them no I don't need
to design them I would just like make a
video on them it's like give me your
clothes I'll make a
video Yeah would be nice if they would
actually like I don't know give the
outfit to you as as a life Tod outfit or
so had something like that before she
got a a one piece related outfit so cute
yeah that'll be nice very cute very
demure so mindful I don't know about you
shoes because shoe box oh shoes would be
cool but I don't know the question is so
broad it is but you got oh what about
like boxing clothes for G cuz you're a
Fister CL oh yeah or like any cloes
who's looking to face
yeah I do think it's it's good to like
work towards something and also
establish your own brand as a senpai I
want to tell you like for me with kfp
I've been like constantly like working
on this like image of having a fast food
chain and cooking Etc so I think if you
continue working towards something um
building up an image then eventually you
game got dream sponsor hey I got the
game got cookie the cookie people
responding to you why
not they love
sponsorships actually for me I think i'
I'd be stuck in Tech cuz I already have
like a bunch of tech videos
technically yeah I'm sure you could like
get something
maybe maybe like
a sponsorship for some motion capture
also or that that one's a little
different yeah I
guess some I guess then you could get
the PC PC sponsorship oh I already
already got one oh hell yeah yeah even
better why can I I would like keyboard
caps that' be neat or keyboard nice
keyboard Go Get It Go Get It get those G
key caps
what about a gem
keyboard
yes I would love the colors if it would
be funny General colors I love that it'd
be funny if your keyboard caps were like
the letters were flipped or written
poorly or like it just like not even the
actual
letters it just be so evil I know your
Doodles it's like what am I supposed to
do with
this yeah I can't read this keyboard
people would just put them in the right
you know the right
spot I did the book quests but it's
still not level 33 this will take a
while yeah it is taking me a while too I
do all these
dailies I buy
another you should just sell shoe
boxes sell shoe boxes yeah without the
shoes just the shoe
boxes when I start reselling used shoe
boxes from random
[Music]
[Laughter]
Brands they're totally you'll make them
special people will want the shoe boxes
because they're who wants a shoe box
that was put slug in there yeah you can
get a slug
back the Slugs we're giving them
homes a they can have homes what do you
call that re re um when recycle no no no
when you when you give people homes re
rehoming not
re the
word not
sure re rehabilitating slugs yes oh oh
you make them sound like drug addicts
though
maybe they are breaking bad yeah
Breaking Bad slug
Edition next
Quest okay Wetland Wonder Wetland
Exile got to manually turn the page why
can't you do it for me Quest
yeah rude
have you ever seen videos of snails
eating oh aren't they just like kind of
slugging around over the doesn't really
like they're eating they're like they
use their little moue and they're like
Yum Yum Yum Yum they're so cute I don't
know I see videos of snails and I it
makes me wish I had a snail a you know I
jumped I owned a rat the other day and
it was such a vivid dream
actually a what was your rat's name it
didn't have a name but I kept trying to
keep it away from my cats in my
dream I've always wanted a rat I just
don't like that their lifespans are so
small and it yeah I think they only live
like 2ish years and
they're small animals don't have big
lifespan sadly unless you're like a a
dog or a cat I
think yeah yeah but if you want a snail
you could make you could easily get a
snail just pick it up outside and make
it a little
terrarium wouldn't that be cute but what
if they're leaving their families like
they were just coming home from work and
they have a loving wife yeah where is
your family I'll find it for you is it
inhumane to get a pet snail by picking
up a snail outside and forcing to your
home I think the oils on your skin would
hurt them too or maybe it's a different
thing like you have to handle it certain
or so and then put them in the terrarium
and then never use those Chopsticks
again why why not I guess you could
clean
it whatever what's the correct way of
getting a pet snail would you have to
buy it from a breeder a breeder now go
to
go to a French restaurant sa I think it'
be just kidding I think probably most of
them wa do they esar go do they all go
on the menu can you like make any snail
your pet or is there like a I mean it's
not like say
no why do you limit yourself so much
don't let your dreams be dreams I just
need to know what the humane way of
owning is cuz you don't want to get
cancelled by the snail Society right
yeah
exactly here I I'll I'll prepare a snail
for
you I'll catch one in my wait wait how
long did they even last for like
lifespan wise the expiration date yeah
probably way less than the rat how long
snail lives cuz I was thinking like
you're holding it for G and then she
takes like a few years to show up two or
three years but 10 of it's large large
larger species nail W how big is a large
snail have you seen the snail that like
they can hold in their arms large snail
hold
arm here we go should not think so is
that photoshoop though do you like
snails if I send this will you be disted
by the snail s send it send it send
it oh is that real I've seen that
picture
before think it's real oh this so he's
kind of like a bunny it's kind of cute
yeah they're cute let me Slim find it
the video that I was watching where
they're eating I'm like like oh my God
they're so
cute it's kind of a cute little snail
but I wonder how their minds are it's
not like they know you're the owner
right they just think of you as like o
the one who feeds me but that's it but
they're cute to look at why does the why
does the face give me like spider Vibes
though
just the face you think you can dress up
a
snail maybe you P the shell honestly I
feel like that true give it like make it
more attractive to Predators
right as long as we're protecting
it brightly colored equals toxic no one
would want to eat it oh yeah yeah yeah
we are making their lives even longer by
protecting
it
snail with that huge snail oh my God you
it that's so much meat why are you
thinking about cooking I am a chef I
have a cooking sponsorship I have to
think of
cooking no but e can't e I'm going I do
wonder what it tastes like what is the
texture of a really really large snail
e it's probably chewy
[Music]
oh no this guy
has thank you somebody I feel like you
should eat those big snails they're not
they don't oh but they're so big I would
feel bad for killing that right in front
of
my they look like they they would be
pretty rare too can you even encounter
them in the wilderness that would be
crazy imagine seeing such a huge snail
irow randomly in a in a garden
I would
faint please leave me alone don't attack
me snail have
mercy I trying to find it but I found
this instead that's
cute I need to find idy where is this
person what were you looking for I'm
trying to find the snails eating I don't
know where where the Tweet is a drawn
icon vector image of a cat
snail yeah
cute it would take like six hours for it
to reach you I guess I'm not in danger
then when I encounter one if it takes so
long to reach me but who knows maybe the
big ones are faster than the small
ones they're definitely F they got to be
faster they yeah they cover more ground
exactly terrifying f
that size snail is perhaps like the
accurate size if you want to have a like
a like a kind of relationship to S like
B Oh you mean Gary I found it yeah found
what they're eating look they're so
silly check in a
bit music okay I'm hearing it okay yeah
it's kind of cute
cute they're just eating is that sped up
that's really sped up right I think it's
sped up I don't think
that they're really cute when they're
eating they look so happy I know before
people like Kiara wants to eat
them no don't worry I I I I don't even
like mushrooms how am I going to eat
snails oh Choo Cho it's kind of similar
probably in
texture more disgusting I'll stay with
uh I like eating
snails you like eating s yeah yeah when
I go to a French yeah yeah I have you
had it before yeah I made it really tiny
it's kind of like um the texture of what
like lams or tiny
little are
called oh yeah they're like seafood
nails
yum oh muscles
yeah well with a lot of garlic anything
can taste good
huh and butter so much butter garlic
butter I do have that compound butter in
my fridge what if I combine it with the
slug in my garden what's for dinner
tonight kiaha I think I'll make
cabonara ooh but like legitimate
carbonara what's not legitimate car when
you when you like add um like cream to
it you got to make it just with the um
the golden part of the eggs and the lots
of cheese peino and uh
paragano yeah so I'm going to make it
Del legitimate way cuz it actually
turned out pretty good last time I made
it and this time I have the better
cheese
oh yeah the bacon bacon is important I
don't have the bacon that
they ask you to use normally but good
enough
bacon will you be posting
pictures maybe recently I haven't been
posting pictures because yeah I like
your food photos yeah it makes you look
at my food and how I don't do
[\h__\h] yeah hungry
I've I've been taking a little break
from my like food subscription that
sends me the
ingredients those who shall not be named
but but yeah now that I'm just cooking
things more on my own I'm not trying to
make them look too nice because they
usually just look nice when you have
lots of side
dishes then you can plate them up nicely
M but when I just cook
something like without the food
subscription I just make something
simple like the carbonara and then it
doesn't look very
special so yeah let's pictures from the
wa
recently I think it's still special food
photos are
beautiful well I am doing a cooking
stream again soon finally for the first
time in a long
time yeah
kitchen whenever the things from my
sponsorship arrive ooh nice nice I'm
excited I love cooking streams
m i I don't know they make me nervous
but I I want to do enough of them that
I'm not nervous anymore while doing them
I will always be nervous for cooking
streams took me 3 hours to make a stupid
hamburger yeah I'm I think I'm nervous
about the logistics of streaming it yeah
yeah exactly that's probably the part
that makes me most nervous cuz hey
there's this like level 90 dude in aen
wearing a pumpkin
head is
evil he's a heroic boss he will kill me
uhoh don't
solo careful oh yeah I remember smacking
him and then running away on accident
don't penis you're like level 71 you you
can take
him you'll get one
shot I see but that makes it
tempting oh where's the auction I want
to see cute
stuff cute clothes please oh wait I'm
already FR free what the heck I didn't
no this I kept I keping for so long you
are grinding I have so oh mindlessly
grinding all right I'll finish this
little Quest though guys guys who are
around me can you just kill the the
enemies that spawn I'm just going to
kill the
stones cuz that's all I got to do thank
you next
Stone where more Stones oh
here oh so
cute oh you can fight with a
kebab there not a lot of items in the
auction though I don't think the player
base is like too much probably yeah
yeah
it's not
huge okay
H right this what was the quest that you
got to do when you're 33 where you go
for the money they will not be able to
buy as if
I you go I'm sorry forgive me
where is the main
qu what did you guys do once you reached
level 33 I didn't even realize I was
level 33 until you said
so I just followed the quest I have I
have B things for give me people oh
thank you thank you
Auntie look this stream is not sponsored
no no Eden ET Turnal we're we're looking
at you
Eden
my these are all oh but I only have one
at a time oh you're killing me you are
killing
me where's
[Music]
I hear this little
kitty your
baby oh wow good twirl you so good nice
trick where where's the kitty at and
leave my kitty
alone where's the back our Guild leader
hey don't drive away let me look at you
Flex nice motor
bike m here's the
backpack level
90 our Guild leader
how
this maybe I'll go back to
the or I'll try entering the next region
maybe a
Lelo like any more but how what about
the bank you need a bank least to unlock
the slot oh my God the banks take
advantage of you in this game too A Bank
lease yeah to expand your uh your bank
stuff in the
game wow oh I got the main quest guess
I'll just keep expanding my
bags I I appreciate thank
you I got the main quest deep into I got
to go to Soul Guardian me too me too
he's not bringing
me need a
Wetlands I thought so too but it led me
out of the wetlands oh this is this a
new area actually yeah I think so oh new
area
yippe the valley of
king that's like The Lion King
ah found
portal talk to Derek Derek do this is
not the light this is a
forest
okay are we back to questing girls yeah
I got to talk to
[Music]
Derek Derek probably killed my my
family no he didn't dere is
Chill DK just trying to raise a
family of his own there are so
many daily quests in this area yeah
ignore them ignore I picked all of them
up no this do the
make when will you get to do these
dailies I don't know they're just so
tempting the way that they're right here
in front of
me you need to clean clean it up get rid
of it all right maybe that's the feeling
that I had yesterday when I was cleaning
everything I even used my Roomba again
your room Roomba I do I don't I do not
use it I still end up man Ving you
should use it I need to use it more
often my cats get upset you with it
really yeah mine surprising why you
don't care like one of my cats she hates
when I turn on the vacuum she freaks out
and runs away into a corner but the
Roomba she doesn't mind cuz it's like
not as
loud the Roomba will make me
trip make you trip yeah cuz I ped her
around and then the roomba's there my
Roomba it had a name I changed it
because I had to reset it up now it's
just W bot
oh I hope CeCe has a Roomba and it's
called the WBA
the wom the w w I see I saw those tweets
I know what you're talking about oh
giggy can't have one she'll just ride it
like those cat mes says
herbs is that true
giggy no that's not
true you can't be trusted with a
[Music]
friend you can't be friends with a
room why not she's friends with Cece
no no they're great friends yeah CeCe is
just like a
[Music]
Roomba why is she turning around you the
whole time like a cleaning robot yeah
just just like
a is she constantly bonking against the
wall yeah exactly what she looks like is
she having trouble getting over the
carpet the Fig
carpet must be rough man she gets stuck
constantly on on edges and stuff and you
always have to reorient
her she I guess you will stick 100
goggly eyes googly eyes on it only two
because it has a
face I should put I I haven't put any
eyes on my Roomba yet I should yeah I
like it when they have costumes but I
don't have one for
mine cost
yeah you can get them a m
outfit I know that we talked last time
we talked about outfits for pets but if
there's room outfits I think I'm in yeah
I'm pretty sure there are might be like
an
though the that's
crazy maybe that's for people who aren't
allowed to have pets in their uh
Apartments cuz there's I want like a an
ant Android someday like an Android
Butler instead of a pet I already have a
pet though they don't they don't Butler
for me all they do is [\h__\h] on my
floor yeah
let's they actually [\h__\h] on your floor
one of them when they're upset and
they'll get enough attention they might
[\h__\h] on my floor oh my God that's also
the cat that tries to be like dominate a
dominant between the two I the one who
sucking the other cat yeah yeah actually
it was he was the
[Laughter]
sucker that he would like uh climb on
top of my smaller cat and bite him and
all that stuff to assert dominance a
he's a nasty
cat seems pretty
nasty yeah his name is pepper why why
did pepper why did pepp pepper [\h__\h]
everywhere
why did pepper become so
spicy I don't know he's just a big
cat how old is pepper I think it broke
like two years now oh so young I would
excuse the [\h__\h] if he was
old no he's he's just a young
Brad damn he needs Brad
correction what are you guys talking
about in The Guild
chat don't f
ink
well are my ink Wells getting bullied
kfp are you bullying my
Inkwell not sure what's going on hey ink
balls are good people what's going on
thanks for killing the mobs that I have
to kill no problem I still got to kill
one more Scout though yes yes you have
to please oh thank you GG for
potentially killing them I got it I got
it
we're working together see we could be
questing so much faster if we were
actually always on the same Quest and
not delayed by one
minute daily Quest daily
Quest I come join the guild but already
play M noi M noi is still going on oh
man yeah they're getting an update too
oh it's pretty amazing I heard it was
really good I couldn't get into it
though software update when it first
hard I I made a character but I don't
know why what happened I was I get still
too busy with my other mm
RPG but it was pretty cute I heard that
you can just cook in there you don't
have to fight and you can play music on
there yeah you can start of like a
[Music]
band wait is this a I miss Maple Story
2 oh I played that actually
so good I want Maple Story 2 bad wait so
Maple Story 1 exists but Maple Story 2
is dead only for like the
West yeah it's dead for the West because
we didn't pay it enough they couldn't
yeah like it's because the end game to
the greatness of the first one no it was
really good but I think it's just like
the grind once you get to end game and
then they weren't um go back to it
wasn't really healthy and then the
player base just died
a was so fun why didn't you save it why
didn't you do anything yeah why didn't
you spend so many years ago you killed
it you killed maple story I I bought the
$100 Founders pack was that not enough
no no you should have bought the $1,000
father's pack I don't have 1,000 have
,000 wait where's Garf he's not spawning
I I see him he just has kill
him nice actually questing together
can't believe
it he's dead now don't worry about him
oh good
point yeah I play like story too me was
it 3D yeah 3D yeah it was 3D it's like a
little isometric I think it was so cute
let me look it up maybe I saw the
visuals before Maple start too it it is
cute I like it
one a I wonder what class you could have
done I think you could get two classes
veins if that still existed I wouldn't
mind playing it
now it was so good it had so many
Community things and you could full edit
your home the only thing is that there's
like a lot of copyright stuff that
people just upload onto the game oh
okay why do they do
that no one stopped them it's the
internet of course we have to collect
worm skin we're skinning the worms no
not the
worms it's okay I guess you didn't love
the worms enough we don't love them
enough yet I would love you guys if you
were worms I would keep you in the glass
jar if you were worm oh so you'd love me
still of course in in a way in a sick
and twisted way would you use would you
take photos of me and post me on the
intern
you use my worm body for c yeah I'd be
like look at this dirty worm
so
no please I have no autonomy as a wor
well you could have crawled away but you
didn't when you had the
[Laughter]
chance is fast
enough is it any of you all worms let's
tryes look for worm skin I remember
no I did get a
skin
okay
warm give me
more are you also skinning the worms
girls yeah I collected them all you
finished already I I'm not getting the
drops okay now I'm
getting now that you have it all I'm
getting
them it do be like that sometimes huh it
do it do
be one
more oh did her
the oh he's probably an aen again herb
asks would you still love me if I did
the worm I would love you I would be
impressed so much if you did the worm I
would many many people who have
attempted the worm so
far you can like dance a a little can't
she cuz I saw her moves in VR chat for
herb ah yeah I Sonic was cute her stream
with the new model she was wiggling
bless small she wiggle
yeah she says she
Wiggles is that your signature move herb
the wiggle the
wiggle full body
wiggle who up wiggling day
worm I'm hungry
well there's worms
[Music]
here
worms I'll make um worms later worms in
the form of
Spaghetti
O my mama makes this dish that I call
worms I actually don't know what it is I
need her to teach it to
me I want a photo of it the next time
she makes it you call just cut up beef
anyway and like gravy but I always call
it worms cuz it's brown beef and gravy I
think so but like the Gravy Sauce tastes
a little different than just gravy what
the what makes it look like worms it's
all
brown and just cut up beef that's all
brown and a lot of brown
gravy like worms
enough
here sounds like a Michelin star
restaurant I need her to teach me the
recipe she's always like I'll teach you
next year I'll teach you next time you
visit it has they're keeping the family
recipe why is she
hiding she wants you to continue relying
on her for the warm yeah she wants to
keep visiting going teach you it yet
she's scared that if you know it all if
you have all the knowledge you'll run
away run off maybe you'll even sell a
book with
it imagine what the Betrayal you can
barely
[Laughter]
cook yeah ask yourself why can't you be
like cook why can't you cook because
she's not teaching you yeah it's her
fault she's not letting you into the
recipes of her family the gatekeeping is
real
mhm Gat keeping by your own mother let
her cook let her cook let let her cook
let her cook let her
cook it must be said out
loud you need to have
courage courage to cook courage to say
it or or may you were having a dream of
that rat because of Ratatouille and
cooking actually never watch R Tulie
really we NE you both have it yeah oh my
gosh you should maybe we should watch
childhood I think I've
actually besides watching Shrek with
call I don't think I've ever been in a
watch long with anybody else so far we
should watch would we be able to watch
rat Chey I don't know oh wait isn't that
Disney but we can still watch it as long
as we oh that's true we can watch it and
just like not do a watch along I guess
no no we can still do watch it uh is
it I don't know I don't know how it
works oh well all I know is that we're
supposed to avoid like uh
jibli and probably maybe Disney too
honestly Disney and
Jojo I just know we shouldn't sing no
songs but watching a movie without
showing the movie should be
fine I don't know JoJo G no clue times
have changed I see
yeah no JoJo why no JoJo uh I think I
think someone watched it and then they
had to like
stop
oh oh no well good that I'm not into
[Laughter]
Jojo I bring flow cute Must
Destroy no flowers here oh oh spawned
right away in the same
spot no
don't why why must you why would you
take her flower yeah right in front of
me right in front of me right in front
of her you would take her flower you are
an [\h__\h] go to the corner and think
about what you've done think about it
yes letting you guys follow me just for
you to instruct me
next
Quest what before before you guys get
confused so how things work is that if
some if someone didn't get in trouble
before prior it just means that they
were caught at that time how it works I
do this so it's like
completely situation dependent so that's
usually how copyright also works it's
like they're not montoring at all times
so someone who could do it later could
get in trouble and then someone did it
earlier like someone to get weing that
yeah that sort of
stuff oh will we get I actually don't
know what will happen will we get in 25
minutes an update an
email Emil will we get the email I made
them sign up for the sponsorship emails
oh o there's like a like a every day
there'll be like a reveal I think of one
of the things in the lineup I think I
think so the first one should be in 25
minutes I honestly don't know what
they're going to
reveal I'm excited too woohoo I'm
excited to
see I mean I've seen the the full lineup
I just don't know what they're showing
today but let me tell you there's some
exciting stuff coming
up I want to see I want to I want to
know what they're revealing have you
signed up you need to enter your email
gigy
promoting so I can see what they are
releasing yeah you should I'll send you
I'll show you where you can sign up
later thank you I expect you to actually
sign up I will I'm C I'm nosy I want to
see
it feet F okay oh my just went went and
made a noise
it went
[Music]
like gy are you close to
F I am not close to Fay theck I think
she already killed Fay for me I I killed
F so f is someone you summon with like
the item and then you kill it I did see
you just running past me Shi why how how
come you girls have already like have
why do we have delay
again I'll I'll wait on the next Quest
no no no it's fine it's
fine okay I'm
summoning okay this one we're about to
be like getting to the dungeon soon so I
wait in front all right that can be
our big thing to end it on maybe okay
I think I need to drink some apple cider
vinegar
after oh no it's supposed to be healthy
for you I don't know if it helps a sore
throat though it might just burn away
the bacteria and do you think you only
have a sore throat or something I I
currently only have a sore throat at the
moment it
hurts drink hot tea with honey oh I do
but it's not hot anymore it's just like
room temperature tea need a f cup F Fus
I
should and you should take froat candies
I always have froat candies right at my
desk because especially in the winter
time when I read super chats my throat
is constantly dying man we are abusing
our
throats
yeah can't be
helped it's our job
to eat a
loeng yes yes yes eat it's good for
you Lo can you like overdose on lenes or
like not death but like can you have too
much I think it probably does say on the
packaging uh do depend
alcohol whatever content maybe it
depends cuz there's some that you get
from the pharmacy right I feel like
those some of those might have like a
tiny bit of like pink in something in
there right I think I've seen that
before to
like get the swelling or whatever from
your throat gone I don't know yeah it
messes up your tummy but you won't die I
don't think you can overdose from throat
candies time to test that
out
girl oh my quest is already finished
without me lifting a finger nice
wow my full freaking
a this place is
beautiful talk to gray gray why did it
lead me there I clicked on
it apparently that's not where I had to
go lead us to
gray have you talked to gray already no
I'm them right now okay cool I just
can't find zepherus
that's like the end of the quest or
something I
think yes I need to set up my humidifier
again but I don't know if it really ever
helped
me but got to bring out all the big guns
for the winter time I already noticed
like I have so much legum in my throat
again especially when I just wake up I
notice there's like M it's
all all
yummy yeah I was thinking that yesterday
I'm like damn I should get a humidifier
near my PC and I'm cold again you should
I have like three humidifi so that I
have one in my bedroom and one in my
office along and air air purifiers as
well I have three of those but I
ooh I was I was forced by my chat three
and a half years ago to buy air
purifiers because they thought or one
particular person thought that it would
help me I got one how do I open my
pet no did it no I don't think so but
maybe it did but like
0.05% impact in my life that I wouldn't
notic but they look nice I mean when
when somebody visits I could say oh look
you will have the best air in my home
because I an air purifier in this corner
and in that corner and in this corner
yeah they do look
cool I have one tiny air
purifier or like a humidifier and it's
of chiawa and it comes out of his
brain there a hole on the top of his
head he lights up and all the the the
air comes out of it nice that's cute one
question uh I I think a follow-up Quest
did you girls get one I got one what's
it called
quest uh followup quest
after uh I'm on like rotten 3 Quest
right now which is like a main called
rotten
three ah rot and free main
party yeah a single player dungeon okay
it does say party though right me yeah
yeah yeah okay I guess so
I'm just killing random
worms don't worry don't do not worry you
have the quest uhoh do you have the
quest I do I do thank
you I'm just going to be a bar so I can
level it up okay let's go
Yi
into the dungeon
this dungeon looks like a I can't help
just the dungeon map it looks like a
worm oh my God it's a worm would you
still love this dungeon if it was a worm
I don't know I like this dunge only know
it as a worm it's a poison dungeon I
think
bugs are
cute in photos you're cute you're cuter
than any
bug oh oh that's good it would be really
worrying if she wasn't cuter than a
bug I've never seen a bug cuter than you
honestly there are pretty amazingly cute
bugs especially like um
fluffy um what are they called the
little fluffy worms I forgot the word
for what they talking about the fuzzy
ones fuzzy ones yeah the ones before
they become a butterfly or M
caterpillars fluffy caterpillars are so
cute I think beetles are really cute
too yes they can be depending on some
Beetle yeah depending on the beetle
there some some of them are really cute
yeah they can be a
pest as
well I have I like them in photos I will
not go near one in person but I like
looking at stay away stay
away is there oh it's going around in a
circle I'm like why is there a fork in
the
path ooh oops dungeon with choices but
it's false I know it's illusion
illusion giant are really good oh yeah
yeah I mean this B's after me please the
fact that they're Giants makes them a
bit terrifying though yeah I don't know
I don't really like flying bugs cuz they
scare
me I'm scared of butterflies I hate
flying
cockroaches oh God thankfully I never
had to deal with
them I used to like cockroaches I mean
at least I I didn't really like them but
I thought they were kind of like cute
not as like as long as you never
encountered them right yeah no no even
when I like saw them running around on
street bro I killed them I never I never
saw them in Austria honestly but like I
used to see them in summer in Japan and
I just thought well oh there's no need
no reason to need no reason to be so
extremely hysterically panicky about it
is what I thought but of course if you
have it suddenly in your home I would be
panicky too but outside is like whatever
outside it's not too bad but inside like
if you see them you got to kill
them they are piss mhm Genie I already
attacked Genie what you say for once it
was oh no wait was it after me someone
kill it
GG sorry sorry sorry wait you're
supposed to be
the my
brethren gen no Genie goodbye good night
gen
no okay I got
you Genie is dead where were you when
Genie where were you when Genie
die when Genie is
killed go next go
next que AB
I was outside the
dunge oh you I used to live in an
apartment and then it had cockroach
problems the month that I was live like
the first month I was there and it was
so terrifying and horrifying I woke up
to one crawling on me and it was the
worst day of my life
no okay I was like why is this happening
to me I just got here then what did you
do did you leave or I make so many
complaints um I just no longer slept in
that room and then I locked myself away
somewhere else until the problem was
fixed good good good for you I would
chased them around with the vacuum
cleaner though because I didn't know how
else to deal with them because I'm
scared of killing bugs because a why
they why are they jump at me I can't
handle it I don't know I'm scared I
don't I can't kill a bug they're scary
I'm useless splattering their bodies on
the
walls no the thought of bugs give me the
egg there's this one time where like uh
uh my parents' home was infected by a
bunch of fruit flies and I had to go on
a killing spree and I had like 30 fruit
fly bodies by the end of that day oh my
God I also have a [\h__\h] ton of dead F
Well actually now the problem is pretty
much Sol but the past weeks I had a big
F prot please I'm agoing this but I
bought an uh electric fly water which is
so good it's like a tennis racket and it
kills all the bugs it's so good oh it's
very helpful yeah they just fly into it
so
dumb and it makes zappy
sounds fun zappy sounds
zap yeah I like the sound it makes when
a fly runs into it yeah oh yeah the
sound of death
beautiful thanks for waiting for us in
front of the
dungeon moving
[Music]
on well you once had a cockroach problem
I when I lived in Japan in the beginning
of my whole lifetime I had a rat problem
oh my God it was so like traumatizing
but then it became kind of a part of my
identity while
I and then I was sad when I left that
house and moved back to Austria because
no there was some weird sentimental like
connection at the end of all of that
rats yeah it's weird it's a whole thing
is it cuz they like you see them
inside but no not I I don't think
they're cute or anything but like first
I was really terrified and I wasn't
feeling comfortable I didn't want to
sleep I kept on hearing the noises tpps
and everything but then basically I
think the reason why I became so
attached to it it was because at the
time it was in the middle of Corona and
I was just kind of like in a bad mental
state that was just kind of sad and
alone and isolated and all that and then
um it came to the point where I had to
leave
Austria but chat made a character out of
the rats in my house and we named it
Casper and they you know they just like
role played as it and they sent super
chats as that rat and I built this
connection to this Super Chat rat and
connected it to the real rats in my home
I thought this was like some Stockholm
story at first but I I didn't expect
this
twist no it for real became so wholesome
that was the only reason why I could
bear it and I could see it also as a
funny thing whenever I came across the
rat and and and then I felt bad for like
attempting to kill it cuz like I first
got like professionals to come in trying
to solve the problem but somehow it
survived every single W that's crazy
yeah like mutant rats or so um and then
I at some point I was like okay they're
not dying so I'm just going to give up I
feel bad they
they're probably already blind and
everything they're already suffering so
yeah may maybe to L A nice healthy life
after you were gone yeah I don't know
about that because after I was gone the
whole house was renovated so well they
probably just move somewhere else you
know what what they yeah hope I hope I
hope they found a different place that
made them happy yeah maybe they're
living at a mansion now they're like a
some sort of YouTube Creator moved away
yeah but I I I I don't know when I was
back in Austria those the Casp Casper
was the name of the Rat you know and it
just it just disappeared and it was like
man I miss Casper
now which is so weird because I should
be happy that the rats are
gone somehow I well I'm I'm sure Casper
lives on as the neighborhood the
yay no Casper probably dead by now let's
be real well the
Casper that long but I'm sure he died
happy yeah you know the reason why I
called it Casper in the first place was
because I first was like embarrassed to
even admit that I had rats because it it
made me so uncomfortable and it seems
kind of like the place is dirty or so
but it wasn't dirty because of me it had
already a rat infestation
when I moved in that's why I got it so
cheap but yeah so I was like pretending
that I had
ghosts whenever I heard a noise I was
like oh the ghost's in my ceiling and
eventually I said it out loud I think
like oh the rats and then it was like
okay the
rat yeah but we kept the Casper name cuz
Casper is a ghost name that's true
that's
true yeah it's not your fault it's
always the apartment's fault cuz they
should have dealt with that yeah but I
got it through uh like connections
really cheap so oh it it was kind of a
emergency solution cuz when I joined
Holo I was living in like a Japanese one
room apartment that has the finnest wall
ever super cheap and you can hear but
even when I was whispering like this the
neighbors were knocking on the wall when
I was speaking like this I swear to God
they should get over themselves
I was like how the [\h__\h] am I going to
stream here so I I I really needed a a
quick solution to this where I could
talk like a normal person so I got a
house I was really
lucky that is so stressful never hry
home with
friends yeah the friends are the rats
the friends that's the
rat the friend that is the rat yeah
would you ever just get a pet rat at
this point to to recall the days with
that rat I was like what if you got a
rat named Casper would that be cute that
was thinking if I um if only I brought
my cats with me to Japan for that one
year then maybe the cats would have
taken care of
the what if they were too lazy to hunt
it and they just become friends
rat well my cats do try to hunt bugs
when they see them so I feel like they
would have tried hunting
maybe could they hunt slugs actually
like genuinely why we back to slugs why
are we cing back to slugs everything
circles back to slugs at some
point the world is a
slug yeah y
yeah this makes me think of
man everything circles back it it really
does it came circling back to the slug
see that's like good storytelling right
there though it's like when they have
the beginning and then it's actually the
ending but you didn't know isn't that
what they did with berserk
actually not that I ever watched it I've
never seen it I want to see it I'm too
lazy to see
it I just feel like there's a lot of
Classics I need to watch or read but I
I'm lazy yeah that's like dedicating
time to actually pay attention and focus
yeah when I can be mindlessly playing
some other
game I feel like back in monari you have
to have so much
Focus yes that is true always talking
that is true you need a lot of focus but
the good thing is if you don't watch it
in a watch along like I do you can just
pause it and reread the subtitles and
everything just take your time with it
relist to the dialogue whenever you feel
like oh I zoomed out oh my
God that's true now I used to do that
when I first watched it I paused the
anime so many
times there's just so much
to I consume I guess to take in
yeah and they have so much hidden
dialogue in in the scenes also in the
anime like they quickly switch they give
you like half a second to read it cuz
they're not really thinking you will
read it but if you're watching it you're
just there to listen to the Japanese
ASMR
yeah no but I will stop it I will read
every
dialogue it's important to
read
yes how will you see all the
secrets you check the
Wikipedia I like the tropes page is like
ooh this is this TV TRS yeah or I go on
red and I'm like can someone tell me all
the Easter eggs in every
episode they're flexing in the GU chat
are they flexing showing off their
musles
gems from what I don't know
gambling gotcha
turn away from
[Music]
gotcha stop ging it's wrong for
you I don't want to hear that from you
everyone nobody can take it seriously
stop spending money on Roblox it's not
right yeah give the money to Gigi so she
can spend it on roox yeah so I can spend
money on Roblox
no why you should get a Rox
sponsorship I don't
know Roblox roox do they sponsor anybody
at all I don't know actually they don't
need to because the kids I didn't see
the actual thing but I heard about
it they don't need
sponsorships Roblox sponsor it's her
childhood I guess life is Roblox
can't relate I I didn't even grow up
with Roblox I started playing like two
years
ago well what got you like into it and
what made you stay though there has to
be a reason you stayed is it the
community there I do not talk to anyone
when I open my
Roblox I don't it's the gacha the gacha
is what's making me stay I didn't even
know started with swarm simulator and I
played so much of be swarm and it made
me so
unproductive
bearm yeah the whole purpose of bees
swarm is that you have a bunch of bees
and you have to collect honey and then
you have to increase your hive or make
your hive larger so you can collect more
honey and that's it that's the entire
game riveting cute it it's riveting
else
Roblox oh I have this much inventory
what the
heck
yeah my inventory is So Co my inventory
is so
disgusting sure I need a pack
mule but that's incription
I got to go kill a cany in
Ultra me too this is another
dungon really are we already at the next
dungeon yeah I have I'm only at Camila's
group ambition number five defeat that's
okay we can wait for you we'll kill
things so you can also level
up
okay I'm just leveling up my Bard anyway
can you kill
gador I don't I don't know who that is I
think it's a turtle must killed him
already maybe abor
G the VI for
drop what is it what is it I need to
check my emails o did they also tweet it
out I wonder or is it just email only
gatekeeping my businesswoman
kiawa wait I think it's in my spam
folder check your spam
[Music]
fold oh my [\h__\h] god I can't believe
what I just found in my spam folder
spam spam click here for hot woman
now sexy I saw that you um uh need a hot
woman in your
area need hot woman or you want a
raffle you know when I was in Japan I
was setting up my my computer and I
think I was trying to to download like
some song because I actually needed it
for work and it didn't provide it for me
and in the midst of downloading it from
like
YouTube uh I think I accidentally
enabled something and ever since that I
would get notifications of hot woman in
your
area I was like did I just go to fire
YouTube um in in anything actually I
would get random popups out of nowhere
like notifications I had to go back to
the site that I accidentally allowed um
notific
from you allowing viruses onto your
computer your work computer at least it
wasn't my computer
technically their computer
yeah someone's going to get that
computer what if I get that computer no
I'm sure they fix I fixed it I fixed it
it should have been fixed
theoretically but but you'll know if it
was my computer if it has the picture of
the Mei that's like shirtless
they should have changed it though I
told them to I told them to change it if
they didn't it's their
fault charless Demitri what are you
doing here on my
P I feel like a indirect connection to
you shi because of your love for Demetri
it's like so close you know that Meme
with the cars passing by and you look
out of the window and you're like what
the heck looking at the person in the
other car you know what that mean yeah
that's the Academy scene that's what I
feel like with with uh shiry because you
love Dimitri but I love I love like Adel
guards and oh are you obsessed with edel
guard maybe more what was her name sop
sop that maybe I like the most oh the
the woman the uh the bare
goddess yeah but in any case the girls
you know yeah yeah I like sis but it's
kind of sad because she's technically
just in your head and she'll always be
in your head
yeah like this is some weird
relationship no she's real she's real to
me Petra Petra well Petra
I'm salty towards Petra why did she kill
someone like in the game I was playing
the the Ard round right and the like all
the uh students that you can get umh
like pretty much every girl I talked to
was open to
marrying the girl protagonist CU I was
playing the female protagonist except
for the one that I was pursuing Petra
that she was the only one who was like
completely straight and I was like what
the heck why you breaking my heart you
like I actually I hate it when um routes
are gender locked it's like come on I
just want to play my game and get the
girls
my yeah you need to like
mod I
can facial
conversion oh oh my [\h__\h] god is this
the right
oh yeah no it's okay it's okay I can do
it I can do it I I know how to do I was
already linked to the right one you
fool I didn't even realize it looked the
same to
me I'm just going to stay as the Mage
for this I led my soul what would do
without I
know you be so
lost okay let's defeat Kenny y
poor Kenny why is Kenny always
[Music]
being oh I remember this place wait you
love this place you definitely need a
Healer for this I will not be the healer
for this I want a level of my stuff this
is a hard one yeah I will try to heal
then okay okay uh what's which one
you wait why am I oh crap they like me
more I have so many m
here yeah it's a good
dungeon as I try to level up my stuff
yes isn't this dungeon reused for
something else though cuz I remember it
using it in the like end game a
lot maybe like the assets were so it
looks simar they sleep me
so far only heal
shielding just because they keep coming
after
me why don't they get attracted to
Chi me who is the one agroing them but
they come to you yeah you're so
delicious looking look at you gu so I
don't look like a strong urine
they're terrified of the strong
urine too strong for
them thank you for the heals you're
welcome maybe I don't need constantly
heal maybe I'll just
uh why you up
there so I don't have to go down
there magic
boost attack
we are strong I'm pulling more no no be
careful gigy for real I'm pulling them
[Music]
gyin they can't hurt
me man if Gigi was a fire emblem
character I think she would die in
classic Mode pretty
fast you I'm like the one that's in the
middle and you have to come to me in
order to save me in like x amount of
turns or I die oh no you have fireblood
experience what the heck I
know played
some I haven't played through three
houses though I only know through
osmosis but I played some others I
really like GRE I need to finish
Awakening I'm just stuck on it I was not
a big fan of Awakening craw bin wait
that was the newest one right Awakening
no that's old engage is the newest one
I engage that's the one that I mean yeah
I finished that one I like the game play
not so much the characters and the story
though free houses is where it's at for
me but I only played those two so gu I
shouldn't I'm sure there's better ones
for if I emblem fans I'm sure going to
say but I want to self insert it's not
the same if I can't
why make that noise
like GG you're so
funny what do you mean is my noises I I
guess so you're like an 8hd
child I can't focus I have it's okay oh
[\h__\h] that's a boss that's a boss come
here oh that's not even Kenny
yeah it's okay dinosaurus meant to be
extinct uhoh what do we have to kill TM
at again it's okay oh we might oh no oh
shoot it's too late die
you is this stop hitting
me hold where good job hopefully
hopefully only Kenny is necessary but
that would make no sense kind of
actually where even this cany I guess I
think the middle of this I remember this
dungeon pretty Show Yourself
keny there's on this side and there's a
la on the other side left side of this
Circle Healing
please yes don't worry thank you I got
you Kenny you better be over here
or we will be
mad this dungeon is so difficult when
you don't play it
Sol I remember this was high
level it was high level but Solo's just
like so different now I
guess and you need some MP
m p o Elemental
Guardian
[Music]
Kenny I pulled
him all right he died
now I'm out of
MP I'm dying for some
reason oh I'll heal you okay I'm okay
I'm balancing oh W oh he keeps having a
oh oh oh but he's dead oh that's good
what happened who do we talk to I think
po
aath pulling everything you're pulling
everything I'm on the autop paath we
don't have to kill the the the
dinosaur yeah I should be like the next
Quest that will be another
time is like killing Charles three times
again
there's Excalibur over there wow oh yeah
that's another boss yeah there's three
bosses in this dungeon
actually do you want us to kill them now
oh Jesus Christ they all came for you
Gigi yeah the quest now says
kill the Dr the I'm Ked I'm going to
good God I paid for your
[Music]
mistake well uh I will I will wait until
set the dungeon cuz we have to kill we
might as well oh wait let me let me talk
to St really quick oh okay I I'll I'll
kite them away I'll kite them away don't
worry I keep on aering them back to me
by healing myself and you oh no you're
running out of
mp2 paid for her mistake okay okay we'll
fight them we might have to anyway
okay I have to run back there I'm just
going to run back why why do they do
this why don't they give us all those
bosses as Quest goals right away oh oh
no oh it's fine guess I'll die wait do
we get like
exp problems are you already I think so
oh are you already back in the
dungeon girl yeah I'm in the dungeon I
think you're about to kill me I just
want to go to St
um I guess I'll
die okay I'm in comat okay hold up let
me let me have him kill me wa should
should we should we exit right I'm going
to exit okay I have will exit then no no
you should get the quest I'll help you
where are you oh I I killed myself you
didn't accept the quest yet oh okay yeah
the Sur Quest yeah cuz I I had to die
for Chi since
no all right all right are are you in
the dungeon
again yeah yeah we'll do it we'll do it
okay we'll get the quest I'm here thank
you you guys want some healing yes
please I'm hurt
oh
cure
cure thank you okay let's
gtir I would heal you if you're not if
you wouldn't be running
away what are they running to G you run
to the left this
way I mean I I assume it loops
around yeah he he's closer to the
left full party wipe
[Music]
yay what the heck KY stop
running we're in trouble here
I'm just going to run I'm going to run
please I'm following thorth why are you
so
far which one do I want this one look
nice okay I can go to tmat now okay uh
shall we try to clear these mobs and and
exit normally or I I mean we we'll see
I'm
dying uh are you oh you want to die okay
sorry I end up killing them oh it's GG
muted yeah
oh we just teleport to the opening
anyway fine don't be so
dramatic you're
fine oh her mother her mother father
tell your mom I said hi can your mom
hear us well she's playing a video game
and
multitasking mommy sorry
Mommy all right shall we go to the
entrance now yeah please please I cannot
teleport from here that sucks
zooming why is she alreadying in the
back I don't know today I my dominance
yeah I'm actually a Christmas
tree yeah I already put up my Christmas
tree
yeah how you ever seen a goth Christmas
before yeah you guys are
so
un UN unupdated about yeah what's what's
hype and and and uh cool these
days okay so it has been reset
yeah let's do
this uncultured yeah yeah I'm I'm so
uncultured that I can't even remember
these words
oh I can't wait for this attack I lik
it was that me or was
that oh GG's not back yet I guess no
we're inside oh okay I'll be I'll be in
there I'm using a useless class right
now by the way just letting you
know oh my God my inventory is
I want to level up all my
classes bless you bless you thank you so
much I should do this later what what
I'm doing
now no let me the item this place
I need to LEL
up thanks for the membership
yipp
[Music]
yippe
okay this is going well so far
maybe we can ignore KY maybe we can go
around yeah yeah we
can there's a third boss I think after
killing Tiamat we have to get the Quest
for the third third one too well let's
kill him first but he's
wandering oh yeah there's
[Music]
um the camela
people
mhm he's like just walks in a circle
yeah we have to go it's like all like on
the opposite of where we are
now let's go that way on our
way guitar
man I just like zoning out to this like
I'm not even
thinking that's the right way the MMO
grind yeah sweepy
sweepy
Kenny Kenny no not
Kenny yeah come here we're killing all
your
dragons dinosur and then we'll kill you
next if you feel like it
it's walking
clockwise
no should we we'll get there should we
go towards him instead of because the
enemy's already cleared at least if we
go that way partially and then he goes
around
again around the world
around stop typing in chat by
accident around the
world where are
you
[Music]
XD oh we're so close that's not
him he must be bigger he must be more
intimating yeah
mat I see oh he's right there he's right
there yeah yes attack
kill don't let him breathe no
longer oh no why are they always after
me stab his to oh
shoot oh shy shy I heal you thank you
wait where
going yeah where is he running hello
what what's happening he's Justa did he
just despawn
yeah oh he's he's over there he's over
there why it
reset reset ah we brought him too far in
his Circle that's so dumb we maybe he
should have a better Circle to
far okay okay oh he's always Happ it's
okay it's okay don't worry I got you I
got
you what is
this I don't know but I'll
greed no no no I want to pick up oh
let's talk to St
again damn you st for making us do
this oh I like the required level okay
oh my
inventory now we got to kill snap turtle
gamra snap turtle
gamra yeah I think she's inside yeah
right
here I'm talking to Earth VB okay we'll
just kill the
mobs level
up okay G I Can't heal you just let you
know it's okay we'll go at one one at a
time healer's
coming I am
here I just like doing the random guitar
RS
right I'm doing a concert for you guys
oh
well oh
the cat climbed up the pillar snap
turtle
camra count your
days okay okay I'm here
I'm you will die to our
wand to our combined V power oh oh man
why is it always after
me I'm just a sister of the cloth we did
it we did it we we have to reach level
38 now why
[Music]
boo it's okay it will be the problem
of ourselves from the future future us
problem
yes okay we'll leave it at that I
think yeah that was a good
run thank you I think we did like three
dungeons today yeah effective day yeah
thank you for for the Eden of eternals I
saw you're playing Eden again this week
shy yeah for mambers oo how you want to
level you want to
grind I I can yeah I mean I'm going to
be going on a trip soon so during that I
don't know how how much grinding I'll be
doing that's fine I think I'm also on a
little trip this next or next next week
so wee trip
buddies
spy SP ooh a
spy sounds so good I'm so
excited so everybody take care of
yourselves yody I hope you get well soon
thank you I'll let you know if I didn't
die thank you
I need you still we need you for our
eeden Eternal Endeavors don't die you
just want me for my healing that's all I
am to all of you guys I want you for
your sweet body I see I see you would
love me if I turn into a worm I would I
would let you crawl on me I want to keep
you in the jar thank you thank you
time thank you also for the viewers who
participated in again today hope you're
having fun
everybody we'll see you soon for more
etal I think I'll read a few super
chatos so goodbye girlies okay byebye
have a
nice byee than for guys
[Music]
goodbye all right she still my screen
hold up I got to leave the room there
you
go all right thank you for joining me
for this um my my voice hurts I might
still grind after stream but I will be
like quietly grinding probably so I'm
just going to quietly grind I'm sickish
guys I'll see you guys tomorrow for Fall
Guys until then to see you and Eden
w