foreign
[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
so
okay
[Music]
hello
[Laughter]
yeah it is
oh my transition
oh you noticed oh
yeah we can redo that
uh
i think
testing
there we go
okay
fixed it
and this is uh
my my first pgm i used this in my debut
stream
yeah old really really old vgm not
scarcity
hello
[Music]
i'm drinking sprite
which i usually never drink
but today
a few days ago i saw someone drinking
sprite and now i felt like drinking
sprite myself
[Music]
not not seven up we don't really we
don't really do seven up here in austria
i mean it exists i think
but it's hard to find
and
really hard to find
normally you can't yeah i don't think
you normally find it
now just normal sprite
no orange soda
[Music]
not orange soda i really don't care much
about orange
[Laughter]
ironically i don't care much about
orange soda
at all like not in particular
hello everybody uh i'm so sorry for the
wait uh
i was running around errands i wish i
could have taken a shower um it's
[\h__\h] hot outside
today obama
it's incredibly hot
oh my god
it's so hot it's so hot
but at least it's not humid i guess that
would make it worse
at night
they have a fat oh no i currently don't
have it on you know why because actually
coming back into my apartment it's a
little bit cooler than outside so i
guess that helps
um
you know in comparison to outside
it's not that bad
not that bad but i might turn it on for
a little bit
let's turn it on for a little bit
[Music]
yeah i bought this this dyson
uh
fan
i was just gonna buy like a super super
normal
basic ass
fan
you know like the
the round ones really the basic one yeah
but i yeah a bladeless i bought i bought
a bladelet i ended up buying a bladeless
one because it just looked so nice
i was walking around the
the fan section
and i was looking at them and i was like
really the most basic one will do i
suppose but then
then there's this dude this staff
person standing next to the
dyson fans
and they're like actually like
out of the boxes and being like like
operating and i'm like
that looks nice
and i guess they're more quiet than the
other ones probably
um
they're usually worse than normal ones
no that i mean no i see no problem with
this one
[Music]
it's strong and and fairly quiet i think
quieter the dude said so too
quieter than the normal fans how does it
work
yeah right i mean i look at it and i
feel like
what
what kind of magic is going on there i
would like to know
uh
strong and independent fan yeah
there's a fan inside no [\h__\h] way
no way
there's no fat inside
there's no space for a fan inside
um
it's like a turbine turbine turbine
i mean i can i guess well something is
in there that makes it go swoosh
something something
the base has the spinning yeah when i
put the the thing on top of the base i
saw something there that like when you
take off the i don't know if it's not
locked properly but when i tried to move
the
fan the top part came up and then the
air came out of the bottom
so it doesn't come through the the
the
round
thing with the hole
it it comes from the base and then it
goes through the
through this weird shape and then
makes you think it comes through the
hole
it doesn't though not really
yeah anyway
uh
hey walmart's fan way more quiet and
more powerful well whatever at least
mine got style
yeah mine is fancy
all right
mine looks nice
yeah yeah and i have a
i have a
remote control
copium
yes so what
[Music]
how cool was the real life cave before
oh you mean the one in the uh
any plus cafe i didn't i only saw photos
but
uh
i thought it was funny how it's served
on this really [\h__\h] tiny plate
like the food is spilling over
looks like kind of difficult to eat like
that's that's what i was thinking
the plate is tiny
but i don't know the people who actually
ate it i wonder how they felt about it
i'm planning to go there really
so i've i've read some information
apparently like uh
over 200 people
were already or like 250 people were
already standing in line
at
4 00 am or something like that
and then by the time of the opening it
was already 500 plus people
the problem is
and i feel for you i failed for your
korean friends
this is not so nice the problem is that
apparently you know that limited menu
it is it is very limited it's 10
[Music]
10 per day
which means
if you really want a limited one you
have to i mean who knows how this is
gonna be going on for a while so who
knows how
how
how the lines are gonna be like in a
month or so
should be better
but the limited menus are also going to
change
at least the 10 is the information i saw
from like people who went there i'm not
sure if like it's really just 10 but
that's what somebody who went there
wrote
yeah
uh
i don't know
10 really is crazily little like 50 or
so would be nice at least
but yeah since there were already like
250 people lining up at 4am
[Music]
well that was opening day so let's hope
for them that the next days are not
gonna be
that
bad i mean it's also at the same time
good i'm very happy
to see that there were so many people
standing in line yeah and
someone
sent me
don jado june
sent me this picture
look at the top row
hey y'all
chihuahua badge
the bet out of the basic badges quavo
completely sold out what the [\h__\h]
let's
go the rest seems still at that point
stocked rather nicely i'm not sure at
what point of time this person ah wait
he said he said i entered the store
11 30 a.m
sadly basic potential can badge out of
stock
cookie is yummy
and you always want to see some pictures
i've been looking at people have been
sending me like in replies
like korean fans have been sending them
to me in reply so you want to see
okay so there's like
this like this really i like the wall
it's cool cool wall
this looks like it's right next to the
counter where you get your food
and they're playing specs
nice
thanks for the advertisement
and then
uh oh
apparently there's even on the tables
my face
it's a table
see how there's chairs next to it it's a
table
i'm a table you can eat on don't spill
too much okay keep me clean
[Laughter]
yeah that's cool
and uh oh
[Laughter]
went to the cafe and showed me this
that's my food
that's my fried chicken with an inner
drink and a gouda drink and a kiwa
kotori cookie on and i'm a table
and the the little mascots they are i
think handmade by this person they look
amazing
but the food that's what i mean with
it's a [\h__\h] tiny plate like what the
[\h__\h] how how
but okay the food looks amazing i guess
it makes the food look even bigger
is that a cake no it's like actual
fries and actual chicken and the sauce
i've been told that it's not spicy i i
expected it to be spicy because of you
know korea likes to have their things
spicy a lot but i was told it's just
like um
like a
sweet spicy sauce with
not much spicy left in it which is good
it's not
it's not i know it's on the dessert menu
but as far as i know it's
that's the funny thing it's not a
dessert it's not a cake that uh is made
to look like fried chicken when you cut
through it's a cake inside no no no no
would be a big [\h__\h] bamboozle though
that would be funny but i mean look at
it no no way
no way no
no
so
that's that and then oh that's so cute
i really love this
wait they have that table too they have
a table with my with what i currently
look like as well oh i look so cool from
that angle it looks so different
oh and those little chickens they look
so cute
i want i want
now that's enough a table empress table
yeah really cool
really cool stuff and then this person
he
got some merch
and a kiwama birds
you are wearing this uh
some cards
and uh stickers maybe and the acrylic
stand and the oh no the cookie is a
little bit broken
but then yeah yeah some stuff there and
the chickens chickens look so cute oh
wait i just noticed one of the chickens
has like a
oh wait it's a female chicken
it has blush and the two red lines
and one of them is sitting on its feet
because it has no feet so i'm guessing
it's like
sitting on like
has its feet inside it's fluffy
fluffiness so cute can i please can i
please have
one of these
please
now um
i asked
uh i asked um
management
if they can show me
the schedule
for the limited menus
because i think you guys uh who are
going there
my korean friends are you here are you
listening
are you listening korean friends
i think it has not been made public but
i've been told that i can tell
people
i can talk about it i've been told
so if you want to know when kiwawa
special menu
is happening
i can tell you
or do you already know
i have the insider info that i'm allowed
to share
you know
[Music]
i got the scoop yeah
they know
you know
[Music]
do you have an exact schedule
tell us please so you don't know
don't know
okay well i'll tell you i'll tell you
and
you better be thankful
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right so the first two
can't read excel file
google delivery drive
uh there we go the first two weeks is
cali right cali's special menu we're
talking about
soru
and another one that i can't read
something with yama
but it's i don't know it's in japanese
but uh it should i don't know what it is
in
i said busan uh-huh okay so
uh
the first two weeks it's not weeks there
that looks like weeks and then
kiwawa
special menu
it's a curry
from the 4th of august
until the 17th
so the second and the third week
okay
mine is next yeah debbie order oh
oh i guess it is yeah it is the debut
order and then after that the next two
weeks is ina and then the next two weeks
is gonna and the next two weeks is
ah yeah i don't see
i don't see a break in between
so it goes on until the end of september
and then uh there is like
there's another schedule but i'm not
sure if i can also share that one so i
will shut up
about it
there's another schedule of like uh some
different locations that open up later
uh which i think that itself has been
announced so this was in the morning
look i'm so surprised there's so many
people
what
like what
what here's some impressions for you
guys oh my children
this is like at the at the front of the
shop
oh
what do we have here
ah on the left side there's some other
uh
collaborations but in the front you know
the big big one with the big screen
it's us
oh
oh you see that that's when you know oh
i've reached the goal i'm so close i can
i can already smell the chicken
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
wanna see more people standing in line
here there's more people standing in
line i don't know where that is but
yeah
holy [\h__\h] i'm what thank you so much for
coming so early
in the morning
[Music]
wow
so early thank you
yo
i wonder what they're looking at on your
phone
hopefully kiwami streams and vlogs and
archives
what are they
i'm really happy to see that
and then and then
[Music]
i don't know which part of the store
this is it's really hard to like imagine
when you're not there but there's like
this part when there's where there's big
standees i was hoping for standees look
at us
and like in the back there's all kinds
of like
portraits whoa
i like the decoration
let me make it a bit bigger what do we
have like screenshots from
is those that those are those are frames
not right not screens on the left
what is that from my mine or here in the
middle
where's that from i wonder
what nerfed
they made me
you think they made me a bit smaller oh
i think it's about right it's all right
it's okay cause kylie's wearing heels
you know
and then the jazz jack art and then oh
we have some so yeah some general like
pictures from our moments from our
screens cute the one in the in the
casual and the fancy outfits in the back
yeah
noise oh oh you see that that that that
that's my my fancy room my ballroom
there hmm
right yeah
coolio
and then again
and then there's
oh where everybody sits
the walls
the walls behind them are like this
wow
cool
cool stuff man
well they even have like yeah nice
graphic design because those are not our
official logos they made something there
i like it it looks cool
where's mine i want to see
i didn't get a picture of my wall
where's my wall
or our only cuda and inner walls because
they're so flat just kidding on the
right side i do see ame
on the right side
but yeah um roasted
those are some impressions that i found
uh there's this like korean
website that posts news about whole life
and they posted these pictures
let me try
let me try to give some credit
what was it called again
squirrel squirrels girls graduate
and people have been like sending me
their their halls
of merchandise i had whole life dot
korea dot kr
and if you wanna look for the article
there you go
take a look
you can take a look there i'm waiting in
front of us already
what
it's midnight
it opens at 10
are you good
are you okay what are you gonna are you
gonna sleep
well if you or if you're there already
you might have a chance at the
at the special menu
i recommend that you arrive before 7 a.m
and line up there are more people on
weekends
oh yeah oh wait
tomorrow is friday
probably go for the weekday if you have
any questions korean friends will help
you a lot
well it is until the end of september so
i don't know you guys
have actually enough time to check it
out if you feel like going to korea on a
spontaneous trip in theory like korea
you can actually enter
unlike japan
as far as i know
[Music]
visa wise i think tourists can enter
normally
before seven yeah i mean this person is
lining up a tent at midnight so
crazy
i hope you're
okay
uh but at least i can i'm probably gonna
stream for the next five hours so you
have something to look at
for the next five hours out of ten
i live in busan so i was going to go
there but my heart was broken
why what do you mean what do you mean
your heart was broken how can i help you
hey korea requires seven days
what
really what
i don't know
is that really so even with you know
vaccination
or a test
sold out oh but maybe you can go again
it's gonna be for a long time don't
worry don't worry
just pcr is good
policy keeps changing
well i'm a bit [\h__\h] if it's a seven
day quarantine
but
[Music]
yeah i wonder if are there any other
people waiting at midnight don't don't
wait don't go there so early guys
it's like you know it's like coffee
coming where they and for comic people
for many years they always you know
um lined up like overnight and then at
some point they banned it uh
and then you were not allowed to come
before the first train
arrives at the venue
yeah and then people
actually um
follow that rule
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
the people camp at the train no no no no
like normally not like maybe there's
like out of a million people going there
maybe one or two bad cases who still
somehow camp somewhere around the venue
but
so she had to she had to
me
and i mean there's probably no rule for
aniplus but if it's really that bad they
might have to make a rule
[Laughter]
oh my god but don't worry kiwa's special
menu
not now anyway kiwami's special menu in
two weeks two weeks okay okay
so oh please eat chihuahua curry okay
i hope
i hope uh it can be more than 10 items
per day
[Laughter]
but yeah only 10 holy [\h__\h] wait so if
it's two weeks
and then uh 10 per day and you get an
item like did you see kelly's special
menu it comes with a comes up for class
right so only um wait two weeks
is 14 days
14 times
10 140
does that mean that there's only 140
curries and 140 of kiwa's special item
give it given out
that is really limited
yeah i did math
wow
140 whoa
17 what's 17
17.
me
i waited in line for the first time when
i bought a flower
what
17 17 people are how do you know did
somebody count somebody who's watching
the stream now counted them at midnight
at midnight 10 hours before the store
opens already 17 oh my god that means
okay only 10 out of those 17 are getting
the special menu for today
which means for everybody else who
wanted the special menu can already give
up on it and just sleep longer and come
later sleep longer come later
gosh i'm so sorry that's like really um
like i never
did something like that before
staying
like in front of the venue overnight or
so just to
get into a store or something like that
i never did that before
it must be really
i i prefer to sleep you know
[Laughter]
me neither
i wish they could sell the merch online
too
[Music]
i can't for the old iphones when i was a
kid
oh yeah that's also something people
camp for huh
i do not do not underestimate korean
fans and [\h__\h] well at least as i said
at least you guys have something to
watch wait tell me that all 17 people
are watching my stream right now
[Music]
a fighting fighting fighting
[Laughter]
ah are they gonna sleep i hope it's safe
to like you know
doze off a little bit
[Music]
i was trying to do a snoring but really
not good for my throat
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello
hello 17
legendary 17 korean bros
hello
[Music]
time to get comfy
don't fight okay don't fight i know only
10 out of you
can get the limited menu but please
don't fight okay maybe they start like
you know making some deals like yo
can you let me
be the one who gets the limited menu
in exchange i
whatever i don't know what what can i
offer you
oh no
blood will be shed no
no
don't fight no don't fight
[Music]
everyone gets to have friends yeah you
could share there's two pieces of
chicken
and a couple of fries oh wait oh wait
that's kiwa menu we're talking about
cali menu which is an ice cream oh isn't
that nice you can you know if you're
going if there some of them are going
alone you can like
make a couple
and eat the ice cream together
but the glass you cannot share probably
unless you move in together
which would be
beautiful i would be
so touched by that
yeah but you can share the food at least
yeah share the ice cream with a homie
with a bro
give them the brewfist and then share
the ice cream ask for two spoons or or
just for one
[Laughter]
oh man
cute but my my fried chicken will be
easier wait no my fried chicken is not
limited we're talking about the curry
okay
well fried chicken you know the dessert
is good good easy to share as well
though i wonder if that's like ever like
running out too i know it's not limited
but i wonder if it ever runs out
who
this is so small but
somebody who ordered
and then a cali
[Music]
menu it comes with this glass
that's a
ah that's callie's drink too right
i think and on an ammo table
oh there's a queen standing in the back
there oh
[Music]
wait that's one of the legendary 10
people
of the first day
whoa
sorry this is so fascinating to me
i'm so excited that we have something
like this
[Music]
fighting fighting fighting
fighting
yeah
all right i should probably get to the
real program
[Laughter]
uh
yeah yeah and yeah i have to read some
chats that's what i'm here for today
oh
wait did i show you i didn't show you
this one
it's just such a um
[Music]
that's a good image quality
food
crispy
[Laughter]
what a
dessert i mean
to be honest
it for me it actually makes kind of
sense because sometimes i like to eat
the dessert the sweet stuff the actual
sweet stuff
before
the savory stuff sometimes i just feel
like it
and
and then i would eat the savory stuff
afterwards which kind of if you think
about it that way
would make the savory stuff the dessert
and then this would make total sense
you get what i'm trying to say
[Laughter]
i wonder how big that actually is like
the plate is so tiny i think it's not
that big the chicken is big though
oh
and amaze
with banana fruits banana fruit smoothie
i'm guessing there's banana and maybe
kiwi because of the
the
dark dots that looks like it could be
kiwi seeds or
i want to drink that
[Music]
but yeah i like that it's not too big
portions to be honest though because i
i think that would be actually maybe
that's not banana because in this photo
in this photo okay there's definitely
kiwi in there
just look at those seats
nice nice pictures by the way thank you
han solo
thank you hanzo that's passion
[Music]
okay true could be something with
passion fruit mango
something like that too
ah goddammit i wanted it to be a banana
smoothie when i first saw the menu i
thought it was a bananas movie and i
really was excited for that i don't know
why i really like banana
i really like the banana
banana
[Music]
should we keep it on the screen
i'll put it like here as if
and i want to can somebody
have somebody like uh oh this one this
is also nice
that represents can somebody take this
photo and then um make the like the
surroundings into a png
for me
please
so that i can put it on my table
now
something deep and meaningful
that's that's kind of nostalgic i used
to tell people to write something deep
and meaningful into their super chats
i should pin it to my own
yeah i can't do that but i needed to be
a nice png well i wanted you to see this
one too
yo
the gouda drink i love that blue color
oh oh and then oh in the back there's
the gouda dessert
i don't know what that was next to the
gouda drink
it's also so blue and the cali
dessert
another person who got it
maybe it's not that limited after all
or it's just really those lucky people
and chihuahua fried chicken and the
cheesecake i think that was amazed right
ah that's enos drink behind cuda
and then in the front you like some
cards that i guess you get when you
order our menus
[Music]
i want all of them me too
my menu presents what do you mean
i mean it definitely stands out it's
quite funny and i feel like you know um
i mean
look judging by the pictures of the
people standing in line there's an
obvious
um
imbalance there's more
dudes there than girls okay
and i would i would think that if you
can choose between four desserts
and the fried chicken with with fries i
feel like
the
a lot of the dudes would go for the for
the actual savory food rather than you
know
the sweet stuff
i mean they would still go for it just
for the sake of you know getting their
oshi's food and all of that but don't
you agree with me yeah
i have a sweet tooth so i would go for
the sweet stuff but
but wait no i need to i'm potential i
need to i would totally choose my food i
would 100 go for the fried chicken no i
will i would go for a cake and then the
fried chicken and you know my menu and
then the the one of the nice drinks yeah
yeah
[Music]
cheesecake i'm not the biggest fan of
cheesecake i think my what was my
favorite dessert
where's the where's the menu again
what is my favorite
i'm looking at pictures from the
from the special limited time only menus
my favorite is the one from ame
i love it i really want to eat it but i
don't think i can
but i love the almond dessert
yeah oh okay so
yeah cali's kelly's cake or
inna's cake
would probably be
what i would want to go for
and then ammo's special menu limited
time only
okay enough enough of that
enough for that uh if somebody
finishes
the
png let me know that would be nice to
have
i'm gonna check twitter
and you're not that fast right nobody's
that fast
nobody's that fast
[Music]
[Laughter]
somebody just sent me jinlo's tweet
come on
it was just one person buying all of the
badges i thought it was several people
it wasn't just one
i said i think he's sending it to other
people it says here's the merch house i
got from miffex and plus korea club
asked friend in korea ah a friend got it
for him
and finally it's a time to make
tanzanita back yeah you'll need a lot of
badges to make a bag but this is not the
first time that we're selling badges as
as a
as merchandise
right so
[Laughter]
oh they got the portable charger nice
that's the reason why they do know you
little [\h__\h]
that's why
everybody's like
[Laughter]
okay they're probably back in stock on
the second day so don't worry guys
oh man oh god he got even like more but
mostly just one from every other badge
oh nice i love the merchandise looks so
nice
there's some here's some good uh
some gouda stuff
oh i like the memo memo pad it's cute
the phone charger the phone stand
charger i really want that one
[Music]
good stuff but um show me the eater bag
when it's done okay because um we need
to see if it was worth the sacrifice of
everybody else who went there and
couldn't buy the [\h__\h] badge
because you needed to make a eater bag
there we go [\h__\h] fast thanks alex
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice
store has opened for me i'm digging in
yummy
wow
all right
all right it's been
50 minutes
maybe we should read super chat
okay
let's see
i want to get this done today
i will get this done today
binges sure why not
i'll put it on my table let's go
everything you got
seven hours to eat the perfect fighter
you stalling no
no no not in particular
[Laughter]
okay whether i have to continue i think
the minecraft or the australian snack
box
uh
i think my aussie snack box ah minecraft
i turned off i guess or i was only a few
and i read them already
okay
snack box
oh okay
uh
thump nails
from nail here
okay
uh yeah it should be alright
we'll get there
i'll i'll i'll try to be a bit more fast
because we need to get this behind us
okay
have you had any drinks no
no not at all only sprite
but you know it made me really excited
to see the photos
it's exciting
[Music]
there are a few tangents okay i will
don't doubt me
time to go to speed oh
you're nicki minaj i hope
you know this could be a nice thing to
fall asleep to for the people who are
standing in line in front of the shop
[Laughter]
okay
yeah
okay i'm winning this match hell yeah
and when i ask a normal question oh
that's not gonna be normal is it
since you have 3d now and blue piano is
back is it possibly we have 3d blue
kiana
yes it is definitely possible
yeah
yeah not gonna do it now though
but we can play around with that
important question yeah sure
happy birthday i sent a 50
ah super chat live stream but i forgot
to write something oh how do you forget
that i guess that's my fee for work this
week at kfpd and sorry about that
exactly you always make me smile and
keep me keep giving me motivation each
day thank you oh really
i'm glad i can motivate you i can't even
motivate myself a lot of the time
well thank you let's do our best okay
every day
every day we're struggling every day
we're hustling let's go
fight oh
motivated
thank you for the super chat rokenzi
danke soon james
lovelace thank you for the pinky
thanks thanks mate okay i hope you got
some vocals and shapes that's the good
stuff
uh we had shapes but no volvos i don't
know what that is
but apparently it wasn't important
enough to be included because bails
included pretty much
everything that's important
at least judging by the reaction from
the chat back then
ah
yeah
what's volvo
what
fluffy pink picky what
are you talking about
[Music]
i'm glad it wasn't included
uh anyway thank you thanks mate
um mulo construction you
so thank you soon dremel rango thanks
for the red super chat how can i miss my
chance to send you a birthday red chat
basic week at work i saw i missed the
live show but i did catch the archive
breathtaking show i was blown away by
the girlfriend talent you just played
happy birthday and keep being awesome
danza oh
thank you arigato thanks
i'm glad you liked it for sure i'm gonna
turn off the
okay
turning off the
fan
thanks tiramirego i'm gonna do my best
to continue being
awesome according to you i wouldn't say
it about myself
i mean a fan guy hi there what's up
what's up buddy
yeah sorry for for taking so long to get
to your super chat but i do appreciate
it thank you for the love and the
support
fresh chat a fresh kiss for you
yeah are you so sweet thank you
[Music]
thank you
old bgm makes kiera cuter than usual
there's no way that that's true
what are you talking about
[Music]
fresh chat for your kiss
i can't talk
what do you mean i'm normal
i'm normal
[Music]
why do people say i took something
i'm normal
normal
what i'm always like this
i'm always like this
oh i always like this i'm confused
and maybe it's the bgm my pixels look
brighter who are you talking about
yeah you like my frog
i love my frog it's cute go go go frog
yeah go go go go go
keep spinning
[Music]
go go go one day you'll catch that
that fly
one day
it's bean i miss
1440 pizza
i'll bring her back sometime but i would
absolutely you know change the size of
all of this [\h__\h] clutter in my office
and it takes a while huh i was like us
that's just
you know small size kiwawa again
yeah
[Music]
go spin
happy birthday from new zealand couldn't
watch it live due to time zones but this
is an appreciation of the hard work you
put in to not only your concert but the
collab songs original songs and all the
other projects you do
thank you so much
i do my best i try to do my best i work
hard yeah thanks for noticing and new
zealand that's nice to hear actually i
started watching a new
um a new show
on netflix
uh
i think what was it again it's called
god's favorite idiot i think
um
it's pretty funny and then there's one
side character
who
uh
speaks in a really strong new zealand
accent
and
it's so funny
it's quite strong i like it i like it
though it's like a
like a
like a weird british or
australian accent like a more intense
one
you made a show about me
sounds interesting
i think it's pretty fun uh it's like you
know just like a like a comedy show with
a little bit of fantasy in it because
like it's about god and satan
[Music]
yeah
you really like those accents i think
it's really interesting to listen to it
and this this show
mixes a lot of like interesting
things like just recently i was thinking
and i was watching like like like some
shows i was just recently thinking yo
why do they only cast like super thin
people
it's so unrealistic why is everything
everyone so so fit you know and looks so
perfect
it's so unrealistic and then i started
watching this show
and there's a lot of like overweight
people
chubby people
and not so perfect looking people
in in the show
and i appreciate that because it makes
it feel way more realistic and way more
relatable and nice also i like it
like the two the two main
uh actors are
chubby
yeah
and yeah
it's nice to see that to see that main
characters get casted
uh by actors who are
not you know
perfectly fit
i like it
feels authentic yeah it does
yeah like normal looking people exactly
although
there's this this one of the main um
actors one of the main characters the
the female one i think her name was like
her actor her real name was melissa
mccarthy or so you know she played in
gilmore girls so i was really excited to
see her again but now you guys said
normal looking and not really though
like um uh
she wears like really in the show at
least she wears really really really
really uh
like funky outfits it's really cute and
funny
really cute
she's so cool yeah she's a great actress
she's
cute cute i like her fashion in the show
too
forgive me my opinions my membership is
so bad i'll be running down to the store
shortly to pick up another car and i
want nothing more to become a bucket for
you
it's okay chill don't worry i don't know
how it works like how much time you can
have in between but chill
it's all good you'll become a bucket one
day
[Music]
run run
end of the [\h__\h] world it also has
really realistic looking people that's
such a weird thing to say
[Music]
it also has really realistic looking
people it's as if like it's implying
that
the other shows are like using actors
that are just robots or something
okay continuing where was i
wait here i endless here's a case for
you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
for your support please continue
supporting kiwawa gotta go everybody
james lovelace thank you soon black
friday and pepsi
and travertine
maxi king 92
for the pinky point angel i saw your
concert and it really left me speechless
you were incredible your performance
your vocals the stage everything was 10
out of 10. i'm looking forward to your
future stream and your german channel
let's go
thank you
i'm currently getting
um
some
graphics made for the german channel so
once that's finished
um
probably in the first week of august
i'll do i'll start i'll start you know
working on the channel which will still
not be that frequently probably but you
know you know you know yeah
we'll at least put something into the
channel some
content probably start with like a debut
and then
yeah put up some clips and stuff and
yeah i don't know we'll see i wanted to
um maybe start uh what was it a gothic
play-through
and then i saw that there's a remake
being planned being made right now and i
was like maybe i should wait for that to
come out
since i don't think and i don't think we
have permissions for gothic right now
anyway but maybe for the remake it would
be easier to get them you know what i
mean
and then yeah i don't know when
remake is a long time away but i saw
just somewhat recently there were some
noise looking updates
not the remake
the remake looks good
okay i'll think about it i can try to
get perms but you know you understand
that i'll be playing it in german right
because it's you know i thought that
would be a good idea
because it's like from german people
watch anyway okay
that's fine okay
and german gothic is the only way to
play
wait and stream on the german subject
that's what i'm saying
that's what i'm saying you're a little
bit slow today aren't ya
that's what i'm saying yo that's the
plan
yeah
bruh
chicken brains is low
[Music]
still booting up you're taking your damn
swing time
yeah it's an immersive experience
exactly
thank you maxi king
uh i'll see you on the german channel
hopefully soon thank you for the support
thanks for waiting i'll streak or
outstrike it
thank you al tessa 29
[Music]
thank you for the right to chad another
win for real australia
[Music]
australia
oh we're talking about the same
australians
well no uh mate i'll give you that you
guys have good food good snacks i like
them yeah
yeah yeah i i can give you this win but
only if you also give me a win sometimes
okay okay mate
[Music]
kishan rick bain thank you robert carney
thank you in the game mccree thank you
james lovelace oh again thanks for the
pinky back and leaving again vodka for
me
you kept on sending super chat saying
you're here and then leaving and you're
here and then leaving must be busy
thank you for saying hi
thanks mate thank you shane
thank you very much
hope you enjoyed watching the vlog yeah
and also you know since you're from
australia i hope you also enjoyed the
australian mario party
thanks man
bentley thank you
thank you robert corny thank you for the
pinky
you have great tastes when it comes to
bread one of the many reasons you're my
favorite gtg oh gotta go i need to study
for my emt license
not using a single period in your super
chat
triggers me
i want to roast you about it
robert
robert robert robert
this is this is literally three
sentences and you did not use anything
yeah
no no period no comma
nothing
and but you're lucky that i'm so smart
that i still understand what you're
saying
[Music]
thanks y'all hope you got that license
thanks mate happy birthday birthday i
wasn't able to watch it live but your 3d
performance was awesome
oh
thanks mate
i'm glad you liked it and even if it's
belated i appreciate it thanks for
remembering
it's better than you know not saying it
at all i know it's like super hard to
when you forget someone's birthday i'm
not saying you forgot it but just you
know when you forget congratulating
someone on their birthday and time
if it's someone you're relatively close
to oh god
i feel so bad about it
but in the end usually the person
who's being congratulated
doesn't really care much
whether or not you set it in time or the
day after
but two days or three days or four days
after
that's when it starts getting iffy
that's when i'm like
yo
like especially if you have me like on
one of those
social media networks that notifies you
of my birthday
then you should
i've seen it there's
you i'm basically like helping you i'm
giving you a cheating card telling you
when my birthday is you should
no you should not be late
yeah
yeah yeah
and then i thank the internet dearly for
you know doing that
giving people
the info yo this is today's this
person's birthday
now go ahead and act as if you already
knew that and i didn't tell you that you
already knew and you didn't need that
information from me go ahead and tell
them a happy birthday
i appreciate the existence but then
there's a few people
who don't have their birthday public on
like you know
facebook or whatever
and i'm like
do you actually expect me to know your
birthday then
if they don't have it somewhere publicly
like that
then they shouldn't expect me to
remember their birthday
so the other way around if i didn't
notify you guys about my birthday in
advance then i wouldn't expect you to
remember it either but i very much did
notify you
but it's okay i don't mind you guys
saying it later
spreads out the super chats nicely too
anyway
hey
well i think i was at some point i was
like
i i
i may have considered or i actually did
like make my birthday
on public private
on such social media sites
to see
which friends actually still know my
birthday without the help of facebook
whatsoever
that's evil
yeah i know you're gonna you're gonna
test it out who actually still has a
[\h__\h] calendar and puts in their
friends birthdays in there
actually speaking of
birthdays and speaking of this kind of
experiment you know
um
normally like within whole live
management and all that behind the
scenes
we don't like you know
like tell like the managers don't tell
us their birthdays and when even if it's
their birthdays
like the actual day they they're not
like hi it's my birthday congratulate me
so
there's like
probably a lot of managers and staff
staffs birthdays that
the talents don't know about and don't
react to
um and that's i guess fine too because
like it's not like they're asking for it
or not like they're sharing it
but um very early on
when i got general as my manager
um i was like
hi
i want to know your birthday
and i want to be ready and put it in my
calendar and then congratulate you
and i think i'm the only one
out of the talents that ever asked her
that
so i got her birthday and i put it into
my calendar
and then
eventually
i saw her birthday coming up and i was
so happy that i knew it
i'm not gonna say when it is but you
know my birthday was coming up and then
i was planning to get her something
from a certain
fancy brand that i know that she likes
but a bit difficult because
i couldn't take her shopping in real
life so i needed something i needed
something that would like fit
size-wise
not gucci but it's somewhere in that
league yeah
yeah it is it's uh something like that
so
um i was like looking looking through
the online shop to see what i could get
for her
and i wanted to you know send it to her
for the online shop thankfully that
worked out and then you know what
happened
you know what happened
thanks to me having it in my work
calendar i put janma's birthday in my
work calendar
gouda actually saw it
yeah and she was like oh
are you
are you like like giving general
anything for her birthday i saw i saw
the birthday
you know like you know like help out i
wanted like you
know chip chip in i'm like all right
okay
all right because you know
same manager
yeah yeah yeah yeah so we shared uh the
cost of the
of the present
and then i sent it
yeah yeah
i sent it over
and then
later on when i met jenna again recently
she had the item you know i was happy to
see that yeah
i just i felt like
i'm really glad that i did that that i
asked for the
birthday
i think you know when you work so so
closely together with someone
you know sometimes i feel like
i want to
you know break that
[Music]
i think it's important to keep
everything professional and all that but
i do want her to feel appreciated and
and like a human you know i don't want
her to feel like she's a machine
to to me
specifically i want her to know that i
see her as a human and that i appreciate
her hard work
yeah so i wanted her to have something
i excited for crunchyroll expo hell yeah
i'm doing a panel with inya
and was doing meet and greet
yeah figuring out uh the times at the
moment
i think
crunchyroll like literally everybody
from whole life english and
indonesia
we'll be at crunchyroll expo we're
taking over
we're absolutely taking over
hope i can get into the meet and greet
and now you have two chances you can try
getting into the crunchyroll meeting
great or you can try getting into the um
kiwawa birthday meet and greet
yay nice you get two chances so many
chances
oh yeah crunchyroll expo is stacked it
really is
yeah you get a nice experience there if
you like home alive
yeah
i hope to see some pictures and stuff
because i won't be there in person
um but yeah guys send me pictures of you
going i want to say
[Music]
the info yeah i need to need to i think
it was already supposed to be out
i'll ask again
[Music]
i think it's
where is it
is it here
[Music]
i don't know where it went
okay i put up
the topic again
i just got informed about another thing
that's gonna
be
announced sometimes
[Applause]
yeah many exciting things um
i can't say anything
yeah but there's always fun things being
planned behind the scenes
um
okay anyway uh thank you lopen here's a
kissy for you
[Music]
yeah
even if you couldn't watch it live
that's all right i uh you're sending a
super chat from australia so i suppose
it was like in the middle of the night
for you and that's okay totally
understandable
yeah thank you though
not danny with the funny i haven't even
started the funny
i'm all
or i'm always doing the funny
piano 4dw incoming poor d
what would that be with scent
chicken scent
just saying because i eat a lot of
chicken not because i am a chicken
man that looks so good though on my
table
[Laughter]
[Music]
when she saw
you smell the gravy
i already said that i know i'm just
saying it ahead of time because once i
say anything like that you guys are
always like oh what did you just say
are you saying that you're a chicken and
i'm like no
i'm not saying that
i'm just
good
you know bring damage control ahead of
time
[Music]
i am confused because this super chat
says uh and i've read hints at it later
on too
this says santa gaslighted me into
thinking drop bears were real thanks for
the stream
and i suppose okay i guess they're not
you know i was thinking like that's kind
of weird because they look exactly like
koalas
is it just you know scary pictures of
koalas and like
like people
like meme it into it being another
animal
i was like
i don't know that's sure if i said
believe sana but she was so serious
about it
i thought she couldn't like lie to me
right
that little [\h__\h]
that's the first time i called her that
uh
this calls for dot dot key i don't know
if anything oh wait are you doing it
that way because of australia
because normally it would be
dot
it's kind of weird
let's scare foreigners it's an
australian meme yeah i understand now
they're photoshopped also it's not even
real pictures because it looks like um
just you know
not so flattering pictures
of
koalas caught
throwing a hissy fit
okay i'm done with the snack box super
chat those yummy
next up
next
[Music]
there we go
how's the 17 people doing are they more
now
how many are you guys 18 now
[Music]
are you chilling guys are you watching
me
are they watching me hopefully on
speaker everybody watches if anybody
brought like an ipad or so they could
like form a circle and watch it together
on the floor
if it was outside it would be nice if
they could even have like a fireplace
grill some marshmallows and some
sausages
doesn't that sound like really fun
having like a kfp
camping
trip
wouldn't that be nice
let's take shifts into the phones
together yeah save battery i'm sure they
oh man
yo if when if they come to stand in line
10 hours before opening time i'm sure
they prepared enough and brought battery
packs mm-hmm yeah
idea of camping scares me
[Music]
i i did it like a few times when i was a
child like specifically with my mom and
once when like a children's camping
um
thingy
camping trip like a big one
uh
yeah but i think if i would do it
nowadays i guess
it would be nice to
um i like i kind of want to do it but if
i were to do it i would probably want
it'd be i wanted to go into the
direction of glamping
[Music]
yeah be like really prepared have like
way more than necessary
uh yeah
maybe even rent
a wooden house that it's not even
camping anymore is it
oh well
yeah glamping glamorous camping
okay we're going to read super chats
guys
cruz thank you and jay swag broke down
question fly perform quiz
thanks for pinky oh yeah oh yeah what is
this
what is the first town you visited after
character creation
and number one state morning number two
flowers number three darken uh flares
and i think saint morning was like the
second one i think
and what is the weakest monster you can
counter number one love wolf number two
mush pang number three i bought
[Music]
i was even two of free
it's probably free yeah i'm pretty sure
it's free
the the bat monster
if you get the one answer wrong i must
sit straight did i get anything wrong i
think i got it right
i think i got it all right it was pretty
difficult though we barely remember it i
got it right let's go oh no i want to
play fly for fun
hi mommy wow today is my birthday happy
birthday
what's your name
at 77 i gave birth
happy birthday
it's weird i want to wish you happy
birthday but that's not even a proper
name feels kind of not so personal
are you 77 years old and you gave birth
to someone
[Music]
i don't think so i don't believe it
nice sprite
okay
thank you
generally
by the way jokes on you i'm actually
sitting straight i'm i just have my legs
like crossed you know like a lady
but besides that i'm sitting straight
actually
ah surprisingly
i am a t
lorenzo
i'm glad to see you again i thought you
were like were you on the vacation or
something didn't see you for a while
the game agreed
thanks for the pinky
what is that
profile picture
dear lord sean
are you here
that is
thirsty and deserves a horny bunk
[Music]
i don't know if you're here but let's
bunk him
bunk
he is here
doko
don't see him
sentenced to bunk
yeah yeah although i will give it to you
it's pretty brave for you to be so
publicly horny
by putting this as your profile picture
ah
i don't have my
my
live charger
wait a second
[Music]
obs what the [\h__\h]
what is that timing the moment i
i plug something into the wall
ops is like baba i'm out of here
hello
that was weird
oh you unplugged your mind no i didn't
[Music]
okay okay okay it didn't like it yeah
that's weird
[Laughter]
no no no no
welcome back amigos
some weird disturbance in the electrical
force you know i wonder if that actually
is like a thing that can happen
just by me plugging in something into
the wall
would it do something like that
i don't think the outlet is overloaded
no not this one
can't be it's not connected to the other
where where all my pc stuff is
try again to find out no
it's possible
that's crazy
weak weak as [\h__\h]
anyway shun says
yesterday was my first birthday with you
i'm very happy to have met you your
charming attitude helped me in moments
when i felt down
man this super chat was way too sweet
and real and normal compared to your
profile picture
i hope to continue supporting my great
yoshi for many years to come could you
please call me a little [\h__\h]
did i maybe already do it i called you
horny and bumped you
but yeah we're calling you a little
horny [\h__\h]
[Music]
i hope that pleases you
you're welcome yeah please continue
supporting me and do something about
that horniness
yeah
thank you thank you soon
it's frankenheim thank you for the red
super chat happy birthday enjoying the
spicy geese please spicy mmm spicy
mmm spicy
i love playing it aina is so sweet like
oh my god
like
sometimes she's like whenever like
something happens
sometimes she's like the only one who
notices and is like
supportive and
and caring
[Music]
so sweet
it's either her or ame
i really appreciate it
it's nice to know that i've got a friend
in them
yeah i love them
so anyway thanks banking time
[Music]
i usually notice when i'm banned with
friends you mean notice
when
you mean toe it's me or towards your own
friends and so on
don't worry about it don't worry about
it if it's about me
[Music]
come right to the newly wet verbs
you finally decided to get married after
a year may your honeymoon be divine and
spicy papadashi forever don't worry
organic already got the honeymoon down
yeah
that was so cute though at the end it
really felt like we were
running through town letting everybody
know
hey this guy is so married now
congratulations
with the bell going
[Music]
with everything that just transpired in
this pretty collab i guess now is a good
time to bring up maybe turn duncan could
sing
unknown mother boos as a collab cover
what what is that a vocaloid song
i don't know this song
[Music]
oh wait
that's that song
i never read the english title properly
wait one second i want to listen
[Music]
to this it is a vocalist song
oh it's a good song
[Music]
yeah welcome makes a lot of very
difficult songs
probably gonna make it to bali soon
i mean i'm not in a hurry because i
already have like you know other things
planned out for the year
like korea
[Music]
oh yeah there's this part that goes like
literally like that
holy [\h__\h] hey i don't know
i don't know if i could even do that
that's insane i was just listening
listening through it
it's quite insane i'll link it in the
chat in case you guys are curious
ghostful turkey mode i guess you could
say so yeah
wow
i mean i could try practice and then
suggest it but
just because of the title i don't know i
would prefer to go for a song that
i really feel like
would fit
us free
um so if it were to be a song that fits
us free i think it has to be more of a
derpy
fun song
yeah
derpy and kaku nagashin and we're done
with this as well let's go
[Music]
next up
okay
next we have holoqueua
i wish i could read super chats as fast
as
that one part in that song
[Music]
but then you know i don't want to even
if i could because it just feels like
i'm being unthankful
i just
zoom through them so fast
feels wrong
it feels wrong
[Music]
let us hydrate everybody
raise your glasses to the sky
and drink
no me
[Music]
for the pinky hey boss i just want to
say we love you and appreciate you
thanks for always working so hard for us
i know you're still working for all that
love and appreciation from a week ago
just want to say how do you know
yeah i'm still working through it but
thank you very much
that's such a sweet message
thank you so much
yeah
i tried to work hard because you guys
also support me so much so i need to
need to even it out you know
i love you guys
thank you dog hood
now we have one two three four pinky is
from denzel vault oh it's one of those
messages again
you guys ready
but for this i must turn off bgm because
it's more dramatic wait do i have like
an
rpg
kind of
it's gonna be hard to find it i'm not
sure if i named it
what is this one
oh that's not it
there we go
[Music]
to a reverend kiara tv your vassal and
humble servant greetings
after our army had approached the walls
of phoenixton a council was held and
lftt the great the duke of kaz
sakanashida strong and saint sodas
keyblade ordered that all with bare feet
should march around the walls of
phoenixton in order that she who entered
it humbly on our behalf might be moved
by our humility to open it us to us and
to exercise judgment upon her enemies
we marched for seven days with bare feet
around that city as the bamboozlers
shouted abuses
from the walls
from the walls above and the sun
scorched down a nose frying without
mercy
but hot wings was appeased by this
humility and on the eighth day she
delivered the city and our enemy to us
with the fall of the walls our chickens
were quick to charge the enemy women and
engage them in combat the bamboozler is
called unawares by our charge made easy
foes for the might of kfb
thus
phoenix and was reclaimed in your name
by sword and chicken
baby
[Music]
what
what's going on
what can someone give me like a summary
like in in normal english
what happened
i read it but i did not know what i was
saying
we surrounded the city
until they are we won
yeah let's go
oh man
yeah mako make a whole like book about
it i said it before i think
i read it and i absorb none of it
exactly i do that a lot like stuff
doesn't enter my brain
unfortunately
and i don't know do you guys have that
too
i like it though it's very dramatic and
i really enjoyed this super chat i just
don't understand really what i'm reading
but i still enjoy it very much it's like
how you guys maybe some of you who don't
understand japanese you still listen to
japanese music and you're like this song
is a [\h__\h] banger and then you don't
even realize what it means sometimes the
lyrics mean something really weird but
you still you still [\h__\h] enjoy it so
much
oh
i agree but i also don't understand
i have to reread pages and classes yeah
me too i when i start reading a book i
read
like the same page over and over and
over and over
oh thank you
thank you very much desavoid for the
report you know what i like the rpg
music
i'm gonna keep it
it has birds birds chirping
so peaceful
i like it
[Music]
nice rpg music
yeah
nice
oh
i feel like we're in a tavern hell yeah
i like that
it's like uh like i'm giving you guys a
quest and the quest is to protect kiwawa
cherish kiwawa
praise kiwawa
[Music]
your reward will be one
pair of leather gloves enchanted by the
holy frog
froggy wow
[Music]
seems like it's been a lot yeah i want
to play i'm rpg now
now now i want to play world of warcraft
actually
i don't
i wouldn't mind playing some world of
warcraft
um
[Music]
world of warcraft
or maybe ah
fantasy i would feel that vibe right now
too
but as you know it's kind of like world
of warcraft has that nostalgic
feeling to me
and final fantasy doesn't really but
it's a beautiful game and all that and
i'll give you that but if i play it like
on stream
it's really like
it's not the typical experience
that i would get normally from playing
on mmorpg privately
so it's completely different and that's
that kind of takes away a lot
for me personally
with world of warcraft even if i stream
it i can still like
look over
that whole streaming aspect
because the whole nostalgia
is so strong that it's so much fun
anyway
you plan on playing any of the
single-player ff games definitely if i
finally get the permission someday
yeah would be nice i'm gonna play
immediately
immediately but currently i can only
play 14 the mmorpg on stream
live for fun i know
don't have life for fun purpose ever
though
no i cannot
[Music]
i keep on asking though
i want to i want to
oh also i need to let you know ah
for like catherine and persona and so on
i'm also still waiting a little bit i
could play the japanese version already
but still need to wait a little bit
longer for english version so i'm not
gonna immediately play catherine after
all it's still gonna take a little bit
so please be patient
but
starting from the first week of august
i want to play something
i don't know what
i don't i really don't know what
[Music]
i'll think about it is something
releasing
um
[Music]
oh yeah i wanted to play tunic
i don't want to play yakuza game
already hopes you mean the one where you
blast millions of enemies
i don't think i would want that to be a
serious i think it would get boring to
be honest
like a one-time stream would be okay or
a two-time stream
but not yeah octopath
i would if i could
so that's a no
a tails off game would be nice yeah
i personally that would be like one of
my top choices
but i don't know about you guys i might
do a poll
[Music]
spray
you know i mean a serious i want to
start a longer series straight i will be
done with immediately
[Music]
okay
well we'll think about it
i think about it i'll get back to you
guys
in a pool
[Music]
okay
i'm getting tired
but probably not as tired as the bros
standing in line for the aniplus cafe
collaboration
after midnight
[Music]
publicly is 34 streams into the game and
only 65
done holy [\h__\h] what is she doing
[Music]
damn i mean it's an mmo so like there's
so much other stuff to do
it's obviously made to be played for a
long time
[Music]
thanks for getting me into the rpg mood
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thanks to the pinky
and despite the recent news i hope that
we can all transfer the time we got to
spend together with you the rest of ian
and whole live in general these moments
are fleeting but hopefully our love and
appreciation for you last forever like a
phoenix love your boss
thank you i agree
[Music]
we have to treasure the time that we
have
together yeah
indeed my nose is feeling
tingling
for a while now i keep on touching it
actually yesterday last night that
reminds me i was watching
i was watching the the console race
stream
it was so cute
ah the models are so cute those tiny
tiny models the smalls
so cute the expression so cute santa did
a great job designing them
and um
i liked the the whole world that they
were into
yeah
they were so huggable yeah
huge heads
i wonder which models have bigger heads
the wealthy ones or the sana
sana models
not sure
like compared like in a ratio between
body and head
[Music]
yeah i saw
he tweeted that he like holy [\h__\h] he
really
he was like close to dying
so
horosifo boy
just like kanouru getting absolutely
tortured by the whole live english
members
but
i mean you guys accept our suggestions
with a really tight schedule you could
just say no
but they all love us too much they can't
turn us down
yeah i will try to not have
such tight schedules
so much anymore
but for the next things you know i think
i think like i gave
honolulu enough time
i thank the proof for stuff they did for
the community hell yeah thank you guys
for working hard everybody who
helps us out with stuff also for all the
you know fan artists and so on as well
who let us use the art for thumbnails
and stuff like that
i'm getting tired why am i getting tired
i think it's the super chat breathing
making myself tired breathing myself to
sleep
soras keep like thank you twilight
vanilla
in the game okay
real hell
[Music]
thank you
casual thank you soon mp one five free
garlic stun cushion rest forage
one duncan
hungry
no i'm just tired
i want to take a nap on my table right
now
[Music]
just gonna sleep
no i was tired already before turning on
this bgm
it's not it's not that i think it's all
i know why because i was outside like
before the stream for a couple hours and
it was so [\h__\h] hot
it's honestly really just the heat yeah
[Music]
it's so hot
yeah i lived a few years in japan with
an ac
i was the best time of my life being
inside in the summer
[Music]
um
oh put a cold towel over the fan
what does that do
normal life aces and eel yes please
i remember last year was it last year
when i was like
hunting last year when i was hunting for
apartments
i checked out like you know
apartments and like
like a more a little bit more expensive
price range you know and even those
didn't really have a seas like like
what you can get sometimes is like a
low-key ac
that gives you in the winter gives you
floor heating and during the summer
there's like
no visible ac in the room but
there's some kind of cooling system in
the ceiling
but it barely does anything
that's what you get in like
more expensive apartments in austria but
usually no apartment comes with
actual air conditioning but i don't know
maybe maybe more and more they will
add that too because they see that
it's really nice to have
how hot is it over there
well recently it's been um
i think it's been like 33 44 45 46
degrees celsius
during the day
but
uh
relatively dry
[Music]
and it's really hot
yeah it is really hot
in northern germany 39 holy [\h__\h] oh
and without a scenes we are bed
but today i was um i was in a like in in
in the other day i was riding in the
subway and subway is pretty cool
totally fine pretty chill inside
but uh overground trans public
transportation i took one today
ew it was disgustingly hot
[Music]
yeah
oh man
all right so i definitely i think the
heat made me tired yeah
that's probably that's gonna be a
problem for a while throughout the
summer i'm sorry guys
um
i'll try to not go outside too much
[Music]
ac fund i was thinking about that but
you know
it's just a little bit something
difficult with how my apartment is like
built
[Music]
and
doing like a normal ac where you have to
make a hole
a hole for the outside wall
i don't think my landlord would allow me
that because it's uh rented only not
bought
and then portable you know
not
fixed acs are usually not so good as far
as i know
i don't know i'm thinking about it but
you know my my my fan is fine my fan
helps me
but no matter what
it might be
on it you guys made me know more about
this kind of stuff but the moment i
turned on
my
fan
my obs turned
itself off but
my fan is connected to a different
electrical outlet
on the other side of the room
i mean
am i using too much energy is it the
same circuit
but why does it not like turn off my
whole pc then and only obs which is you
know
based on
my internet connection
do you think that can be really
connected
[Music]
a slight power well let me test it i'll
turn it off
and it would be funny if it happens
again let me turn it on
[Music]
okay it was fine this time
let's just keep an eye open the next
streams and see if i plug anything in or
out turn anything off or on if something
happens hi chunky wonky
are you happy because mommy
cut a little bit of your butt fur today
mm-hmm
yeah yeah she did because uh
you had some
a small knot
on your butt fur
and i took care of that because i'm a
good mommy
i'm wondering if i should give her like
a proper
a whole trouser trim as you say
because
her butt
is so fluffy i don't know how it does
not get in the way of her pooping
i feel like she should constantly have
dirty
dirty butts but she doesn't actually she
actually is usually
very clean
back there
[Music]
but i think it would help her
a little bit fluffy pantaloons
she's such a fluffy butt
she does
donkeys only has idol meetings how dare
you
yeah i'll get okay yeah sure
she mastered the poof
she used to be much stinkier back in the
day
yeah but then one time
one time when i was gone
my
uh ex-roommate
she
apparently shampooed
concrete which absolutely traumatized
her but after that
she never got that stinky ever again
just one time you know normally you
shouldn't shampoo them with shampoo cats
and all that
dana does get her catching poodle i was
shocked at that
regularly i'm like girl cats don't need
that you know they clean themselves
right
anyway so we did it once for junkers and
after that you know she never got that
stinky again she learned to listen and
she learned the lesson to clean herself
so that we don't have to clean her
i know there's shampoo specifically for
cats but you don't need to clean cats
with that
unless they're they jump into
a puddle of dirty
water outside or
i don't know you spill some oil on them
or whatever
[Music]
no it's really unnecessary
you shampoo dogs yeah but you don't
shampoo cats
you can but you really don't have to
it's so unnecessary
and they probably don't enjoy it
[Music]
yeah
yeah because dogs don't clean themselves
yes but cats do that's why you don't
have to clean them that's
i mean if you
smoothie
specifically especially smoothie
she's so soft and you'll be you'll be
surprised
that i have never ever in my whole life
washed smoothie
and yet she has super clean beautiful
super soft
smooth hair
she does not smell at all no no no no no
not even a tiny [\h__\h] street if
anything she sometimes after she cleans
herself she has that little bit of a
wet cat fur
smell which i like too actually it's not
like wet dog it's wet cat smells
differently than wet dog
indoor cat perk oh yeah that's the thing
like if your cat goes outside
if my cats would go outside i would like
clean their paws maybe and if
there's like a dirty spot in there
um fur okay yeah okay that's a different
story
but if it's indoor cats then
absolutely no need to to uh wash them
[Music]
i brush uh
i brush chunkers
because she needs it if i don't brush
chunkers she gets knots
but for smoothie
fur is like magical
she does not need uh
brushing which is good because she also
doesn't like it
but sometimes i try to
at least a little bit very quickly
before she gets angry at me just like a
like a
few strokes i try to brush her a tiny
bit
when she loses a lot of fur because she
always sheds a lot
i didn't do anything this time
i didn't i didn't connect or disconnect
anything
obs is just being a little [\h__\h] today i
think
obs is just being weird
don't worry
i didn't do anything this time
i did nothing
no no no no
no obviously
i'm sorry
i'm streaming
[Music]
and the rough week with the connection
issues yep the the strain
stream was killed by youtube
what the [\h__\h]
i hope it's gonna get better again
okay continue reading super chat
uh
um
mp15 free garlic extension
okay stop
razz forage one thank you for the pinky
i went skate ice skating recently while
on vacation it turns out the fever night
is the best song to jam out while doing
laughs on the ring ah at one point i had
it on repeat for several laps it was so
good
i can't imagine that yeah
i can imagine that would be
a great song to
go ice skating to or normal like skating
um
like in one of those fancy funky
uh indoor skating rings
the
four
four wheel skating
with they're all four wheels but like
side to side
at the two pairs of skates what do you
call those yeah like a roll of disco
in the atc yeah it sounds like a lot of
fun
yeah
[Music]
i wonder if you can do some
cool tricks raspberry because i remember
when i went ice skating last time
you know 90 percent
or even 95 of the people
who are
at ice skating places whenever i go 95
of the people are just normal people who
can't do [\h__\h] and then there's always
those five percent usually one person
per day
who goes there
you know and actually has some skills
and does some cool flexing and stunts
and some some turns and flips and [\h__\h]
okay maybe not flips they don't do that
when there's so many people around i
guess but there's
always somebody
who actually
can do some cool stuff no not me not me
but that's always nice to see
[Music]
really cool i always wish like oh man i
wish i could do that too
[Music]
yeah
that would be so cool
thank you rest for reach mm-hmm
panopticon thanks for the rental chat
sorry this is late but i wanted to say
how much i enjoyed your concert it was
very emotional seeing you on stage
dancing and singing it was nice to see
you finally realize your dream and got
to show everyone what you were reborn to
do yeah much love thank you thank you
yes
yeah yeah that was just the beginning
just to start but a nice start
into
the things that i want to do
much more often in the future hopefully
i can
do it more often
it would be nice
there's so many so many songs i have in
mind that i want to perform
really nice pgm yeah it's like a rpg gym
i like it too
so thank you panopticon
yeah glad you enjoyed the concert thank
you for watching thank you
a director's cut coming soon
s 17 b 32 donkey shin optimus prime
thank you andres villagra
m
87 thank you for the red super chat yo
long time no red brick last summer
almost a year ago you helped me out with
advice for papers for my solo green
strip oh this year i'm going across
northern europe amsterdam
did i read this before this looks very
familiar to me i think i kind of
read it a little bit while when i saw it
the first time
uh copenhagen stockholm and ending in
berlin i was running oh yeah yeah
recommendations in berlin oh yeah yeah i
couldn't really give
any recommendations
unfortunately because as i said i only
really went to berlin for work
so far um
but i'm sure you'll have a great time
there yeah
thank you for the support thanks for the
red break
enjoy your trip in europe i i'm sure
you'll have a good time you're visiting
some amazing cities there
many of who many of those i have not
seen myself yet and i kind of wanna
yeah
that should
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
chat
i've never been so glad to have stayed
up till 4am for this i have witnessed
ultra pro super late game on kia
takanasi
oh yeah i remember now in this stream i
was [\h__\h] unstoppable i was so good
holy [\h__\h] that was really fun
it actually really feels good to for
once
be good at a game and uh yeah i only got
wins i didn't expect that
i was hoping for like one win
and then every every run was a win
and i was not expecting that that was
fun
[Music]
thank you
ultra noob
yeah i hope you learned something from
me
from my gaming
mm-hmm
unstoppable
there's a level 100
[Music]
okay shut up
why
[Music]
why my connection looks super stable
what could it be
why
why why
my internet is fine
let me check
oh yeah
oh yeah my internet is fine
my internet is very fine
overheating i recently see reception
overheating could be
yeah
maybe
because i actually now don't be mad i
actually left my pc on overnight
i tried to turn it off but then you know
when you sometimes when you turn off
your pc and then you leave the room
and you realize the next day that it did
not actually turn it off because because
because there was some kind of like
something that stopped it from turning
itself off properly
you guys are so shocked but i'm sure a
lot of people keep their pc on a lot
yeah but maybe that's why it's a bit uh
black
all right if i mean next stream if
everything's fine again then it's that
jupiter that's okay sorry for the
interruptions but at least it comes back
immediately so don't worry about it um
ultra milk is a kiss mwah
next up we have
project and knm thank you for the ride
of the chad the mighty phoenix warrior
against the clear way to go dancing
thank you thank you i wonder was that
not the first first win or
[Music]
what because
damn i won four times it was so much fun
thanks for watching i hope you enjoyed
it thank you soon
jim tracy duncan aerogamer
[Music]
avior thank you for your pinky
see if you don't run directly into the
enemies it's way easier
[Music]
are you trying to pick a fight with me
that seems passive aggressive to me
that's super chat
[Music]
can't you you read the wrong one what do
you mean
oh i did oh okay i'll i'll reread it but
um abbier you little [\h__\h]
sorry and project k m i i i read the
message from below i i slipped
below in the line
actually it said she's the video game
bird she's the one who wins
with a music note as if it's a reference
to a song
[Music]
what song is that referencing to
i reacted to that one on stream did i oh
i might have yeah see
i remember now
uh
very don't like game grumps meme
oh i don't know that
oh it makes me feel old again but thank
you
[Music]
i bet it will be longer than 15 hours
total
me getting for the birthday super chance
yep yep i don't know has it been at this
point i mean
getting for the birthday super chats was
not 15 hours but getting for the whole
uh piled up
super chats
i don't know hmm could get close to that
brandon duncan i don't ears dance and
sky wait that's those are flush super
chat side things
tai chi thank you for the rest of the
chat with chunkers sleeping emotes
actually chunkers is
indeed
sleeping behind me on the floor right
now
which makes me think taiji
you sent this super chat on the 13th of
july i think you you like
looked into the future didn't you
you knew that the moment when i would
read your super chat chances would be
sleeping behind me
and yes she is
i'm so cute
it's okay she looks so fluffy
yeah she's becoming one with the floor
she learned from inya
she heard that inya sleeps on the floor
she was like i gotta try that
[Music]
okay
wow
already cleared so much
i wonder how much i have left
porto was closed right no super chats
yeah okay
super mario bros deluxe
there we go
next up
is
[Music]
this
come by thank you yes i am valuing
only been two hours so far i would say
i've been pretty fast three more streams
above 300.
how many did i have in the beginning
[Music]
i'm tired
this game has some back seating in the
next level well but i kind of deserved
it
1 4 16 at the start
i only read 116. oh god okay
okay yeah the first 50 minutes i tended
it i didn't start reading until the
first hour
that is true
so i read 160
in one hour
basically
which sounds a lot better
[Music]
thanks for the rest of the channel
um
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
or kia the mother of chickens i found
where the mail address ah it wasn't hard
actually ah
seems like i always get scolded when i
super chat you
ha ha sorry my chicken head doesn't help
have a nice mario stream and you're the
one who asked about like oh how do i
send you fan mail what
there you go you found it i'm looking
forward to seeing your fan mail
half a year later
or maybe earlier who knows if i
if i get to um meet
jenna
beforehand then you know she might bring
me some stuff earlier than expected
yeah yeah
so think hard about what you're gonna
write into that maybe even add a
christmas card
to it just you know
ahead of time think ahead
mm-hmm
maybe in happy new year's card as well
[Music]
why don't they simply send you the stuff
because that would mean that they would
send me
one letter
what per per week or per two weeks or so
it's just stupid
i understand that they don't do it
better to just collect it but maybe
don't collect it only twice per per year
maybe once every two months or so
but it's okay
it's easier to send in bulk um
probably should send you a christmas
card right now yeah exactly
[Music]
everybody who wants to send me something
for christmas send it
[Music]
my
yeah i'm not kidding
[Music]
yeah i got tired
wake up oh god
oh my god
i rubbed my face so strong i can't see
clearly anymore
i don't have an energy drink i don't
have one
[Music]
messages messages messages so many super
chat messages to be read well not here
tenshu i will write nothing here and you
can just go on to the next switch i had
knowing that i saved you some reading
and you got closer to cat pads and fool
and taskmaster and oh [\h__\h]
i appreciate the sentiment though thank
you
it did not help that much but yeah it's
alright
it's a jerk
so i like it i like the humor
i just don't have the energy to laugh
take a power nap if necessary oh you
should know that my power naps take
one hour minimum
if not 2.
[Music]
degenerated
i saw your fruity concert so late thank
you for your amazing fruity concert by
the way i saw your cafe branch finally
come to korea
is it for your market research wait your
kentucky fry phoenix thank you
market research yeah definitely that
will be very helpful
i want to see
actually it would be really interesting
to see how popular that kiwawa fried
chicken is
compared to the desserts because like
i mean i totally understand that if you
go there
let's say cheesecake is not your thing
but ami is your oshi
you might probably still order the
cheesecake because it comes as it looks
like it comes with an amicard and just
you know for the sake of it because
shizuoshi
but still like as we said before i feel
like the fried chicken is like
would be a very popular choice even if
your oshi's not kiwawa
[Music]
and then they eat the chicken and then
they turn into a chicken themselves
and become
my employees that would be great
that would be best
[Music]
but i believe
i will i will believe
that also a lot of the people a majority
of the people who buy the kiwawa fried
chicken
buy it because
their oshie is actually kiwawa
yeah
i believe in it
i want to believe i believe
yeah
so hope you can get something in the
shop i hope you can visit it garden park
and then report back to me
eh
thank you you're the one who made the
current
and loading background by the way i'm
probably going to go back to documents
loading background at some point but
currently ah for some reason i felt like
putting pudding putting
something new
in there yeah cause it's really a great
great pixel loading screen in my opinion
i want to use some
other people's
work as well
sometimes
[Music]
yeah the kfp city is really cool as well
i should use that one too
i'm not going to clean them
[Music]
uh what
how do i read that phoenix deplete thank
you the monster envy
[Music]
mr kyle brown thank you
every now the cult thank you for the
pinky my ocean is amazing not only is
she ceo of kfp
idol performer and part-time warrior but
now she has successfully a career as a
game
so so good thank you
it's just even if that were so it's just
because i am so charismatic
and so good at promoting games that they
want me to be their game journalist you
saw how good i was at promoting tales of
a rise
i'm good at sponsorships
so yeah that's the only reason why i
would be a game journalist
and i would
i would
i would be honored to be that
for them
in a different way
[Music]
i am promoting something next week
yeah there's a sponsored stream next
week
[Music]
did you see guys
it's called alice fiction
i thought it looked interesting so i was
like hell yeah why not it looks cute
[Music]
yeah yeah
we've got not with her but like separate
streams
i'm doing uh i think i'm just doing a
normal
game stream
where i play the game i think
most likely probably
it looks really cute yeah
i am interested
you guys could check it out ahead of
time too if you wanna but maybe just
wait until after my stream because maybe
there's a link that you guys can use i
don't know though
maybe
and maxwell the first time soon
[Music]
entry log week one it's been a week
since the last incident at kfp good
thing as tacos can turn into anything
and anyone
really
it was discovered who i replaced
something will begin i must be careful
what i say or do
i must make it back to mama ina
well i'll gladly
kick your butt
and catapult you back to her
right in front of her eyes
and then tell her
[Music]
what you did
the shenanigans that you did at kfp
oh yeah she will be very displeased i'm
telling you
[Music]
anyway
pack the tackle out
yeah
no it's not a win
no
[Music]
i'm gonna go get him
i will no more cookies for him uh-huh he
won't get any more cookies
i know you want those cookies
[Music]
i'm gonna make the
korean bros tire to the ones who are
standing in line
where are my 17 legendary peeps
already
don't fall asleep
don't fall asleep guys don't don't
[Music]
they're probably more than 17 nalia
oh my god
stay woke
oh [\h__\h] it's getting to me
change me gm
[Music]
the recent event i realized something i
have been watching kendra for almost two
years ooh joined membership for 19
months sending super chats here and
there traveled abroad and even joined
the meet and greet but i never said how
feel that
oh
so here i go i'm gonna say it
[Music]
here it comes from the bottom of my
heart you probably already know what i'm
going to say already but it needs to be
said okay then any second now i'm ready
now here it comes this is the moment now
i love
why
oh it's too loud sorry
you know the thing is
around the end of this super chat there
were several
like
hyphens
that you could have just replaced with
you
like even with all the rambling in this
super chat
at the end you could still fit it in if
you would have just gotten rid of the
hyphens
it's like you did it on purpose
did you perhaps do it on purpose
huh
genma didn't fit
yeah but it's free hyphens there
it could just be you
i love you
it feels like this is on purpose
kind of rude
well you know what then you won't get an
i love you back
yeah
you don't say it to me then you i won't
say it to you
stupid sassy [\h__\h]
[Music]
as you've learned persona would be so
long it would take half a year or more
but there's a similar and shorter game
by atlas called
sessions fe it also has idols
yeah i'm aware of the game and i already
could have played it like ages ago i
always had permission for it but
[Music]
after looking into it uh a long time ago
i didn't feel like i wanted to stream it
yeah
maybe privately i want to play but not
stream it i think
sorry
i'm sorry
maybe one day if i
get really desperate for
games
to play
or i'll play it properly and i'll let
you know what my opinion was
[Music]
but i would love to play more fire
emblem games to be honest if they bring
out like
they'll probably release one next year
right
i'll play it i promise i'll play it
[Music]
i'm already excited now
zeno x zxc
thank you
this is the biggest draw of
fe we've had for a while oh really
i heard that normally it comes out more
often
oh i know it was a pinky so
he doesn't get a kiss for it
[Music]
i did read it though
are you tired too patsy
are you a little bit confused by being
tired
it's okay the heat is getting to me and
to you is probably the tiredness getting
to you
it's okay shake hands shake hands
[Music]
swc ronin says i've been fried i'm so
happy to support such a kind earnest
skilled and dedicated person been around
since october 2020
i used to always be a lurker in chat but
you got me talking a little more yeah
thank you
for everything you do
thank you so much thank you for being a
member for so long you look so delicious
i wanna take a bite of you yeah did you
guys know
speaking of memberships did you guys see
or know
that apparently
youtube lets us do
three years no two years and
not three years and four years now
perks membership like um emotes like
thingies
badges
yeah
because up until now the maximum was two
years for whatever reason i don't even
like youtube has been around for so long
and i'm sure memberships have been
around for a while
or have they when memberships
implemented in youtube does anybody know
but it's nice to like have something to
look forward to afterwards i just don't
know
what to do with you guys
because
what are we gonna do after you become
a phoenix chicken
should we start the cycle again
yeah uh reverse
i'm not sure
maybe in the member stream we can
discuss it
become ashes it's just a pile of ashes
hmm i don't know what i will have to
think about a golden egg
nice
[Music]
or maybe
no wait
uh maybe maybe uh that that chicken that
you become at two years but with a suit
and then and then in the fourth year
just a pile of ashes
i don't know something like that
well think about it but i'll get you
guys opinion on it definitely
we can do a poll as well
but for now
it will be two years for the first
uh eggs
soon
uh in september
[Music]
that will be the first accomplishment so
we're not we're not too stressed about
it we don't have to
think so far ahead
yeah at the earliest it would be 20 23
september that anybody gets the free the
third year badge so
lots of time to think about it yeah
time flies it really does
it just got fried i'm so far behind don
firey i'm really happy that you're part
of it to begin with thank you so much
chicken run
nah but maybe a different chicken movie
so thank you for the plush chats guys gd
duncashion jules vern 1668
aoyama blue mountain thank you
thanks for the pinky
you won't get this super chat for a
while yet but i just wanted to ask you
if you had the time to check out the
projects on viva la kiana there's a song
i'd really love for you to watch it
means a lot to me i hope you like it
happy belated birthday
wait which one
i saw
i'm pretty sure most of it
which which specific one
[Music]
my chat stopped moving
are you guys just quiet oh
oh it's moving again
[Music]
huh
what was the website again
kfp
okay
i keep on forgetting
i should bookmark it
aviva
[Music]
wait where ah
no by now i've heard the orchestral one
i don't know if i heard the favorite one
wait a second
is that oh
i didn't know about this one
i don't think i can play it
probably or maybe i mean
i don't know because it's uh probably
it's sampled
it's sampling the my favorite things
melody i'm not sure how strict that is
i want to listen to it though
okay i'll i'll listen to it now
i like i like the instruments
ooh
it also has like a little bit of an rpg
feeling
kind of like also a medieval feeling
[Music]
these are things that are potential
loves
[Music]
about me
ah i love the art too it's beautiful
i think i know this female voice
oh
[Music]
beautiful
i love the the song from
sono music
[Music]
and the chickens are so cute
i'm not sure if that's how chicken legs
work though
if they can bend like that
[Music]
oh
and then i don't feel
so bad
so nice
oh
harmonies
oh let's go that was beautiful
that was beautiful i know you guys
didn't hear it but
that was beautiful thank you
oh so many people were saying that in
that one oh
very pretty voices you got there
he watched long nice
yeah very cute and i really love that
song great choice great choice of a song
thank you adigam thanks i i somehow
missed that one
[Music]
thanks for asking thanks for reminding
me
can't miss something like that
okay back to super chatters because i
need to zoom through them thank you so
much patsy thank you oh kfb for doing
stuff like that for me thank you
you guys are so so so so so so charming
it's such a sweet song
you're so cute
martin ate
[Music]
so
for getting no pets from guava
[Music]
for the pinky you made the boss a race
for you what an aussie
wait what did that didn't i end up
streaming
like in kind of a rage quit
[Laughter]
didn't get very far
okay it was kind of embarrassing but
[Music]
i will practice the next time i'll be
better but i feel like you guys should
be grateful because it's a very precious
thing
to a chance an opportunity to see
someone
so bad and a game like this
and a mario game
like start from the very bottom
you should be honored to see it because
it's such a rare experience and then one
year later you'll see me being a [\h__\h]
pro at it and you'll be like
i raised that girl
and you'll have to try to take credit
for it even though you [\h__\h] roasted
me to hell
when i started out and made fun of me
but i think honestly it's in general
funny anyway to see someone be so bad at
it
i don't understand why anybody would
complain about it i think it's funny
[Music]
i thought it was funny i mean
no at some point i got really annoyed
but i think it's funny to see someone be
so bad at mario
yeah
well anyway i will i will improve just
like i approved of holocure
you don't believe me well i will prove
it to you
someday
[Music]
surely i will
i will i will
thank you thanks for the recipe thanks
for the applause at least taiji because
he never writes anything in his super
chats he at least also can't roast me
i love that
[Music]
brandon
cruz
[Music]
okay
done with the super mario super
[Music]
i turned them off for the mario party
collab
so next we have the new hairstyle reveal
this one
you guys for the longest time did not
understand what i was
gonna be revealing
or surprising you with and even when i
put out this thumbnail to be honest when
i made this puppet i was like yeah bit
i guess this is already pretty obvious
what it's gonna be
and then
i put up the reservation thinking that
everybody will be like oh okay it's an
it's a new outfit reveal or something
like that
but even after putting it up you guys
are still like oh i wonder if she's just
singing with herself
maybe that's what she recorded oh she
pre-recorded herself so she's singing
with herself
i'm like eh you're still not getting it
[Music]
[Applause]
listen we may be dumb well thank god
dad you don't only
make fun of me for being [\h__\h] at games
and stupid but finally here we have
proof that you guys
are not that smart either exactly
i thought that everyone was pointing at
the logo no the error was supposed to be
like oh
i turned into this on the right side
from this to this
i thought it was pretty obvious
[Music]
is
didn't even notice the silhouette oh my
god that's next level
mm-hmm
we always have been bird brains are we
not
i would agree with that yeah
surprise
because you guys are such bird brains so
it was such a big surprise to you guys
then and that was fun
[Music]
i only now notice there's a silhouette
oh my god
not even looking closely at the
thumbnails that i put so much work into
a chunky monkey bye bye she's she woke
up and left the room i'm sorry i want to
give you a hug
no she's ignoring me
you know i have to
admit something
something happened yesterday that i felt
like a really really really really
really really really really really
really really really bad cat mom
[Music]
it's happened with strong grace
i feel so bad for it
[Music]
well
i have a balcony okay
and um
last night
[Music]
um
i had the balcony door open
[Music]
and then i closed it
and she was still outside and i didn't
notice
and then
i actually like i went into my office i
closed it because i was like okay i
gotta record something now that was
after the stream
[Music]
after a council stream i had to record
something
and because i didn't want the outside to
hear so i closed the balcony door
and um
it didn't i mean the recording didn't
take too long
but
she was
i don't think she was out there for
a while but because i had headphones on
i wouldn't have heard if i
shut up
shut up i wouldn't have heard if i
uh if she would let me out and all that
but then i took the headphones off and
then i was you know
i was you know about to leave my office
and then i hear some distant meows and
i'm like chunky monkey why does that
sound so distant
and i go over to the balcony and i'm
like oh no
this never happened to me ever before
i never did this before and i'm so sorry
she she desperately me out like meow
meow
[Music]
at least it wasn't hot because like it
was already at late late late at night
it was just chill outside
no i'm so sorry too don't don't be mad
at me i was so sorry and then i opened
the door and i'm like oh my god i'm so
sorry john grace and she like runs in
and
and i immediately i immediately gave her
like one of those hi
i immediately gave her one of those
licky snacks you know the the liquid
slurp snacks
immediately like i picked her up i
immediately brought her over to my bed
and gave her a snack there and then i
gave her the strongest hug and pit pads
the moment i picked her up and gave her
like uh like the hug
she she purred so strongly like as if
she was so relieved she was like
and gave her the snack and so on and you
know then afterwards
after a few minutes
you know she calmed down
i calmed down
so
um late at night i actually i sat on the
balcony
to have a snack
um it was like already really [\h__\h]
late and
i sit down
this is actually funny because i sat
outside and then i see shonkers at the
um at the frame of the door
sitting
not moving a single pole outside of the
frame of the door and
dramatically endlessly meowing
meow meow meow meow i don't know if she
was trying to tell me to get back inside
because she was worried about me or
because she was desperately meowing
because she wanted to be with me she was
scared without me or she wanted to go
outside but she didn't want to be like
locked out again
i don't know what she was she was she
was endlessly meowing and then i was
like okay let's see what happens if i go
inside and the moment i stepped a foot
back inside
she immediately stopped meowing
[Music]
that was funny like she just really
didn't want me to be outside so yeah
yeah she was probably like careful yeah
the door suddenly closes exactly
yeah
she probably was worried that the claw
the door would close on me or so
that's so sweet she worried about me
[Laughter]
that's when i truly knew that she has
forgiven me she doesn't even know that
it was my fault probably
she's so sweet man
oh man but you know today she's already
back to normal she already forgot what
happened yesterday
but i felt so bad about it you have no
idea you know how much i love my cats i
felt so bad about it
i gave her an extra amount of cuddles of
course
[Music]
it's like the video of the cat that
tried to save its owner from drowning in
the bathtub yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
my cats check up on me too when i take a
bath or so yeah they're like what you
doing
[Music]
they look over the
over the bathtub
like they they stand on two legs and
they look over and they're like when
you're doing mommy
when you're doing the uk
and then they sit in the bathroom until
i'm done with my bath
[Music]
yeah i really felt bad about it
i feel like
such a bad cat mom for that moment even
though i'm not okay but like it was
really dark and the thing is i saw
smoothie inside
and
jonker's you know chuckerson generally
doesn't like to be on the balcony that
much like she doesn't go out there even
when i'm out there she normally doesn't
go out there that much she would she
would only like spend like two seconds
and then run inside again
so you know i thought okay i see
smoothie inside so tronkers is probably
inside too like she she doesn't even
go there on her own that often anyway
[Music]
no
just because of how her habits are
normally but i'm sure
i'm showing you know when i think about
how scared she must have been oh
it breaks my heart
[Music]
foreign
um she thought she did something wrong
you punished her for it no i don't think
so no no no no she doesn't have that
kind of understanding she wouldn't
she knows she would never do something
wrong nothing she does is something
wrong
how would a cat know anyway if i'm not
scolding her for anything no no no no i
don't think she even thinks that way
[Music]
anyway gotta read super chats we're
gonna read these now
i don't know how many those are
eyes are okay all right all right all
right all right all right let's go
[Music]
has lied down in her spot again the same
spot
[Music]
i don't want to be too loud then
um
[Music]
i think you can finish the super chat in
under 1.5 hours if you don't tangent
heart
well i'll finish it under 1.5 hours
oh as you said but yeah i'll finish it
way under 1.5 hours then
start a challenge i'll take it as a
challenge
let's go that's what he said
[Music]
hmm
kfb dumpster thank you for
four red super chats what the [\h__\h] what
is this
lady kiwawa you probably don't remember
but to answer if i still want your
streams admittedly not as regularly as
i'd like but i catch the archives when i
can i'm bought a slave to work and it'll
be that way until the day i quit you're
the first i've ever considered an ocean
and kfp is the first time i felt like i
belonged to a community and that fact
will never change in spite of how busy
or inactive i am you will always have a
place in my heart you have been my
motivation and viva la chiana.com is a
physical proof of that it's the first
time i've built the front end of a
website oh
something i've always dreaded learning
in the past whoa i don't usually talk
about my feelings so i will counteract
that by resetting my first ever super
chat to you ah
oh my god
[Music]
blah blah blah blah
thank you
thank you beta licks oh you're here now
too
hey
thank you
thank you so much for working on the
website and we're still trying to be
there to watch the the archives yeah i'm
glad you're at least still interested in
me
that is a big relief thank you so much
[Music]
nice latin so i'm assuming that you
obviously speak fluent latin right you
didn't just copy paste that from
somewhere
right that's pretty impressive pretty
cool
pretty awesome love you quinoa
i love you too but only if you come to
my streams
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you so much
i appreciate it nice to see you hope
you're enjoying it
and i hope that
work
will be less stressful for you
in the future
and the devil guard and donkey shoot is
there a hashtag you want us to use for
the annapolis stuff
[Music]
no
not in particular you can just use um
kfp
hashtag kfp and you can just also tag me
in a reply as the others have done so
[Music]
the last thing i remember is falling
into the fryer is this heaven because i
hear the voice of an angel singing oh
thank you sweet
unfortunately on that day and my
my voice was pretty [\h__\h] later on
um
sorry i wish i could have done better
next time i'll hopefully
feel a little bit better
throat wise
thank you i'm glad you liked it anyway
[Music]
oh
no message
why
why why
but thank you thank you so much for the
support
[Music]
well there you go right so freeze
i know you couldn't hold it back
oh that's okay i love you too i guess
now that you finally said it
a little chicken
you're chicken
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's not me being done it's because
it took him
so much pressure and time
to actually say it
coward
[Music]
yeah but with so much passion in the end
though i mean look at those exclamation
marks
so much passion
i appreciate that i i i feel it
yeah you're like screaming into my ear
like literally popped my ear
[Music]
tensions are inevitable what tangents i
don't know what you're saying
tapioca dancing mp1500
[Music]
here's my paycheck it's not like i
wanted to listen to a cute phoenix sing
beautiful songs anyway
it's not like i wanted you to listen
anyway you know i actually i wanted to
so thanks for being there
yeah
[Music]
oh well i mean
if you made an mv with my whole fast
performance there's an obvious reason
why it got taken down because it's paid
content
um so
yeah that's that
but you're welcome to make something out
of my public a birthday concert that's
publicly for free on my channel
you can do something with that if you
wanna
[Music]
uh how ironic yeah
very ironic
thank you spanking time
spice you can talk about chicken papa
duncan bird donkey shouldn't be diving
[Music]
can she become somehow even more
beautiful and elegant the answer is
somehow yes she very much can love the
look love the songs and most importantly
love kiwawa even if the hairstyle may be
a dead flag one more repurpose worth
that look
i really don't think so
because it looks different than the
typical one
i mean
the braid is
not the same ouch also i have you know i
was wearing thongs today flip flops
and i
i i got like a
you know where the where the flip flop
is between your big toe and the one next
to it
it like rubbed it open and then i had
an open wound so it hurts
yeah
anyway yeah it's not the brains braids
it's the ponytail but still i feel like
it looks different mine looks way more
like girly not like a mommy
but whatever
[Music]
i just thought i saw casper for a second
but it was just a leaf
being blown by the wind
oh my god
yeah maybelline thanks for the rest of
the chat working on the courage to ask
the cutest girl at oktoberfest to dance
around the main pole along with my
fellow chickens oh wait when you say
dance around the maple
for some reason i imagined
um
you know dancing
with the maypole like a like a
lego
is there a proper term for a stripper
pole but i guess we probably just mean
hand in hand around the pool in a circle
like that
[Music]
a pole dancing that's what i mean
but uh i think you probably didn't mean
it that way so i don't want to imagine
it like that but it would be funny
it would would be funny i guess
[Music]
uh
no what do you mean mind always like
[\h__\h] you for that
has nothing to do with that
it's just i don't know what to call it
because let's be honest that's the most
like
you know
you know well-known reason for it to be
used
huh
[Music]
it's not my first language
you suck
[Music]
i know a maple is different
but the word pull in my head you know
you know the things it does to me
ah
you guys suck
stop making fun of me
oh no
nice hair attention good to see you papa
is quite the hair stylist no no no no no
no no no no no no i huka papa did a
great job um putting it like
into reality but
i gave very exact instructions for this
hairstyle
that was me
that is 100 me yeah
so you better praise me for it
thank
you yeah maybe thank you soon and thank
you for putting a weird thought into my
head
thank you very much
[Music]
to be honest we're much so much worse
about it yeah i think so too
like i say things that i mean totally
innocently and you guys are like
phrasing
that phrasing phrasing which obviously
means that you guys are thinking about
it in a weird way whatever i said
even though it wasn't meant to be like
that yeah
apple thanks for the pinky love the new
hairstyle so cute i think i'm glad you
like
it nice surprise right
i'll be wearing it a lot in the uh
coming weeks and months probably it
seems like most of you guys prefer it
over the complete updo
so
yeah i'm glad you like it so much
mp153
thanks for pinky the new hair makes you
look so pretty for real this hairstyle
is actually one of my new favorite
hairstyles that you have now great
choice
thank you
i wanna do so many different hairstyles
but at this point now um there's i guess
there's only one major hairstyle that
i'm still
missing that i haven't done yet because
i've done
fluffy long hair like i have right now
i've done uh long straight hair in the
kimono i've done spiky long
twin tails
i i should maybe do short twin tails at
some point but i've done
uh braids
i've done uh an updo i've done a side
do
braid with a french braid
i need to sneeze
thank you
yeah i guess we're missing like a
ponytail yeah yeah and oh actually also
a short
uh cut
like a above
above above shoulders hairs down
oh yeah those two those two
but once i have those two i am i'm gonna
get more creative
mm-hmm
[Music]
short hair going to be amazing
i'll be very very picky with that too
though because i want it to look a very
specific certain way
hmm
m
[Music]
yeah yeah i don't really think he's a
real sailor moon animator though
i love that you can get so much input
for it
yeah at least for everything after
the default outfit
yeah yeah
that's noise
um property says this was a great
surprise this breathtaking the
breathtaking beauty kiana got an act apt
new spicy mommy hairstyle god i love it
sang songs for your daughter and for
santa nana causing my ceiling to leak a
bit on you and then went for blood yeah
okay the best always fun thank you
thank you thank you glad you enjoyed it
even though my voice was a bit [\h__\h]
but i tried my best anyway and i really
wanted to sing astro girl i really
really like astro girl so much
appropriate ah i didn't know what it
stood for
ah so okay i see
[Music]
yuria that's so sweet but i don't think
i agree with that but thank you
let's sing astro girl again sometime
i love it so much
um
cruise thank you so much
thank you so much hope you're doing well
maybe another cold dance shines and
loopers beats duncan liver liver duncan
conduction flaming pants
donkey
[Music]
wow
thank you
next stray and sorry you know normally
under normal circumstances i would have
loved to continue with straight today
but i have to read super chats
i'm not sure when i will continue
hopefully soon
i just felt like you know i can't let
them
you know lie around in the back for too
long but then again
i want to turn them off for every stream
you know a girl's gonna make
make money
the girls gotta
bring in the cash
for her cats
[Music]
need that bread yeah
the girl's gonna eat
yeah jago needs his dough yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
that's it that's exactly it
so
straight super chats
and now let me change the bgm it's
making me go crazy
what do we have here
[Music]
those are the pixel pgms i got for hulk
here
how about this one
huh
[Music]
no all this is making me fall asleep
audio's duck
dot japan
what do you want
something that doesn't make me fall
asleep
house how about house
house
is house just house in japanese
bgm
um
[Music]
i don't think it really understands what
i mean with house this this says
uh
bgm for when you're under
like when you're announcing the results
for being under third place
third place of a race
and i can see that i can imagine that
with this btm and now in the first place
we have
takanawa with her daisy and the stupid
card that she always has because she
never gets the new one
on the second place we have estonia
oh what about this one
this actually a house maybe
[Music]
wow
it's actually cool
it's pretty cool
[Music]
you think that's specific there's
another one that says
uh for announcing the results of being
first in a race
[Music]
yeah that actually does sound like mario
kart doesn't it i think it's a
referencing to that
[Music]
[Applause]
that's funny
i liked the one track but what about
this one
[Music]
no
um
[Music]
are you stuck
it's nice but not really something i
want to play when i read super chats
check new house dance
music
no
i'm not really actually that big of a
fan of normal house i guess i really
like tropical house though
i think
this is supposedly
mid tempo tropical house
it's kind of weird
i don't like it
i'm surprised i actually don't like the
results for once
i'm gonna go with one of the first ones
i heard the first proper one
[Music]
a show
yeah whatever anything we'll do
where was i
oh it was nowhere right i didn't even
start yet
straight up
cruise donkey shoot and strive to fight
on kashun
[Music]
i pre-ordered this game too can a cafe
employee have time off to play
even if you don't approve of time off we
still love you no well you could play
the game at the same time as me on the
side but you still have to pay attention
to what i do and write in the comments
section sometimes okay
but uh generally
the best thing to do probably when
you're struggling with
uh having no time to play games you
should probably just play at the same
time time as i play
cocoon patsy thank you and trevor g
thanks for two pinkies after the kia
dolce i was still admiring your new
cock-a-doodle-hair dude
why are you calling it cock-a-doodle
hairdo
and while being entranced by your new
style and naturally beautiful features
like your eyes and lack of nose it
dawned on me that the reason i love you
and you bang so much is because they
look exactly like the vein of a feather
ah
no clue who if that was intentional but
the way everything is in this new mommy
hair cell strikes straight for my heart
in just plain birdie
i think i know what you mean
i think
well
since we talked so much about this new
hairstyle i i'm gonna just
put it on
now
to me
too
yeah i think i can see it but don't most
of my bangs look like that
anyway
but i can see it i think yeah you mean
it looks like a feather right
oh
oh thank you not so obvious oh okay but
this one's more obvious yeah
i can see it
oh
thank you so much i'm collecting monkey
could it be that you have once again
fallen in love over me once again
[Music]
i got you curled
around my finger is that how you say it
wrapped around my finger
close enough close enough
close enough
same thing
uh
[Music]
foreign
and my room is getting way too dark so
let me turn on the lights now now maybe
obs will turn itself off when i do that
but
i'll be right back okay
and i'll give chunkers a belly wrap okay
really quickly
obvious seems fine
it's looking good
it's like almost as if i i just turned
on the light and did nothing else
obs was fine right
don't want to have a longer cat break oh
i i wish my whole life was a cat break
are highly intelligent darius
did you see that guys
so that means i am highly intelligent
highly intelligent yes yes i am
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i
agree yeah must be
thank you
um
for the pinky
yeah
first thank you for all your hard work
please be sure to also take good care of
yourself secondly wanted to apologize
for it or if any of my comments super
chats have been inappropriate i will try
to behave better in the future cheers
i don't recall anything being
inappropriate
was there something
i think it was probably dijobo
i think you are fine
please start acting it
okay
logical paradox usual room
let me just quickly
also time you out
use your room for it
three weeks you little [\h__\h]
no that makes me very angry very heated
oh [\h__\h]
how dare you
[Music]
the chat kiana you always shared the
energy and spread sunshine with okay i
already just shook them up
i don't like this piece yeah
[Laughter]
i don't like it uh
let's just type in luke bgm
no genre surprise me
surprise me
oh
[Music]
i like that
oh
it gets better
[Music]
[Applause]
it lifts my spirits
[Music]
oh
wow
okay i know it has some
it has some weirdness in it but it also
lifts my spirits
so i want to play it
okay let's go ahead says kiana you
always share the energy and spread
sunshine with all of kfi i really
enjoyed it also like to tell all the kfp
employees i have an idea to show our
strength and how we can be dominant in
the world it is to make santa's channel
reach 1 million subscribers
all
by
the kfb the power of kim fee
uh that sounds difficult
that sounds difficult but i think a lot
of you guys are already subscribed to
her anyway yeah yeah
i mean who knows
maybe maybe in the future people will
still subscribe to her uh but yeah one
million is a little bit difficult
[Music]
i'm pretty ambitious
but you guys i recommend you to
subscribe to her even even you know
if it makes no sense because now
literally yesterday was basically her
last stream right
or like today i don't know yesterday
today today i guess today i guess it was
today
the the sandbox stream and then the next
one is on the
31st
but yeah
um
so just to show her some love you know
already sub there you go i thought so
um
[Music]
or even more than subscribing just you
know watch the vlogs that you haven't
watched yet
but i guess you have a lot of time
because the vlogs will stay up so maybe
actually don't watch them now
but watch them later like spread them
out a lot so that you always have some
sanana content
don't watch it all at once
[Music]
now turns and explains inexplicably
into a cat now needed his bucket more
than anything
the narrator probably
the narrator or the
yeah rita
[Music]
yeah you think that the
sales parabol is involved in this
um
is the cat
what a conspiracy theory
i think jackson deserves the tinfoil hat
for this one not me
thank you and jackson for that input
i don't buy it
[Music]
ultimo mk 203
there is ladies
i stand before you with but one humble
quote request
of utmost importance may i lo your lowly
servant ask you one last question
featherdoco
do you mean do you mean the the one from
like uh the meat and green dookumi
[Music]
i actually did see it today
i saw it
and i unpacked it i even took a photo
it was in fact in the one of the
extra boxes
that was sent to me like they sent most
of the gifts in one big box but then
there was one really really really flat
piece of
uh
cardboard
like really flat like literally just
folded
one piece of cardboard into a lengthy
thing
and i i thought that it would be in
there
yeah
it was in there
and it's not damaged or anything it's
perfectly healthy
and beautiful looking
i had a feeling it was in there it
wasn't there so no worries i got it it's
all safe yeah it looks really pretty
yeah all good
thank you thank you very much
no no no need to worry yeah they the
staff is reliable
they sent me everything properly don't
worry about it
thank you
for the lovely gift it's a really big
really long feather
it looks really really really
vibrant orange i like it
[Music]
thank you
garden park
why is it crying so much what did i do
what what happened with the baby it
cried so often
are you good was it in the pre-chat or
something
thank you thank you soon evan's el
danger
i am a tea
hunt
you can't
i tried to beat i know i'm wait that was
the wrong button ah there you go thank
you
andre santos
i during the
ah when the stream was dead ah
okay understandable
and brandon thank you soon thank you
you're as beautiful as the 10 minutes i
lost you
it was it felt like longer than 10
minutes
but like endless eternal
black friction
tickets
thank you
thank you for the pinky it catches me
off guard every time i read this one on
the stream potential calls out my name
while i'm at work my co-workers get keep
giving me where it looks as i look at
the stream every time
well
i'm not sure that's my fault the fact
that you're watching my stream during
work in the first place probably makes
them
wonder about you but
i think
i think you can continue watching my
streams doing work proudly
represent kiwawa
yeah i don't think it's you know not my
fault but i think you can continue you
should continue maybe tell them about me
yeah
tell them the deeds
thanks yeah but nice workplace you got
there where you can watch streams means
you
have enough time
i hope you're paying proper attention to
the important things in life aka me
yeah yeah yeah
um
[Music]
the concert was spectacular oh my god
there's still birthday super chat smith
what the [\h__\h] you live in the past or
something
the concert was spectacular and i hope
that uh it was a happy day for you early
july was really tough month personally
but you did manage to bring a smile on
my face and even happy tears love you
kiara
i'm happy to hear that and i could help
you for a rough time love you too
well well wow wow you guys also helped
me for a rough times
yeah
so it's nice we can help each other
thank you very much
thanks for reminding me of my birthday
again
i almost forgot
that that happened
what would i do without you just kidding
uh but
i'm glad you liked it i hope that uh now
it's going better for you
um
everything hopefully is going smoother
like smoothie
thank you mwah maybe a kiss for you
jeff start done for the pinky your
amazing sticker thank you
you are quite the amazing chicken too
sir i like those
those uh the way you put the breading on
the chicken it sticks to it very tightly
and firmly you're doing a great job jeff
good job
have a good job
thank you for the pinkies sorry okay if
he loves you so much
sorry that i love you so much
it's a
real omo in japanese real only when both
parties feel the same way about each
other
[Music]
have some more for blood cover funds
because it's still stuck in my head
since then i actually tried listening to
the original recently since you were my
first exposure to it like most vocaloid
songs but it's just not the same without
your voice thank you but i really really
really really love the sound
of you know when kira
mixes
a vocaloid
character's voices
i really love it like he really makes it
sound
so natural as natural as it possibly
could be with like a computer voice
and you know because it's his song i did
ask him if i were to make a cover for
blood if he would be you know open to
mixing it
and he said yeah so i'll probably have
you know the original creator
mixing it
yeah
yeah he's a wizard yeah
people really really really
like always praise him so much because
of how he
makes the vocaloid's voices sound
different makes sparks
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
oh my god
now in theory i only have the ones from
today left i think
[Music]
let me turn them off real quickly
they're
no closed
[Music]
the doors are closed i think it's
loading
oh [\h__\h] it didn't it didn't [\h__\h] do
it no ah
youtube stop sabotaging me
[Music]
okay okay okay i think i got it now
oh
yeah
[Music]
you guys are like motivating me in the
super chat like oh it's just a little
bit more but you're just adding onto it
oh john chris is looking at me hi
dominique
at least these are not red ones
cruise thank you speaking of red ones
general rob thank you for the
reservation hey boss sakanashi our
muscular chicken is likely
[Applause]
going to go undergo some surgery he's
been ill for over a month but has shown
unshakable loyalty being here for your
streams wait i saw him in the chat
are you okay
what what did you break something are
you okay
did you lift too much
dijo boo
[Music]
you good
is it is it the fins
stomach eggs for over a month oh
oh maybe oh could that oh
like is it like some stones in your
tummy
i've heard about that oh no i'm scared
that one day maybe i'll get something
like that too i heard that really hurts
a lot
or i mean it could be a lot of things
but yeah i hope it goes well
i'm supposed to
donate my case to you i'll gladly do it
i hope it goes well
i don't know how soon soon is but
yeah you better come back healthier than
ever
and don't
immediately go back to sport you know
don't over
over exert yourself is that the right
word
take it easy okay
it's okay you already have you know
you're so buff you don't need to work
out every freaking day
just chillax for a little while take it
easy
yeah gal stones that was uh what
that was what i was thinking of
i had girls like the surgery three years
ago oh my god
but i'm sure you will be fine fine
i wish you all the best let me know when
it's over and when you know when it all
went well let me know
so that i know that my one and only fish
is healthy
[Music]
oh you actually went too i went to
collab cafe and bought goods i think
it's very successful about 200 people
waiting in line for entering this collab
cafe i couldn't enjoy for a long time
but i'll try again this weekend
did they like
was there like a like a time limit of
how much time you could spend in there
when you eat your food and all that
because i'm guessing that they need the
space when there's so many people
oh my god
you can go again yeah
it says you'll try again on the weekend
it probably will be more busy on the
weekend but i'm glad you got to go at
least and there's still going to be many
more chances and you obviously have to
go
when it's my turn when it's kiwa curry
time
yeah i want all the korean kfps to try
to get the kiwa curry
yeah
my korean frenzy let's go
and then test it i want to know if it's
not too spicy
[Music]
i wish i could grow so bad
understandable oh i see you got that
you got that membership card you went to
the store and bought the card and got
the membership back
i see
you did it during the stream
[Music]
a few minutes ago you were still no
member now you remember again
character development
i wish i could also taste it i hope they
release a recipe well i mean from the
looks of it it really just looks like a
normal japanese curry
so you can recreate it normal japanese
curry and put some kadage on top some
fried chicken japanese style fried
chicken
easily recreatable to be honest
well have fun
enjoy the collab cafe because you know
all the non-korean bros are so jealous
that you guys
they're molding
that they don't have that so you better
make the most of it and enjoy it while
it lasts yeah
yeah
comfy wombat thank you for the red super
jack
oh great wise and spicy fire chicken
what is your wisdom huh
who is he talking to
[Music]
anybody in the chat who's a fire chicken
i must refund this super chat because it
obviously went to the wrong person i'm
so sorry comfy wombat
i i need you to contact youtube on your
side to
let them know that you need the super
chat to be refunded because i can't do
it on my side you need to do it okay and
let them know you sent it to the wrong
person
obviously they will understand because
they know
that i'm a phoenix
there's like no possible way that you
could mix up something like that so it's
a you know maybe even an ever in the
system
yeah they'll understand let them know
okay thank you
[Music]
thanks for the pinky
hey hey cute fun
and that's me you see that is obviously
me that is not a mistake
i must work today but i wanted to drop a
super chat to say as i watched some of
cali concert i couldn't help but think
this will be catchy soon full free live
audience amazing dance moves just
excited for your future oh thank you
yeah you want to do something like that
too like
like an avenue and an audience yeah
would be amazing
yeah
that was not me dancing by the way you
know people were honest so i say that
was not me
uh
uh me and the girls we were back up
dancers for a song during cali's concert
and i think it was obvious yeah
i mean i could i could honestly i could
dance that on my own
but i don't have that kind of
environment i mean ina doesn't move that
way exactly
[Laughter]
yeah you know
if i if i think if all of us had
um an easy
proper professional environment to do
that on their own we would have done it
probably
um i don't know i don't know i don't
know about them but i i would have done
it myself
yeah
i don't really like i i i want to
i want to do everything myself with my
own body
i don't want any
any other
person or
computer controlling my body
yeah once japan opens up and all that i
will make sure that everything is me
yeah
everything but you guys know you guys
know that i could dance like that if i
wanted to
you know you know you know
[Music]
is just like
just standing there
menacingly for the past 10 minutes she's
just
sitting on her butt
like
right in the
in the
doorframe
of outside my room to inside my room
she's just waiting for me she's not even
looking at me she's just standing there
maybe she's trying to assure me that
she's like around you know
she hasn't forgotten me
no
no she's planning no no no no i almost
finished it yeah that is true let's
let's finish it let's finish it
i want to eat my leftover food from
yesterday
[Music]
oh now she's leaving
now she's leaving come back
i missed you already
[Applause]
cuddles
[Music]
yeah she wants me to chase her you know
impatient
kitty cat
i miss her
ah
wait
where am i ah here
birthday night thank you soon cats
okay
thank you for the
pinky
i remember that i forgot to send a super
chat for the concert so here it is
not another one
wow just wow so that is the true power
of the dancer of ian you blew me away
with the moves especially during four
blood and ladylike really
love the concert and can't wait for more
to come well thank you
well four blood and ladylike were
actually like the least
some of the least choreographed songs
i kept it very simple because of lack of
time
and lack of skills but thank you very
much
uh
thank you
now this must be proof that chickens
have more
than a
one second memory safe
[Music]
because you still remember what you
wanted to say from like over
a week ago
two weeks ago or so so you guys can
never ever use that as an excuse ever
again
if hook and remembers
then you guys
have the capacity in your brain as well
to remember things longer than one or
two
seconds he wrote it down yeah but
wouldn't he have forgotten that he wrote
it down
i don't know but
i'm not buying it anymore guys
unless you prove me
that hold on cheated
[Music]
what a pain in the ass
thank you for the red super chat you
added the
english reading to your name
but but i know now
when i was reading super chats today i
saw your name and i knew it before
putting it into papa go i remember
[Music]
i remember
thank you
very considerate
[Music]
he wrote in german i think he's asking
us to go to the club cafe together oh oh
oh trust me they wish they could go they
wish they could go
would be nice of you to show them around
yeah
you know one thing you can do is go
yourself
enjoy it
as much as at least 10 chickens would
and then
you'll make up for that
for at least 10 chickens who couldn't go
thank you
[Music]
okay i guess yeah it could mean
something else whatever
[Music]
thank you for another red oh
double red super chat thank you thai
team are so awake
you're still awake
good evening tai chi hope you're doing
well thank you for always being here my
loyal chicken so loyal
this is the example
of a loyal chicken if i've ever seen one
oh young
thank you for the membership and you
i love your art please draw kiwawa in
this hairstyle please
with cats please
thank you please
putting pressure on you
pressure pressure absolutely
[Music]
iverson duncan
rocchi ah thank you thank you ah this is
the one who's waiting
roxy how's it going i finally reached
your super chat it only took me four
hours
we spent four hours together
out of 10 hours of you waiting how you
feeling
i need a life update or are they
sleeping like i don't know if i would
like feel safe enough
to sleep like at airports for example
but like i would always travel alone and
i wouldn't feel like i could fall asleep
even if i wanted to
but he probably fell asleep oh he's not
watching my stream anymore that little
[\h__\h]
[Music]
where are you
where is he
i'm giving him entertainment here while
standing in that boring ass line
for 10 hours i mean he's probably
sitting at this point
but still
he's not here
what
okay maybe one of the other 17 people is
watching and can scold him now
scold him
bonk him
asking why he's not watching my stream
anymore
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh well okay
yeah let him sleep
if he's sleeping good for him yeah yeah
yeah
good for him he wants that kelly
limited edition
glass
allen addison oh wait i read that one
kissing thank you
buddy
[Music]
birthday gift
3d concert was absolutely incredible the
hard work everyone put into it really
shown through i hope this next year of
your life is filled with happiness and
many beautiful memories thank
you yeah it's like it's following me
forever i can't escape from it
which is i guess nice it's nice to hear
these things over and over and over
again
[Music]
thank you so much for not forgetting
about my birthday you know for some
circumstances you must have you know not
had the time
or the the monies the funds to send this
super chat before and that's okay
that's okay
thank you so much for still thinking of
me
thank you very much
uh shane's youtuber watching channel
thank you
[Music]
ah
fighting
[Music]
soon
oh you can get a number ticket when you
stand in line that's a good system so
wait that means you don't actually have
to
if you get one of those number tickets
then you don't actually have to stay on
site no
[Music]
like that's at least like how i know it
from like japanese events
sometimes you go there early
you get a ticket with a number and then
you come back hours later
with like stand in line at like in the
area where the number is assigned to
if that's the case then maybe roxy was
able to go back home and sleep
maybe maybe maybe maybe
use your voice in a
hey there i'm starting an experiment
with ai i want to give you permission to
use your voice in a deep fake voice
model
i will not publish the model and keep
the phrases appropriate
[Music]
i don't know
i don't know what i mean like
[Music]
[Laughter]
no don't make me admit anything because
there's no admitting
i mean if you're not going to publish it
you know in the end i'm not going to see
it so you know
what what kiwawa doesn't say
hiwa cannot
see
so
i mean in the end you can do whatever
you want i guess but i don't know i
don't know if it's allowed i don't know
well you know i don't know i don't know
i know
okay now i don't want to listen to this
[Music]
i need this calm now
i need to become
apparent
[Music]
thank you
no what does this mean what are you
making me read
i am feeling suspicious
google translate
[Music]
it doesn't translate to anything
it doesn't
translate to anything
okay
but what if it means i am
because it's three words you know
i'm just very paranoid you know
it's not like we'd ever trick you to
anything of course
not
who would do that right right
anyway it's a red to potato thank you
very much so for something deep and
meaningful wow so
meaningful
i am emotionally touched by this thank
you for the red super chat
i hope your name didn't mean anything
y'all bit
angel thank you
for the
also read super chat that is
just as
deep and meaningful as the one before
incredible thank you thank you that is
mind-blowing
don't worry yet
no now i worry even more
what an angel you are
something like this
so deep and meaningful can only be sent
by an angel yeah
jingle thank you soon
okay jingle i forgive you i don't know
about the others but i forgive you
wolf in sheep's clothing duncan
internet weirdo
black worf thank you squiggly mustache
that little [\h__\h] again
thanks for the pinky it says log two two
weeks since i took over is someone in
kfp no matter what i must deny if
confronted i must deny myself to myself
uh
i must keep hiding let's find a way back
to mama arena
but
why do you i don't understand the logic
why do you hide in kfb if you want to go
back to enos so badly
just go
just go then if you don't want to be
here anyway then just go
[Music]
your little [\h__\h]
find him
kfp get him
slice him open
take out his stomach his heart his
all the kind of [\h__\h] that's in the body
that i don't know how to say in english
take it all
and then feed it to the chickens
better than the corn that i feed you
every day right
it's something different
[Music]
yeah
got it
nice you can grill it you don't have to
eat it raw
um serves him right
only i have 20 minutes left
no problem mom at the end
mopped it eight thanks for the pinky
oh wait so tomato i skipped a few last
onions
at 77 i gave birth
to the first time
since you mentioned uh 14
and everyone asked about it a long time
ago fubuki i yeah it's 44 streams into
the game and only 65 percent done
yeah flookie's strong so strong
i want to play an mmorpg but they don't
really put out mmrpg's anymore that i
like like you know the typical
yeah cute anime mmrpgs were kind of
shitty and kind of pay to win but you
know i don't i just kind of really like
those
yeah with some cute little fashion items
you know that you can buy for real money
yeah
i want new ones i don't want the old
ones i want new ones i want something
fresh that i can start from the
beginning and then be on the top of the
of the ranking of my class i want to be
number one healer whatever the [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah but they don't make it anymore for
pc they only make that [\h__\h] for phones
nowadays
who wants that
who wants android m rpgs
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
monster hunter
that's not the same kind of thing that's
totally different
koton dan kashin
huh divinity original sin two
[Music]
nah
thanks for the suggestion but that also
doesn't look like something i want
ooza
face with a pinky when it's really hot i
keep a few bottles of water in the
freezer so i can just take out a bottle
let it fall of it and have icy toilet
icy toast
tasty ice cold water
sure and i've seen people do that like
for comic yeah in summer like people
have like these
uh frozen balls of water with them they
bring that at the beginning of the day
and then you know
have a cold water all day it's really
smart
it's really smart actually
mmm icy toast i don't know
you know what that exists actually
because
uh you know that that um big big big
toast
and honey toast with ice cream on top is
basically icy toast
and i love it it's so yummy
[Music]
i i played final fantasy 14 before whole
live
and i went to max level at that time
and then i had no one to play with me
so i quit
it's just like you can't get into the
community and i'm playing mm-hmm rpgs
now on stream it's just like not the
same thing
it's not the same experience
i can't really like
like once i have my character known
that i also can't really trust people
i can't really like
relax and interact with people
freely then that's special treatment
also
and you know private conversations and
joining a guild and all that
joining someone's guilt and that's also
like
special treatment
all that kind of stuff it's just not
really like as a public person like that
possible and i'm playing it privately i
don't have the time for that because
mmrpg's need so much time as a
commitment and then i don't know anyone
there anyway but if i would like you
know ask you guys because obviously
there's people like you guys who play it
yeah well i can't rely on that because
again here we go again here we are back
with the special treatment so it would
have to be someone who's not a fan who's
not a viewer it has to be someone like
within my friend's circle and the only
one that i know that plays it um
actually i know i don't know anyone who
plays it privately like you know used to
play but i don't think she plays it
actively
so you know she's too busy
i'm too busy too
so it's just not the time to play mmos
you know
one day i'll get back into mmos
i'll be
playing 24 7
10 hours at least per day i'll be
grinding and grinding hard
those mmos
i'll be killing all those mobs and i'll
be farming all those items and mats
yeah
i'll get there
right now there's not really any
specific
game mmrpg that i feel like playing
anyway
yeah
sure i always may have had a stream like
that and i could do one too but does ir
did iris continue it no
[Music]
did she continue playing it no
neither on stream nor privately because
it's like
difficult time wise and like just
logistically
yeah anyway uh
uh tremolo regal document
[Laughter]
yeah i get it
what is the female phoenix called what
just phoenix and it's me
elsie lapindangashin patsy dangashun
tatsu
ah
thanks for working on it great job
thank you so much
everybody
soon
ah
you noticed something was different but
maybe you noticed but you weren't sure
about it
but yeah well in that case most people
just didn't understand what was
happening
pansy duncan phoenix fairy shiny shiny
hunter thank you for the pinky sorry
buzz i have picked up on the hair
reveal sooner
eh
i would have picked up on the hair
reveal sooner if i didn't go feral every
time i see a question about a question
about question mark on your and a
certain other magical youtuber schedules
until if it finally happens every
surprise will i will immediately assume
that assume is the fated encounter
i don't know you know for a while i was
a bit more hopeful but
looking at recent
uh
what's the word entwick lumen
recent
[Music]
developments thank you
it just uh feels like it's never gonna
happen it's sad but it's okay we're
friends um behind the scenes and
i
wished her a very happy birthday
yeah
all right oh free once again thanks for
the pinky
i'm glad you're finally true to yourself
and your feelings
it's okay we're like on good terms
we appreciate and love each other
yeah uh
yes
yeah
it's sad
hmm
ooh good luck studying
brandon van gashen pepsi tungsten
her hair like this really
yeah we'll remain in contact
logical paradigm establishing for the
pinkie that's the last super chat
and i want to apologize for calling you
logical paradox crawling back on its
chicken knees
i want to apologize for calling you
an incredibly smart phoenix now that i
type it out that may not be the part you
were obsessed with
but i'm genuinely impressed by how
clever and skilled you are it was jork
please accept my apology
[Music]
you don't even apologize for the correct
thing and you just like vague about it
i don't think you're reflecting on your
words and actions
[Laughter]
all right i will lower your sentence
from three weeks to one week i will take
no more excuses i will change nothing so
give up and just take your sentence
anymore complaining of whining
i will throw you back in there for even
longer you're lucky you got in that one
super chat when i was closing it down
no complaints okay okay
enjoy your time or don't
don't you dare enjoy your time in the
usual room
if you're even in outs
or in feeling joy
i will make you feel pain
okay so thank you everybody for
sitting through
all these super chats with me it seems
like i'm done
it seems like i'm done
[Music]
well oh thank you
thank you
[Music]
finally finally
all those
super chats from the birthday until now
it's behind us
i told them i told them i have the high
ground i told them they're going down
now they're down there
i'm not going to open them now
[Music]
start the next back look no no more back
long
[Music]
um
uh
so um
guys
um
i
[Music]
i won't be streaming tomorrow
um
probably one stream until next week
but
i have the director's cut coming up and
i have uh another
and i have another uh
carrot video coming up so they're both
pretty long director's cut is over an
hour
cow carrot video is you know one of
those lore videos so it's gonna be a
little bit long uh
too and so
i hope that makes up for it
i'm sorry
well next week um
i'll stream a lot okay
i'm sorry
[Music]
i miss you guys too
don't
don't complain okay
you make me sad
[Music]
and
be good chickens okay
make mommy proud that
you guys are good chickens when mommy's
not around
okay
[Music]
the best ones
okay
i love you guys
next week
um
oh wait so this weekend is a debut from
english holostars right
so see they you know
i think it's a good timing for me to not
stream anyway because then you guys can
focus on that if you're interested in it
you can check that out
and
yeah give them your undivided attention
wait what you didn't know
yeah the whole live uh
the english holostars have been
announced a few days ago and they'll be
debuting apparently two per day
so two on the saturday two on sunday
yeah
so go watch that
um apparently some
no might i don't know if that you guys
know that so i'm not gonna say it
but yeah uncle watch then
enjoy
and i'll be back on monday
monday
and then i swear i'm i'm gonna stream a
lot next week oh yeah
well for next week yeah yeah there will
be a schedule but just kind of
late
uh i'm still waiting for
some things like to
come into
place
oh [\h__\h] next week is already the 31st
the month is ending
perfectly on a sunday
oh
[Music]
there's a
i just looked at the schedule you know
and i see like the other members
schedules too
and i'm not gonna say who but
somebody put in a very
very concerning
um
thing into their schedule
uh
it says
and then it's i think it's related to
sana's
stream because it's like
around that time
it's like
drinking my sorrows away
oh
man are you good mate
[Music]
oh man
no no no no no it's not cali okay
just because it says drinking doesn't
mean it's counting
[Music]
yeah
ah
oh man it's gonna be a
sad end of the
weak but let's enjoy uh up until then
let's enjoy it okay
[Music]
okay i'm spoiling the fact that we'll be
sad
oh no kibaba leaked the fact that we
will be sad
[Music]
okay wow i can't keep a [\h__\h] secret
yeah anyway guys so thank you very much
josh
um
it was nice chilling with you
yeah
and um i'll miss you
i'm really soon
you know
maybe maybe i'll do a twitter space or
so
maybe keep an eye open but also yeah
i'll be uploading some stuff so my
channel will be kept alive
hey
it's only two days that is correct
though
and
with that
we say and in german we say
[Music]
feel free to watch the deputies of
hollow stars english fighter
to the boys
quite a fight to fight over
hope they're not too nervous
i feel like
everyone in her life english besides me
had a decent debut
i feel like i'm the only one who had an
embarrassing debut
with like weird [\h__\h] audio and just
being everything
weird
yeah
[Laughter]
and you got my sub oh thank you oh yeah
that's right kelly
kelly's dab you holy [\h__\h] oh yeah that
was very very laggy
uh
you know one thing i have to say i'm
glad callie doesn't do that
anymore
ah
it feels like she has
grown
[Laughter]
oh man
yeah it was kind of a catchphrase back
then
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
kelly's review of her debbie was
hilarious
i think i saw that
no more
inaudible does she really not say that
at all anymore
[Music]
i raised the senate three times with me
to make mike i almost feel like that was
on purpose
she should say it i like that i like
naina
i think it's all wow now
yeah but e9999 is nice too
[Laughter]
mommy why not playing rest
i don't know i'm not really interested
isn't that basically like arc
but with no dragons maybe
[Music]
mosquito
yeah i know it's like like you know
other en members want to play too and i
know it's currently doing like a little
bit popular game to
play but that was really
yeah i don't know when i don't feel
something
like immediately and naturally when it
doesn't click with me
i just don't really want to play it
[Laughter]
we'll see what we play next week um i
have a members stream planned and i have
a collab with navi mama planned
a sponsorship stream besides that i
don't really know what i'll be doing but
uh those three things are in place
[Music]
okay
i'll go eat food now you guys should go
eat too
and everybody who's standing in line
for
the collab cafe fighting
report back to me
of your purchases
bye-bye
[Music]
do
you