[Music]
oh no fell into the unknown left me
bleeding heartless all
alone no
control don't you dare
apologize turn my back and a cold night
listen up cuz here's some advice
you're out the time way out the line
it's taking over like around g i for a
I'll make you
cry tearing it down to just water keep
calling me think
so got
Ted taking the crown now you calling me
King you going to hear him I'll sing now
sing
[Music]
back it up don't back it up keep that
aim I got thoughts that will drive you
insane come over if you like we'll have
a lot of fun but I got a lot of buy I do
what I want make sure you don't forget
it an Army on my back say I'm sick I'm
just stic living in the in the I want to
see the way you bleed
it's taking over like rate I for a lie
I'll make you
cry tearing it down just water keep
calling me yes and no think
so got me
TST taking the crown now you calling me
King you going to hear Sing
Sing l
[Music]
I want it all so give me some more
Flames burn me up down into my core oh
you wish I'd stay down but then I just
R you're not my
enemy baby your dad a man my screaming
out loud no doubt
[Music]
tearing it down
just keep calling
me got
T taking the crown you calling
[Music]
meing la la
la la la la la la la