assistant
[Music]
foreign
again
I used to have a
Christmas version of my docomo loading
screen
[Music]
you guys probably know it
foreign
[Music]
video the whole time of nothing nothing
prepared nothing except dungeons okay my
cats are finally leaving
I need water I'll BRB
[Music]
okay
um
where could I have saved
the Christmas
background
[Music]
are you watching
whatever it doesn't matter if I guess
[Music]
now hmm
uh
[Music]
so this is Christmas
song This Is Christmas
[Music]
foreign
last minute
everything
last minute today
um
[Music]
huh okay
let me fix a chat
I've been busy all day hello
Christmas lights well it's a little bit
updated I'm not sure what has been
updated but it definitely looks updated
the Christmas office at least I got that
because I need an exile just sent it to
me thank you
thank you
yeah hello my voice is
seemingly back to normal let's go
let's go ahead yesterday it was uh still
a little bit you know a little bit
painful but I definitely noticed like
every single day uh you know I know this
changes I mean it took
it took like two weeks though
wait wait we have Saturday to we have
Saturday today no wait maybe one and a
half weeks maybe I healed in one and a
half ways because I started Tuesday last
week I think
so I felt like it would be okay to
stream
you know oh I have so much to talk about
ah where do I even start oh my God I
mean I don't want to talk about
everything maybe yet because uh we have
like
uh oh sure
oh
I I do still want to finish I'm fixing
the Audio I want to finish the uh
Pokemon before I go to Japan so I guess
I can keep some tensions for that but I
said I said that a lot recently and then
I ended up really not tangenting that
much after all so might as well
there we go I hear it now
okay do you hear the Xmas Lo-Fi music
ah Casper is a little tree true cute did
he always have that tree I feel like he
didn't
[Music]
okay you hear it okay good
if you know normally I don't cough at
all anymore it's just maybe a little bit
when I'm talking
um but really only when I'm talking but
it's not bad like my voice doesn't feel
strained anymore at all
um
[Music]
a little bit loud okay
yeah okay oh why do I [\h__\h] start so
first of all uh Merry Christmas
everybody
[Music]
in Austria we celebrate Christmas on the
24th only we ignore
[Music]
ignore the 25th oh nothing happens for
us on the 25th it's really over on the
25th like brilliant I mean Christmas
markets still open some of them on 25th
but we don't do anything I think Germany
is definitely the same Merry Christmas
ah it's so weird to say that because it
doesn't feel like Christmas I don't have
a Christmas tree up I only bought like
you know one of those tiny
um little plants
Christmas trees like houseplants Style
Christmas trees like a tiny one I saw
one in the supermarket I was like you
know what good addition to my Christmas
wreath
this will be my this will be my excuse
for not having a Christmas tree but I
don't think my family cares at all
speaking of family you guys surely are
wondering you know because the plan was
that my family was gonna be uh here for
Christmas and they are coming tomorrow
originally we planned for them to come
today but
where I plan for them to come over today
but thank you for the membership
[Music]
welcome and thanks for super chats guys
I will read super chats from this stream
um I don't know when but I will I
promise
but uh what I was saying um yeah I I
told them you know
um I don't know how how long because
apparently bronchitis which is one of
the things I had uh
you can give to other people
so I said okay I better be safe I don't
want to get all of you sick uh don't
want you guys to suffer for the same
[\h__\h] as me definitely so just be safe
maybe one more day because my my sister
and her BF we're gonna come on the 25th
anyway while my mom and my brother said
they were gonna come on the 24th so uh
then I was like why don't you all just
come on the 25th and then we can we can
make sure that one more day of being
contagious is being ticked off
I might still be contagious who knows
but I'll be careful when I look up the
whole time today this is weird
it's weird my eye tracking is weird
oh well
um
is your sister single oh
um consider it sure well um it turns out
that I also really needed time today
because the whole day I was making
the sauce
um for the finale of the Holo Ian Advent
calendar is finishing them I had like
last night I stayed up late to finish
the remaining basis
um uh yeah
um
and today I made
with the bases AKA just like putting the
cardboard into this
um
yeah uh and then yeah I finished a
couple of them today
and then I made the video just right
before the stream I I I first I put the
audio together because I I got all kinds
of audio files that I had to get
together first
and the worst word to censor it really
you guys know what I'm talking about
um but yeah sorry thankfully
you know what I I
are interesting I've actually really
relieved you know when I when I said to
the girls I needed some voice lines from
them
um here's the script please record it
until this date I wasn't sure what to
expect but so far with the Advent
calendar as well
um there have been like everything
until the very last couple of days was
pretty much on time
um but all the videos were still like
pretty much created last minute like uh
the inner video was also up so late
because it was so last minute but it was
planned like all the videos like I I I
started with like a plan
um I said like Okay who wants this thing
who wants this day any any volunteers
for this day hey I need someone for this
day do you want to do this one maybe and
do you want to maybe pair up with this
person and so on and so on and so on and
like slowly and surely I while it
already started I filled up the the
schedule and then every like one day
before and two days before I messaged
everyone like hey hey uh in two days or
in one day at this time your video is
supposed to go up so I need your video
please thank you thank you
um so yeah I was I was like so on top of
it like oh
every single day on my mind was the Holy
and Advent calendar and yeah and then uh
if like for the last couple days when we
announced song covers that was actually
like my idea was like
oh we have we have some covers coming up
how about we announce them in the Advent
calendar would that be okay management
and they were like yeah of course let's
do it so then I made groups for uh each
of the groups I made like separate DM
groups for each of the groups uh of the
song covers and I was like hey hey I'm
not even part of your group but I just
want to help you schedule this so that
it happens for sure
which was definitely necessary uh
otherwise
[Music]
it wasn't gonna happen so that helped
them organize it and figure out a date
and the time to record it and blah blah
blah
um well the crony one or the bands crony
one unfortunately ended up being just
Bales but that's okay though the one
from
um me also was just uh two of us me and
Amir you know circumstances and so on
but I tried I tried my best okay
um I did expect everyone to be uh
available for the videos anyway uh at
the same time it's difficult
um especially at a time where everyone
is sick or somewhere else uh yeah the
past
two free weeks
truth
yeah
um it's honestly a freaking Christmas
miracle that everything's still
Loki worked out somehow and was
still more or less on time
no members
[Music]
so I've been watching so much of bae oh
because she was like the one of the only
ones streaming
uh thank you guys it was a lot of work
to organize the Advent calendar but it
was fun and very very glad it went
smoother than I expected really it's
smaller than I expected much smaller and
then what I was trying to say is that
um
when I when I'm like observing
management
[Music]
um have to say management managed
managed by management uh projects
foreign
[Music]
let's just say the deadlines are never
um
yeah no like deadlines deadlines
deadlines are a concept it seems of
your imagination uh or their imagination
and Management's imagination
because uh yeah when it comes to
management managed projects
often things are being turned in even up
to 10 days late
um uh but so that was what I was like
shocked that
in like maybe it's because I'm a like
colleague I was talking to this to Jen
and I was like maybe maybe it's because
I'm a call like that day actually
sending everything pretty on time oh I
was quite happy I was really happy
I was really happy about it and then for
the last thing this puppet thing finale
thing I was like yeah I don't know if
this is gonna really work out I'm so
sorry for annoying them because like
every day I'm like hi guys I need this
video I need that video of what's
happening is this happening so I I
really didn't wanna
stack one more thing on top of it you
know because there's even besides those
things there's a million things going on
for everybody like record this we need
this we need this and that sponsorship
um yeah but I was like ah
I need this I hope I hope it's okay
because I want the finale to be special
so I asked for another recording
um it's not much you know just a couple
lines for everybody and
um
yeah actually
it was all maybe not exactly in time for
the deadline originally gave but I
purposefully gave an early deadline
thinking that
it's gonna be you know sent in later
anyway but
with that in mind
[Music]
The Voice lines all of them
just in like time more more I had more
than enough time I just kind of still
was busy with creating the bodies but I
think I already had all finally all
lines by the day before yesterday Maybe
hmm
[Music]
yay so I was very pleasantly surprised
thank you so much to all the whole live
English members for your cooperation no
one's watching this but still thank you
so much in case uh maybe maybe the
spirit maybe in the thought reaches them
um I will tell them after the final
video is uploaded I will tell them uh
anyway
that you know I'm I'm really happy that
everybody participated and we got it to
work and it I think it became a really A
really lovely ritual ritual to you know
get into every day and check out what's
going on not not only for the fans but I
think also management and the members
checked out the videos
it's fun
some got really into it
and I I
said this before but when I started this
out I really what I expected was
just like maybe 20 to 30 second messages
of hi everybody this is so-and-so from
Fall life English uh well how you guys
doing I just want to give you a little
Christmas holiday greeting so yeah stay
healthy and so on and yeah Merry
Christmas all right see you soon bye
that's all that's like that was my my
expectation or my my minimum hope
and um it's fine that some of the videos
were like that because I think in
between that's totally fine but it was
so so good that other videos were
um like very creative and much longer
than expected and had some fun ideas
behind them uh so you know a little bit
of variety here and there hmm
yeah yeah
I was like oh the video just had to be
like two minutes or so that's okay but
then I was just so many videos were over
five minutes long yeah I really want to
say I so much for taking your time to
the en members to make something for my
stupid last minute project thank you
very much I think everybody appreciate
it very much and this way we had
something nice
um I think without the Advent calendar
especially because there's no full Holo
Ian collab this year
um without the calendar I think
something would have felt very lonely
and I don't know something would have
been missing don't you think I think so
hmm
um
[Music]
well the website got lots of traffic you
guys checked it out every day
and the videos were appreciated by
everybody so I will say it was a huge
success
the last video
is coming out in two hours
so it's not finished yet but I think it
will make it on time no problem I'll
keep an eye out though in my DMs
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah I already I did all the
like putting the video together cutting
the video cutting the audio overlaying
it um timing it uh uh on creating
everything in the first place oh yeah
but I I needed some help
in the last
help from car carat thank you so much
you probably can't even listen to The
Stream because
he helps me to subtitle it and you know
I thought it would be nice of some
subtitles
um and maybe some additional details
yeah
thank you thank you he must watch The
Vault instead
yeah
um
so yeah that's the album calendar thingy
I will make the so
have a video public
after a day or two
um
yeah and tomorrow I will not stream
because my family will be there uh but
song cover is coming out tomorrow
and uh I will I guess put up the
reservation after the stream sometime
soonish
um oh and then
I think Monday I will be streaming
Pokemon until the end
go going back to normal for a short time
before I go to Japan because
I think I think around this time next
week
I will
be in Japan already
[Music]
very busy I have to prepare things
um
I have to prepare some things but um
I think I think I hope I hope it will go
well I'm really nervous about going back
to Japan I'm so scared I imagine like
insanely nervous about it
uh I'm very scared for many reasons for
many many reasons
um
yeah
[Music]
my nervous so scared
oh well
oh man I can't wait for you guys to see
the chocolates because they look
so cursed
in the last couple months today and I
was I was starting out I was starting to
to create Bale's hair which was the
biggest challenge which is why I didn't
make it the way I did the other ones you
know because Bales has crazy hair and
I look at her now and I'm not sure if
she's my best creation or my most cursed
creation on the other one I'm I'm proud
of is pink Ina
um
[Music]
yeah for fun I would have liked to add
add more details for the well time
restrictions stay oh definitely look
like who they're supposed to be I even
you guys you know how I bought so many
supplies but the members know I bought
so many supplies for this
um to craft everything and
[Music]
um
uh I thought I had like fitting colors
of a wool for everyone but when I was
like making them I eventually realized
I have no Brown
and Iris hair color
I don't really have that
and crony haircut well I don't really
have that either so I
am dying
[Music]
ly
attempting to die
the Wool by myself
with
acrylic color
I mixed acrylic color with water in a
cup and then I I took a lot of the wool
cut it off
some of them were dyed yeah those three
I died and I cut them up and I put them
into the cup and then I like smashed it
a little bit to try to get the color
into the wool
and then I left it in the in the water a
little bit I never did this before I
tried I hoped for it to work because I
needed the colors to be more accurate
would that even work well you know I was
worried that the acrylic color would
make the wool
like really like stiff and um or like
almost like
not movable anymore
um so yeah then then oh man it was a lot
of work
I I had the wool in there for a while
and then I then I drained it then I
tried my best to um get it dry uh by
patting it on some paper tissues paper
towels paper towels without getting too
much of the color off of it again uh and
then I I blow-dried it Etc yeah lots of
lots of work
um then I some of them I even just set
overnight
um and then uh turns out it worked
pretty well the world definitely is
stiffer than before
and because I I didn't want the color to
go off I didn't even attempt to brush it
anymore
um
but yeah it worked and then
I used that to put it on the head I mean
so you can pretty much guess what I'm
working on anyway
even if you're not uh members
will it take any to Japan with you I
have a feeling that my suitcase is gonna
be really really
um stuffed already and I'm worried that
if I put this
that's in there that they're gonna get
you know destroyed
that's definitely a danger
but maybe
like Callie's
um maybe I'll bring Callie's at least
and mine
um in my hand luggage
secure my bag
take out like an iPad and then when I
take out the iPad they see that they see
the sucks and they're like ma'am
ma'am and I'm like hmm
and they look at me and I look at them
something weird and anything weird sir
and they're like the no no no no no no
no I guess not sorry sorry about that
they'll probably think I'm like either
10 years old or that I'm like insane
[Music]
oh that would be sometimes
maybe both
ah you know man
[Music]
okay so yeah
um that's that topic
um
oh my God so another thing uh song cover
was free song covers were released on
the whole live English Channel yesterday
the day before yesterday and the day
before before yesterday did you watch it
guys did you listen to it
um
can you listen
[Music]
foreign
let me
post a picture
find it oh my God
English
[Music]
what are you guys doing right now by the
way but besides watching my stream are
you guys done with Christmas or is it
upcoming or do you not celebrate it at
all or not today or
um
I'm coming making cookies yummy upcoming
wrapping presents
I'm done
just woke up oh
I'm coming I slice of cupboard oh no get
well soon I was isolated until today too
playing you in Hulk hero thank you
2 p.m here so not much yet
so anyway okay this this was on the the
first day uh released on the 22nd a song
cover of snow halation between amigura I
was me
and then there was
a magic
that came out on the 23rd
and then after the wrong one
this one and then this one Bales and
crony unfortunately no Ina would have
been nice if we could have had enough
too but
oh well
that one is uh apparently a Toradora
song cover
oh
yeah
which I I listened to it I really like
that one they actually I I was surprised
by how well they sounded together and uh
how their voices actually fit so well to
the song I wasn't sure if they would fit
because I'm I don't know when I think of
crony I think of like lower cool kind of
songs you know
um
was really nice yeah it was very elegant
and pretty I really enjoyed that one
that might have been my favorite
actually
yeah
I didn't make it what do you mean with
AI what is that
um
yeah they sounded so good together it's
really good so these are the free sankos
that were organized by management
um I think I remember like we were asked
uh what kind of like genre we want to
sing I think
and then everybody voted for their first
and second choice and then we ended up
in these groups but I think some changes
have been made anyway because I think
the Holy Night one was supposed to be
something else first and then they
changed it into Toradora I think
and uh yeah Chris
to tell you if I had to choose
I saw him out of these free if I would
have known which song it was because we
only chose the genre I most likely would
not have chosen snow halation
now in the end it was uh nice because I
didn't have to practice it it was it was
fun anyway and it turned out really nice
too but I wouldn't have chosen snow
elation
I actually oh okay so here's the thing
here's the thing I think
um they I think management made some
suggestions for songs uh after asking
for the genres as well and then they
asked if we also have suggestions and I
think ski Yuki Maji magic was a
suggestion for me and one more song was
a suggestion from me
um and they ditched the the one more
song
That was supposed to be like J-pop
um genre
that I recommended they did stood for
snow halation and then I was like no
[\h__\h] way because slow halation I'm so
sorry it's a good song but it's so
overdone I
haven't heard it
the mans no why did you ditch the other
song they took sukiyuki magic though but
so I was like well I can't accept this
so the song that was ditched
is the one that I am doing with Kobo and
bottame
because I I was like
classic Kiana brutal honesty I'm just
being honest it's true though it's true
so yeah I yeah my voice is starting to
hurt it's okay it's okay
[Music]
I was like oh my God I can't believe you
ditched that song okay you know what I
understand I understand but it's a
really good song it's a Christmas theme
song so fine I'll do it myself that's
exactly what I said so I I contacted
Kobo and I contacted vatam and I was
like hey you guys wanna sing this with
me
so uh that sun cover is gonna be
uploaded on my channel as I have
organized and paid for everything
uh tomorrow
um
foreign
[Music]
curious curious it's a very fun uh fun
song very fun song
um
yeah I did some Derpy things in it as
well
yeah but uh
I felt like I couldn't leave that song
behind
so that is coming up and then and then
and then most likely around uh New
Year's Eve this was also supposed to
come out like today
but it was moved
uh which I'm really grateful for because
otherwise it would have been like free
song covers from me within the span of
two days
um but yeah one more song that is being
sponsored actually a song cover that is
being sponsored I'm being sponsored to
sing it
um it's coming out around New Year's
and probably on the 30th for 31st or so
uh on my channel and it's it's a duet
money
is it wet it shows another member is
coming up on my channel but I chose
another member to sing it with me
um
yeah it's gonna be sponsored
get that bread hell yeah
we've hoped for who well I can't say yet
but you will know
soonish I
attempts yeah
actually
um there was like wasn't there it wasn't
that the group that covered them
[Music]
that was the same
anyway no one gets it no one [\h__\h]
gets it
appearing what no one gets
a song that was covered by some cute
girls
I like the cover
look at it you just don't get it then
they just don't get you wouldn't get it
and you wouldn't get it
I know you wouldn't get it
he just wouldn't get it
so so uncultured anyway
uh do you wanna know do you want to know
the song that me and Coco and batama are
doing
I don't care about spoilering it now
it's not really about spoiler it's just
announcing
[Music]
and there's a I have a thumbnail but
it's not the final thumbnail probably
but
good enough to show you okay
[Music]
ooh curious curiosity killed the cat
hopefully not
wanna know
oh okay three a two one
[Music]
yay
between
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh yeah
yeah Channel project yeah believable so
I had to step up
had to step up I think I probably sang
it before last year in karaoke it goes
like this
[Music]
yeah
and
art by Desu but also this artist by the
zoo but there's more art I actually
commissioned two artists
two wood artists
cute isn't it cute I asked to have like
some kind of cute Christmas outfits that
are matching but not like you know
cosplay kind of like outfits I thought
there's too much of that out there one
more like casual looking
but Christmas themed and somewhat
matching but still different from each
other outfits
um
[Music]
all lined up with the sake of the
thumbnail you guys don't get it you
wouldn't get it you just don't get it
sometimes you have to line it up just
for the sake of you know having it look
better aesthetically pleasing otherwise
Kobo would be like on the bottom of the
freaking thumbnail
that joker reference yes
[Music]
yes just imagine her standing on a box
or jumping she's mid jump she's mid to
jump
laughs
[Music]
yeah just a box
of the water help me oh that sounds
exactly like her filter
yo I got a new phone case
you know I I got a new phone like ages
ago okay it's not ages ago like other
people's ages ago other people's ages
ago was like five years ago for me it's
definitely not five or six five years
ago maybe it's one or two years ago and
then I got a new phone and then because
I wanted to protect it because it's a
Samsung Galaxy S2 22 Ultra
yeah needs to be protected was very
expensive I got like a one of those hard
covers for only the front only the front
pants that glass and
um I had it put on by like a
professional you know this little shops
with
where they sell like phone accessories
and and they are able to reset your
phone or whatever and put stuff on your
phone and [\h__\h] those those weird kind of
sassy a Little Bit Sassy stories
um I went there to have them put that
cover on my
um on my phone
and
within 24 hours you know that's really
supposed to protect your your phone
quite well within 24 hours I I dropped
it slightly
and
the screen immediately breaks into 5
million pieces that but only
thankfully okay okay but I expected that
the cover would be able to
you know
withstand quite some damage itself
is that normal
then it also breaks immediately
because that thing also it's not like
that just cost I understand if it
immediately breaks if it just cost five
euro but I think it costed something
like 25 to 30 Euro
and for that I expect I I expected
to
be able to be dropped a few times
[Music]
depending how
hmm
where it falls
oh well but since it was within 24 hours
I was like [\h__\h] that I'm not gonna get a
new one immediately and I was hoping
that even though there were already a
lot of cracks in it that it would still
protect what's underneath so for months
for at least a half year I just kept it
like that
and people were always like oh kiwaba is
your phone okay so I'm like no don't
worry it's just a cover on top
they want to replace it because I paid
money for it and it broke immediately
and I was I was so starting to wonder
after over half a year if my phone is
really okay below that because you can't
really see it well
so I finally removed it a couple days
ago planning to put a new
um
cover on top of it soon
[Music]
um so I removed it and the phone
underneath was perfectly fine
nice
so I saved money
but I just lived with a broken screen
for a while which was no problem was no
problem wasn't really that noticeable
most of the time when I was using it
so then a few days later you know I
still didn't get to the store to get a
new one
please later I
I really just gently dropped my phone
[Music]
no okay
isn't like such a dramatic fall it
wasn't
that fall out of the phone I had before
that which was a Huawei
no cover whatsoever no protection on it
for like two years dropped it a million
times and it never got even like a
little crack in it and I was looking at
my friends who had iPhones and they all
had cracks in their screens and I was
just laughing at them and I was like
my cheapest Huawei can withstand
literally falling from a [\h__\h]
Mountain
funny so I was so spoiled by that and so
used to it that I guess I fought the
Samsung
would
withstand some things as well I thought
it was only the iPhone that just breaks
so easily
[Laughter]
well I kind of
it was really really like a small fall
but I dropped my phone and
it cracked but
and I see this as a win
it cracked on the back
mine is white on the back
and it has a big crack on the back but
like it looks like it's kind of inside
you know it's kind of weird like I go
with my finger over it and I don't
really feel the crack
and it's not like super visible
but yeah it's there and I was like you
know what no problem I guess I'll just
buy a cute case and now I finally bought
a cute case
cute it's cute I I took this opportunity
to go on Amazon and buy a cute case for
my phone and there you go it's perfectly
covered no one will ever know that my
phone has a crack in the back but I
don't know if I should I'm you guys do
you guys have experience with this can
can if you have like a case for your
phone
does that kind of like also protect the
front of it somehow
[Music]
because it also goes around the edges
okay because I'm I think it would be
Overkill to add another uh protection on
the front as well because then my my
phone is gonna get really thick it's
already thick because of that
stupid case
hmm
yeah okay yeah all Corners are protected
so I hope
it's not gonna I'm gonna be
kill again soon
[Music]
yeah so I just wanted to tell you that
because I was gonna look at my phone
to check what tangents are definitely oh
yeah okay let's talk a little bit about
being sick you know what I I will keep
my Nabi tangent for my Pokemon stream
but
um
I want to tell you everything about my
disgusting sickness okay
let me get rid of these things though
if you didn't check them out yet check
them out on the whole life English
official Channel okay
and this one's coming out tomorrow
okay
[Music]
oh I fixed it I fixed myself you're
tough
yeah okay so uh yes I will tell you how
I almost died
[Music]
um
like
don't worry I won't show you
this is her documentation
um in case uh the doctor was wondering
what color my flag was
[Music]
and uh yeah
just
don't question why
it's important because the the color of
the flag tells you a lot about whether
you're sick or not
you won't show us see there's someone
someone who understands you want to see
it
yeah okay
don't worry I won't show you shut up
already
don't question it so much I think it's
important to you know just in case
documents these things so last
week's Monday
uh in the morning I saw off Nabi right
um
and then
why is there so many [\h__\h] fruit
apartment
at the moment I killed so many already
there's no fruit lying around being
consumed by them I don't get it what is
this
makes me so aggressive
uh
[Music]
no the trash is closed my trash is like
inside uh
like the thing kitchen you know inside
inside a cabinet thingy under the sink
Froot Loops
[Music]
oh yeah call the [\h__\h] Europe and I
have fruit flies taking a cup in my room
maybe it's something like that maybe
they're just chilling
anyway oh and plant pots ah yeah that
could be I have to check I guess how my
plants are doing so anyway okay so last
week's Monday
last week's Monday
I saw of Nabi Center off
uh goodbye bye bye
and I went home
and I streamed right I streamed Mario
Kart in the evening
and then
I'm gonna be honest
at that time
you know often when I read super chats
and especially after streams where I
screamed a lot I noticed okay throat a
little bit rough but since I do this as
a job like almost every day
I I definitely notice when my throat
it feels rough in a different way than
usual
and in that evening I noticed something
was weird something was off it was not
the usual roughness but I was gonna just
sleep over it and then in the morning I
woke up and I I noticed oh [\h__\h]
oh
it's happening with my throat
yeah and then I think I canceled a
planned stream right that was supposed
to happen on Tuesday what was I supposed
to do on Tuesday was it the
um
not sure anymore Pokemon probably
Pokemon right
oh yeah oh yeah Pokemon
hmm
yeah and then I was hoping for it to get
better but I definitely noticed that
something was weird and then I think on
was it on Wednesday where I had fever
was it already on Tuesday
[Music]
because I think like first
it was more like a cold and I I read the
bronchitis and everything I had often is
like the follow-up from having a cold so
that makes a lot of sense
[Music]
um so first it felt like a cold like I
only had like a sore throat but no
coughs
and I had like a little bit of a fever
of 38 degrees on one day and this is
where I was thinking maybe I have the
sea thing
I was I was uh sussing myself out I did
like
a little test at home but negative so I
was like okay but I was still doing like
someone okay it was just not in the
condition of really
um talking I guess but it's already so
long ago I barely remember
thank you
[Music]
then it wasn't receiving uh so I can't I
had to cancel everything I had to cancel
the weather thing and then this week we
were planning on doing the girls talk
but I had to cancel that as well I had
to cancel everything so sad
um
no unfortunately
[Music]
yeah and I was just kind of waiting for
it to get better but uh at the point of
Thursday
I don't know I felt like it was getting
worse I don't know when exactly it got
worse I don't remember anymore but
eventually my cold turned into something
worse and
uh even though in the beginning flag was
not the problem eventually it was a big
problem
I I had to continuously cough it out and
continuously had the feeling of having
something stuck in my throat
and sometimes when I would cough it out
it would be so bad that one time I threw
up right
um and uh headache really strong
headache all the time and yeah really
sore throat and oh my my my body was
feeling really sore overall
uh so yeah
I was taking
um something that's really popular for
when you have a cold here uh
uh wait I forgot what it was called what
was I taking I I told you guys what I
was taking
that you get over the counter in the
pharmacy
that was it yeah
um my my friend my best friend she was
praising it that was really really good
oh I got him finished
[Music]
and one second guys can I just check
something really quick
[Music]
because of the Advent calendar video
I want
[Music]
no it's not what I want
um
oh that's cute but
[Music]
foreign
stock
[Music]
I stock photo.com
it's cardboard in German again
[Music]
uh
um
[Music]
trying to find a good frame for the
video but
I wanted to have a cute cardboard frame
[Music]
Maybe
oh maybe at least
maybe at least
[Music]
sorry guys it's important it's not the
video goes up on time
[Music]
come on
I guess that's I guess that looks okay
[Music]
okay where was I
mean
foreign
thing and my best friend was praising
and I'm I'm guessing it's good for a
normal cold
uh it was actually yummy because it
tastes like hot lemon
um
I was drinking that but apparently also
not to drink too much of it apparently
it's a quite strong actually for normal
cold
but yeah it wasn't helping me it wasn't
helping me I was getting worse and worse
each day I woke up it was just getting
worse I was like no well like
I think what's getting worse but at the
same time it was getting better because
like certain certain symptoms would get
weaker certain symptoms would get
stronger new symptoms would show up each
day and other symptoms would go away
each day was weird every day I was like
transforming
and then eventually I cracked on the
last Sunday
I was like I can't I can't I woke up
like after sleeping what two or three
hours
I woke up early because I have had like
a coughing fit again
and I was like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] I was
planning on going to the doctor on
Monday if I was still sick but I was
like [\h__\h] this and I messaged my BFF and
she was awake thankfully because it was
like early in the morning and and she
told me I should just go to one of those
like emergency doctors or Hospital
wherever
um
yeah and I was like you know what
instead of trying to sleep again even
though I'm tired I will do this right
[\h__\h] now
um
yeah Urgent Care um
so
I I'm I actually have to say I'm really
proud of myself for going in that moment
because I was hoping to fall back asleep
again but I couldn't
uh and I was just feeling really bad and
I wanted to heal faster
yeah so I
got up
I put on my clothes I addressed myself
really warm because it was [\h__\h] cold
outside these days and uh we got into
the
train
and I went to the Urgent Care place
and I had no waiting time I expected
some waiting time but no waiting time
and you know because I couldn't speak I
literally I really had no voice
um so I wrote down everything on the
phone and I I gave it to the like
reception lady and she read it and she
was really nice and uh you know I I was
worried at first because I think for the
longest time I don't know if it's still
like that but for the longest time
um because of the sea thing
um there was I'm pretty sure there was
or is a rule
that says that with Corona symptoms
you're not supposed to go to the doctor
unless it it's really really really
really really [\h__\h] bad that you're
dying then you go to the hospital but
besides that you're supposed to
quarantine at home
yeah
you're not supposed to go to the doctor
at least no no what's the thing here
um
uh yeah you can take a test or whatever
but you're not supposed to go to the
doctor because yeah it's gonna spread
too much
hmm
yeah and I I didn't think I had to see
thing because I did those little tests
um
but they can be wrong and I had some
symptoms that align with it so you know
but at this point at this point and on
that Sunday I was like this is not
[\h__\h] Corona when I had that before it
was different it was different I know
the difference and you know how a couple
days before I went to the doctor I was
on Twitter I was like hmm
I know people don't like when people do
this but I think I looked it up and I'm
pretty sure I have like evil bronchitis
or a sinus infection
I wasn't sure because both of those
felt like exactly what I had even though
I never had it before but you know I
read it
and then
because of course people are always like
don't don't jump don't diagnose yourself
through the internet and like I
I have this [\h__\h] so I felt very
satisfied when the doctor tell told me I
did not only have one of those things no
I had both of those things plus one more
thing
I had bronchitis
a sinus infection
and
uh laryngitis hmm
it was it was it was funny I went into
the doctor's office the lady I think
didn't tell him that I couldn't speak so
I had to show him the the phone again
he only read like the lower part I
didn't like them but okay you know he
only needed to know like my Korean State
because I was the road like
um my before state in case it mattered
but my current state he he read that and
then he
um
yeah he looked inside my mouth and then
he touched my neck and then uh he looked
at some part of my upper back I guess
uh and yeah he listened to the symptoms
and I have headache and so unbelievable
and then yeah he said well
kiwawa Mrs kiwawa Mrs takanasi
you have everything and I like it and
I'm like what and he's he tells me well
you have really strong this and really
strong dad and he also have this
I'm like oh cool that was actually
clapping
because I couldn't that
um I could not express my excitement
through my voice so I was clapping
yay silently
I was very very
um satisfied with that
because that also meant that finally
um I'm getting some proper care for it
some proper stuff for it because the the
cold medicine
was not working for this anymore or he
never really did
[Music]
so yeah that's when I posted my
prescriptions on Twitter
I don't know I wanted to want um I guess
I guess like part of me
the whole time when I was sick I just
shared so much because I I felt
obviously I felt lonely you know being
isolated for one and a half weeks man
when I really wanted to stream mostly
because I felt the pressure of needing
to stream number one because my Japan
trip is coming up and I don't know how
regularly I can stream there and number
two because all of Ian being like sick
and gone and feeling like I I need to be
there because like this doesn't look
good
um yeah and I had plans of like
finishing Pokemon and so on
um I'm doing fun streams but yeah so it
made me feel kind of guilty and made me
feel like I I oh like all these
explanations I guess partially
um that's that's the reason why I posted
that and also just because I was lonely
and I wanted to share all my suffering
with you guys
um
I live alone with my cattles
and
um
it was rough
[Music]
oh you know for some reason
um until someday when I went to the
doctor I didn't really have much of a
coughing problem
it was only really you know like trying
to cough up some flavor
but after going to the doctor suddenly
again I had a new symptom suddenly I
started coughing a lot I kept on getting
into coughing fits so
it [\h__\h] sucked on my way back uh I
had to cough so much like I sat in the
train I sat down train starts going
and there's a lot of people around me
and I start coughing
and I'm like oh [\h__\h] this this feels
like that kind of cough that just
doesn't [\h__\h] end uh uh and I already
you know I was wearing a mask and
everything but I felt like
the people around me probably are like
this [\h__\h] has covered get out of here
so
Nan literally looked at me and I tried
to play it off a little bit but and I
tried to keep it in but the more I would
keep it in you know when you try to keep
a coffin you just [\h__\h] choke
so after the like right after the first
like at this first station after I got
it I got off
because I don't want them to feel
uncomfortable because of me even though
I don't have covet
um
and I got off I tried to I I really
tried hard to find water but there was
no shops open it was a Sunday couldn't
find any any vending machine to sell me
water and I was just coughing and
coughing and coughing and coughing and
it was so bad that I felt like throwing
up again and also there was like so much
phlegm in my mouth and I was trying to
you know how how I complained the other
day about uh
um
uh you know
people spitting on the sidewalk I don't
want to be like that and I had like two
or three um dishes with me
um but then I ran out of tissues and I
I'm gonna admit it I did it I did it I
did it I had to do it but I always did
it when people weren't looking in
Corners where I knew people weren't
looking
but I had to yeah I did say on Twitter
though so the replies I replied to them
saying that okay if you of course if you
have no other way of doing it then okay
spit it out but if you have a tissue or
if there's a bathroom then please go
there but some people I don't know I
have a feeling that some people do it on
purpose they go like
foreign
it's so [\h__\h] disgusting like some
people do it as a habit that's the kind
of people that I mean not the people who
are like sick and you know can't can't
help it and have no no no tissue
whatever
that's so [\h__\h] disgusting because
those people they like suck it in
through their throat and nose and it's
so loud and it sounds
so disgusting and then they spit it out
right there in front of everybody
[Music]
so I didn't want to be like that but I
was left with no choice but I tried
really hard to hold it back but I was
like choking and dying on the on the
train platform and yeah eventually
felt like I calmed down so I got back
into the train
but yeah after going to the doctor my
cough got really bad so
I ended up on the next day
going to the pharmacy and getting myself
some cough syrup and that one I think it
helped a little bit yeah but you know
you know it was still it's not nice
I was taking
anti-biotics and some painkillers that
are also supposed to help with
inflammation inflammation
inflammation
inflation
flight formation inflammation
in inflammation
okay
yeah
I think tonight is my last
antibiotic I was like looking up because
uh the I think the pharmacist told me to
take it until the end
uh yeah
but then you know I read some things
that people take too many antibiotics
and often they're prescribed just as
like a
attempt to make the the
person feel like you
[Music]
know what's that effect what's that
effect were you you think
the placebo placebo effect or
um you know and then after people get
too many antibiotics or didn't need
antibiotics in the first place and so on
but generally you're supposed to finish
your antibiotics but
uh ideally you would go to the doctor if
you feel better
have them decide at that point if you
should continue taking it or not because
there are cases where you could already
stop but you're not supposed to decide
it yourself I get that
uh uh but yeah I didn't go to the doctor
so I'm just taking it until the end even
though I feel like maybe I didn't know I
don't have to take it anymore I don't
know who who knows you have to take a
test the thing is though in order to
really know if there's still something
to fight inside your body you have to
take a test and to get the results it
takes two days and within those two days
I would have been finished with the
antibiotics anyway
so it makes no sense
so it kind of makes no sense to do it
yeah anyway have one more left so but I
did stop taking the painkillers couple
days ago because I I don't feel like I
need them anymore
everything was getting better so
I stopped taking it like two days ago
[Music]
I don't want to Overkill you know
now I have a lot of leftover painkillers
[Music]
uh Base Post which one
no no what do you mean
do I have to reply to everything
this is something important
[Music]
don't they expire yeah but not that fast
the cough the cough syrup though expires
really fast
[Music]
face crazy tweet
ah the one where she tagged everyone
wait no she didn't tag everyone
[Music]
huh someone else tagged everyone and
then Bane replied it no wait
what
no they attacked everyone ah ah and then
I I was also tagged in the reply
um
[Music]
oh that's what you mean ah
I'm the first one to write in the whole
life English Discord
Merry Christmas to everyone so I already
said
Mr everyone there
anyways
why was she losing her mind why
[Music]
oh she's also getting sick right this
was that was also a reason like ah
I was so worried that I couldn't get her
lines in time because she was getting
sick
[Music]
and yeah yeah she had to make also the
Advent calendar video it was like babe I
know crony is not really available but
are you able to take the Advent calendar
video
oh I'm kind of worried you'll get even
sicker if you don't take it take the
video today
um
uh
that would have been a
a problem if both were M.I.A
both crony and veils it's getting
[\h__\h] everyone guys you got to be
careful honestly like I've read that
maybe it's because a lot of us stayed at
home for the past two years a lot
and therefore we're not as immune
as we could be
or should be
and that's why everyone's getting sick
Maybe
[Music]
like normally I never get the flu or
something like that
it's really a rare case for me too
anything this is the first time
I got
really sick or like even sick at all in
a long time I rarely get sick
the last time was a while
maybe a half a year a little bit more
than half a year before
I went to Japan no wait
no halfway maybe around half a year
before I went to Japan I got so sick I
had like some kind of that was no it was
right before the sea thing started I got
something that was kind of like the sea
thing but not really because I had this
the weirdest [\h__\h] cough fit
24 7. I swear I could not sleep it was I
also had to throw up back then and it
was so bad I got like an inhaler and
[\h__\h] it was really bad I couldn't sleep
I was I was
in a terrible condition when I stayed 24
7 I really mean 24 7. she was patient
zero you know you know when the ceiling
started you know I was living with my
with my roommate at that point and I was
talking to my roommate and we were
wondering she was like Wawa do you think
that thing you had like one or two
months ago was a c thing I said no
that's impossible I remember after I got
better
I was at work
and I saw the news that the saving broke
out in China
so that was after it it couldn't have
been it couldn't have that I didn't get
early access to the better version of
deceiving
[Laughter]
ah
had something nasty December 2019. yeah
that was around the same time as me
um
pre-order
early axes yeah yeah yeah I got the
Early Access permission to test out was
a better tester of deceiving no no no no
no
I guess packed and it had a different
name but no yeah I I don't think it was
a c thing but that was the last time I
was really sick besides the sea thing
this summer
hey I
I was lonely during it very lonely but I
was also the complete opposite because
um you guys were so so sweet oh my God
so many well wishes
[Music]
and I felt very very loved
during that time you know
had to move whole talk unfortunately
that was uh something I felt very
frustrated about but Canada was so sweet
you know I didn't want her to think like
the reason why I called her on that day
on the night before all the talk
I wanted to wait until last minute
to make sure
you know I really tried everything I
could
but the reason I called her is I didn't
want her to even
I don't think know she would have still
been like oh no problem get well soon
and so on but I just I just have this
issue that
I want to prove it
so yeah I felt like I I needed her to
know how bad it really is it's not just
some [\h__\h] sniffles it's really
[\h__\h] bad so I called her I was like
come at the same point can I call you
and she's like yeah and I call ring ring
ring and I'm like foreign
[Music]
what's wrong
I started breaking out in tears I did
not expect this I started breaking out
in tears you know this thing when you
are not okay but no one ever asks you if
you're okay and it just don't happen
they don't really know when you say
you're fine but you're not really fun
but and then you're asked and just by
someone asking you how you are you break
out in tears
yeah yeah yeah what happens when you
have a lot bundled up and you're holding
it and then
someone finally asks you how you are
and then bam it hits you like a truck
[Music]
um so I started crying I did a lot of
crying
it was very dramatic
and I'm kind of the same time she she
talked about it on her stream too but
when a girl cries she says her senses
activate and she wants to protect so she
got really really sweet she was oh it's
okay it's okay don't worry about it
there's no problem at all I just want
you to get better
he was so sweet and I was like what what
[Music]
If I Had No Voice that was so funny
though as after crying for a while
I was laughing at myself because I
sounded so funny
so after I apologized to her and moved
the date
um
I made that video why the [\h__\h] did that
video get so many views did you guys
think I was announcing a graduation
I I don't know what happened but the
algorithm hit the video
like what the [\h__\h]
did some people think I don't think it
really like title wise and formula wise
I don't think it looked like a
graduation announcement
was a short video which gathers more
attention but still it gathered way more
attention than my other short videos
it was like around 700.
dear Lord
wait why does this stream have no
thumbnail what happened
what the [\h__\h]
does this stream have no fun thing I I
had a thumbnail in there wait it has it
but it didn't it doesn't show me on the
YouTube main page right now
it's so weird
I mean
Let me refresh it
oh sure now it should be there
Everywhere YouTube being weird
um
oh
[Music]
if if this goes on it's gonna be in my
top viewed videos and I genuinely don't
want that
I don't want such a stupid video okay
now it has 730k I know you know when you
sort here sort by popular videos oh my
God
that stupid ass video
is
very up high I don't want it to be up
high like that
it's it makes no sense
private it hmm maybe I will
[Music]
because like
I don't know it takes up a spot from
something else that should be viewed
instead
um
oh yeah unlisted maybe I will maybe I
will maybe I will
um
anyway
yeah uh
throughout being sick I binge watched
Wednesday from start to finish which was
a lot of fun I really like winter did
you guys watch Wednesday it's on Netflix
at least a show on Netflix that is good
and I haven't watched yet thank you
Anthony thank you Merry Christmas
everyone merry Christmas
[Music]
if you haven't oh in two minutes by the
way it's 25th here but as I said we
don't care about the 25th year
[Music]
in two minutes Christmas is over for me
oh
I give Enid vibes
I wouldn't I wouldn't go that far but
yeah I've seen people make comparisons
takamuni and Enid and Wednesday
[Music]
anyway I've been to watch Wednesday I
really like that I'm hoping that a new
season will come 2023 I don't know if it
has I it definitely will be a new season
because the end of it was very obviously
showing that there will be
um
I hope it can be 2020 free
[Music]
and 24th is almost over I'm saying we
don't celebrate Christmas on the 25th so
basically that means Christmas is over
for me
[Music]
so sad I miss Christmas from when I was
younger when I was a child
Christmas tree
mommy sending us outside so we can
spend some time in the snow and then
when we come back the Christmas presents
are under the Christmas tree
and then I started unwrapping them in my
old cat from the back then goes crazy
because of the Christmas wrapping paper
and the Christmas tree it was like zoom
zoom zoom zoom
oh
one of the best Christmases was probably
when I got when we got the GameCube and
Tales of Symphonia
hell yeah
oh and then there was a Christmas where
we got the the Wii
the Wii
[Music]
was it we and then Wii U or is it the
same thing
was first Wii right just the Nintendo
Wii right
yeah okay okay yeah okay okay okay yeah
we never got the Wii U but we got the
Wii
now remember trying it out right away I
think we started with like we we sports
or something like that some or or was it
part of the console I don't know
[Music]
oh yeah and I remember my brother
playing uh
Zelda uh Twilight Princess on it
um
Collective favorite drink well now I
have a Wii U just for the purpose of
streaming one game
hopefully I can use it again sometime
[Music]
hmm
uh Star Fox oh that was one of the
things I played on the GameCube I loved
it Star Fox Adventures on the GameCube
with that hot furry chick I'm not into
fairies but that chick hmm that blue
chick she's a little bit too blue for me
that's kind of weird I'm not gonna lie
the blueness froze me off
but yo Chris yeah Crystal
she was so sexy how can a [\h__\h] furry
be so sexy I don't get it
ah she's so pretty I I really only
played the game
because Crystal was so sexy
yeah I didn't I never got really far
because I was still young back then and
it was really not good at games I never
finished the game hmm
anyway oh yeah Merry Christmas to
everyone else who celebrates on the 25th
because now is the 25th year but for me
it's over Christmas
oh so sad
[Music]
but I'm glad that I at least get to
stream a little bit for you guys
yeah
um
I'm gonna probably only do like
half an hour more
I don't know if we should watch your
sock puppets together should we
maybe we should
one more hour
[Music]
I said it
ah
[Music]
um he didn't hear it
leaked uh what a surprise
oh man
I said it at the start
no way
no way impossible
videos rendering now by the way the
finalized version apparently
I want to watch it though before it goes
up so I'm gonna
to like mute for like five
minutes or so to check it myself
and what was I saying
oh yeah Christmas oh but at least one
thing I can say is that I went to a lot
of Christmas markets when I was you know
hanging with Nabi mama
and I was showing her around
sightseeing with her at least I
listening
[Music]
um got to go to a lot of Christmas
markets
no I wanted to go with my BFF though
and then I got sick I couldn't go with
anyone I was thinking you know going
with the family
when they come on the 24th but
you know
[Music]
and then I'm going to Japan so hmm
but I guess I got my fair share of
Christmas market experience this year I
saw I saw way more different ones than
like in the previous years just by going
to a different uh two different cities
and
seeing like so many different ones
walking through the city checking out
all the Christmas markets you know
yeah
but I think
um that one day that I spent with Nabi
in Salzburg
you know Nabi didn't get sick so I don't
think I got anything from her
but
I think I might have just really gotten
a stupid ass cold
from being in the cold the insane called
for a whole day
or half a day actually
because that was insane
that day was insane we were freezing our
asses off but you know I was I was
wearing shoes
that weren't even
um
uh they were waterproof actually but
um it was snowing the whole day
so like my gloves were not waterproof
and they got hit really hard eventually
my gloves were soaked
um by the [\h__\h] snow it was like a
snowstorm which was beautiful and really
added to the experience I'm happy it's
snowed but
because of that even though my feet were
okay for most of the time my hands
eventually started freezing like crazy
and
I was terrible
that was terrible it was so cold I was I
was
devastated by a cold
um I actually wanted to do much more
sightseeing with Nabi mama I planned on
doing much more things but I ended up
like
you know not doing a lot of the things
first of all because well we both
arrived late
and we didn't have much left of the day
when we finally met up it was already
getting dark
so that was like around like three or
four P.M
I was kind of unfortunate
she didn't really get really get to see
Sal's book in the daylight
but at least it snowed a lot and that
was really pretty
[Music]
and
um
yeah
yeah what was I gonna say
that's just [\h__\h] cold you don't even
understand like it was like I think it
was just zero degrees which is I guess
not that much compared to sometimes it
gets like minus 10 degrees or so even
but
zero degrees the whole time in a
snowstorm when you're getting soaked
that's extra cold
that's extra cold that was really rough
yeah Celsius
what's that in Freedom Units I don't
know Google Google zero degrees Celsius
in Freedom Units
um
hey
you know
I said navicent wasn't sick but one
thing I found is really funny about
navitana I also noticed this when we met
up in summer in Korea
but she has this thing
where she has constant sniffles
cripples she was like really tiny
sniffles though
the whole time she has constant sniffles
foreign
[Music]
it's still okay because she's cute
but uh I I I've made fun of her and
started joking that I should call her I
should give her a new name I should call
her kazachan not navitan because
kazakhan is like cold having a cold Chun
sometimes I would call her because it
done because it's done
could be a sinus problem yeah she
probably has something like that because
I can't imagine like 24 7 even in summer
having the sniffles
um I don't know if she ever got it
checked but yeah
[Music]
um
using her she thought she thought it was
cute she was laughing at it
she was becoming a frost muff we both
were
you know uh
so mad
um I
so I originally had a reservation
for uh I think early dinner I think it
was early dinner
uh no I think maybe more like late lunch
or so in a restaurant in that City
Salzburg
and I I picked a nice restaurant and was
looking forward to it showing her that
and then since we're above late I had to
cancel it
and
[Music]
it was a weekend
and apparently it is [\h__\h] absolutely
impossible
to get a a place in a restaurant on a
weekend in Austria in Salzburg on the
same day
so if you guys ever plan on going to
saad's book on a weekend
make sure if you want to go to
um I mean if it's just a random place
like
like like I don't know like a like uh I
don't know Chinese restaurant or Indian
restaurant or so I think they would have
no problem accommodating you but I was
looking for Austrian cuisine restaurants
and I contacted I called
about 15 restaurants
[Music]
literally every single decent looking
Austrian restaurant that I could think
of and I could find on Google
[Music]
while I was on the train I called them
all
called them all but none of them
had a space for us no matter what time
on day it didn't matter at what time we
would come early or late no matter
um
and I eventually even started contacting
the ones that I didn't want to even
consider but no not a single one of them
and then walking in was also not
possible walking in and just hoping to
get a space so I was I was feeling
really really bad and guilty about that
because I wanted her to eat some really
good yummy Austrian food I wanted to
impress her with that
um and then it didn't work out oh and
in the end you know where we went to
have dinner
[Music]
we were walking for the Christmas
markets and trying to stuff our stomachs
a little bit there but eventually we
just really not so much for the food but
just for warming up we just really
needed to enter a restaurant
it's so cold
so bad
I can't emphasize this enough
and Nabi was like oh even McDonald's is
fun I'm like no I'm not letting you go
into McDonald's no [\h__\h] way no we're
not going to a fast food restaurant
it turns out in the end we kind of did
go to a fast food restaurant but not
McDonald's at least
um
So eventually
uh we walked by a restaurant where I was
like not be done
I really don't think and I'm really so
sorry but I don't think we'll find a
good Austrian restaurant right now
so
what we have here right now is a
restaurant that I used to go to all the
time when I was still a student so
actually I have a lot of memories with
this restaurant chain it's called indigo
uh it's mainly in Austria and maybe one
in in Germany but I think so far pretty
much only in Austria it's called Indigo
and it has like all kinds of curries
mostly Curry and some noodle dishes and
so on
but it kind of uh focuses on
um what kind of westernized and
Indian curries but also curries like
from uh other countries like Thai
curries and uh yeah all kinds of curries
and they're kind of like westernized it
a little bit kind of like austrianize it
a little bit
um
and I love oh my Indigo it's my Indigo I
guess officially and as a student that a
me and my classmates and generally like
the whole school I feel like it was a
thing for the cool kids in this case yes
I may have been a cool kid in this case
but or at least all the kids from the
art class we would so often in the big
break when we had a one hour break we
would go to that restaurant and get
ourselves a yummy Curry and and we will
come back to both the curry boxes and
some kids who didn't go sometimes when I
wouldn't go to uh and the others would
come back with their curries oh the
smell in the classroom of that yummy
Indigo Curry would just be everywhere
and ah that is such a deeply ingrained
memory they had like student discounts
and so on and they were like relatively
okay price like a good good yummy Korean
they had daily curries too for like five
euro or so I think
um
yeah they changed a lot since 10 has
been many years but I was so happy to
see that both of the branches that I
used to go to were still intact and yeah
so first we answered one like the
smaller branch that they had and I was
like they have really good curry here I
used to go here when I was in school
still
um it may not be like super fancy and so
on but at least it's warm and we'll get
food right away and it's pretty decent
food so she was like okay no problem but
they had like no sitting space in that
tiny one so I was like
I'm so sorry we had to go outside again
but pretty close by walking 10 minutes
or so we can go to the bigger bigger
restaurant and and have our dinner there
so then we went to the other one and
then we had a nice dinner yeah she made
her Curry really spicy she had me ask
the the store person the restaurant
person if they have any spicy curries
but even the supply security that they
had was not spicy at all apparently and
she put like a [\h__\h] ton of hot sauce and
like chili flakes and everything on top
of it and then she was like yeah okay
this is good now
that's good that's okay
probably even without all those
additions would have struggled eating
that
probably
the Korean thing yeah yeah
her taste buds yeah taste buds are like
Toleration levels
of spiciness
um
by the way I think the video is there
let me download this
[Music]
download
you mind if I watch it
check
[Music]
Okay one minute left
I feel like such a business lady
organizing this Advent calendar
yeah I have to do a quality check
[Music]
polenta I'm not a big fan of polenta hmm
oh wait it's still downloading take some
time
it was quite big
1.4 gigabyte
the heck
my internet speed is maybe a bit slower
because I'm streaming
hey I love corn yeah but polenta I don't
know
it doesn't taste that much like it's not
20 minutes I think it's maximum like
seven or so I don't know
what prices do you have for your family
oh
I purchased some
like uh like you know how my mom has a
house that she has been trying to
renovate for years uh
it's like really [\h__\h] cold there
apparently
and uh it's not really isolated the
house is not isolated at all it's
[\h__\h] insane
um and she can only heat up one room and
she like last year she used some
electric panels for another room but the
electric bills went up like crazy
um I paid some of that already earlier
this year but she didn't want to use
those again so or insulated oh okay
um so I paid for some insulation
material it's a weird Christmas present
but if anything you would want to give
something that you can actually use and
that makes sense right so yeah
oh okay video is downloaded let me watch
it
and then for
my sister
um I got her some calligraphy
set because apparently she likes that
um
and for my brother uh I hope he's not
watching this but I got him
um like 150 euro worth of uh IKEA gift
card because I know it's kind of lame
gift card's kind of lame but I think he
will appreciate it because he's looking
for a job in an apartment and I don't
think he has any furniture at all
um so I'm gonna try to help him a little
bit with the furniture
[Laughter]
I think he needs her the most is I think
it's probably one of the things
the most
um
yeah it's better than just giving
the money straight up at least you know
this way it has a very specific purpose
okay okay you don't hear any audio right
now do you
let me really quickly watch this oh it's
six minutes 40 seconds
you're done okay
foreign
I hope none of the girls feel insulted
by how I
made them look
laughs
some of them look like
[\h__\h] clown
what was that
ah
I I actually I wish I could have
recorded it with better light I regret
that a little bit
but I was kind of
I had no time
so the light is not the best
yeah fauna wrote the story
I think this video was fine I don't even
have to watch it until the end
you know
Kelly's voice acting stands out so much
in this video I think
because she
put on a really like dramatic character
voice While most of everyone else just
wasted really like normally
so it's gonna be a little bit of a
whiplash
she really like embodied the sock puppet
spirits
[Music]
oh did I just say it again
whatever at this point whatever whatever
let me just look at the end
[Laughter]
this this again
um
like I said this before there's one one
one one one puppet that
looks like
I'm so proud of it but also partially
I feel very scared when looking at it
um
[Laughter]
hot mess
uh yeah
you know you know for Bae I I did two
sets two rows of teeth you know and
looks funny but her hair though her hair
but I love the ears I love how I did the
ears I'm proud of the ears
all right beautiful good okay I'm
uploading it I'm gonna upload this is
[Music]
I hope you guys don't like this one I
wish I could have taken a little bit of
lightning would have made it look like
quite a bit better but oh well what do
we call it oh wait what I mean what do I
call it I have like a typical title that
I use
YouTube Studio
um
copy paste
copy paste description
okay
Maybe
let me put like a
thumbnail
I don't want it to be like no thumbnail
you know what white background thumbnail
okay
okay it only takes two minutes it's
taking shorter time to upload it than it
takes to download it
this was so much more effort than I
thought it would be making the puppets
took me like several days
ah
yeah I found out to write a script now
the editing and all that
generally I mean the Advent calendar
was a lot of work but also
this video
worth it though yeah worth it
worth it
um and this way
this is a full hole of English collab it
is
[Music]
the only way you're getting a full whole
live English collaboration
for this Christmas or this this also
yeah there's nothing happening I think
for
uh for full collab for New Year's
anyway
here Christmas music Come Back to Me
[Music]
which one should I do
ah [\h__\h]
I hate this and my settings reset
ah
oh yeah oh but that's uh by the way
that's pretty much
since we talked about the presence
[Music]
all of it because like those are the
people that are
coming over
um
[Music]
so too loud
really
hey how about now how about now
[Music]
okay
but you guys still have to wait half an
hour a hit
down down
wait I saved it now it should now it
should be unlisted okay oh wait no
apparently it still needs 45 minutes to
become HD but
whatever
it will be fine
[Music]
anticipation is killing me don't expect
too much
don't don't get your hopes up too high
we need HD well you can re-watch it when
it's HD
[Music]
I kind of want to do a Premiere because
I want to see everybody's reactions but
I guess we're streaming over it now so
I'll get your reactions here okay
[Music]
if it's anything like I miss puppets
like I don't remember that what do you
mean with that like people haven't
mentioned that Amelia puppet
[Music]
ah okay the one that's just digital
you mean that one
not like like real like fabric puppets
or whatever
[Music]
Merry Christmas yeah Merry Christmas
yeah I'm doing okay I mean it's been
like two hours streaming now and
I I feel like
a little bit
4C
what about um
is all right
tomorrow I'll doing when my family is
here I'll I'll just not talk that much
either I'll leave the talking to the
others my mom is a big talker anyway so
[Music]
he's a big talker
so yeah I'll leave the talking to them
I'll just be like not not not
last year last year Christmas I invited
my
um family we went to a fancy restaurant
because like so far like all the
Christmases were kind of like my mom
cooking a lot of stuff and I felt like
well maybe it will be nice if I can take
that work off of my mom and we just have
a nice dinner in a nice looking place no
need to like work for hours to present a
Christmas dinner
good daughter well she did not really
enjoy it though
I don't know why but she did not really
enjoy it so this year we're doing
um like normal at home
cooking again
but actually it's not my mom cooking
this time either
apparently my my sister and her
boyfriend are
cooking something really curious I think
they said they're gonna make beef
wellington what the [\h__\h] is that I'm
probably sort of beef wellington
ah the covered beef
uh
I guess that's kind of like fancy I can
see that as a Christmas dinner
you guys like beef wellington it's a
British thing
Gordon Ramsay what are you guys all
mentioning Gordon Ramsay
you didn't invent it did he
[Music]
knows
Ramsay popularized it his signatures the
one
well Jamie Oliver cooked it too
[Music]
he has his own version really
well
I've never eaten it before I think
so I'm really curious about it
tomorrow I hope it will be good today
I'll still eat my hair no fresh
reminders for my reminders when I cooked
yesterday it was really yummy
I'm a genius
I'm a genius what I cooked yesterday
maybe you saw it on Twitter if you guys
are not on Twitter you're really missing
out on a lot leftovers yeah uh I cooked
austrians pet slab which are like kind
of like noodle dumplings
like an in-between kind of thing
uh with a cheesy sauce cheesy cream
sauce and uh
uh
pear peer pair peer repair
and bacon and lots of chives and parsley
[Music]
I don't wanna
espresso is so versatile you know it's
better we use it for a lot of the dishes
like instead of noodles or instead of
rice
like for example pepper cut chicken a
lot of people eat it with noodles a lot
of people eat it with rice but in
Austria we like to eat paprika chicken a
lot as well
um
stuff like that
especially are very versatile yes
anyway anyway
um
anyway oh let me oh [\h__\h] I need to ask
my sister when she's arriving tomorrow
she didn't tell me
[Music]
um
she's still awake
[Music]
I don't need Popeyes strong arms I don't
mean it let's whatever heavy stuff I
have be carried or opened by Canada
speaking of Canada said bye
haunted
like I
I assured it's like beforehand as if I
knew how long it would take me to get
healthy I moved it to that Friday and
I'm gonna be honest in some days like
Monday Tuesday I was like doubting if
that's really realistic
if I really have a voice at that point
um
but I had enough of a voice to to do a
proper stream yesterday thankfully that
was perfectly timed and went really well
and before and after the stream we still
talked a lot and after this after the
streamer I showed her another like an
actual actually a K-pop group that I'm
really into I showed her new jeans I was
like yo yo yo what do you think about
new jeans look at this look at this
together with me so I I made her play
it's at the same time as me and do a
watch along
I showed her attention no I put it I
think hyper
I think I showed her
yeah we talked more about Idols as well
and and some other things secret things
and yeah we talked for a while and then
even even after uh
we ended the conversation because I said
I gotta eat breakfast and my voice needs
to rest even though this is a lot of fun
um we both still stayed
um in the collaboration room you know
the life today thingy
and for a while I was just doing some
side stuff I was reading comments and so
on after whole talk but then eventually
I looked over to the side and I was
gonna like close the program and I
noticed kind of the same place still in
there and she's like moving a little bit
and I was like I was like moving a
little bit too and then we noticed each
other at the same time and I'm like even
though we don't hear each other
I was wondering
what
did she is she looking at me and she's
like it seemed like she was also
wondering the same thing
and then we were trying to give each
other signs like winking and and moving
around and uh doing stuff like that yeah
yeah we were communicating just by
movement
like 10 minutes after we already ended
our conversation and then we were
playing around inside the room like we
were both making ourselves really really
really really
big and just derping around and then we
were making us really really small and
then we were like moving around like
this
I don't know what the [\h__\h] we were doing
but it was cute
I wish I should have like I could have I
should have I should have recorded it I
should have recorded it is
[Music]
yeah we were like kids on the playground
somehow
it's so cute
yeah it was fun
but it just kept on going and going and
going it was so dorky and eventually I
was I was the first one to
uh close the program I was like have to
end this otherwise this is gonna get
awkward eventually
[Music]
we got along so well
the idol Chit Chat was so much fun
afterwards we talked a little bit about
um some Hello project related things and
we had many things to agree on
so
really noise yeah
we're definitely gonna collab when I'm
in Japan and
um you know I plan for one more person
to join us because I thought for some of
the whole life Japan members you know
they're a bit shy or they say themselves
they're a little bit socially awkward or
whatever and and I thought it might help
them if it's not just one-on-one but
like one more person so for a lot of the
meetups I planned to
um you know bring one more person
but um so that was the plan but then we
got along so well during whole talk that
I want to go one-on-one uh karaoke with
her uh to sing hello project songs only
have so many many many many many many
many hello Patrick Songs in their
machines as well so I'm not talking
about streaming to karaoke it would we
could we can do that too but I just
really want to go into the karaoke
without worrying about which
instrumentals we have permission for
which songs we have uh the copyright for
blah blah blah I just wanna just wanna
just wanna hang privately and sing hello
project songs for like five hours
screaming and dancing
hey
ah
I think I'm gonna do that
[Music]
in Canada I told her that you know I
already have a lot of trip a lot of not
trips but like um Hangouts planned it
would be kind of nice if I could get out
of the city out of town with her and go
on a little trip and I don't know if
that's gonna work out because the third
person that I invited apparently doesn't
have time for a full day so now it's
kind of awkward like oh I want to go on
a trip but uh like a day trip but she
might not have time but Canada Senpai
has time and she was like even looking
up like some some places where we could
go to
there's actually one place that I've
never heard of before that she
recommended
um
do both yeah but the thing is my
schedule is already so packed and I need
to keep like a couple days in between
empty for normal streaming
and resting and practicing
dances
Etc
[Music]
so yeah there's also some work related
things that I have to do as well during
my time in Japan I'm trying to not fill
it up too much but even even then it's
like five of collabs per week
okay
[Music]
it kind of added too many
scheduled
[Music]
but but uh
I can I can
cancel some of them possibly if I need
to because I already have a
an idea or like pretty much set date of
when I will when I will go back to Japan
again and that will be not so not so
much later not so far after this trip
[Music]
so there's no brush first you know I
thought oh let's try again as much as
possible but then I figured I'll be
going again pretty soon after
so yeah no need to rush too much
uh who knows for what it is who knows
[Music]
now my nose is so hairy
so many cat hairs oh my God
ah
um will you meet Ina well I think people
know by now that she's in Japan right
because like remember Senpai talked
about it so I can say it too right yes
I'm planning on
um seeing Ina
foreign
[Music]
I don't think she said it herself though
right
but Cali and mega Senpai talked about it
okay so I can say it too
I'm planning on meeting Ina
[Music]
I don't think I think there will be an
off collab but we do have a sponsored
stream
plan for the beginning of January
Valkyrie connect by that time
I I don't think she will be in Japan
anymore I'm not sure about I don't think
so
um
so that will happen as a normal collabo
sponsored yeah Valkyrie connect uh what
are we what are we doing I think we had
a doctor connect stream where we
announced
something really early on right
and said oh but it won't happen until
January right
so I think yeah our vacant awakened
versions
why did we announce them so early
um
[Music]
yeah I'm not sure what we're doing
though because we already showed off the
art
so are we actually playing the game this
time
hmm I'm not sure we will see
but Ina is gonna be a part of that and
she said wait what day did she say that
she will be uh returning
did she write on Twitter
[Music]
the eighth wait is that not just our
sponsored stream
is that not exactly when the sponsor
stream happens let me see
I know it's one day before
I think no two days before okay okay
seems like it's like two days before so
[Music]
I'm cooking
hello it's raining cookies
oh yeah
[Music]
yeah it should be uh on the 10th
but maybe PST nine
[Music]
the time is
even evening jst
but still a while to go so no need to
worry about it now
I buy another traditional German outfit
no no I'm meeting so many people I'm not
gonna give all of them umiage uh
souvenirs I might just like buy a bunch
of Austrian chocolates and then
distribute them but I don't have time to
make the those really special but you
guys have
[Music]
ah
iron beat thingy that one I will
give to somebody Senpai I know I said
back then that I want to make all like
one of those for each
Japan member I'm meeting but I'm meeting
so many this time
[Music]
yeah well I have to pack the iron bead
thingy I I should make it into a
keychain
before but yeah I'll try but maybe I'll
try it once I'm in Japan
I'll just go to the Daiso [\h__\h] love
guys
[Music]
by the way my flag M did not really stop
until
today actually
just want to tell you that I kept on
suffering
Loki with the flag m a while longer
afterwards
[Music]
it's very annoying but it doesn't have
it's not as big anymore and it doesn't
have weird color anymore
[Music]
um
but yeah this morning I still had to
cough up a bit but I haven't haven't had
to do that in the past five hours or so
so I think I think I did it I think I
did it yo 12 more minutes guys maybe can
we release that early I'm impatient
can we release it like five minutes
early
Kento is typing
can we release a 10 minutes early
[Music]
healthy Fitzgerald healthy choice
yeah later I still have to learn one but
not honestly we're in Japan
[Music]
is the door aren't ready I don't know is
it
I don't think the door Arch is ready
[Music]
100 percent
let's give it some more time
maybe maybe
the last minute
the
door art I've saw I've seen a work in
progress
yeah oh one more thing I want to talk
about uh
that I didn't didn't get to talk about
because I was sick I
at the what was it comic Fiesta in
Malaysia I mean I wasn't there in person
but uh when when was that last week
Thursday or so
[Music]
I think it was the first day morning
really early Thursday morning
the crowd was insane yeah the photos
that you saw
apparently
um the phones that whole live English
account posted
from the back that was in the middle
that was not in the back of the room
that was apparently in the middle of the
room
that already that photo already looked
crazy but that was in the middle of the
room there was still like another like
thousand people behind that
and yeah yeah yeah staff told us that
they had to turn uh at least a thousand
people down who were trying to enter the
room
so oh the eye is ready speaking of the
devil
let's let's wait let's wait because I'm
tangenting anyway
um yeah that's [\h__\h] insane I did not
think like
I did not expect so many people because
I was doubting remember I was doubting
that people would come because I am not
so aware of having a lot of Malaysian
fans
oh yeah but maybe it's like
maybe me in particular maybe I don't
have so many Malaysian fans but whole
life in general does and they just come
to the panel to support whole life I
don't know
but it was crazy
they speak English in chat yeah yeah
sure I I guess like you know I don't see
where you guys are from by the chat so a
lot of this is by my Impressions from
Super chats
from the currencies that show up the
most in super chats
which surely of course does not 100
reflect
like my audience is
of residences or Bots and it's the only
thing that I can really connect it to
because I don't look at my YouTube
analytics at all I know I know I can
just look at the analytics but who looks
at their [\h__\h] analytics every day I
look once in a year
[Music]
I checked once in a year
yeah anyway so that was insane the crowd
was insane since
foreign
[Music]
so I was really surprised and they were
all so energetic one thing I found
really interesting and I haven't seen in
other conventions and you know I've been
seeing a lot of conventions by now uh
either by going by myself or going as a
guest
um with her life but what really stood
out to me was Malaysian fans with their
big ass Flex
[Music]
a lot of them were
carrying and waving huge Flags I'm not
talking tiny flag I'm talking huge flag
like 10 meters up in the sky and bigger
than like a normal person Flags often
they had lots of huge flags and they
were waving it like
what does that remind me of I don't know
like maybe a maybe a soccer match I
don't know
I know like whole life Flags but also
probably also Malaysian flag but oh I
didn't look so closely what kind of flag
it was but a lot of wave flagging what
flagging wave what
what
what wait
[Music]
flag waving flag waving
yes
uh yeah yeah yeah and I had the MC that
was funny
the MC was dressed up in the cosplay of
magni
[Music]
it's funny and like he was like joking
kind of like in character
a little bit acting as if he was really
magni
yeah it was funny it was it was macking
I guess and there were some other
cosplays in the crowd that I saw like
Amelia cosplay I think I saw kihuahua
cosplay didn't I my imagining it we just
saw myself in the mirror
and I saw
well some cosplays I don't remember
anymore it's already been too long but
the thing is that was last week's first
day when I was like already sick but
my voice wasn't gone yet
and
I don't know if that kind of made it a
lot worse but it's definitely felt like
it because after the panel I that was
when I absolutely lost my voice in the
panel I was like
talking okay-ish a little bit hoarse but
not so noticeable but coughing and a
little bit and and feeling
like a lot of pain in my throat
but still totally able to do an
important panel I wouldn't cancel that
in that condition but after that
strained it so badly in that panel
because after that it was gone
but you know it was a panel it wasn't
even a stream like it was a panel so I
felt like you know the stream I I feel
like okay I can even cancel it or I can
just be really quiet especially if it's
a collab I can just let the other person
do the talking but in this case I
couldn't I wanted the crowd to be hyped
up I wanted them to have a good
experience I can't just be there and be
like oh sorry guys I'm gonna talk really
quietly no I can't
I had to be an Entertainer like they
came to see us and they squeezed
themselves into that tiny ass room Zone
I had to be Genki and energetic and all
that so I tried I tried to hold back
but also at the same time be energetic
hold back without it being too
noticeable
and then then I got so [\h__\h] up
oh
something
anyway
uh okay uh oh we have four more minutes
during the panel
um wait
you know the panel was with me and amen
and I'm not gonna say what it was I
guess or maybe I could at least for one
of the things
um
but both me and AME
did an oopsie
that
maybe at least one of them could have
been avoided
if if briefed properly
and the other one was not a big deal I
would say
uh and I don't think that could have
been briefed on
[Music]
um could have been braved on it's not a
big deal like uh I don't think I I
wonder I wonder what the audience was
thinking at the moment when we said
those things
uh that we both said there is apparently
really no recording because they're
really strict and they they follow the
rules there there's no recording of the
panel
um I would say like from our point of
view
here who who's here now I think we all
wouldn't give a [\h__\h] about what has been
said
but I said something
and then while I was saying it you know
I was I noticed that in in Discord in my
Discord I noticed management being like
oh oh oh okay well stop talking about
that that's not that's sensitive
um stuff and then like oh I'm so sorry
so without like making it noticeable
during the
um during I was while I was talking I
just tried to like just get out of the
topic quickly and then Ahmed talked and
so I I typed I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I
didn't know I didn't know
but the audience didn't seem bothered by
it I'm not sure
I'm not sure honestly I I hope it wasn't
a big deal I didn't know
and yeah and then and then I'm ma said
something later
because
um let's just say uh we had to answer
some audience picked questions uh no
management picked audience questions and
uh one question was
um what kind of movies I may watched in
this year and which one she liked and
one of the movies she mentioned
apparently was banned in Malaysia so
well it was too late at that point
um okay uh are you guys ready for a
whole calendar let's watch it together
it's in a couple seconds
I'm gonna mute my audio but we'll watch
it together okay just wait for me and we
will count down okay
ten nine eight seven six five four three
two ah wait don't don't don't start it
yet guys here link for everybody who
doesn't have
okay
hello Ian minus advent.com
okay okay okay okay you ready
is it there
I can't go again
does this work for you it won't even
open for me either can
[Laughter]
okay
it's okay Kanto it's okay take your time
you know I'm just joking when I'm when
I'm roasting him but uh it seems he
really takes it too hard when things go
wrong but it's fine don't worry uh
refresh refresh click click click let me
in
did you get the time wrong arm
maybe it's
maybe it doesn't recognize that it has
to be up there at the top on of the of
the house
placement
let me in
another one open up
open up
it don't feel don't feel stressed
whatsoever by the pressure of the
thousands of people that are waiting for
the finally don't feel pressured
don't forget to tweet but it's not even
out yet I'll tweet after the stream is
over I guess
yeah
[Music]
but don't play it without you know guys
we have to watch together okay you're
here for a reason we're gonna watch it
together do not touch anything
oh
doesn't mean me I think I can't touch
things
click click click
click
it's so nice that it's filled up with
those pictures though isn't it
of all the little images that wasn't
even originally the plan that was just
added
later on
can't do his panicking
no no they're not a holiday honestly
like the big thank you to the team for
you know every single day being there
to work on it with me check now
not for me not there for me ah
okay okay you guys I get it we're gonna
we're gonna click the play button uh on
zero okay master
zero yeah
free
two
one zero
Iris
does it look like Iris
this is some wool that I had to die
did you see the black flash
it wasn't just me
yeah
what the [\h__\h] is my adult Premiere Pro
is weird recently
isn't mermaid's ball cute the ribbon
also see how I added like the black and
the white strands in her hair
both of those hairs look kind of like
[\h__\h] because I had to dye them
now
normally
no
[Laughter]
I love this part
bye
the Kiana sock puppet feels like the
most scuffed one because it's the first
one I made
looks like [\h__\h]
see how dramatic Cali is speaking
yeah my hair is so funked
and my mouth is so wide
mold wide
five-year-old
I'm so cute
I'm so sorry
I miss one of my worst sock puppets I'm
so sorry also one of the she's the
second one I made so
or the third one or so
it's so scuffed
I'm so sorry
but the hat is so cute I love the hat
did you see the airplane
I even braided her hair and colored that
part darker you see it
and she has some tennis
foreign
[Music]
this is when I started experimenting
with dyeing hair first I
thread mixing
uh different wool colors but then I was
like this looks like [\h__\h] so then I
started dying hair
so she has different hair colors
and I had no gray or silver thingy for
her forehead
because I look so [\h__\h] Derpy I love
it
because it looks so dirty also good as
Fang inside is falling apart because I
used her too much
too violently
I love that part the banter
these two are my favorites I think
together
in terms of banter
bye
I love hello Medina
I'm so proud of Ina
for her basically I just reused what
sound recordings
didn't realize
laughs
sorry
she had better days
one of her eyes are stuck it doesn't
move
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry can you listen to this seriously
oh
ah
Max
Merry Christmas that was the finale of
the oven
I know it's so cursed they're so cursed
I don't know if they're cute or cursed
but they're probably a mix of it yeah
bye I get nightmares from this ever
since I started making them
ah wait I have a photo of all of them
let me show you and let's let's look at
them and let me comment a little bit
about them before I go okay so first of
all
kiwawa uh the first sock puppet that I
made um first you know I finished them
her without a nose and I thought oh this
is fine but I ended up adding a nose and
and blush and uh the lashes
um because I thought you know
maybe it would be cute and then it
turned out to be really cute so I added
that for everybody
um
what are you talking about
actually I have to add the gender
foreign
yeah so this was my first sock puppet
done in hindsight I mean I guess it
looks okay but the hair
um
could use a bit more hair she also has
different lengths of hairs and the mouth
is too wide so after after what was the
second one I made was it you guys I
posted on members but was it a good hour
or was that uh
or was the dominant
okay so my second one was
I I you know I didn't want everyone to
have the same eyes so I used like
smaller like kind of wide eyes
see that difference
um and I kind of uh for the first one me
and I'm good at you notice how the eyes
are so far apart for Amit too but then
around Cali I realized that if they're
closer together they might look a little
bit nicer but
um you know it gives them personality we
have some personality
yeah the good one I I put so much effort
into the hair I used different colors
and layered them and I I used so much
volume so much hair
I also gave her the cute little pigtails
um I think she's extremely Derpy but
there's a lot of effort in her so I
think you can see that that the teeth
that's when I started experimenting with
teeth and after that I did Ahmed and I
was like okay Emma has the cutest smile
I love how her smile is such a prominent
feature of her so I want her to have
teeth too
um but I didn't want to give her like
single little teeth I wanted her to have
one big smile
and I have to say I regretted a little
bit especially because it looks kind of
like messy uh because I I didn't glue it
on so that it would cover up the you
know a little messy part there
um I regret that a little bit but oh
well
um
it's okay I guess
um I like the Hat I had to like
improvise for the Hat the the ribbon on
top of the hat is fabric from a cut up
sock
and the hat itself I used like the same
kind of hat that I gave myself I had
like little little hats for decorating
old pockets
so I repurposed those but then that hat
was actually green and I put like a like
a pantyhose on top of it to make it look
Brown because I had nothing Brown I had
no Brown fabric so it had to like cut up
things yeah
uh and then I made Callie
uh Callie I made on the stream right
um the members Stream So if you want to
see the process you can watch my members
stream oh it's quite funny I did a whole
concert at that point too
for Dad Robert Robert
Rob Robert
have a Merry Christmas
yeah for Cali I put the Eyes closer
together and I think I like them they
make her look very muppet-like don't
they
they give her such a muppet look
and I gave her like the the Black Crown
and I think she looks really good but in
hindsight I feel like she could have
used a bit more detail I gave her really
long hair and so on but Avail would have
been nice I guess but I didn't have any
fabric like that and
distressed already and then I made
um Ina for Ina
um
I know that the hair the hair is not
perfect but I think it works perfectly
fine you can totally recognize her
um
uh I had fun making the tentacles and
you don't see it here but her little ear
thingies the flaps and yeah yeah I think
she turned out really good she has a
very narrow body or face or head
um but I think she turned out really
good I love that everyone turned out so
differently like kind of different head
shapes so I distance and so on I did
that on purpose I wanted them to look
different but you know
um
Pam
then Iris for her I had to dye the hair
but I'm not happy with how the hair
color turned out it should have been a
bit more pink but oh well I think it's
okay
um she looks very dirty in that picture
uh I added you see in the middle of her
bangs I added the little strand of a
lighter hair color also I gave her elf
ears you see those some of theirs
not the black ones and there's white
ears around the height of her eyes
properly pay attention to detail hmm
yeah no I was I was trying to make it
look like the new Iris but I guess it
looks more like the old Iris I don't
know
um
yeah and unfortunately since I dyed the
hair I couldn't really brush it
um so her hair is really messy
unfortunately
I'm crony
the reason why I started dying hair she
was the first candidate because like
first you don't see it in this picture
but I combined light blue Wool with gray
wool
um but I was like um I don't like this I
wanted to be more crony color but I had
like no dark blue wool I didn't want to
fly anymore I was sick too you know so I
had to do with what I had and I have a
lot of acrylic colors so I started uh
um trying to dye it and mix acrylic
color with water dip in the wool
try to get that color in there
and I think the color turned out pretty
damn good I like the color you see the I
think the bags are no way oh my God
that's not even all before I started
dyeing it with a curly color you don't
see it here but you know what I did I
use a tiny dark blue
felty
like
a pen
and
try to die
sharpier try to not a Sharpie a marker
more like a yeah felt pen a felt pen I
tried to die those tiny strands of wool
each side I kept on turning it and going
over it again and again it was pretty
difficult pretty [\h__\h] difficult and
took a lot of time So eventually I was
like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] so the back of her
head you don't see it here but the back
of her head is like a mix of all kinds
of different colors
oh yeah that was like [\h__\h] this and I I
was like I need to find a different
solution so I started dying it with
acrylic color
and then I was like this is it this
actually works amazing so I did it for
Iris as well and for mume as well
um
yeah for crony I feel like
um she doesn't look quite like her
I tried to give her like longer hair in
the front shorter hair in the back
um and have the front hair kind of stand
up by going over their accessory but
it's not perfect maybe I should give her
the big clock
on back the back of her head but um
hard to replicate Perfection exactly
then fauna I'm quite happy with farmer
even though it's so simple but I think
her hair turned out pretty and you don't
see it so well but the left strand is
like partially braided and then also
with a felty felt pen uh colored darker
she has the beauty mark and her antennas
I wanted to add Little Flowers in her
hair but I didn't find anything I
couldn't think of anything that would be
good for making those tiny flowers I was
like whatever maybe later on I'll add
them with some balloon
then mume I'm really happy with ume so
for mume I dyed the hair and I gave you
also several layers of hair I made a
ponytail
uh and I I was first thinking of using
feathers because I bought a lot of
feathers but I would have had to dye the
feathers as well and at this point I was
like
[Music]
more so I used I had this nice brown
polka dot ribbon that kind of is the
shape of her feathers anyway so I
thought in this case I think it would be
cute
um yeah also she has those those strands
of different colored
hair the white one just Blends in with
the sock though but I'm happy with the
mermaid one quite like that one
and
which needs its own picture because you
don't see the whole Glory but
um
so
first of all I didn't have perfectly red
wool uh
so I was like should I use those those
little cleaner thingies
but then it would look so stiff and it
wouldn't move around nicely you know so
I was like well I have feathers and the
feathers would at least
like make her hair stand off nicely like
her pigtails
yeah pipe cleaners um
um so I thought I will give it a try
with but only the the bags are partially
um wool
and also again the black one is painted
with a felt see
um but the rest is feathers and you
don't see it here but I also painted the
edges of the feathers black
uh on the bottom and it was kind of
difficult because the feathers they just
do whatever the [\h__\h] they want so I
tried to bend them and oh my God she
actually this looks better than she did
at some point
when I didn't cover up the top of her
head with a whole feather I think I
think it's pretty good but she looks so
cursed but maybe that's a good thing hmm
Stussy look for curse
yes she's the Masterpiece yeah oh god
um
but I think the most beautiful thing
about her that's not cursed is her ears
those are like big pink
um bullish cotton-ish balls that uh
where I wrapped like a pipe red pipe
cleaner around it to give it the red
Edge
and then I put that little
little thingy little uh yellow thing on
top of one ear
so I love the ears I think they look
really cute the ears are perfect you
don't even see them so well here but the
hairs are perfect
I was worried about the teeth because I
thought
um if it's two rows
then she won't be able to close her
mouth properly
uh I don't know how it was in the video
but it didn't particularly bother me
anyway she looks like a [\h__\h]
clock
I please don't think I um
I am mentally well okay I I am okay I
did this for the finale of the soccer of
the Advent calendar and you know I had
time so while I was sick I couldn't
stream anyway so what the hell
[Music]
oh very cute and I'm planning on doing a
little concert with them like in the
members only stream because that was a
lot of fun
now we have 10 new friends they were all
ready my friends
they are quite something aren't they
who's your favorite guys
out of this
coming now
I think my favorite like out of
derpiness points is good on bales
but I have prettiness points I would
give it to Ina and mumei those are I
think I'm the most proud of although
lumi's hair unfortunately it's like very
stiff of course
you guys just like the clown Derpy ones
I'm a big tooth
this is really you think oh I'm so glad
I'm so relieved
I'm relieved thank you
mm-hmm
we heard chat news gets oh no no no no
please no
I have to say it was a really nice
creative outlet for the days where I was
sick
making these
cats were watching me
[Applause]
while I was making them observing me it
was kind of comfy
uh
well yeah I want merch of these designs
merch
playing with yarn yeah they played a
little VR and I had to take it away from
them it was cute
[Music]
I know
that you don't know
[Music]
um
right
okay oh my God bails
ah
it's looking
that's been kind of flattering on her
in the video she looked um
worse
the problem was also that one of her
wobbly eyes was stuck
but I was like whatever but you know I
was taking the video
um right before the stream with my phone
and I had my I had my headphones on I
was listening to the to the audio that I
put together and I was watching
I was acting it out and watching it on
the phone screen while I was acting it
out and I just
break out and laughter because it's so
[\h__\h] ridiculous
I wonder if the members saw it yet
final win heels up
um please check the
absolutely
cursed result
feel like oh she should have made me
prettier
I hope they appreciate the derpiness but
so far you know when sometimes I would
post pictures of them in the while I was
making them except for today today I was
grinding but I would post pictures and
show them to the members and their
reactions were like oh my [\h__\h] God
laughing laughing laughing laughing
uh
I kind of on a remake I'm mad and and
mine if I had to remake some I would
make mine and I'm a
yeah
but like mine maybe just needs more hair
and and the mouth could use a shortening
but oh well
they have soul right
soul
eat them properly so you can have to
kiss what do you mean they can already
kiss
I already made them kiss
would you remember
don't you remember
how much personality hell yeah
that duck bill duck bill what
yeah we're all made with love yes they
were
called Advent calendar to the finale I
hope I hope you guys enjoyed it yeah
thank you fauna for writing the script
thank you Kendall for taking up my
urgent last minute request
yeah thank you thank you
for drawing the art contributing the art
even though it wasn't originally even
planned but I feel like it added so much
charm to it as well
made it more like special
exclusive
thanks to everyone who helped out yeah
Dinah for making the the layout
mm-hmm
and I mean everyone else included in the
team
and again thank you to the en members
who
took the time out of the days to make
the skin to make the videos
and you know get creative and so on yeah
yeah yeah I I doubt that I will organize
this again next year
it's too much work but um I think next
year it will just be a management
planned project so expect a lot of
delays
[Music]
expect a [\h__\h] ton of delays all right
me
yeah
um the videos I told the girls they can
make them public like after tomorrow or
so if they want
uh the sock puppet one will definitely
go public
and the URL I guess the website will
keep it up for maybe a couple more days
maybe until the end of the year and then
I'll think we'll take the website down
the you the the URL I had to buy it for
minimum one year so it will still exist
but I think we will take down the the
website I guess because I think hosting
it endlessly or maybe it takes up
resources I don't know
um
and next year it can just be remade and
next year I will be I won't be paying
for the URL next year
no no no I will let the URL run out and
then management can try to capture the
URL themselves
I'm not gonna pay for it again
yeah
easy it wasn't expensive anyway the URL
so they should be able to pay for it
I am
yeah I think you know they would
definitely open on doing it it's just
like the time when I came up with it was
too giddy giddy to last minute for it to
be something official
um but they ended up supporting it for
tweeting it every day and so on and and
letting me announce uh special things
during the some special Advent calendar
days so it was definitely supported but
it was too last minute for being like
organized by them so next year I think
we should be definitely possible
[Applause]
hmm
no it's okay it's all right it was my
pleasure I'm glad I could bring
something some Joy to the community
um during some rather lonely days
especially because not many of us were
streaming
no big collaboration
and yeah you know
I'm glad I could contribute
and yeah with that I will go now
um but do you guys know how much uh you
guys probably don't know because I
played offline some Pokemon
because I wonder how long it would take
me to finish
on Monday
I really need to read super chats I'm
very aware of that
we'll get over it we'll get over it
eventually but I'm planning on reading a
lot of them hopefully on Monday
thank you guys so much for the super
chats today I will get there I will get
there
but I can't like
I shouldn't straighten it unnecessarily
yet
thank you guys thank you thank you
and it was fantastic I'm glad you joined
it guys
thank you so much for supporting it and
checking in on it every day
and being patient sometimes
um
thank you thank you thank you yeah Merry
Christmas to you guys I won't say happy
new year because I'll see you before the
new year
and uh yeah I'm back
more or less yeah
so Monday stream Tomorrow song cover
um
yeah
I will try to get back into the more or
less usual Rhythm but you know the Japan
trip is coming up so that's the kind of
impossible
so excuse me I'm sorry I'm sorry I was
sick for so long it was really a
terrible timing um
but I guess it also gave me a lot of
time
to
like also mentally take a break
and you know what that's good that's
actually a good opportunity it was a
good opportunity
because having to stream every day
like recently I was also very very
stressed also because of like outside
um fact factors reasons
that have nothing to do with streaming
as well but like generally has been very
stressful
and actually the break was helpful for
my
Soul as well
thank you guys
[Music]
I'm looking forward to reading them
thank you guys so much for the support I
wish you a Merry Christmas
I hope you guys get some nice presents
or give yourself a nice present
mm-hmm
oh by the way I started watching
um
Ted lasso
because I was binge watching so much now
I'm watching teddler so so funny I like
it but holy [\h__\h] they're British accents
in in the show are so strong often I I
don't even understand what they're
saying I need subtitles
[Applause]
yeah Tad last was the Apple Apple only
show
finally got my hands on it
[Applause]
was really funny
I need stuff for British shows too
tangents oh my god oh it hurts okay I'm
gonna eat now and drink
so much a very Merry Christmas
you're happy and you know no no no I'm
not gonna stand
hmm
thank you guys I'm glad I could spend
some time with you guys on Christmas
thank you James Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas
yeah
Christmas always already over for me by
the way
hmm
bye bye bye bye
bye bye
bye bye bye what's up
bye
[Music]
I miss you guys I miss you guys
finally Pokemon
soon
TM
bye ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
ER to write the script so that um
there's never more than two sock puppets
on the screen because obviously I only
have two hands so and I I asked to have
like some kind of story where one puppet
gives something to the other and they
keep on giving it to the next person and
so on and then yeah you know yeah
good that I came back
then yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but it was
still tough to record that even though
there was only two at the same time
because I couldn't record it in one go I
always had to stop in between and then
change socks and then go again
I wish I had more hands
but yeah
[Music]