[Music]
so
cake candy cane
[Music]
hello
welcome
to
kiwawa fest let's go
let's go
how are you doing
i'll turn down
i'll turn the reverb off a little bit
wow
yeah
um
i'm
currently surviving on energy drinks and
one piece of bread for breakfast
it's 8 p.m
i'm doing okay
considering the circumstances um
today's stream will be a special karaoke
if you look at the top left you may
already see it says surprising about
seven songs planned that's the plan
could be earlier could be later um
and um
fly is my favorite song me too mine too
oh my god
um
uh now uh i have stuff to do after the
stream two as i also have before the
stream
um so there will be no superchat reading
afterwards um
i know i'm really far behind but next
week we'll do that okay we'll do super
chat reading stream again next week
um
yeah yeah uh yeah i'm currently in
a big hole of things to do
so sorry about that
uh but i want us to enjoy this stream i
want to sing for you guys and there's a
special occasion but i will not
surprise you with it just yet
yeah and just you have to be a little
bit more patient and surprised
[Music]
[Laughter]
because it's archived it's gonna be
pretty much
almost maybe only
um japanese songs because you know
licenses and uh
and i think
some songs you will not know
because they're idle songs some songs
you will know cause they're classic and
some songs you will definitely know
because there might be whole life songs
that i haven't sung before
so i tried to learn uh
two new ones
oh
i
got something in my throat i'm fine i'm
fine i'm using the mic that i got from
cali yeah it's kind of short though like
it's just uh you know it's really short
it's a little bit short let me scooch
scooch scooch
as good here over here i still need to
figure out the screen in the back like
because the screen is like kind of like
diagonal
i need to figure something out about
that
eventually for now the chat is chilling
there have fun chad i see you i'm
watching you we'll start off with a
classic to warm up all right
okay oh let's go wait let me write it
down and then oh you didn't hear that
thank god uh i will have to also adjust
the
audio levels a little bit
perhaps
i'll write it down before
i sing it
so that everybody knows what's up
kanakudi piano
from
40 mp
yeah
let's go
[Music]
i think it's the first time
m
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
uh
i had a feeling that i had a cat hair in
my mouth for part of the song
thank you
[Music]
i think i
have a typo in pierre little in the
english writing i guess it's double r
is it
nice thank you
thank you that was absolutely amazing
thank you
sweet
hello everybody
uh
we haven't done a karaoke in a while so
it's nice to sing some songs again
uh
i wish i could move my body together of
course as well but
yeah this will do
this will have to do
it's french not english well yeah no i
know but i mean i mean like in the
romanized version uh
i mistyped instead of the japanese
because i mean the title is supposed to
be japanese but
yeah putting it in
i'm not sure
oh my dishwasher is ready
let's go
susan what so
susan
small hiccup wee bag why is
what the why recently why does
susan interrupt my stream so often
monday
you could hear the beep
that was my dishwasher dishwasher wanted
to say hello hello dishwasher let's say
hi to dishwashing
hi
he's very happy to have your attention a
twist the twist is coming soon
twist
yeah can you repeat please i don't know
what i said i'm just saying uh susan is
stupid and dishwasher is ready um
people people
people people it's that people people
again thank you dishwasher i know you're
done i know
no need to like remind me several
million times
i'll show
you
rachel
[Music]
i don't know if i sang this one before
probably i probably did not this one i
probably most likely did but i want to
sing it again
just to fill up my set list because i
can't sing all new songs uh
i didn't have the time to learn that
much
i just i just love this song so much
i just love it so much
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
a
foreign
[Music]
my
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
me
[Applause]
so
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
that's such a great song oh my god so
did it
can't be kfc archivers did i sing this
one before
wait i need to update
uh the top thing as well
five songs
now that i remember oh maybe i really
didn't oh my god why not i guess i kept
it for another time
yeah it's such a good ah
song
i don't think so i guess i didn't
good then
now i think karaoke piero i also didn't
sing before
oh surprisingly more new songs than i
thought it was gonna be
yeah bluebird was one that i sang
several times
[Music]
[Laughter]
but i want to learn more
um because they have a really really
great choice of songs
but i need to learn more
i want to learn more
yeah
how are we doing 23. i see i see
wow wow
uh
okay let's switch this i want to change
this with this
our next song i don't think you guys
know unless you're a morning muslim fan
[Music]
peeps where are you at
where are you at
did you recognize that if you are a
morning muslim event did you recognize
that
[Music]
it's actually
i guess it's like a sub unit of morning
musume
what i'm gonna sing now
[Music]
now i haven't i mean i'm mostly singing
this just from listening uh to it
several times at concerts
so it might not be perfect when i sing
it but
at the instrumentals
the instrumental is kind of like nah not
so good but oh well er
no
sono
touch my heart
let's go
i hope i will be okay
this song is so good for concerts like
when i was practicing this today it's
like it loses so much when it's not an
actual proper concert with an audience
because they go crazy for the song they
go insane for this song in particular
you need to watch like a live
performance it's crazy so good
uh like in a yokohama arena or something
like a big arena venue oh my god let's
go
just imagine imagine
[Music]
hello and trail
hey
every time
i'm so proud of you
oh hey every time
i'm so proud
of you
catch my heart and touch me please
[Music]
touch my heart and touch me please
um
[Music]
bye
of you
[Music]
touch my heart and touch me please
m
[Music]
hey
i'm so proud
of you
[Music]
yes one of the
one one of the morning muslim classics
so to say yeah one muslim fans will
notice i'm sure or hello project fans
thank you
we're also proud of you you are ah well
then then we're mutually proud of each
other wonderful
the instrumentals from this channel in
general sound kind of like
like an old karaoke machine most of the
time
so the instrumental is a little bit lame
but the song is good uh i i saw you guys
liked it in the chat
i'm glad you liked it i'm glad i can
teach you some old idol songs yeah
i need to definitely
be able to sing more morning music
like i've heard them all before
but
singing them like myself i need to
practice
[Music]
the countdown the numbers what do the
numbers mean
it's four now
what
what does that mean
oh my god
all right
are they
ready indonesian fans here right now
people from indonesia donka
where are you at where you at where you
at where you at where you at
hello
[Laughter]
i'm glad you were awake
could it possibly be i practiced
yeah it wasn't even that difficult but
let's see how i sing without kobo's
voice in the background
uh i have for you
when is she gonna pull out a full
version and yo
i need the full version
we can sing it twice and it's almost
like a full version but we'll see if i
up then we'll sing it twice
if i do well then we'll just leave it at
that
vlc
indonesian membership
[Laughter]
let me see let me see is cooper
streaming kubo
is she streaming
she's online on discord i'm gonna sing
it now
i'll send her the link to the stream
just in case she wants to maybe
check it out if she's available
she's not streaming all right then we
have a chance
yeah okay don't know if she'll see it in
time i don't know
uh i warned her several times that i'm
gonna sing it
i don't know the score will stay up late
does she i wonder she's
she i feel like she would sleep around
1am at the latest
so
but i i just got the instrumental from
her like
an hour ago
so
she might still be awake
sorry i'm 30 minutes late why you better
watch the vod once it's ready
and you missed some good stuff yo
eh no no no i'm singing mantra now don't
worry
[Music]
okay okay are you guys ready
my first
attempt at uh indonesian language
song
okay
god i'm nervous now i'm gonna up
hi
i hope it's not too loud
[Music]
masala
uh
[Music]
yay
oh man i was so nervous right now that i
didn't sing so well i feel like i can do
better
how was my what was my pronunciation
okay
[Laughter]
how was that
it's actually not so difficult to
pronounce like i have more problem
troubles of other songs with other
languages i would say um
i learned from kobe
[Music]
one more time what's so short goddammit
okay
[Music]
down
um
[Music]
masala
foreign
[Music]
i think this one may have been a little
bit better
i love this song so much
now i was also trying to learn
reyna songs but
i couldn't make it in time i'm so sorry
next time next time i swear um sorry
lenny you're next i already got the
instrumental frolina songs
[Music]
i'm glad you liked it guys
oh
did i wait one i originally wrote seven
so now it should be now it should be
free right one two three yeah yeah okay
let me update
the numbers are
holy macaroni what's up
yeah singing trying to sing in
indonesian was fun i want to try more
hope i didn't mess it up too bad thank
you soon everybody
i'm not done quite with singing whole
live songs but some some more later for
now
let's chill a little bit i'm
probably gonna mess this song up but
uh let's see
so it's a difficult song
next up
i don't think i've sung this one before
either i could be wrong but i don't
think so yeah i don't i don't think so
but
from supercell
musa
[Music]
me
i
[Music]
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
me
da
[Music]
do
me
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm so sorry ah the bridge i the
bridge up so bad because i got
not the bridge though
that you know what i up yeah i
didn't
i forgot too nervous too nervous
the rest was okay we'll challenge it
again sometime
ignore everything uh no ignore that part
but the rest
is okay
ah no not the chords course was fine
yeah nervous jaw never straw
[Music]
surprising two songs
yeah
i can sing more supercells now
supercells supercell songs now because
we got more permissions
let's go
let's go where's my next song i want to
sing more
oh
another new song wait so far
so far every song is new i thought i
thought i didn't have so many new songs
in my set list but
now that i think about it
pretty much every
every song is new
okay
there might only be
one or two songs in here kobo you missed
it should i sing it again i'll sing it
again okay
okay third time third time's the charm
listen listen
stay now okay don't leave now i'm
singing it for you now okay let's go
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
yeah the greeting at the end it has to
be
can't do it without yeah
[Laughter]
at your service
oh yeah like i tried to make do the same
kind of thing with kiki kiara because
there's a lot of keys in there i thought
it could work you know
i'm also kind of a sunshine you know and
a whole lot of english people call me a
sunshine so it's not too far off
indonesian joseph i got indonesian josue
thank you
i'm proud of my mom
ah i hope you make a full virgin kobold
that's that's what your mama your mommy
wishes that you make a full version of
this song go go go go i want to sing the
full version
yeah i love you singing
sing my songs next okay
singing songs exchange i can give you
all my instrumentals no worries
i wanna hear kobo saying
[Music]
every song but which one would fit her
the most maybe her challenger because
it's cute
oh okay
you don't sound so excited about it
maybe she's pressured pressured
sparks is
oh
i feel like i mean she can sing any song
but i feel like sparks is not so
not so
much like you know kobo style
but oh ukulele if she does a ukulele oh
no a guitar version guitar version of uh
sparks then no it might be
overwhelmingly amazing
yeah all right kobo go back to sleep
it's okay unless you want to stay
i'm having a special surprise in two
songs
yeah singing uh mantra
three times does not change the number
it's still two songs left
so next
uh where's my list
okay
uh where did that karaoke go
this one was this one
yes okay
um
okay this one also
the
the hook the hook might be a little bit
suss
as well but
let's try
my best toss my bestest
let's go it's a caion song
a new one that i haven't sung yet i
think
i think it was like from the second k on
the ending i think
no thank you
[Music]
up
let's start from the beginning
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
songs
thank you
[Music]
foreign
yeah that was no thank you
[Music]
no thank you
from keon
thank you thank you thank you good mix
today i would
uh
now
count down
not me
now i think
i can get rid of that
[Music]
um
fashion monster
let's go
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
surprise
[Music]
i wanna be free
monsters
[Applause]
[Music]
time
fashion
[Music]
flushed
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
i
[Music]
the surprise was
me a new hairstyle yeah
cute right
you want to take some photos of me
before we continue
[Music]
wait let me uh
i can put the uh i can put the chickens
on my head too and i could can put the
blaze around and all that uh i just
can't add the flowers to it but besides
that it's pretty much you know same
options yeah cute
what happens if i mirror myself well
then i'll just be mirrored
that's mom hair no
cute hair i wanted a side
and
side ponytail with a
is okay what are you talking about it's
just a normal hairstyle
oh no no it's just a cute hairstyle
come on
no
it's okay um i can i can
i can come back to life it's digital
eh let me do the other one
and we can do this and maybe that looks
even more like a mommy
[Music]
what do you mean i'm gonna die because i
have the dad mommy hairstyle
no oh no i don't want to
oh i have so many plans for my life
don't do this to me
i'm safe
okay you'll protect me i won't die
okay thank you
close up
sniffing my hands
okay i guess that looks a little bit
like mommy but no i
would say you know i was very very um
have to say
uh
again with the same with the different
with the other hairstyle i was very very
strict with like the details like
these little strands of curled hair i
was very very very very um
demanding there
like you know so just i wanted it to be
curled and then i wanted some strands to
be like kind of loose and not not all
just one block of hair yeah
yeah
which one do you like more now don't you
guys
you prefer from the previous one
compare
[Music]
what
this was before but i can take off the
flowers you know but yeah it's still the
the formal updo
don't make me decide
down this one do you mean the the long
hair one down one the new
one oh so many people that like it
[Music]
well then then we shall continue this
i know it's cute right
[Music]
when yeah i was very very picky and like
i don't know what's the right word to
choose but like
uh i corrected a lot in like the
original draft like oh this is how
i wanted to be and all that
old is good too
all right
i'm glad you think so
they're both good yeah
yeah
cute all right then we shall sing a song
with this but um
now
it might get kind of sad in the coming
songs so
be prepared
[Music]
um
then this is the right hairstyle
i i guess so
well finally finally for the first time
in history chihuahua sings violet
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
oh
why am i so nervous i could sing this
better what the i'm so nervous
is such a pretty song
isn't it ah such a good song i want to
release like a more
i mean the chorus gets pretty
loud but generally i want to release
some more calm song like this at some
point too
calm calm and
serene and gentle
thank
you yeah sentimental sentimental i guess
i guess it's sentimental but
when we're speaking of sentimental now
this is where it really gets sentimental
um
the following
uh three
songs are dedicated to sana and she
doesn't know
uh that i she knows that i'm gonna sing
a certain song but she doesn't know i'm
singing three songs
i don't think she's listening either but
maybe she'll
see the um
vod
now this is one song that i've sung
before i think
the first one
now they're japanese so maybe the
meaning doesn't come across to most of
you but
they have meanings that i thought are
fitting for you know
dedicating them
to
[Music]
my
me
[Music]
so
oh
[Music]
my
a
[Music]
is
a really old song
about leaving a place or somebody
leaving a place uh
but you still go to the places that
remind you of that person
and you're not forgetting about the
memories
i mean you know i didn't i don't um
i didn't you know i have so much uh
to do with sana i'm gonna be honest like
time zones and
her being like
not around that much uh
kind of like you know where in the way
um and i didn't expect this to
happen
for a long time so
i thought you know i thought eventually
i gonna we're gonna
be able to
you know become closer eventually
because i've always thought you know we
could be
we could get along so well
um
and i kind of regret that i didn't
properly make use of it
and that should teach you guys a lesson
you know
i mean i can still be in contact with
sana but it's not quite the same
but i should teach you the lesson that
you should make use of the time you have
with people
as long as they're around that sounds
very dramatic i mean sana is gonna
continue living on
but you know
yeah
well well well i have another song for
her my throat probably also partially
because of the energy drink that i drank
today well when uh and the lack of sleep
my throat is getting worse but it's okay
we have a few more things to sing
yeah cherish those around you
that's the lesson
um
i shall next song
is uh what was it again
full bloom
cherry blossom
[Music]
yellow
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
me
day
[Music]
know
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
uh
yo
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is empty right
there's one left but it doesn't really
help that much oh well
um
one more song that how do you know it's
just one more song left i'm i mean i
mean
let me see
i actually
i planned
at least two more songs actually three
more songs but
give me a moment
oh yeah for santa one more song but then
i have a few more songs
it was at least originally planned
[Music]
yeah
okay i'm trying to get the most out of
this
um
fruit
gummy
i wonder if i can sing with this
[Music]
if i just keep it on the side of my
mouth
thank you guys
but for sana
for sana i will do it
next song is
of course
astro girl i freaking love it so much
i just oh my god
um
[Music]
you're probably sleeping
but
one more song
for you
and this lurks
okay
god
[Music]
can i redo
time i love you all
[Music]
i knew it was there but then i was too
shy okay i'm sorry one more
[Music]
the intro is banging anyway
starlight you shine illuminate the sky
the endless void reminds me of ian's
gone by
and that's your girl watching galaxies
rise and fall
[Music]
i'm not alone
when our hearts were bigger than the sun
there's no challenge we can't overcome
so send them over and watch our
supernova explode
i'm not alone that you are here the
constellations are so clear your gravity
is pulling here until our hearts go
light
what's that the light will dark it's
nice got the customer setup
[Music]
somehow
the universe is fun now
i'm not alone
[Music]
girl watching her story come and go
wondering the punch line of the joke
like a comment came into my orbit i know
i'm not alone
[Music]
[Applause]
when our hearts grow bigger than the sun
there's no challenge we can't overcome
so send them over and watch
the constellations are so clear
infinitely so good for me as long as you
are by my side
now
i'm not alone
[Music]
[Applause]
i love this song so much
i love it so much
what's the twist my new hairstyle are
you blind
the twisters i got myself a new
hairstyle a young
how people not realizing this
ah
yeah astral is so good i want to sing it
a million times i'll be singing it in
the future too yeah when my voice is
doing a little bit better
then i'll sing it again and again and
again and i'll continuously remind you
of sana if you want it or not
now
i know that was kind of sad maybe
um but i wanted to sing some songs for
sana
now
[Music]
ah stupid instrumental kinda go find it
again
there it is
oh is it there is that it that's it
one last song i want to sing a little
bit more but uh i'm not
doing so well anymore
it seems so
one last song
and it's a song that you guys heard
before and then if you watched my
birthday concert and you guys liked it
very much
so i was like alright if you liked it
that much i'll sing it again
but it might be not so good this time
we'll see what i can do
foreign
[Music]
i'm alive still breathing stop to hide
done grieving realized that to survive
someone's got to stand and buy and i've
tried to believe in only time stops the
bleeding i'm not waiting anymore i know
what i came here for
[Music]
[Applause]
coming for blood
[Music]
be the last one to laugh and you run out
of breath catching up
i'm a friend and a half baby you don't
even know me at all
i'm alive still kicking break the rules
rewrite system and my story wasn't done
sharper knife and rock the guns cut the
cord burn the witch and you'll regret
what you're missing and i'll take it to
the grave that's the price that you pay
yeah
because feelings are
temporary but broken hearts give the
spies
to darkness no
[Music]
be the last one to laugh when you run
out of breath catching up
baby you don't even know me at all
[Music]
higher
cause feelings are temporary
[Music]
be the last
yet
[Music]
yeah that was actually not so bad
if it's a high voice i can still do it
pretty well
in that case
you want an uncle
that is pretty high
uh
pretty damn high
yeah
[Music]
that's so good so good
yeah
okay i wonder if i signed this before
because it feels like i did just because
i know the song for so long but i maybe
didn't so
last song
for real zones
is
met
[Music]
la la la la la
la la la
[Music]
oh
hey
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
a
foreign
[Music]
wow
la la la la
[Music]
foreign
that
[Laughter]
[Music]
of course i lied
hi
[Music]
a
you
[Music]
um
me
[Music]
is
foreign
hey baby
[Music]
so much fun this song oh man
i think you can notice that i've sung
this song a million times in my lifetime
yeah
one of the
of the songs i know the most
nah that was it now i got some songs
done that i really wanted to sing so
yeah
um and i think
besides
besides for blood and water that was all
first timers
i'm pretty sure
yeah and then four blood wasn't even you
know in the normal karaoke stream was in
the concert so
previously
oh yeah yeah my voice is
a little bit better oh thank you thanks
to that uh throat drop maybe even
but generally
yeah i'm not at my bestest uh
so yeah and i i have some stuff to do um
next week i'm being kind of busy um as i
said in a previous stream i won't be
around that much but i just want to show
you guys this ah
urgently before
i go i i had it you know it was already
originally planned uh actually to come
out originally but then
uh it didn't make it in time
with the original reveal
so i was like all right i guess let's
let's like do it later so we have
something exciting for later
yeah
is this high so hairstyle only for this
outfit yeah it is yeah
yeah yeah it do be like that um
will that bring your schedule
no
yeah
no schedule next week
so maybe sorry sweet my story
i hope you enjoyed today um i wanted a
non-archived karaoke at some point soon
too
perhaps within this month you know
archived kind of restricts me a lot but
uh i found a few songs as you can see
that um
are nice to sing in uh archive streams
too yaya
yeah and we got kobo to listen in and
then i sang some songs with sanya nanya
so all is good my mission has been
accomplished
my job here is done
if you want to
screenshot do it ha ha
i know you want it
now some soothing tea
yes yes please
[Music]
yeah
thank you so much for your love and
support and next week we'll do super
chat reading some time during the week
i'll keep you guys updated follow me on
twitter so that you will stay updated
and stream favorite night and with that
i say and in german we say avina zayn
thanks for the two lovely fun streams
today yay
the surprise was this new hairstyle
honestly what's what's with people
coming in like what's the surprise
what's the twist
this is your hairstyle oh my god did you
think i already had that or did you not
notice you know in the world is mine one
of the first lines is um i want you to
notice my new hairstyle
when i was singing that line i was
reminded of it i was like oh yo that's
actually so fitting
yeah why don't you notice my new
hairstyle
stupid saucy bucket don't even notice my
new hair so even though it's so
obvious
[Laughter]
notice notice me
don't test me notice my hairstyle
yeah but nice hairstyle but what's the
surprise oh you you must be kidding
right you're kidding now aren't ya this
is a surprise isn't this surprising
enough to you i think it's quite the
surprise quite the nice thing to
surprise you guys what are you are you
not satisfied
you're not satisfied
it's not like i did it for you anyway
all right
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
i wish i had hair oh no
i wish i could give you some of mine but
it's orange i don't know if you want
orange hair
when is the funeral oh shut up okay i'm
leaving
[Laughter]
no i'm not you dead mother
oh man
and in german we say
hopefully the same
have a nice weekend everybody
yeah skye youtube youtuber
catch you on the flip side yeah
thank you
[Music]
do
you