[Music]
goodbye
you woke up wearing your disguise never
give me something I don't think twice
[Music]
you won't find another baby
tonight treat me like treat me like
ladylike treat me like ladylike
oh yeah
[Music]
the
stupid girls
[Music]
foreign
like a lady
[Music]
treat me like ladylike
no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
I'm alive still breathing stop to hide
ungraving realized that to survive
someone's got to stand and fight and
I've tried to believe in only time stops
the bleeding I'm not waiting anymore I
know what I came here for
cause feelings are temporary but broken
hearts keep the skies
the darkness no longer scares me I'm
chasing and hunting and this time I'm
coming from
[Music]
being the last one to love when you run
out of breath catching up
[Music]
baby
wasn't done sharper knife and cut the
guns cut the cord burn the witch and
you'll regret what you're missing and
I'll take it to the Grave that surprise
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm chasing and hunting and this time
I'm coming
be the last one to laugh when you run
out of breath catching up
[Music]
baby you don't even know me at all
yes thank you thank you thank you and
well welcome everybody first of all to
my concert and I hope you enjoyed the
first two songs how was it how was it
how was it thank you thank you thank you
I hope I already got you hyped up this
is gonna be a really fun show but a fun
show also needs some special guests some
people to talk to maybe some call-ins
some games and don't worry I got you
covered I have invited a very special
friend to play a very special game
together with and my friend is none
other than my audience member
yeah
today happy birthday
[Music]
thank you yes
Japan number one Idol in my heart so I
thought that the following game would be
very fitting um so I fought up this game
the rules are the following first of all
the name is
the following I say a Japanese word and
they usually are built up in syllables
so the syllable that it ends with ninety
will have to think of a new word that
starts with that syllable and then we
keep on connecting and connecting until
someone makes a mistake or says a word
it already has been said but here is the
twist we can only use Idle Words or cute
or girly words feminine words so
anything that's cutesy and not only yeah
I think us too we shouldn't have any
issues with that is
[Music]
doki
ah wonderful hello
round one I win one point for her
okay okay okay okay
dude
you
okay you you you diva
blue movie
[Music]
Superman
I said that Sakura sit in there
um
[Music]
foreign
yeah foreign
[Music]
good good
morning
[Music]
good morning
no no no
hey
[Music]
e e e e e e e e e e
oh no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
because I lost so we decided that we
both we both win in the end yes well I
may have won twice and she may have won
once but in the end we are odd ends so
all is good we love each other world is
beautiful world is peace
foreign
[Music]
land down on the floor late night and
you don't know don't know don't know
what to do I have to tell what's wrong
what's right
[Music]
don't forget what I said
get out of your head life is only what
you make it you're gonna be okay
go ahead and do it do it if you want it
let's get to it everybody's gonna know
your name cause Sparks like the flame
[Music]
spikes
that's how we
how we let you heard what I said get out
move your head life is only once you
make it you're gonna be okay
[Applause]
[Music]
ashes
[Applause]
[Music]
so don't be afraid
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
but sometimes I do don't you think of
the things
[Music]
telling me
foreign
[Music]
hey hey come on baby
thank you
[Music]
hey come on baby baby
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
put Daddy
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
you looking at me
today
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
that is
[Applause]
[Music]
all right everybody how was that did you
like the previous songs it was the
biggest
Ohio from honey works yeah
um especially the the I was really
excited to perform for you guys because
it's a hello Braddock song that probably
a lot of you guys don't know but did you
like it did you like it did you like it
it's pretty cool yeah
it's good so next up we will have more
guests more guests more guests
previously was nanichi who could
possibly be my next guest what do you
think guys
cool well more friends are coming none
other than my beloved ter Duncan
remember
[Music]
[Applause]
very happy thank you to for coming for
flying over here like the birds you are
yeah
[Music]
well I'm already doing gestures but I
wonder what are we doing with you guys
oh what could it be
[Music]
the typical game that you have to play
when you're in 3D well I think we have
like a synergy
synergy so whatever movement I do you
will understand right
yeah of course okay actually
uh the words are provided by none other
than who is somewhere behind the scenes
so she will feed me the birds I will act
them out and you guys will guess them so
shall
Shall We Begin
yeah
yeah okay word number one
[Music]
animal
uh
Turtle oh
slow
[Music]
snake
breathing
the slimy slimy it's slimy slime
slimy a snail snail
[Music]
s
[Applause]
yes
um
brush my teeth
with with
toothbrush yes
people people
OMG
[Laughter]
thanks a juggling okay circus
[Applause]
[Music]
okay last word I think last word last
word last word right okay let's do this
um
okay chicken dance
chicken dance chicken yes
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay my dad one more
you you you
[Laughter]
as me losing after such a winning streak
I think I lost
that's
[Music]
but I
said
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
but it's okay we're still the four out
of five well
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you to very much for coming
bye
[Music]
I'm tired of the same song every day
like it's on repeat I need a whiskey
breakdown oh honey
[Music]
can you make it original
take me away like it's just the two of
us
[Music]
I don't need no drinks tonight give me
that please
[Music]
thank you foreign
come alive
[Music]
you don't need no drinks tonight
foreign
[Music]
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
come on
[Music]
foreign
go back
[Music]
[Applause]
could you tell me please
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
I wanted to see it once again my
favorite night is a new very new my
newest single so I hope you're listening
to it a lot are you of course okay if we
always streaming kiwamu songs thank you
very much for your support so your
father was done with Collins huh no no
no no no there's more there's more
there's more
aren't we missing certain myth members
um yes we are of course we are so please
come and say hello to
good
night I can't wait wait wait I I I wanna
do
hello
[Music]
birthday you could say it's not my
birthday but it's my birthday
[Music]
is so cute
finally finally like I can do my whole I
can show off my body in 3D like for the
whole stream yeah it's so detailed and
beautiful
figure is very nice what's your favorite
part your tummy window
[Music]
you can only see that in 3D right in the
little wings too are precious
yeah is he gonna pull out your sword
you're gonna get your sword out someday
for us oh that's a good question well
maybe another time maybe maybe at a 3DW
stream which this is not right yeah
right right all right well girls we are
the same generation so one would assume
that you know a thing or two about me
right
have now met in real life thankfully yay
yeah you have hopefully a lot of
knowledge about me and I will test that
with them
yeah
I have five questions for you girls and
if you answer at least four of the
questions correctly then I shall take
you out to dinner sometime oh cool I'm
just gonna ask for a prize of course
it's a surprise yes there's always a
prize at kfp so are you ready for the
first question
Get It On by the way you can work
together if you want oh what it is yeah
let's do it yeah put the two the two the
two biggest brands in the whole live
myth together yeah there should be no
problem what are you calling yourself
again the boneheads no bone Bros
[Laughter]
we'll solve all the questions
now we got this unlock it's just math
just don't ask us about math no no I
don't even know math either so the first
question are you ready yeah yeah it's
crazy question number one
what does kfp stand for
Kentucky Fred Phoenix
did you say Cara Kentucky no I I I've
never heard of that place I said Kiara
you guys misheard sorry
Phoenix I I know
I should almost give you a minus point
for that answer no no no no please don't
take away my degree in chiarology please
excellent that was easy though it will
get more difficult maybe maybe
uh-oh all right next question I wrote it
down
what is it I am okay question number two
okay yeah imagine some quiz lights quiz
quizzes
yeah okay
[Music]
okay a new rule I will only allow
correct answers if he had one if you
lock in one wrong answer that's a no
point all right girl don't [\h__\h] this up
yeah all right like okay
second original single heart Challenger
yeah
I was gonna say that too
sorry Goombas you need to give her some
time yeah to shine because I need to
shine okay girl the next one's yours
I'll be faster I'm leaving the hard ones
for girl actually it's all part of my
plan
by the way what what was Kiana's Virtual
Song by the way
foreign
did you uh probably acoustically Oh I
thought you said first no sorry I can't
yeah my th8 sounds like an F
it's okay it's cute
number three of my song was but that's
not a question Sparks yes okay good
thanks like the flame
okay no that was not the first question
the third question is coming now can I
see it this is uh okay okay now this one
let's see question number three
what's the name of the mouse slash rat
that I lived with in Japan
I know this oh I'm gonna let her answer
yeah let's see I feel like I've been
told this before Oh [\h__\h] if you know
this oh no oh do you need to vote a
friend
um
Okay Casper
so
the easy ones Man actually just police
and Remy just recently I uploaded a
video uh Allure video that explains the
whole story behind Casper on my channel
so if you guys are curious you could go
watch that if you want to learn more
about Casper mysterious yes
[Music]
at first I hated him then I loved him
okay fourth question question if you'll
get this one right then you already have
a free dinner with me
so thank you for carrying Cali
no you got this girl you definitely got
the next I don't know if I do that
okay question number four
how many three debuts
have no think before you yell it out
loud
um something
wait what counts as a reader view well
and not debut but debuts after the red w
I do have a history referee that was
there hasn't been one in a while but
there was a time where I had many
reasons for many red WS
I might know this
[Music]
too but I don't know okay girl let's
brainstorm
um
the next one was the German one right
right right right okay so I think it's
two the other thing is two are you sure
yeah I think it's two
[Music]
okay okay well I still have one more
question though they're a winner chicken
dinner from the chicken let's go I think
we're four for four so far yeah
a little bit too easy so nah the next
question you will have to answer
correctly otherwise otherwise
yeah it will be changing the rules on us
can we Double Down do we get dessert too
of course of course right let's do it
okay excellent last question and how
should we do this
um I want your separate answers
so what happened wait no change okay I
want no I just want to see if you both
get it right without hearing the others
answer first okay I'll take off my
headphones okay okay ma'am um but wait
no how do I give you a sign that you
should come back whatever just bring it
back in in 30 seconds okay okay do like
throw up like um some kind of weird like
hand symbol uh okay I'll do this do a
little heart yeah and then I'll come
back all right
I actually have a feeling you'll get
this one right really oh okay spell out
for me without thinking too much you
have to say it quickly
Alf vidas in
[Music]
how we
the
auf Alpha is the first part B the of
using v i e d e r s
e n
it's hard to follow you Final Answer go
Aus V
i e d e r s e n
one
okay Kelly come back can we come back
all I heard was wrong
is that part of a question throw it at
me no Charlie Kelly recently
um had a lot of fun learning German with
me so you might [\h__\h]
the German question yes all right buddy
spell and you have to do it quickly okay
no thinking spell my ending greeting Alf
readers V
[Music]
I
mean uh
oh [\h__\h] that's too hard of a question I
thought this was not a spelling bee
oh chicken
let's see
no
um no no it's not a river Dashi it's
it's Evita Zane
what the [\h__\h]
I mean beep that out beep that out
whoever's editing this it's okay on my
channel it's allowed yeah okay well you
know what I said double down but I'm
still gonna treat you for dinner yeah
thank you
winner winner and chicken dinner from
the chicken as in the chicken is the
dinners from the chicken not the dinner
it doesn't mean that the dinner is um a
chicken it's from the chicken it's the
winter winner uh chicken I'll shut the
[\h__\h] up now thank you Kiara happy
birthday thank you what's the answer you
can't just leave us hanging oh
space
[Music]
since I just sell it out I will say to
you girls and
[Applause]
[Music]
all right on to the next songs
all right guys
[Music]
okay
wow
[Music]
hey
my teeth
[Music]
later
boys
[Music]
and let down again
wow
[Music]
here
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
I see
fruit
there's no one else in this world that I
would trade for you
[Music]
together
hey
wow
[Music]
yes
remember a while ago at dokomi where I
had backup dancers who were doing the
dancing for me and now I learned it
myself and performed it myself yay that
was fun hope you enjoyed that well you
know if you look at the time you might
think oh it's gonna be over soon yeah
there is one more song but before that
let me say a few words to you guys
special yeah we're we're getting close
to the end and I wanted to do something
like this for a long time as you
probably know and I wanted to show off
my dance moves for so long which is it's
one of my I guess most prominent skills
and it has been my dream tends to start
to show it off to get into this 3D body
finally be free to do whatever I want
yeah today has finally come I hope you
guys enjoyed it so far yeah
I want to definitely say a big thanks
[Music]
for helping so much with the recording
and the setup you know I'm gonna
basically build a whole studio for me to
record this and I really really really
appreciate that and without her it
wouldn't have been possible at all
and also big thanks to Canada for
putting together all of this into a
proper concert and even creating this
beautiful stage here wow look Isn't it
nice
yeah thank you so much in the future I
really hope that I can do more like this
more often and get more members to join
me in 3D if possible to dance together
yum
especially you know
mythology
with all of them I Wanna Dance and you
know have fun together and I think we're
getting there slowly but surely
um by the way if you missed it the
birthday merchandise as announced it was
announced in the previous stream and
before this one the countdown stream and
it's linked in the description so please
go check it out if you're interested and
yeah last but not least I want to thank
k f p you know how much I appreciate
your support and you believing in me and
trusting in me means the world to me so
thank you for giving me the strength in
a very very stressful period leading up
to this day yeah
I think it was worth it yeah so thank
you for waiting for me and I will
continue working hard to give back to
you as much as I can please continue
supporting me and watch me grow into a
bigger bigger bigger bigger Phoenix
yeah now
there's one more person I want to thank
but I will do that with a song so please
listen to that last song
that's all
like
[Music]
morning
[Applause]
[Music]
crochet
your name
[Music]
saw your black Crush
ES
[Music]
thank you
sir is
[Music]
forever
thank you
[Music]
I saw this
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]