[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
good morning
and first of all let me say happy
birthday
[Music]
apparently it is our bosses yago's
birthday today
oh God cat hairs I can't clap
bye
[Laughter]
yes yes happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday dear
younger happy birthday to you
um okay
our best girl hey
hello hello hello
welcome to a sponsored stream the stream
is sponsored by Countryside the game
that we are having a nice collaboration
with a cool collaboration so I'm gonna
introduce some things to you
um even though it was written in the
pinned comment a lot of people have not
really
um
realize that this is not a collaboration
in terms of the girls will be here with
me live and talking with me no but we
will hear their voices and we'll see
them moving we will see them moving yeah
um uh you you might hear from Ina
possibly uh right here at Ina's
multi-dimensional party
um
uh but before we dig in let me explain
it's a kind of Agata game okay
um that has been around for a while from
Korea and uh
I played it a little bit yesterday on a
private account but I was told to use
this account from them
um because I will have like all kinds of
gacha money and stuff probably
uh and and then I saw that I was not
supposed to log in I was told not to log
in because I will miss this cutscene so
I waited until now so I don't know what
it looks after this cutscene I just
played on a different normal account
with no gotcha money
but there's this cutscene that only
plays once
um so didn't want to miss this yeah
so so so so so so
uh I might be a little bit confused in
the beginning after this Cuts in but
let's hope for the best right and so far
who who here has downloaded the game and
and and looked around a little bit
there's so many cool features you have
to check it out you have to me really
there's a there's a a QR code above me
that I think leads you to the download
page
my phone cannot read QR codes so I don't
know
I think that's what it does though but
if first of all yeah if you're curious
about what's going on then check out the
QR code or in the link in the
description and I may sound a little bit
tired but I'm not tired at all
oh
no my phone is
Foundation I don't have a potato phone
no no no no no
it's a decent phone anyway let's hope we
get audio because right now I have no
audio here maybe it comes now
um let's just uh get started with this
for now and then hear it and see it inas
multi-dimensional party which I wonder
if it is a reference to her like
um outside tea drinking
um Garden kind of thingy that she has
remember
enough
this game has a lot of sweet
um cute references like that so
um it's really a lot of effort put into
it yeah yeah let's appreciate it and
also okay I hope I hope this goes well
let's go
audio let's go
oh oh okay oh this is not voice but we
voiced a lot of stuff okay so you will
still hear some stuff
let me try to be enough
anyone up for another cup of tea
I don't know
hey
do you have any red wine
ah yes Kelly I got one just for you I'll
be right back look how beautiful
[Music]
pretty oh my God
perhaps to the artists who had to draw
all of us especially Ina like look at
the patterns it looks exactly like her
outfit like her and it's moving so
nicely so smoothly I'm like so impressed
with the life could be work in this game
also it's way too loud I'm so sorry
for sure but the music's nice it's like
comfy
and look at can we oh she's got the huge
Scythe she looks she looks badass
oh thanks Cena
I think Kelly's voice I kind of got down
I
[Music]
boys I've
the best person to do my voice
[Music]
not my sword my sword is kind of flaming
and it kind of turned into a long spare
kind
which is so cool I'm so happy with that
what are you looking for your tail tells
me you're up to something
oh um it's nothing okay I really I can't
even attempt to do her voice oh oh
bounce bounce bounce
oh that was a tail wiggling
look at that tail winkling oh I'm a crab
dad Taylor throw it over the mountain
one day
oh here we go again
you always want to throw small people
over mountains maybe one should throw
you for a change
yeah yeah Kelly does like to do that eat
as if I'll get caught that easily
unless you don't have a reflex like a
hawk like I do you won't stand a chance
look at that smug face look look at the
smog face and look at those hips though
good job artist good job good job good
job
but but you were kusoti chicken
[Music]
I'm a phoenix oh my God I can't take it
this is unbelievable what what I'm I
can't I can't I can't
same thing no
no oh my God have you not learned
anything in school Cali all right you
two calm down and Kelly here's your
glass of red wine wine why did they not
do that wine wine
why did they not insert that hmm
the Wine's fragrance is so good thanks
Inna
now what about my teeth
[Music]
her default outfit even with the coat
does not hide her Bubba anymore Bubba
that much
I think normally to me it always looks
like there's not that much there but
there is and then look here you see it
very clearly
I got yours as well of it let me grab
another cup
please please
[Music]
I can't
I wish I could do voice acting
just I just thought about this but if we
make the inside of the teapot to time
leap ah would we be able to infinitely
pour out tea
sure you know yes
oh that's a nice interesting question
and the answer to your question is yes
it's possible
I just I just realized
obviously British so obviously tea time
is just her thing look at the clock
so pretty wow and her huge coat
everything is
so big
except We'll Never Land
we need to be
Evelyn
we necessary expected to make the tea
the old-fashioned way
it's the old-fashioned way
really oh want to experience time
traveling
better go to crony for that
oh
um what's going on
my letter
the one that I was going to read later
did you lose it
I didn't lose it it was in my pocket I
swear and for some reason it's gone now
wait wait that outfit has a pocket
I guess
yeah
it does
don't worry about it Coda it's not the
end of the world
yeah it's not a big deal it can simply
write another one
perhaps the letter is inside a teapot
let me take a look wait why why why why
why why why why why would it be in the
teapot what
put it in there Ina that's the only
reasoning what
what
Nina I'm pretty sure there's nothing
inside the teapot no I'm 100 sure there
is nothing did you check did you check
well I'm kind of on your side there Cali
but did you check
no
which one is more like on this
a man
I think it is time to use my clock
Google when was the last time you knew
you had your letter on you
oh what third one what what did I ask
what ah the first laugh okay
um I think it was when Nina was giving
out
something to everyone
you mean a team that starts with
twinkling teeth
that's not a pun right that's just okay
um yeah I know I definitely had it in my
pocket at that moment look she has
pockets
at least she has pockets like there's
but girls you know there's so many
outfits that just don't have pockets
yeah we need more pockets
mm-hmm
right I think that's good enough
information get up around the clock
everyone well
crony is part of the collab what
going back in time to find kuda's last
letter okay everyone
oh is that our mission in like is that
what we came to counter-side for
[Music]
ever
time to rock and roll
I'm sure everyone can travel I mean can
that little clock safely allow all five
of us to travel we'll see we'll have to
test it out
it's about to
go well this is the first time taking
more than one person but
I'm sure there will be no problem as
long as no one touches the clock while
it's operating oh oh what happens if we
touch the clock when it is operating
Anything Can Happen really uh and that
that's why we need to be more careful
oh I see
well here gospel
[Music]
does it sound for real
oh
who stepped on my tail
sorry there's too much turbulence in
here
wait don't don't push me ah just gonna
touch it
ah the clock
oh God
oh no we touched it I think we touched
it
for Cali boys I think my Cali was pretty
good yeah oh Beach Paradise
where am I Beach
okay that must be like the game
protagonist aka me
ow where is everyone wait no that sounds
more like
[Music]
and it's scorching here sand is so hard
to step on and my stomach is growling
really bad
but that's beautiful oh my God it looks
like the Maldives
hahaha
I was so focused on finding my ladder
and forgot to eat anything at the party
what are you watching
HRT Barry's live stream
lined was reading chat no wait
Chihuahua's live stream huh who is who
is that
since when did you start watching HR
takanashikiara's live streams
well I had an interest in them for a
while now I'm just on their Channel
today because they said
they are doing a special worldwide
stream
oh maybe that's the account name
oh no it's counter-side streamer they
have a streamer I didn't know that
didn't show up in the tutorial
no streamer I didn't see a streamer
hey
no no let's say it's takanashikiwawa
hmm what the just who might you be oh
I'm good I'm a way bigger streamer than
you never mind about that can I look at
your phone for a sec
how many Subs do you have HRT Barry how
many Subs
what for the live stream yeah here but
you are uh
[Laughter]
battle
oh
where is this
oh are we in Seoul now
this is a scenery that I haven't seen
before
um oh they're separated oh no the last
thing I remember is when I accidentally
dropped on this clock uh don't tell me
is that why we all separated what was
that what was that slimy tentacles down
oh oh
[Laughter]
what did you press the stream now for
huh
[Music]
what follow me what what bummy's asleep
again we're streaming live across the
world and she's asleep are you serious
pull me done cute
live stream live stream huh
she's familiar to Dad
or bumbar
what where am I am I where am I where am
I we were together just a second ago oh
dear what happened with the others I
should get back to them right away
hold on everyone I'll be right there
wait that live stream
right live streaming I remember
that could be more efficient to find
everyone than on wings which I I'm 100
totally have
a lot of
can we oh can we
oh cool music here
hmm
scenery here is somewhat similar to that
of the underworld but this but different
well first off I need to find everyone
the problem is how
that is
hello everyone I'm HRT Barry's leader
Keon oh
cute hi that's one of the streamers
while smiling brightly
that that's manager manager you know
[Music]
it's manager is that is that what she's
been up to
what
oh I got an idea
screaming gears I need them right now
what's what's streaming gears
oh this is bad the clock sent us not
only to the wrong time but to a
different world as well
ah how am I gonna find everyone here
it looks nice here
nice beautiful weather well I'm a
detective number one detective I can
solve this problem too let's see I need
some sort of lead to start investigating
oh female student hey
isn't that HRT Barry they are
broadcasting on the LED Billboards too
worldwide today I wanted HRT Berry to be
my only Idol Oh you guys don't know
about whole life yet they'll change your
opinion about your favorite Idol after
finding on life
hey I see if there's a live stream here
problem solved
I guess so uh assuming that everyone
else will be listening to that live
stream
if this is Bailey has a huge audience
watching them I'm sure others will think
the same as I do oh
right everyone sure yes yes
you just get me
hello hi yeah
what's up humans
good morning afternoon and evening
[Music]
welcome to the special live stream
oh wow
um I think I'll just go for normal
um yeah sorry I I have to do some
settings now oh my God
look look wow wow wow Everything Is Us
oh my God so cool
[Music]
so cool
what a home love yeah also the loading
screen when you have to like get into
your account it's also all of us
it's so cute
not quite maxed accounts yeah not quite
but it's enough
okay
uh should I like already look at this
kind of stuff what is that oh oh it's
YouTube I'm scared of um playing that oh
oh my God oh my God it brings me to
YouTube okay we have to go through some
um stuff here I guess
so I will not really show you actual
gameplay but I do wonder if this game if
this account has played the game
oh yes it had okay
um
but mostly I'm here to play some gacha
and show you everything about the holy
moly Hall alive strange Hollow myth
collaboration
yeah click them click one oh yeah click
us I
oh
[Music]
there is nothing more intriguing than
learning more about the others I'm
talking
[Music]
whoa whoa see how it's like a bite from
that
my breakfast
can I oh
okay
anywhere
let me know if you want to time travel
with me
well now you're offering it but you just
everything up though
go so well she's already back to
bringing in more people to time travel
with her do you want to hear more Inna
guys
[Music]
oh
I guess sometimes they don't speak with
me
there you go
[Music]
wait but the BJ was kind of loud maybe
maybe we can um
make the PGM a bit more quiet let me
hide the screen for a moment because I
don't know
I don't know if you'll see
something you shouldn't be seeing sound
uh PGM
there we go voice higher
okay
that should
help let's try again
I'm the host of the show you want to go
to an amusement park with me nice I like
watching people yell on roller coasters
because it makes me laugh
she would laugh at me when I yell at the
roller coaster
yo yeah let the blood and Rhymes free
flow I know that line already
there look at her vibing
if my tentacles are ticklish
them for a bit not my fault if they get
all over you
I don't think anyone Minds more
more Inna speak to me
that's the same line we took up but
about like a hundred lines if not more
[Music]
cute cute okay so this is you know
the main screen main screen oh
I think you can probably like realigned
them differently
and then here
oh
is the holy moly whole life strange
whole myth uh like
interface I guess um
if you press on us here
you can also get some voice lines
okay okay they both say okay please stop
stop please stop now
she's really thankful she really changed
her mind on that one yeah um the artist
by Jazz Jack yeah a lot of cute art has
been done for this so this is the
starting screen and then here is a
little gacha screen
um I posted already something about this
on
um my Twitter last night when I was
testing the game I was cracking some
eggs we'll try it too but let me just
show you an overview these are missions
um that you have to fulfill like play
the game a little bit and use this
gotcha and to get some stuff yeah yeah
there's a lot of unlocked ones as well
and if you do all of these missions you
will get
one of these skins for free
at random
but if you want a specific one you can
also buy them
anyway here's a collection
[Music]
oh yeah collection rate 11 at the moment
yeah these trophies can be placed in the
dorm because we also have like a whole
setup of a room
um
okay let's look at them there's so many
versions of us and there's our our
mascots killed the chicken oh
listen
to
hear that
that's good
I recorded
um like her own version of humming to
the music I suppose you can hear it
every now and then
so yeah these are uh all the kinds of
trophies that you can collect and then
there's some composing thingy here
[Music]
um
but I have not really tried this one yet
so I can't really explain it to be
honest
you'll get something out of it something
anyway so I guess we can like start
right away with some gacha let's try to
get more of those trophies right I'm
gonna
show it to you here there you go
this is so
cute
it is so adorable they start out in this
Grass Grass screen I'm holding a chicken
there look I'm but I'm I'm covering the
eyes of the chicken and the whole face
oh it's so cute but yes she's got a
ground pound pull on uh what's an Amelia
let's go
what we get uh
Trophy and we can do that a lot more
times because I have so many eggs is
that the only
I don't want to waste them is that the
only way of using the eggs I think so
I think so we can let's do it 10 times
mission complete fighting limit mission
complete mission complete yay yeah just
pulling these uh a Millions
oh I got like an SSR so the good uh
small one I thought I can like dance in
the in the um dorm that you create and
so on it's really cute they can dance
and perform it's adorable they come in
3D kind of um
yeah oh look a lot of chihuahuas
uh free dupe koalas
a sleeping chicken
sandwich we just got an inner before
that
[Music]
wake up
but understandable it's not my usual
streaming time
it's purple this time oh
well cool
cute cute
oh you know it's reading the book I
never saw her reading the book before
cool cool
mascots some purple ones
we've still got some more
oh
nothing beats a ground pound
here they are more trouble there's lots
of Cali's this time
adorable and nine more times
[Music]
[Applause]
oh another purple one
a bad all right
then you can look at these ones here
sticker animated takanasikiara watch the
milia stand gaguda stand you know my
inner new stand
um
and then you go to your collection you
see now we have way more oh wait we got
all
was this already like this before
did I already have all five of these
ones before
those are the realizes ours and those
are awakened what I didn't get a single
SSR but here they are in our casual
outfits and then the fancy outfits and
in the kimonos
I didn't get any of those
no look how unlucky
and then we get these ones
[Music]
but now I could I guess
I could compose something can I
oh not enough I need like
two more here
ah
unfortunate anyway we can also complete
something here and then we get
egg
by collecting some Hollow Mill figures
wait is that the same egg no that's a
different egg
wait what's that egg for
not sure about the golden egg I can open
the egg
[Music]
free Essence
I know I know we got some like I also uh
oh God
I already have so much money
oh holy oh wow wow wow more eggs
[Laughter]
oh
whoa
okay okay okay uh we wanna also hear
some we have to do so many things okay
let's let's go first
so I really love her by the way I think
she's my favorite
Horizon I love her design she's so
God is like
but look at look at some of them here's
Ina Ina's new name is edel mightner but
basically how this works is
um there we are only skins that are put
on top of existing characters but the
one that I have is really powerful
actually like
special power yeah
um
see and then here's the screen look at
the background
maybe you already saw it in the preview
oopsie but yeah so if you have the
character you don't you can get the skin
before getting the character and then
just try to get the character eventually
and then you can put the skin on top of
that anytime so here we go to dialogue
and then we can listen a little bit want
to listen I want to listen to the
million million voice lines that I did
this is not even all
[Music]
make sure to order Lots from our kfb
branches okay
[Music]
oh she kissed me you won't kiss me
yay let's start another beautiful day
with smiles on our faces shall we hell
yeah I I am very Smiley and tired for
Smiley indeed
and the host of the show Hall on top
there is nothing more intriguing than
learning more about the others so true
I'm asking if I am a phoenix
believe League said that
one more down and I will send you
straight to the usual room oh no not the
YouTuber
anyway there's a couple of those yes yes
yes
ah
okay now uh I don't want to show you any
more of those um voice lines you gotta
get them for yourself but I want to see
where is this um
uh
Dom
wait don't don't don't do the
Contracting live concert is supposed to
be a thing
somewhere here
[Music]
loyalty loyalty
loyalty ah here there it is
there's just so much going on on the
screen okay this employee has reached a
Mass lottery and is now qualified for
the following effects all stats plus two
percent enter lifetime contract do you
want to enter lifetime contract with
koala
yeah
yes let's go
time to show off my negotiating skills
wait was that even it yes yes yes yes
I thought I had it
they sent it to me I thought they I
thought I had that okay well we'll check
that behind the scenes
I should have it
how come I don't have it
okay we'll check the egg though
if we go back to the main screen
uh and then two
storage
and here we can there you go we can
crack the egg let's do one first I think
I only have one anyway oh
we are here
all of those are wow
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that's a sign of trophy oh yeah hyped we
are happy we are here wow
oh
cute in you
well so many rewards oh my God
oh my God
by the way guys speaking of eggs
I will show you on the bottom left now a
coupon code you have to enter it exactly
like that yolk Kiana now
and what you will get is 10 Hollow
mythical eggs
that you can use in the game
um
[Music]
very very exclusive go get those eggs go
get those eggs
on the bottom left bottom left woke yolk
piano now you have to take care uh about
the capital capitalization yeah has to
be written exactly like that
um
and with this uh coupon yeah you get a
gacha ticket
and you can pull the gacha for 10 times
what'd you say about that Cali
talk to me
I ain't good Adam but I like playing
them hmm are you serious I am going to
use my real sight
snapping snapping yeah actually
yeah my weapon was changed but Callies
and goudas look the same and I don't
know about uh I mean Inna right now you
don't really see them like that but I
know I'm gonna use as a gun like a big
rifle or so I think and in a cast like
super cool big magic it's really sick
yeah
and anyway let me go back to uh no no no
no no let me go to management again
and let's take a look at Inya Mrs edel
mightner
and maybe listen to her dialogue a
little bit you want to hear her voice
[Laughter]
we haven't heard her in a while so let's
listen
hi my name is of course
um
[Music]
everyone everyone
has been a good taco Daddy I think so
small steps for world domination what a
big step for the taco dadd cheese
I already heard that one
maybe I seem so calm sometime because
I'm always freaking out
yeah she's always freaking out is that
your constant state really
oh too many crumbled houses around here
I hope they get fixed soon
just like my life
what that's so sad
no
worried about where I sleep
you're so sweet but don't worry I uh I
can't sleep almost anywhere yes yes you
can floor is best bed floor gang what's
up
enough of my own
[Music]
today's mission is to find inspiration
for a new drawing
oh oh can you draw me in yeah me and you
together drinking some tea I don't know
oh
yeah see you can hear some more Inna if
you're missing Ina then get the game
download the game and get yourself an
inner skin and listen to all all of
Ina's um voice lines well we don't know
when she will be back so for the
meantime this might be the only way to
hear her yeah and
um this skin is time limited obviously
it comes with a limited illustration
card and
yeah this is the only chance you will
get the skin before because yeah it will
well quite possibly never be released
again so don't
go get that SSR in yeah where are the
others here's Gouda
oopsie
want to listen a little bit
here let's go
Aquarium
wow cute doing something productive here
surely always
[Music]
wait it's not oh I like her voice acting
it sounds very natural
she says it's a fork it's a fork
ah skin button oh oh oh well here you
can see I guess more
um clearly oh yeah you can also see the
in-game SD
um cute and then can we watch this oh
one more
was when they activate like a special
skin skill and then this is all over
your screen then but honestly the
fighting animations are so flashy I kind
of want to try if we can uh do that
after we checked out everyone right
let's check out uh I'm a little bit
my clock looks special
you got sharp eyes oh practice oh this
clock right here
is a Sci-Fi clock yes if you want oh we
already heard that one in time travel
and listen to
this
young break oh it's time for a tea break
do I sound like her
you son nothing nothing
okay uh look at the skin
your skin and then here's her cute SD
and the skill cut in oh
what are as dangerous your pose
dangerous
wow but she's so cute okay
and then where's Cali here's cat oopsie
that's not Cali cute though
okay some dialogue from Cali
ready to read but Scythe is ready to
reap see I sound exactly like her catch
you on the flip side catch you on the
flip side
[Music]
Keepers to have one of those days you
know understandable have a nice day
finally
this game yeah hell
's cool
and here skill cutting
[Music]
hey oh look at those nails
stick
hell yeah
hell am I just got a base character oh
nice to her base character looks like
this by the way oh
wow actually
kind of Suits where makes sense doesn't
it
wanna look at the wait that artist looks
familiar to me
that artist looks like uh very familiar
to me like an artist that I follow I
don't wanna say anything in case it's
wrong
but yeah and wait what did I want to
check here
actually I don't know I see it I kind of
see it
oh
oh my God who is seeing you Aussie
okay that's uh that's ama's character
that you have to get in order to um play
with Ahmed
a
uh oh
God
oh my God
oh she's hacking cute yeah
[Music]
so many oceans
and then enough was someone called Ayla
nightner which sounds so German oh
pretty which is something like tentacles
looking not really though but with the
eyes oh no
oh
I like her Korean
um
voice acting by the way
yes yes Korean voice acting pretty damn
cool
um
yeah he is he's our inner again make
sure to select the inner skin yeah and I
have 100 loyalty with all of them
and then behind my character is a very
powerful awakened character look there's
like a phoenix
oh no look
show show me whoa
that was always me and then we
transformed and like she leaves the room
and what's left is this
[Laughter]
let me see oh
cool look then you guys are flying
flying
cheeky cute I love this this is so cool
the art is so intricate so detailed and
beautiful yeah
that's you guys yeah you can fly you
have like fire wings now okay okay
let's move to practice mode
wanna check that out for sure
and I see how they fight because the
animations are so flashy and so weak oh
oh yeah oh yeah here Place me
here show up look
here
it's so fitting solar flame you guys are
fine
sick
wow
solo play oh and voicing of course of
course
these are the the all of the voicelands
that I had to record
that I talked about like doing a lot of
um
hey yeah yeah kind of voice lens
can I
oh wait oh no
good night because I reset myself but oh
and I want to use the ultimate
oh
oh that was guilty
and did she use it oh the purple icon
above my head that one said I thought I
thought it was something else okay
purple I could well we'll try again go
flashing
and now there we go okay
[Music]
wow okay absolutely
blasted his ass
oh you guys
[Music]
oh
my God he's already dead he's already
dead oh my God
no one will survive that I'm telling you
let's look at Inya
want to see her fighting of course you
do of course you do
let's go check it out what she can do
going yeah
[Music]
action
here this is like a standard Attack
yo her legs so long she looks so elegant
and thick cool this is her skill well
you can dodge this
and ulti let's go you want to see the
ulti
I think
oh I heard the tentacle sounds
[Music]
she looks very powerful too
nice that's Inya got eaten
what tech
all right let's check out Gouda
uh practice go practice
bad ending Ina
yeah yeah it's about the same amount of
spooky
in as good as like a Defender I think
so she's on the front line see she's so
close to the enemy are you guys your boo
it's gonna be fine what so much water
oh
skills this is a skill poke
not not but
[Music]
again again
I want to see the whole thing
[Music]
cute oh this is so cool
so much action
I like her
um voice acting very much
all right look how Wings gonna give us a
live performance please everybody get
out your your sticks
the light sticks
level 110 Kelly whoa the way she comes
into the field is so cool and she floats
she flies yeah
oh
blast him away let's go
okay let's let's do this
holy it looks so powerful
I want to see it again
a bass
here we go yeah
yeah see today
yep yep yep the dead beats very very
very powerful looking so cool it's a
little bit basically we get them to say
all right yay
Anna
I almost skipped her
here we go
I love I love her because she has the
small animals around her
it's so cute
look at that look at that
she can use that rifle with one hand
bear up cute that was uh we are did you
see with the VR goggles maybe she will
grace us again
[Music]
let's do it
look at her animations please it's so
adorable it's so Dynamic too
oh one more one more
concoctions
[Music]
that FPS gamer coming through
yeah so those are what the in-game
animations of us look like
if you were to use us and fight with us
now I want to pull some gotcha I want to
pull some gacha um I know that I may
purchase a whole move skin which already
they're already under
[Music]
they're all ready
I mean I already have them so I don't
have to pull them but but but but look
at this so this is what the store looks
like very cute you can get a activity
pledge package yeah with some extra
cords and the SSR Furniture we haven't
really seen that yet we'll check it out
I think
um but look you can get new small these
ones are so cute look at them this looks
like
um at the one year anniversary
looks like
you know when we were sitting together
taking that picture remember
also manager son just just to confirm am
I supposed to buy these is or should I
not buy them I have some money on the
hair
I think I think I was supposed to buy
them and you can yeah here you can get
the Italian fan club package with like a
frame and some eggs and this message
here this sticker message thingy reply
thingy
so this is what it comes with oh
okay I'm doing this on PC
um frame the Eternal manager special
frame to commemorate the everlasting
life force of the Phoenix equipped it in
profile to showcase the power of your
company
yeah yummy emote used in Gauntlet mode
and here the hollow mythical eggs but if
you want extra 10 homo mythical eggs
look at the coupon code on the bottom
left wokio Kiana now and then you get
some extra don't forget about it but
here are some more eggs eggs
and this is
skin with some eggs
wait a second
I want to look at that
and this is the interior set look it's
the
VR world made into a little gacha
interior set oh my God
it's got all the details I mean look
what the doors
small Cali timeline you can place them
however you want the sofas the fountain
with the with a myth sign
microphones
flooring
surveillance portraits ah
the clocks clocks timelines
United with small cute some tables signs
of timeline in memory of the AMA Wars oh
a list of time traveling detective
battles so far because details of her
marks are small amicoded no one can tell
exactly about it
portraits are full of members they were
drawn to commemorate the decision to
watch every member forever
oh cool
oh yeah and then there's um the
Smallmouth Auditorium stage
wallpaper and the lobby wallpaper and
the lobby floor
okay and
these are just a couple more things you
can get like a cute
camping mascot or the town lights
and there's unique interactions
teammates
Deadbeats
yeah okay okay okay
so these are all the things you can get
let's let's let's let's give it a try
how about
we try for this I mean I think this
account already has everything but I'm
I'm gonna try
um
wow surprise this was not really gotcha
Oh I wanna do I want to do the random
like gotcha and see which one I get is
that not there's no random
one here I guess here you can only
choose which one you really want
um
I also I think I got a ticket
uh
somewhere I don't know where to use
though I got a ticket to get like a
general SSR character of General gacha I
want to try go to record okay let's go
to record
here
and
wait isn't that supposed to be the
ticket
[Music]
no more recruitment oh oh look at all
those SSRS
whoa
I didn't think
I'm confused
one out of 20 I am
confused a little bit
[Music]
I like I could roll for her now but the
account already has her
I guess the account has everyone what
see this is this is my character that
you need
to put my skin on top of
well so right now you would be able to
get her
here hmm
[Music]
okay I don't know how to do this
let's roll five days left yes five days
left
uh anyway I should also show you the
dorm
um
I already received all the mail
I don't know
[Music]
I pressed the wrong thing
no no no no sorry sorry sorry sorry
it's cool
let's check out the dorm I didn't get
this far in the tutorial
uh
rear end room clock on the room with the
hanger
I hear oh my God I'm so blind
I'm dancing I'm dancing when someone
joined me and dance with me
so cute oh this is placed in this big
big VR stage world that we have oh join
me join me come Cali single
singing
a
she's using your size to play guitar
[Music]
I'm not good as cheering
you know what are you doing you know
come here
what the sorry sorry for touching you
[Music]
yeah they made me record cool I
am allowed to swear
all right I just need to take a little
rest
that's the loading screen Music stream
is starting
[Music]
she's cooking is to sing the same thing
you guys do what you want do what makes
you happy what happened with the taco
Dashi
what the
[Music]
no no no Casper Casper's not here don't
worry
I
always while shooting Guru
and you can like touch these to look at
them they wink
you're cute
yeah this is what it looks like maybe we
could try to
Warehouse wow oh oh what
you can get these things too
whoa whoa
it's different stage sets for all of us
Mamma Mia I don't have them it seems
oh these are standard ones and end hours
the theme preset
oh I was already placed but there you
see it all the details again
okay okay I think we showed up and loved
that
but now you know where it is and I know
where it is wonderful
huh what next room what Nani
okay I'll go again I'll go again
dorm
ing
we have those
cute
yeah let the blood and Rhymes what
painting a taco daddy another one
another one thank you
so we interact we interact with our own
sets as well that's so neat why do I
need to go outside for I can do all my
investing
she runs like Naruto
Romano can we like tell her to go here
go here come on go here
go here
I don't think I can tell her to do that
maybe if we wait long enough
it sells chocolate mint desserts around
here well I want to go there sometime
Cafe Street
sounds like there are some cool
waitresses there you guys want some
chocolate mint dessert
ah there we go no I didn't drag enough
she doesn't look very happy about it
okay can I place it on anyone no only my
set oh
yeah I'm dancing with the fried chicken
in my hand what about Cali
oh there you go
it's also dancing of course you must
perform
ah man we're gonna Place her here
oh good
I couldn't kill them in the middle how
could I move her oh I'm sorry gouda yeah
Cali wishes she could do that
oh no he want to stay where you are
sure
okay there we go see all of them in
place
a Time
all right we're all performing can we
also like let me try
do they go to the microphone
oh yes but which one this one hmm
which one is purple
oh wait they're talking with each other
it's a collaboration
they're having an exclusive
collaboration
almost turning green
there you go
okay it must be this one
and then oh no I'm assume
what about what about
sitting I want to see Cali sit this is
how Cali sits let's make everyone sit
sit
do a sit
do I sit
oh cozy
yeah this is what it would be like if we
lived together
[Laughter]
oh
this is the lobby so yeah you can uh
design your own room for us basically
and then have us hang out there
click long time oh
what if I drag him around for a long
time they're gonna do something
foreign
that's the dangerous thing to say don't
throw the children don't throw the
random children that you don't even know
oh Kima was cheering for Cali
yeah very yummy
all right all right all right I think
we're done here and then one more thing
we'll try again
um
storage
the SSR yeah it's here
oh I can use it from this screen okay
okay let's use it
[Laughter]
really
out of the things I could get I'll get a
tank yes there's tanks in here and ships
and so on
well
let me try this one Thanksgiving SSR
testimonial come on give me a cute girl
there we go now we're talking oh
um
pink long twin tails and see through oh
killed yo look at her
weapons I suppose
on her hands oh
don't wanna get scratched by her Bishop
should we try it
wait employment contract oh yeah yeah
the employment contract I still want to
do the lifetime Contour let's try it
again maybe this time I'll figure it out
uh
[Music]
um
here see foreign
Center
convenience Goods
well I already don't I already have it
oh I guess it didn't I have to buy it
here there we go
lifetime contract
um
I got to
go to kiwawa
skills
decided to read a special letter that
she has written foreign
[Music]
here it goes
soon a radio call arrived saying that
she has arrived backstage
stomp stomp
foreign
[Music]
Wings to travel great distances
probably hide most of the time though
damn voice I'm I'm lip syncing her right
now you know something though These
Wings Are Not Just My Own
these feathers that make up These Wings
these are you guys kfb
of course I could have been a talented
and hot Phoenix on my own but one that
can't fly
I am whole now because you guys are here
with me regardless of the distance
between us yes you're right here next to
me
with kfb I was able to become a phoenix
with vibrant wings that would allow me
to travel anywhere at any time for my
dreams to grow infinitely yeah
yeah ah emotional I'm gonna cry
you can be proud of this one does not
simply become a part of Phoenix you know
yeah smoke smoke face cute
oh oh we got to stamp it that is
official our lifetime contract with
Chihuahua stamp
oh
[Music]
excellent we're married
to myself
[Music]
let's be together forever and ever yay I
love you my preciously okay mama loves
me I can't believe it
I love you
oh well I I I I was told to show up this
one I don't think I am I should show you
all the other ones unless if yes and
now's the chance to tell me that
management as far as Arnold I've
shortened spoil all of them
um did you read the small print no no no
no no no need to read the small print
and I wonder was there something I
forgot we did the dorm we did the
lifetime contract I showed you
um the eggs we cracked some eggs
and I showed you the animations the
battle animations
and the voice lines
oh that's uh
um oh wait are there like now
and it can draw more potential even more
voiceless because we're
oh wait wait I'm on the top I'm at the
top
battle five to me I kind of want to do
that
oh
oh yeah the lifetime Contour you can
like listen to it again now here if you
wanna if you feel a little bit
I want to hear kiwava confess her love
to me
yeah yeah this account is very bubbling
I really like her
whoa and listen to her
[Music]
I want to walk over the horizon together
with her hand in hand
oh pretty I think that's my ocean
she looks really powerful too
hey can we try I'm gonna try I'm gonna
try I'm gonna try I want to try
um
see if we can
oh they're already in the team oh my
okay okay so the squad is set
Horizon top tier PVP oh you seem like
you know what you're talking about on it
um operation
already ready yeah okay I don't want to
like I'm too scared of like
yeah buy a really strong stuff
um we can also go to simulation I guess
into attack training
attack what the
let's try this
pair to operate
and see them all five in action
oh
attack turning six
oh two I'm scared
I guess it'll end really fast okay yeah
I might be so you place them on here
[Music]
oh yeah okay
too powerful perhaps
fast
I would absolutely obliterated them I
suppose okay I guess we can do something
stronger level 90 here let's do this one
[Laughter]
level or the sixth one with level 90
we're 110 but
it's a bit more of a match I would say
yeah it will last a little bit longer
yeah Miss power
all right
go kiwawa and then we need gouda and on
the front lines
oh oh that's that's not a myth member
but all right
so what's going on
holy
[Music]
how much points yo okay okay one more
one purge
your holy looks so powerful oh my
God
wow wow we saved the world once again
the world is safe
you are welcome oh we can't even gain
exp anymore
oh
[Music]
but
with that we did two simulation
trainings and that might be
um
one of the things
that we needed to do
here
yeah yeah only already completed no
perform five simulations oh
but I can complete that and get another
egg hey yo
I wanna can I try composing but I need
like two more of those
um
let me try it
wow
ground pounds
and I want to see in a stir the pot
did that help us
all right all right right
it's also here as you know this she's so
cute she's like peeking when the bottom
to change
oh oh
this one I can do
this one no this one no this one no no
but this this one I can do
let's try then compose
compose electrot trophies composers and
obtain your desired great trophy let's
go
oh
it's kind of exploded and we get uh the
animated Watson Amelia trophy yay
using good as Fork to stare yeah yeah
for that
it's what we need
um oh
oh
I am allowed to check
uh another
lifetime contract you guys wanna hear
Ina's lifetime contract
yes you do you do you do of course you
do hey I'll buy another one
it's on me
here there it is
it's on me I'll treat you to some Enya
oh wait am I going the right way I think
I can do it from here right
no
no not Reginald you
uh here at salary negotiation wasn't it
also here
no I have to go to the
way I did it before so I don't get lost
um
huh
how did I do it before
I forgot oh wait I
hear I'm so oh so confused sorry
loyalty you got something for me yeah
yeah can I see what it is ah we'll make
some tackle that she's happy now by
entering a special contract
already married to kiwawa but it
shouldn't hurt to also get married to
Ina
bye you know my English decided to read
a special letter that she has written
for her loyal viewers takutachis
be quiet okay yes okay
soon a radio call arrived saying that
she has arrived backstage
surprise yeah kind of
so happy the feeling I missed you
Slide the great all the takorachis like
always
[Music]
these moments always make me nervous
right okay here we go okay I'm listening
I'm going to read a short letter I have
written for you guys
surely I can make it to the end this
time
dear takorachis
Amina or you I know who I am I do it's
enough time zoomed by so fast when I was
here that I felt like I left you guys
time travel
you may be still oven's watch
but you know what I always say hi -5
when you're having fun does she always
say that
I experienced a lot of fun and exciting
things while I was here
how about you guys
hope you all had a wonderful time too a
wonderful time
it's like how I got unlimited support
from all of you guys
I hope my love and support will reach
you guys as well
I'm sure that what everyone's support we
can get through the hardest challenges
any challenges
we'll get over it together even though
they fail oh shout go next
deep climb up the mountain called life
but I'm sure the view from the top will
be Unforgettable especially with you
guys by my side
Mary
it's totally totally marriage contract
you don't understand you couldn't you
wouldn't understand I want to take this
moment to say thanks for everything oh I
hope you don't forget how much you meant
to me
okay
[Music]
oh no
thank you for marrying me
[Music]
[Laughter]
so the others if you want to hear more
of them you can get the skin there might
be another uh sponsored stream about
this game very soon where you can
remember one of those
ah no crying you're crying we're all
crying or crying so yeah that was
um pretty much all the important stuff
that I think I needed to show you don't
forget the the coupon code to use it and
this is limited time so make sure it
just started yesterday but
um yeah make sure to get it before it's
gone
um and then have fun with me forever
they will be eternally forever in your
account
and you can fight with them and poke
them and see what they have to say
stuff like that you know all right
doesn't want to talk with me
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys do what you want do what makes
you happy
innocent no in a sauce
yeah yeah
so all their voice lines they're so
adorable but yeah this already has been
one and a half hours so I'll listen more
to it privately I mean I already know
all my voice lines but I'm curious what
all the other voice what are the other
voice lines of the other members are we
recorded so much for it and there's so
so much stuff so many like cute
illustrations and animations and so on
that I want you guys to find them all
every little detail you have to check it
out look closely everywhere yeah
mm-hmm
[Music]
trophy voice lines
uh
uh why would I check those I can I can
show you but I don't know where they
would be
trophy tons of voice acting oh I don't
even remember what did I voice act for
that
thanks for all the uh Facebook
in management
ah
and you are cute oh my God wait can I
hear the chicken
[Laughter]
yeah that's just me that's not that's
not the employee well
the nickname
oh yes there's even more voicelands here
what about the small ones
oh what excuses be in the way of your
learning you hear that you hear that
everyone no excuses
go let your dreams come true do them do
everything just do it
[Music]
yourself on the back give them a
wonderful job today
she's watching my sponsorship stream and
she says I did a wonderful job
so it's the lines basically that they
say uh in the dorm room
I'm in
I can't spell gamer without Army
oh you're right
what the
bird
cute oh what a lovely smell sip
it's relaxing on her tea set
adorable wake up
don't slack on your job
[Music]
that's where he is that's where he was
[Laughter]
yay
you look cute oh there's so many of
those oh
oh I've got so many dupes
yeah this one's still because chicken
out
that will be me now because I'll go eat
some breakfast now and I'll cheer
exactly like that and yes I will eat I
will eat some chicken legs exactly like
you saw just now
yeah there's so many someone should
listen to so many voice lines so please
enjoy this collaboration limited time
only and check out the QR code above
above me and if you want to get it then
use the link in the description ideally
because I think it will be tracked that
you got it from me hmm
enjoy your legs I guess I will enjoy
your legs
yeah I'm done with the game let's go
enjoy
ing done with it yeah it's on the global
server so you gotta get the global
version of counter side all right
counting on you guys
to get Countryside
donkey showing everybody for watching
and in German we sell Venus dance thank
you so much contact for sponsoring the
stream and for this amazing
collaboration like I think it's just so
cool it's just so amazing
um we are forever engraved eternally in
this game and it's just so high quality
yeah
for your support and without your
support stuff like this would not be
possible it wouldn't happen hmm
so thank you so much
[Music]
calendar there's a video all the videos
you should check them all out and today
there will be a special announcement one
so make sure to watch it ASAP when it
comes out in
14 hours approximately
um
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]