[Music]
a
n
[Music]
PA
a
[Music]
e
a
n
[Music]
e
n
d
[Music]
a
okay
c ah hey no I didn't want that to go
away I wanted to read that apparently
Rome is coming or
so
hello it is um
your Yours Truly takanasi kiaha who's
getting bullied by her
cat once
again Rome is coming sounds like a
warning it sounds it
sounds it sounds like Asterix and Obelix
are close as
well
hey I I watched on my last uh airplane
ride the Asterix and Obelix
movie yeah and I was like didn't I watch
this like years ago how is this new but
I guess this was like a a new one
different theme do you guys know Asterix
and
noix that's one of the comics that I
used to read when I was uh small small
W yes yes yes yes
nice me me very European so
true oh but I'm I'm surprised so many
people know it well known in que I guess
cuz it's
like h no no but it was written
originally in Italian I would guess it's
not way French is
it it's also popular in Asia oh really
oh I I don't know who dog M Max was
anymore uh at this moment but there are
some pretty funny
characters
H very special oh is is it it is okay
then never mind cuz then for a moment I
was like wait something about it being
French but then why why is it about you
know those
those little Italian
people because of Rome but wait are they
French and they just go to Rome I a they
girls are girls are
French
really cuz Rome invaded friends
oh well I mean you know back in the day
there was a lot of invading going on and
speaking of invading other
countries welcome back to
aoe2 let's
go perfect perfect segue wooo do you
know how people nowadays like Snap their
fingers instead of clapping what's up
with that what's that what's that about
I can't even do it that fast it's
like it's so difficult too let's just
clap
please Zoomer f
yes it
hurts who does that people do that now
yeah they do I see it all the time these
days but it's certainly like young
people relatively young people or
like well
anyway ta this we have a little bit of a
tournament
tomorrow uh with um
M
Ana let me see M
Ana FAA
crony and me that's one 2 three six
people six people uh and I was like girl
MAA like she suddenly was like hey let's
re re restart
that plan of doing a tournament that she
brought up ages ago and and she chose
this date uh after asking us for our
availabilities but I was like girl we
don't really have time to practice do we
and she was like oh don't worry it's
just like a a light light uh hearted uh
tournament just just a little you know
not really a tournament not I guess she
she doesn't want us to feel like it's a
tournament um more like you know she
loves AOE
didn't the ID girls like Ana and Ela and
Mauna have this before under ID Girls
then I don't want to compete against
them I also a Wonder cuz fauna and crony
I don't think they ever played it on
stream but I wonder if they prepared
behind the scenes on how good they are
uh I certainly streamed it a few times
but IDE hardcore that's not
fair that's not fair MO is a bro o o
yeah I wonder how how can you even what
are the options for playing against each
other can you have a three versus three
or is it only one versus one can we have
two versus two cuz we're six people two
then I guess two people would be waiting
for a bit
but there is free versus
free wait so free countries that are
playing together against other free
countries at once that feels like a lot
is going
on damn four versus four is Max 2 versus
2 versus two all six
waa oh then I feel like the fairest
would be 2 versus 2 versus two pairing
up an experienced ID member with a Noto
experienced uh Ian member don't you
think I want to know how she's planning
to do it let me ask
MAA how are you planning to uh pair up
the teams if there if there if there are
any I heard two versus two versus two is
possible and maybe the fairest because I
think ID
has way more skills than Ian
L yeah let's see let's see I have no
idea what's planned oh and also um so
for today so far I've only played like a
few uh campaigns single player but
somebody uh suggested and I agree with
that for today it might be best to just
play um skirmishes against
CPUs because that way it will be more
like the actual uh tournament
right um and then I realized can you
even pause game
in skirm like when you play against
another real
person
because does that pause their game too
or are you in an advantage the more you
pause your game or no you can't yes you
yes no not against other people that's
what I thought that's so stressful cuz I
need to pause to
think you can request a pause game would
be paed for everyone oh oh oh
uh
uh that stresses me
out like I really like this game but
maybe you guys
remember like after like like a few
campaigns in the beginning I already
started
struggling and like being overwhelmed
with what to do next and how to balance
fighting with rebuilding my resources
and stuff and I I kind of like stopped
playing it first of all because it's
annoying to get permissions but also
because I just I just felt so
overwhelmed that it's like stressing me
out I want to be better at it and I
don't want to be stressed out by it but
I do get super overwhelmed by it
yeah
yeah civilization is more your sty wait
do you mean the game s isn't there a
game called
civilization
what oh why would that be easier for me
that's
interesting it's turn based turn
based
okay that could possibly be helpful but
not at
all but I like this too also because
it's also nostalgic to me but you know
there's so much cat hair around my God
here let me get
some some of the cat are on the
[Laughter]
microphone okay if I want to play
uh against a CPU in a skirmish what do I
choose
multiplayer play with or against human
players I guess not
[Music]
cool go single player okay
Skirmish okay AI civilization random
random I think random random is although
depends on if we want to do random
random for our tournament or if we get
to choose then I might want to practice
with the one that I end up
choosing
right cuz every every civilization has
its own little perks but I wouldn't say
that any one of them is like
significantly better than another um do
we have
austrians I could do
Italians uh something that's close to me
would be
fun uh I
guess the
uh two tons what are you guys saying
because they're Austrian they're the
closest but people keep on
mentioning the tuttons wait where are
the tuttons oh there oh that looks that
does look like the like
austrians we have that like animal in
our flags
too uh infantry
civilization uh wait infantry wasn't
that the the people on the
horses monks healing range two times
okay Towers Garrison
no oh that's walking o okay slow
people uh but I can have horses too
right uh Towers Garrison two times the
units uh-huh murder holes I've never
heard of murder holes before what herbal
medicine
free what for free what a deal Farms
cost minus 40% oh that's a big one town
Santa Garrison plus 10 I never really
used that though cuz like I
don't
ah
oh I see I see defense feature of cast
yeah okay I think I've seen that before
in like movies and shows barracks and
stable units plus one armor and castle
and Imperial age plus two total unique
Knight the tonic Knight
mhm uh unique Tex iron clad Siege
weapons extra melee
armor okay crenulations what the is
that plus three range
castles Garrison infantry fire what what
where's the verb in this what what was
it
what plus
free four range C what what what what
what what's it
mean
huh this this
the uh
what it's missing a
two Garrison castles have longer ranged
arrows an INF plus free range ah plus
free range for infantries that are
garrisoned in the C castle for their
arrows right
man why write it like this I don't
understand
anything hey Koreans no there's a h
hukam hukam hukam there is Koreans what
do Koreans do defensive and Naval
civilization
wow oops shink Chong there's even Korean
words
what do Japanese people do
[Laughter]
yasama did they really just catapult in
Katakana kaparo I thought it would be
kapo they're trying to fool us and make
us think you would you would you have
thought I feel like if you don't know
Japanese you you may think that it's
indeed a Japanese word but if you have
like this like Japanese knowledge then
you immediately recognize this is like
them just trying to make a an English
word or so try to sound more
Japanese it means cable yeah surprise
surprise and they have Samurai she wait
is there
Indonesians I guess that's like kind of
[Music]
a maybe back then they were part of
something else like austrians and then
so therefore there's no Indonesians and
that's kind of of a political thing uh
yeah okay I see
uhhuh
yeah uh wow okay okay I guess we go with
with two cuz I don't see anything wrong
with them either team bonus units
resist we resist conversion oh snap your
fingers that's amazing wait what did the
others well I wonder what the others
would
choose military
[Music]
a conversion is like pretty
sick no Vol
Vol we we'll be protected whoa
blacksmiths work 80% faster oh Bulgarian
strong relics visible on the map at the
start of the game oh shes oh
shes I think that's
good 100% healing
speed sh it would be good to like once I
know who I'm opponent with who's my
opponent to know what like quickly know
like what their things do if there's
anything that I should really know stop
of a free llama what do you mean there's
like actual proper llamas not the one
that we were cheating
with
HS
camel all right like some of these have
really like unique stuff that the others
don't that's so interesting I hope we're
Vikings though that's so
cool hey what are we missing Sicilians
Romans poles garas
dravidians what that sounds like
straight out of Game of
Thrones is
that oh dynasties of
India Lords of the West DLC burgundians
Bohemians balies that's a
cat that's oh W sorry I'm like I'm I'm
stalling I'm stalling I have 100%
stalling okay let's say hi to the
tuttons and let's say like let's
say what do you think one of the others
could be
choosing and let's play something let's
play against one of those that we think
that they would be
choosing we could even already know if
MAA or so has a main ER if we check
their streams melee you think they'll go
for
melee um Spanish
Franks and Ido would oh really okay then
I mean but hopefully they'll be on my
team uh if there's teams
okay let's do that and then should I
change something here D mod default
random map yeah location
Coastal
um ooh the arena map I think I saw this
one and uh when I was when I was still
in my AOE hype and I was like watching
tournaments oh there's some cool
ones like special looking ones
what
[Music]
interesting wuli waa I will not be made
into one of you
never can't convert me so try to hurt
me chat isn't oh oh I didn't notice oh
some sometimes it just doesn't want to
do do it until I change a pixel and
there it
is no I wasn't talking to you guys KY I
was talking like in Fury to to you know
my opponents Mega
random ever dreamed of an endlessly
unpredictable map where anything is
possible and nothing is guaranteed
multiply it by 10 and you have mega
random
[Applause]
NY Mega random
seiz the mountains
Scandinavia oh they look so
cool not a hold let's go with a pretty
basic one though I guess
uh something with water and with
green Mediterranean is my favorite Black
Forest the old classic where where where
is my where are those black forest
uhhuh islands of grass in the sea of
trees follow the paths through the
forest to find your allies and enemies
[Music]
ooh where's the other one Continental
continental
breakfast Fortress wait what no what was
I looking
for something a forit no wait no wait
what was it I forgot already
Hamburg there's a hamburger map the
ultimate Easter egg map located on leave
a side of the tast of burger will you
eat fruit it or sail around the bun and
surprise the
eny what's it on that's so
funny kill a man
jro
well land Madness with resources
scattered across the map and Forest
surrounded by unbuildable rugged
terrain Walling is nearly impossible and
Military presence will be crucial
sheesh okay sorry there's there's cool
stuff and I'm stalling
again I I pronounced it on purpose like
that cuz it just came up in um in uh
what's it called home
renovation Home
Improvement no star tweet well then it's
just TW
pranking me again cuz I did write one
okay let me let me
check Twitter you little you better
be tweeting my tweet it didn't where did
it go where did it go like sometimes at
least when I go back onto Twitter it
will like um like show me that it's
loading still the Twitter the tweet that
I was trying to
send but it's not here wa where's my
tweet where's my tweet where is my
stupid tweet it's just not there I'll
make a new one there might be
doubles
starting we have begun ages ago Age of
Empires
ago I hope that's the right
link sending post yeah you better I'll
stay on Twitter until I see my
post hello there it
is okay
okay all right back into the
game this is so funny but I I don't know
if it's like extra difficult we should
go with something medium
difficult
[Music]
um
maybe maybe something like this
or then that that would mean that
nobody's like going to any other place
with ships which is fine to me cuz I
don't like the idea I'd recommend hide
out is this sorted by yes AFK ha hide
out hide out
oh that looks very
[Music]
special four is common too the one I was
looking at let's just go with this okay
and the other
things should I change something we
don't allow cheats turbo mode select to
that buildings create units faster
villagers GA faster but oh full Tech Tre
ooh
oo leave those alone okay but we don't
need the
cheats any tournament rules nothing that
I
know Map size tiny two player a
standard did somebody say I should go
medium I don't know I'll go standard for
now cuz I'm I'm terrible I'm terrible at
this game I wonder if it be allowed to
be a little bit back seated by chat
during the
tournament how long has it been too
long game speed should I make it slow
can I make it slow so that I can take my
time with
it won't be talking to your teammates oh
yeah if there are teammates
[Music]
yeah just read some strats and try to
copy them maybe I will the problem is I
don't have much time anymore like I'll
be playing this then I have to go to
sleep early and then I uh wake up at
7:00 a.m. for the or like 6:30 for the
tournament um at least I scheduled a
practice stream unlike
others okay okay let's let's go uh here
I'm
scared don't know what I what do I do uh
I make a people right create villager
and then uh we already have this so you
I think you oh speaking German heya
right click was
it uh you tree uh you also tree and you
you you go to places check it can how do
I send them automatically around again
oh look I already found what there's an
elephant how do I send them
automatically two
places that's almost
German use G what's G
again oh it stops them from walking
interesting oh there's so much stuff so
tropical too turn on a oh is that is
that is he Auto scouting right now
scouting
scouting uh more people probably oh and
uh should I research Loom what was that
again let's research
Loom okay okay good stuff wait he's not
moving
go uh I want another person so I can
mine the
stone how do I build a house
again
I don't know how to build a house again
also how do I move the map oh
okay select the Villager okay uh let's
select uh you uh
aha buildings house okay
house that's not something I understand
oh do we have to build that and then the
new villager comes
out okay okay F have2 12 to pause let's
try to not pause it at the moment
because yeah we don't want to get too
used to pausing the
game all right good scouting good
scouting oh the chicken you saw
that thank you dingo
Ringo
well that wasn't completely on us I
would say to my defense okay
let's make another house can we like
make him touch or is that not good I'll
make this touch what is my uh uh okay no
we don't have
any any like non workking I remember the
idol
villagers hold shift and click to set a
path to follow for him oh well it's fine
he can do whatever he wants right now
okay you uh you
go uh right
click to the
stones I'm surprised the elephant is not
attacking us I guess they're generally
more are they really that friendly the
zebras I think would not attack us but
damn are we going to eat elephant
meat HZ yeah HZ
yeah HZ is a Uh
Wood you'll be a tactical genius in not
I don't know about that I'm not ready to
attack this
uh elephant I don't I don't think I'll
survive it like realistically speaking
how could one oh Loom how could one of
me kill an
elephant ah yeah partially
wall
walls uh more more more more
people let's make two more that's the
maximum I
think qu qu qu I have I'm a baby boomer
apparently I killed five
villagers okay chill Lama chill
everything's okay so far right food wood
gold stone and dark okay do I need more
um okay next person
will uh attack the
Sheep go faster we're
dying H
H K's about to UE
no put all villages on food to make oh
really
okay oh wait does he have to do that
together with
somebody how do I make the the Farms
again wait wait wait wait
you farm build Mill mining cam is a is a
mill right is it a
mill m m cam oh yeah well we can the
mining camp should be close to the
mining resources
right so that they can put it there
quickly right have a for berries I don't
see any berries oh maybe those okay
correct okay so one here and
then enough of
that we can go back there later how am I
doing so far it's the first time in like
a year or
so the basics I understand wait what
what oopsie sorry sorry sorry what am I
doing so we have a couple people on the
on the meat and on the one person on the
berries now the rest is like
working on the stones uh and some
gold slow but your hand on the Bas well
this is slow to
you
that's I know the
basics just been a little
while but I'll I'll make more uh people
again one of
you go attack
zebra G I hope it won't kill you oh oh
it's pretty easy to kill
really it won't even put up a fight
sheesh
okay only first stage boom to oh really
okay okay in that
case now
this elephants fight Z are save okay I
see I am
learning and
[Music]
um you could
probably should I build another house so
I can get more villagers
right that's so bow b b he's trying to
say build uh bow oh there's more sheep
there oh my Scout is still scouting O
Fish is that a
relic he found the
Relic I found the
Relic boow Not Bow Bow house built okay
um oh yeah go why is nobody doing the
berries
huh okay
retrieve take it
take wait I need a monk to take it do I
can he take
it click a monk yeah we don't have monks
for a while don't
worry I can send the Sheep back to you
uh how do I need a person for
that where were
they like oh there's another Relic I
can't see the Sheep
now I lost
them H
um
more Scout is doing a good job yeah keep
always making yeah okay okay okay okay
okay okay Hey sir uh more food right
more more ah ah uh if I attack those
they they he will bring the over
right build
Mill
okay
okay move oh I can control
them where they not I thought there were
some
here okay well he bringing them now
you build um Mill Mill close to berries
or or just close to the fields that I'm
I'll be building hopefully at some point
very yeah
okay okay and you can hey
heyy
you maybe another house right
okay now I'm starting to need some wood
though so you
go you go yeah you said spam food so I
took everyone else off of the other
resources
mostly but we need some wood I've
noticed don't
worry oh she finished this
one what's
that and attacking hopefully
not yeah uh
do don't need the stone for now yeah
okay maybe uh he can join oh okay uh
okay house bu Mill build okay
easy uh they'll start using the mill
automatically right just like everything
else
M I'll leave one person on
the on
the stone okay
[Music]
you maybe another tree HS HS yeah
htz now I can build farms
[Music]
too oh oopsie no I not receed Farm I
have no Farm uh build Farm probably for
a villager huh
okay here Farm
go go go go oh we have more Idol
Hunter's
[Music]
Idol
more bu Hunter now become
farmer set them on berries
okay another one okay
I can go catch fish it's so
far I don't know I don't know how's my
Scout doing he's going over there then
surely the enemy is like here or
here another Relic ooh we found three
relics
nice
yeah uh uh wait
uh probably should go no no
HS no farms for
now
okay good development and good workers
ra
okay need some more wood true Hey
sir now they're like pretty
far should I like build something to put
the wood too like close
by Lumber
Camp uh wait uh oh we have many Idol
Lumber Lumber no wood for the lumber
Camp okay uh work on
[Music]
the yeah I used up too much wood for the
Farms
oopsy
hey
heyya they're really fans of that song
they keep on thinking about it they
won't let it
go oh wait there's a little water here
oh yeah right cuz I should have know I
should know cuz I chose the
map uh okay try try to
Fisher
oh maybe it's the other
Haya what's going
on
get what's going
hey
hey I said
hey what's going
on I want to sing that in K
man
okay he's fishing he's be he's be
fishing
okay oh we can
advance oh we could have advanced maybe
soon soon
TMM oink
oink H Advance will be good okay once we
can do it we shall do it right cancel
villager cancel cancel
uh okay canceled one uh seems like we
can
advance all right
uza
advancing let's go uh okay uh what do we
need we have still a lack okay now
obviously a lack of of food actually do
you want to help
fishing and lamb can okay Lumber
Camp Lumber Camp
here and
then Barracks Barracks also through the
same way through the the the villagers
right okay when do I still have one
upcoming no
[Music]
uh you look so idle you're not doing
anything
how about you build oh no no Barracks
here is that
a after
the advancement
wait should I build another
house the other tab
ah okay Barracks I don't know where to
put them maybe
[Music]
here
still haven't found the
enemy wow more room chat can see the
mini map oh oh H
well that's
fine leave it up to your
imagination okay okay uh almost almost
advancing
um maybe now we can start going back to
gold cuz gold is my
littlest
resource I don't
know hey you don't need to see
it now some gold okay but I have no one
um I don't know I wait back to
400 food then I'll get some more
people take some wood away okay
um it
is that uh gold guess I'll go for this
one ah does the gold also go to the to
this one
Advanced nice
sh
e no docks in the
village you will not have my address no
no you have 10 people working yeah
because first you said it's important
so hey
sir
h or actually stay here yeah then we
shall build a separate
mine uh just a mining camp right let's
put it
here you need Army soon mhm soon don't
stress me out should I do real
Barrel
research Town
watch oh found them is that is that are
they pretty advanced they have a lot of
farms
it will be
good looks about the same
okay uh
[Music]
um maybe a bit more gold
oh yeah okay he finished building that
now let's build another house I don't
know I think it's
time and you can start creating militia
span or man at oh upgrade to man at Arms
should I do that
now should I already upgrade man at Arms
I'll do it I'll do it let's do
it oh they just hay Advance the feudal
age oh so they're a little bit behind me
actually
I don't need them cancel do I get my
resources
back give them arms how are I going to
fight without
arms okay I got it back okay build walls
now if I build walls which kind of walls
should I build simple wooden walls or
stone
walls hey
hey y military buildings are there walls
in military buildings paliside
wall parasite
wall not now build Stables stable yes
let's make stable a very stable stable
stable Stables are the best Stables
unlike not stable
Stables still few no reason to
okay
wall is useless in this map wall is
useless in this map hm why explain that
to me I want to
understand oh oh don't go after him it's
fine it's fine it's fine as long as he
doesn't attack
us what are you doing they have a relic
really close to them
too okay uh wait
uh uh oh they're done with the berries
oh okay more Farms done one more and
then uh we have we need archery range
perhaps maybe
[Music]
yes m
okay this map is too open for walls okay
okay good to
know check what you need to get to
Castle
H 800 food uh yeah 200 gold we have the
gold and two feudal age what a feudal
age
buildings
no not Scout caval I don't care about
Scout
Cavalry
night why can't I make a
knight ah I have them stable and archery
okay
yeah yeah
y I don't know can I attack this
thing yeah go try oh it wants to attack
you y y you'll
die attack
together go go go help ah he'll die was
not good idea he's also very slow why
are you so
slow yummy need more Hunters than that
uh-oh uh-oh uhoh
uh-oh
no Samantha no here I'll bring you
someone to oh wa it's too late you're
too late he didn't even get a
hit in he just arrived at that moment oh
my
God can someone somebody Clean Up the
Bodies Andy am I clicking on the right
thing
no
okay
uh well can we fish more I don't
know one another Farm maybe it doesn't
[Music]
hurt six villages to hunt at once oh
okay need more houses and soldiers okay
Hey
sir more houses I can do that all in a
line it's very
realistic what else could we build and
maybe an outpost or Watchtower do we
want an
outpost also I should make should I not
like start my my Army
here let's make an
army build a forge wait
[Music]
Forge Forge you mean
blacksmith probably we need a blacksmith
right blacksmith I don't know can be
anywhere really right it's not so
important where he
is do you want to rush the AI no I don't
what are they
doing they're not doing anything right
that doesn't look so Advanced
TBH but they have a they have a fishing
camp I need a fishing camp I need that I
want what they
have it's usually best to focus on only
one or two unit
types you mean like even like if we have
these three things focus on like archers
and and whatever this is Spearman or one
per you know what they offer what do you
mean they want to kill him
try did they just
say well no that will be a silly hunt
don't do it
yeah uh what's the what's the the dock
is it the dock for
fishing but that's for ships no does it
also work for for fishing faster I don't
know should I put the dock here okay yes
okay all
right
okay
uh let's
do wait somebody said build a tower you
mean a wat Tower or an
outpost where's the difference again is
the Watchtower just a better Outpost
Watchtower should be like kind of
distance but not too much right I mean
it could be anywhere I guess they can
shoot okay all
right we can advance let's
go we're advancing
guys iy oh not so bad I think I'm I'm
feeling fine right now I think I will
start not feeling fine once we have to
attack and then I lose all my units and
then I'm like what do I
do what do I
do fishing ship need to build more
houses
okay are they done
fishing oh he's done fishing that's so
sad uh can the fishermen like help with
fishing or do the ships just do it on
their
own oh yeah we need we need houses
quick multiple
M I'm
good he so what I want to focus on I'm
not really focusing on anything but I
guess I didn't make any horses yet so
I'll focus on these two so what was the
actual answer to my question though I
wonder what was the
[Music]
answer
Knights where are these so-called
Knights these ones wow I don't know how
to make them do I have to make
a do I have to research
first
oh Castle age oh
okay
uh okay okay Watchtower buildt
nice
um
how how how do I can I still like fish
with normal people or should I leave it
to the
boats
Hey
sir
actually leave it to the boat okay
then let's make another Watch Tower
here uh almost Advanced let's
go taada ooh oo fancy and again we're
ahead of the
others uh okay
Knights there we
go more Fisher
boats fishing very
good spamming Knights yes yes build a
castle okay
uh Castle probably in military Castle
six okay here comes the stone shortage
uh here Stone quick let's get some Stone
quick
quick also can I upgrade something here
maybe not
now oh wait there's six people idle oh
my God I'm so sorry hey sir why are they
all idle oh cuz they were building
houses
okay um very bright I
[Music]
am okay we still have like a bunch of
stone here for later
okay wait now that I have a cat can I
already get a
monk love Castle dropping AI wait are
they they're still behind me
okay what do you mean Castle dropping AI
build castle Yeah okay now now I can do
it uh castle castle castle castle castle
castle where is the best place to build
it like in the middle or more on the
outside of my place wait there it was
well still not enough not not enough
next to the to D
towns that's a strategy
huh uh next to the enemy beside okay
outside towards okay okay okay wait I I
just need more Stone Hey
sir I'll build a mining camp
here
hey
what the why you not doing anything
you little
shits no okay they're in Castle H but
who says they have enough
materials ah no not SC
carefully
night mhm okay now I can make I can make
I can make the castle
now outside let's make
it I don't know
here I guess cuz they're probably going
to come from that
direction the enemy always has enough
materials don't say that we'll help
building
it you'll help building it
[Music]
and food shortage coming soon so let's
make another
Farm get a monk and take the Relic yeah
but Monk for monk I don't I need like a
church or the castle I
guess make a mon see I know I know that
I know that I know
that blacksmith I I already have a
blacksmith though isn't this my
blacksmith yeah
um what should I
upgrade is there something for Knights
infantry Cavalry
attack upgrade is this for Knights or do
upgrade the night
here the knights are mounted so yeah
let's do
this Cavalry
armor so is that what I just did I don't
know uh
goodbye goodbye uh nobody's idle that's
good they're working on the castle it's
taking some
time maybe we can spare
one top right blacksmith upgrade this
one ah
okay what did I need food ooh food ah
food uh
Farm more farms and how about another
fishing ship oh more
houses okay after they're done with the
castle maybe more
houses
I wish these people could do something
besides standing
around night created
okay
oh wait I see a red thing here there's
an
enemy
MIM H what is this by the way are are
they building something something
here complete what's
complete did are they going for
my o o Hey
sir
o what are you doing
this oh you little
shits how that's what's
huh how dare they the
oh we're too slow to kill
him go go
go oh my castle is
shooting aim
do tonic Knights should I make tonic
Knights yo you're so bad at
this not worth it
yeah oh oh okay H this is stressing me
out I'm already stressed
out you don't need to go after the just
stay just
stay I think just stay as long as he
doesn't attack what am I doing what am I
doing what am I doing research
ballistics oh in
here not like I can do it right
now it's meant to stress me
out uh wait what am I doing uh okay uh
uh
um oh go fishing oh I'll go fishing here
um heyya
heyya uh can we build a church for the
monks
Monastery it can be anywhere right
although they have to walk so far to
bring it there so maybe build it like I
don't
know I know here
maybe okay and then the others can help
with
that be
faster uh what else do we
need food is like looking
okayish
but make another Farm
here styish town I'm not trying to make
it stylish but uh you
know I guess we could make more houses
too just free more castles and free more
castles group your units and start
harassing the enemies how do wait
okay F12 was not um pausing what was
pausing
free really no which one is it no you
guys say different
things just let press p no P doesn't
work F10 really okay um um uh uh I was
going to ask something but I forgot what
I was going to ask um just like General
like strategy
discussion oh my God should I
what do I do how do i group people again
and like should I go now attack them I
need more Knights right should I make
tonic Knights now too cuz I mean that's
my strength right ah oh yeah double
click the units oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
how uh I used to know how that works a
yeah yeah
so these are all my nights and then how
do I make them a group uh Cal number
okay okay Hey
sir close later let's make
them are you still trying to work okay I
have grouped them I think yeah so I
should create some tonic
kns is my thing for finished oh it's
finished convert most enemy buildings
and all Siege units convert enemy
monks monk speed I want monk speed so
he's
faster cuz I already know what all the
cool things
are okay
[Music]
uh uh gold we're lacking
Goldy oh and houses wait never mind
you're not you're not doing that you
make
house elephant still chilling here I'm
not ready to attack the
elephant could I attack the elephant
with some of my Knights and then let the
farmers do their thing
afterwards monk
created monk go get this thing it's
really
close is there is this also a relic oh
yeah hey
sir maybe another
[Music]
house only upgrade your Knights I don't
see any more upgrading options
or maybe here
something ah uh should we
do no I don't know this one chain baring
armor
okay Relic picked up okay you know what
to do with that right or do I need to
like tell
you uh what's going on I hear
stuff okay goodbye I'm so
stressed uh uh
I where's my monk where's the monk sir
where is
he where is he monk with Relic I guess
just
here oh oh he has it okay go faster you
little yeah on you get this one
this okay what what do the relics do
again what's their effect again what
does that do I forgot I just know I need
to get them that's all I
know should I make another
Castle more castles is a good thing
right just needs a lot of lot of things
ah they generate free gold passive ooh
free gold per second oh okay okay
okay more castles
okay should they be close to each other
or maybe one
here I think that's a good idea right
more
castles okay
okay if if fa and crony haven't gotten
like an insane amount of secret practice
I think I'll be
fine I think think gab your Army near
the castle
okay yeah this can I I can Garrison them
can I or not was that only like normal
villagers that you can
Garrison should I build another
Castle maybe one more one in doubt just
Build Another Castle
or no
previous RTS
[Music]
yeah oh oh we're attacking this are
these Farmers oh yeah Lumberjack those
poor
Lumberjacks well I don't know what what
your leader was thinking when he put one
Camp here what the hell are they still
not in Castle age
sheesh shees
weak that's that's really
weak oh they're dead wait they have
something
here the yeah let's attack it let's
go they have an archery
here oh they are just have to explore
again is this does this look like Castle
AG to
you stream make something that's like
like a petard that's good or I can't
make TR why
[Music]
not uh I am being attacked oh oh um yeah
by help help
me that's imperal age oh
[Music]
okay
Don't Panic counter attack okay
attack damn they spread out so much
actually no it's just really close Okay
uh okay we're winning we're winning
it oh don't leave him
alive it
okay what who what's my monk doing by
the way there you little faster why
don't you know what to
do hey how do I add someone to a group
does this get rid of the
group oh
wait let's add him
to my Knights the monk to the Knight so
he can heal
them
okay
yeah oh I have a lot of food lot of gold
no gold is like me but okay what could
we do with all these like all these mens
that want to
work healing take a lot of
resource more
gold
H build a seat
Workshop sieg
Workshop Siege sieg Workshop sieg sieg
Workshop I don't see that ah here let's
keep it
close I think
Castle always got to be effective always
got to have people working on
something uh what could you do more
villagers really I don't even know what
to do with the ones I have
now hand card research
[Music]
go mhm
okay uh uh should I attack enemy base I
think I'm ready a no not that no
it's so cating it
no
yeah okay wait Siege weapons uh what do
we
want
[Music]
uh I don't remember what was
good
Rams okay how many three four
Maybe Hey
sir wait what's with my
gold is it because of the healing does
the healing take
gold yeah
yeah somebody said that that healing
takes uh
resources among cost gold oh wait we
should send another Monk to where are my
monks there you should go get another
one of
those relics let's let's get this
one how do I send him to places
again with G was it g no oh yeah
g Knights cost oh okay well we need
[Music]
them
okay don't be concerned about the sound
of Fire
that's from the
enemy running low on wood
oh well we still have many many trees so
that's no
problem to get more gold more food for
nights yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep no problem no
problem yeah um we have plenty of stone
maybe more gold
I just send more more people to the wood
farm so that's
okay mhm okay where am I there here they
are that's three or four should be four
no still building one right okay then
let's make um uh three my
Rams
H and then we can go oh yeah real
University I made a university for a
reason
um building hit
points he a
shot Miss sounds more
accurate what should I
do put people in Rams oh was it does did
it have to be
like far like can it be Farmers too or
or does it have to be like one of these
people I'm fine with putting them in
though
one per Ram or
[Music]
more put elephant in
Ram none or walls if you build them well
I guess we're not building walls
though oh can I put
more okay all my foot soldiers are going
into the
Rams that's an Archer though I do like
archers oh
[Music]
well okay okay I'm ready
soon you check out how how it's looking
over
there tonic night created ooh ooh o they
got like elephants in there
what
ooh oh looks so cool so
fancy hey guys how's it going no ooh
wa looks nice
okay okay he's going on his own again
here are my tonic Knights do I have more
coming yeah no Castle maybe we just
didn't see
it okay
uh are we ready to go Hey
sir
okay
okay let's go what do we attack
first what's what's the best thing to
attack first just whatever is in
front protect the
Rams
okay the Town Center this is the town
center right villager Center everything
people here we
go and make more just in case we get in
trouble Hey sir
oh
yeah
this why so slow what do I attack what
do I attack what do I do I attack with
the Knights uh everything else too or
like do we attack to together with the
Rams the same thing or like do we do we
scatter what do we do gosh why why don't
they attack this
thing now the Rams are going to the town
center oh they're there're Dar Knights
are going to attack me that's good
that's
[Music]
fine okay just attack everything go
go attack what's attacking
[Music]
you
okay okay
okay what what are they
doing yo it's working we're doing it
we're doing
it yeah let's go what's
next people
everything what do I have to do I have
to just kill everything that's red in
order to win
or
[Music]
my resources are
fine I'll just I just want to make the
idle people do
[Music]
something how's the battle going
they're having
fun I don't even see their Knights
anymore like it's we're just attacking
the
[Music]
buildings okay okay yeah kill him kill
him yeah nice one isn't that our Scout
no it's a
knight oh oh there's a KN what what is
this
thing we should attack
it
all right wait isn't it an archery
range oh he's still creating they're
still creating
people what this Monastery kill monk
where's the monk where's the I'm I they
can't they can't do anything about me
anyway oh they're going for the monk
okay okay okay okay found the
monk he's very slow and now he's
dead
all right use the Rams
oh oh I don't know maybe this one one
can go I'll Attack this one this one
this where's my last Ram or did it die
oh yeah one one ram
[Music]
died is there a way to choose Idol uh
Warriors
there's a
button comma or pun
uhhuh looking good looking good looking
good looking good looking
good looking
good grac Hill grow too near to my to no
wonder though when Victorious I shot
salt up apate that sounds good that
sounds
good y we're to win a chicken
dinner oh I'm so happy that feels so
good I feel like campaigns are like more
difficult to me than this because for
campaigns there's like so many different
different things to like take care of
they're like do this do that do this and
that this was just really clear what to
do M mhm
simply just build an economy and an army
and then go and kill okay have I gotten
an army oh oh okay okay
okay MAA repli to
me oh okay okay
okay okay okay there will be seemingly
two versus two versus two teams
mhm I already know who I'll be with but
I don't know if I should spoiler it
maybe not but it's someone I'm happy to
be with I
think who who who watched ID play um
aoe2 anyone
here if yes then tell me who's um who
was like really good who is especially
good and who is not so good I did I did
yes I did yes I
did
MAA MAA MAA
MAA really ma maa MAA ma maa MAA best
everyone else is weak hey
no moaa Ana in that order okay okay
really just
MAA MAA bullied the
others it's not
fair e well maybe the others have
practiced since as
well R is surprisingly good okay
okay ma maa
sweep okay
oh God my Coca-Cola is coming up my
throat MAA plays a lot of RTS on stream
after
all okay well well well we should play
another one somebody suggested me doing
um should I leave the map what's we're
turning to
map why would I do that it's like it's
dead it's
stopped let me out I guess just quit
current
game it saves what I did
right it's over anyway or to admire or
to
review
mhm The Art of War teach how to play Oh
Art of War tutorial ah look at this
995 in
score that what is that what does that
mean economy well we're like in the only
thing that were not as advanced was
technology but the rest we were strongly
winning all right good
good
good very good takak Chan thank
you don't know how it's
calculated that is very good just
slightly
one-sided I was so
worried
okay uh turn to main menu somebody said
something about is it maybe
here Advanced Techniques
maybe Art of
War where do I learn The Art of
War
oh I just like all of ah this whole
thing is the Art of War oh a good start
is half the battle train yourself to
build an effective Dark Age economy in
order to gain all right let's go sunu
teaches us not only how to engage our
enemies but also how to manage Logistics
an army cannot fight without the proper
supplies without food arrows and arms an
army cannot stand its ground yeah I know
that the words of sunzoo bring War
material with you from home but forage
in enemy territory then the Army will
have enough food to survive
let us if you understand yeah okay I
think understand it's a it's a strategy
to take your enemies resources but it's
it's it's really it's important to begin
in the right manner living early economy
will allow you to reach the feudal age
in a strong position from which you can
continue toow battle your opponent we'll
start off did glitch oh why do you guys
not see it I see
it from them sure not to kill all your
animals at oh no it's just a all of our
V on a single sheep and they are harves
meat move them all together to the next
one this minimizes the food Decay when
Gathering resources it is important not
to lose too much time walking to the
nearest gather Point make sure to place
your mills lumber camps mining camps and
town centers close to resources you can
also queue up multiple tasks for your
villagers by holding down the Shi key
when assigning tasks this is a new
feature in the definitive edition
the last less is a danger ATT are very
to hunt they are away and fight back
when fight back to why why why window
not come back and kill it safely before
we do this we may want to research loom
in the Town Center as it makes our
villagers stronger next select one
villager then right click on a nearby
boore to go hunt it watch closely as the
villag stop wait no I accidentally
skipped it cuz I CLI clicked into it I
hate when that happens wait let me I
don't know let me make
um Studio
mode game
capture ah
uh what
happened
what
happened I think I need to restart cuz
it's just weird I'll restart the the
game
yes it's weird cuz I was still seeing
everything
normally
sunu recommends to restart the
game EA Games challenge
everything oh there it is
okay maybe we can hear it again we heard
this as you are growing your
civilization important to begin in the
right I think this is like just this
part is
bugged when I go here it just
basically stops working look at
this yeah it
just I see it
normally let me I think maybe we can't
do it on
stream maybe I can still maybe I have
some time off stream if I end a bit
earlier than
planned sorry no tutorial perms yeah the
video bugs the game once the video end
maybe come to no no I ended it though it
didn't come back
[Music]
H yeah
sorry cuz I clicked on it and it it
ended it by accident so I guess
all back in the game come
[Music]
on capture this
hello hello
hello come back to
me I'll restart
again I broke my game with the
tutorial you went for the tutorial of us
as the advisers
anyway yeah I felt pretty like like okay
I get it and especially I'm I feel
already like so much
more like secure just by the fact that
we're not doing one versus one but two
versus two versus two which means I
always have someone else to like think
about what to
do and you know
split things to do
possibly yeah so I feel less nervous I'm
good let's do another
Skirmish um
let's do just a random
map wait no I want this is is
random maybe it will be the
hamburger
wait
random R is it random now how do I apply
it what I don't understand you still
can't see it
oh money the
why it came back fine the last
time sometimes I have to be in the
window for a while until it like decides
to capture
it hello I'm playing the game please
capture it
now
no you don't want to
maybe maybe you should capture it I
don't know I mean it's just I mean you
know your choice
but you don't you don't feel like
capturing
us it's all
broken OBS come on let me try go here in
here
hello
um
please
why the
game is way too dark for
me yeah it's kind of dark isn't
it oh it's not captured for Elgato it's
just I don't need an Elgato for this cuz
it's not a console
game
um
please tutorial really broke the
game sunu broke my
OBS come on I know you can do
it okay one more restart one one more
restart one more
restart before it uh came back when I
restarted and then it
stopped
it Dark Age be
like very a very super dark age it's a
handicap whoever can figure out
where where to click on the
screen
will practically basically just win the
game already just by
that
um how was it again when I restart OBS
was that like killing my
stream maybe I should restart
OBS
uh looks like it's not
working
okay but I will not be a kill forever
where were you when while I stream and
AOE was kill I will uh restart OBS for a
moment let's see what
happens I'm
scared
um am I
back I'm back back okay but the game is
not
back it's not it's just doesn't want to
be captured
anymore restart computer or wait now
that I restart OBS let me restart the
game one more time but just one more
time I already did several new game
captures in OBS I tried that okay here
we go
again here we go again
One More
Time One More Time One Last
Time okay come on I I am counting on you
I would like to stream please let me
stream y it's just too big but we can
fix
that
yeah this is uh too
big how
big here okay y finally we're not going
to try the tutorial again cuz it's going
to break
me what was I doing I was trying to
change this to
random but I don't understand how this
works
cuz it doesn't say
apply I don't get
it but okay
um this will be a realistic Recreation
wait let's do
one two
two three
three and yeah I'll choose for you how
about some we want some some where my
Italians where are my Italians there
some
Italians some
Brits some
Japanese Ana will be Japanese probably I
don't
know
and how
about Franks you got to love the Franks
yeah this is this is can I give it a
name I wish I could give it a
name why do they have should they have
like team colors oh they
can't oh everybody needs their own color
I guess
okay will
be I don't know who the others will
be
mhm Map size for six
players and uh we can the speed is on
casual now let's just let's just keep it
casual cuz before we had slow should I
change anything else
the teams are fine this way
right do normal normal
eh
okay smarter AI let's have like one one
how do I make them smarter do I have to
make all of them smarter I just want
some of them you know it's got to be
realistic some of them got to be smart
some of them not so
smart
yeah like one MAA AI that there's one
that should be like really really
good I guess we can't do that but we
could do moderate cuz standard was I
guess really easy just
now
yeah okay the rest is fine right but the
what about this location I want to
change
the oh wait this is just the
distribution
ah no I want I want
random but I can't apply it let's just
reset it I don't understand lock teams
how ah here okay what does that do
changing teams or Tri tributing oh
okay that was
important
h
ah I'm adding them to the
pool oh okay I don't
know
okay that's
fine don't click it did
I no mod what was that did I click
it feel like I almost did oh almost yeah
why not what's what's bad about that
one definitely
hamburger that's such a meme
map different mode oh really okay here
we go uh okay my my friends are here is
that is that what that is I'm blue I
think they were
red okay we start with food
right you guys told me spam food in the
beginning so that's what I'll be doing
and you can go Scout Sam I'm already
already like I have a plan
already good turkey found turkeys we in
it even blue perfect my turkeys go here
oh cute they make Goble Goble cble
sounds oh my God what map is this I see
like a lot of funny
animals is this a joke to you we're not
funny map map
map love it oh my I have to build a
house I actually have to build a house
uh
oopsie okay
house build the
house how fast can you build it can you
do it
alone man imagine there's there's six
teams on this small still relatively
small looking map uh build another
house not enough food
okay oh oh oh it goes up
there we're like in in a tropical region
it
seems
mhm
[Music]
right next person who gets created will
build all
Mill and the next one we'll build a
lumber Camp is it still building one
yeah uh a person build a
person
uh a lumber camp but now I don't have oh
oh I have to get actual trees normally
first okay we'll
do oh ah MAA already put up her stream
reservation so you can actually already
see the teams MAA is with crony is that
good should I be
scared I'm with
[Music]
way and Ana is with fauna h M when you
think about these
teams I'm
scared lucky crony yeah anybody who gets
with Muna is
[Laughter]
lucky anybody who gets with me is also
lucky anybody who gets with anyone is
lucky Pabi yeah it's lucky though like
cuz she apparently used a random team
generator but yeah poni Power let's go
Ana toldi is not
happening so
sorry wait I was going to build a a
lumber Camp
to oh there's a little animal walking
around in my M cute what is
that one day Ana toi will be
real today is not the
day uh wait I still ah there we go
Lumber Camp I guess like
here or like I want to build here but I
don't see what there is stairs let's
build it here that's close enough
hey good good good probably another
house uh necessary
though I'll get there in a
moment villager created
okay uh no materials for
house five more there we go
okay okay okay okay dozens of us dozens
that sounds like a
meme That Is Random full ID teams oh I
don't know about that maybe that's on
purpose okay you guys go to the
berries cuz they are done with the
animals oh who is that that's purple MOA
no what color was MAA wait I don't know
I didn't set stone who Mauna is I only
know who Anya is I
guess
hey that's right and I guess red would
be now
way wa I want to see oh are they is R
even doing
anything ta is located in this area oh
here wait who told me that my my my
teammate so Ana is there cuz that's
Japanese
Anya what the Lena get it together
share vision is off what the okay
that's weird can I still turn it on
probably not
right ah until I build a market oh I
don't know if I'll be building a market
what about this map guys should I be
building walls later on for this map cuz
like last time you guys said to open I
don't know about this
one
Ana playing sua game right now
apparently I said no Ana is here right
now with me Ana is with me I know I see
her I see her she's real I'm not
imagining
it can't see the mini Maps oh well it is
what it
is does this does this help you it's
still only
black you usually Rush enemies oh
instead of building a wall H not hold
that um anyway we need
[Music]
more actually
no mining C but we have have so little
Stone why why is so little
Stone F what
the
huh what do I need two Dark Age
buildings I have that uh meat oh wait I
can do it too oh I didn't see that kind
of looked red to me cuz like part of the
logo is kind of
red went Richard the lon okay
everybody's going I'll be the last it's
okay it's okay it's okay we we we'll get
there um you
know we'll get there
too okay uh I don't even have any gold
here
N Gold but you guys said I don't need
gold that early anyway right where is my
Scout here why don't you Scout my area
like closer to
me
man go here I want to see if there's any
gold old close
by okay uh Hey
sir what to do oh wait there oh we need
Farms they're
all not doing
anything there must be on the left you
mean like maybe
here there a there's a foreign
turkey Hey sir now it's my
turkey gobble gobble gobble gobble my
turkey mhm nothing
here gobble gobble just R it checking up
on
me m
oh okay I have final I'm so
late
hey
um Dock dock we can build a dock right
here my
water oh well I found something it's not
it's it's golden but it's not
gold
what is
this
oh something what the ah wait here's the
gold okay never mind you can do what you
want now I don't care I have found the
gold
actually uh we need a mining camp
here okay okay okay okay let's
go
okay
um one more and then we'll make some
fishing ships let's go also need houses
more
houses you built house ah wood now we
have wood that was
fast okay oh there's a lot of gold here
too I should claim it oh wait there's
gold here too what the
sparkly beautiful gold also look at
these animals I could claim those too
can I can I claim them now no I need to
see them actively I
guess oh yeah H go fishing uh where are
the fish
here Barracks I need a Barrack a Barrack
Barrack uh what's the Barrack
again bar Obama
sir was a uh bar
Barra Barra Barra Barra too
expensive bar Obama is kind of busy
right now um just go go wood wood go go
go
go almost there it is there it is there
it is there it is a little bit more just
a little bit more just a little bit more
come on come on come
on
come
deliver ah one
off
yeah okay there it is
Barracks I have them all in stone I mean
I don't know because I
guess we'll send more of them here
he but only one on Stone feels like too
little so I'll bring one back
there Hey sir HZ htz M
htz okay
um more
villagers
maybe another house
soon okay
now and then you what do we we want
Knights anyway right I
mean
but for now maybe
some ooh the cheaper thing
sperman okay hey
um one of you make
farm one of you
join join the
Gold more people
okay I was also thinking of experiments
we're making chewing gum so this in
there what do we know oh wa okay this
looks very different from what I'm
doing it's okay it's AI who knows if the
other girls play that well a market
should I make a market is that like
priority now when I play with like other
people like this l c blacksmith
though yes not really yes build Market
yes
okay um Market can be anywhere or close
to the outside I'll just build
here what's the Oink
Oink what's with the Oink Oink calm
down
okay is this going fine we have so much
Stone wow
good militia line costs minus 15 food
uhuh oh H okay
probably
forging and this armor stuff later on
though but I'm doing it
early okay oh now I can see everything
oh okay well not that I really care
right now I care when they come to
me maybe I'll play
defensive I don't know if that's a good
idea
um sheesh all the wood HZ
yeah let's make another
boat there's Lumberjack upgrades
oh
oh I did not even
realize should I upgrade these things
too maybe not right
now oh chill guys
chill
St what do I need to upgrade just a lot
of food okay just a lot of food if
that's the
case one more
farm and this boat goes fishing
now all
right nobody has upgraded yet though to
that uh Castle
age food and
gold gold I actually have plenty see I'm
well prepared on that front should I do
something
here should I get a trading card I don't
really care about trading
stuff ah okay there there goes the
castle
age
yeah oh well do we have any animals here
yeah do these attack they don't attack
right okay
no she'll also be a
hunter
heyya maybe another
house oh oh Ana is Castle aging she do
be castling no stop the
Ana how how far am I away I'm almost
there I'm almost there I'm almost there
Wood please wood
please Raina asking me for wood wait I
don't know how to give it to you are
they seriously asking me for wood like
like for real for real wood
please how go to my market buy it in my
market I gu yes how do I react to
that sorry you can't have my wood I need
my oh I have a I have a lot of wood two
5,000 okay wait wait maybe maybe now we
can chill with the wood um now we
can one of you another
farm much's
farm type 11
top right The
Laurels
what
what top right there's a
oh how do I give
food
[Laughter]
They're laughing
what
huh
diplomacy okay that was
embarrassing okay I give uh do I click
on this oh how much do I want is this
enough 200
maybe what I was
laughing 300 is good
okay okay all right you're welcome Winer
thanks it will be wisely spent yeah you
better make us win why are you lacking
wood I'm not laging wood you shouldn't
be laging wood what's going on something
went wrong in your economy then fix
it
it's not good not looking good okay uh
uh uh um let's build
something Watchtower go watch the
people what's this oh I'm in Castle L
let's go now he makes the
castle make us the
castle in one
moment and
Stables yeah yeah so is uses Castle
Go castle
go I guess here it's right next to the
Watchtower but oh
well I'm being
attacked
what
where oh it's just my Scout probably
right I don't see anything going
on
freak
scary
he um stable for the nights for the
nights
fortnite
okay probably Scout yeah Scout always
does these kind of
things oh Wood
please what's what
no a little bit maybe you little
what why why you have no wood I
mean okay maybe cuz you built so much
holy
please look at me look at my economy
Rainer I need the wood for
myself I'm not doing so well either you
know I'm being attacked again okay
probably fine probably Dieu
[Music]
um I should start mining wood elsewhere
maybe uh Lumber
cam what are these explosions
BS what the
mining wood yeah we are mining
wood he
sir um okay uh
Knights oh no not these Knights oh yeah
wait wait wait stable Knights wait where
my stable this my stable
no this my
stable
maximum
stability of my
Army
yeah watch
to oh they're right next to me those
Purple People imperal AG wait that's my
No that's not my team
right was that
Rina yeah wa wa first one to reach
Imperial because I gave her all the
wood
okay that's good that's
good um all right hey what's with these
red people wait that's my stuff the
she's going into my territory okay
I guess it's fine it's kind of
intimate what do I
do
what do I
do what do I
do more golden
Food gold yes definitely gold can I use
this camp this mining camp
too what do we not share do I have to
make my
own just
kill
no let's let me let me mine this here
okay
hey
no
go I am being attacked oh I'm being
attacked for real for real for real for
real for real for real for real for real
for real for real for real go go go go
go go go go
go Wood please oh no shut up r
look at me I'm
suffering do I look like I have time for
it to give you like wood and yeah
nine
nine I'm winning though what they buil
something right there those
not enough gold not enough gold
please how do I ask for gold gold give
me the gold give me ah
ah calm it's Okay
shh uh ask for how do I ask for
help chat chat okay what I
wait
help uh do I really need help or am I
fine I'm being
rushed being rushed ah being rushed
[Laughter]
five oh yeah gold pleas gold please gold
please will they give me gold IET s that
I not Des spare do you not remember how
many times I have spared things for you
you know how politics in in in the
Medieval Age works right you have to
give in order to
get oh oh they are helping me though
okay wait I'm losing my whole
Army because you didn't get give me
gold a my
people they br out the Ram okay
wait that's that's my friend's Ram okay
y
y I have no Army
left you kidding me those purple
people those purple what
oh my
God wait I need to
attack wait uh uh where do you make oh
oh oh oh oh
ah uh
uh
ah ah
hey another
pic
KN gold
please what do you say
they don't give me
gold I'm still being attacked
though was this the right thing to
ask help me help
me
okay
okay uh byebye this is this is how it's
going to be huh is this how it's going
to be this this how it's going to be oh
they came with elephants they're kind of
rams
shees
okay we need to attack this
thing
Sasa can they can the farmers enter that
no uh where am I where's my why do all
these buildings look so
similar uh maybe not the best idea um
don't leave
yet okay go away go away
ah
help
help nice to I'll take oh my
God blame your
ISP
oh my God being rushed being rushed
rushed don't just immediately leave me
[Music]
always uh I'm I'm I'm like forever in
this endless
loop uh oh
a walls s is
there
well I want to give
up imper can I do that too no all the
elephants are coming once again wait
let's let's uh let's wait
yeah
mhm they sent the elephants again
[Music]
okay oh the elephants are
dying later
no wait where's the rest of the
elephants
I will not give
up y my
gold my go oh my
gold
wait huh fishing boat no more fish what
the what
well uh gold oh but no not this gold I
guess unless
oh God oh God are you a person you're a
person this is my gold you little
you need to
understand what do I do when I am out of
fish fish
traps
okay
uh mucha's
gold and and wait
ah okay we stopped them from attacking
me
yeah not enough food oh my
God wait so this nobody's working the
Farms I don't want you
ships also I need people to
repair repair
this yeah
okay
this how's this work once you have
the build castle Another
Castle
yeah
really or should I build
walls make the fish make the Trap your
fishing boat needs to build the fish
trap oh okay
uh
ah Hey
sir Castle usually
better yeah especially if they're so
close we need something
therea food please give me food they
they never give me anything what kind of
relationship is this only taking no give
giving
huh might actually I'll I'll keep some
people
here hey gold
please I think I'm breaking up later
what I'm being attacked again or what
now you want gold again I'm not giving
you
oh wait no no no I'm not letting
that
stand oh they're attacking the scout
you are not doing anything about my
castle the castle is happening where
about you wanted to Holy uh are we
strong against this no we not right
um what the what the what the
what the what the
[Laughter]
my castle no my
kns no no no oh what's the right
building what's the right building I
don't know a oh no they're
killing
me
no
help Rush
rushed
[Music]
archers archers uh where where are The
Archers which one is the Archer building
which one is the Archer
building which one which one is the I
have an Archer building is this the this
is not the Archer building which
one is the arch
building no no no no yeah do I have an
Archer building I
don't I can't build it I have no
[Music]
wood
no no
no no no wait I have so much gold now
wait wait wait we can stop farming the
gold um we
wood wait hey
hey do I have anything I can fight right
now oh no uh oh no oh oh oh they sent me
some help how nice of them oh buy
resources from the market um I'm buying
what am I buying
food and wood
okay
no
no keep on sending help keep on sending
help I don't want to die I don't want to
die
no
no let's go somewhere else to start
again
no then that's that's like starting over
I can't start
over gold
please not give me gold you never give
me anything
okay okay they're actually attacking
that building that's very
helpful shall we
help I mean my my Knights are very weak
to uh these Pike people I
guess but hey Raina sent the right
people for once let's kill this
you for building your
here
you I'm building my castle again oh if
only I had Stone if only I had Stone
where was my stone Farm here's some gold
left there's a little bit of stone here
where's the
stone don't take my
stone don't take that's all I have
way can you tell them to go
away
um what do what do I do okay it's down
uh can I can I build the castle castle
castle 650 oh God I think I have to buy
it I think I have to buy it buy
some okay uh
uh okay it's finally calm again it's
calm now
never go go go go go go oh an I resigned
what was going on there it must have
been some
drama o la wait let's get help again cuz
like I'm so scared they're already
starting to fight me again oh I sh
apate okay we are already we're already
minus one uh enemy
so oh they came with the Rams they came
with the Rams
no no no no no no no okay okay okay oh R
thank you thank you maybe I'm not
breaking up with you after all wait
thank
you I have a ram too do does a ram need
someone to be
inside okay okay the Rams are coming yay
I hope I hope Raina is fine when I'm
already wait she's like everywhere oh no
never mind she's fine I was going to say
like I hope it's okay to take all her
people all this all the time to
survive my mission is only to survive oh
she she's going in she's going in oh my
God
okay let's make some tonic Knights here
okay and then let's focus on
please what wool a wood uh I might
consider it now since you have been
helping me a
lot like if you if you really need do
they really when they ask for that do
they like really need it like for real
for real or are they fine if I don't
give it to
them oh I God I have so many so many
people who are not doing anything
okay I need to catch up I need to catch
up I need need to catch
up uh okay we're out of uh Stone here
that's like really
dear no wonder though where I sh
Francesco has the Franks I think have
abated y I've stood my ground more than
they did okay okay okay okay uh Stones
would be really nice though
like I want that Stone but it's like so
deep in their Camp if only we could take
down the the purple ones why won't the
purple ones Abate or have they abdicated
was that purple just now no
right okay oh god um yeah how do I get
maybe I'll just mine more gold and then
just buy the stone I don't
know I'll join them on the
gold he
sir
that was indeed the one that kept
attacking you oh really hey so purple is
gone for real for real I can take the
stone Hey sir I already forgot the color
you
know okay let's
go let's go that's big that's big sheesh
that honestly Raina did
that but if they weren't so aggressive
attacking me all the
time what why are you wasting your time
here wait they're gone they moved
out there's a score button next to the
map use that to see
it what what am I trying to see
score what what does this
mean I'm I'm currently the the worst
look at those
numbers oh player what does that
mean hey
wa
I don't know I don't know I don't know I
don't can't look at this right now I
need to do other
things I'm just trying to survive I'm
not helping at
all but as long as I survive I'm like
still you know in the end I might come
out the
strongest not trying to mingle in the
battles oopsie that was bad placement oh
look at all
these well wait tell me if you need help
tell me if you need help all
right
ah
uh uh oh
okay food please food food M yeah I can
give you a little bit since you've been
so
helpful I have so much gold wait I can
buy myself a ton of stuff yes not
selling bye bye bye bye I sold by
accident bye
oh stone stone stone stone Stones okay
um now can I what I need to advance we
need more a little bit more gold H oh
now I I sold all my gold no
okay never mind we'll get the gold back
quickly
um we'll get it back quickly we'll get
it back we'll get it also it doesn't
matter cuz I'm I'm surviving as long as
I survive everything's thriving I'm
surviving so I'm thriving you know all
is good what could I do like I'm so like
panicking that I I'm like not not is it
worth building a monastery now I would
say
no I don't
know maybe you need to play Spanish or
Italian they were perfect Tech treat
why get all Villages working yeah what
do we
need maybe now we need more gold
again
hey
um we could go down here get some more
gold
uh it feels like it's going to be over
soon
though it's kind of far but wait where
did it
go ah where did it go I
here kind of far but at least it feels
like there's no danger in being
attacked okay and
then we were l kind of lacking wood
sometimes and I had to buy it so let's
get some
wood n I'm being attacked by wild oh
that's what's down there wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait oh ah it's fine
that's fine that's fine
okay now maybe we could make some more
nights
again that was bad why if they resigned
why do they still show are the dots not
only people but also buildings look at
this guy he's still on
it oh
oh waya is like probably needing help
but but I'm just chilling but she's look
at her she's fine how did she do that I
need to find out how the AI did that my
God I'm just
chilling maybe maybe I should also make
an army and Mingle
wait
okay let me get some
Rams I feel like it's already too late
like who's even alive food please okay
see I I'm I'm at least like you know
helping I have a lot of food I have all
of this um what was I going to do a yeah
Advance oh I can't still not enough
gold I can sell some
food all my Beginnings no wonder after
kid it see I don't even need to do
anything who's the last
one green or blue blue Right light blue
light
blue
uh
[Music]
make trading cards for
gold but they're already on it aren't
they no wait that's H green is
green what's going
on they just did Red build a mining camp
in the middle of light
blue
NY oh they're going okay okay we shall
help uh uh where am I uh we shall help
we shall help we shall make ourselves
useful help we
shall make ourselves useful for
once two more at least once in this game
play what do we
attack we'll need a while to get there
anyway m
[Music]
M I don't know what to
attack just
[Music]
uh
people archers are not good
though
okay I need people in here what the
where do I how do I where where what was
that
there
how do I know there's
someone Z out six six
okay
mhm
um uh oh okay uh how do I how do I do
this where's the market what the is
the market wait wherever this one is
going uh wait where which one is the
market tell me which one's the
market which one's the
market
huh
huh this
one I don't know food please oh
yeah e e
e this one
maybe wait yes yes I was right okay I
hope that works okay I made a trade rout
route route uh how's my blue
doing oh we're doing
fine helping let's
go probably too late for
Rams I don't see them though
sending some
help and E
on did the stream die oh I'm F sorry I'm
focused on doing stuff
here I'm helping though look it's all
falling down blue is actually doing
something let's go Papi
strong all right oh there's a castle
let's take down the castle
guys take down down the castle oh way
built a freaking whatever that is triet
yeah in the middle of that she that AI
is
smart wow my Rams will never arrive in
time that's okay I'm happy with how my
resources are looking after that where I
was like like losing everything oh they
abated that's it I think
yeah okay I mean I was more like the
helper which will I that's probably how
it will be anyway
tomorrow yeah but I with stood it while
absolutely panicking but I survived I
didn't like I didn't need to like
restart in another area as some people
suggested yeah I did a comeback I had a
lot of resources there I was able to
support my partner which I would say
that is also important yeah while my
part my partner was absolutely rocking
it killing every enemy and help
helping me too at the same time yo check
the timeline how how how how wait can I
see that here where do I see that is
that it's not here right oh oh now it's
just
sounds
wow
oh how do I see the detailed wait I have
to leave
right quit current game yeah
let's see what does it tell what does
this tell me did I do well Society my
Society was high high society my my
total score is like La second to
last but I won okay holy look at
all these numbers wait I chose the right
person to fight with
me I'm
lucky my
military oh compare my military to the
others
oh my economy is second highest
their econ I don't know how their
economy is so high when I was constantly
giving them
but my economy is second
highest
whoa she that was an aggressive
AI
okay oh I was late for every was the
only one who didn't reach Imperial age
cuz while everybody else was like
getting Imperial age I was attacked the
whole time units
lost I won something wait no wait no I
lost the least units oh wait okay even
though I was like constantly being
attacked and recreating units two
castles 2 two one one zuro Anya had no
Castle I guess she didn't have the time
cuz she was the first to apate
Relic gold oh she got some
relics they also did
actually oh survival to finish yes yes
yes ah what do that what does that
mean you can't lose units if you have no
units so true so true oh oh oh what does
this mean
oh a lot of red
here decent blue here at the
end I was like pretty stable if you look
at this like they all like become small
and and
die I guess that's what that
means I did worst mid game well yeah
that's when I was constantly being
attacked by purple and couldn't do other
cuz but I tried my best to
multitask creating units constantly
creating uh villagers
constantly that was funny red wanted for
me might not be so lucky next time with
the best AI on my
team I was keeping up till Castle age
yeah until then everybody except like
waya is just abnormally thick isn't
[Laughter]
she don't take it out of
context I Lally last night that you
played aoe2 and to Total War first time
I ever had a dream about a streamer as
well
oh well it became
reality what does this mean this
fighting
[Music]
symbol
je a battle
events there's no no wonder
constructions what are Wonder
constructions does anybody he ever get
to that
point you means a big battle
oh oh all those battles in my city were
not considered
big they kept on like coming in small
teams slowly
slowly a unique building gives a win
after 200 years game what a different
way to
[Music]
win
beding a wand cost a ton of resources
and defending until the end you see I
could have done
that I I was going for that that that
that that's what I was going for that
yeah I was going for Wonder construction
that's why I was not helping with the
battles yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
mhm
wa
oh
did you hear that that was like 10
cracks I failed every single one of
them sorry I'm in pain
okay I can't help
it I'm so I'm sorry it does feel good
because like I always feel like I'm
constantly M
[Music]
tense didn't we talk about that two
years
well my pain isn't going away do the
cracks are not going
away spend your resources as fast as
possible spend until you're constantly
bankrupt I guess that's what waya did
cuz she kept on begging me beg begging
begging wow W give me some gold and some
food begging begging wow wow I'll fight
for you you'll be
[Music]
good it even rhymed oh okay I want to
play one more one more
[Music]
time
okay I'm I'm just happy I survived cuz
this this could have gone wrong
it probably will go wrong
now could have probably just pushed play
again but I want to like change things
up
uh what's these other
versions 1 2 3 4
6 oh they automatically became the same
people I mean let's switch it up a
little bit how
about gos Shi
my hot golf girlfriend how about some
Kels some Koreans
hukam and some Spanish
people
espanol let's share the
exploration oh wait handicap is a way
to you know make a little of difference
give everybody an a handicap except for
the one who's supposedly
MAA no I won't do it
but
um play against Korea you will learn one
or two something new oh really yeah I
mean I'm I I will look at the teams I'm
going to go with mle as my teammate
again
okay the rest I think is fine the way it
was like the AI difficulty
was already plenty I would
say
uh
yeah game speed normal that was like
stressful for me
already M treaty
length oh that's interesting while
treaty is active no player can attack
another oh that's that's interesting cuz
that's like also you know a thing that
just happens in medieval times or any
anytime really I guess m is a water SI
or well who knows maybe we get a water
map Korea and Spain lands is that is
that something to be scared of oh
okay let's let's get let's take
something else what what else is
interesting to have as a partner for
me doesn't mean they us without exactly
like I mean they were were rocking the
map yeah Vikings okay what the Vikings
do docks cost minus that that's a that's
a
water sa for sure more than
[Music]
Malay black is are my favorite who knows
we might lose because of that Britain
and France we had that in the previous
match bantine what the what the is
that what country is that supposed to be
monks plus 100% healing speed camel
Riders
skirmishers Middle East Romans Eastern
Roman oh East Roman Empire oh
right okay yeah I'm fine with that
because like Vikings who knows if we get
a water map okay ah I'm scared let's
go St
all right uh gold uh uh
food um build
house go oh I see
barries oh friend is over
here
g
good luck with economy good start the
first three seconds Good Start
wa thank you what's this stuff oh is
that bamboo bamboo
Bamboo
interesting it's a water map
uh is
it I mean yeah I see a lot of water well
we have to practice we never we don't
know what what Muna is going to bring
upon
[Music]
us
house you can't get to the center that
easily and kill my my thingy if I
surrounded with
houses wait oh did I make you stop
working on that sorry
sheep found
oh look at them go look at them go more
house more
house sorry I'm building it on top of
him houses are good to put at choke
points M
he it's actually in proper German
nowadays it would
beer German language has changed hasn't
it and now we shall start with some wood
I
think get a m close to the bushes here
but then there's not so much space to
build the farm
around uh materials
toal actually go for this one cuz this
one's currently really
close so for now that's good as long as
we don't have a lumber
Camp ah oh I can just build around the
town center true I guess
so but for now we still have berries
and there's sheep down
there I should get the Sheep
too go get the
Sheep okay okay
okay
[Music]
currently in terms of resources I'm the
lowest I think if it's in that order
seemingly
so I was going to say I was going to be
happy if I wasn't the lowest but it's
not such a big difference right
now and my my teammate is
second Hey
[Music]
sir I'm just chilling for now I like I
like this calmness before the
storm
how about a
mill why why do you want me to build
here because it's like hard to reach for
enemies
or why I want to build farms around
it yeah I know this is for not for wood
oh you meant near the bushes ah okay
okay okay okay that I can get
behind more
wood
okay going going
well what the M build
okay m
h Huh Hey sir what a f is located what
what are you trying to tell me with that
what what does that
mean M near a deer is also good oh the
deer
yeah I heard an arrow
scary
wait who who what's the arrow
sound I'm going to
start no I need I need a I need a lumber
Camp did I build one
no Hey
sir quick quick quick quick
quick or this one
[Music]
um Lumber Camp Lumber can be
here
okay yeah muchos wood oh my guys oh
they're hunting okay sorry I have
PTSD
scaryy
okay more more villagers more villagers
ADV
ADV okay I need a lot of more stuff ah
okay we got the buildings just need a
lot of more
food yeah we'll get there we'll get
there oh friend
boat I'm keeping up with the villager
production though I would
say villagers more important than
upgrade
ages you can cancel villagers and
upgrade now nah it's
fine I'm fine uh we're going to build a
mining camp uh in the middle then we can
reach both the gold and the stone quite
well start on just one person on the
stone and then one person on the gold I
know I know I know maybe no need but I
will do
it
I'm still the lowest and holy look
at the heran corz both of my team are at
the bottom not doing so
well not in the middle it's too
far more wood okay I think I can yeah
advance
mhm
ooh I don't know what I'm seeing I don't
know maybe more houses now and then
start building like Barracks after we
after we
advance we build hey
house oh are you done with the berries
oh that means we quickly need to stack
up on the
farms
okay
house
villagers uh who's not you're not
working right where are you I don't know
oh oh actually that's kind of
far maybe go
here and then what was I saying I was
going to do oh yeah I have
Advance build Barracks go go go
go no I'm um put them on gold for now
yeah maybe one
[Music]
more um let's see maybe another
Farm okay okay we're all
advancing what could I
do wheelbarrow
research Hey sir and what I need for the
next advancing a lot of food okay yeah
uh how about we make a
dock do sorry I'm like really focused
I'm trying to do this correct so maybe
not so funny right now I'm just trying
to focus ah let me place it oh not
enough materials or what
H
what
huh is it because I can't see
it that's
is a fully in the
water ah here
okay help
him
um
Stone okay okay I think like my economy
is is doing well how am I so far behind
look at those numbers I'm under a
thousand okay now I'm over a thousand
but look at them
NY and I'm trying my
best I think I'm doing fine like better
than before
even a few a few oh oh way is attacking
stupid fisher boat R you're wasting your
time but oh yeah okay with so much water
I guess I'll also have to like do some
some
warships a galley is a galley a
warship I think
so fire into water maybe I should have
gone for Vikings huh yes okay then let's
make some
G okay not enough wood sheesh Hey sir
more wood then two more people for wood
action
cast Okay this purple guy AI is really
good that's MAA sasuga what was I going
to do oh yeah a
house
yeah can I
Advance
he no actually no um go go go go go
[Music]
sheep okay you're doing well keep it up
thank you any good upgrades well I
should be building some more interesting
stuff like um
stable
right and then
[Music]
archery what are those houses well you
don't like how
I how I put them this time I'm improving
thank you yeah keep on spamming the
villagers okay okay okay
M okay
but you know it takes so much food I'm
trying to like save some food right now
but okay my G should just be chilling
for now or should I like send them to do
[Music]
something I can scout with
them I guess I'll send one oh wait this
is not g
Patrol oh I don't I don't no it's just
patrolling there Patrol I don't
know where do I click or
Scout is there a scout no just
patrolling go C archers clearly
eh oh hey guys chill chill chill
chill
more houses ah more
houses houses there one
here one
[Music]
here are they too close together I
wonder
Patrol the ocean my
ocean look for the one piece maybe
you'll find it somewhere on the way and
then we get automatic win wouldn't that
be
great oh God we have so much oh so many
workers uh wait how's my soon now now
now TM not soon TM not TM let's
go um what do I need let's add someone
here add someone
here
maybe cuz somebody already said this is
too far away I'll I'll build another one
right at the Gold
maybe okay
cast
one piece would fit better into AOE 3's
time frame but who plays aoe3 we all
play AOE
too okay I think my economy is like so
much better than before but also who
knows maybe we're going to get attacked
soon and then I'm going to be like
what do I do what do I do now
do there's so much water we should do
more fishing boats I just decided
that oh oh oh you guys sorry the sorry I
guess I guess A3 isn't that
bad sorry it's fine it's fine am I being
the last to advance to Castle age
again but at least I am
advancing he sir
[Music]
um you're not fishing anything right
let's
go
what are you do what are you going to do
what are you going to do
gold job
change oh now I can make a castle okay
Castle time castle time castle time ooh
too expensive need W uh Stones okay
go fast fast fast fast
fast more
villagers maybe a few
more
oh okay
need Stone I'll be there soon uh how
much Stone wait what what uh what am I
looking for
here oh I can make it um now where
though
like red is like over here so it doesn't
make sense maybe here H depends like
where they're coming
from next to my
mines
here by the water maybe here is that too
far on the the shore South want to like
here then South and
Shore okay looking good
okay okay we'll help
them also need maybe more houses soon I
don't know no not
yet not
yet I like this
music makes me feel like everything's
still fine
[Music]
what else uh should we make a market and
a blacksmith and a mon let's make uh
blacksmith
first in the market yeah I don't know
should the market uh I guess closer to
waa Wood please wood please here we
go wait do I have uh plenty of wood how
we doing this
again oh oh I need a market first okay
then you're asking too early wa I'm not
ready yet not
quite um I can help building the market
here um besides that my resources I need
more
Stone and I will add one more mining
camp
here am I doing well
Market further makes the train it's
better when it's further away oh well
okay I'll remember that for next time I
think can still plenty far away cuz like
they got to go all around
here look at all of this oh I should
build more how did hers look bigger why
do hers look
bigger four
docks yeah four
shubas is that normal
dogs this is just a safe
difference can I make them just
different okay um then I'll build one
here I just feel like eh was it Imperial
AG already over
there oh wait I forgot building
Knights do I need Knights even when
we're like fighting on the ocean
I mean a few won't won't hurt
right ah they wanted um what was it
wood I think they wanted wood
right uh tonic Knights you will need
Knights yes wood
BL I have plenty well okay maybe not
that much 400 maybe
300 hope it's not too late wait thanks
it will be wisely spent okay
um I mean I guess somebody will have to
ride the galley right upgrade to W gy
Fire Ship should I do that makes sense
right seems like we're going to do a lot
of uh fighting on the
ships yes
okay um okay Hey sir uh let's look at my
resources okay
not where should we GA
them I'm being
attacked really I don't think so it's
just it something small
probably
[Music]
M let's make more tonic
Knights literally my name is in there so
it's probably just a scout yeah you're
right no Panic hey
wait I'm number
two in the ranking is it because I'm
already advanced
or yeah do I need another
Castle Wood please I just gave you
wood
they go for spikes so don't make a lot
of okay I thought so yeah so not too
many people on horses is what you're
saying right I'm being attacked no I'm
not build all the castles castles are
good even when we're like fighting on
Water I guess they're just strong for
defense are
they um Okay so one is down here so I'll
build one
here good placement I would say good
protection uh we need houses now cuz I
have reached my
limit Hey
sir yeah grouping some
people Hey sir
yeah
okay caras are super strong better build
more
warships War
Galley War Galley oh they don't even
need that many resources but should I
put people into the war G
now car a
scage imperial age
uh need more
[Music]
gold gold please actually I could just
sell yeah you have nothing to spare
great thank you for nothing I'll sell a
little bit a little
bit
okay Imperial age let's
go I'm yeah and I should make the the
cart oh sorry in a moment I'll make a
cart
right one more
house oh don't don't worry about the
don't worry about him oh the G are
killing
him oh yeah he's going down oh I'm
killing the Scout or am
I no aim do Co oh there we go
okay hey look at the
numbers
wa not bad although oh wait waya is like
winning again look at waya 4,500 y my
waya AI is so strong I'm so
lucky wait so um what was the wait wait
wait let me let me read
something don't Focus too much okay okay
University better aim oh
really
uh did you say something
about um putting people into ah you
can't put people in water only Transport
oh so they'll just be doing their thing
on their own n a so then I need some
transport ships maybe too though
no houses don't provide anything other
than being a blocker and IND
destructible build extra as walls around
the castle
H okay okay more houses around the
castle okay um I'll be back in time
thank you in the morning yeah you also
need transports to get your units okay
okay transport chips transport chips are
overrated you have land access to enemy
true okay can only move 10 units at a
time 20 with
upgrades don't let transports get
converted I can't be
converted can really mess up your ships
oh okay
um so we need a
university
um H maybe a Siege Wood
please
uh M what else was I going to do a yeah
a trade
[Music]
card I'm being attacked for real now
oh oh they both went no they're not both
them
oh oh oh oh
oh oh I
[Music]
Advanced ah not the
trade your Bo is this mine yeah hey a
bit okay now you should be fine what's
what's what's happening wait wait wait
wait wait ah ah
ah
uhoh now hold
up okay
D Castle
strong okay theat
[Music]
this okay just keeping them like all
across so that I have people easily at
reach
somewhere
um uh what do we
need what do we
need probably another Castle or another
oh repair Castle
okay another dock oh I'm being attacked
again no no no no no no
no upgrade ship can I do
that wait how uh ship
armor gallion should I upgrade to
gallion
okay
um
yeah build more units so
SN just going to focus a bit more on the
tonic Knights this
time Wood
please if that means we're winning I'll
give you as much wood as you
want perfect timing oh my God
zero wait did you hear it already in
that moment or did you anticipate
it oh I'm I'm like I'm like I feel
like I'm doing so well I don't know what
to do what else is there to do wait this
this trade cart needs to go to the
market where is the
market what does the market look like
hey how the do I know what's the
market oh maybe this that looks like the
Mark is it the mark yes okay let's go
trading I literally cannot see um the
dock uh I should not have built it
there should I also get the carer Karine
karening
also there's space for another Castle
here should I should I should I
hey I
mean upgrade to Elite
Knights O
Okay kening is ship armor yeah but it
also says like something about the other
like the transport chips I'm not really
going to use I think I don't
know
okay that's okay no upgrade is really
wasted
okay then did I do it yet yes I did
it R Castle oh wait H University I
wanted to do something there uh building
head
points Castle attack versus ships
sure uh range Siege where's the
[Music]
aim which one's the
AIM
ballistics okay all right we're studying
back to school 14 people who are not
working oh we're out of stone uh is
there anything close
[Music]
by do I just not see it and there's some
here I'll I'll I think I'll send some
there
um nobody seems to be occupying
it I can take it
right I'm so bad at like moving
around wait I'll give you wood in a
second
okay or help help building Uh Wood Wood
Wood Wood hi hi hi n one more
okay I'm being attacked by wild
animals oh
oh that's not so good that's not so good
but it's almost
dead
okay okay she that was a that was like a
leopard or something didn't get Loom
yeah okay let's get
Loom yeah yeah probably good idea to do
that
um
um ooh hit points on the
castle villagers plus 15 attack versus
buildings military buildings work for oh
working crenelations okay
oh wait nobody's working on that
castle
click also Lumber Camp kind of far
should I build another
one U we need more gold too but they're
still working on the gold that we have
what are you guys
doing
I don't even see another gold resource
close
by is there any
relics get a monk to heal them heal who
are these people
oh wait do we have a do we have
a I didn't build a church did
I I don't think I did
anything looks like this I wish I wish
the buildings didn't all look so similar
okay Monastery doco here it
is and we're look we're doing so well I
think we're doing well but we can start
like attacking maybe sometime
[Music]
soon speaking of
attacking what
[Music]
okay I was going to do a monk wood
please oh uh do I have
wood
sheesh oh man there's a no no it's only
free we're fine yeah kill their gies
kill them
he you can't win you take down maybe one
galy of mine no not even
that
[Music]
okay 26 tonic
Knights nine should I build more
horses he
sir what are those
sparman H what which one is
you huh did the name
change oh wait
here n n n just this oh M they took down
the one that has had really
low low
HP surprised no one surrendered yeah but
look at rain like holy she's like
the biggest economy again how am I so
lucky with my
AI uh what was I going to do was I going
to do something oh yeah I was going to
heal
um wait they don't need healing who who
did you want me to heal I thought the
the gold HP was the Villager HP for that
[Music]
moment and and house I'm one house on
the ocean can I can I own that one I
want
it
oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh you want something you want trouble
you want some trouble
huh
hey wait is she trying to fight no okay
good yeah yeah yeah yeah you run back
and tell them try tell them that they
should never try to fight against me
again my partner is waya remember
that wait let me see who did you guys
tell me who I was going to
heal I need more houses you must
construct additional pill what what if
you have many ships
why oh should I attack their their uh
boats and
docks
oh was I going to repair the gy with a
monk I thought you have to repair those
also with a farm on a
villager blacksmith upgrades okay
okay you can rate and test can Retreat
of not
working uh what's
pylons and
Si is Village yeah
mhm try to text see what they
have I need gold w
w not that
much
hey oh were you guys not
[Music]
working
oh hey sir a that's not mine
oh wait I thought there was going to be
a castle what is this a Siege Workshop
don't I have two now
no wait that's rain is I just realized
that's rain of
SE huh she
built why why would you do
that why would you do
that can I build a Wonder then I win I
have the resources for Wonder and then I
get automatic win
right is that kind of
boring what was I going to
do yeah do it not automatic I could
try oh I need to protect it for 200
years oh I don't know how long that is
in the
game I can make another
Castle I just I I need my people to
build
something it's not a bad thing to build
a third
Castle she fought way ahead to help me
that is true that's a
smart more Farms
okay what's happening
oh
yeah
[Music]
mhm oh
monk
stated oh oh red is passing by oh wait
no that's not not where I am
oopsie
hey
oh do they not have a castle close by
that's not very
smart
he how long this is going to take maybe
a Wonder would work
oh
uh-oh what do you think about this is
this a good match for
me let's attack the ship should
we yeah yeah
true is that a castle if yes and that's
a tiny ass
Castle my best so far let's
go a I feel bad though for killing
[Music]
them Wood please
wood yeah it's good that he's always
asking for the one thing that I do
have okay oh they're already trying to
build a new one wait wait wait
wait
yeah took one
down okay multitasking right now but I
have like 20 any villagers I want to do
something with them but I can't
multitask like that I don't even know
what to do with
them every every everyone's just playing
oh oh uh uh how about just doing uh
Lumber
Camp
okay
uh which one to fight
first uh wait wait wait
wait what's the sparkle
sound
oo
o go go go go
go
yeah let's
go ah is is but I can't be converted
right yeah I took another one
down see I'm finally going a little bit
aggressive and it's kind of working so
I'm quite
proud what's this chase down here
oh hey you can't convert me as far as I
know what is this by the way
Barracks let attack on Barracks rape
Monk
is this even worth it what I'm
doing
yeah
ah
oh honey what do you want you're not
even like a war
unit gold please I'm kind of busy right
now
gold um you can have a tiny
bit oh Korean War cards it's not a
trading card oh any free damage is good
why does the AI keep building there to
to to defend themselves
no incredibly resilient to
range
[Music]
yeah are they worth fighting holy
they are incredibly
resilient your enemies is in your
town okay
um I'm giving up have fun I that was
that was fun so
so uh you need help
where I don't think you need help you're
imagining it is it just this one
boat watch out for Turtle ships Turtle
ships about is there even more advancing
no okay let's get my people to work um h
if only I had more gold is there
anything
here no what are you guys doing stop
that that's that's just
useless where we don't want to do that
okay run away run away run
away and let me get uh one more Monk and
this monk will like be here do I
automatically
heal
oh we're down to 11 tonic Knights what
[Music]
happened okay it's
fine be healed
I didn't heal them
on
okay what what do you guys think what to
do about the gold do should should I
just like rely on trading cuz there's
literally no gold resource and I just
like try my best doing like good with
everything
else yeah more trading cards
what's
coinage I don't understand
that Guild
trading put the market further
away
[Music]
oh a
market further
[Music]
away all
right gold St the map but like here
there's enemies I I could like see if
they still have gold but I'm guessing
no I it's fine though or he's also
asking for gold I will not be giving you
any gold hey
heyy okay you win some you lose some
it's fine can the monk heal
himself should we research something
convert most enemy buildings in all
Siege units
convert enemy
monks monk speed that was something I
wanted monk hit points
yeah monk regeneration speed all right
let me have it
all
[Music]
hey I I know what to do
yeah
building some watchtowers I think or
Another Castle like closer to them I
could build a castle here maybe I
will I'll go
here hey I think I'll do that wait build
a
wall first a wall and then
okay m
build stone
wall
[Applause]
here oh can I not help building the
wall oops
ah oh no not the
Koreans
ah uh uh uh uh wait wait oh my my God I
just noticed
yeah Ah that's just my groups that are
being depleted but I still am building
okay oh wait okay they're fine against
like normal Warriors thank God it was
just the G that really couldn't do
anything you hide a little bit and
then s they're coming
can you maybe help me I don't know would
be nice A little bit of being rushed
little bit of help I would appreciate
that might not need
it ah he's going to
die the ram is
coming
theator oh
[Music]
so uh purple and uh the Koreans are
working together right
uhoh
it I make them of
these oh
[Applause]
oh okay can you build this like
now is it time yet no yeah they keep
they keep on sending
purples okay now actually stay here cuz
otherwise you'll be
stuck or okay no no no no Richard stay
here stay here stay here it's fine bait
them
okay okay okay okay
okay no problem
um oh they just okay I I know I could
change their stance
but yeah okay maybe we can kill them
before
the wall is build there we go there we
go all right all
right press a before moving with an army
it will automatically attack all enemies
in path okay bring ships near shore
oh oh I could put another dock here
TBH good idea though okay they're being
healed let's put them in a
group and okay wall is built that means
we're really safe
now
um building another
Castle when under attack how Y is
it
where over
here she'll be fine
right I'm number
one I'm number
one oh they're done with the forest
[Music]
sheesh
Gap and wall there's a gap
here what why I hate building walls like
this in AOE like it's so hard to
see oh this one this one
piece okay guys you have you have an eye
for that
huh
nice m
oh my God my
gold uh oh wait I was also going to send
someone right uh again to waya I
guess
oh yeah okay
um
what else is there to build you have a
lot of space for more units I
know
okay I think you guys uh make a
uh another l Camp here and start working
everybody you guys start working on this
one wait did I choose the ships
too no okay now we're
fine
hey okay are we going for Wonder Victory
or what maybe I should
how many years how do I say it where's
the year number number of
years let me build a
Wonder ah now I'm out of gold ah
wait can we get to 1,000
gold
uh should I do an upgrade does this like
give me more gold when I sell something
I don't know more trade
cards
I have 5,000
food I don't know how I got so much
food should I have upgraded it
first I don't
understand gold please m now I'm I I
need my goal to make a Wonder my
friend I'm winning because this game
seems kind of weird like I don't know
why there's no not much fighting going
on they're scared maybe like honestly
why has nobody resigned
yet set of oh fishing
boat
mhm
I wonder if it takes like much longer to
build this than other things what is
this sound what was that ah me me
starting building a Wonder oo oh that
that's probably going to take a while
huh so I'm going to get a lot of people
to work on
it and then I have to keep it alive for
another 200 years or 200 years since the
start of the
game o wow
oh I can't I can't have any more people
working
there wait did I just send the cards to
are they they're going where they need
to go right oh no ah yeah it was a
mistake carts you
go
here
right now I can still add so many
people
let's research
that now my resources are looking kind
of rough
but I'm not even like stressed out right
now I have like so much in Japanese yyu
YY so much like
leeway in terms of like I have so many
hands fore basically I can I can do so
much
more
it takes a lot of time otherwise okay I
need a lot more people actually no it's
progressing well I might actually do
this I wonder if anybody oh wait no I
can see if they're trying to build a uh
a wonder I just noticed because uh that
looks like that's what it's telling me
on the bottom right the Wonder icon
nobody else is trying to do this
really okay all my Manpower goes to that
now almost at least a Manpower who isn't
been used right now d
B they know and could attack so they
won't lose oh so me building that they
they're worried that maybe and will be
more happy to attack me that's fine try
me try
me I got ships I got everything I got
threee cast four four I got four castles
Mama Mia a try
me I'm going to wonder
when
oh he so actually I would like to know I
didn't see an answer cuz sorry I'm like
I ask questions and I I don't catch the
answer the 200 years is it from like
when I started building it or start when
after it's finished 200 years or since
the beginning of game uh the time the
game 200 after okay and then where do I
see the
years
maybe don't
[Music]
know
IRL upper right
corner
uh uper right
corner and ah does it just not show it
yet ah after it's
done around 20
minutes I'm sorry I'm
excited and look at my food and my my
wood still being really up
high
thank God there's so much wood because
like the other materials are really
scars oh waya is attacking uh
green is she doing well yeah she's she's
doing it okay not wait wa wait I want to
what the is waya doing is she
trying to protect me by building like a
sieg or something
there
that's so sweet that's so
romantic that's so cute oh my God what
the I love this AI I think I want
to marry this
AI I'm kind of
touched not going to
lie e
do you hear the sound it sounds like
it's raining or like not raining but
what do you call it a really strong
hailing it's
hailing let's build
[Music]
some let's make some
units
sheesh sheesh sound the sound is
freaking me
out what is this maybe it's a castle
actually I don't know there a castle
she's building a castle next to
me oh my God I'm going to cry I'm going
to help you can I oh I can't help
them oh my God
I love her do you need some materials I
mean I don't really have gold right now
oh almost
done
building three or two oh
one three oh two
oh oh year one 299 it's oh oh it's going
down fast 298 297 okay okay all of you
um since you're already down here let's
build a lumber Camp make yourself
useful so many I I made so many extra
villagers just for
this yeah um hm what now what what can
this W do nothing okay oh I should I
should build more things to protect the
Wonder maybe a actually a
wall
right
yeah
hey oh
yeah it's hard to see I can't change can
I could you change the
uh the the the the the
view I
forgot
no not an AOE
to okay I don't know U I just got to
connect this should I make a gate too
because there's a castle she might want
to get
out
hey oh my God I'm like so
winning I was scared cuz like waya
wasn't her AI wasn't doing so well in
the
beginning see I'm not good at battle but
I'm good at like winning by
defense I'm proud of
myself okay all of you seem to be done
so wait a gate a
gate uh like
this don't get stuck
inside said every casual RTS player ever
peaceful victory yeah I literally
peaceful Victory cuz I just win by
having the uh wait how many years was it
cuz I'm already down to
249 I accidentally resigned by mistake
no wonder they win Victorious I sh
abdicate green is gone nice job way for
putting like pressure on
them now let's close it up not that
anyone is trying to attack my
Wonder real players won't give you the
luxury yeah but you know I probably
won't use the strategy in reality will I
is there a Gap now I don't think
so let's see where they will exit they
go through the gate okay so there's no
Gap okay my job here is done let's get
some more
wood deforestation just Spam tonic
Knights not enough gold okay uh I could
trade um oh my
God what what are tributes why would I
research banking does that help
me guess I could research
this
research
guilds the great wonder the great wonder
that I
built they would all turn on
you if you coordinate with with Rea yeah
who knows if if Wayne is really this
aggressive when she plays um the game we
would be a great
team it's been so peaceful like nobody
is asking for help no I'm not being
attacked at
all what's what's purple
doing they're still so
small or is it just because that's the
last time I saw
them maybe I could help her like I got
nothing else to do I just have
my I just have my my w to protect and
yeah
easy
yeah I should build but why why would I
build that when it doesn't look like I'm
ever going to
battle but
okaye oh There She Goes e e yeah have a
thousand you can have all you want my
queen the grade isn't connected to the
right wall eh well it's fine they're
probably never going to attack
me you should practice building armies
fast in a peaceful situation
yeah maybe tomorrow I'll crumble in
stress
H well you know what I don't know I want
to go attack but I didn't even I didn't
build a
gate am I helping where are my shippies
oh there they are oh rain retreated or
what isn't this the Town
Center oh
yeah I attack
them
uh-oh oh that seems
manageable
yeah yeah yeah
yeah are green they any oh oh they're
gone oh then let's follow
waa or wa where you going to go
yellow
okay sorry boat sorry
fisherman oh yeah that that was the
resigned player
I could kill the the the this Trading
Card yeah nice aim nice aim no more
trading for
you
hey oh there's a relic
here what can I I should bring a
monk how's it going here everything okay
yeah okay I should bring a
monk and just take the Relic since I
have nothing to do
Rob the Caravan what
Caravan a lot of gold
[Music]
M let me just take down this just one
dog or the
[Music]
church oh I saw their ships they're not
going to trying to protect anything here
oh there there we
go I am not now being
attacked
easy
oh what do you want what do you
want you want a
mangle you want a tingle Wood please
that's so
Random
okay my ships might go down
here you little
come on there we go all right then
the rest I'll just leave to whatever my
ships want to do because I want to
make the the transport ship and I'm
gonna put a monk in there and maybe some
villagers right
yeah is there some villagers
here and they're going to get into the
boat yellow resigned oh I didn't even
see also I only have 123 years
left nice is this
gallion gallion transfer ship wait wait
where are you going so they
enter let's get some people in
there maybe maybe actually some people
to fight in case I wonder if there's
anyone else where they are they oh no no
it's just resources
okay
okay let's go soon soon soon soon soon
soon okay ship is leaving Cho ch ch ch
ch ch ch ch ch what's happening what's
happening with the player nothing right
I don't
care it's fine I guess red is attacking
purple or what's going on hey no no no
no no no no no no leave me alone leave
me alone leave me alone okay I'm fine
I'm fine do dock do
dock who's attacking
me okay how do I let the people out
here all
right take it take it hey
Sir W what is
that there's some your bu animals good
that I brought some some Fighters I
guess what are those what are those
alligators or oh they're
weak can I get meat from
them okay how about go get some gold
let's
go mining camp
here all right maybe I should bring more
people they're going to they're going to
protect them ship is going to go
back what's happening are we good we're
good we're good we're good we're
good okay how do I get these people over
here
easier
gold have you heard of my recent
scalation AO dragons ah might as well
build a I was thinking so too
y maybe maybe do you think this really
going to be that much longer 67 years
left I want my Wonder to
win I want my Wonder to
win
here okay let's
go see that I I even fought so far to
bring them some
protectors take wood cutters on boat oh
I got 12,000
wood uh wow wait then let me sell and
give him gold like he wanted
to gold was it gold he wanted oh wait I
don't actually it's hard to get gold
there you go you're
welcome I bought Stone yeah I wanted to
buy Stone cuz I I saw I have barely
Stone any stone there's only gold
here I brought some more workers yay new
land yeah wait oh ah that's the that's
the monk I
forgot
where's the where's the villagers that I
brought here okay
okay monk I forgot about him go go
go go go go go
go uh where's the church
here uh quick quick quick quick quick
quick plundering the treasure I forgot
about it is there more I think only one
right only one Relic is that the only
Relic on the map I like this map it's
kind of cool
damn that was that was a smart decision
I'm like so smart what's going on here
hey I protect the Winer go
go is this my ships too a she's
protecting herself
oh okay unload your one passenger that
an expensive
Uber hey okay
drop off the
Relic ah
[Music]
no just right click on the church
right wow stretch
POG he's doing it he's doing it look at
him ta so what did that do uh you guys
said it just gives passive gold I still
don't really understand that doesn't
give me like lots of gold at
once Wood please wood please hey you
came to the right
person one extra gold per second ah okay
okay
okay man this going so
well should I try fighting just for
practice but no I
need maybe cuz like I didn't build a
gate purple didn't resign yet
right okay I don't have enough a free
years free years until I win two one I'm
going to win one
yeah
yay
that was
fun that was
fun
oh oh look at my economy holy
waa and my Society my total score
was almost as much as
theirs they were going to Red was going
to be number one if oh they are I guess
but I help them a lot so
I won by just sitting there yes the best
way peaceful just like a it's very
Austria you know we're
neutral neutral country oo food
collected wood collected Stone collected
oh tribute sent
5,500 and I received
nothing
whoa they did a little bit of trading
here h gold they got a lot of gold here
at the end I was like I should have done
that a bit earlier I should have noticed
that there's an island to take with lots
of gold then I could have got number one
in gold
too and I was a bit late on making more
trades like more more Trade Centers and
more uh trading cards so I'll remember
that I was not too late like okay
compared to the other maybe but like at
least this time I got to imper it was
just generally really chill anyway total
wonders
oh the the Greeks also had four
castles they're Greeks right the name s
looks so Greek to
me oh Relic gold 45 I got it pretty late
wait they had
relics
it this all comes from relics
right oh where did they get those from I
didn't see any more relics I guess I was
too late to see them villager High
sheesh she oh I had a I had a ton
of villagers compared to the
others basically Greek
M later on
Greek whoa a total seven relics you have
to scout at the start I was scouting but
I didn't see any
relics timeline oh
W look at
this
W you it
SC w a blue
[Music]
ocean I
dominated previously was a pretty
aggressive one this was a more chill one
so I feel like I I I I'm like mentally
somewhat prepared for both mostly for a
chill
[Laughter]
one yeah if if tomorrow is like they're
not too aggressive then I'll try the the
Wonder
thing but it really depends it's
probably not possible I guess they're
going to be aggressive
probably
yeah units killed 215 units lost 68 oh I
got ah again I lost the least units well
well well I wasn't really fighting most
of the time buildings raised buildings
lost zero units converted zero largest
army oh largest army and I didn't use
it
wow
uh wait I we won as a team but they're
they're the most valuable player but I
won because of my
Wonder guess we're going to win we going
to win
anyway early defense H if you County
units you can win try to come up with a
strat with way beforeand yeah maybe
yeah Wonder Victory usually disabled
well I mean it's not a really serious
tournament
so human players use much more devious
com compared to yeah that's fine I'm
probably not going to win in the
tournament because Muna is apparently
extremely strong but it's okay as long
as I kind of know what I'm
doing I'm going
to I'm actually going to uh have to end
it now because I have to sleep um the
tournament for me is
in
11 11 hours but I got to get up a bit
before that to be like preparing with
the
others and and I still got to cook and
sleep in between that mhm
mhm I think I can read I think I have
time to read super chats
still so if you have time I strongly
recommend oh The Art of War
tutorial oh yeah I guess I should do
that okay okay you can build unit just
food and wood but cheap ones you should
build those two just not gold
ones we're ready tomorrow for collab
stream yay I watched a vot for the
tourament okay yeah sorry it's like a
bad time but I I got thankfully I got
them to change it from 4:00 a.m. to 700
a.m. you can leave it for ff6 streams I
guess so yeah then I'll play right after
the stream I'll play the tutorial then
I'll cook then I'll hopefully sleep and
wake up at 6:30 or so love your AE two
friends thank you I had a lot I have to
say I had so much more fun playing
skirmishes over playing um campaigns so
maybe I'll play more
often campaigns just stress the out
of
[Music]
me yeah that's unusual really that's the
way it's supposed to be played yeah
screamish right no yeah but campaigns
are fun because of the story I do want
to play more campaigns if they weren't
so
difficult yeah they have scenarios to
limit me too
mhm okay so guys uh tomorrow or like
today depending on your time zone here
I'll show
you oh I wonder if everybody will be
streaming I I was planning on
streaming
on
[Music]
MAA made thumbnail stylish wow cool I'm
with way what's croni looks so smug and
MAA looks like she's going to attack me
oh FAA also looks angry why do we look
we look the most friendly don't
we
y y
cute so we're like the red team cuz the
others have like other
colors oh yeah way is pum is
blue I'm excited I'm excited now I was
really like nervous about participating
in this I almost wanted to resign but if
I'm not going to take part in in an AOE
uh two tournament in whole life who else
is going to take part right like I even
streamed it a few times previously so I
gota
participate you did good you ready thank
you yeah I wonder I really want
wonder how much crony and fun practice
did did they mention anything for
anybody who's watching their streams did
they say anything at
all barely anyone in Ian plays RTS it's
the German blood in me I mean it's
Austrian but you know pretty much the
same thing
haven't heard D they practice only
practice today okay okay okay okay
okay F said she would do some practice
that means that you know the practice
was really
[Music]
recent I'm the only RTS gamer in Ian
kind of yeah seems like it I'm I'm
interested about Civ civilization cuz
you guys said that might be easier for
me I want to try it out didn't it didn't
fauna play CF
once like somebody played
c f is pretty try hard she might be
scary yeah yeah M did um ah that was M
yeah s this
n oh okay but now I feel like honestly
I'm I'm feeling much better about AOE
[Music]
now Lena should brought her default to
match how's that matching how's her
default
matching I'm going to maybe try to get
waya into live Tod room when we stream
so that it's at least within our team we
have us moving instead of
[Music]
pngs oh oh Fair Super Chat thank you I
literally don't understand Indonesian
but thank you
I can place Austria and build a vies
coffee house what
what
n Co practice before the
[Music]
um I don't know if we have time for
that nice way to sell it so
true SI six PS oh yeah that's a lot of
different CS too right like which one is
the one to
play which one is the
best Austria has some cool culture stuff
damn I didn't know they had Austria the
let's
go 5 six 66 five okay it's between five
and six
huh Yellow Ostrich gamer is ready yay I
am I mean I don't want to get too
confident now but I really enjoyed the
practice I hope it won't go too
bad m
whatever Even If I Lose I'm I'm going to
I think have decent
[Music]
fun I got to check with waya I'm going
to I'm going to tell her
yo yo we're a team NAU I practiced on
stream and I
am uh better at being
support role I noticed I don't know
about
you but I
could help a lot with resources and
being
defensive but otherwise we
could make a
strat together that works for us
let me know if there's a way you want to
do it I will be
wake half an hour the latest before the
stream but I will try to be awake
earlier
maybe yeah just just say Wood please if
you need anything just say Wood please
I'll give you all the
wood will we have receiver R yeah I
think so of course of course map will be
random I don't know that's also a good
question bisen tie's best defensive s
well but now I practiced with Tuton and
I I like not being worried about being
converted and they speak German so you
know
yeah
after doing a bit of cooking some
checked out any ProBuild orders for
a no I don't think so there's Spirit of
the law for ao2
analysis I don't know if I have enough
time to like do any research like that
still ah resistant not
immune is that what that what it
was um
uh okay well you guys can send me some
videos that you would want me to watch
uh on Twitter and then maybe like to
fall asleep I'll watch
those
not okay all right I'm excited make sure
to come to my stream to watch my POV and
stream POV my album he
[Music]
yeah and then 7:00 a.m. we do
that so I'll see you there it's
in 10 and a half hours I think if I
calculate
correctly g g actually good for uh Na
viewers I
think
okay 7 a.m. for
me so you're Europeans are I'm
sorry but at least not as as 4:00
a.m. I saved
us 1:00 a.m. for ESD oh well I mean
every once in a while you can stay up
late for me
right I did not calculate correctly
oops oh well okay in German we sellas in
and I'll see you later
G what
see you later I'll go eat I'll go sleep
this and that and watch some videos and
this and
that you last stream for a month I'm
going to the middle of nowhere after
that maybe I will no how can you say
that why would you no longer be a kfp
say to no what the no what the
hey you can't say that to me
without a
reason we just gone for a month when you
come back you should come back to kfp
thanks for the
pinky yeah don't go makes me
sad like the fit thank you
what's what a
bombshell bombshell
bombshell no one leaves kfp y
please
tempor now that's not a good way to
finish a stream promise you don't just
leave me like
that you're not
allowed I understand maybe within that
month that's okay but when you come back
you come back you'll come back you can't
leave no no no no no no it's not
actually possible you
can't
okay
guys
sh
byebye I
resign you can have my land you can have
my castles for
now
[Music]
oops
space
[Music]
water come back
there
[Music]