laughs
[Music]
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]
go go
[Applause]
wow
welcome everyone for the first ever full
whole life English collaboration
well I hear a lot of motivated crewmates
only crewmates of course in here
[Music]
of course talk about that
um
we're gonna talk about it especially
about you follow it doesn't matter if
you hide behind that little but you
still do a little sprouts
you guys
I see a green root are you an um
I just want to mention what happened
before the stream we had a little
testing session and uh we just wanted to
play the game seriously for once and
then uh after a little while we had no
reports which was kind of suss sophana
doing an emergency meeting and just to
you know because she was obviously
scared and which I was too
um she reported okay she did an
emergency meeting and then what what do
we see free deaths
of course she's not us because she made
the meeting but turns out she was the
Imposter how Reckless is that not to
mention she killed so many people so
easily it's a little scary
was so short yeah
oh no are you serious
[Music]
one minute late doesn't count
you're right
it never has counted
like seven minutes later
it's fun we're all here though somewhere
right
yeah all right then um so I would like
to get some introductions from everyone
and everybody stream up yet
are you ready
yes yes okay I have a stream going okay
okay I hear you guys all around me
loud
because that's self-introduction can you
all got girls give me a reason why you
are not sus today starting from Amelia
girl oh why I'm not such today um
[Music]
I'm not wearing pants
were you wearing pants I was wearing
pants that'd be more more worried you
know I knew it
oh okay definitely knocks us so next up
Bae your introduction please and why are
you not saying
representing chaos everybody how you
doing wait can you stop vlogging because
we have to follow in order to hear you
proximity
baby
sorry okay I'm not sucks because
um I got a cute pet look at my pet oh
yeah
you
bought it real money real money on a mo
ghost real human dollars
I saw the hamster thing and I was like I
gotta I bet
are you is that your child are you a
hamster yeah good question
wait no what huh
um
wow that's kind of kind of weird what
what interesting yeah right
then uh definitely not says Cali here
next all right
um so yeah
um death is real sus but guess what
everyone I'm not deaf I'm the sheriff
around these parts and because I'm the
sheriff the sheriff has never sus the
sheriff obviously didn't do it
um some people may say I I Shot the
Sheriff but I did not shoot the deputy
meaning uh I don't know what that means
it just has something to do with the
sheriff
how can you be the real sheriff and you
can't even spell sheriff fry
but
[Music]
does no my name is fauna and I am simply
a potted plant therefore I cannot kill
two plants I want it that's a poisonous
poison ivy no no no
you've already killed enough people for
today so your deed is done
I remember that musical
um
[Music]
hi my name is because
um
uh uh I don't believe in it simply story
I don't believe in sauce
all right
all right okay
Iris it's Iris I love English project
cup the YouTuber slash resinger uh I am
very excited I am 100 say so I would
never lie which is why I would never
reset the Minecraft story
explains everything I would never I
would never do anything don't trust her
she's a pain killer
Iris yeah no trust Iris Iris that's not
what happened to my fox yesterday
[Music]
very very
um Good self-introduction by a lot of
people mostly just say hey my name is
this
[Music]
[Applause]
please give us your introduction
oh yes hello my name is crony Oro from
the council and I am blue
um
I asked nicely okay
where's the blue okay don't look at the
color objectively look at the color
that's inside all of us
um
red and fleshy stuff
good as outfit she's right baby she's
right
[Music]
because look at this I'm wearing a mask
I am doing my uh part in this situation
don't get close to me
well I tried to social distance but uh
I'm not science because I'm doing my
part in the society and it's pretty
funny I'm an upholding
oops
hold on guys give us a second we're
gonna go to the I mean we know he's
coming anyway give us two seconds sorry
guys we're gonna go to the BRB screen
we'll be back in 30 seconds hold on
sit tight
bye
[Music]
umster
is always on time
[Music]
they scared me action and why you're not
says
Mommy
that was my turn yeah yeah okay okay
okay okay I am moving the national
actually I am the guardian of
civilization and I am an apex predator
of the sky and I could kill you if I
wanted to
okay
interesting how to defend yourself that
is that that is the most nonsense
introduction ever yes
but I don't want to so I won't
so peace full
of those buried bushes sweetie I take it
back I take it back um I I might not no
taxi back seats
hello I am you know my illness from Paul
love English
um
the uh Priestess of the ancient ones I
think you think
I think yeah sometimes I forget but um
oh I am not soft because I'm already
dead look at the the Halo above my head
oh
[Music]
that chorus of O's was wonderful
that makes a lot of sense all right then
thank you enough so stay there next up
Santa is not streaming but she's here so
please let us know who you are
okay
um hi hi I'm Sana sukuma from party life
English Council uh it's been a while
hello guys
hi welcome back
I have a big limiter on my head yeah
if anybody thinks I'm Swiss I'm going to
take it off and take all of you down
with me oh that's threatening
back into back into the space where you
belong right
you should be fine you should be fine if
you get kicked out I have no I have no
reason to
oh um well I'm very happy to have you
here thank you for participating we're
really glad to have you as part of this
even if you're not streaming free yay
we'll be back soon so we can all look
forward to her streams again
yes we do
our last but not least is
live English and uh I am the one
organizing this and I'm really happy
that we could all get together 11 people
is a lot but we're gonna have a lot of
fun today so let's get right into it are
you girls ready to be
[Music]
oh boy
I don't want to be impossible first time
oh dear what's this
this man
I think it's we just have a lot of more
stuff to by the way does everybody know
we're using proximity chat uh we are
using proximity chat uh and I think what
that means is
what is it ghosts are gonna uh we can
hear each other when we're alive but
when we're
dead ghosts can hear each other dead can
hear each other and then whoever killed
us can hear us as well so we can haunt
uh whoever's killed us
um
I don't know we played one round
I was just explaining to them uh what
proximity chat was in case I didn't know
that's it that's literally it
oh okay I was like uh oh I'm putting
files away
oh wait you have to do this every time
wait what why is there a ninja star but
I recognize this game from Iris
I recognize this from uh
uh what
what is what is the other game called
hello
this is from Mom
ah
hello
babe all right all right that was uh
um
wow
wow oh my God
absolutely ballsy coming out the first
ring with the lights on with multiple
people around what was that about wow
who came out
it looked like either Iris or Bae they
were before
a girl
it was right in front of my face
no wait hold on I am black screened
again
no not again wait wait we just got
started should we do a new Lobby yeah I
don't know if it's gonna be any better
though
I'll try fixing it but maybe I don't
know maybe reinstall among us or
something like that because you had that
before
yeah we can restart
books
it was it was it was Iris it was Iris
Iris was right in front of me
babe you're what I thought we were Kiara
where did you spawn
where where I spawned yeah I think in
the middle thingy there a record okay uh
where did you spawn I spawned in the in
the I was by myself it was the room with
the folder on the table
did you spawn
uh where did I spot let me look at the
map real quick she's being a detective
um I do not not really played this map
um I think somewhere like in the main
hall
okay well me Sana and crony all spawned
in the cargo bay and we were all by
ourselves and we checked the vital
screen down there and Cali and two
people were already yeah they were
already fauna and Cali were already dead
so whoever spawned with them
and they posted at the same time
I was alone I did not wait hold on a
second all right so do we skip both the
line didn't you I have to vote somebody
who's right in front of me all right
we're talking about the beginning right
all right okay I have to do it okay uh I
appreciate it
that's true
they're making the wrong
don't know about this but I'm gonna
steer clear of the Rat
what do we do now wait wait wait wait
wait wait
I'm Maddie okay it respawns you in
different areas all right
God why is this rap so big
records I don't want to go back to
records the showers or we're near the
showers and I know in the showers
the showers you have to Bonk
what's going on
ah don't touch me
ah touch me no no no I don't know how
can I trust you if you're safe
yeah yeah yeah I'm still trying
there okay okay bye
man oh man oh man oh man
um anyway
yeah oh nice I like this game circle
triangle X star I can do that one that's
from the old game uh I'm also not
reading chat I'm just looking over to
chat I'm looking over to you guys out of
habit but I'm not reading chat
um okay
so now
wait what in me
I don't even know where to find anybody
because I know last time I played this
you kill me now I
didn't go down the ladder
a space a space fixed all good oh nice
is it the same to go up the ladder
oh gotcha I'm scared I'm sticking with
Kiara I don't know I'm I'm wondering
right now if we should if we should
close the lobby to let Ina um test it
out again
okay
yeah we just got clothes in here my guy
yeah
[Applause]
oh what
how do you open it I'm too stupid for it
no no
yes you can look I opened it
oh okay
I don't know she was just with us
I'm scared
this map is too big I'm going to the
lounge if I die I'm sorry
okay
how do I open the door chat I gotta do
my my task
oh oh it's okay how do you get in here
do you know how to get in here
how do you open the door
Jesus
is it the space bar
um it's a it's a card sway mission
uh how do you trigger it
uh you have to uh go near the door and
then just click on the you
on the what
and this proximity chat
with me I did it oh nice
uh
uh oh Lounge okay
is this the lunch
yeah this is the lounge training the
dookie butter
oh literally
hey
I'm locked in the latrine
hello
where are you I'm stuck in the bathroom
I'm trying I don't want to look at chat
but I don't know how to get I don't know
how to get out of them clicky oh space
bar never mind I got it hi Anna's dead
so whoever Kiara was with Sana last so
it might be Kiara
um we should go press the button and
have a meeting
why don't you just press it
where is it there's a report button on
your bottom right yeah but you have to
be on the body I didn't find the body
because I was looking at the vital
screen
oh okay I haven't gotten there yet how
do we uh I have not left this area yet I
need to go up
to
so you have to go you gotta get down to
get up
I'm going down okay if I was an imposter
I probably would have killed you already
unless I'm on cooldown
uh
um
I have found this bunny but I have
absolutely no clues because I was
running around a while here and I'm I
met no one close by there was so I guess
someone vented yeah you were saying
we're seeing last with Sana what do you
have to say about that no no no no I was
seeing last for the bay
so who's done with our tasks right now
because I'm done uh I'm not done yet I'm
not I'm lost
yeah
I can say though well it says total test
completed but I think that's something
that an imposter can do like show that
show the delay that it's I think they
can fake then I don't know I've heard an
answer today anyway I think crony can
vouch for me that I'm not obsessed right
crony what do you think
well I I know that Watson and Sana were
definitely safe because the killings
took place when uh all of us were still
around and the only people who are
considered suspicious to me would be
or Kiara
yeah yeah all right Greg's definitely uh
yeah
toilet missions
honesty my guys then we'll just check um
yeah
I'm gonna check uh Bae first and see if
the uh um
um I honestly you know what I think that
says I don't know who to vote for I
don't I'm out the whole way like how
Amelia is trying to control this whole
room makes it says to me no no no no
watch is definitely in the clear because
I was with her uh with Sana well I can't
undo my vote now
what if I'm kind of suspicious what if I
don't vote because I got stuck in the
bathroom for the entirety of the last
round because I know I didn't know how
to open the door I don't know who to
vote for
I
feel like you I was cleaning my guts out
of the toilet I couldn't see anything I
thought it was babe but maybe it's Kiara
yeah
cause I don't know I can't even begin to
make a
workout oh I it's been a while since I
play this oh yeah oh you choose where
you load in yeah yeah oh
Wonder oh okay okay okay okay okay
bye
they shouldn't give you so many tasks
this is just okay uh this way let me go
up no okay this way and we go to the
brig
let me go this way to the brig
now it's this way to the brig
let me go to the left yeah I'm probably
throwing because I don't know oh items
oh shiny
nice okay
I think cleaning the toilet was my
favorite like there's more
listen guys I can't be a good cameraman
because I gotta do these tests because I
download the files I gotta make sure we
have the latest Windows update for our
Mothership
our mommy ship must be okay viewing deck
why is this map so big maybe we should
have done a warm-up game in the not big
map
which day it is anymore oh hello
I need to go to the viewing deck
hey who just did oh
hey don't touch me guy
thanks
I need to okay I did it
oh
connection
or
just touch it I'm doing it
we're waiting for the router to reboot
somewhere that'll take us far far away
I'm pretty sure it's Kiara
well we'll see when they if we see Bay's
body on our way back up wait I was with
her for a little while but she could
have been on cooldown
um is there a cooldown like when you
spawn in I I don't know but uh but a
different match though a different match
I was with her
so I'm going to the showers if I die uh
bye
okay guys to the showers
this is the bunk one
a test
long
okay I'm going up to the meeting room
I'm going
I I uh
okay we go this way
no oh wait I can fix this
uh
I'm sorry guys I gotta figure out how to
get this
okay wait Gap Gap room so we go down to
records and then we got gotta buying a
Larry right
then we go ah no and then we go this way
again and then we go up to the bridge
and then we go
right
now
[Music]
could you guys hear me and I ran around
because I'm done
I watched it all happen we can hear you
oh this is trying to figure out how to
get to the Top If you've been with me I
could
let's make this quick though so that Ina
can come back next time I gotta ask for
an escort
I was checking uh they in the
surveillance camera oh game audio oh
asks she was just walking around I'm
sorry guys
I mean were you doing tasks yes yes what
were you doing what was the last task
you did I have a good one describe it in
detail it was kind of overrated
I don't like them that one that one's
annoying Kiara what's your Kiara what's
your last message
for example was my code and then I would
have had to go to the other side to
input it yeah
that is
um
I think it's between storage and like
developing realm the question question
room
um
I had just seen Kiara like right next to
me uh we were together by The Doors
yeah Kiara was the one who reported the
body too right this is my second body
I'm recording yes
yeah
all right dinners
[Music]
ladies well done oh oh hi oh my God I
haven't heard you guys in a long time
bye doing tasks
it looks like Iris on my screen though
she as I don't know if it's ping or
something I don't know Iris said killing
me [\h__\h]
no but on on my screen because it was
Iris and Bae in the room and it looked
like Iris zoomed over the body okay
thank you so yeah I mean everything
prophecy I was so science
[Music]
new Lobby yeah okay okay okay
BRB
hold up how do we leave the room
um
um leave
[Music]
be like all right so who did it
hi hi
everyone's just like uh you
reverse card
all right which one of you suckers is
the Imposter
um it's probably you Kelly it's probably
you
oh so it's Cali
it's Cali okay is Kelly looking in the
future already yup on the Imposter
Sheriff's got a gun
you're welcome
but I'm pretty small right now Corner
Crow
[Music]
be there
okay I mean apologize
[Laughter]
you won't get revenge or anything right
yeah it was kind of Heartless she pushed
the fox down the hole
[Music]
a wild one wasn't me
it was an adoption and you know it
doesn't matter
because Tina isn't getting in on the
wrong words
[Music]
she made it in last time though
oh okay
she got in last time so
oh
no
I am Royal are there two people in here
okay I'll be right back
foreign
oh my God
[Music]
[Applause]
where are we dropping boys
alone all right
all right we're in the break okay we're
gonna do these tasks lickety-splickety
best uh
oh
oh oh okay
I
Can't Touch This are those hot pants
and a Viking hat is that right
oh you literally have to oh sorry I
wanted the hot pants okay
okay task done I should really find
somebody though I need to find uh an uh
an accomplice I need to find a
a uh okay down left down down
left
down
download
I'm a little scared this is a really big
map I need to find somebody
hello hello
okay goodbye
iris is by herself I need to go uh down
hi
oh
holy [\h__\h] oh I can say about that the
only thing I can say about that is that
I heard Cali's voice close by for a
moment but that was like I didn't even
see her close by I only found the body
like a a few moments later Blair where
did you find the body uh at the very
bottom right it's uh in that bay because
Cali was I was going down to their
bottom oh I was bottom left
[Music]
the bottom area but I wasn't I wasn't
doing anything I was like looking for a
pass to do well why were you not that
cheap I don't think you're done with
task we just got started there's a lot
of tasks I doubt it it's a bit okay to
play The Devil's Advocate it's a really
big map uh I saw her coming up towards
me and I was in the Armory which is on
the bottom left side Cali passed by me
together but Kelly went off pretty
[Music]
oh really you just said that you didn't
you weren't doing any tests now you said
you weren't doing the tasks
what oh god I know how to play the
[\h__\h] game
if you really don't know how to play the
game I will give you a tip now a serious
tip a press tab to open the map so you
can run around while seeing the tasks
and that makes a very easy tap tab
okay I was like I was like looking back
and forth between the map wait what do
you tell us
I don't know though I'm not voting I
have no tab
yeah I'm not sure I'm skipping okay I'm
skipping I didn't see anybody do
anything suspicious
yeah voted I'm not skipped
Iris and zombies
this collaboration again
what
interesting oh that's enough that's
enough to throw me out what
how was that enough oh okay it's not
thank God I was gonna say that's not
fair
uh I have stuff to do here
okay let's finish this test okay so oh
hi
hello friendly we have oh tab tab
oh oh well okay
oh wow all right
wait what are you doing
I'm I'm scared I have to go I don't know
I have to go down to the down here hello
fauna
hi guys I'm going down to the viewing
deck
um I have to do my task keys
don't kill us I'm not going to I'm doing
my
[Music]
it's doing my task each mile
my little Sharky task
oh no it's coming out
okay taking care of
well guys we've done one
I gotta be fast
oh God okay
oh oh you have to like drag it up
oh
[Music]
nice I had to finish all my tests so
that I can ah bye
do I can uh
I'm so scared of everybody
uh oh I'm done here okay I know
hello
Revenge interesting
oh the showers Circle
it's to go hello
can she hear me
I have to plunge the toilet again I kind
of like that one ah
hey hey all right one of you which one
of you just closed the toilet door
I saw that
I was in the the cockpit I was about to
go uh to the very very bottom
to uh who used the toilet
I was not anywhere near that area toilet
because I the bathroom
I tried I wanted to go in to slide the
toilet but it was locked for me
um because when I found iris's body
right as I hit report the door the
bathroom door closed
someone hid in the bathroom stop you can
do that
I can vouch for Sana at least
I was trying to I don't know I'm just
lost every question I was trying to put
the egg on the uh the frying pan
I was tracking her and she was muttering
to herself she's like oh my God
you can kill me
where were you last moment at the last
moment where were you I was also in I
was in the area Below in the bathroom I
was doing the test where you pick
everything up off the floor and gorilla
did see me there but I didn't go um I
came from the other side someone's in
the bathroom
well who happens
here's a better proposition whoever's in
the bathroom wait when we spawn back in
while I see you come out no
no no
all right that's unfortunate at the very
beginning I spawned with uh inner and
folfo I can vouch for
I just remembered yeah just because you
spawn of them you can't vouch with him
I mean I was running around with Sana at
one point lost
okay okay
but are you guys really just not talking
I don't know maybe her mic maybe her mic
sensitivities low because I had no idea
she was talking to me I thought I don't
know
hello
um
[Music]
I am leaving
I am going to away
main hall
um
huh
someone just
oh
wait where is this
I am also lost assistant
hi hello
oh it is here
hi
hello
oh oh this is not the thing hi hi wait
how do you
[Music]
oh they have to okay we go back to that
one I guess
oh I can
um
I'm innocent I'm just lost
here do we do we look at this thing oh
my gosh I cannot wait what happened
I
saw something sauce
oh I was in the top right area that's
like uh before the wreck right yeah
around the records area yeah
um when I was about to enter the records
area I saw Cali so I wanted to say hi so
I followed her and next moment she's she
completely disappeared I went I went
into all other like like
ways to look for her but she disappeared
and there was a vent right where she
disappeared
out of the room man you can vouch for me
I went down to the bottom and tried to
go through the vent and I couldn't hi
partner
stop stop stop let me talk let me talk
let me talk let me stop let me talk let
me speak let me speak okay what I mean
is there was a vent down there and I
couldn't get through it because I'm not
the [\h__\h] imposter that's what I meant
oh man went down at the bottom I was
trying to go to cry
the second time that she says the second
time guys it's the second time
she just wants me to get thrown out
um
could you call this [\h__\h] suspicious
emergency meeting Kiara
imposter tactics
I still have no idea
you're doing a good job I'm gonna skip
fun I'm skipping
here I'm not too sure you don't have to
vote I just want to mention it so I'm
gonna vote
interesting oh
no interesting
I I'm trying so hard to do this test
let me finish this okay now they're done
I know 0.7 about sorry
I don't trust it
is fine I don't trust you
oh you don't trust me I don't trust you
I don't trust anybody
foreign
I just want to do my task okay for the
crying out louds let's get to the
how do I get
oh
I gotta get up
hello I am going oh
yes
oh my God
oh yeah
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
oh there's not any of you
[Music]
here we go
found her in the kitchen
which I normally what the [\h__\h]
I reported the body holy [\h__\h]
you're just you're just being like I
don't know clumsy I think [\h__\h] in the
kitchen I was just wearing my crown
today
and Sana this whole time so like we I
think we can vouch for each other
um we saw at the end right before the
buddy was reported we saw Ina and gurat
together
um yeah Carol's with us too actually
yeah yeah they're fine they're all fine
which kind of leaves um
kidding me maybe she's trying to save
her reputation by reporting the body she
killed
someone and then report them immediately
but we
also
um
right well I don't like you putting the
finger at me babe and I think that's
suspicious so I'm gonna point it right
back at you
boy I'm just trying to be a good [\h__\h]
Sheriff
[Music]
our Sheriff uh are you kidding me
nothing personal it's just I'm loving
this sauce this is beautiful
[Music]
and it isn't now sana's awfully quiet
and so is moonme what are you guys been
doing yeah
when I like literally why would I could
have killed you if you guys were alone
who would vouch for Cali is there anyone
listen uh I haven't seen Callie either
last time I saw her she was standing
idle why are you pointing the finger at
me
you haven't seen me
[Music]
you guys gonna regret this
yeah I don't think it's Cali
I really don't I didn't think it was I
really had something about someone
vouching for them except him it's really
hard but not I don't know
oh geez oh God
excuse me hello hello this is bad
um
you know
let's how do you get there let's all
walk together
is it up let's walk together with two
in-game spaces between each other so we
can see who does what yes that's an
excellent social distancing yes
[Music]
I don't know
all right I'm going for it
up right away
right right if I die
[Music]
someone has to do this
star circle triangle X did it wait
that's not what I was supposed to do no
that's the wrong one
[Music]
is that it
hey nice
I got the butthole I did the wrong thing
hey you know what tasks do you have left
let me
is gone
electrical here I have to go to the
toilet hello
[Music]
here with us
uh
okay I do have a task here nice
I think
um
I might regret this
I'm live regret this
they they
gotta finish these tasks
hi I'm gonna go to electrical oh oh oh
wait
it's her card uh is that it oh wait wait
you got it hey okay
I'm going to oh
electrical
a couple extra
wow
where'd you do it
all this time
she's playing the dummy card
I trusted her
I've been made a fool
this whole entire time
suspicious
[Music]
what do you mean
I trusted you know Ina kept saying that
she was lost and I thought that it was
suspicious I thought it was genuine oh
wait they can't hear me never mind
[Music]
what was the last house that you did the
last one I did was the one where I had a
dress
[Music]
um
oh
my God
all right let's finish this test
let's go boys
not my problem I got my tasks to do
goodbye
oh nice
[Music]
tasks completo
oh
or it was mermaid but it wasn't Canada
[Music]
what I don't know who killed you did you
do your tasks I did
um
I gotta go pick on Inna we're gonna go
find Ina
what's this
it was Kelly
what
wow I actually didn't think it was Cali
Cali was pretty convincing
what you guys you know oh God I'm so
trusting that's so not good oh oh God
you know too Ina got me they both got me
oh no oh no okay
I'm nervous to get imposter because
um
oh my God
that should be probably longer because
there's really long tasks that kind of
can't stand out the oh lion
I love you too but what
oh new room okay okay
I am
hide your imposterness for so long
I waited for my chance I was patient the
world it was so perfect because it was
her first round too so it was believable
that she didn't know where she was
okay
Cali the performance was so genuine you
actually were talking about my
Heartstrings
sometimes
[Music]
Watson was laughing in my ears the whole
time
[Music]
I wish
I wish I guess I'm relieved I'm just a
shark who likes berries and cream where
am I going
I'm a little shark who likes very easy
cream very sweet cream I'm just a
chocolate very sick
what
amalgus
oh
it's so fast
once again
no no no no
Mina we are gathered here excuse me
excuse me hello can I have the floor
please I was just walking out explain
yourself ventricle excuse me taking off
Kiara's head excuse me
I have I have the megaphone I have the
megaphone because I reported it cause
you panicked the question was the shark
near the washroom no question I was in I
uh
go left and then I saw Guru was also in
the room that Kiara went right
that doesn't mean it wasn't enough I
watched enough
for me
no you were by yourself you were by
yourself in electrical because I was
humming bearish and cream oh no I was
humming the berries and cream tune and I
was like I know where electrical is
because that's where I died last time
that's where you killed me last time so
that's right
did I stop by the way by the one I
spawned and I spawned in the place with
the folder on the table and I went right
down to electrical I don't remember how
what passing I took I just stopped by
the washer
how is that sauce
I just walked in and I saw it last time
every time you were in listen you would
do something in the washer
[Laughter]
cloning the washroom hmm wasn't in the
washroom we just spawned in give me some
time to get to the toilet pretty I'm
pretty convinced can I can I have a
moment
[Music]
can I have a moment can I
have a moment please to describe how
Inna has suddenly flip-flopped her story
she's gone from meek and shy to very
suddenly very demanding of the room's
attention I
[Music]
yes please I would love to have a
follower around
I don't know how to defend myself here
guys I'm innocent
I mean it's still early in the game I'll
keep that right now zip at you
I remember I need a makeup Burger so I'm
gonna go to the kitchen
all right we need to find somebody to
vouch for us because I don't know how
else am I supposed to defend myself
I need to find people that are gonna
defend me
um hello I'm looking for a good
um some team members hello Cody
hello Sheriff Callie you gonna kill me
can I ask you honestly
oh I'm not gonna kill you are you gonna
kill me absolutely not you have my word
because I just I just vote you out I
know because I believed you yeah well I
believed you last time so oh thanks but
I would also like a buddy oh but I would
like to not be starting to get obsessive
with the hi cronie no no no no no no no
if you trust me no no no no no no no
well then I'm gonna have you
I really need to do tasks but I cannot
be in your email
finally there's three of us in here so
if none of us were the Imposter we
should all be cool together yeah yeah
unless she's on cooldown
I'm sorry
all right I'll go off and do my thing
then
am I just not
I don't guys I need lessons on how to be
a good liar because I I guess
wait really okay all right that task is
a little
I swear oh bye-bye
how do I get them to trust me because if
I go off on my own that's going to be
suspicious because people are already
suspicious of me
and I ask you guys but I'm not really
supposed to be reading Chad
man I don't know how to be
um
I need to do tasks I think it's because
this map is so oh
okay
this map is so big
okay avert crash course sets up to the
right
[Music]
I crawl is that a lettuce Burger I'm so
confused are you guys safe one of you is
at least six I am not going to kill
either of you
oh yeah sure absolutely absolutely
um
lettuce
[Music]
don't follow her please
you're lucky I'm here kroni
[Music]
go away shark
you really don't want me to do that
[Music]
trust me
okay okay
I don't trust either of you we both know
stop following me all right I'll I'll
buzz off
I'm going this way then okay we're gonna
do
oh God uh electrical let's go do that
stupid Electric
Al task
hello crony hello I'm not I'm doing my
tasks I am just doing my tasks
you know what
I'm just gonna be
honest and open because I don't know oh
no it's it's gross it's Gruff
[Applause]
she's been acting kind of sauce
yeah I kept telling her not to follow me
it's literally Eva no I was trying to I
was trying to keep an eye on you just in
case you know I go for that kill yeah
okay I have a question please
how is it okay that Ina keeps watching
you for protection but it's not okay if
I do that I don't know but when on the
very first round when I reported when I
reported Ina absolutely flipped her
story and went from the super Meek I
don't know where I'm going to suddenly
super loud and abrasive as if she's
trying to protect herself
either of you so okay that's fair but
just
what both y'all are a little suspicious
okay all I ask is that you're suspicious
of both of us and not one versus the
other then is all I can ask went to go
do a task and she ignored me and I yeah
and I'll have to talk just now
I was waiting for my cool down I thought
two imposters still though
but the reason why I've been suspicious
about girl was because I kept bumping
into her every time uh it was just three
of us in total so if one person uh left
it would just be two of us and I kept
having that situation because you were
being left alone with Ina and I don't
want you to be killed and I wanted
somebody to be
my watch
okay we can try going together then
are we skipping
a thing for now there's some reason
put my vote on gura I don't have a
reason so I don't know both the Ina and
Grace please be mindful of Ina
that's all I can say you're being
imposter too
it's possible
all right guys
because she did it right in front of me
all right I won't bother anybody this
time I'll buzz off
just gonna do my tasks now
uh uh let's go up to the brig no let's
go where do we have to go meeting room
let's go up to the meeting room
all right I think maybe I was being too
maybe how do we get here
maybe I was being too
clingy
I think I was being too clingy even
though I mean if I wasn't there
if I wasn't there if I wasn't there then
they would have killed Ina how do you do
this one again
seven
no they would have killed crony if I
wasn't with
if I wasn't with those three then they
would have killed him I mean they're not
gonna believe me anyway so why bother
defending myself because
pop up
all right
okay okay
am I that's scary
I don't know how to play this game very
well
right I have two more tasks I have to do
if you'll excuse me I probably shouldn't
have said that around someone who could
be
okay
hey what's up please don't kill me yeah
no I trust you
the few people who you didn't trust me
you literally I won't kill you you ah
you didn't trust me last time though no
no I trust no no I I trusted you last
round too I trust you yeah uh well I
decided in trust all I mean okay I'm
just gonna go do my tests yeah thank you
I appreciate you listening to me
please don't kill me yeah yeah no don't
worry I got you right
I would appreciate not killing me I
would love a
I would love a
uh
uh okay
unless you and Ian are working together
because why else would you two be
together so much
that's okay uh what else do you need to
do I just need to do two more tasks and
that's about it
it was I was
okay sorry I did not stop report I
I bought it right
I just want to say something crazy that
grows in the clear have been uh
following her around and
yeah oh yeah and I saw her doing the
karting and okay yeah it seems like
she's in the clear so does that mean
that you guys trust me now that it's
enough me so I'm pretty sure she's in
the clear too
yeah Asana is also in the clear we saw
each other and didn't kill each other so
I thought it was okay as well so girl
you really could have killed me that
it's Ina though because I she what I
mean I've ran into so many people excuse
me is your name girl is your name girl
ma'am is your name girl no it's not let
me answer the question thank you the
microphone is in my hand uh because at
the very beginning of the match I was
singing the berries and cream song and I
went into electrical and right then and
there in a beheaded that person
the story's changed get out okay no it
didn't it's your story nice job
detective you can't read your own
handwriting it didn't change I don't
know I'm going to be voting in Ena again
the third round I'll be voting for Ina
I saw me and crony showers yeah yeah
Iris isn't in the clear
if it turns out that it's not Ina
I don't know I still I mean you guys see
cronie following girl
he wasn't with like nearby girl though
oh that's a little suspicious
well suspicious of Watson
well I don't know what to do
something
memories yeah
where'd you find it yeah where the
mannequins are
oh Watson why would you ask there why
would you lie so easily
because you said I changed my story she
said
you said I changed myself
Amelia no no you accused me of lying
when I didn't
I did it
you didn't accuse her of killing you
just said she was more suspicious no I
absolutely is my mic cutting out she I
absolutely did I not accuse
all right I'll be quiet this time
[Music]
Ina and Watson
okay Circle star triangle X I haven't
played this game since the last time we
played it on stream so
um my deceptive skills are not so great
let's look at this
well all right iris is dead
hey that's me
well one went in
hello gamer hello gamer hey hey hey Iris
and Anna just went into a room together
and only Anna came out
I saw it okay we should okay uh is there
a what is to the left of the engine room
oh there she there she is where's Iris
I'm gonna go see that body you just
killed
I watched you oh look at that oh wow
there it is how convenient all right
everyone to do a freaking task hello
everybody
hello I have the microphone I was
watching the security cameras and Ina
and Iris Iris leading in a behind went
into the room to the left of the engine
room and then only Ina came out and then
crony came in and I said hi crony and
then Nina came in and I said oh crony
I'm gonna go see that body that Ina just
left in there and lo and behold there
was the body of Iris
oh well that's a very convincing you
know do you have any defense
no she doesn't live
wow girl I'm sorry I doubted you that's
fine
I feel bad I mean I never I never voted
against you that's true
I thought I was going to um
not last the very first trial but I
turned it around and I think that was
good enough for this round
I lost it this long the other imposter
huh and why is it Amelia Watson no it's
not farewell I haven't killed anybody
I'm a roommate a chance to Kill Me Maybe
I had it I guess I had a chance to kill
me sorry neither of them are safe
watch somebody stay with me next round
you'll see
thank you
finally
okay
howdy Sheriff
oh I'm gonna finish this girl if you're
I gotta go
I gotta go sorry I gotta finish this
task because I'm still now that I've
proven my innocence
finally
okay triangle God I love this one I can
do this one oh hey hey
hey hey hey are you done with your test
no I was so busy trying to prove my
innocence now I have to go speed run
them
all right well I think
oh well why can't you do that hi
stream
the one
wait why couldn't crony do that
oh God Circle X triangle star nice
oh back to the Vault okay I know how to
do that
it's not done
me I'm not done oh my God I'm gonna go
no nope nope you accused me so easily
goodbye nope
out of here
I thought I thought it was you I didn't
vote for you yeah why'd you blatantly
why you said I changed
you said I changed my story when I
didn't what was that about huh
I saw Ina doing the killing but then
this time you said that you did see her
take off the head and that's why I
thought it was suspicious because it's
part of a change in the detail because
that's like a pretty big detail yeah
well on my side I did say that detail so
it must have been the microphone cutting
out because I would not leave out that
detail
okay now I need some space while I dress
this mannequin
no no no no it's fine
how about you go fix that so we don't
die
[Music]
win
party
all right
I'm happy to call it there
honestly that sucked the life out of me
I got this track
oh the ghosts were singing
[Music]
I got this at time limits good job
like a joke
[Music]
unless we would have done all the tasks
so good job
I was really stuck for moving with good
Adele because watching the whole
freaking cold from the first moment
[Music]
[Laughter]
does everyone have imposters here Dead
uh checked because it didn't work the
last round
I I'm I'm more curious about the private
talk events is that working because I've
never like I mean oh yeah
I think so yeah but only the hosts can
change it yeah
[Music]
okay okay okay
idle meeting I need to play some classic
music
[Music]
it's the Symphony of cute girls
we're done we're done singing what
happened she's not back yet
[Music]
I'm ready
[Applause]
advertise
[Music]
[Applause]
I was just about to say I wanted
uh I'm going to the viewing deck
I'm not gonna lie you guys
my girl hi Sonya
man wait viewing tank okay I'm going to
the cockpit I'm doing a ask right now
does it cost right
I don't know if it's my introvert side
but that last round that is the most
I've been
how do you describe it when you
I don't know it kind of drained me
speaking trying to defend yourself I
know it's a gate how do I do this one
I didn't do this one oh
you know like
I don't know I never talk to people like
that oh hi please don't kill me what's
up I'm just talking stuff from the
cockpit nice
what kind of stuff
like three important documents yeah
yeah
there's other people here by the way
right
I have a task here bozo
for some reason didn't light up last
time
yeah I'm literally just trying to find
here I'm doing the task here
probably
[Music]
all right let's stick to the lower the
lower portion let's take a peek at the
cams real quick
okay Kiara's polishing the gym
records yeah hi me hi Mom
and his cams kind of suck just saying
hey what's up
hi hi I don't know I can see myself hi
nope
oh Watson's following me though so I
don't know just don't kill me no I won't
I'll I'll leave you be
bye
yes
hey there's a bed here with two pillows
Watson
one for me and one for Bubba
oh wait there's something here
it's a scary room to get killed in
I love Cali Asana by Sana
hi guys
why are you standing still
hey I just I just saw fauna apparently
apparently it was doing a task but the
bar didn't go up
right and I just saw you standing still
and then the Lights Went Out
is that equal to right
right
I was so mad I was like the moment I
died I was so happy that you saw it but
I was so mad when everyone was like up
against you pissed me off so much hey
it's all right I feel like it's just I
don't know it's just the way it is also
distance distance distance thank you
[Music]
it's all right okay we need to go to
record no first we're going up to the
meeting room
uh and to do that we go this way
up up
Audi
yet
the password is don't tell anybody Chad
Kelly look how Kiara says that and as
soon as you know that there's a report
oh interesting vouch for Cali because
she's been doing tasks alone and I keep
on running into her and I can watch her
uh as a detective a beacon of the law I
cleared Cali and gouda uh from being uh
imposters as I was hoping
um
I did see Watson at the end I was trying
to open the door I couldn't open it
stupid car no the card keys
and fingers I do I did see bae I did uh
I saw they and
I got that but I'm not I saw uh I came
in to the middle of a room I don't
remember and fauna and they were
together
and yes you openly accused fauna
okay
[Applause]
I have nothing to base my conjecture on
yeah
sun is dead
yes
[Music]
he's talking to you right now huh
oh no no oh yeah
[Music]
the case
Watson uh out her own teamwork yeah I
think I'm gonna skip but um
[Music]
foreign
I didn't do my reading room I was just
there
oh
oh this is the worst one this has to be
the worst one crack up
papa papa
[Music]
I just want to do these stupid tests
stupid mobile game Taz just let me push
button push button push button push
button push
push push push push push push button
Albert I know where that is now it's
here and then we're good
in the shower
I gave you a kindly howdy and a winner
on my way
I was trying to get to the whatever it
was sabotage I forgot what it was crash
course or whatever I was in records but
you were in records
I was in records
I was in records and then I went to
crash course
records it might have been the room next
to it the other side does it have the
the table at the folder on it that's the
record room
from what wait I'm not so sure anymore
[Laughter]
[Music]
something and you answered
if you didn't see me but I'm pretty I
thought it was records it's like
describe it
um
I'm pretty sure it was records
no it's not I take my vote back where
are the showers
pretty close to the showers it's pretty
close it's the circle room with the
huh
I don't even know where the showers are
I don't know
I haven't heard a lot from mume or Ina
true
oh I was all like okay I spawned in
kitchen with mumi and then I went to do
my task in the uh the bottom left thing
let's go what it's called Uh so our
suspects are Iris and Kiara got it if 30
seconds
don't vouch for me right
I mean you didn't kill me you said Hi
and then left fair at the top of room
where it's really easy to kill people
but I didn't well Iris got caught in a
blatant lie though I'm sorry we have 10
seconds left so oh what I don't know
um
I wasn't very convinced by Iris I was
not convinced
I don't know guys to be honest with you
Jimmy she could have lost track this map
is big as we've all been saying is
foreign
yes
the lights I will do that after I finish
my little task here we go six three five
eight nine okay
oh
I gotta do my tests
uh Lounge which is also latrine
so yeah this is records which is where I
was
but now I might have a Target on my back
oh like a dartboard baby
I want to play pool
clean the toilet
the ultimate sucky
nope
yeah yes
why are you always at the toilet I like
the toilet one also goodbye
cargo bay I know hey
[Music]
oh thank you Ina why are you thinking
enough why were you thanking Ena nothing
nothing no no no no no
um how were you thinking you know Iris
all right here we go we know who it is
now we know who it is interesting let's
uh I guess we'll see
oh yeah well sounds about right hold on
hold on hold on
wait Kiara is dead
yeah I need to you need to hear me out
right now okay so I was doing my
favorite task the potty task right elbow
deep in the toilet
um and
uh Kiara came in and Ina came in
Kiara is now dead I was the one that
found the iris's body because I left
because Kiara and Ian I said haha I did
the sucky toilet okay guys bye bye
and then I stumbled onto iris's body and
now Kiara is dead
I was with
um I was with Ina and Iris and Kiara and
I left and I saw Cali and then now Kiara
is dead so that will tell you
um uh
I think it's either who are we voting
for uh I think it's Iris and Inna I have
no idea
it was literally me
it was I don't know I'm trying to think
it was me Kiara and Ina and literally
seconds afterwards unless somebody came
in between them
I mean yeah it's I think it's Irish too
oh I haven't voted wait uh
just voted for Ina though guys so if you
I think it's Iris and Inna
yeah it's definitely both of them but we
gotta be strategic about who we vote off
well we could just call it for each of
us and then we could call a report and
then vote somebody off now yeah
I think we have to get to the button
meeting oh boy
skip it
yes what the heck
I think that was the right decision
I don't know
emergency meeting
okay
[Music]
okay we're gonna go the long way
we gotta do a strat Watson
okay I don't know how to get there I
don't know how to get there right
[Music]
she's gonna kill me I better not make
any wrong things
foreign
this is bad not for long
crash course
[Music]
right side okay
[\h__\h]
yeah
I know I saw
say father
your Button Mash is not fast enough
sorry we had to die Watson
Last Words any last words
that was fun I'm sorry I'm sorry Ina I I
totally forgot about proximity chat
that was pretty funny though I got this
thing Irish more like throw wrists
oh man what a game good virus goodbye
[Music]
never mind that's dark
um oh God
yeah well you know what um regardless of
where you fly after this I hope you
learned your lesson
to not to not kill people that's my job
I feel bad I feel bad yeah I feel guilty
um I will I learned my lesson I'll be
I'll be so such a good I'll be a good
girl the rest of this you could be a
good citizen all right all right letting
you off with award this time
I'd be I'd be very grateful if we can I
can stay on the ship a little longer
yeah sure but we're gonna have to tie it
together we're gonna have to put a leash
on you or some kind of collar device put
a leash on me anytime anytime um I'll be
obedient very obedient you seem very
willing that's very that's that's well
what
well how could
help
it's in the name Iris
it's in the name
she goes
I'm not going anywhere I'm not going
anywhere
[Music]
nice that was fun but oh my God if only
I didn't say that we would have been
clear oh my God how come you didn't kill
me when I was going off the ladder did
you not have it I wanted to cut it oh
okay this cord
I don't know oh this card okay hold on
[Music]
Discord audio oh all right sorry guys
yeah we're leaving game audio
um
[Music]
anyway I'm here uh that was some room
tooting cowboy shooting good fun
cheating
that was fun yeah
[Music]
yeah I was really surprised that like
you would assume that you would assume
that the reaper would be like the number
one killer of everyone but I'm actually
just a task master like this I think
I do like the tasks
you were so scared of death I know right
because I'm I don't like yeah exactly
well see that's the thing is death can't
die so in the prospect of death dying
becomes a thing it's quite frightening
oh you're super scary hey
um I think we got a lot of really golden
moments out of this stream I'm looking
forward to all the clips to see the
other point of views
everyone's point of views yeah yeah the
proximity chat here goes yeah
like like this is good but I couldn't
say anything so I was just chilling you
around
or not so no no that's why like I I
thought we were going to do a double
kill too that's how I was like around
and then I killed someone and then I see
you went somewhere else it's like oh no
no the double kill and then I think yeah
because all right
so yeah
I kept my mouth shut we would have won
[Applause]
that's something you want to talk about
what it is but you know at the same time
like you know sometimes I I can't I
can't go and kill my senpas right away
I like that I like that way of life good
good one well okay girls I'm gonna go
for everyone from top to bottom again to
give a good buy one by one and maybe
tell me your favorite moment from today
or your favorite kill or whatever so
let's start with Amelia Watson oh uh
wait what are we doing oh goodbye and
your favorite moment last your favorite
Kill from today okay uh thank you guys
for watching and thank you Kiara for
setting it up again and organizing
everything and my favorite moment uh I
really like messing with Cali that was
fun yeah that was pretty funny I gotta
admit that's pretty cool
no she would just outright say things
like like I'd be like are you gonna kill
me she'd be like yeah you're lucky my
cooldown is off and like run away
that's another one for the archives for
me okay well thank you Amelia makes some
bales
um
thanks for coming guys I hope everyone
had fun thank you care for organizing
again so powerful thank you very much
um
wasn't actually in game
um it was when I went to have an idol
meeting and uh everything wasn't Mayhem
just how I like it what was going on
someone please explain okay
to your idol meeting yeah
even more chaotic when chaos is not
there that's that's the sad thing we're
gonna have to talk Iris very soon
freaking way
I don't need to wait right I mean you
can oh get a room right here because
everybody really got it okay and a room
now let's dial a bag just a little bit
give me your goodbye
me oh let's see my favorite moment has
to be um when I was trying to hold up
the the cell phone to get the cell
service on the deck where anyone could
have killed me and I saw Sana come up
behind me and I was like holy [\h__\h] this
is where I die she was like Hey Callie
and she just walked away and she's like
no I have to do my task here and I was
like okay so we just switched spaces and
we like washed out for each other it was
kind of cool it's a bonding moment I was
like oh I feel safely
yeah oh really I thought that was so
cute yeah being Sana all day today
I'm just excited to explore yeah yeah
yeah it was really fun well thank you
next up
hello thank you everyone for watching
and thank you Kiara for organizing
everything it was a lot of work and I
really appreciate it uh my favorite
moment was not being the Imposter oh
yeah I don't know I think I prefer not
being the Imposter too it's just people
being imposters
being imposter is just so much pressure
you can't really say anything because
[Music]
foreign
I wanted to get into that situation
unfortunately it didn't happen today so
yeah well thank you fun I'm glad you
enjoyed it next up
how salty are you I'm fine I'm fine I
was saying I was talking to my Channel
about like how I don't usually I don't
know have conversations I don't talk
like this usually like accusatory
whether it's in a game or not so it like
it feels very draining uh mentally I
guess
I don't like yelling at my friends even
I mean we all know it's just a game I'm
not salty at all I had a lot of fun uh
my favorite moments were uh and I I'm
asking clippers please uh the various
perfectly cut screams with the proximity
chat Callie specifically the one that
one round where everybody was terrified
of me and every time somebody would walk
by me it would just be blood curdling
screams in and out
foreign
compilation of some sort if there are
enough uh and I also wanna see right
thank you
thank you thank you
it's my honor it's my pleasure my
pleasure I was very terrified yeah
okay yeah thank you so much for
organizing this wonderful collab Kiara I
love among us to bits me too glad I was
able to do this and I I would go for
Among Us like off stream anytime if we
had enough people oh I like it yeah
yeah it was a lot of fun and being
imposter was great pressure but great
and my favorite moments have to be yeah
killing a lot of people that was fun um
well personally for a moment that really
didn't have much to do with me
um I really liked how Cali you know when
she found Fonda's buddies like it was me
boys
oh God I need to be careful with how I
say words sometimes
genuine enthusiasm enough yeah
all the time all the time yeah
a new imposter though because I was
playing safe I was like okay if I get
all the aggro then maybe the other
imposter can go on a killing spree oh
yeah that's right I was doing when I was
imposter two I was like oh you know it's
probably I'm probably gonna have to be
aggressive sometimes yeah I'm feeling
and killing yeah
aggression is the way to go but I was
trying to clear my name and that was how
I got out trying too hard to clear my
name is suspicious man I was yelling in
her ear the whole time
laughing a ghost in my ear
okay next oh
sorry
um
what was I was I gonna say oh yeah thank
you no no no thank you so much for
arranging this
that's fine we don't need it once again
yeah so thank you so much to Chiara uh
for arranging this I really love this
game and it's been fun I think my
favorite moment was
uh well every moment was pretty funny
but whatever the the proximity trying to
explode whenever a meeting happened
and the the first time when the meeting
happened everybody was screaming and I
didn't even know what was going on but
that was funny so thank you for that
I'm glad you had fun drink
hello thank you Kiara for organizing
everything everyone says
[Music]
I'm blushing thank you please continue
uh I think one of my favorite parts that
I experienced was I spawned where Ina
we're with Ina and I turned and I said
wouldn't it be something and you're the
Imposter three times in a row yeah that
really would be she just walked away
laughs
[Laughter]
I was like floating I was like yeah I've
been really funny
it's absolutely drenched in sweat oh my
God
you know there's so much blood on her
hands today yeah I've heard that many in
the last two games
who was your favorite kill Maybe
oh felt the best putting a knife through
their stomach geez
well
um it's gonna be half
um
but I think it's gonna have to go with
the
uh crony in the wasn't the first game or
something where she was like please
don't kill me and I was like okay
you could have just said sure but it
worked as easy
yeah and I wanted to see Peroni as an
impossible
like Cali like The Gambler oh yeah
yeah this would be very scary and
intimidating though because Cali was
every time when I was sussing Callie
like she was like so intimidating to me
I was so scared he was yelling at me oh
I'm sorry
laughs
now it's you no you reverse
okay Santa give us your your goodbye and
your favorite moment please
okay thank you very much for organizing
the collab Kira um I'm really happy to
play a game with you guys again it's
been a while me too it is
[Music]
we're so happy you were here today Sana
and we're waiting
I didn't think about my favorite moment
as uh pretty much every time I heard
Cali scream but now my videos yes
spending time with all of you guys
[Music]
[Laughter]
you see it next time next time you
should uh leave me leave me alive
because I believe everything you guys
say again
[Music]
all right well
um uh for me my favorite moment when I
had so many but I guess the one that
stayed in my head now is
um I think it was in this in the rounds
before the last round where uh everyone
was saying gouda and she was just trying
to speak but then like good I was really
mad and then am I was like well I'm
gonna follow you to see if you're really
innocent and I was like chilling with
Ina as ghosts and we were just talking
about the better curling uh just
standing there together as ghosts and
then Ahmed and gura ran into the room
having a huge fight like discussion
kindergarten fight okay
that was good that was good they were
running in circles yelling at each other
it was so funny
oh man um but yeah uh um it was it was a
I'm really glad this all worked out fine
in the end uh Ina had some travels in
the beginning but I'm sorry I'm sorry
about no no no no no no no no
you came in just in time yeah it worked
out for sure as the organizer I'm just
the happiest dad everyone had fun and
and no holla here and scuff was that
present today
[Music]
thank you for appreciating I'm sure
there's some some Among Us who are a
little bit tired of this Among Us game
but I think with proximity voice chat
mod it made it a whole lot more
interesting and kind of refreshing so
yes I agree with that it was a blast
okay let's do this sometime again in the
future
okay you don't mind hell yeah
yeah yeah
Winter's coming
yeah
how about jackbox
one more thing I kind of want to do is
like because I organized the Ian ID
Mario Kart tournament now that we are 11
ens we could do a full en Mario Kart
tournament as well yeah
[Music]
let's do it
unlock all the parts well it is uh past
5 a.m for me so I hope we can and that
we all got our nice yeah yeah definitely
[Music]
do you want to announce
um I have an announcement for next
weekend that we will be having another
um
yeah
big Halloween collab details are secret
for now but uh yeah now you guys mark it
down
clear your calendars boys and girls and
friends
yeah this one is organized by Honest so
you know it's gonna be amazing
amazing
amazing not even directed as a pun I'm
just really saying it's genuinely gonna
be amazing
amazing
could we sign up with uh no no we're not
only myths
in English
Okay yeah
you ready
three two one
foreign