[Applause]
[Music]
T
[
Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music]
De
[Music] A [Music] [
Applause] [
Music]
DET
[Music]
A
Chaos Chaos
Hello everyone, I
mean, I don't know how many people are there right now,
but I can't tell from the top, but hello to everyone. It's
begun, and
since it's the eve of the Noe Hol Live Sports Day 2023, I'm going to do it today. Thank you very much.
Thank you
[Music]
Since there are so many people,
we are going to enjoy all the vegetables together.We are
also going to have a little practice and play together,
so
please join us.Thank
you.
Hello, I'm going to say hello to everyone one by one.
Isn't that okay? Isn't it
okay today? Is it okay if I bring my dog
? Well, okay, let's move on. There are a lot of people today,
so I'm joining you today.
These are the people who are doing it. If you press the tab key, you can
see who is participating. It's
amazing.
1234 How many people are there?
11123114 or 14+14
means 2087 people.
Amazing
Meni Meni Pimeni  Hello, this is Menipipo.So
today, I'm thinking of playing
with everyone for the first time with that new implementation, playing Holmen,
hunting, and playing around with 27 people.
Okay, let's go ahead and talk to
all of you listeners who are still asleep today. I've
never seen you playing. I'm thinking of
starting with hunting and doing a little bit of nya,
but let's
do it. Well, I guess this is the best.  I'm
sorry for the late completion,
but I feel like it was, but no,
no, okay, see you soon, then here
's the place. Now follow Jamiko-chan.
Today, I'm the teacher. Sui-chan is here. Cat-
chan is here. Stop hitting me and fighting.
Stop and look at everyone and see what this Subaru is
saying. We should all get
along, right?
[Laughs]
This is a Subaruzo. It
's not the Valzo we made. What are you talking about?
That's it.  Well, Susu
said that she
has two nipples, so I can't help it, Mio-san. This is the
most unpleasant way to use Sumaru. I can press it properly. I
can press it properly.
What's going on with Reteru?  I'm
embarrassed to say that I'm being pushed. I'm being pushed. I'm not being pushed. I can
erase it, I can
erase it at any time, but Su-
chan left it there.
What if it affects the system? I can't erase
it.  It was built into the system.
Hey, there was something wrong. What are you doing
? Miko-san, why don't you bring out the button? Alright
, everyone. This time, let's start with the red team, and
let's play with the red team.  Okay, I
think there's probably a good balance of everyone, but I'm too upset about it,
or there's too little yellow, or there's too little red,
so I don't really feel like I've seen it, so I'm
like, Okay, so here's the red hair.  There are
people who play hunting.Yes, it appears.Yes, it
appears.It's not Ako, it's this one.I
forgot to say that, but by the way, I
don't know if anyone has already gotten it, but there
is a book at the morning stand.  Let's
go back to where we were earlier and
get it.Here it is.Yes, everyone,
here it is.Here, please head over there and head towards the school.This is it.I
made a rule book, so I
don't have an en version yet.  I'm sorry,
but please give support to the JP members.Yes,
yes, here.The
Holme Hunting rules are such that each team
will select 6 people.
Okay, so the red team will be the first one, so I
guess I'll just decide on the six Hunters and get them together. Ah, yes,
what about the voice chat? I'm thinking, let's
just divide the voice chat
into red, white, and yellow.  Is it
going to be crowded?Then the red team will stay like this for a
while, and the yellow and white will go to the designated areas.Okay, that's
right.Yes, that's right.Okay, let's stop.How
many people are in the red team now?
1234567 Asoma-san is here.
Wait a minute, there are too many servers right now,
and I'm losing track of where 6 times the servers are. I'm sorry, I
'm moving. Oh,
red, yellow,
and so on.  Thank you for your support.
Please give me red. I will do my best. I will
do my best.
There are exactly 6 people with Ekoe Zeta right now. EMIA
1234567 That's 8 people. In total, there are
8, 8, or 9.  Oh, Hello Men Hunting. Who's going out?
Yes, it's me. Kade is out. Kade and Niseo. Oh, it's
blue and gold. Oh, then
Miko too. Should I join in? Is this it? Yes, Miko too. I wanted to
try it out, so I joined in.
Okay, okay, let's go now. I
might explain that, so just participate. I'm just going to
participate in this way. And
if there's only one more person, Kari, Biji, or Fuwamoko
can participate. What is this? What is this? Kome hunting.
Ah.  I see. There's no one here. Please help me. I
thought of the crab's voice.
Calliope. What should I do? I'm going to go in. I might be able to finish it.
This is the
entry sign. Click on the entry sign. There are three players at first. The
yellow player has already
entered.  Is it
ok to have 3 people? Maybe 3 people each will be fine. I'll
do it once in Toku, so I'll ask you to watch it. Oh, I see.
Oh, I don't think this is the beginning of hunting. That's
right. The
yellow team that can't enter is already
in hunting.  I see you're making an entry.
That's what you mean. Ah, that's what you mean. Hey,
let's go to gold. Yes, please wait a moment. Yes,
this is the first game for yellow. Sorry, I
did yellow, but it's okay. It's
okay. There's no order at all. Yellow should go first.  Sorry, I'm
going to do it from the yellow part,
please.Okay, I think there are 6 entries for the yellow one, so there
are 3 people.  I
just came to ask about Kao.Yes, that yellow one has
entered, so I
guess I'll make it yellow, yellow, red and white.Okay then,
O.Oh, yes, sir.Yes, that's a
fugitive.Everyone will be included in the fugitive category.  So, I'm going to ask you a little bit.
Yes, yellow, please wait for a moment.
Yes, yellow members are here. I'll
be waiting in the audience seats. Yes, then,
all the fugitives from the white group. Yes, this purple one, the
fugitive.
Right
[Music]
Cook, OK, please. So, please wait a moment.
I'm not doing anything. Everyone,
touch me. Sorry, everyone's going to do something.
Sorry, that order is yellow and yellow, then
yellow, red, and white.  Okay, now for the red team,
please touch the signboard of this fugitive.
Yes, thank you very much.
Fushi did it.
And he was one smarter. Was
Kukukuku there? Fugitive
345 Did everyone do it?
[Music] That one
and that one.  I
can do it, I can do it, but I've never done it before.I
can click on fujiti-light with power on.I can
click on this, like this, uh, this, yeah, that's
right.  I was so
excited about Zoro that I remember a little bit about it.I'm confused as to what it means.
Okay, you can run away, right, you can
run away, you can run away, right
? The three people in yellow are running away. The people in the red team are
in danger, so run away, run away. Run away, run away, run away, run
away, you idiot. Run
away, run away. Help me, Edo.  Demon I
don't know who the demon is, but it's definitely the demon.Yellow
team is the demon.Yellow team, ah, yellow.The
demon of the yellow team.It was easy because it was the yellow person.Oh, what's
wrong?I'm sorry for
catching you.I'm
really slow.  I see.
Run away for a moment. Run away. Oh, okay. Let's
go, haha. Let's do our best and play chess. The theme has become white. The
person in the white group. The person in the white group. The person in white. Now the person in white
has become a hunter. Write it at the top.  There's
still a lot of things going on. I can't believe they're still running away. The
white team is running away,
isn't it? I
see, they can't get caught. Yes, they're members of the tete team,
so they're in danger.
Polka.
Senpai. Ah, the polka that was ignored.  Senpai, I ca
n't
catch you, no matter how much you do that, you're going to get in the way.Get in the way, it's definitely a nuisance.Good, good, please catch me.Perhaps, that's
not it, this is it.If you don't
catch it, it'll be the other team's fault.  You ca
n't get in the way because it doesn't get you any points. Ah, that's right. Ah, that's right.
If you interfere, the yellow team will get points,
so you'll have no choice but to
support only the people on your own team. I
see, that's right, the yellow team.  I'm turning into a human.For the
time being, I have to get caught by yellow.This
is the end.Yellow
doesn't contain yellow, so yeah, it's definitely the end.What do you
mean?I'm sorry.What do you
mean?The yellow color is right.  The
title is tentative
[Music]
Yes, it's like this.The venue on the day is
like, for example, how tall are the people,
how old are they, and who made their debut.It's
pretty good.  It's hard, it's hard, it's
hard, it's hard, it
's easy, it's hard, it's a little bit like that, but it's
true that it's delicious, I understood it from the 6 people's 6 people's
DMs.For now, I
'll just summarize the cats.
Okay, so I'm
going to read a little bit. I'm going to read a little bit. The
other beauty, power, and foot are going to go to sleep. Please
go. Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.  Thank you for
your hard work. Yes, please follow that person.
Since this is a tentative title, there are some people who call people from the yellow group and
try to catch people from their own group,
but please don't worry about it.  There are rumors about
people who are taller than 2000
or something like Holomen who debuted in 2000.And then there are
questions about something a little easier, such as people who are all Holomen.I'm
starting to feel like that.Thank you for watching.This
is strong.  Thank you for your hard work, Kamao.I'm
sorry, but that topic is a bit tentative,
so I won't have my own yellow team,
but I can do something about it, but let's
just say, how many centimeters will it be tomorrow?  I'm
sure there's something to be learned,
but
if I catch the wrong person
and touch the signboard,
it's different.  Oh yeah, I'm
not going to go inside when I'm getting off. What if
I can lie and say I'm not like that when I'm being chased?
Yeah, I
can't lie. It's already been
2000 years.  How many years did the debut date remain as that data? I
can't even lie in order to do it,
so maybe the voice chat is not connected anymore
. I
can't compete with it. Good
evening. Well then, it's time to start.
Yes, I think I'll get started.
Yes, please. I made a mistake and clicked on the fugitive,
but this time, it's
okay to be brief.
So you don't have to worry about everything.  Okay,
if that's what you want, just touch the
signboard again with that one click and you'll be able to fix it. You
'll even start saying ``Oh, please!'' Yes,
Okay, I'll catch you from here, I've
got to go.  Let's catch it. Let's
go. Right click.
[Laughs] Let's
catch the red. I wonder if I
can catch it. I'll practice catching it. I'm
sure I'll narrow it down to yellow or white right now.
If I put the wrong person in there, the
hunt will fail.  Hey, I'm
going to fail, I'm going to fail, so I'm
going to fail, so I'm going to get a reduction in that point?  It
doesn't really fit, but click to capture the
person from the white group Click to capture the person from the white group Click to capture the person from the white group The
person from the white and white group knows that Kia-senpai is there, white, white, white, and I
climbed the bumpy stairs.  I'm
here. Did you find the rain?
[Music]
Yes, where is it? Do your best, do your best for 15 seconds. I'm
running away. I'm running away. Where are you? Where
are you?
Cooperate with me, do your best.
[Music]
Go, go, go, go, yellow.
There's a lot of yellow near yellow Yellow, yellow, yellow
It's on top There's a lot on top It's falling It's
definitely falling I'll pick up the falling person It's
falling Wait for it to be yellow Wait for it to be yellow  All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right.  It's
difficult to run away.Next, we're
all infected people, non-infected escapees.They're
also jumping, but
maybe they're just slow.Yeah, they're also
pushing when they run.Yes, push.  Is this the
control? Yes, this is running, right?
Where is this? It's
at the entrance. Try running. It's running right now. It's
running. It's running. It's okay. Oh, are you
okay? Yes, press and hold jump to speed up. Yes, it's okay.
Long press.  What the heck is
that? It's
okay if you don't have it. I learned something by pressing and holding it. I can
do it. Thank you. Next time, I'll
catch them all. It was fun. This is everyone. It's a Fugitive. It's
going to be a board Fugitive. Fugitive
Now that I touch the board, I'm always quick on my feet.I've
become more popular.Push the
ribs.Okay, you've made it to the ribs,
baby.Kihanta is
fun.Here's the one below.What's
going to happen with the topics that haven't been mentioned yet?  I'm
looking forward to it. I
think it's going to be quite difficult to find a home, but I
need some cooperation. Three people can use this person. I'd
like to narrow it down to one person. Yeah,
yeah, that's definitely this person.  Does that
mean we don't decide on something like that?
Yes, we'll start. Yes, we're really fast right now. I'm really fast right now. Apparently, it's
important to hide.
First, it's the red group, so it's dangerous, it's
dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's dangerous, it's
dangerous.  Run away, run away, do your best. You
can hide here.
[Music] It
might be quite difficult to be expensive.
[Music]
[Applause] I'm
talking about my favorite person. Maybe it's white, but I'm sure
it's white. It's white to white.  I
feel like it's not going to happen.The red group is also holding their hands.Can't we
help now?I
want to
help.I want to help,
help, help.Help me, help
me.Help me, yellow.Can I help you?Help me,
help me.I'm helping you.  The number of people in yellow is
increasing, and the good news is that the yellow ones are getting caught.
No, yeah, in the end, the yellow ones were more likely to be
caught.
No, no, I can escape
if I feel like it.Next time, I think it's definitely not possible.I don't
know.I don't understand it, so I
don't understand the question below.This
time, I lost because of the speed of my feet.  But let's win with our brains.Yes,
with our brains, we secured a red-red team.We
had 3 people.But
no, no, no, but we still have this, that, that.We
have brains, we have high claws, and we're hiding.That's right,
that's right, if we dare to get serious now, we'll get found out,
someone.  If it's strong,
I'm sure I didn't catch it.It's
painful, it's painful.I'll
contact Mio-chan for a moment.Okay, okay, let's do
our
best.  I'm sorry,
Mi-chan, right, Mio-chan, I'm in the middle of this game. You can ask me to do it. I
can't do it
right now. That's right. Well, I'm sorry. Let's
look at the instructions now. Popopopo. I'm having trouble with the instructions. Please
take a look.  I
think we should get together, so please come to channel 4.
Ah yes, 4 is here. No, it's number 2.
[Music]
Excuse me. Could you please come to channel 2? Yes,
yes,
please. It's full.
How do I kill him? How do I
kill him? When I told my friends that it was too much, it was very
reassuring to keep them waiting. Everyone, I'm sorry for the inconvenience. Is there any help on the second floor?
Well, this time, the
topic is the same. Even though it's the same one, the actual performance will be
one more time.
Okay, okay, tomorrow the topic will be completely different,
so I'll think about it a little bit, and the three of us will
work together a little to catch one person, so
please try it with teamwork.
Also, look at the current balance,
and
please be aware that there is a possibility that that tall building may be cut down a little.I see,
because it's a big
deal.Mona is in trouble.The antis have disappeared.They have
disappeared.There are no antis.  I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.  You might
want to practice with a partner, right?
Yes, that's true. So, if you have a partner, you're probably already there.
Listeners, it seems like you've already
decided on a partner. Yes, it's already
decided, so each team decides.
Yeah, I'd like you to do that with your partner,
so if you
're a fan, please stand up on that signboard. Yes,
only the person who is a species who is not a fang made a mistake. If you make a mistake, if you make a mistake, just
one click.  It
stinks, so wait a minute.
Please separate it into red, white, and yellow for once. Please move.
[Music]
Please 4 White
4 He's not here.
Hey, he
's not here either. Let's team up. Where is that?
No, wait a minute, the operator who just got off
has not decided who
will be at the top and who will be at the bottom. Of course I'll be the one at the
bottom, but I'm really disappointed, but this is what an aura is.
Thank you very much, Miko-senpai.
Kasua Aristo, just knead it a little. Just
press the button and the start sign will
be fine. Yes, thank you for this part. Thank you,
yes. I'll turn into a Lystim chat. Yes, I'll go back.  Kaka is now the general
. Kaka is the general. This is it. Right now,
there are people below that. Under that
position. Yes, under position. That
F. You should press F5. Press F5.
Then you can see everything.  So please protect me and win.
Yeah, okay, okay, why
do you need someone to push that button? It's okay, I'll
push you, okay, please.
Oh, okay, maybe this is it. Stay close to the general.  I think it's
better to focus on the same person while protecting them. Maybe we
should all move together by holding them. The brain seems to
be good. For example, let's say the
chocolate line and the leader are approaching like this. Let's
do this together.  As
expected, I don't know if that's the right thing to do.The
plan is to pick up one person at a time, stay close to the general, and then run away.Suma-chan, you
can run away alone, or you
can fight together.It's the same.
R
Keo I'm going to give you a quick message.
[Applause]
[Music] I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'll
press Rukore. Please, please. Yes, next time,
can I have you explain to me? It
's an explanation of the rules.  Hey, I can't see it right now,
so please explain it
to me. I'll go then. Yes, this is it. Hmm, how
many times have you defeated the enemy in this few seconds? Excuse me,
Jami-chan, each of those teams.  I
can't look at the rulebook right now, so
could you please give me a quick explanation? Understood.
Yes, I have a spreadsheet posted at each team that summarizes the rules,
so if you could take a look at it, it
's the same content as the rulebook.  Oh, I'll explain.Okay,
okay, I'm
sorry to have kept you waiting.Hey, Red Team.Red Team.No rules.Are you okay?Red Team, now, wait a
minute.I had that translated for you.What
should we do?Wait a minute, what should we do?
It's okay to fight if you're good.  It's okay to file
because O-chan pulled me and I
got the start. I'm going to
kill you. I'm light as a feather. By the
way, it's that Calliope general, so now I'm Mamoru
Leader
Dawaki Kiri One Point O  Bonus
points, so we have to protect the power,
right?We
can focus on the same person while protecting the point general.For example, Toa.Then that
person who came is a little far away and you
can't see her, but her name is Iris.  Then, let's
all hit the Iris
on board. We'll make sure to beat it up. We
'll move around it like this with Style O, and we'll all say let's move. Let's
move like this. We'll get a good, strong OK. Then, as a
group.  I'm a group of people who want
to act, so even if I respond, I
can feel it.It's true that
teamwork, teamwork.
Cool, it's better to do it well
Hey, what about the 5 yellow teams?
Hey, it would be cool if we could use this. I'm sure it would be cool to
do this. I'll definitely kill this. I'll definitely kill this.
Who was there just now?  I'm so far
away I'm so far away I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm so
tired I'm so tired Mememe nice nice jump
jump It
's okay to jump Jump it's
okay Jump jump It's
good to jump
Where is it?  Moko-chan is so protective Mamoru
Mamoru Ah, that's a shame. That's the kill leader. Yes, that's the one that just
came out. It's not Chiara. It's not Chiara.
Watson said
8 kills. That's right. Chiaraa. Aaa has 8
kills. And that one is amazing.  I
don't think it's bad that Ka and Ka's team won, but it
's not bad. I want to beat them up a little bit more. Even if I beat them up
a little more, Senpai got 3 kills. I was disappointed by Senpai who got 3 kills
out of 3 kills.
Because she was good, I'm
sorry to have to look at her now, but I
guess I'll make her the next starter.Okay, okay, I'll
watch it with someone else, but
then I'll gather everyone together.
Come on, the other person can't come in. Ah, he's in.
Okay, then
it's just our team 3, or something like that.
Or maybe that's it. Then maybe that Suma-chan
should come in. I'm sure that's it, or something. It's already in the
mix.  Oh yeah, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Yeah, there's probably one yellow person who's roasted, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but I'm going to team up with raw, and I'm going to support you today, so I'm going to do it, even if the red team comes,
okay? Yes,
please, yes, please.  Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Line: Let's
do it. Let's do it one more time. Soba. We haven't done it well, so we want to do it
again. Let's start. Let's
split up again, please.
That Subaru-
chan, I got it together, and I
got it.It's okay, it's okay, it's floating all the time, it's always on top,
but it's on top, it's on
top, it's good, it's good entry,
and Suba-chan will be on top.Yes,
thank you very much, I understand.I'll
protect it.  Yes, jump
Mamoru-
senpai, I'll do it. Thank you very much. Masu-papa.
Yes,
gore, oh, Kiara. It
was an operation, but Chiara, please kill me
. Please, really, senpai. It's not easy, no, no,
I'm heavy. That's not true, Amiko.  My
senpai was like a feather,
light as a feather, like gold.
Yes, yes, yes,
yes, she was a mess. She was just like my stinky girlfriend. Yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it was terrible. That
's what it means, right? But no, that's not it.  That's
right. That's not the case today. I
came here to get Kali's Nekill Power. I'll
give it to you. Please
be kind. I'll give it to you. Go ahead.
[Music]
Let's go. Let's go. Let's do our best.
Let's disturb everyone's channel.
Let's protect them, everyone.
It's a group of people. It's
a bit
yellow.
[Music] I
might die. I might die. I'm in danger. They're
coming from behind.
They're aiming for me.  Nice, nice, nice,
bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, wrinkles,
enemy team, enemy team, yellow team,
maybe we're being hit, hit,
hit,
yellow is brutal,
low, I don't know what's going on, let's
hold on.
[Applause]
[Music] It's
a little
amazing.  Eh
[Music]
Eka, Wow, you were really strong. It's
great that Wako-chan managed to run away. So nice.
Nice. But the enemy is a bit complicated.
Oh, I'm calling out to you.
Everyone, please gather at number 02.
Everyone, please gather at number 02. Is
that carrier senior going to handle things now
? The
actual event is filled with so many surprises and escapes that it looks like you're in the dark.
[Music]
That's
interesting. I'll see you guys after this. If you
want to practice with different teams, we'll
practice whenever you want. The person on top,
uh, the person in the cavalry role can make that start. So, I'm
sorry to hear that.  That cavalry person
can press the start button, so it's not a big deal. Even if we
were on separate teams practicing after this, I'd still ask him to do it. I
think I've pretty much figured out how to do it. I just
have one question. Okay, so what?  I
didn't really understand how many kills that general would get, or whether there would be any benefits for each kill, but hey, every time that general is
defeated, you get 1 point.
Hey, this is the team points from earlier.
Inside, it doesn't matter, the number of deaths of generals will be
added to the final total, and it will
be the same as the victory points for the battle.It will be added
regardless of the points from earlier in the battle.  That's a
bonus point. I
see. At the end of the scoring, the first place team gets 15 points. The second place team gets 10 points. The third place team gets 5 points.
That's why I understood that power.Also,
even if that kill was made
earlier, it wasn't added to the previous one.I
feel like everyone else in that sense, but I see.For
example, the third place team will have 5 generals and
5 points.  As I was playing the rounds, I was in
3rd place, but it seemed like I would get 10 points.I
see, I see.I see, that's right, that's it.It's so
interesting and interesting.No, this is a bit like it's going to
turn into a rhinoceros, but I can't keep up with it, and the rest of the
time goes by.  Aim for the target, I
thought, ``That's okay,
'' and I thought, ``Oh, yeah, that's right,'' so be careful, General.Okay,
okay, I understand.Okay,
what
do I do next?Isn't it better to check once with the princess?
Are you going to go? I'm going to go there.
[Music] I'm
talking about Masho Ing. I wonder if
Esp is amazing
. There's a lot of bugs.
I've been beaten up.
Gather around. It's hard to go outside. Oh,
then.  This is divided into teams, and I
still have the fire line equipment, but I
have the fire line equipment,
but I don't know what to do, but it's been canceled,
so I thought it was okay, so I just stayed.  Moa,
but I'm
not doing it, so that's
fine. Now, split up into teams.
That Calliope isn't participating in this event,
but what can I do? Just
watch it. I think you can watch it from here.
Where is this? Where is
this?  Even if Fuwa does it with me,
okay, okay, that's actually Shion-chan,
but since she's not here today, I think Shion-chan, Kanete,
Blue, and Door will be fine. Yes, yes, yes, yes. I've
learned a
new recipe. Well, let's take a
look at this one. Maybe I'd like to take a look.  Hey, let's do it. Let's
do it instead of Fu. Hey, yeah, okay. I'm
fine.
There's something I want to check. Yes, I'm sorry. No, it's okay
, please.
Is this game different? Yes, Princess.
Well, even if you're not a princess, you'll
get lag, right? Well, let's
try it today. If it becomes lag, then we'll
think about it. Okay,
okay. I wonder if that's the case at the end.  It's
just that, yeah, I can't help it, that enemy is
coming out a lot, but yesterday was the
only time I've ever been in love
with it.Ah, I was fighting an enemy from the past.It's so
cute.Thank
you so much.  All the cute princesses are so
cute, you should get married
. What should I do? There
will be so many husbands, so who will they be?
Yeah, I guess I can't nominate them either. Sorry, that's
impossible. Why, why, how cute are you? Princess Towa,
Princess Toa. Okay.  Yellow is
okay Yes, it looks naked Princess Okay, let's start. Yes,
yes, yes, it's a little different. There are a lot of things that are different. That's
right. I'm
not sure if it's cool or not. Yes,
let's go, let's go, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your
best.  Yes, red, red, pink, white, yes, red,
yes, pink, dangerous, white,
yes, oh, don't make a sound, don't make a sound, do your best.Wait a
minute, red, red, ah, sorry for tomorrow.Sorry, it's
fine.It's okay, it's
okay.  Don't chill,
sorry,
pink, yes, red, yellow, white, pink, white, pink, red, white,
red, white,
okay, okay, chill, chill, chill, chill, chill, chill, chill, red,
white, pink.  White
pink, red red, white, pink red,
okay, yes, please. This is the knight. Don't talk, please.
Next, please. Yes, it
's paprika. Yes, it's
like paprika orange.
[Music] Oh,
this is dangerous. No, what was that
?
[Music]
Oh, wait, I understand. Wait a minute.  Hey,
this is it,
yes, it's nice, it's nice, it's amazing, it's
grilled mutton and elite pancakes, so I
see. Elite
pancakes, the mutton is refined in the kitchen.
Yes, the elite pancakes are on a chopping board, and I'm
making wheat sweet berries.  I'm going to
make some elite pancakes, so
please make some barley.I made some flour, so I
cut up the sweet berries, and then I put flour and eggs together on a griddle and
bake them.Now I can
cut them into regular pancakes on the serving table.  The
blue one with the sweet berries is so good
. Wait a minute. Isn't the blue one too good?
As expected, I'm good at it. I saw the
pancakes. It looks like a pancake. I was thinking of making it tomorrow, but
this, this, this, this,
this is amazing. This is really cute.  So cute, so nice. Let's
go. There's a page for each of them. It's amazing!
No, I
want you to tell me the top left orange, the bottom
left pink, the top right yellow, and the
bottom right. Orange pink.
Isn't it too early to do it? It's
not too early now. I went from the left, and I started from the left.
Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, keep beating me up, beat
me up, kill me, kill me, kill me,
drive me to where are you at the end?  1 person last,
1 person
Naaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  I'm
just going to the left.
Ah, write something here and there again. I
wonder if you're aiming really hard. You're aiming at the same person you're aiming at. It's cool that you're coming in. Above all, you're right. I can't say that. You might not have come back to life.  Do your best, do your best, it's
okay Ah,
that little one's cooking was too good.
As expected, everyone was strong. No, I do
n't think I could use the arrows that I didn't hit. I can't use the arrows by holding down that long button. It's
no good.  Ah,
hmm, I see. This is the worst case scenario. I guess it's
like having to pinch-hit for someone else. If you kiss the safety, you'll
have to take that into consideration as well. I see, the Red team.
Oh,
poor internet, that's so fluffy.  It's
only once, so it's not bad. I
have about two practice sessions
for Fuwamoko, but the ones that come out are two. Oh yeah, the ones that
come out are individual, the race, and the Kiba line. That's
right, two.  It
might be better to have someone who doesn't have one. Well, it's
not because one sticks out. Yeah, that's true. Then I
guess it's best to ask Fuwamoko-chan. I've been doing Japanese for quite a while now, and I'm sure I'm weak. Please.  I'll do
it. Thank you very much. I'll do my best. I'll do my best. Every team is the same. Yeah, yeah, yes. Yes, I'll do my best. I'll do a lot of work. I'll do it. Thank you very much. Thank you. Thank you.  I was
stubbornly early.
Well, let
's get everyone together. Thank you for your hard work. Thank
you. I'm glad we made it into a sexual gathering team. Go back.
Yes, call the red team. Please come back.
Where is that cat now?
[Music]
She was called Netsuhime because she was always in a good mood.Every princess
thought about that new cooking menu.However, have you
seen Subaru's Subaru's
Karaage and Fried Chicken?I was surprised.  There were
hamburger
steaks, pancakes, etc.
Yes, that's nice. I want to eat that. I
'm
sorry. I was a little surprised. Okay, that's what
I said.  I don't mind having them do something like this for a while,
but the
follow-up is too much for everyone right now.
Someone's wobbly, just ah-chan, that's so
cool, it's so nice.
Let's go, let's go, chocolate, chocolate, what's going
on? It's not there, what's wrong, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
That's what I thought, but it was the wrong person. It was
me. I'm sorry. I
want to do the follow-up practice. I also want to do the relay.
But yeah, I want to practice the relay. The person who wants to practice once.
What should we do? We're divided.  Is that
better? Or should I do a follow-up to everyone?
Well, maybe this is something that can be done with unlimited numbers right now.
Maybe I don't know. Maybe I
should give it a try. There are already red players. Oh,
right now.  If I can't do it now, I
can't do it now. If I can't do it today, there will be three of us. Yes, there will be three of us. Let's go
now. Well, Chiara and Su-chan.
This will be the same for the actual performance. Maybe,
but I'd like everyone to take a look. Yes, I'll do my
best.
Jashin-chan, Chiara, and Biji, are you
going to that other server? Let's talk. I
think it's okay to split up into groups. I
feel like if we cheer, it'll get messy, right? Let's
open up a group
with the members who will be playing that match. 6
Alright, let's move to number 1. I
can't hear everyone's cheers, but I
want to listen to what I want to do while I'm at it.
So,
Chim, each team,
please, I'm scared.
[Music]
Io.  Let's go!
Oh, do your best, do your best, please do your best. The infected
person is banging on the infection sign. Where are you?
This happened. It's true. Awesome. The
Specter touch. Ahh. So many severed heads
flying. Yes, it's true. Awesome. This is blue.
Where are you? I feel the same way
. I'm so high up there.
[Music] Uh, what's that? One
more time, one more time, one more time.
No one fell down, I just fell down.
[Music]
Yeah, did someone push me?  It's not like I
pushed it or something is wrong with me right now. I
don't know yet. Good
luck, good luck. There
's no training. It
's a spa. I
'll do it again. Good luck, Fat. What's going on right now? Well, it's
cool. Look at this entry.
Everyone, please keep this as a sign.
Yes,
O.
[Music] Oh, I'm
about to read it. Do your best.
[Music]
Other people will respond. I want to
eat
hamburger.
It's good. Hanba-senpai is also good. Is it okay? Yes, it's okay.
That's right, yeah, it might be
okay, yeah, yeah, that's good,
okay, okay, do your best, it's okay, it's okay, you're good at it. [Music] It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's steady. I'm
still going to lose,
okay, okay,
okay.  Sensuai-chan is coming, it's close, it's close, it's
lined up, it's nice, it's amazing, beautiful cat went there too.  It
's a good game, it's good, it's
too good to know it's
okay, it's okay, so it
's okay because there is a bed.
Bye-bye, Su-chan, there
's a pet too. It's true that there's a pink bet here. No,
this is just a matter of reaching the goal in the remaining time,
so it's certainly not about speed. So,
oh, okay, wow, it's really, really fast. The
switch is going there. Do your best, do your best.
Even the colors are in your book.The
stage is completed and it's calm
and cute and colorful.Yes, it's colorful here.There
's a big jump here.  Ah, ah, that's nice, that's
nice, that you haven't come back even after a while. Nice,
nice,
heart-pounding
Ropa
[Music]
Yeah, you're good, too
.
Nice. Let's do our best and just power. Thank you, you're such a genius. I gave you a
toy.  There's more than a minute to
go I can go, I can go, I can go, I
can go, but it's nice, it's okay
If I fall here, it's the worst It's okay, it's
okay Checkpoint, it's
okay I can
do it, I can go a little more
[Music]
6 meters left to go
Everyone  I made it to the goal. I
ate a plain hamburger. I
'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. I've done a good job. I've never been so nervous. I'm
nervous, but it's a lie.
So, I'm back. Let's go home.
What should I do?  I don't know what to do. I
wonder if someone wanted to do it
again. I probably haven't done the relay yet. I
practiced, but I haven't done the relay yet. I
feel like I want to do it again.  I
want to
do it again. Yeah, I want to do it.
[Music]
Well, I guess there's one more person left.
Actually, I was able to go around without having to do it. That's
right. My team is Chloe,
so I'm not sure about that, but I'd like to ask the other teams.
Okay,
wait a minute. Then I'll do Zeta.
Zeta is sorry,
but the point is different when you reach that point. Okay, okay. Mio-
chan is on that side. There's
another member of the team who's home.  Yes,
no, I'm not here today. Okay, I'll
ask Yellow as well. Please wait for a moment. Yes, I'll
come in. I'm sorry
. There's still a follow-up person for Yellow over there. Airu.  There's
one more person,
there's no one, there's one, there's one in red, and there's not one in white,
so let's add someone in as a substitute and we'll do it
one more time. Ah, oh, oh, wait. Then I'll enter.  I'm the
second person,
can I ask one more person?
There are some members who would like to try it, but that's
okay. I'd
be happy if you could enter. Alright, let's
do it one more time.
Okay, anyone can try this on someone,
okay? I'll wait for the white group and
go. How do I fly? It's
a little painful,
but this one,
right-click and
hold.
No, that's not right. I was hit a while ago, so I just got hit back because I was dropped twice. I wasn't messing around. That's wrong. I
thought I was going to drop that thing, and then I was like,
Okay, okay then.  That's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine, that's
fine, okay, we
can practice one more time.  But
somehow, Anya, you're trapped in a world of war for a moment,
and even though you're trapped in this world line, you're stuck in this world line.
That's right, Anya, you're supposed to have
entered the country, so I can't help it. It's
true, I can't wait.  I
keep writing that I haven't gotten my game back. It's
true. I'm so scared, Fumoko-
chan, so I just posted a log. I see. I'm
trapped in the world of the Kiba Line. Anya-san is
a little ah-nya-a-nya.
This is another one.  Can't you turn it
around and touch it? I'll try to enter it. It's a trick. [Music] Where is Seramoto now? I wonder if it's okay. I'll go there for a while. Yes, I'll play the tree. I'll try to push it now. How about pooping?
What about the book?  It's still there, but it's been turned into a book, so I
guess I
can't. Yeah, it's okay, it's okay. It's that Ludbock thing, so it's okay. Ah, well, you know, I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go.  Eh,
that's the usual, that's the usual, it's
always been this, stop
it, No, that Subaru also has 41, so I have 41 now.
Okay, let's get along and
come out. I'm going to come with my nipples exposed.
Mikoshine and I'm going
to have a pink poop. Nine is beautiful. Thank you. Good
morning. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. I'm glad I
did it again.
Well then, the white person also entered.
Can I have one more try?
Yes, my life
is over. It looks like I'm safe. I'm falling. I'm being targeted. You're
doing an amazing job. Oh, I'm
angry. I'm throwing a trident with the power of a god.
Oh, I
see. Trident, the game where you can do this has started. Wow, wait a minute. Wow! Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, and oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, and oh, oh, oh, oh, a
game that can do all kinds of things.
If you can do it the other way at the beginning, that's
amazing.
[Music]
Nere
Okay,
Kukku, Sorry.
ONE. Wait a minute, okay.
Oh, nice. I understand. Is it a bit late? It's fine. It's
okay. Just
be strong. Beginner,
Beginner.
Okiara wants to practice one more time,
so he's doing one thing. White team oh.
Yeah, do your best, do your best. I wonder if Ande will show up. I wonder
if Andy will show up. There are
a lot of yellows today. Red, red,
yellow.  Yataka, let's take a look. It's difficult to actually
do it. There
are two difficult ones.
Trident piece
[Music]
Nehaa
[Music] It's
difficult, but it's difficult. It looks like the second round will be over. It's just the actual performance. That's
right, that's
right.
Yes, it's true that quite a lot of people are
worried about it, but it's actually really difficult.That's why the
first three were so
amazing.It was really hard.No, but they practiced a lot in the middle of the night.I
also watched One Piece yesterday.  I was working on Nagarasa, but
when I came in, Chiara was working with Eternity, and
A was working with Eternity.
It's an effort.
[Music] It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's
okay, it's hard.  I should have made it more difficult, but when I
tried to look up, and when I was flying, I
pressed W to move forward, and if I felt like I was going too far,
there's no place for me to make adjustments.  I can
understand why you couldn't even click on bed number 1 when you first tried it.I
know, you've never climbed it
before, but it's faster than last time.It's really
fast, it's really fast, it's really early.  We've won in a row,
Chiara has been doing it all night. Oh, it's so bad,
why, why, why? Oh
wow, if you fall here, you'll lose quite a lot. It's
hard. Oh yeah, it's amazing.
There's a checkpoint at the end, so it's
true.  But, it's
okay to say, don't worry at all, it's totally fine, don't be quiet at all,
shut up, no, not at all, don't talk anymore,
oh
really, what's going on?  But right now,
Asamiko, this is a mess, yesterday's layout is completely
different, this is different. I've made a few adjustments to make it look simple. In
fact, it's stuck in. I
was surprised to see how much it has changed. I'm sorry, but Ani-san
can do it.  Hey, thank you very much.
You've already won, so you
might as well throw it to the top. It's a lot of shots, so it's
going up, but there are a
lot of options around here. When something like that happens,
you make that little adjustment.  It's like, oh,
that's the goal. It's nice, so it's number one. It looks like it's high. Well, it
means the course will be different tomorrow too.
This is the final one, so I
see. If you practice, it'll be as good as the actual one.
Good, good, because it's 321.
[Laughter]
[Applause] I
feel like it was easier to do things yesterday than yesterday,
but
maybe it's just my imagination. It's just a little bit of a problem. If you don't mind,
let's practice together.
Let's practice. Let's
get everyone together, then we'll do the Les once,
and then we'll be able to do it pretty freely. I
think we should leave the
voice server as it is.  I'm
going to the one who
has to poop. Yes, I think I
decided the order automatically.
Thank you very much.  Nekone, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice, rice.
Can I have everyone enter for now? There are
8 of us, so maybe we can all make it. Well,
everyone is okay, so let's
all put our minds into it. Sorry, we've
got 8 people to enter.  Is that
okay? Yes, that's what I'm doing. I'm
out. Yes, I'm still pushing No. 5 Mel.
E No. 6. If
Amiko also joins, I'll be in the red group. Eh,
No. 7 Ina and the last one will be Shion, so Eh Mito.
Yes.  Ao, Kanate, and Zeta can go wherever they
like, ok, yes,
they like it
, it's ok to go wherever they want.  I
thought I'd watch it, but I ended up leaving it at the end. It's
good. Do you like it? Yeah, I like it.
By the way, yeah number 2 number 4
number 6 number e
[Music]
diff
Eh this is gone, isn't it?
So it's Jita or Ao.  There
are
1,234,5678 people, Miko Sakura, and I
think there will be 8 people on the day of the event, but
there are even runners in the Taiku race.
Wait
12345678 Oh, it's true, so
today is Japan.Today, there are 8 people as well.There are only 8 people,
so is 8 okay?
Yes, yes, yes, bruises, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, there
is no one entered in yellow.  I'm going to keep an eye on
it. Right now, including the ones for practice, it's possible to max out 9 people.
Ah, I see. That's right, so you can ignore that last row. It's
okay to enter 2 people and carry it properly.  I
want Obu to hold me.Once everyone is here, let
's start.Okay, I'm a senior, so
show me what's cool.That number is
5, isn't it easy to understand?Here,
yes, this is the closest
book.Here, in front of Fubra.  Front pla number 2
number 4 number 6 number eh
this here oh ice ice ice before ice cream
before
this By the way, when it comes to the next operation,
it will warp automatically Ah, that's
right, it's wonderful Yes, it
's all the time  It's okay to just look at it, and you can
automatically see it in the center of here, which is
amazing, but I haven't tried it yet, so I thought, let's give it a
try.The
baton was probably left-
click, because everyone started.  Do you want to
do it? Let's have some fun. Yes,
yes, infected people will automatically
come here. Okay, fight, fight properly. I
have a bat. I have a bat. It's really true
.
It's a good fight.  It's a pretty good fight baton
touch, so everyone punch punch baton
touch yeah yeah,
stubborn  I
couldn't go Okay, ah, I can eat now, really.
No, ah, I can't fly. I can't fly, but it's okay. It's
okay, you know, I have to eat bread. Energy,
eat bread. A, long press, long press, Yachamo-chan, it's okay
. Do your best, persevere.  Do your best, try your best, do your best, punch,
punch, punch, ooh, nice, practice, do your best,
seta, do your best, okay, ignore me, ignore me, ignore me, no jump, no jump, oh, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.  It's
falling, it's falling, it's straight
here, it's
here, it's leaf, it's
okay if you say leaf, Lilia, you're doing well, you're
doing well, you're doing your best, you're here, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best, you're doing your best
Jump, you're doing your best, you're doing your best This is
control control  Control
Hohoho dash and g are controllable Oh
yeah yeah I don't know what to do now I can go
here Oh wait wait wait Moo no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no I will do my best I will do my best I don't know
what to do now
It's okay even if it comes out, left click Raku Raku
Raku
Raku ruoooo Nice oo
Do your best, hurry up, good job, dash Hurry up
Wow, today is practice, next time is practice,
so it's
okay What should I do next?
Oh, go ahead, go ahead, go ahead, do your best, young lady, give it your all, but you've fallen. Go ahead, do your best, come
on.  Do
your best, ride the wave,
do your best, do
your best, do your best, do your best, do your best
Nice
bib Good, what number is it?
No, it's a punk place. If it's punk and I'm not bored, I
might be able to go. Yeah, it's true. It's better not to go
here. [Music] It's better not to go here. I'm
sure the snow is right.
Pi who moved is okay, nice leader. Oh, it's
falling. Okay, nice.  It's falling, it's
okay, it's falling, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's falling, it's okay, it's falling, it's falling, it's falling, it's okay, it's okay, it's chill
, so it's okay.  I'm
doing my best,
hey, I might be lined up with gray hair, I
might have some woof-woof,
y'all, y'all, I'll be waiting for you at the anchor.
If you don't have a cloud, there's
something creepy about the suddenness. Don't
worry, go, do your best, go, go, do your best, you'll be able to do it. Yes,
finally,
I'm waiting for you. I've become a thick voice, and now I'm gone.  I'm
waiting. I do
n't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I'm already
at the goal. I'm waiting for you.
Miko. Seriously, turn around once. Seriously, really, really quickly.
[Music] It's
okay. Hello, everyone. I
won't forget the wonderful Fu. I won't forget the Fu.
Hello
Hello,
thank you, do your best, do your
best,
hey, that's amazing. That's great. I think it'll be okay if we practice. Yeah, it's okay.
Practice a lot. Masuko-san, you're the
type of person who can mix things up, so it's true that you mix it up.  Is
n't it okay? What's wrong with the team? What are they
doing? These people are scary. Okay,
so I'll just call out to you once.
Yoshimiko-san, this is it. With this system, it's
pretty confusing and you can play easily, so it's team-
related.  I'm going to try mixing it up for now.The
amazing thing is that it's all mixed up.For
example, you can do that fang line while also being able to
play a hunter.It's different.
So for example, everyone can enter
by touching the entry signboard, and at first they tend to be fast, but if they touch their favorite white,
yellow, or red, they
can enter,
and up
to 32,739 people can run.
Well, if you limit the number of people to 9, the anchor person can
run one
lap in a hurry, so if you can do that, you
can do it next time.If you
can't do it now, you can participate for the second time.
After that, I thought, ``I guess we should just do whatever we want.''
There are some people who are so violent that there are people who haven't made other teams, so why don't we
do it again with the full members?
That's right.  If we're going
to make a mess, I think it's okay
if the teams are all mixed up.Then how do we decide which teams to choose?The teams tend to be too
quick, but once they're done, we'll be able to cheer
them on as we see fit.Maybe it's
okay to just cheer them on as we see fit.  I
think, Masuke, all you have to do is enter one more time. Just
press the entry button and
get it. Right there, the white and white group, the
white group of the white group, or the white group, which doesn't matter.
Wait a minute, ah, I have to interrupt the game.
No, wait a moment, okay,
yes, this is it, I see, only the red one can
do it, and now it's the red team and the
white team. Yeah, yeah, yeah, but
maybe there are some people who can't run.  The
whole team asks me if I don't run. It's
yellow. Yes,
don't go. Those who weren't running just now,
just hit the space as hard as they can. Wow,
yes, yes, what's
going on? I thought I was going to run one more time.  I'm pretty
satisfied with Yellow, but if there's one more match, I'll do it.Yellow
Yellow has the most people,
but I think it's good for the blue one, but now I'm
hitting it repeatedly, hitting it like crazy, Miikeko.  I
don't know if I'm practicing right now without starting, but
if I had another one, I'd do it at all, but I'd just walk normally.I wonder if it's
okay.Then I'll
practice without using that system.  Is that okay? OooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaI
don't have to
eat but if you don't eat you won't be
able to recover your stamina so it won't be slow and you wo
n't be able to run and you won't be able to take that food.  It's
okay, but if you're full, you can eat it.Pa
wants you to take away the bread.I want you to take away the bread.I
want you to take it, but yeah
, no, it seems like you just want me to take this.I don't know.
Yes, you can reach the goal without it,
so it's quite difficult, so make sure to take it and eat it.You don't
have to eat it.Yes, you don't have to eat it.However, it
's not like if you don't eat it, it's against the rules.  If you
don't win Japan, it's against Lulu. Well, I
'd like to make it feel like each team is together, but I guess I'll use a system.
In competitions, only one of them can move, so
yeah, yeah, people who want to do it.
Well then, let's make it feel like we're going to gather them together.Oh, then, that
yellow is being held over here, and
when we have a competition, we'll ask you to chat with us and then we'll go over there.Yes,
please, please,
please.
[Music] Moshi-
moshi-san, what are you talking about? This is something that
allows you to practice without using the system.
So, this is something that allows you
to practice freely without using the system, without starting or anything like that.  So,
those who use the system
have to do it one by one, so if you want to
give commands to it, then those who want to do it, oh, I see,
then oh yeah, yeah.
For example, I'm going to do Holomen Hunter
one more time, so anyone who wants to do it, please come.
So, if you want to play, come along, I'll
give you the command, and I'll say, ``Hello, take the bread.'' I
had a question about this, so I'm sharing it with you. You
can also do a dash without taking the bread.
But if you can do that, it will
be quite slow, and it will be slow,
but
if you don't do the act of picking up the bread,
there is a possibility that it will be faster, but that will do it.  Mi, I
dash without taking bread, so
taking bread is a must, and I have to make a rule that I
don't take bread.However, I
thought I'd share if you agree to the rule that you are free to eat or not.
Okay, okay, so when we do that competition, I'll just
say a little bit and
let them
know. I'm sorry, but for the relay,
don't use the system, just do that practice. Okay. There
was a question about bread, bread. Yes,
take the bread.  I was asked if it was okay to just eat the dash without eating.I was asked
if it was okay to just eat the bread, but I was told that I really wanted to be able to take the bread.  It's
better to eat like that,
Tomiko thinks.I'm so hungry, I'm getting hungry so fast.That's
right, that stomach is going to get empty, right?I'm definitely going to get hungry here, that's right.You
can't run when you're hungry.  I'll
have to walk, so oh
yeah, that's right, I'll be in trouble if I don't
eat.To be honest, I don't think there's any benefit to not eating.Yes, that's okay, so let's go
in that order.Only
those who want to do something, only those who want to play,
gather a little bit and each  I'm thinking of doing a competition, so I'm
free from now on.Even
if it's not a competition I'm in, if you feel like having a little fun with everyone,
please come by.I'll go out there and play with you, and if someone asks me to play, I'll pet them,
so that's okay.Then
let's each practice on our own.  Please
come and visit us.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you,
thank you
,
thank you.  Thank you very much for your
hard work.It looks like this
after making the final adjustments for the sports day.As
expected, everyone has practiced quite a bit, so they
want to do it at their own home, so it
doesn't look like this right now, so I'm starting now.  I'm
thinking of collecting those competitions, but which one do you think would be better
?
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you. I guess I was
at full speed right now. Okay, I
may have left you all behind for a while.
Sorry, everyone, please come and see me tomorrow. I'll be your guardian.
Thank you very much for your support
Holomen
Hunting Holomen Hunting
This time's topic is Holomen Hunting Let's look
forward to tomorrow's Holomen I wonder if we'll
do something other than hunting Holomen
Hunting There are quite a few people who have tried this as well.  I
think it's good, everyone, it's
better to try this one. It's
hard to go and get it for the people who go above this one, so it's
better to give it a try tomorrow as the cheat stick might run out.  It might be
better on the other hand.
Well, it would be quite easy to do it with people from the red team and the white team,
but you have to choose people.
This might be a little too high.
Neona is coming
[Music]
What is this?  I feel like playing home hunting for the red team.I
wanted to do that.I wasn't able to do it a while ago,
so I'm going to play it on the day as well.But
since I couldn't, I haven't played it even once.Well, I
don't know how to play.So, let's talk
to everyone about Holomen
hunting.  I'm recruiting Ah,
thank you. Thank you very much.
Yay, yeah, yeah, yeah,
okay. I did it. Yay, I feel like the streaming should be over by now. You can do it at all, and it's okay if it ends.  Miko is
streaming, so why don't you just chime in
? Okay, I'll close it for now.
Yes, I believe in it. You can also stream freely.
Okay, how are you going to do this?
[Music]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but I'll still stream it.
Still streaming
[Music]
Oh, let's do Nico as well. Alright, the
red team has entered. Only yes, the red team has
entered. Oh, the yellow hunting red team that entered was
quick.
[Music] [Music]
Akami Amaibijuana Senpai is different
Oh let's use this as a platform for the second half I'm back
I'm a fugitive Is red okay? Let's get
started
Work harder and harder I'm
alone
How
can I survive?  Left click left click left
click to catch me It's the red team's red team
so go ahead and catch me catch me you can catch me now I'm
not having fun now I'm not going to catch you I'm going to catch you and I'm
going to catch you on the top of the top who's who and
who's doing it.  If you catch me, you'll be caught. If you do
n't put it in, you'll
catch it. Where, where, where, where, where, it's over, it's over.  I'm
here, I'm white, I'm here, I'm here,
I'm here, I'm here, I'm on top, I'm
hiding, I'm hiding.  [
Music]
Time, yeah, it's better to increase the game time, it's
better to increase it,
right, Zeta, yes, come on, come on, come on, come on, yellow, click on this, click on that
Lyrica, click on that Lyrica, click on it,
click on it.  If you don't press the Hunting button,
you wo
n't be able to enter, right? You can't go inside unless you touch the board. Yeah,
yeah, then touch this board. I have
n't learned how to do this, so I'll
probably try it once.  I
can't attach the rope to the rope.First of all, I feel
like I've caught it.I feel like I've caught it,
but I wonder if I left-clicked on that book one more
time.Oh, I'll
try one more time.  I wanted to
practice catching the red team one more time.Oh, I'll
stop right now, but I'll do it with the first one.I'll
contact everyone for a moment.Yes, I'm
sorry, there's no one here right now.I'm sorry,
that house.  Even if the members of the red group
still don't quite understand how to do it, just
for the first half of the first half,
can we practice one more time? Yes, I'm
sorry. Yes, I'm sorry. Everyone in the white group, that's white.  Group:
Yellow group, sorry, that red group
team is still touching the rope with the rope. Yes, it's just a
little bit in the middle of the first half.
Can we just practice for the first half?
Well then, I
wonder if it's okay if I have another entry with that hunter.
Or maybe this one enters. We're just
practicing, so punch and move on.
Hey, there's one more person. That's that, that's that, that's out, that's
not out, it's not out, it's flow up.  So, that
's right, I wonder
where it came from. It's here. I
entered. I
haven't
entered yet. Maybe I should do it again. Go back.
[Music]
Oh, let's try it.
[Applause] [  [
Music]
Hey,
red and red
people, I want you to practice this and that. Mihane, you're
different, you're different, you're different. The head of red is
provoking you
[Music] You
're talking about Kurute Terue Nene Click Click Knic.  I'm
already here, I've
just been caught. I'm sorry, I've been caught. Oh, well, next time. If I
click that one time, I wonder if I
'll talk. Yeah,
yeah, that's right, I'm making a face that says I got caught.
Where is this bib?
Left click.  Right-click
on the top to let go and capture it, and it's
already gone.
Oh, I can go a little bit. I caught it. Oh,
oh, it's more than enough to sled. Here,
please, please, go ahead.
It's no good if I let go.  That's right, it
's no good. If I let go, it'll
go back to normal. G. I caught him just as I caught him.
He just touched the signboard, touched the signboard, touched that strange board.
[Music]
There was another person who looked like he was there.
Another person who tried
[Music]
Sorry I got it so quickly I
got it
Oh no no I'm really in it I
already got Subaru
this time I didn't get Shibaru here and there I caught it I know it's nice.
Thank you for your hard work. You're doing well. Okay, nice, nice. Okay, nice, nice. Okay, thank you. Okay, I
learned to run like this, so now I can do it. Yeah,
yeah, Okay, then the yellow
person. Now, the person who
runs away. The person who runs away.
Lioiichihifui.  I'm
going to press the team, everyone is a fugitive, so
it's okay for people to do the relay too. Oh, right click and pan left. That's the
yellow one on the left. The other yellow members
can also become fugitives.  So, Okay,
maybe you can write that down. Okay, just catch the yellow one. That's
right. Yes, that's okay
. The white team will also do the hunt.
Do you want to do it? OK, let's do it next to the yellow one.
Okay, okay, okay.  And
even when that white team was that white team, I was a fugitive
and could be another member of the white team.
Yes, yes, please give it a try. Yes,
yes, that's not the next one.
Thank you for taking the day off.
Alright, I'm going to light up my computer.  But it looks like the computer is
almost here.Thank you
very much.Thank you very much.Thank you for your
hard work.Thank you very much for your hard work.Thank you very much for your hard work.I look forward to
seeing you tomorrow.
Oh, I'm running away
because Asodafu was doing it
[Music]
I see.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you. I'm still
streaming. Yes, Amiko is also still streaming. Yes, I'm here. Ah
, are you
okay? It
's starting.
Hey, let's go! Good night,
everyone.
Bim, good night, everyone. Let's
take a break and try it out.
What should we do next for the white group? Wow, I got caught. No one's been
here, and it hurts. No
one has noticed it. It's really weird. It's the
first time I've been caught.
He looks happy, but he seems to have
made a mistake.He's making a mistake.I do
n't know why he came out.He's
being targeted, so he should run away.Wow, he
's from the white group.  The
White Team It's the White Team,
right? It's Kao-
senpai. I've been here forever. It's a really
nice place. Yes, no one
has noticed. Really, no one has noticed. It would be
better if we stayed away from each other. We're far away. We
're fighting.
Yeah, they thought we were in the white team, and it was
red that
caught that and that, but how did they feel about it?
White, who was caught,
didn't realize it.It's like this,
Polka-senpai, didn't he just want to use it?
Ah, there's that theory. I'm
sure he likes it because he keeps getting caught. Maybe he likes it. Maybe he
'll have it if he pops it. I
wonder if there's a thing like that. He's not there, but he's
not there.
Why does he get caught because of his hair?  My senior who is thought to be yellow,
no, I don't like it again. I'm
trying to catch it. It's a problem. It
's a problem. I'm good at it. I'm good at it
. That
's white. It's a bit of a correction. Let's get in there,
listeners.  After all,
when that big one got destroyed, there were
some people who were there all the time, thinking they were going to break it.Oh,
that's a great entry, entry,
entry, entry, etc. It's a drop that hasn't fallen, and
everyone whose entry has been cut off has been cut off.  The
people who gathered here are really
lost. I'm sorry, everyone.
I thought I was going to hide here.
Oh, it's true. I'm starting to feel sorry. I'm sorry,
everyone. There's
nothing I can do about it. I'm just pretending to be a listener.  That
's right, it's okay. It seems that I
thought I was a listener. I
thought I was being cut down.
Okay, hey, let's do this. Let's
try it out. It won't come in. It won't come in. It won't come in. It wo
n't come in. It won't come in.  I can't get in. At
first, I'm mostly from the red group. I ca
n't climb up. I
can't get out. Is it possible to get out even outside the entrance? It's not like I can't get out. Normally, I
can't get out. I can't get out, but that's it.  Please help me
if I can enter or not. Even
if I can enter, I can't.
[Music] I
'm the first person to enter, but I need to
help everyone.
If I don't help them, I want a team member next time.  I
miss my friends, Miya,
Ueo-senpai, Miya,
No-aotsu, Oke-
senpai, senpai.The only one in the red group who is being beaten up is Miko-senpai.Oh my, it's tough, it's
okay, there's a lot of white group, they've
been captured.  Hey, Aka-Aka, are you running away
? Did Aka-senpai get caught?
Hey, hey, come on, tell me what's wrong. You shouldn't say things like that. You're amazing, you're amazing, you're right, on the contrary. On the contrary,
on the contrary.  Hey, it's amazing,
hey, it looks
delicious, isn't it? It's amazing, Yomiko-senpai's special is making me angry. Somiko-senpai's special is special, so it's special, so yeah, there's a lot of yellow, but there's no red, but wow, what are you doing?
Ah, the spider's nest that's stuck in it.  I was
trying to escape,
but I wasn't able to escape.It
was too good, after all, I was
able to do something like that.But I was
caught in the cloud's nest,
but as normal, Ririka-chan suddenly disappeared from the game.
Please reset, please interrupt. I
have a signboard in the middle
of the board, where is this? That's what it means. It
was a ku's nest. I don't like Senkyu, but in
the end it disappeared when I was thrown into the cage.  Yeah,
well, maybe it was a waste of time.Ririka-
chan suddenly disappeared, so she was probably
taken away.Okay
, everyone, please keep practicing, Miko,
Tachimiko.I'll call out to you again.Yes, okay,
what should I do?
Nahi  Is your voice good?
[Music]
Hey, it's good.
Hey, you're here. Yes, I
think it's going to take a lot of time if we're going to play all the rounds
today. But there's probably a team I want to practice with.
Miko calls out to me and makes a loud voice.
People who want to play are flooring up.  I was thinking, ``I'll pass it around to whoever wants to do it,''
but even if I get removed, I'm
like, ``It's okay,'' and I'm free to
do it.Then I'll close it once, and
say, ``Yes, that's right, I'll gather everyone together.''I'll
do that.Okay,
white.  Is it okay if I collect them? I
'll let them gather on 2nd. Yes,
please. I'm sorry. I thought I'd close it once,
but after I close it, I think it's
okay to have people take pictures. I thought I'd do that.
Tate, that's where Miko is,
where's Moshi Moshi, Hoshi Moshi, Hoshi Moshi [Music] What's that?
[Music]
Everyone can talk [Music]
No, wait a minute, the voice on the call
is dead Moshi Moshi The
clip you joined is valid  The
members who are doing this
are [Music] [Applause]
[
Music] [Music]
What
[Music]
This
Desimo-
chan That's over.  Is there anyone who understands?
Reboot. Wait a minute.
[Music]
Okay.
Reboot. Nico's Disco, which everyone is playing, is
coming. Hello,
this.
Well, I heard that. I'm
sorry. I think I'll close that whole thing for now.  It's
okay to leave the frame as is, but I'm
thinking of closing it for now, so can you please
join me in the room where everyone is?
Oh
yes, there was Rolo.  Ao, I'm
going home, and some people
will close it and leave the slot as it is.I'm going to close it once, so I hope
everyone has gathered.Isn't
Ospor here?Ah, Sporu, you see.I'm back, so it's
okay for the first time.It's okay,
yes, it's okay.  So,
everyone, thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much. You all put a lot of
effort into the practice, or rather, you
practiced like crazy. I'm very happy,
and I'm very happy. I hope you'll
also be able to support the members who couldn't come.  I
hope we can all have fun together,
so please
join us. From now on, I'll call you Miko. It's
okay even if you're not related to the team.  Is it
okay if I come at the right time and get it? It's the same with the Fang Fang line that starts up, the same with the follow-up, and the princess can't do everything at once, so I'm thinking of doing it in order. Yes, yes,
only gather the people who want to do it and come.  It's
like I'm going to give it to you, so I'm going to go ahead and give it to you, and then you can close the frame, or you can leave that frame, but thank you very much.  Thank you everyone for your
hard work. We look forward to seeing you again tomorrow. It's
6pm tomorrow.
Thank
you very much. See you again. Please excuse me.
Sanro will be on No. 5 for now.
[Music] "
Yes," the parents said.
Thank you everyone. So,
where should we go?
Let's gather some voices.
Who is this? Mio, Mio, that's sorry. Umiko, who was
doing that, is going to stay and watch everyone's
practice.  I thought to myself, `
`I'm not going to close my eyes,'' and I'm just going to make a sound.Okay, that's fine.It
's tomorrow, Miko-kun.It's
early.Yo,
no, it's already been a while.Seriously, oh,
but...  This time, the quality has
improved significantly compared to last time, and we have been able to incorporate a lot of things into the system, so that's amazing.I think it's a good thing, after all.Even so, it
still has to be adjusted until the very end.That's true,
seriously.  I
feel like it was amazing, but it all worked out.
Yeah, yeah, tomorrow I'm
going to buy cookies for the three of us to eat, so I'll
bring Ei, and Mio-chan will be carrying the
sweets.
Well, we're going to do the commentary in a different studio,
but tomorrow we'll be in that studio.The
three of us will get together for a bit.Yes,
last year too, Nemi-o-chan brought all sorts of
sweets.  I
feel like he brought a lot of things with him. He brought
a lot of food. He brought a lot of food. He brought a
lot of food.
Mio-chan, I think he brought a lot of food.  I think it's a gift. I
love Mio's gifts, so Miyoko.
No, thank you very much. It's good.
Let's get together in number 01.
Voice. That's right. Let's get together. I
see. That's right. That's right, Higo.
Just the start. Yes, the
members are separated.  It's like practicing the "yes, yes, yes, yes, yes" voice.
Yeah, um, maybe, please, please,
please,
please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. Please, please, please. The
streaming of that Mikochi is still ongoing, so please
take care of me, please.
There are all of us, but yeah, yeah, how about we
divide the yellow members into 444? How many
people are there? It's totally okay. How many people are there now?
1234567888 There are 8. If so, we can
divide them into teams. We
can do it. We'll see how it goes. If there's
anyone who wants to team up.
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
please just move on. I'll
ask you something. Oh, sorry, I have one more question.
What is that? We're going to make a figurine and guess what it is.
Yeah, well, a knight shouldn't talk or talk,
right? Basically, the
voices and things like ``Later'' are good, but with words,
this is that.
Yes, yes, yes, put green here, and words like that.Then,
that princess is allowed to speak, and the princess
speaks.If the princess were the other way around, then the princess would
say, I wonder if that thing is a refrigerator.
When the knight shakes his head while listening, or nods up and down, does that sound like a no-no? Yes, it's true, no, yo, no, it's fine, as long as it's not a word. No, no, no, that's like an answer.  Things like that theme in Koshi, things like
that change on the day of the day.In
terms of themes, the one about cooking,
the first half of Yes is not exactly the same.Well, it's
random, so in reality, it's red hair.
For example, if you do something like a lot of paprika
or a lot of refrigerators, you
might think it's inevitable, but that's
true. But it's completely random, so I do
n't really understand why.  He
seems to be angry, and the
topic for the day is
random.It seems that the one that is currently appearing is the same and there is a possibility that the same thing will come out again.As
for Achinami, the person who makes that creative thing is
...  The first half doesn't change that much,
but the second question is about that day
's special question.Yes,
that may be quite difficult, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.  It's
not like it's going to interfere with that. Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
[Music]
Well,
here I was at 44. Yesterday's heat is still divided. No, it's not
like that. Yes, it's yellow. What does it look like now? It's
probably yellow. The yellow color is yellow.  Looks like we're going to get together.Yellow. Should we
do it now?Then I wonder if we should enter as red and white.White.That's right.Let's
enter that white.The team that will do it on the day.Let's
make a separate team with people who are happy with that.This is the
red team and the white team.  Isn't there a dream voice?
Yeah, yeah, they've
disbanded quite a bit. I guess they've disbanded quite a bit, but those three teams are all together. We
can still practice without them, so we're like, okay, let's
do it, let's do it.
Everyone just has to enter.  If you can do it, I
can do it.Oh, then I'd like to play a princess.I'd
like to play a princess.No, I'd like to play a princess
Anya.I'd like to play an ancient soldier.Okay, I
want to see the princess.Please, I want to see the princess.
Mio-chan, you can come as a knight.
That's dead. She's dead. Well, I'll
ask you to be that mi-knight.
Oh, you're cute, Suma-chan.
Isn't that
cute? Start
button. Yes, where is the start button? Where is the start button? Where is the
start button? Shall we separate the voice server?
Oh, yes, then let's go to the actual performance. I'll be
number 2 on the team, please. Yes,
yes, ma-chan, number 2. Oh yes, let's
go.
Oster, can I ask you to protect me?
Imiko-senpai, Wata Anya, in your order.
Blomisa, let's go, Shiro Nemiko, the
white orchestra is a little short, shut up, Higata, hurry up, yes,
white, pink, pink, that's strong
, hey, it's a princess, stop the princess, right there,
block is in danger Nice, hihihi, go back.
There's
more, yo later from white, back, back, back, late, pink, pink, pink, pink, pink, which way, which way, which way, which way, white, pink, red, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, princess, hey, the princess is already in tatters.  I've come all the way to red,
white,
pink, white, pink, oh, white, pink, red, red, red, yes, yes,
yes, please, pink, red, don't move, don't move.  It's
not okay anymore, it's no good, it's
no good, it's on standby, it's so
good, it's so weird, it's
weird, it's so weird, it's so weird, it's so weird,
it's so hot, it's so
white, it's so white, I can't understand it.  [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
But the
amazing grilled rabbit meat and viewer's characteristic hamburger with one shot There
is rabbit.
Hey, raw
beef, please, please!
Ojaji, potatoes, rainbow.
Okay, raw garlic. Raw beef.
What are you going to do with the potatoes? Cut
potatoes, rainbow potatoes,
and carrots, too. Add the ground beef, cut potatoes, and carrots on a hot iron plate. It
's a great minced meat. It's minced meat. It's
just what I want to say. You, please, please
do this.  You should be able to do it if you fry it in a pot. It's
done. Look, look, look at it. Look, it's
cute.
Where did you go? You smoked it. I don't
like the grilled rabbit meat. I'm sorry, Miko-san, and Miko-
san, too.  Isn't it charred
? It's okay, it's okay, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's nice, it's
nice, it's next, it's dangerous, it's a monster, it
's red, it's red, the top left is orange, it's orange,
and the top right is yellow, orange.  Red red orange
yellow yeah red orange yellow red orange yellow red
orange yeah bottom left red top left orange top right
yellow red that's red orange red this orange
yellow bottom is red bottom is red top orange right yellow ah
orange yellow ok.  Nice at all, I didn't
understand, Nice.
Cats bloom in battle,
so they're coming, they're coming, they're
slipping through, they're slipping through.
Mikochi runs away, runs away, protect that place by yourself.
Alright, alright, nice, nice, nice, you're
not coming.
Do your best.  I'm doing my best, I'm doing my best,
okay, it's hot, it's hot, it's hot, it's protecting, it's hot, isn't it?
Everyone's on fire, everyone's
on fire.
But I'm exhausted, I'm exhausted.
It's okay. It's
okay. It's okay. Who's to blame
? I
didn't do it. I didn't do it at all. By the way,
Nimiko didn't do it at all. Look at me, I'm
irritated.  It really stings.
Don't give it a weapon. It's the worst. It's so bad. Let's
do a little server together. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes."
It's a success when something like a star appears, right? It's easy.
When the star appears on the opponent's body, it means it's a
critical hit. It's
amazing that you even learned how to do a critical hit.
But it's amazing.  I wonder if the person with the bow
should end up with the demon king nesasuyana sas festival.Wait
a minute, that one from last year
required a huge critical hit.Oh, last year's
sports day, I'm sure it was better than a critical hit.
I remember, what happened when I jumped? There
was mob subjugation, there was mob subjugation, there was mob subjugation, there
was fencing, there was sing, there was
Shidama-san who fell down, Daruma-
san fell, and by the way,
something like that.  There are other people I want to practice with,
okay. It's okay to
follow up. I think there are people who can participate in the follow-up, like Suisei-senpai. I
think I'll have to follow up with my husband.
Wow, I have the impression that he's already got the hang of it. Yeah, that's
definitely Anya, too, Anya-senpai.
Ah, that's right, let's collect the follow-up. Let's
follow up. Okay, follow
up and do one yellow. Shall we call it
quits?
Yes, when was the next practice?
12The next practice is tomorrow, uh, tomorrow, uh,
tomorrow, yellow.  I think I can go from 1 o'clock to midday.I might go for
a little while.Oh, it's okay.It's
okay.In the beginning, on the contrary, if
there's something I want to practice,
let's practice a little after this. Let's go play together.
Time is running out,
but if you're doing it, please join in. It's
totally fine. Well, it's a good time to start. Feel
free to do whatever you want.
Thank you very much. Thank you for your hard work.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
There's still one more person on the floor, but Anya is coming.Who's going to do it?
No, your stomach is sticking out.Put
it away.It's cute, right?Yeah, yeah, put it away.Actually, I'm
going to move.There's
no flirting, please move.There's already one.
We're here
and we're getting used to each other. I can't believe we're here. I can't help but notice that my stomach is sticking out.
By the way, it's so cute that my belly is sticking out. Chao-
chan's belly is sticking out normally.
[Laughs]
Tamin's heart is one.  The moment it turned into `
`Yashun'', ``Oh, that's it,
please touch this.''
Okay, uh, I'm late. Oh, Ani-san, too.
Sensei-senpai's entry is yellow. I
changed it to white, but why should I change it to red?
Ah, you can use yellow, I
'm sorry, I changed it to red. Oh, I changed it to red. Sorry, I changed it to red. Red is
also open. It's really open. I can go to that, red. I can
go to that. Ah, meow. I can make an entry. If the
yellow player changes it to red, I
can do it. Good luck.  Ei, let's do our
best, my strength is fast, no matter who's in the middle of it, I guess it's already begun. I wonder if Miko, the amazing creator, will win.
I'm the creator's slide cancer. A
battle that can't be defeated can't be lost.  There's a battle
here that doesn't exist, but a
new word has been
created: Ganba nya, Ganba nya. Today, Ganba nya, Ganba nya, is
n't Ganba nya cute? Gamba nya, it's
cute, is
n't it? It's early, but this one is an early author, as expected.
Now that you know the route,
if you just follow the route, you can get there in the shortest possible
time. That's not
true. Everyone is amazing. That's why they're all good at it. It's a
shame that they're not doing things like that.
Aji
Nemiko-senpai is really good
, you've surpassed me, you're amazing now,
wait for me to die, ahhh, I'm sorry, I'm
not waiting, let's get along
okay, let's get along, okay, that's a bit scary, right? I
'm back in the middle of falling.  Ah, the second checkpoint.
When you realize that you can't do this anymore, you'll be able to come
back right away. That's amazing. You'll be able to come back right away. That's
good. It's okay. It's not a competition. Finally,
where can you go? Yeah, it's mental. That
's why this game  Well, it's a mental gel, it's
mental and physical, so mental and
physical passion is what's important
. As expected, as a person, I'll get there quickly. It's
another team, another team, this is a different source.
So
do your
best, ah, that's it. Good luck, you're amazing.  It's so
stable, it's stable, things haven't been going
well for me, I'm going to die, but I can't stop because I
won't be here tomorrow.
Karasa Sui-chan and who are you? Yes, I'm with you.
Hey, Ririka, please stop. If something happens, I'll
go instead. I'll
stop, stop, stop. Ririka, stop.
Ririka, stop. I wonder if I'll be there, too.  It's
safe because I'm here. Seriously, I'm
also a follow-up, so my passion is
going to be a little messed up.
Hey, everyone's going to be broken by the follow-up. Come home, Miko, hey. There are
still people streaming here.
There's a mess, there's a mess.
Hey, what's going on? It's currently on air. It's currently
on air. That's right. Why did it fall? How did it fall
? We're all watching the flow-up. The
last try. The flow-up is the
last one.  It looks like it's going to be bright
tomorrow.If you
ask me for today's practice, it's
not much different from the layout, so I can't reach it anymore.It's
a waste.Good luck with this.Good luck.I
can't reach it.If the water could reach the top, it would
probably be yesterday.  The layout is almost the same as the
one on the top.The bottom is quite different from the bottom.It's good to see you've
reached the third checkpoint.Idiot, are you
okay?It's not okay.Good luck, A.It's
okay.There's still time.  I'm going to
go slowly. I'm fine. I fell. I'm fine.
Please leave me the speed of your recovery. Please
leave me the speed. I
can do it. That's
great. What should I do?
19 seconds left. 19 seconds left.
Okay, 15 seconds left. You're serious. I can't see you, but you're falling. You're
an idiot. You're an idiot. I want to die. I want to die. Idiot bye. Bye. On the contrary, it
was amazing. On the other hand, it was amazing. I'm sleepy.
[Music]
[Laughter]  Well, it
's over, so this is no, no, no, it's over.
After this, it's going to
turn yellow and
it's going to end. Yes, okay, then. Those who close the frame, do
your best. Thank you for
staying. Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
That's it, let's
break up for now. Mr. Ba, oh, that was interesting. It's so difficult, is
n't it? Everyone. No, but in the first half, there were quite a few times when I would
hit something if I jumped. So I'll
wait and see.
Com-com,
don't throw it, don't throw it.  Don't throw it,
let's do it one more time. I
tried really hard to reach the goal, but don't throw it. Don't throw
it. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. I
tried my best to reach the goal. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. Don't throw it. I tried to do it one more time. I tried really hard to reach the goal, but I really tried to do it. Don't throw it like this. Don't throw it like this. Isn't there a shortcut somewhere?
[Music]
Let's reach the goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Goal Unto Goal
Alright
[Music]
Okay
Alright, I'm going to put a little emphasis on the reverse.
Hey, it's dangerous. I can't fall down here. It's dangerous.
[Music] De
[Music]
Okay, Hey, I can't fall down here.
Music] I
won with 144 seconds left, 144 seconds left.
Awesome, Miko,
amazing. This is amazing. I love competitions. Na-
chan, you came late. Do
n't you think so? That's the pride of the creator.  Yeah,
yeah, it's nice. Kachan,
Miko's Yellow Miko is in first
place. By the way, I can't go home after finishing here. If I had finished
earlier, I wonder
what people would say if they had more time. It looks like a bonus bonus place.  I
thought about making something like this, but it's
faster if it's smooth, but if I
make a mistake during the actual performance, I probably
won't be able to reach the goal like I did before.I
wonder if this is okay.That's a
bonus.When the
stages don't go well, there
's a lot of it.
In the
end, the competition ended up being a bit complicated.
[Music]
Yeah, that's
right. It didn't feel that way.
[Music]
No, no.
It got to the point where everyone could finish.
Okay, seriously, this is amazing.
[Music]
Okay, so how was everyone today?
Tomorrow, it's the real show. Win
or lose, it's the real show, so please
come and see us tomorrow from 6pm.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much for your support. I look forward to seeing you all tomorrow as well.
Everyone is putting the most effort into their practice than ever before.  They're
doing it behind the scenes,
especially the newcomers, and
everyone at enid is also coming together every time and
doing things like that, so even though I couldn't come,
all the support members are
taking the initiative and doing things with the seniors.  I
think it's amazing.Thank you
very much.Thank you
very much.Thank you very much for your continued support.So,
I hope to see you again tomorrow at 6pm.Well
then, it's time for
dinner.See you soon.Let's move on to the ending of the shrine maiden.  Okay, let's go to the room. Let's
hang out for a
while. Thank you, little boy. It's going to stay like
this. I think I'll
be a little nervous if I leave tomorrow, so I thought we'd have a chat. It's
already my 4th time.
Hey, it's
okay. The people who are showing up are already
used to it and everyone is supporting them.
As long as it's really helpful, it's okay. It's the
only day a year where you can see a cool face. Why?
Why? Why? It's always cool. It's always
cool.
Yes, it's a mess. Even
though it's the end of the live show, you're still supporting us a lot. We've
even set up a slot for tomorrow. They're
really supporting us.
Minnazu-chan and others have
also been especially involved this year.  They
make things easy for me to understand, and each group has someone acting as the middle child, and they come over and ask questions about things they don't understand.
Nesoutowa-sama is a really good senior
[Music]
Nanesouwa-chan is always running around to everyone every year, and
even today before the broadcast started, she was supporting the kids who didn't understand. She
didn't care about the details or anything like that.  I
know, as a shrine maiden, I don't do it once a year or even
once a year, but I especially feel the warmth of my seniors and juniors.  I
really feel that it's amazing. I'm really grateful for the
follow-up. No, but I'm really busy as usual, so
there were some members who couldn't participate.
But I'm so busy.
Thank you. I'm glad I was
able to do it.  I do
n't think it's finished yet, but I think the members of Rigoro
and the members of en were
really involved. After all, the
sports day is full of vegetables, and the
practice session in front of Sane is
definitely a collaboration.  I wonder if it'll
be a chance for you. I think that makes me happy as a shrine maiden.
Hey, good job. Thank you for the performance. I'll do my best. Everyone, I
think it would be better without that expensive part of Holomen hunting.
Hey, everyone
.
[Music] That
's right.
Hey, everyone, see you tomorrow. There
are 6 types of topics
,
3 lots of red bean paste,
18 lots of red bean paste, and 18 of them.
Even if it's really hard to think about it, it's impossible for Nemoko and the others to
do it alone.  I thought, ``I asked the management if there was anything
like that, and I said, ``I
tried it,
but the comments stopped.'' It was really, really difficult.They
asked me what the problem was.
There's a theme, right? This time, we're going to
catch the red group, catch the white group, catch the yellow group,
but to put it simply, it's
limited to people with animal ears in holo live shows.
If we were to pick out the people with ears from the group that had trouble and the group that had yellow ears, it
would be Maruto, so if that were the case, then there would be four people,
and so on.  I
made a lot of adjustments, trying to choose the one that had the most answers, and in the end, I
had to try the number of red, white, and yellow questions that would be asked today.
That's why it was so
hard, the balance, that's it, it's so amazing. It
's so hard to think about it, it's so hard, you
know, it's hard to think about problems.
[Music]
[Music] I'm going to contact you right now. [Music]
Well, the
more I do, the more I
want to do this.  They come out every year, right?
[Music]
But
Yeah
[Music]
Okay
Hey, it's hard to decide where to put in the effort. That's
right. It's
not just cats.  There
really isn't one, so if you make adjustments to the individual commands and things like that, then you
have to ask the supporters for a little help.It's really difficult.  To be
honest, I
thought it would be a bit difficult, but it's
amazing. There are a lot of people who do it while leaving 100 seconds or so.
Everyone is amazing.  There's a lot of
pressure on me, so I
think it's amazing when I score in the actual game.Yes, I'm at
that level, so I get anxious.Yes, that's right, it's usually my
first game.In the games where I
get started, I often fail to score a goal.In
practice.  No matter what I do, it's the same thing when I'm out of bed
. No, I'm going to sleep properly again this year. This year, it's in the evening. Yes,
there are some things like that, but Miko and the others are so
excited when they play the first game. Really,
honey, I'm going to take a good rest.
Thank you.  Everyone, please
look forward to it.What will happen
tomorrow?  If there's trouble,
or someone crashes the game, or something like that,
we've decided how we're going to respond. There's going
to be games where the game is interrupted. For example, in the second year,
everyone's on the verge of reaching the goal, but someone...
In order to deal with the situation when one person falls down, they
put in a gimmick where everyone goes into a stay state,
but even so, we still
have to get the listeners' consent.
Minecraft is a game after all, so no matter how long you've
retired, there will still be times when a bug or
some kind of tumble will occur.It's the
same with any tournament,
but at those times, don't blame anyone and
encourage them with your supportive comments.  I wish I could get it.
Yes, I'm shopping after all,
so I'm sure some people are prone to thinking that this person is at fault.
But in such cases,
it would be great if you could let me know with a warm comment.  I think it's a little warm.
Well, I
'd like to end this with the members who participated saying that it was fun,
so I'd appreciate your cooperation in that regard, listeners.
Thank you very much. I'll just cut out this part. It's
okay. Please say yes.  I
hope that the listeners can see it from the perspective of real parents and have a warm heart.I hope that everyone can enjoy saying things like this in a friendly manner.
That's the number one thing,
and of course all the members are practicing and
doing their best,
so please give us your support.
Yes, we have the spirit of getting along. Listeners, there
are also comments like, ``Even if we get along, we won't be able to do anything.''  Even if there is a
comment like that, just
do your best, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
If you can spread it in the comments, it won't be noticed. Or rather, there are so many things that we can
all do our best with the comments that support us every day.
Please listen to us.
Thank you for your comments.
[Music] Let's
have a great Akaikai.
Well, I think this is
aimed at the listeners as well, even though we are getting along well. I
don't know,
but something has been increasing all of a sudden.
Who increased the number? Who increased it? Is this
Papa? There's a flying Coronet.
There's a flying Lone
.
Hey, the quality is high.
Thank you very much.
So,
everyone, please take care of me tomorrow. Well
then, let's go.  Thank you, Hesta. I
'm going to read the Super Chat again, so I'm going to wrap it up here today.
See you tomorrow.
Let's do our best on the sports day. Well then,
I'd appreciate your feedback from the management perspective. So,
Otsu.  Mika Matane Bye
[Music]
Bye
[Applause]
Ah