[Music]
hi
it's my birthday soon this is the
birthday countdown stream
well for some of you maybe uh your time
zone maybe it is my birthday already
um
[Music]
hi guys hi
do you like my background do you like my
setting
my environment is very blue thank you
too be in pc
thank you for making this this is really
great and they made me a special badge
button i'm the birthday girl so i have
the birthday better so you want to see
my birthday graduate
oh
birthday badge look at my birthday best
wait
[Music]
smile birthday girl that's right i think
i'm
9486 today
i don't remember though so who knows
[Music]
give her my birthday bags alright girl
let me interest in my chair
so
today being the birthday countdown
stream is the music too loud by the way
it says you're eight years old
well
that's not right
[Music]
that is incorrect what was i gonna say
though uh being in the birthday
countdown stream we're gonna do
something else today called collins
um so
i'm going to be accepting collins from
pretty much anybody who's available
uh
today
um
it's it's pretty early for friends and
jp so
um
yeah anybody though anybody anybody and
everybody who wants to call in can call
in and say hi and answer my birthday
question uh but first of all i do want
to say thank you guys um
i want to say thank you to the
zombies
i received a gift from
manager
um
manager what did you send me
digital fan book
from the chum buddies thank you guys
thank you so much
thank you
it means a lot to me i don't know
there's so many people that can get
together
and um create something for me it's just
ah i don't know it's crazy i really
appreciate it though thank you guys
let's go yeah oh
you're welcome buddy
thank you guys
are you having a good day today though
are you having a nice day
i'm having a nice day i'm okay
i
have strawberries
i made it a point today to go and get
strawberries because
as some of you know i have a very bad
strawberry addiction um it's one of my
favorite foods in the summer
strawberries but yeah i have
strawberries today um while i was
carrying them around i sat down with
them in my lap and i didn't realize them
but now i have like strawberry
strawberry juice all over my my skirt
unfortunately um it's in a very bizarre
pattern so i'm a little embarrassed but
i don't think it's that bad i just have
this like frightening urge now if
anybody looks at me funny to be like
it's
it's it's it's strawberry hello ma'am
damn it's strawberry ma'am do you like
ma'am
a crippling addiction to strawberries do
you blame me though they're so full of
vitamin
a
vitamin c something like that thank you
guys so much for your super chats as
well thank you
you want to see my strawberry stains
why why do you want to see my strawberry
stains
do you think it smells like strawberry
oh it's also father's day that's right
so um
everybody wish
if you have a
wait that sounds bad oh wish your
dad's a happy father's day
if he's back from
getting the milk
oh
vitamin c
do you guys eat your strawberries like
stems and all
i have a bad habit of eating my fruit
like as is
he reasonable then stems and all baby
listen it all goes to the same place
anyway so i don't really understand the
point of taking it off
you know
[Music]
okie dokie
first of all i want to start with a gift
from one of my senpai that i received
um
just because it's really cute i want you
guys to see it um
hard working kiara kara is working so
hard
so
you go kayara
[Music]
oh but i want to show you
what i want to show you i'm sorry guys
i'm a little bit of a scatter brain it's
very stressful birthday very stressful
but it's happy day so it's okay always
smile because happy day
anyway
you want to see what i got from a senpai
korean a senpai sent me a happy birthday
[Music]
she sent me a message and then she also
made me she made me this
wanna see
gouda
happy birthday
it's a delicious pungent bouquet of
various uh dead fish and crustaceans and
also pizza and i think a vegetable that
might be a sign she might be telling me
you're eating vegetables but i say not
no
cute
she says
happy birthday
bouquet of flowers with goura's favorite
pizza
i always get so overwhelmed with
birthdays
i don't know why you guys because
i don't know
i get so nervous i think you guys know
i'm nervous though because i've been
talking to the members about how nervous
i was about today
um
so yeah i just wanted to know that i'm
still very
really nervous but uh it's okay
is the pizza soggy it appears so it also
smells a fish but this one i don't mind
[Music]
i don't mind at all
looks like we have a collar already
would you look at that let me dry can i
try it i can't drag
let's join i can't drag it's kiara by
the way
yeah wow
uh
i don't know if she can hear me
oh wait hold on what
[Music]
are you on oh wait
hold on
that way hold on
hold on she's coming through uh
a different speaker let me say hello
sorry guys setup's a little wonky
okay turn the music down too sorry guys
uh sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
oh sorry
let me
real quick here
i don't know why it's coming dude why is
it going through my speaker
what
um
could you guys hear kiara or did it
sound funny
[Music]
oh no
wait say something
yeah you're coming through
wrong output hold on a second
hold on one second as i slam the mute
button
slamming the mute button the discord
call is like shutting the door shutting
a door in someone's face i'm so sorry
hold on one second
oh no
quick cora
use your brain
[Music]
glad please work
hello
oh i can hear you oh bless
[Applause]
oh yes but you too hard working always
sharky shark yeah
no
no no no oh it's your hard working
finger
always
trying the best the best we can all do
right
yes of course
trying better even better than the best
ah
you know goura it's already your
birthday on my in my time zone
yeah
is but is it bad luck to and you know
when you're not there yet no
i don't think so why is it bad look
i don't know
maybe is it like a bad luck for some
people to wish you happy birthday before
your birthday
i feel like i've heard something like
that before maybe but whatever but happy
birthday
senpai
i have this thing that uh maybe you have
the same problem with like the new
um japanese members like horo x
uh i call them senpai by accident is
that do you have the same problem is
that weird
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
no because they're not i recently but
whenever i hear
like when i talk to a japanese
member
i always assume in my brain that there
is something
oh i think my brain like saying
like
uh coyote senpai it sounds good in my
brain so my brain like attaches it right
yeah it's like tasty treat for my brain
i'm like oh cool
it sounds right i keep on saying polly
senpai to her indeed except laplace
laptop oh it just sounds right in my
brain
yeah there were some things but whatever
let's change the
the topic that you are in right now
yeah
it's so beautiful but it reminds me of
um actually like you know you know i was
in the maldives a while ago right um
and
there is a hotel that has a restaurant
that is literally like like this under
the water
you should take
it i think i've seen that before
i've even saw it like years ago when it
first opened just as advertisements
and then later on now i found it again
and i realized oh that's in the maldives
oh
isn't that scary though if you don't
have gills then like i feel very scary
yeah
but i feel like my flame would be
wet
yes wet yes my flame would be wet maybe
like depressurizing too depending how
deep it is the deep pressurization could
also make your head
explode interesting eat you your
eyeballs pop out of your head like one
of those squeeze dolls
speaking of the moldies have you ever
been snorkeling no
what
i mean why would you snorkel if you can
go deep deep deep underwater anyway
right precisely
precisely plus if you go snorkeling you
have to put on all that gear
it's not that much gear me and jordana
tried it out and we just put on those
like the flippers on the feet yeah and
then the the head piece
but nothing else
did you see any sharks
so there were supposed to be baby sharks
do do but
we didn't see any they told us that
sometimes at that reef there would be
baby sharks but disappointingly there
were no baby sharks we saw other cool
stuff though you know you should wow i'm
surprised you never went talking that
was our first time too but you should
you should go snorkeling with someone
maybe perhaps me or someone else
i can teach you how to snorkel now
yeah
well maybe the maybe you didn't see the
sharks but maybe the sharks saw you they
decided
alone that is scary
and don't don't don't
want to ask since you don't seem to have
like any kind of like topic thing going
on i do i have questions if you want one
oh really because i was gonna ask you
for your birthday
what do you want from me
your company
okay no it's not it's very close fetched
take me out
wait come here today
i will take you out to dinner what kind
of dinner
cook for me
like a proper kitchen and ingredients a
lot of ingredients
strawberries
guess i gotta learn how to make strudel
now wait is it okay sorry i'm taking a
lot of time but last question
what kind of sweets do you like
chocolate i like chocolate right but i
also like strawberries anything with
strawberries or anything with fruit or
anything with chocolate like you like
things that are very chocolatey yeah
yeah yeah all right perfect i got you i
got you from extreme chocolate
all right all right i i know everything
that i needed to know
and then i guess i'll make way
why
last thing i say is i'm proud of you
happy birthday keep on going keep on
doing what you do also uh
congratulations on four million
subscribers thank you so much kiara
be proud of yourself um
fluff
and then right here strudel i always
think about the terrible
not my favorite food
strudel apple strudel that's just
through them
is that offensive
it might be
you never had to ask for your question
ah that's all right that's all right i
should ask her in japanese dang it to
test in my history kiara sensei test my
japanese
kiara sensei
oh
hello
sorry i barged in
what are you doing here
i'm here to wish you a happy birthday
you're now
nine more billion years old how does it
i feel as spry as the day i was hedged
from your little sharky egg sack my
little
sharky cocoon papyrus cocoon
hi
hello
not on your birthday not on your
birthday you don't even sound like that
you don't even sound like what if i want
you to do it though
you want to be bullied yes please
you make it sound so much cuter though
no
nothing can be cuter than you
sorry you want me to bully you
your stinky shark thank you stinky
smelly how odorous
can smell you all the way from the
discord call
yeah
it's extra strong today
uh thank you for coming by for now
yes i have something for you
just a little something thank you
oh there you go
oh my god it's so cute
that's you
gum
goomb
hold on
okay
guys i feel like when i imagine you in
my brain this is like what i think
i drew you in my brain this is how i
appear in father's burning yes you're
like a perfect little cake topper
delicious dessert
oh so chewy texture
would you be made of gummies or
boneless or chocolate i think either the
texture of like a gummy shark or a
circus peanut
oh
do you like circus peanuts i don't
i don't know it's been a while i've had
one
aren't they flavored like banana or
something sorry that's off topic no it's
okay i think so but they have like the
texture of the styrofoam like packing
peanuts
do they
maybe it's marshmallow
i don't know
i just remember seeing bags of them in
like a store and just i don't know they
always had this
scary
i don't know so did meringues though
meringues were scary
they don't seem like real food seems
like it's made of plastic or something
i mean some plastics can be tasty micro
plastics oh oh that's so sad to hear
from a shark oh no
water no you you have to
have no choice but to eat plastic
i love your your soda can toppers
how delicious
please eat something other than micro
plastics for your birthday but they're
so there's so there's so many there's
such a circle
someone must remove them i know
you can't eat all the micro plastics by
yourself join me
okay okay for you guru i will eat the
micro plastics out of the ocean
see sharing is caring
just slurp them out with the straw
can i ask you uh uh uh one of my
birthday questions that i have here
yes please okay
uh
what's your no wait i'll do this one
what's a game that you want to play
together sometime
oh i actually have one i want to play
together yes
yeah should i spoil it for the stream
though
well yeah
if you okay if you want though if not
then we can then don't worry about it um
i can spoil it a little bit but but
how can i ask you to play with me live
on stream and so from so many people
because it's guaranteed they'll say yes
oh well it's a funny game it's a
communication based co-op game where you
have to describe
a shape of a monster from one person to
another and the other person can't see
it so you gotta be like oh this guy is
he's shaped a little bit like a cucumber
and he's the color of moldy cheese and
then the person has to figure out what
you
mean oh
that sounds fun it's like i'll show it
to you i'll show it to you it sounds
like no i give it to me it's like
telephone but was like yeah
yeah
i'll show it to you
that sounds good i have your picture
hold on
i am kiwawa you are now
no
hold on
uh
yeah i'll play that with you sounds like
fun yeah
i want to hear your descriptions
your brain comes up with some funny
things uh-oh my word vomit
chewy stinky sticky wow
i love herbs
thank you for for having me i will i'll
get out of your way so you can talk to
your next guest but happy almost
birthday thank you thank you for being
my friend i love you
fun i love you thank you so much for
coming today
yes have a great rest of your day and
have a great time talking to everybody
bye bye
[Music]
you just correct me chat those are
adjectives describes a noun what
describes a noun
why am i so stupid
what's wrong with me i actually i went
to the store and i picked up this stuff
today called brain butter it's like
peanut butter in the tube but it said
brain butter they got me with the
advertisements because i said yes
i do need some butter for my brain
well you guys would get a kick i thought
of you guys when i picked it up i was
like oh
well they'd really get a kick out of
this no and i was literally falling for
the sales
sales gimmicks promising to fix my brain
well
well i did make
i did make some pink butterfly like the
other day
thank you
yeah i did i did make some pink butter
maybe maybe that is
brain butter the real brain butter oh
wait pink like a
ring
um when i was making the kirby cake
i ended up i ended up mixing the i ended
up whipping the cream too much it turned
into butter and i just had so much pink
butter i bet i could make the brain out
of it ah
it was actually really good but i just
had so much you can get like one of
those like molds that they have for
jello and stuff but instead fill it with
the the butter and then freeze it
oh maybe i can get like a brain mold
yeah exactly and then and then i can
switch or switch your real brain with
the butter brain and then that's actual
like that's the more use out of the
butter brand in my brain
it's probably just as smooth as the
other one
i told you i was going to give your
brain a mess massage because you've been
working so hard you did
thank you yeah yeah i can i can
pulverize your brain remember i beat up
the warden and i'm pretty sure i'm
pretty pretty good
please pulverize me santa
and a big big pulverizer you know just
take me in the blender and give me a few
spins one
are you a big shark now i am officially
400 and what 4
i think
um so close to your first billion
that's what i tell when that's when i
want to talk to my chat and they're like
oh guru i'm so old i'm 35 or something
i'm like you haven't even hit your first
hundred or thousand
no you're telling me i haven't heard my
first billion so
yeah i mean like when you have fun when
you have fun with your friends it goes
in a blink of an eye right
[Music]
and with you it's always fun
1000 it's a bit of a blur so i don't
know how you can keep count
i don't know how to count i don't know
how do you
count
no idea
you'll just be you're just a big shark
now thank
um
over our heads
um in my mind yes but physically
unfortunately no
we know
the
space australia sharks if you're a
smaller shark you are the big sharks
wait what food chain
yes
sorry you better be a big shark
um wait oh my god they're gonna look at
me like i'm a sardine
wait i'm not i don't taste very good i'm
very stringy very very lean very very
stringy not much meat
well clog your gills up it so it won't
be good they won't eat me i'll bite them
i haven't been marinated with my um
brain butter yet this is that you need
to
preheat your grill to like steady for
what is it 200 celsius or something
[Music]
i was gonna say thank you but i guess
like thank you for
being the legendary
most special beloved shock
of the universe
i hope that
you are you have a lot of fun today and
everybody tells you how much we all love
you because you deserve it
thank you
bye-bye big hug goodbye big sana
big hugs big
because
[Music]
i refuse to get emotional chat i refuse
i refuse i refuse i want to get
emotional i was like emotional we used
all the emotional juice last time
correct
no more emotional juice
no
now we wait
ah
[Music]
how are you
i'm good how about you i am very good
very happy
nice nice nice i have gift for you
you do
yeah
how did you know
wait what how did
nani i knew it
nami how did you know
because i also love to eat
means so great so
you also are a mint chocolate yeah
one of us
some people say it tastes like
toothpaste
japanese almost japanese say that
but i love it i love it too
yeah
[Music]
hi can i ask you a question
yeah for sure you wanted english or
japanese
which one
which
well it's okay english okay
okay hmm
what was your first impression of me
uh
guru senpai
so first impression is
uh
i think uh
you have the shy
personality
yeah
it's so shy but
i think very cute and
very kindness
when i
talk
start talk with you
so
i love your personality
yeah
market mortgage friendly
mm-hmm with you so
um
thank you though that's so sweet
ah you too sweet
my face is burning now
bright red
[Music]
please eat a lot today i will eat
i will eat enough for everybody
yeah are you ready
everybody i'll eat ah everything
yes ellie do you want to eat me
okay
have a nice day
thank you
isn't she cute
i am blushing though guys i'm very
bright red
we knew this was gonna happen i've
actually been blushing on and off all
day today um
so i think
i think i've been nervous about this for
a while so this um should be interesting
um i'm trying to keep my cool um
guys
look at all my
stuff
look at this stuff in the name
lynch tank my collection is complete
what's the next stinky
smelly
hello
[Music]
[Applause]
god has entered the chat
tommy zama
did you try this
mod city senpai
i love you
[Music]
i love you matsure
god
[Music]
[Applause]
bye
i'm so red i'm so red
oh my gosh
oh
power color
how long
how old
[Music]
mina
i hope i have enough room for
all my stuff
ah there's the stinky i was expecting
hold on
hello um
happy birthday
and
congrats i'm so sick of the morph meme
people congrats on four more billion
subscribers
you tortured soul i can hear it in your
voice
i know
oh you typed it out though
dummy i know you even i know how did you
know did you barf when you typed it did
you like have to breathe into a paper
bag well you type that too
i felt my stomach turn but you know
i had to
like there was an opportunity and i had
to take it but anyway i'd be more
brilliant
happy
oh i almost said happy more billion
again happy
happy birthday thank you happy yeah
and
like
i hope you're having a good birthday and
everything and
like are you good
overall
wait what more i'm saying i think you
more of your discord and more
oh god dammit um so are you gonna do
anything for your birthday
eat strawberries
oh you like strawberries i really do
right now they just
taste like
candy
oh i know right you like strawberries
you should have like ice cream like
strawberry how about strawberry
cheesecake ice cream oh yes
or i'll treat you
wait what about cheesecake with
strawberries and then ice cream on the
side so it's like
yeah oh no no oh you want it separate
because it's a you know okay okay i can
do that
i can make arrangements yeah i use a
piece of cheesecake and then you dip it
in strawberry sauce so like it's a
strawberry shell around the edge oh
like a
strawberry fondue kind of thing
exactly
yeah
we can melt like
[Laughter]
and strawberry be like runny jam with
cheesecake
i was thinking
chocolate strawberry chocolate oh no he
makes oh no i don't know
how to melt chocolate the right way
there's a special word for it i don't
know what it is
there's a special word for it yeah when
you melt chocolate
tempering when you temper chocolate
oh i know it's just like felt chocolate
yeah you can stick it in the microwave
and hit a button
oh
no that's dangerous
but
i don't know i've never tried it do you
want to try it let's try it tell me how
it goes let's try to get
i'll use you as my human shield just in
case we get sparkies in the microwave
ah that'll be wonderful but you don't
you don't have to like that's very
generous if you but
yeah
like
if we
if we ever like you know
meet up or something strawberry
is on me
yeah
yeah all right like ichigo
we go ichi go to the ice cream store
i can't believe oh gosh
ichigo
to the farmer's market stand and buy
yourself some strawberries
yeah i guess that pun was explosive
internet is out of control but yeah
i'm gonna go now okay
thank you cody
yeah happy birthday show me
destiny
and we got some crow nichi morbius thank
you stop
okay
inside
stop
hello
[Music]
konnichiwa
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
today i am the birthday princess
yes yes
princess and the king
and king
king you are king today's king today is
king the birthday king of the day
yes oh today's the main shaku
[Music]
yay
mario party
[Music]
i am not brave enough because i am not
so good at english myself
mario party et cetera
[Laughter]
let's play mario party someday oh puppy
again
hi hi
i watched your 3d
thank you you are very
cute
very cute
[Music]
thank you for my birthday
crown yes
uh
i want to sing with you someday oh yes
please
i love your voice too your new original
song
oh
let's pray together some time yeah
yes
that's collaboration
[Music]
happy birthday
happy
oh my gosh your voice is like pure sugar
hi
no that's
oh that's pure sugar and strawberries
seriously though your voice is so sorry
i just have to get i have to tell you
this your voice is so
addicting to listen to it is so velvety
smooth
with just so much sugar
it's like
it's like um
massage for the brain
i'm telling you that's too much i'm the
one getting complimented and it's not
even my birthday your voice is amazing
senpai i have a present for you present
oh thank you
i'll send it on dm's okay uh i'm uh i'm
a little bit of a dumbest i forgot to
make a png i'm sorry
okay i understand
i hope you can stop my
jpeg i guess eat jiggle
oh thank you
nothing special of it
happy birthday it is special it comes
from you you took the time to make it
for me it's very special thank you zeta
welcome i added one more extra
strawberry in there just to make it a
little
sweeter it's not for us to share you and
me
want me to hear me let's share
let's play something together sometime
oh
yeah yeah yeah we should play something
together
that would be awesome yes please
please
[Music]
yes yes but do you want to play though
do you like minecraft are you playing a
lot of minecraft lately
oh yeah i do like minecraft yeah yeah
yeah yeah
um
explore the new update or something
we should do that yeah i think um
we can probably play minecraft yeah that
would be fun yeah
[Music]
i was gonna say earlier happy almost 1
billion years
yeah thank you
you're um send fire
three more you need three more billion
years to be older than earth i feel like
am i correct
earth is
wait how many six billion
earth is six billion years old
is it four point five i don't know it's
a big one wait three point wait what did
you say three
one numbers three point three one two
three billion plus three more four point
five million more billion did you say
more billion or billion
more billion
okay earth is like 4.5 but that's
according to google
4.5 more billion years old
[Music]
ah that's all right you know the older
the older you get the easier it is to
accept that you're getting older
i've come to learn
it all gets time flies bye you get nicer
exact well
maybe wiser but not smarter
unfortunately
that's debatable
maybe like life experience as you get
smarter
that's true
um
i i guess we can maybe play minecraft or
maybe like
games or any nintendo games any anything
i would love to
play a horror game with you i love scary
games i would love to
what's your favorite have you played
like outlast
oh yeah i actually recently finished
outlast two and it was
it was okay it was pretty good
yeah
yeah have you played the original
not yet
i i skipped through it i know very
very weird i skipped through it but i
was so excited for our last two and i
was like oh okay i'll do outlets two and
then one
i understand yeah
do you like horror games and i love
horror games scary games
that's cool
i want to play poppy playtime really bad
have you seen that one
oh my god i've seen that one poppy yeah
yeah yeah with like the red blue hands
maybe someday
maybe someday that game's perfect for
you
[Music]
all right thank you santa
thank you as well happy birthday again
thank you
bye-bye
[Music]
hello
congratulations on your birthday and 4
million shark
my soul happiness
is your feeling
thank you so much
thank you so much thank you for coming
and calling into my birthday as well
thank you of course so why not so
yeah so you're very
happy jerk yesterday
very happy today very happy i'm being
very spoiled by all the senpai and the
kohai today
you know i remember
that you were born with
you like your
sense of humor
or um the choices of kalauki stream i
love your choices of songs oh you do you
listen to my karaoke
yeah so
i usually work
oh i i usually work so
with your karaoke stream so
please do many times
oh you listen to guru radio
yeah a great ear is the best i think oh
my gosh thank you
thank you so much
wow i'm so i don't know have we ever
spoken one-on-one before
yeah
i have we have spoken
personally i don't like this i know i've
been together with you in uh like group
chats and stuff but
yeah yeah yeah you still remember we we
remember so um
summer
yeah you're having having a
opportunities to virtual maybe it um
it's the first time to
speak so dialectically or
when versus work
versus
yeah i get a ton all to myself today
yes so i'm glad so
in a very ballyard's meeting thank you
thank you later
yeah
you want me to can i ask you a question
can i ask what your favorite food is i
like the food topic
family food
of course
i love um
okay hot spicy spicy curry or spicy
something i love and how harvard do you
like
spicy food yeah too spicy food i love
birds so if you
will come to japan so can i
can i take
you spicy curry on like a scale of one
to ten though how spicy ten being like
oh my god or one baby
i recommend you to
have so the spiced one okay i know my
favorite curry in in japan so
please that's together yes please i love
curry so okay okay nice collaboration
great collaboration
i know you um you don't have to so
endure you don't have to do so
ever so
i i'm glad if you
if we have some opportunity to
helen to arena or
yeah i'm i hope you
um will come
to japan soon
i will come just to have a curry with
you
okay
thank you so
you so much
thank you so much thank you
and i hope you
um i hope you can do what you what you
want this year more and more
of course yeah
again have a nice day and
have a great year
of course
see you later
yeah thank you so much and anywhere so
happy birthday and congratulations
thank you
[Music]
yeah we work together with umichi but i
think this was the first time that
i've ever had it on all to myself you
know what i mean
like group stuff little groups yeah but
like all to myself
that's the privilege of being the
birthday girl i guess you could say
somebody else here now hello hey
hey you
yo
hello anya hello it's been oh my god
it's been 10 bazillion years it's been
so long how are you it's been so long
i'm good i've been doing good how about
you it's your birthday today how is it
going it's good
it's very good nice thank you so much oh
happy birthday
thank you
happy birthday happy birthday
it's it's been so long it's really been
so long it really has we should play
something yeah
yeah totally
you have like do you have something you
want to play
um
yeah i mean anything really what's your
let's go go-to's lately
[Music]
just for genre
um
if it's i don't know if it's collab
games maybe we can do a cool off game oh
but i saw you play um that game with the
ends um what was it again prop 9 yeah
prop 9.
i don't i'm not sure if that game is
like good enough to do it like two
people because
unless you want to play you want to play
a game that we can do with all of us
or we can invite the others
anything works for me
you know yeah anything else is fun you
like prop night yeah problem is fun
it's such a fun game
like prop 9.
can i
can i ask you the famous what was your
first impression of me question i'm like
my first impression of you
um i like how you
do um what was it again um i think you
did
um hand dry thing and driving on your
debut was it yeah
yeah i like that i thought it was super
cute
thank you
i think you were more space on your
debut
definitely because i was like yeah
because i was like oh she's just so cute
she's such a stay so short
i love her
yeah
i don't know you get comfortable and
then the say so layer starts coming off
slowly like a banana peel and then all
your left i mean that happens to
everyone i think yeah definitely i
remember what happened to everyone
during my debut i was i didn't think
about this but with the handwriting i
was so nervous i was shaking so badly um
that i had to like i'd have the the pen
pressure oh no no the pen stability up
to like all max percent because i was so
nervous of shaking so badly
oh my god i feel that
why am i doing this i can see how
nervous i am because my hand is shaking
i feel that my writing is shaking come
on
i was also really nervous on our first
collab
i was super super super nervous super
duper nervous we played that by daylight
right
yeah we played dead by daylight
yeah i remember i forgot to mute my mic
was oh my god yeah you're like i can't
hear her but she doesn't know what i get
and when you told me that i'll go by the
way you didn't meet your mic i got so
scared yeah yeah
you muted yourself on obs but you didn't
mute yourself on this court so i could
hear it from my side i was like oh
oh is she okay hopefully hopefully
things are okay for her
oh girl don't say anything you're stupid
now
oh my god
it was funny though it was cute it was
good
nothing you buying happened so it's okay
oh
thank you anya
yeah thank you too oh also also i think
i also asked this question on our first
collab but how old are you now oh god um
nine
nine thousand nine
nine no nine nine thousand one thousand
nine
000 something okay something something
like that 480 something
all right i don't even remember your
answer on our collab maybe i don't know
i will check later yeah i don't think
anyone anyone does
i don't think anyone does
yeah just some funny numbers exactly
yeah
happy birthday thank you anya
oh i'll be taking my leaf now then okay
let's let's play something again
together hi
hmm
[Music]
isn't on your cute anya is another
there's another hall i remember with a
super sugary sweet voice
on the uh
who doesn't know her own age exactly you
must be new here
that's not news
and guru doesn't know a lot of things
did i why
my name is
[Music]
hi
happy birthday
happy birthday to you
a happy birthday to you a happy birthday
here
goodbye
happy birthday to you
thank you very much
how's it going oh my god i was listening
um while eating breakfast and then i was
like i wanna call i gotta go i'm gonna
miss it
wow what did you have for breakfast
i had
a waffle a croissant
a croissant waffle
oh croissant waffle she's like is that
waffle
oh a quaffle like the cronie oh yeah oh
is it a cronut oh a quaffle i don't know
croissant doughnut a cronut
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's a crony mixed with a donut a cronut
a cronette breath
yeah i had um
what was on it bacon cheese corn
bacon cheese and corn
yeah
yeah yummy i've never had a savory
waffle before
way really i only get savory waffles
whipped cream and strawberries
oh
yeah
i'm not a sweet plant
i mean i love it from time to time yeah
i'm weird i don't know i'm very salty
as a
yeah in both meaning i'm sorry
um yeah it's the salt intake i swear to
god it's making it just made me into a
very salty rat how many milligrams a day
you have of salt
i don't know my kidneys i'm
sorry okay
love you you only need one so that's
just true
don't do that everybody
don't do that think of your your kids
kidneys guys thank you for your blood or
something
yeah oh my god are you having a good
birthday i'm having a i'm having a good
birthday
kind of stressed me out but other than
that i'm
oh my god you know this morning i
actually forgot to set an alarm and i'm
so proud of myself i woke up um because
i think your stream started at 10 for me
and then i didn't send an alarm last
night and i woke up at 9 47 i was like
my internal clock knows it's got his
birthday i'm gonna be awake internal
alarm did you dream about your alarm
going off like did you hear your alarm
going off in your head
i literally just like snapped awake and
i was like oh hold on what time is
it
it's gooby time
time i wish my internal clock was better
mine used to be really good but now it's
not
i've grown immune to my own internal
clock and also my my alarm
oh my god do you turn your llamas in
your sleep and then you wake up and
you're like what yes the hell happened i
never i never thought i would be one of
those people that does that but i am now
one of these people i am now those
people
i hear oh no no i listen to it and then
it's like music i'm just like oh music
oh
and then you fall back asleep yeah and i
fell asleep to it
you gotta get like the classic iphone
like alarm the one that goes
it is now music i've heard it so many
times it's now just white noise i just
mute it in my head no
oh there's also one that just like it's
like a siren
bam
maybe you can like you probably have it
like rotating so you don't get too used
to the same one
oh
well i have edm as my alarm so
edm
yeah
as a smooth jazz is an alarm
the worst alarm smooth jazz
that is true oh my god speaking of like
smooth i was watching you around 4
million karaoke every single time i'm
like you know there's no she's already
an amazing singer i can't get any more
blown away than i am and then i heard
you sing killing me wasn't killing me
soft i don't is that the song i don't
know i don't know english music
i was like in tears shaken on the ground
it was so
thank you
thank you i watched actually speak of
karaoke i listened to you sing koi
i'm one of your karaokes because i was
like stalking your karaokes to see what
songs you sing because i was trying to
like oh my god learn new music through
you by listening to you sing and i was
telling you
music
let me see what bass playing because
bae's got a good taste we see
everybody does that
like when you're playing
i look up you and i look up iris i'm
like what are you guys singing oh my god
i need new songs that's what i do
iris as well
yes
oh my god
[Music]
thank you
i want to sing
oh my god happy birthday i'm so happy
for you congratulations on everything oh
my god you're there you're like you're
popping off you're always open enough
but like recently you got like the ring
the the night circulation and then you
hit four million oh my god it's been
it's been crazy yes
i'm so proud of you
[Music]
me
anyway happy birthday i'll get out just
told this other
person oh my god like this next person
they enter chat and i was like this is
the most awake i've ever heard them but
anyway happy birthday
thank you
thank
if it wasn't crony who was she talking
about
who could it be
the most awake
hold up
take two
[Music]
how are you laughing when you play it
it's it's the thumbnail i don't have to
use my use my breath to play it it's all
in the it's on the fingers goomba i
thought wait i thought you
no you just like hold the finger and
just place the note
it's like guitar except you like
you know it plays on its own
how are you
i am
i am good
okay
here
positive
you biting your lips
[Music]
oh cracker girl
so i'm gonna give you a big hug and a
pad on the head i could use one of them
i'll send one over email thank you
thank you
for calling and saying happy birthday
no
any time
[Music]
it's like
when i was just sitting alone in the uh
and
the waiting room i was like okay
dude i'll tell my tone i'm gonna tell
her all these things but i forgot i
gotta say
you have a wonderful wonderful aura
around you thank you what color is my
aura today ina
uh
i forget it's the forgettieora spaghetti
url what flavor with that yeah
my friend literally can't think right
now
you know
come on break yeah
i can't i feel like i just haven't
talked to people in a very long time and
i've just forgotten human speech
you speak in automaton now
yeah basically do you can you try do you
speak automotive i mean i can i can
oh no because i thought you breathed
through it oh okay so okay i'll i'll
leave that for google translate later
but
um i just want to say
happiest happiest greatest birthday for
our
smallest cutest softest shark
um
it's been
man it's already been here you know
you're already more than nine thousand
something years old so you probably lost
count of all the all the years but i
hope that
the upcoming one is the most memorable
year
for you the most happiest filled with
love
lots of good food and company
and um if you ever
do you think have
can always
so i'll be i'll be here
i don't know where i'm going with this
but
love you a lot
eat lots of good food
um i keep saying food but
i mean literally food i mean birthdays
are about food you know
exactly exactly it's on their birthday
so
um i don't know maybe i can
i can order taco eats for you someday or
something in the near future i don't
know
we'll see it we'll see i must i must
also say um
thank you so much for all the help that
you've given me for the past well since
since the start of it all but uh thank
you
um
i can count quite a few times i've gone
running to you
oh my god you're gonna help me
oh you're always
to help
even withdrawn
um step-by-step instructions hand-drawn
from my brain so thank you so much
[Laughter]
it's okay i i know the feels when when
your brain just you know refuses to work
yeah
so sometimes a little little diagram
helps
i'm always happy to help you girl
thank you yeah
happy birthday thank you
okay okay i'll i'll i'll leave you now
all righty
with your shrimps okay i did have shrimp
for dinner today anyways um
okay bye okay bye
[Music]
okay i have something from
shion
[Music]
bye
she is busy busy busy
uh so she don't give me this
ceo
wow
for me
it's so big
what a big rock you've given me
wow look at this oh man it looks too
heavy for my finger shield
maybe i can use it as like a napkin ring
wow look at that how many carrots do you
think that is
a lot of beta carotene in there
put it right here
happy birthday
let's get married
well with this giant rock how could i
say no
okay guys
um i don't i don't i don't know
uh
uh i have my list
one two three four five uh all right
there might be more
people calling in i don't know uh quite
so
oh
wait
hmm
[Music]
is it bad that i always send emojis back
first like i always send emotes back
first like oh i guess then i'll send
like five right now unfortunately my
brain speaks some pictures
and then and then and then
and then and then i'm sending a
thank you guys so i wanna i wanna say
thank you to you guys as well for
keeping me company today
um on my on my on my birthday
and um wait a minute
watching the stream
sorry my brain just put two and two
together
yo
[Music]
hi
sorry my brain is overwhelmed i got that
though afterwards
wow
god damn it dude
i'm sorry is this is it is it time for
sora i'll be back after no
no until it's it's
okay sorry i just woke up
i just woke up to my late alarm i'm
sorry oh we were just talking about
alarms it's okay what's your what's your
alarm song do you have like the apple
mine goes
that's that one
like android or something
i don't know
yeah
it's kind of cursed at this point i hate
it i hate the sound of it i want to
break my phone
yeah
you better be like
yeah would be pretty bad that's why i
can't put songs that like
my favorite song is my ringtone no the
is wrong with you what are you
doing because then you speak vibe into
it and not actually do anything exciting
yeah exactly
nice song gonna go back to sleep
that's nice to sleep too thanks for
calling in oh my god you're welcome it's
goombas it's your birthday goombas
what gum a whole new yeah
yeah i know right i'm so
i'm so happy for you i'm proud of you
thank you you're always doing cool
and um
i know that you're gonna keep killing it
this next year too
uh
and yeah i'm just
i'm super proud of you i
i was gonna
sing you happy birthday
but
my voice is
awful awful right now like it's i should
not be singing anything
hard working
business lady getting done getting
done i guess it would be like that
you know a little
just a little bit
but nah seriously um
seriously you've been doing so much cool
cool and i'm just i'm proud of you
thank you
of course
yeah i mean recently you recently got
the big the big four which is the best
number in the world that's right it's
people even somewhere it's like if it's
my fave number and so i just felt extra
extra proud of you and i was like hell
yeah
girl is also getting done too and
uh
we all love you very much um
i'm glad that there's somebody else who
is you know not not the strongest in
math
um
but can do a bunch of other that
makes up for it absolutely
[Music]
girl
yeah it means a lot when you're coming
from you it means a lot because i i know
how
great well i kind of know how crazy busy
your schedule is like all the time and
has been since your birth
so
i don't know thank you it means a lot
coming from you so
thank you oh man
oh geez
thanks guerra i mean it's the truth
seriously so wait but i don't know what
but wait
i wait that's that's me
turn it around i look up to you too man
i look up to you
this i guess something like that you
know what that that's a nice thing
actually
appreciation
yeah
yeah that's really cool actually french
i'm glad
i think that
is so cringy
is this good quench for you so no it's
not it's not going for me if it's not
queen for you
yeah exactly
same same that's right it's only cringe
if you call it cringe out in the open
exactly
leaving words means they don't exist
that's exactly you just refuse to
acknowledge it and you're fine amen
yeah just don't look in your closet the
monster is there shut the up go to
sleep
yeah
exactly yeah
i'm gonna
yeah i'm gonna die um and let
flora senpai come say happy birthday
thank you
you're happy
thank you for calling me
well you're welcome happy birthday girl
we love you bye
you best first
i love kawaii
kawaii morrison
clubby
[Music]
i know you guys want to be the hello
hello i'm talking
happy birthday
to senpai
oh it's a
for mario and the happy birthday
wow
it
i'm always watching your stream
really
wow
thank you wow
you are
i look up to you a lot of somebody
thank you i love you i love your singing
i like your minecraft streams too
minecraft
yeah yeah i'm i'm always as your stream
uh minecraft
you like my minecraft streams
yeah um grad minecraft stream um i love
thank you
wow
so doesn't bite
hi
come on yes i have a question for you
uh yes
um um
minecraft aura
uh do you like horror game
yes hi yes
yes
um
and it's prey let's play a
horror game
[Applause]
yes
no
okay
play with me
[Laughter]
[Music]
and cute
uh
[Music]
chocolate cake
oh
yes
cupcake very good mmm
very good
very good i hope we can
enjoy
games and cake together someday
oh yes
yes this is sunday um
hi
[Music]
bye
[Applause]
guys i'm buzzing hold on
sorry my brain
calipers is that what it is
my count my brain calipers are firing on
all cylinders
i'm okay
i'm gonna sip some water also hold on
i got a message from manage manager one
second
hey
okay this
okay that's recalibrating hi
this is
me
manager is uh helping me um a lot so
thank you very much um
waiting for i see i see we have more
more company
i'm just waiting
who will jump in first
thank you guys by the way for hanging
out with me
thank you thank you
hello
hello goodness empire
it's okay
yeah yeah i'm so happy yeah yeah thank
you yeah it's okay
yeah
thank you happy birthday
thank you so much
yeah
yeah i just uh yeah i'm really good i
just finished streaming and i just came
straight forward so you're
i saw him what's up
i watch your stream schedules when you
post them
yeah play a lot of games you stream like
a lot
yeah i really
like playing games so much here so
yeah passion for video games which one
is your favorite
um
the games hi yes game
yeah
most favorite one is actually league but
oh
yeah
[Music]
not really i'm not that good though
no
how can you not be competitive and you
play league that league was like super
sweaty
yeah it's super sweaty though but i'm
trying so bad not to be toxic yeah i'm
not toxic
yes so maybe yeah probably we can play
um do you play like lee no yes i've
never played league before
uh i see i see would you be willing to
teach me how to play wig
yeah yeah we can do like um the pc one
probably i'm playing the mobile one
actually but um yeah we can try probably
try to play the pc one yeah it would be
great
will you will you teach me how to be
toxic like what's what's the best way to
get under a league player's skin like
what is that
if you can say
oh
you want to be toxic yeah teach me how
if you know
oh
how do i be toxic in league
i don't know i i feel like
i feel like um
i don't know um
chad is saying stop feeding is feeding
something
no actually league players is like we
have like some feature of we keep
spamming the
the pink
we can yeah the pink so we can
the not the ping the like 999 ms one but
the question mark ping we get that kind
of uh feature and league so
like we can spam so if someone's died
probably you can just spam the question
mark pink
and uh
in the dead body yup yup yup you die
question mark
yeah yeah question mark question mark
like uh
what did you do how how you died like
that it's kind of yeah yeah
it's like just being a very simple toxic
without uh
without any single uh words you can just
do that yeah spam the question more pink
yeah
yeah i think you can
text me anytime if you want to try oh
yes
yeah sure yes please
okay sure yeah yeah yeah
thank you
i think so oh and um by the way i wanna
say congratulations for reaching of five
millions it's so amazing
bye bye
she's so cute
she is so cute she is
so cute
her voice is so nice
i'm i'm a little speechless right now
and um
okay
okay it's fine it's lime five million
five million
um
we just got the portal guys
shouldn't we enjoy now
[Music]
did you go next mentality
that's your cool hype yeah but
no no it doesn't
feel
hello
[Music]
happy birthday how are you today how are
you doing you i am doing i'm okay
i'm hungry
mmm i just woke up too i'm hungry
for breakfast today
you have a lot of cakes though the
cupcakes and the birthday cake and the i
don't know is that a flower is that what
is that the fish bouquet
it's a fish bouquet
do you eat fish
yes
yes very delicious you can also eat the
fish at the back or are there sharks oh
i don't know but yes
i will eat my own i'm not afraid of
cannibalism you're not afraid of
cannibalism that's the spirit that's
great i mean you know
i am a very opportunistic consumer
you know anything that makes the stomach
full you know you need that survival
skills people always tell me reina you
eat the chicken reena you eat or
something you know what you know it's
fine right as long as you know
it tastes good do you like chicken skin
this is really round
chicken skin um
i guess
i guess i don't know like
crispy crispy chicken skin
maybe it could be
i'll eat it if it's crispy but if it's
soggy it might be a little thick
[Music]
ah
i see i see i see it's like yeah some
people are like oh they like the chicken
skin but only if they're like the not
crispy kind some people like the chicken
skin yeah yeah yeah yeah it's all like
wibbly wobbly and
jiggly
yeah i don't know i don't know maybe
they like it jiggly or something i don't
i don't really know but yeah um
very random question great to be able to
know your opinion about it
i guess we should have chicken skin
together sometime
we should
i like chicken skin yeah yeah yeah yeah
chewy skin is good too or i don't know
yeah people's opinions chewy chewy what
if there's still feathers in it
feathers
we have to clean we have to like take
out all the feathers thoroughly before
eating it i don't know
i don't like feathers i don't like
eating feathers maybe some people like
eating feathers
um it sounds like you hurt like you stab
the top of your mouth and you have like
a feather stuck in your mouth
oh
wow like stuck in your owl i don't want
to think about it
by the way i think i've only like seen
you around and we're like prepping mario
kart etc i don't think we've ever like
talked no we've talked in dms before but
like not really but not really like
talking talking like this yeah it's our
first one-on-one voice
i'm nervous wait not really but you know
i'm nervous i'm nervous
i'm very nervous but
it's okay so far
so it's okay so far yeah
there's a bunch of people calling right
yeah congratulating you happy birthday
and also for m 4 million subscribers
that's amazing oh thank you
thank you
yeah play something sometime
like we should we should we should i saw
you you know i always like seeing you
when you're like on when you're like on
vr especially with the small avatar it's
not cute
i always said i was i'm chad i'm barfing
it's always barfing time for me dude you
have vr
oh yeah i do actually you like it
um yeah i do as long as i don't move
around so much as long as i don't throw
up i mean that's all right oh yeah i
could
unless
i don't know maybe once you get it all
out of your system you can keep going so
you just keep like a barf bag nearby and
then you barf you're still in vr
and be like excuse me guys and then
press the cuff button and like hi guys
i'm back you know what happened oh no
nothing
the people in this chat is like please
don't mute next time
please let me know
i don't know
special asmr um
barfing asmr anyone
yeah well you know what the people want
no you know you're not getting that
sorry guys
no no all right then i get no
name but not
want me
well you know um
well also i want to thank you i want to
thank you oh my gosh it's it's like it's
like the things i always wanted to say
but then i can and i'm like oh my god i
finally can talk to guru now and i'm
gonna say everything i'm gonna say
everything also the uh the noise
complaint the minecraft thing thank you
for writing it it meant a lot to me
oh
this this the stuff the fan fiction
where you wrote a lot about feet
it was fun dang it was it was i mean how
could i not it was so perfect i had to
it was perfect amazing i love it thank
you so much for watching your entire
book when are you publishing your entire
everything um
nah that's that's i think that's only
for the vancoroni but maybe i'll i'll
write something new and publish it maybe
maybe amazon best mailer
may have feet it may not have feet but
it wouldn't be a surprise potentially
potentially
someone should be illustrated
illustrated yeah
yeah very nice
feet
not feet i mean you know look yes
yeah i hope you have a very very very
great birthday i think like oh my gosh
so many people lighting up
i don't want to take out too much of
your time have a great birthday girl
thank you
[Music]
oh man
i think i think a bunch of people just
woke up um
oh god
um
is that the sweet voice of the singing
goddess
[Music]
birthday
thank you
how are you
i'm final how are you
i have been while we haven't talked
it has been a while
yeah it has been a while i don't
remember when the last time we fall i
think it might have been
it's wow
i've been meaning to ask you though i
want to sing together and i want to play
minecraft again together because you
know a lot about minecraft like the the
door that you built cronie
uh yeah you're a minecraft genius and i
want you to teach me your ways i want to
join your
do you have a minecraft construction
company
well
i don't have my own construction company
but i joined one i think
can i be your personal minecraft intern
yeah
oh i'll be happy to teach you something
i will be your underling i will just
follow you and take notes on how you how
you do minecraft
yeah i mean if you want to build
something just tell me
i can't
i can help you
yes something is really cool with like
conduits and stuff
yeah perhaps we can try
it'll be fun now i got
understudy minecraft
minecraft
yeah
minecraft brain thank you for calling in
and saying happy birthday mono
happy birthday and congratulations for
the 4 million subscribers
thank you so much
yeah
and and also um
i i love
your original music
thank you
i hope in the future we can we can do we
can make uh
our own together yes please
high tide is incredible your voice is so
powerful i uh chills every time i get
chills
your voice your voice is like
it's it's calming
i really like it
i wish i had the power though that your
voice has you just have that like
superstar voice you know what i mean
thank you
i i also feel the same way i wish i have
your style of the same because your
voice is so unique i really like it like
it doesn't need an afford to sing it's
like
every time you you try to sling in slow
and and kind of valid things it's sweet
very well
i love it
thank you so much
well i think um that's all uh
happy birthday again
there's a lot of people waiting
so cool
is
[Music]
waiting
here a person for you oh
wait what
wait wait wait no no no no let me send
the p the png wait i need the png
[Music]
happy birthday that's right you said you
had to go pretty fast uh that's okay
thank you
yeah sorry sorry i don't have much time
here but here uh this present for you i
wish you have a great day today i love
you i love your sharpness and i love
your guru
gr grandness
thank you bye
yeah she sent me a message beforehand
saying that she's really tight on time
which is okay but like she gave me a
pair of soul
umbrella
hello
[Music]
how are you
i'm fine
thank you
and you i am
good welcome but good
you got that
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for your time and kravo
and me minecraft thank you
master
yes
yes listen
i remember that listen to that message
oh yes
[Music]
thank you i got those hi you're watching
my 3d life hi hi hi
hi hi my
thank
i'm so glad and happy
[Music]
what your first impression of me was
oh okay okay okay okay
so i'm not good at speaking english
and five so what
kind of
food do you like so i don't know so
please ask me
[Music]
do i
um
so
so so
so cute and so very
kind
typical fast collaboration
i'm so very nervous
but
you you talked to me
i'm very happy i'm not good at that
i'm happy
talk to me
[Music]
my japanese
is us talking to you i am very so happy
happy birthday have a nice day grace and
bye thank you
[Music]
she's so cute
adorable samurai yes
okay
oh
[Music]
i
have a gift
for you
but how do i give it to you
oh this is cool dog
yeah
yes
video
a message message
okay
for you happy birthday present
yes thank you for
[Music]
hi
ah
is very
very cool and
cute and beautiful
i want this in next time
together
oh
[Music]
happy birthday
ah
[Music]
thomas
yes
[Music]
m
i'm sorry
foreign
[Music]
good morning
good morning happy birthday
thank you chloe
yeah yeah yeah how are you today
oh
[Music]
yes
four million fine
yeah congratulations
thank you
thank you so much chloe
yeah
[Music]
i shared
uh
you
said i love
love
senpai hi
hmm
yes i also love
see you soon
yeah
i think us
we thank us
for
you are very cute also chloe
i also watched your 3d debut
oh
really
yeah i'm nervous
very cute curled on the floor though
why
very lot lot of mistake
really
yeah mickey
[Music]
we
hi
hi please don't eat me
no
maybe a little bit just a little bit
only if you can beat me in mario kart
mario kart
if you beat me in mario kart
then you can eat me
[Music]
little
not without mario kart
you must beat me first
of all
you're so cute chloe oh my goodness
i want to eat okay my dream
well listen bye if it's your dream then
okay
you eat okay
[Music]
happy birthday thank you chloe
she's so cute
i'm getting cute aggression guys how do
i stop that i just have to like
you know
man how do you guys watch all these cute
girls at the time do you also have cute
aggression
sorry in my stomach i'm really hungry
all of a sudden i wasn't hungry because
i was so nervous about this dream but
now that i'm kind of just all right you
know
a lot less less nervous now i'm hungry
i can't hear my own stomach i'm trying
to talk over it though like i'm trying
to talk when i hear a start going wrong
but then i try and speak over anyway
we have two more guests it seems
[Music]
so cute
cute vampire
hello hello
hi hi
what's up
what's up for you
what are you doing
thank you
you're welcome i have a gift for you
a gift from the room
yeah it's not that
good hold on sorry
i tried to make it
as long as i could long
readable yeah um
write me a poem did you read me a book
uh kind of really
that's it
no
[Music]
you can make it longer if you want well
hold on
oh my god the file is huge
why is it so big
because this had to be long holy
happy
birthday
i also realize this is gonna be this is
not good for
your screen you can make it i'm sorry
[Music]
let me see what this looks like
look now you can actually see how bad it
is
are you saying that it's cute
you're a good artist
it's bouncy
boiling where can i put her
perfectly slides underneath everybody
there we go
looks like somebody's sat on her
squashed
squash
we're like oh i forgot they're called
never mind what
is it like the
you know the thing it crushes things but
like the crushed skittles and stuff with
that oh the pressure
singing yeah yeah it explodes have you
seen when i put like uh jawbones
underneath it
i'm going to google that off now like
all the teeth get blown out
i'm putting in my search bar right now
i can't hear you
pressure
pressure pressure
hydro
thank you sorry okay i got i got it okay
it's good
i will google that thank you we should
get a hydraulic press and just i don't
know mess with it literally
you can get that for your birthday yeah
oh that's a good gift maybe we can
halloween can chip in
oh
thanks for the hydro hydraulic press you
guys it's the first
that's yours enjoy thank you i love it
thank you
you're welcome
uh
i don't
do i get asked a question or should i go
no no i gotta ask you what am i
okay
sorry i'm not sure how this goes i'm not
used to them um let me scroll
which one would you like
i have
three
to be honest i was only able to hear one
um which one was that except i heard
that when you
i could just say yes
yes
what
yeah yeah
all right get one
um
wait no i'm supposed to put you on the
spot there's no wait that's not good
um alex expires tomorrow
okay i'll wait can you extend it a
little bit
just a little bit um
okay you have a month thank you
um thank you the best birthday present
what should we play together sometime
dang it
i play i'll play any game we still gotta
play sea of thieves we do
we still gotta
yeah i gotta i got a little more sea
shanties
yes please oh see shandy's i like sea
shandies
yeah
i will learn them we can all harmonize
we can harmonize oh my gosh quartet
yes okay there's only two of us but i
guess if we know more than we can quit
oh wait that's four
right for court
it's four
okay that's good to know well you didn't
know a court does something
i was just thinking of i don't know i
was just thinking of the sound they make
but you know the singing sound
yeah
yes okay
i can't explain it within the time i'm
given it's okay
i understand i understand
happy birthday thank you
i will leave now thank you
[Music]
um
sorry i'm getting it
ah
okay
waiting for the last person i can't drag
them i wish i could drag people but i
can't
you two together are something else
[Music]
hello
happy birthday
is that good
i wish
who could i be
i don't know i don't i don't know
who is this
is that you
yeah yeah
yo it's your boy it's your boy charlie
what's up
ohio kelly shark
i'm good i'm i was rapping just a while
ago that's why my voice sounds this bad
oh
but i'm good
wow kelly i get two calls thank you iris
i thank you for calling and hi
happy birthday sorry i'm still in bed
right now i can't hear yourself with you
like i heard blake it's wrestling
hmm
it's just for you blanket blanket
wrestling asmr ooh blanket wrestling
wait i said wrestling wrestling
wrestling i said wrestling sentences
wrestling
no it didn't
click somebody roll
the bag clip
ah no please no please no there's no
wrestling going on and wrestling going
on that stuff
thank you oh wwe
oh my god i can't wait to see wwe
more wwe from you that series is like
fantastic i still have to
make you i have to make you and
bae
in wwe
oh
nice man i i you please make me as buff
as possible i will make you massive i'll
do like noel dx i'll be irish digs
yes
please yes please
yes my discord icon is muscle please do
follow that example
um veins on you can it make you like
really veiny yes please
yeah make me a veiny
make way well
pop out all those blue veins
i am feel weird how the body will note
yes
blue veins please blue you wonder what
happens to the red veins do we even have
red veins
maybe no
um
your skin is
the reason why the veins
the blood
because your blood is right inside your
body right
yeah
wait wha what and blood
i don't know it's wait wait wait are all
veins blue
i think it's blue because you're like it
depends on what your skin tone is like
it'll change the color some people have
green veins some people have blue veins
wait chad's saying no as well um
[Music]
oh green veins
yeah
wait why is oh yeah because it's ah
because of the okay okay the skin i see
it oh your way your veins are blue wait
what
yeah they're actually blue
have you seen those like um humans that
they strip the skin off of and you can
see all the blood vessels and stuff
i mean i've seen statues of you know
like in science classrooms not statues i
mean figures in science class with those
stuff i think my my sister's a doctor
but like
i think my sister has
checked a lot of dead bodies before and
um
basically like our fat
is like really yellow it's actually like
super yellow it's disgusting
and then like yeah the veins are
actually super blue like really blue
i i thought it was red too but never
mind
you're
travis and your arteries are red your
veins are blue
[Music]
ah arteries that's nice
to know it's red and blue the big one
colorful it's color-coded so you know
which ones to eat first
oh
uh
um delicious yummy
what are you gonna have for breakfast
today speaking of yummy
speaking of yummy um
probably a banana
i don't eat that much in the morning i
remember i remember i think it was dead
by daylight where you were saying you
had a banana from the fridge
yes because i always eat it from the
fridge the cold banana i remember that
conversation
sorry
it's it's very refreshing you know
like i think the you know the bananas
that they use to make smoothies and
stuff those are frozen bananas so
those are pretty much like i think
freezer bananas right
yeah but you're drinking it
oh wait unless it's like chocolate
covered is that what you mean
i mean
like
yeah chocolate covered too but i mean
like just in general like you know
cold banana is very common i think what
about cold pizza though
ew
wait really ew
of course
like the cheese is the cheese doesn't
stretch right it's like
the chip and the crust
i know and the crust is just like so
it would be so stale if it's cold
i microwaved my pizza
that's the best or you put it in the pan
and then you let the bottom get crunchy
and you put water in it and you steam it
you know did you melt
oh
really you steam your pizza oh yeah that
actually sounds good though yummy
yummy
oh my goodness is that i reminded
oh no
um this has nothing to do with food but
um
since you're like a shark i've been
thinking like i i've wanted to i still
haven't talked to you about this but
like i i wanted to do this like collab
with this i think there was this game i
saw
on our on that list of games you can
play and like um
what was it it was i forgot what it was
called but it's like that one game where
like you either be like the shark or
like the diver and like you like to
fight each other
i think it's called i think it's called
depth
is it called depths yeah i think so too
like it's a multiplayer and like um
i think it's like perfect because you
shark
i would love to play depth i don't know
if we can maybe we should make like a
private server because i don't know if
people play like if it's an online game
i don't know if they're gonna the
servers are alive still i don't know but
have you ever played it before no but
i've always wanted to it's one of the
games i first wanted to play you know
after debuting yeah
oh my god yeah let's do it
depth oh yeah i love like those you know
like how like dead by daylight games and
stuff like that those games where you
basically either kill each other
yes
oh my god props tonight what looked like
so much fun too oh
that was so much fun and then especially
that put prop hunt improv night
really you did yeah so i think it'd be a
lot of fun like a bigger group
of teams oh yeah
oh my god that'd be so much fun yeah
let's do it
uh
let's do it anyways wait is there people
waiting oh wait wait
wait i don't think so
okay good good good
okay
i'm excited
too can i comment
can i comment on how i love your
background of course today
yes it's like i i do wonder how it feels
like to see your breath in and
trapped in a cage and enjoying the view
though how does that feel i laugh
survival of the fittest
because i have a bigger brand oh
yeah smart i have thumbs and they don't
some large shirts
or poor brothers
yeah thumbs are important imagine with
life without thumbs
you can't do anything with your hands
anymore
there's a i was looking this up i don't
know why um but there's actually some
humans are born with like monkey hands
where the thumbs their thumbs don't do
anything they have their thumbs but they
don't do anything
oh like they're the the thumb is like
paralyzed i think so i think that's what
i remember reading
oh you might be wrong that sounds like
really hard
that's
that's really hard to deal with right
all the things you can do interesting
how they still have it though yeah they
just i mean i guess it's good for like
balancing stuff maybe
life without you i don't know like i'm
trying to like i'm currently like like i
tr i have my like thumb just like folded
in so i'm making like the number four
with my hands but like trying to like do
anything without my thumb is just
ridiculously hard like i can't even
grasp my blankets with
four fingers
so it's just like it's like yeah you
can't hold a pencil i don't think you
can really do much yeah no your thumb is
very it's so important
who would have thought that so if you
ever have to sacrifice your finger just
sacrifice your pinky
the pinky is like you can sacrifice it
to anything i think it's kind of it's
like the use least useful finger i think
the pinky
yes the pinky like if you ever get
caught by a an evil gang and they're
like sacrifice your a finger and you
have to chop off your own finger i would
say go with the pinky
yeah i can see it so i'm grabbing stuff
right now
no problem
i think you're pinky but apparently if
you take your toes off it'll mess up
your balance like
that's why people usually get
a fake toes because if you don't have a
toe it like throws your balance all off
oh really
i didn't know that i i always thought
those were kind of useless but okay
no they're very important next time when
you're standing up uh stand up straight
and then lift your toes and it'll like
be sent to your balance this has nothing
to do with balance but just anyway
they're very important
i did not
know that that reminds me i have a
crooked towel
can you show me someday
yes i will give you a picture of myself
wait really
[Applause]
yes i have i have a i have a crooked toe
it's like this thing that i had since
birth but like
it's like i think uh what do you call
this like the
uh the ring toe of my
uh
my right my right foot
it's like i think it's because like when
i was in my mommy's room i i think it
was crooked and i was just born like
that and then my my doctor my baby
doctor told told my parents that oh
it'll get better when she starts walking
but it never got better
it's very crooked but it has never
bothered me in my life being before is
it crooked but i'm pretty much like
stepping
yeah it's like inward so like i'm i'm
stepping on that toe 24 7 pretty much
when i'm when i'm walking but yeah
it it looks a little a little weird but
yes
people don't notice if i don't tell them
but yes i will i will show you my
crooked toe cool
i'll take a picture after i come after i
cut like clipped my toenails yes
yes okay
anyways i think i've been here for a
while so
i'll i'll jump off and cut clip my
toenails so i can send you pics
thank you
iris thank you iris
thanks
i wish
you're welcome yes happy birthday girl
that'll be the perfect birthday present
yay
talk to you again yes but let's go
all righty
okay
happy birthday girl talk to you later
bye
thank you
she's still there she goes
thank you iris
iris
i got my day
uh well guys i also want to say that um
that my birthday stream is tomorrow this
is just a warm up this is the warm-up
match you know the warm-up game girl
this isn't helping your free case let me
have fun
let me have fun fun is okay sometimes
okay
uh tomorrow's stream is gonna be um
pretty pretty freaking cool uh
um
i'm very um
excited also i hope you are all so
excited also tomorrow we are announcing
the merchandise which i'm also freaking
excited for
um i'm excited for a lot but i'm also
very stressed out but anyway i hope you
look forward to um
i hope you look forward to tomorrow's
birthday stream
um
as well
yeah what am i trying to say i'm trying
to
i'm trying to talk was i this bad last
year
was i this bad last year with um talking
i don't know guys
um
anyway uh and you have
never
i seem to be something is
something is happening to me
something is happening
hello
what's done to me what did i do
oh no
why are you done oh my god it's so
sweaty
oh jeez
did i do that
uh
technical difficulties
one second is the time fluctuations
hold on
what do i do
is it because you have a reload okay
yeah it wasn't me
hot in here
dude you
broke it
like who's that and i'm in his chair
it's my office now
yeah um
oh
[Music]
what the heck
oh hold on one
i know i know what it is
land detective is on the case
i mean
wait
hi everybody hi
i'm saying i'm a doco i'm exiting the
time portal
messing with the time i mean
i'm already fixing stuff hey
i was the one who broke it in the first
place
oh
i don't know how i just realized i like
i don't know how that works but
i know it should work really yeah yeah
i'm just here it's just
i'm here hi everybody hi oh wait i can
use your picture yes that works
anyways i'm calling in like normal
oh wait now what oh god
i won
i'm dead
oh no i
[Music]
um
you know what
management can i have um my own picture
if you're watching
we're png's
we are the png's
[Music]
it's uh weird weird um
you know traveling stuff uh
you know what happens mm-hmm
are you pre-recorded right now
am i pre-recorded yeah it's like
pre-recorded
yes this is a pre-recorded message just
to say happy birthday to good uh
uh the message was so powerful it
actually broke the stream
literally people broke at the stream on
my time traveling
um
hold on we can fix it i can fix it
this is off right
wait yes
that means
[Music]
that works
now
oh
i don't know how to erase the data on
this maybe if i
we have pngs it wouldn't do that yeah
that works i could be png
i can also
sorry
okay
and there we go
all right guys hold on
oh wait
[Music]
i think we're good
yay i'm here working back to normal
i'm calling in um i'm definitely calling
in right now on discord
don't you have like a question for me
here's a photo first of all happy
birthday for real
happy birthday
oh my question oh
um what's your first impression of me
first impression like like a like first
first impression like when we were like
close to debut
yeah sure
what's the debut
i don't know i felt like we just we
could just get along like really easily
and
yeah like kind of i don't know in a
weird way like we could almost
communicate without speaking
and yeah we're like we're like on the
same page i don't know it's kind of
weird we're we're like sidekick
sometimes like that one time we're
playing minecraft
and apparently we were like talking to
each other almost but we weren't even in
voice yet i bet she's saying this right
now yeah
are you talking about my my boots isn't
that like the back entrance or something
oh yeah yeah did you make this the back
turn yeah
uh usually for these things you have
like a present or a cool png and i do
have a present but you do yes but it's
after dinner after we eat dinner
maybe
it's something edible which is yeah
virtually edible
virtually edible no it's actually like
legit edible strawberries in it
no but we can make that possible we can
make that happen she brought
strawberries with her
i owe
i want strawberries
okay oh is it oh am i breaking it
no
okay i think i fixed it it worked yeah
um okay
then now i can
hold on guys we're gonna try it
oh yeah
i was wondering why i couldn't see
i'm blind
okay
it work
there it is okay
oh my god
okay
now it's working hopefully wait
yes
no way
finally
um
okay
yeah
i got a chair um
oh god
oh you're so much bigger than me
[Laughter]
i get cake today
well i was just thinking of those videos
where
you know it's like one of those
realistic parts in place
like uh where they turn like an item
into cake
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah that happens there we go
yeah
you got
it
that's good can i talk about like
uh when we were setting up or what i was
saying oh yeah you're not sure
what it was it was i told her it was so
nice to have like a reminder in my head
this voice so much stuff has to happen
and i just couldn't remember anyway hi
hi we're if i could say we're here
i i guess i'm like a special guest or
something is that cheating no i had to
be cheating
oh but yeah i was like i was like a good
siri i was like did you did you get the
thing or did you do the thing
did you do this yet did you do this yeah
that's right
yeah
anyways we're here do we want to say
what we'll
do later today yeah today all right yeah
uh you do it yeah it's your birthday
yeah we're gonna do
karaoke baby hey
karaoke live
live
off collab karaoke
[Applause]
but not right now during this stream
we're going to make another stream it's
going to be after this it'll probably be
on archived right probably yeah i really
have to eat though yes yeah get us
hungry and i got her some cake and we
have i have a dinner prepared so
i was i was busy i took bubba mickey out
for a walk and uh yeah now i i'm gonna
make dinner so we're gonna have rice and
steak and
fancy broccolini
broccolini do you like broccoli
okay okay good that's the broccoli's
fancy brother yeah it's good for you and
it yeah it looks fancy it's like all
long and kind of branchy yeah and maybe
some mushrooms because i showed her i
showed her my mushrooms i'm growing in
in the kitchen
but they're just edible mushrooms
oh yeah bro
no no no you can like saute them yeah
really cool
golden oyster mushrooms oyster mushrooms
yeah they're yellow they're really cute
hmm
mushroom boxes
oh yeah yeah i showed her my terrarium
and stuff she saw the taquerium the taco
bear is so tiny what'd you call it stone
dot t rocket that's not good
is that that's like the best name ever i
think foreign
well soon maybe
you know be moving on to a new home
hopefully
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it's kind of a surprise for you guys but
uh you know that's just how it is and uh
we'll still have fun tonight and who
knows who knows what happened right
you never know
hello i was full of surprises that's
right yeah
sorry i'm hungry
i'm fading wilting like a broccolini oh
yeah you've been working i've just been
relaxing i went out for a nice walk i
mean
found some like wild
you know things outside of pokemon and
stuff picking up weird grass yeah
touching plants yeah hey i want to touch
this
yeah yeah we were walking by some plants
and it looked really soft i was like
look you got to touch it
it was actually soft though wasn't it it
was velvety yeah it was nice
smell this
yeah wait did we do that do we smell
some oh i don't think i smelled
something today it looked like a little
banana
bell it sounds weird but it was a plant
it was a flower
[Laughter]
it wasn't anyways it was just like a
weird
anyways um
[Laughter]
um
like karaoke with channels yeah my
channel yeah we can do it on your
channel it's your birthday after all and
uh oh i just want to say yeah
congratulations
you know the milestone and your birthday
and everything and
also i just think you're really a unique
person it's hard hard to come across you
know something like that
i think i cried last last year
no no no no no it's awkward well maybe
awkward no no just saying because we're
in person so you know maybe you're less
likely to cry because for me that's it
usually
if there's eye contact
god look
i'm not okay okay
anyways you do your thing and yeah we'll
see you guys a bit later i don't know
what time exactly maybe an hour from now
yeah
mm-hmm we have fun mm-hmm
what
oh
yeah we gotta
[Music]
yeah but you play way better i don't
know better than me i don't know any
strumming patterns so really do it yes
you do i've heard it it's like a
but
[Music]
i'm afraid you play your best i can't i
can't play and sing at the same time
it's hard
we have to flip a coin then because i i
don't i don't
i mean we won't only do karaoke because
i think or or we won't only do ukulele
because i don't know how many songs you
know or i know so yeah we haven't really
sorted it out yet but you know what
what's your lives
you guys are excited cute yeah
well uh if you want to say goodbye i'll
uh
get out of here
if you want
i'll just stay here okay
uh anyway guys that's been my birthday
countdown hold some collins talk
tomorrow
um
yeah oh yeah yeah okay um if you guys oh
no wait what am i saying
i'm really hungry um
it's time for me to go but yes uh stream
later today on my channel and then the
big birthday stream tomorrow yay
exciting
very exciting okay um but i am going to
go now though because i really need okay
goodbye
bye
we'll see you guys soon bye
bye bye bye bye thank you for all your
support by the way thank you guys so
much i appreciate it
say goodbye
do
you