​​​ ​The game which shocked the world​ ​​
​​​ ​has finally come to hololive!​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Cooperate and figure out​ ​​
​​ ​the numbers in your everyday lives​ ​​
​​​ ​in this groundbreaking​ ​​
​​ ​and exciting game:​ ​​
​​​ ​Two-Person Coop!​ ​​
​​ ​Private Number Quiz!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it really worth the hype?​ ​​
​​​ ​1st Gen​ ​​
​​ ​Aki Rosenthal​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll see once we start.​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive staff​ ​​
​​ ​Friend A (A-chan)​ ​​
​​​ ​For now, please look at this.​ ​​
​​​ ​2nd Gen​ ​​
​​ ​Yuzuki Choco​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive English-Myth-​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​Go forth, Private Number Panel!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara | Friend A​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose | Choco​ ​​
​​​ ​There it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​A lot of stuff's written on there.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're on the same team, A-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah! We are, yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara & Friend A Team​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara and I are on the same team.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san and Choco-sensei​ ​​
​​ ​are in their own team.​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose & Choco Team​ ​​
​​​ ​Time to give you​ ​​
​​ ​a taste of blonde power.​ ​​
​​​ ​Match one of the numbers with​ ​​
​​​ ​I choose Kiara's 17!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guess which number matches the phrase.​ ​​
​​ ​The team with the most correct matches wins.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of​ ​​
​​ ​countries visited​ ​​
​​​ ​one of the phrases among the choices.​ ​​
​​​ ​The team with the most number​ ​​
​​ ​of correct matches wins.​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it right...​ ​​
​​​ ​We choose the other team's numbers,​ ​​
​​ ​not our own, correct?​ ​​
​​​ ​Choose from the opposing team's panel.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​For our team,​ ​​
​​ ​we'll be choosing from your panel.​ ​​
​​​ ​And for your team,​ ​​
​​ ​you'll be choosing from our panel.​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose & Choco Team:​ ​​
​​ ​Choose Your Number!​ ​​
​​​ ​First off,​ ​​
​​​ ​please choose a number.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just tell us whose number​ ​​
​​ ​you're going for.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start with Kiara's 102.​ ​​
​​​ ​102 is a pretty big number.​ ​​
​​​ ​It'd be hilarious if it turned out​ ​​
​​​ ​to be the number of​ ​​
​​ ​keyboards she's broken.​ ​​
​​​ ​That would be...​ ​​
​​​ ​hard for keyboard sponsorships​ ​​
​​ ​to endorse...​ ​​
​​​ ​Destruction to all keyboards!​ ​​
​​​ ​* This is a bit​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a pretty good guess.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's quick.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think you've taken a lot of pictures​ ​​
​​ ​since your last visit to Japan,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I'd say that's the number of​ ​​
​​ ​pictures you've taken this week.​ ​​
​​​ ​She might have just been​ ​​
​​ ​shooting a panorama, to be fair.​ ​​
​​​ ​Could be the case.​ ​​
​​​ ​Click! Click! Click!​ ​​
​​​ ​Does that 102 refer to​ ​​
​​​ ​the number of pictures​ ​​
​​ ​Kiara took this week...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah! Yes it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​I did an actual count,​ ​​
​​​ ​and most of them​ ​​
​​​ ​turned out to be cat pics.​ ​​
​​​ ​We also have this week's​ ​​
​​ ​pic count of everyone else here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's compare the numbers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here they are.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of pics taken this week​ ​​
​​​ ​For real?! Don't you guys take pics at all?​ ​​
​​​ ​The gap is quite real.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think most of mine are all​ ​​
​​​ ​just pics of kitties.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aren't you compelled to take even more?​ ​​
​​​ ​The urge to touch them is just greater.​ ​​
​​​ ​Understandable.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's true...​ ​​
​​​ ​That makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't really take pictures that often.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was asked to take​ ​​
​​ ​those ten pics of food.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guess The Calorie​ ​​
​​ ​10 pics for a different show​ ​​
​​​ ​It was a request...​ ​​
​​​ ​What were those six pictures, A-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​I have this habit of taking​ ​​
​​ ​screenshots of notes I take down.​ ​​
​​​ ​Actual screenshots​ ​​
​​​ ​You truly are an office professional.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's nothing wrong with that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyway, congrats on your first point!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hooray!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara & Friend A Team:​ ​​
​​ ​Choose Your Number!​ ​​
​​​ ​Instead of starting with a number,​ ​​
​​​ ​why don't we start with the phrases?​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanna start with those?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which is an easy pick?​ ​​
​​​ ​I've been to Choco-sensei's home.​ ​​
​​​ ​She has a ton of clothes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wanna go with that?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want to make that call...​ ​​
​​​ ​150 is the number of clothes​ ​​
​​​ ​Choco has at home!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa! I got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah darn, she got it right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank goodness!​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I spend the most​ ​​
​​ ​on clothes in general.​ ​​
​​​ ​They are cute, to be fair.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a lot of dresses.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​Especially those with back zippers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right.​ ​​
​​​ ​We got everyone's numbers too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take a look.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yours is probably low, A-chan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here they are!​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of clothes​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-san has over a hundred.​ ​​
​​​ ​They are too many to count,​ ​​
​​​ ​so it's just a rough average.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-senpai and A-chan​ ​​
​​ ​have too few though!​ ​​
​​​ ​I keep things real simple.​ ​​
​​​ ​I carry four of the same variety.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just like Steve Jobs!​ ​​
​​​ ​Exactly!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have four pairs of the same style,​ ​​
​​​ ​which are then further split into seasons.​ ​​
​​​ ​So that's at least 32 articles of clothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Today I learned​ ​​
​​​ ​Steve Jobs​ ​​
​​ ​Style​ ​​
​​​ ​that people like that do exist. Wow.​ ​​
​​​ ​We do.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san had fewer than I thought.​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought you had dance clothes.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't add those into the count.​ ​​
​​​ ​So it'd be a bigger count​ ​​
​​ ​if you added them in?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I have about 50 dance clothes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Casual wear​ ​​
​​​ ​Dance wear​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san, don't leave me behind!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, A-chan.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm just different.​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose & Choco Team:​ ​​
​​ ​Choose Your Number!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd like to guess what Friend A's 0 is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Zero, huh.​ ​​
​​​ ​You have both socks and mirrors​ ​​
​​ ​in your washroom so those aren't zero.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I've got it, Choco-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Give your answer!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've heard her say she doesn't own a cat,​ ​​
​​​ ​so she doesn't have any cat litter, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​You make a good point.​ ​​
​​​ ​A-chan. A-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're whistling...​ ​​
​​​ ​Your reaction makes it way too obvious!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sorry, Kiara-san!​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyway, so is Friend A's 0​ ​​
​​​ ​the amount of cat litter in her house?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes! That is correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't keep cats at my current place.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd want to have one once I move out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see everyone else's numbers.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of cat litter at home​ ​​
​​​ ​grains​ ​​
​​​ ​bags​ ​​
​​​ ​liters​ ​​
​​​ ​The counters are different?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a few questions about​ ​​
​​ ​these highly specific counters, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​Choco-sensei,​ ​​
​​ ​by pieces you mean bags?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like 2 bags of cat litter.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-san's in liters?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's how it was.​ ​​
​​​ ​I ordered them from Am*zon,​ ​​
​​ ​and they were pretty heavy.​ ​​
​​​ ​The box said "liters."​ ​​
​​​ ​One package was about 10 liters.​ ​​
​​​ ​So that's how it was.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a lot, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​I get you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san, did you actually​ ​​
​​ ​count 10,000 of the grains?​ ​​
​​​ ​How did you...?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I have around​ ​​
​​ ​10,000 of them grains.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sure?​ ​​
​​​ ​How could you know?!​ ​​
​​​ ​She probably let​ ​​
​​ ​her muscles do the counting.​ ​​
​​​ ​Swolenthal counted 10,000.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's another point for your team.​ ​​
​​​ ​Congratulations!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Act ignorant next time, got it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll try!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara & Friend A Team:​ ​​
​​ ​Choose Your Number!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's take another swing at it.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're gonna catch up!​ ​​
​​​ ​This one.​ ​​
​​​ ​This 7.9 has me curious.​ ​​
​​​ ​Time records for 50-meter sprints​ ​​
​​ ​have decimal places, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I have no clue how fast​ ​​
​​​ ​that is, to be honest.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's below 8 seconds, at least.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're good, then. Let's go with that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's lock it in.​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose's 7.9​ ​​
​​​ ​refers to her time in a 50-meter sprint!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please be it!​ ​​
​​​ ​We got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my god!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's compare it with everyone's times.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright.​ ​​
​​​ ​50-meter sprint record​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't remember​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't remember...​ ​​
​​​ ​You're pretty fast, Aki-san.​ ​​
​​​ ​That was me at my prime.​ ​​
​​​ ​We don't really test for it now, do we?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you guys​ ​​
​​​ ​record your times back at school?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep, we did.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you do with it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think we use it to set​ ​​
​​ ​the order in relay races,​ ​​
​​​ ​choosing the fastest runners.​ ​​
​​​ ​What about you, A-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​This was a pretty recent record,​ ​​
​​ ​so it's quite slow.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I was faster back​ ​​
​​ ​when I played soccer.​ ​​
​​​ ​You played soccer?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I did!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're learning so much about A-chan...​ ​​
​​​ ​Unexpected, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose & Choco Team:​ ​​
​​ ​Choose Your Number!​ ​​
​​​ ​Friend A's 20...​ ​​
​​​ ​has to be the number of socks she has.​ ​​
​​​ ​Five-day work week,​ ​​
​​​ ​5 days x 4 pairs = 20 socks?​ ​​
​​​ ​which means she goes out​ ​​
​​ ​five times a week.​ ​​
​​​ ​Going from how she described​ ​​
​​ ​her clothing habits,​ ​​
​​​ ​Steve Jobs Style: Revisited​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd say this hypothesis holds, Aki-sama.​ ​​
​​​ ​The hints have been​ ​​
​​​ ​pretty obvious all throughout.​ ​​
​​​ ​Time! Time out!​ ​​
​​​ ​We should go with this.​ ​​
​​​ ​I agree.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is Friend A's 20​ ​​
​​​ ​the number of socks she has?​ ​​
​​​ ​Please no...​ ​​
​​​ ​That is correct!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're too easy, A-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​So easy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's check out everyone else's numbers.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of socks​ ​​
​​​ ​We all have a lot of socks!​ ​​
​​​ ​We match!​ ​​
​​​ ​We do match.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san! Choco-sensei!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why so few socks?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't go out much.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm more of a barefoot person.​ ​​
​​​ ​Team Barefoot​ ​​
​​​ ​So you see,​ ​​
​​​ ​I only have one kind for all pairs.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're all short black socks.​ ​​
​​​ ​I recommend it! Lose one,​ ​​
​​ ​and you just swap for another!​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, that's true, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​You have a point, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​No buts!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't judge me, please!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara & Friend A Team:​ ​​
​​ ​Choose Your Number!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder what Choco-sensei's 0 is?​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe it's the number of times​ ​​
​​ ​she soaks in the tub?​ ​​
​​​ ​If she's a shower person,​ ​​
​​ ​then it makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are there Japanese people like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean,​ ​​
​​ ​Chloe-san doesn't even take baths.​ ​​
​​​ ​True.​ ​​
​​​ ​Erm, hold on.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't vibe with this. Let's change it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure, sure. Denied so cleanly, huh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Not her vibe.​ ​​
​​​ ​Both Choco-sensei and Aki-senpai​ ​​
​​​ ​usually cook their own meals,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I wonder if they ever order delivery.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a really good question!​ ​​
​​​ ​I get the impression​ ​​
​​ ​that they don't often do it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe Aki-san is a frequent user?​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe?​ ​​
​​​ ​Take a guess.​ ​​
​​​ ​No, we're digging in!​ ​​
​​​ ​That 7 is for number of food deliveries!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is AkiRose's 7​ ​​
​​​ ​the number of food deliveries​ ​​
​​ ​she had this week?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay! We got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​No way! Really?!​ ​​
​​​ ​We got it right.​ ​​
​​​ ​I just moved in to a new place, so...​ ​​
​​​ ​That explains it!​ ​​
​​​ ​The only choices I had were eating out,​ ​​
​​ ​take-out, or food delivery.​ ​​
​​​ ​She just moved in, so the kitchen was​ ​​
​​ ​still unusable. Had to order delivery.​ ​​
​​​ ​I kept it at one delivery a day!​ ​​
​​​ ​Makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see how much the others ordered.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal it.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of food deliveries ordered this week​ ​​
​​​ ​I... got kebabs, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​(kebab)​ ​​
​​​ ​Kebab...​ ​​
​​​ ​That's less than I thought,​ ​​
​​ ​Choco-sensei.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've been eating out lately.​ ​​
​​​ ​Eating on the move and stuff.​ ​​
​​​ ​You mentioned that.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's how I've been this week.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm surprised you're at 0, Kiara-san.​ ​​
​​​ ​Unlike Japan,​ ​​
​​​ ​Austria's delivery services​ ​​
​​ ​get very expensive.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, really?​ ​​
​​​ ​I also feel like​ ​​
​​​ ​I keep ordering the same stuff,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I've been cooking​ ​​
​​ ​at home more instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cooking more at home​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you really want that kebab, A-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​I've been on a kebab habit lately.​ ​​
​​​ ​I crave it twice a week.​ ​​
​​​ ​Drizzle it with that super spicy sauce.​ ​​
​​​ ​Delicious, ain't it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's very good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Two-Person Coop!​ ​​
​​ ​Private Number Quiz!​ ​​
​​​ ​Man, we had an intense match!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're not yet sure who will win.​ ​​
​​​ ​AkiRose & Choco Team​ ​​
​​ ​3 Points​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara & Friend A Team​ ​​
​​​ ​But...?​ ​​
​​​ ​We're done!​ ​​
​​​ ​Game over! Bye, guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pack it up!​ ​​
​​​ ​For real?!​ ​​
​​​ ​We had too much fun talking,​ ​​
​​ ​so now we're out of time.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna know the rest!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, then.​ ​​
​​​ ​Any numbers​ ​​
​​ ​you'd like to check, Aki-san?​ ​​
​​​ ​What was Kiara's 7?​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara's 7? Let's see...​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of mirrors at home​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the number of mirrors​ ​​
​​ ​in her home! She has a lot!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't count the small ones.​ ​​
​​​ ​Her home has a lot of rooms,​ ​​
​​ ​each with mirrors.​ ​​
​​​ ​Only the big ones,​ ​​
​​ ​since I have a lot of rooms with them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Choco-sensei only has two?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's surprisingly few.​ ​​
​​​ ​One in the washroom, one in the bath.​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't have a full body mirror?​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, does that count?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, it should.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​And Aki-san has five.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're for dance use.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh right.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have three 180 x 100 cm​ ​​
​​ ​mirrors just lined up.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're pretty big.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna know what​ ​​
​​ ​Choco-sensei's 0 is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Choco-sensei's 0? Here it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Time taken soaking​ ​​
​​ ​in the bath in seconds​ ​​
​​​ ​Bathing time!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't soak in the bath.​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I just shower.​ ​​
​​​ ​I knew it!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm shocked at how I take the longest.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you do to take that long?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I watch YouTube in that entire hour.​ ​​
​​​ ​No work. Watch Youtube.​ ​​
​​​ ​I take that entire time as my break time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guessed it.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's good you find time to relax.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which do you wanna check?​ ​​
​​​ ​Friend A's 3.​ ​​
​​​ ​What was that again?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's check.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of keyboards broken​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​Keyboards?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have the most?​ ​​
​​​ ​How did you break them?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's not a lot.​ ​​
​​​ ​For real?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I've never broken one.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Same here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't they break eventually?​ ​​
​​ ​Like when a key falls off.​ ​​
​​​ ​Never.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wha?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Haven't had that happen.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you press too hard?​ ​​
​​​ ​Keyboard smash!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go for the last one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aki-san's 30.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wonder what is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it...​ ​​
​​​ ​Here it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. of push-ups in one go​ ​​
​​​ ​It's push-ups, wow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Those are low numbers for​ ​​
​​ ​Choco-sensei and Kiara-san...​ ​​
​​​ ​This number assumes​ ​​
​​ ​I can do push-ups.​ ​​
​​​ ​The number is actually lower.​ ​​
​​​ ​My viewers always say​ ​​
​​​ ​I have noodle arms.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's how weak I am.​ ​​
​​​ ​I might actually be too weak to live.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you practice doing​ ​​
​​ ​push-ups, Aki-senpai?​ ​​
​​​ ​I have done much lately.​ ​​
​​​ ​Core exercises x30​ ​​
​​​ ​I did core exercises​ ​​
​​​ ​every day for around 3-4 years​ ​​
​​​ ​3 years x 365 days​ ​​
​​​ ​every morning and evening.​ ​​
​​​ ​Day and night (x2)​ ​​
​​​ ​You are a dancer, after all.​ ​​
​​​ ​So inspiring!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hehe!​ ​​
​​​ ​With all that wrapped up,​ ​​
​​​ ​it was fun seeing everyone's info!​ ​​
​​​ ​For a quiz challenge,​ ​​
​​​ ​Subscribe to the hololive official​ ​​
​​ ​& our guests' channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​A-chan gave out too many hints.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right?​ ​​
​​​ ​It was too easy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Darn it, they see right through me!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sorry for being an open book!​ ​​
​​​ ​No denying that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pretty much.​ ​​