[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
no no
no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no
questions
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello
guys you're gonna help me I wanted to
make
on the right side on the top of the
screen I wanted to make you know like a
like the on the list of Pokemon I have
I don't remember their [\h__\h] names
and I have to look through celebi.net
so uh give me the names please
help me help me
uh yeah I got I mean yeah yeah and the
tarantula but I mean the other ones
um
I guess oh yeah I can put their
nicknames but in order to find their
image uh in the decks
uh flamigo okay flamigo
how do I yeah
flamingo
[Music]
Amigo's not gonna stay in this team for
very long though because there's not
even Evolution for that one right
so
that's oh no no
flamigo Flamingo you're such a long boy
if I want to fit you in here you're
gonna be so tiny
flamigo
and yeah I agree Flamingo is good but we
won't we will keep them until everyone
else is evolved and then we'll look for
something else
um
no but just you know even with two
Evolutions sometimes it feels lonely but
only one like no evolution is sad paw me
thank you
call me oh by the way off screen my
starter was trying to evolve and I
canceled it every time so that we can
have the evolution happening on screen
oh my God shiny pommy is so cute I want
a shiny Pony
[Music]
it's pink
I I want
I want also shiny food cocoa is also
pink like imagine making a full pink
team no matter if it needs to be shiny
or so like you could still have flamigo
in there but that would be amazing
[Music]
I wish we could do that
ah yeah okay so uh one one more
uh what else did we have
um the the the the the the the the
long the other long boy Wiglet thank you
we glad and the chunk I guess I had the
Chunk in there also it doesn't find
Wiglet it's ah two two teeth thank you
linklet
oh
cute
in this image it's totally retracted
small
you will you would not expect him to
have such a long neck
oh yeah yeah yeah
why did why did nobody mention the the
bread dog
unbelievable
ah the the shiny one is like a
like it's made I don't know with some
chocolate like you added some chocolates
to the to the mix or some cinnamon or so
oh my God so cute
but of course I don't have a shiny
because
life and Pokemon hates me
and that's just how it is
shush
here we go
just roughly
placing all that here okay gosh and now
I want to write the names right next to
them you'll get a shiny suit I hope so
they better give me a shiny I'm gonna
get a shiny like ever in my whole life
besides one time I guess off screen like
many years ago
although I'm wondering if that really
really really was a shiny though or if
it's just my memory playing tricks on me
um
okay now we need text layers
uh uh for a couple we called Sparks yeah
uh Sparks
select font
um
uh this one
Sparks
ah
wait I want to
move all of this I guess we can although
if they have longer names maybe not
um
a bit of it
it looks
and then
make a new one
uh what are the other names let's just I
guess go into the game and see
because I don't remember so yeah there
was a speeder yeah and a long boy and
the dakuma yeah okay okay wow you guys
remember everything
[Music]
but Spina you know bug Pokemon is [\h__\h]
so I'm not gonna keep it much longer
either
so sad
speeda
soon to be retired
and then we're gonna do oh
now we're gonna do
uh oh document
s
I never even noticed app breaks before
but yeah you guys told me the shinies
are easier to find the outbreaks I need
to take a look at that I didn't ah wait
Tacoma is not funny
is this one
hold on
don't look at this what's going on here
don't look I've been I've been um so
yeah I said this last night but uh
I was bored in the airplane and could
not hold back I had to go out and do
[\h__\h]
um so I did not go into the city to keep
that but I walked all the way around I
explored everything around the next city
I did not go into the arena we're gonna
do that now and we're gonna I also I
also I also canceled uh Fuego's
evolution
um and oh yeah the only thing you guys
missed was yeah me exploring a little
bit and the scene where the the director
is like how
outside in the white wide Big World
[Music]
foreign
I'm sorry sorry guys it's taking so long
long boy long boy is long
long boy is long
long boy
long boy long boy doesn't look so long
in this picture
oh yeah oh yeah
and then we have text uh
Amiga
bubbles
Amiga vamos
Amiga vamos next Pokemon I'm gonna call
vamos
maybe okay so that's my current team I'm
a bit sad they don't have like um pixel
Sprites but
yeah they
but didn't they like last Pokemon in
this interface they would have uh pixel
spreads right is it that last last time
right
in this interface
or like in the Box wait do they really
not have
that's not that's not pixel Sprites
that's just these ones but even smaller
I caught this one by the way for no
reason
yeah okay that's sad don't forget oh yes
see see
are you hearing it
what
no
don't begin captured
game capture
there it is
gamecatcher being a little [\h__\h]
I
don't also this
is a Pokemon arm is made by noriyuki
Arigato thank you for making it
it looks good but I if I if I show a
little bit more of my lower body you
will see how scuffed it's attached to me
so let's not show that at all
[Music]
started already good morning
I finished
okay
[Music]
welcome you all
lovely chickens let me pour some tea I
got a big batch of tea
I got some honey
[Music]
oh the good honey
oh
ooh many honey
and I got a jug of water I got snacks I
got chocolate snacks and I got a potato
salty snacks
oh
I am prepared for a 10 hour stream
I don't know if it will really be 10
hours but in theory
in fairy we can do that
uh where's my spoon
ah here
all right
[Music]
um
yes I should order food
I mean you can order it anytime
but you can also cook while watching my
stream like on a tablet or a phone or
whatever
some golden path no golden path no
So currently I'm looking at my team and
I'm thinking eventually we will
definitely replace speeda and maybe 20
levels later or so we might replace
Amiga you know we also want to see some
variety and depending on this long boy
have an evolution he does right he just
becomes like double and triple
I think I want to look at that dance
I see I'll see what happens with them
why he's eating something an orange
oh my God no your little [\h__\h] don't you
dare come close to me and I already
fought like pretty much every trainer in
the area
um so that's that
[Music]
yeah and I was just waiting for you guys
to to go into that um city with the bug
Arena and then we can do that really
quickly will be a breeze with the fire
starter
obviously which direction was it okay
what
oh yeah oh yeah okay
[Music]
and by the way today
obviously we're playing Pokemon
and then tomorrow
uh I have something special planned as
well
because
[Music]
um because
I realized oh [\h__\h]
one day this Sunday ah
cute oh
this Sunday is the first
um Advent
and I
[Music]
um
Panic
I'm panicked and before the Stream
I went out to look for a store that
sells like all the things you need
separately to build an advent wrap
brief ref right
because before right I said I might want
to do a ref making DIY stream
second one no it's the first right it
should be the
what
I'm in second lesson the second
pronunciation what it's rape what the
[\h__\h] why is it E A then
God
I need to boycott the English language
this is unacceptable
um
that's that's ridiculous makes no sense
[Music]
let me move my
random screen screams from Chihuahua
okay
what was I saying oh yeah
well we'll have the Dana
um
will teach me Indonesia
um yes yes I remembered she forgot but I
remembered
so I was like Lena what time and she's
like oh I knew I forgot something
so yeah
um
oh yeah you give me a gift please thank
you
[Music]
the trainers oh wow that's quite a lot I
would say
I was struggling with oh I want to
before we go to the arena I mean it will
be [\h__\h] easy anyway but I still want
to look at the attacks of my babies
because I can like if I understand
correctly then
you can see like a text and they should
have learned or whatever
where do you see that Union summary
uh
rearrangements
what was that about
um
or or
but do they all have everything that
they should have is that only when you
like
press a
H there
is it remember moves okay guys tell me
if uh they should if this if Sparks
should remember something I guess not
these are not good
what about here
nozzle nozzle
that was good right is it no power 20
what the [\h__\h] never mind
oh these guys don't look so good okay
that looks great
this looks nice 100 paralyzed
okay
[Music]
and then
I guess maybe quick attack and go
um
[Music]
how about you I mean you're not gonna
stay for much longer but okay you only
have pain whatever I don't care
and then you
um
[Music]
no I never use these kind of moves
now looks like [\h__\h]
[Music]
that was good yeah
and wrap okay
nah okay I didn't miss much
that's fine but
should I give them some attacks and of
the TMS
where are the DMC these are these this
these are TMS okay let's see
um
oh fighting move okay
well tell me if you think I should teach
one of them one of these
disarming the boys Ariel is I think it
doesn't already know what I realized no
swimming on
low kick insane on Flamingo
and you already have it oh I guess not
so
this this one
this attack never misses
huh
okay
should we just put it in instead of wing
attack
when you attack is basically Ariel is
yeah isn't it because like 60 Power 60
power 60.
accuracy 100 is is oh Mommy never misses
I guess means that well even if even if
the enemy has like a block attack
planned
would it still Maybe
okay
after
it's a waste of a TM okay I wouldn't use
it okay
metal clock oh we don't have a steel
attack yet I do want to give you that
one let me look at the other ones
any other steel attack no
that's normal
I think
we should still attacking now right
accuracy power 50 is kind of weak but I
mean
why not
copycat I should replace
I better wait I mean
if we're not going to use it now then
oopsie
wait find something better eventually
then hell yeah
um
but we do have what did I get rid of
you know what I'll get rid of charge
this might be
shocking to you
[Music]
but I'll do it
um what about like Electric Ball Thunder
Wave
sick punch what did I say
that was not on purpose
[Music]
I'm just a natural
low cake
thank you
oh well with low cake better than double
kick
it says no power
it the heavier the target the greater
the moves power
maybe get rid of the text then this move
name is a usage
[Music]
this one oh copycat you guys didn't like
copycat
[Music]
foreign
in a really good situation against Like
a Ghost Pokemon because ghost is
effective against Ghost right
and that actually
helped me out quite a lot
in that situation
just saying
[Music]
you know
rest oh
psychic move would be good but they
can't learn
anything okay
oh Rock move also can't be learned okay
push okay so anyway I was saying that
tomorrow uh I think 1am jst
is the collab of Dana on her Channel and
down
[Music]
because I found the materials and we're
gonna do a handcam stream later in the
evening maybe 8 P.M my time and you know
eight or nine PM my time where we make
what I make uh Advent Reef
[Music]
um
yes I don't think it will be too
difficult it's my first time though
um but I got a lot of a lot of lot of
lot of lots lots lots
lots of ingredients ingredients well
things that will help me build it
um
yeah I actually spent like over 80 Euro
which is like 80 dollars
um for the ingredients haha
no if you if you buy a high quality
one that you don't make yourself then
you might spend like 60 or so if you buy
a cheap one you can get one for twenty
dollars or so but I could have bought
one much cheaper but for me it's not
about
um having it
it's about
just making it for the stream just to
have something interesting on stream
yeah yeah yeah the the green stuff it's
not plastic it's real the the one I
bought that's probably also adds a
little bit to the price and I bought so
many decorations
the decorations one one each was like
really cheap I think what made the most
uh what cost the most was probably
the the plate that I also bought
additionally
and
maybe the base
I don't know I don't know what cost so
much I gotta check the bill
[Music]
um
will it be a reusable one
um I don't think it will hold until next
year but the decorations I can take off
in theory
and reuse
in feeling
came to see this gym huh that can only
mean one thing you're out to earn some
gym matches and take on the Pokemon
League aren't you
yeah I have a question so I know there's
free paths right but does this
mean I can only do one at a time or can
I do them all at the same time
[Music]
what about the ending then if I do one
ending will they give me the time to do
the other endings basically
all in any order okay okay
we're gonna flip flop okay okay
it's made to be parallel okay okay so
after we do this Arena we should look at
one of the things from the other quests
right okay
[Music]
yes I knew it I'm so glad I asked you to
do it well if only she knew that I'm
gonna do everything anyway
it's not because you're special or
anything
just trying to clear the freaking games
not because of you don't think you're
special
I made her feel special
gotta pass a certain challenge set by
them their gym test every gym tests
every Gym's test is different if you ask
the lobby stuff about it they'll tell
you what's up here have these when you
use them consider me healing up your
Pokemon
[Music]
's controller beans and Shop selection
oh the Titan Titan battles unlock
Traverse watches
I'm so excited I can barely stand still
okay
annoying friend
go wherever the hell you want
it's probably spikes to blushes
why would you do that
I'm gonna try to drink my tea
[Music]
what
Olive roll
Olive rolled uh-huh
Olive product is a big part of life with
cortondo with help to Olive Harvest
Festival here each year for generations
to usher in bumper crops
what what's bumper crops
to pass the gym test you'll need to roll
an olive shaped ball all the way to the
goal your effort should help ensure we
get a great all of ours next year too
why is this monster so light
when the rise of his eyebrows and hair
is so dark
the staffer over at the Olive rolling
field will explain the world to you in
Fair detail okay
bumper crop is a big Harvest aha that's
a weird word to use
north of town okay
okay thanks dude
um let's go
one of those pixel butterflies that's a
butterfly from this new generation right
they have like a pixel
pixel thing pattern going on Tech part
in the olive roll North North is like
over there
I think
[Music]
is it that big basket
well when I was exploring in this area I
already saw it
this area
oh but I don't know if the basket was
there oh hello fence
spooky spider web fence is it Halloween
oh it's from X and Y oh
can't jump in this game yeah no but you
can jump when you're in the Mounds
interestingly
[Music]
apparently
humans just cannot jump but Pokemon can
they are just
Superior in every way this new test is
all about stamina which you obviously
don't have but good luck I guess
got a bottle of various obstacles then
push it into the goal to clear the
course now that you're all filled in are
you ready to start a gym test you know
I'm more than [\h__\h] ready I I need to
play Pokemon let me play Pokemon
let's go
wait I definitely need to
okay before I mean I probably don't even
have to but I I should before we go into
the fight I mean if there's trainer
fights here then
we can hope for and uh evolving prompt
we wanted to evolve but um
sounds
okay
what are these ones supposed to be here
are they cheering me on
this is like comedic bounces
I'm gonna save those SSX
anyway yeah let's fight
let me
um evolve my my Sparks please
Miranda
cocoon oh she got a purple Pokemon oh my
God
that is quite impressive but
my attack fell do I do special attack or
normal attack doesn't matter
[Music]
this time I understand what you guys are
going on about
[Music]
um
this was really not uh like an obstacle
though I could have just rolled over
these
tiny suckers
have you found inside the Pokemon no I
didn't get to yet I only played this
game once before this stream kind of
closed I'm not very far
what if I just whatever
[Music]
no no no no no no no
no no no no okay that works
what's the [\h__\h] sound
oh if you just go sideways you don't
even have to fight him
okay go ball oh really
the game really sees this as an
invisible wow wow
maybe this tiny Pokemon are more
powerful than I thought they were
[Music]
all right bring it on
that's an old one but it actually looks
pretty good here
I'm just gonna assume that
fireworks fireworks oh my word
fireworks
[Music]
do you guys know how fireworks work they
work with fire
[Laughter]
[Music]
wasting my time
oh
[Music]
you're in the way you said you would get
out
why are we going
I guess we're going this week
[\h__\h] sake
okay never mind I changed my mind
I deserve this shortcut I
I saw a gun I worked hard for it
finally finally got
up Austria finally gets a goal oh my God
saved by Target
okay that was interesting
to me this is the reason Oscar didn't
get it to the if anything the reason is
me not being part of the team
hmm
mm-hmm
[Music]
with that performance I'm sure we can
look forward to a great Olive Harvest
next year
good luck
please report your results to the lobby
staffer
you know I really want to play Pokemon
but overall
I'm for some reason I don't know why but
for some reason I'm not as excited about
it as I was
um for our kills
our chaos was just
much better
I love Darkness
I can't feel so interesting because you
know it was
it was like different
[Applause]
I mean you know other reasons
I'm sure that rko's got its fair share
of criticism but I really like to know a
lot
let's only get the prompt again if it
doesn't level up right
[Music]
we're getting closer
um maybe I should like try to fight
higher leveled Pokemon though
wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
um who could be higher level
give me gold give me the coin give me
give me give me give me give me the
coins that you carry stop hiding all
over the world
that you carry you make me go crazy
looking for you everywhere
foreign
[Music]
Pokemon just as a flex
per Flex
a Jigglypuff foreign
[Music]
is that one strong I wonder
what level are you
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you have a chance I mean I got fire
let me try Okay
Swagger at least it didn't attack me oh
oh wow interesting it rises my attack
but it also makes me confused so I might
hit myself come on come on spikes
oh yes
oh
[Applause]
uh R incinerate go go
go don't hit yourself please oh what if
it hits itself now
no I don't want to run
[Music]
it [\h__\h]
oh you wanna ride my attack even more
that makes no sense because you can't
get me even more confused
if I'm confused and I'm confused
right there's no like stacking of
confusion oh oh Ruth what's that oh
it's Hill
oh well if you do that then I have no
chance
[\h__\h]
see how much damage
oh now it's a lot of damage
okay I'll try one more time Swagger
again
when it rises my attack I attack a
attacker special attack physical or
special attack
does this even make sense oh are we
getting a hit
yo
this time it didn't it didn't do half
the health before it did though
let's go let's go you just have to oh
that was a cricket
baby like that
[Music]
Queen which is all
yeah
nice [\h__\h] deserved and will that
you'll finally get to evolve you have
proven yourself worthy Fuego good job
spikes whoa
nine levels whatever
[Music]
you look stupid
you look like a old grandma with a
hunchback that leads a walking stick
and with fluffy curly hair
very disappointing
or is it is it not like a fire a little
flame is it an egg I'm not sure it could
also be a really badly animated uh
little flame
um
and that's cool
[Music]
but it doesn't looks pretty cool so it's
okay
I'm so proud of you I'm so proud of you
you proved that you're the boss
absolutely what a killer
it's an egg which will hatch oh how did
I miss you
you got some delicious cake from The
Patisserie so fairy let's celebrate the
battle okay
[Music]
foreign
I'm level 20 holy [\h__\h] yeah and a little
bit too over level because I am
I I just wanted to play
and ground so I'm guessing fire is not
good I'm just gonna have to go for bison
oh I'm 10 levels above and I could not
kill it
oh wow
thank you
it says kfp
on on the Pokeball
this Cake's this cake makes me so happy
I don't even mind losing
understandable I feel you I know what
you're saying
all right where do we go next into the
building again
oh cute
oh
and paint the speed of Pokemon is so
cute
ah poker Center okay
[Music]
hello
please heal my Pokemon
[Music]
it's evolution is not cute this Pita oh
it has an evolution oh I need to say
[Music]
Ocha
oh
thank you why don't you charge material
thank you thank you all right sayonara
sayonara Zoo Berlin
[Music]
foreign
it's an old um an old an old Japanese TV
advertisement
[Music]
foreign
it's um about adding some magical words
animal words to the end of greetings
like sayonara turns out to sayonaraon
for lion and with that you will make
more friends by adding more like funny
cute words at the end so sayonara
becomes cyanideon Ohio
becomesagi for example because usagi's
bunny starts with
kind of ends with u yeah
and then uh konnichiwan konichiwa plus
one
you know dog noise
or you could also do Vani konichiwani
crocodile
um
[Music]
yeah all that kind of stuff you can add
and then then you will make more friends
according to this Tel Aviv advertisement
terevi did I just say Tel Aviv
television advertisement
yeah it's a cute a cute bug a cute song
stuck in my head for many years
uh you're ready to challenge Jim leader
Katie the sugar bug sugar bug
[Music]
sugar bug
celebrity advertisements
[Music]
the battle Court oh
what's Court like
is there a king
and the Queen
waifu incoming you like this person
oh
it's a design I use
[Music]
I think
she's like
[Music]
hey hey
is that your her Pokemon no I guess not
she's cute
[Music]
I like her hat that's cute
I like I like her uniform too she's
obviously a baker yeah cute
I want her to bake me some croissants
and some bread please
what dude's eyes look so weird anyway
my name is Katie
what
does what am I stand by it sounds like
how do I make her voice
uh
I know what she sounds like but
Thomas
[Music]
uh
take something water
look at that
[Music]
wait
live streams okay let's go here
[Music]
I I can't do it
again
what
is
the bgm from the game is too loud I
can't hear it but she has a self-spoken
voice
my my name is Katie and I am the owner
here
yeah it does not sound like her at all
foreign
right now
small mouth oh
forgive me
um my name is Katie and didn't she just
say that and I am the gym leader here in
cotondo ah she said something else
and she's a baker
my main line of work is crafting sweets
as a pastry pastry chef
Fiddler Suites that bring happiness with
just one bite a bug type Pokemon hiding
in foliage
proper smiling is very powerful
don't let your guard down unless you
would like to find yourself knocked up
your feet
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I am not only challenged I am heart
challenged by Gym Leader caging
that is a new Pokemon
don't take my bug type Pokemon lightly
you will be in for a world of pain if
you do
um my world is already only paying but
all right I'll take you seriously but
you
never
Pokemon though but it's too small I
might step on it
oh no no no not switchy
Tyrone to last
let me burn that wool on your back
and see how you look naked
small speed
y
Ursa that's not uh
that's not a
bug Pokemon
[Music]
I'll try anyway with fire but I don't
know
oh maybe I should have terrestrialized
oh well
oh yeah okay
yeah
are you gonna terrestrialize and turn it
into a bug Pokemon
[Music]
wow
it's a
[Music]
bear bear to fly
that it might have survived if it wasn't
turned into a bug type
oh shocking
oh
wow
didn't they use the same music and sword
and shield or does it just sound
familiar to me because of the trailers
[Music]
for that champagne lasted five seconds
isn't it so similar with the audience
chanting
right yeah what the [\h__\h] your strength
froze during our battle like a nice
bread in the oven oh Yum Yum Yum Yum
good reference I feel like I may need to
work on my own strength as well
congratulations you passed as proof of
your Victory against me the gym leader
allow me to present you with this gym
badge
I hope you'll enjoy it alongside a
heaping serving of some of my Deluxe
handmade treats oh please give
[Music]
it cute my mouth is so big
um now I want a cupcake
with one gym bags in your possession
Pokemon of up to level 25 will be easier
to catch and will listen to your
commands as well I see you have quite
the appetite as well how about a little
TM as the frosting on this cake
pounds
uh-huh it's a bug type attack
[Music]
once you've found the TM during your
travels you can then use a TM machine to
make copies of that team you did know
that right
oh
the tip of the little strand that's
sticking out of her hair also is shaped
like like a bug antenna cute
her design even though I don't think I
think I are in the trailers or so but um
I really like her design too
she gives this cozy comfy vibe
um cute kind of waifu she even has a
beauty mark on her cheek oh my God
[Music]
I wish you luck in your future
Adventures may they be a sweet and
lovely as a good dessert
those look like latex gloves
damn
let's say she has Mama vibes
but definitely wife Vibes a very fitting
wife
[Music]
hey hey Mama just had to tell you my
Pokemon are learning some pretty cool
new moves be ready how'd it go at the
gym by the way I passed easily
I just all burned it all down yes I mean
it was obviously we're gonna pass but
congrats I'm so glad I encouraged you to
take on Jim's nice job past me I'm
training hot too by the way day and
night going all over the place to boot
thank goodness we've got the map app it
helps a ton with figuring out where to
go next especially in a huge place like
paldea after all the paths are getting
stronger usually has some strange stops
and detours
speaking of going to strange places I
wonder what arvin's up to and catch you
later hint hint I hope you know I'm
gonna want to battle everyone into each
other
oh I wonder what Arvin is up to
oh don't you wonder the same thing if
not then by now you should be wondering
it because I mentioned it to you
well where could I even be don't tell me
he's gonna show up right in my face now
[Music]
you're gonna be like right here
now okay good
well how do we do the Arvin thing
um
he put something in my map right
oh wait what was that
so oh my God she also looks I need to
look at her
it's not a Gym trainer right she's one
of those
um
evil team thingies
so one of these I should look at those
right for orange Quest
[Music]
um we can go to this one and then go to
the plant Arena and then go to her
because I [\h__\h] love her she's my
future wife
okay how do I
where is that
ah here can I mark it
there we go
oh I should probably I could like
teleport to be closer to it at least
um
this is confusing
over here
where can I fly to
oh I can't really come that slide this
is I guess the closest I can go
press right stick to lock the map oh
it's all right okay
Jim that was a psychic gym
down there the the purple lady
this I mean I guess she looks psychic
with the purple color
ah it's a it's a gym oh oh my God I want
to get to know her but she's like a
little 45 okay so that won't be for a
while
okay everybody
it's like ladies fun and hot oh you
already got to know her oh
no
older lady all the female NPC designs
are so [\h__\h] hot I just I can't
any shiny
don't see it shining all right it's um
it's exploring time
tell me if you see a shiny and tell me
fast because they despawn like
immediately
[Music]
why you look so angry oh no is this a
water type
ah
it's a fish so it's probably Water right
okay
[Music]
water it's electric
the wasn't that the title of the little
Katy Perry song that she did for Pokemon
[Music]
something Electric
trick yes she did but it was um for the
movie I think
it was all about Pikachu when she was
like hanging with Pikachu
Katy Perry with CG
um
electric you don't listen to it it was
actually a good song
are you shiny no you're not pink
the one important thing is to know what
the shinies look like because if there's
new Pokemon then how will you know if
you see them for the crystal if it's
shiny or not
that's my problem but now I know that
the shiny Pony is pink
is that shiny
no but that's a shy Nooks or something
like that right
[Music]
not following me
what's with poor amigo
[Music]
well what happened did you see it once
you did she walked by a shiny without
knowing
Shanks on there you know
is that a muscle car
oh basically yeah hey we're repeating
that
you're right
maybe maybe
when I explore these areas I just won't
explore them too much because you get
lost and you run everywhere
and instead I do this a little bit off
screens
I mean I run through like roughly but it
can take ages to look at every detail of
these areas right so
foreign
[Music]
roughly but we'll see if I can even stop
myself
[Music]
uh
oh picnic you're gonna teach me how to
do it
oh
oh no it's uh you just heal me
no problem when am I gonna learn how to
do a picnic
or do I have to teach myself
[Music]
look at this rock Pokemon I actually
dropped up this one oh my God I remember
this one I have so many [\h__\h] weird
dreams these days but this Pokemon
showed up in my dream and it uh evolved
into a Super Mario World Mushroom
but not like not perfectly looking like
that just like
um
similar but my brain definitely wanted
me to think that it's a Super Mario
World Mushroom
[Music]
I can't be mad you're so round you're so
cute
strong is this is it what type is it
like a stone a ground what it's not
Stone right
Joan doesn't exist
music a little loud
okay
I lowered it a little bit
still flying later
okay you mean that verb we're talking
about the the stone thingy right
[Music]
hmm
that's is that strong
oh
yeah oh yeah
hi
what oh rage hello
Cadet shark Cadet
uh is this a fire Pokemon because then
even though it's pretty cool we don't
need it
hmm
[Music]
it's the Mega Man Pokemon
it's rare
I don't need it though but okay I mean
we can think about it let's see oh I
might accidentally kill it I don't know
[Music]
one HP left
perfectly calculated yes I knew it I
knew I knew one HP would be left ah
still don't want to be in my Pokeball
let's see let's try one more time it
doesn't want then maybe I'll throw in a
paralyzation
come on come on you're Below My Level
what do you want
[Music]
oh oh okay nice
gotta use up my simple Pokeball yeah
wants to learn to move Buck bite
yeah
backpack sounds good what's that
1600.
okay no struggle bug oh maybe or
uh whatever this one then
ah I could have gotten rid of tackle too
I know whatever
Fida is a throwaway Pokemon I really
like its looks but you know
you know are any of the Pokemon I have
in my team right now like do they have a
special thing where they only evolve
if I do something special with them like
give them a certain item or or
[Music]
uh I don't know
walk the dog it really
[Applause]
what does dakoma need to do
[Music]
I don't care about Shaka dad tell me
about it harmonies what do you mean
walked
[Music]
thousand steps outside okay well can it
follow me
how do you do this again here are you
gonna follow me
okay thousand steps that shouldn't be
too difficult
unless I'm too fast
do these steps count
it has to evolve first so it's only for
the the lasso
evolving thing
oh yeah
you run it will go back it won't count
it
I mean it won't count
anywhere
seems like now it doesn't matter okay
I do want to keep that Pokemon in my
team
[Music]
was up okay but
um
after level 16
[Music]
oh it is level 16. huh
oh I could just run five circles in the
center of the town after the walls
after the first like okay the first like
evolving
it evolves at 18 okay okay okay
let's keep that in mind and if I forget
then you're welcome to remind me
huh
there's so many freaking items
everywhere so much to look at
[Music]
um
it was so sparkly and all twinkly what
box
yo-yo arm hair
is so long
no arm hair shaming though because I was
armed hair ashamed before as well
when I was younger
so
let's see it's a verb what can we do
with this verb let me find their shock
it
was right I mean I had a feeling it
would work quite well
[Music]
nice
are good against flying I don't know how
I knew it I didn't really know it but I
I assumed
energy root cool
I want
shiny
we are
you know the other dungeon no is that
the plant gym we're gonna check it out I
think like level wise I'm probably
already
quite ready for it now
we're gonna do something else first
we're gonna check out the open thing
what is that uh but that looks familiar
actually
I remember a boxing glove crab Boo from
before
is it water or no it doesn't seem like
water oh my God
[Music]
come on suddenly attacking me from
behind
you're fighting I don't know what's
strong against fighting
let's see how does metal claw do
not much better
[Music]
Lion's psychic oh well
um
how about digging
bye bye bye Kuma
I don't wanna switch Pokemon it's always
ways to move and see there it goes
here it goes
level up it's 17 now we're almost at
level 18.
okay
[Music]
well thank you for clapping for me
where the freak am I
I should go back up
but let me take a look here
foreign
[Music]
is this the way up
it's night time I ran past night them
ah no problem I don't care I'm gonna
come back here and look at everything
in like a relaxed chill manner but can I
reach that
uh
doesn't look like it but I can maybe
reach that
is so close
how dare you
look at these under your team is too
nervous to eat berries
that's weird
I don't know how that
connects
with one another okay let me get out of
here
hello
you're not gonna attack me so nice oh
there you go he wanted to
he was interested in it
main route this way let me follow the
arrows let me try to follow the arrows
did I fight you yes I did okay
yeah we go
Stars
[Music]
full heel nicer
anti-dote
bit
all right all right uh which way this
way
[Music]
what Pokemon will he use
let me switch to someone else because we
don't always want to have the same
Pokemon out front
she
oh I guess I can see some buba there we
go wow
[Music]
that design looks like with the straight
short hair like that and the eyes looks
like
um
character from what's it called
uh Japanese
game oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
Dragon maybe Dragon Ball too but yeah I
was speaking of him
I think that's what I was thinking of
[Music]
amazing I wonder if that was on purpose
it looks the same to me
[Music]
it was the first thing I thought when I
bought this person yay and brain we
share one brain cell isn't that
wonderful
easily buff what
that could not kill
I'm five six levels above and I use
something super effective
it's good that I added the steel move
at least we had something super
effective
defense curled up okay you're trying to
say that so that I don't feel so bad
about myself that's so sweet
any shinies
hello
[Music]
I didn't fight so many trainers but will
you still give me something
four
six okay has to be six all right I'll
come back
[Music]
yeah I don't want a shiny hunting hunt a
shiny through shiny hunting
I want it just randomly be served to me
right in front of my eyes on the silver
platter
[Music]
what's nanny
am I close to the thing oh Arvin
hey Chihuahua so from what I can gather
the Stony Cliff Titan likes to look
somewhere in this rocky area I look
around but I couldn't find any trace of
it maybe it's way up high on the cliff
or something
no that's impossible
I don't think it'd be hiding somewhere
that tricky so don't go falling off on
any Clips or anything trying to search
it out somewhere too strange
sounds like he's telling me to do that
maybe just give him up or look if you're
feeling stumped it's pretty handy I have
a feeling
um
I have a feeling I have a feeling
that I know
what it could be because it might be
seen in a trailer a Pokemon trailer
before
I think I saw it before if it's that but
uh
you never know
actually that looks like a pancake with
a cube of butter on top
[Music]
I've Got a Feeling
wait he said something about don't jump
down uh some Cliffs right
so obviously that's exactly what we
should be doing
I'm not even kidding if a Pokemon
trainer tells you to not do something
it's a hint to do it
but maybe not this cliff
[Music]
oh there's a try
interesting jackets hmm
would not wear it though
[Music]
for me Larvitar
uh is it dragon
do I need a very I don't have a fairy
Pokemon I think
uh
[Music]
rock is Rock
okay so what do I use
[Music]
you guys always have to tell me what to
use against it
I think
fighting water okay
[Music]
let's let's go with long boy
that looks scary
okay so both are both footwork let's go
with
um let me see which one's stronger 14.
oh they're all pretty weak we need some
better water attacks damn
Court
yes nice one hit that's what I like to
see
um clean very clean
Ralph uh for who what is that
saying I need a fairy move nice this is
power 90. accuracy 90. not too bad
uh I will get rid of
tail whip
or growl can also go next
[Music]
is a good move right yeah I think so too
okay
let me move on
shut up let me go
where was I where was I going to go this
way right
where is this thing that I'm looking for
and I don't really know what I'm what it
is but
oh now it's getting dark
[Music]
I can't see [\h__\h]
trees are on the way
what what
am I wasn't wearing
candy
macron oh oh oh yeah that's still there
what
oh
it's flying
that's just normal
um Pokemon Scarlet Violet things
just another day in Pokemon Sky let's
Violet okay
I guess it's time to catch you huh
you cutie patooty or maybe in the future
I will try to catch an evolution of
yours how about that
yeah the invisible boat will feel that's
that is um
uh
what's it called
SpongeBob SpongeBob SpongeBob SpongeBob
[Music]
random people coming into my stream chat
saying hi let's play online here's my
code
please tell me that you're really just a
rando who looked for Pokemon streamers
in the category of live streams on
YouTube
and just came here just because of that
that's kind of cute is that a shiny
no
[Music]
shiny oh it's cute
but it's not shiny
[Music]
[Laughter]
history repeats itself
come on
I'm not even I can't follow
the map marker because I hear shiny no
probably not because I
oh I just canceled this Dragon man
there's so much you you follow all the
items you see close by on the screen
and I also I know I walked by a trainer
let me go back
Anthony
[Music]
where was that trainer damn it what's he
over here
if only I could see it further
and things wouldn't only spawn so close
to me
then it would be easier to look back
there you are
let's fight
hello who is you
Severino
[Music]
so that's fairy I think and I have no
idea what to use against it
um
maybe bite
at least it's fair oh it's very attacks
will not be so strong on me either right
poison and steel
ah really okay then we better like
be serious now
feel
[Music]
the mighty trainer The Sweep nature oh
my God
bye-bye
Jigglypuff what the [\h__\h] I guess I
already had low HP coming in here
okay okay please let it be a one hit
please please please please please
please please
[Applause]
uh what else do I have that helps
would have gone in with full health it
might have not been such a big problem
uh
uh Sparks okay
should we attack with fire
[Music]
strong
Sparks
uh I've heard that before but I don't
remember let me pour some tea while you
guys tell me if I should switch out or
not
keep
okay
grass he's grass okay then then we stay
then
we say oh I see that maybe this Pokemon
was a problem for fauna because of his
grass and she had the grass starter
then up until this point getting a fire
Pokemon is almost impossible no
I don't I accept that one Mega Man
Pokemon is the only fire Pokemon you can
get at this point
oopsie there we go
[Music]
this one
you can get twirl live
Firebird
Firebird what which one have I seen that
one
I have not seen a Firebird also I just
noticed in the back there's a the coin
Pokemon
it
okay shinies
or The Shining I will not
stop asking for that until again is
shiny you know me
look up oh
I thought a red bird earlier I don't
remember that
maybe I was fighting myself
all right
um jump
[Music]
nice good Landing
and maybe oh
[Music]
kill it
oh it wants to attack me oh he's so cute
he's so cute shiny no
I probably should go back to heal myself
is what I was gonna say
already back
honey
of honey
I forgot to put some honey in my
[Music]
head okay
yes I need the rest
of
the Aeon
[Music]
are you asking me for attention
uh okay I've got some
I do have some tangents
I think
[Music]
let's see
[Applause]
oh did you see yesterday I posted on
Twitter uh a screenshot
of a free member Discord group
consisting of mysterious members that
you guys don't know yet
which is called girls talk not girls
talk
obviously
and it's something that I was planning
or wanting to do mentioned I wanted to
do for a while
because after at the end of a collab I
did with my May
we kind of like
did some girls talk and I was like yo
you know what like having a whole stream
where we just do girls talk oh look at
that there it is
n't it
and you guys also are like oh hell yeah
I mean I I don't do ghost talk in my
private time because I am not a girl but
I want to hear more
I
wish so finally I set it in motion it
should happen
yum
um
next week or no probably the next next
week
now it's Saturday
so I'm in like two weeks time I think
we're gonna do it
wondering who was part of it besides
she's pretty oh stop charging at me I'm
busy here
I am crab
do it oh chill
I want
the does the crab have an evolution and
also look at her
that glowing orange makeup with the
white platinum hair
and the tan oh my God and the white
dress of the golden oh my God she's a
queen
oh
beautiful she's beautiful
Style
okay baby
oh wait
oh I was thinking oh fire because bug
Pokemon but I guess it's very oh see
whatever
it's a blue what are you
is that blue
maybe light blue because on my screen I
have two screens and on the on the right
screen it looks light blue and on my
middle screen it looks White
but you might just be memeing about that
stress right
but that's a famous dress
it's not a dress though
I know
she's like Pokemon
anything else interesting here I kind of
want the crab it's a rock type right
look at how they're walking towards me
so cute
I won
it looks so motivated oh as a female
Club
I don't know
um I don't know I hope this doesn't kill
you
no problem
is it good
I want it
no matter what it's definitely better
than Speedo I assume
speed up
oh my God it's not bad
anger shell what the what what what
what's going on what
stop
when it opens its mouth and stands on
the back legs it's so cute
it's a good rock time
right so does it have an evolution or
not
oh
look how badly it wants to stay with me
first try
oh you should get the salt God you mean
the rock over there but I want the crab
no evolving okay then maybe not until
the end but I want him for now
[Music]
um
foreign
big letters
can I change the name please
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I want to change name
[\h__\h]
for now
um
I'm sorry it's goodbye speeda you look
so cute and I love you forever but you
are week too weak for this fight I
wanted to live a healthy and safe and
happy life outside of Pokemon battles I
just want you to spin and spin and spin
your webs around things happily ever
after without worrying
about being eaten or burned alive by
some fire Pokemon you know
I want all the happiness for you
so it's better to let you go which means
you're gonna have to change
my lineup
[Music]
what's it called
um this Pokemon what's it called again
club right
uh Club
on it
[Music]
oh my God it can be blue it looks like
gouda when it's blue
wow I want the shiny yeah
it's like baby blue
foreign
[Music]
becomes
Connie
[Music]
and get rid of
this one
[\h__\h] I deleted the wrong one
hey which one is it
[Music]
whoa
yeah
aren't you looking for Duty
okay
let's go why is that stupid ass Pokemon
that I have to look for let me just let
me try to go as straight as possible
to the goal
pink let me let me let me let me let me
let me take a look at it
let me take a look at it let me take a
look is that Shining
it's not as shiny is it what is it what
is this
steel fairy
oh
[Music]
it's interesting but I have a fairy dog
and my electric Pokemon does steel tool
[Music]
but Tinker Tink let me let me look up
the evolution Tinker thing
I think
oh my God the shininess is so hard to
see this one in shiny basically the
silver Parts turn into a bronze it's
really hard to see wow
whatever look this is so cool oh
oh
[Music]
my God
yeah it gets a big phone camera
I'll I'll catch it and use it later
maybe we can like switch out
but I don't want to kill it
um do a lick
okay
oh paralyzed us
[Music]
oh that's an interesting Pokemon
so let's go catch it
oh yes first try
[Music]
Tinker Tink
so I think it should be called Bonk
just that
yes
but I don't think I'll put
it just yet but it will be a future
member I think
if I get tired of the others but
[Music]
um
I don't know
ah it kind of overlaps with what I have
now and those are two Pokemon that I'm
actually kind of happy with
well we'll see we'll see and we'll see
[Music]
at some point you should just be able to
like step over these tiny Pokemon
and just get exp from like stepping on
them
what was that
what's that sound
loud loud sound here oh
it's another one though fire Mega Man
Pokemon
[Music]
you can Autobell them that's not what I
mean though like I literally mean just
step on it and that should kill it when
I just run over it instead of initiating
a battle
data
let's try to find
the Pokemon that we so desire
foreign
over there supposedly
okay okay we're close
Mama Skye
huge
[Music]
child of me like
me like biter
[Music]
well I think it's supposed to be on the
wall right it's not a bug but it was
kind of floating though
oh well
it's cute how it jumped at me
it's funny I guess it makes sense
because they have their legs positioned
similarly
[Music]
drop crab
yeah but that's not the Pokemon that
we're looking for right yeah yeah yeah I
mean it is I think but not uh that's not
the one right otherwise something I feel
like it would be
foreign
you guys saw the Gimme ghoul right there
right
[Music]
still
oh let me let me try to respawn it
[Music]
wait a second I guess that's you
gone is it in the wall
[Music]
why come back
foreign
[Music]
I hear it I'm never gonna find it ever
again
wait a second
[Music]
wow that was so close
good job what's up
what's up
[Music]
I feel like that jump should have been
impossible I was just really lucky
soda
um
only that should not disappear I think
they stayed ah it's bad
it's bad don't run away again
y'all
you little [\h__\h]
okay so about this one
where's it gone
does it change location
[Music]
that's interesting
I don't know
wow
crab where are you I arrived at my desk
ah maybe it was supposed to like show up
once and then go somewhere else after
I've seen it
aha
[Music]
don't look at me it's embarrassing
I love crabs
I am crap
I like crab crab do I hug what do I do
with you do I kill you or do I catch you
um
our our Alvin Arvin hello
probably go for something else here
rocks oh God damn it ah okay we have a
lot of effective [\h__\h]
can't catch it anyway okay
[Music]
so cute
what what was that I can no longer skate
but I mean I feel I feel like that was a
given
let's try this
bye script oh my God
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] okay but I do enough damage I
will probably die though I don't know is
it worth healing
I will heal
um how much oh I only have 30 HP on that
Pokemon holy [\h__\h] that's nothing
okay
let's see can maybe it does not attack
so
we get this free heel basically ideally
oh
my God because we're apparently slower
than cloth so
that's a problem I'm gonna do one more
healing
just one more
70.
okay just one more
it's speed foul now
a project
[Music]
oh I didn't realize oh okay
[\h__\h] okay okay okay okay I'm gonna have
one more Pokemon that can find you no
problem
oh I have two more Pokemon that can
fight you no problem let's let's go
let's go Amiga
so many
that go well against this one
wow which one should I do
ready
okay this one's really heavy isn't it
let's let's crystallize too
oh am I is it
what's Amiga is like taking anyway
flying okay but my attack will still be
strong right
oh now it's not sad anymore
don't worry guys we got it in the bag
cute
find it again
it's almost dead though
I feel like kind of sorry for it
shouldn't we just let it do its thing
oh
look at it could we have jumped on it
let me try
oh I should heal first okay
uh wait
oh
[Music]
I wish it would just also revive it
on the potion
and then we're gonna put
um
Amiga in the front again and before I go
down let me check up I'll check out this
place up here
all right we're five
oh one more thing
[Music]
change Connie what why
oh the name
maybe I'll just keep it like this
I want to jump
on big Connie
amiconic
where where am I
me
excusing something does that make you
big
hi Arvin Alban whatever your name is
Arvin okay whoa whoa you found it
dead things the Stony Grove Titan no
cloth has got any business being just
being he's gonna be even stronger now
after eating those herbs
oh [\h__\h] let's watch ourselves
I like it
it looks happy when it's big
whoa pink Power
all right I can crystallize again
[Music]
how is that possible
what if I won him now that would be so
funny
I can't
his Pokemon
don't don't
why not
don't do it
hmm
oh it loses stab then okay
that's it
wow super effective
what's this weak ass Pokemon doing here
speed Rose
defense fell
Special Love fell
[Music]
ouch
apparently it doesn't lose them okay
well this should kill
hey you blocked the wrong one
what did Alvin even do
he was there for mental support right oh
foreign and now it's small
ah cute good job Amiga
quite proud of you wow wow if only you
had an evolution so it would be more
interesting to me
unfortunate
can we can we can we can we can we so
let me use the best Pokemon
ah
no
[Music]
um I like the flummigo but I wish it had
an evolution but
if it had one then
I would love it very much too
can I promise I
strong and all but now I'll keep it for
now but I'll probably switch it out
later but I'm glad you give the pink
burp some love
it's perfect the way it is
[Music]
we all had the same team though because
eventually maybe I battle you okay
did you just did Kelly just end her own
Pokemon stream or what
all right look at my little body coming
through like a champ
what who's your little buddy you mean me
does he mean me I'm not your little
buddy what the [\h__\h] but she's talking
Pokemon no sheesh
I sure do a lot like having something so
tough out to get me
a few hours ago
oh I did Listen by the way to Cali's do
you do you say do you feel the same
yeah Kelly you did a good job but I once
again was reminded of you know even I
struggle when singing do you because
there's just like no braver in between
I bet somewhere in here there's more of
that Urban mystical that Titan was
eating quick let's have a look around
before it comes back
YouTube
[Music]
singing a two-person song solo is tough
yeah because
so obviously in some two-person song
yeah yeah that's why that's why it's a
duet yeah yeah
I mean honestly it kind of felt like
that a little bit to me which kind of
influenced me in my decision to put two
chihuahuas in there
yeah because like so many lines overlap
with one another
so
it could have worked as a duet
hmm
you like our when he comes across as a
drug first
oh
good thing is I already forgot about all
of that because it's been too long
I got my first Chinese thank you kit
okay you're blocked blocked forever [\h__\h]
off
how dare you come here and take my luck
and just use it for yourself how dare
you
what you said it's pretty dark
see
no way Nani
oh wow oh it's also with that green
shiny stuff
this is one of the urban mystica it's
exactly how it looked in the book
why so mystical
[Music]
the sweet Urban
is there a spicy one
yes we actually found one and it's all
thanks to Yuki Wawa
now then let's see what does the book
have to say says here that the sweet
Urban mystika is good for good health
and that it helps Aid digestion
what is this music
it's circus music
says it's great for stomach aches too
when you want to stimulate the old
appetite
hmm
no if I can just get him to eat some him
all right now it's my turn to show off
what I can do you're about to get a
taste of my cooking oh
you're gonna cook for me
that is exactly how I sound when I cook
my hello
she meals here you go no I have an
original sandwich Pack full of herbs and
I'll even give you a bed you know where
so thank you for taking on that Titan
Pokemon I call it a Titan batch made it
myself using a replica of the gym badges
you see oh
what does it look like
she's so happy but the baguette looks
kind of burnt I guess it's the lightning
The Shadow
wow
oh
it's kind of cozy
[Applause]
[Music]
I did not even get a single bite from my
baguette and you already come out here
begging for it
you little [\h__\h]
uh what's up with that thing it just
comes out of its ball on its own
whenever it wants yeah I can't control
it
and that acts like as if it's cute and
it's really not cute
what choice do I have it could almost
eat me it's bigger than me
oh
do you want to give your sandwich
what if I say no
what happens do I still give it to him
anyway
I mean at least in Pokemon the
characters don't have to eat food I
guess
bad ending
You Can't Say No Illusion of choice
do I not get like an upgrade
I wonder okay okay take it take it
sound like you give me any choice
yeah I went through all the trouble of
making that for you when you just give
it away oh look at it it's like it's
gonna eat me if I don't give it the
baguette
I hope you realize that's all there was
so now there's no left for you
[Music]
all right they look at me like that
you're gonna make me another one yeah
she gave me he gave me air
because just okay
could have just put the sandwich in your
hand again
you can have half of mine but you'd
better shave her every last bite
[Applause]
well you already ate the whole thing
yeah you saw it
holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] uh
all right could I don't will not be able
to participate in the Olympics because
it's
been uh using things to
make it more skilled doping yes
and there's literally a live stream
proof of it so there is no choice I'm
sorry Collide on your dreams of being an
Olympic runner will not ever
come true well it was me whereas this
thing sort of powered up somehow where
is he looking he's like looking left and
right
in front of you dude look
s
he's playing like it's invisible now and
and Coney Island is like am I invisible
what the [\h__\h] I thought I'm here
well I can't believe it is right in
front of me I don't know why I didn't
see you for a moment I'm so sorry the
power of these herbs really is worth
guarding
it looked like graduating to me
if they had the big infect on your
Pokemon then I bet
could make me stronger too uh never mind
I bet it will come in super handy for
the treasure and assignment we've got
yup that's what I bet
well you've both filled your bellies
with some of my legendary sandwiches I
guess it's time to tidy everything up
oh don't you worry about helping after
battling the Titan you throwing the
brick yeah cause you did not even use an
attack so that is true
just leave all this to me though I'd be
much obliged if you would get a start on
searching out the remaining for urban
mystical for us
okay so what can my kolaidon do now
[Music]
I really owe you
does he plan on using all this on
himself and then he's gonna be the evil
thing the evil protagonist person coast
is clear what
us you can come out now
he's using it on his own Pokemon I guess
but then if if that's really so then why
did he give me any of it anyway he could
have just kept it to himself
I would probably not have said anything
because I'm a protagonist that just lets
everyone do whatever they want with me
what
professor
hello kiwawa this is Santa
I've missed you so much where have you
been what in Italy why did you not bring
me to
I wanted to eat the spaghetti with you
and then meet in the middle and do a um
why why did you not let me do that with
your Chihuahua
I detect the codeidon has regained some
of its original Power it seems it will
now be able to dash at high speed while
you're riding upon it
Dash okay cool I didn't feel like it was
kind of slow yeah
I hope you will continue to explore Paul
day out with Corydon as you have done
here your route is now fixed by the open
before you which really is just a lie
because in the end
the level does not scale
so you're kind of forced to go the
recommended route anyway which pretty
much everybody does anyway so it's an
illusion of choice once again which we
like very much in Pokemon
but still totally do whatever you want
go to the last arena with the highest
level right now do it you can totally do
it don't let your dreams be dreams it is
so manageable it is so possible you can
go anywhere you want nothing will stop
you
so have fun all that you experience will
help you grow in some way great or small
go forth on your journey and take good
care of kuraidon for me
okay
we killed the big crab
and now
I guess we even go to the next Arena or
we try to you know go to the red lady
what do you think chat
to the gym
[Music]
yes agreed
foreign
[Music]
what is the sign there's a grass sign
there
but I have to go here until the city
called artesan
I feel like I missed a lot of them but
okay oh it's a Raid Battle huh
[Music]
wait what is it with my
is my
is my taco man not already level 18.
that will change soon I have a feeling
have we been for that tunnel before oh
yeah that's what you just came out of
let me let me go back and see hey we
can't go in I wanted to explore
you can try solo race you can get some
cool Pokemon that I got the ghost logo
from one of those in the ice tail type
oh should we try one
uh all right
um let's see
let's try this one then
yeah
[Music]
how do I reach that
uh
[Music]
uh that one
it will be my first
wait is it the left one or the right one
uh the left one is just a
terrestrialized Pokemon so it's the
right one never mind
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I felt like that jump could have worked
um
[Music]
but you look weak as [\h__\h]
I'm sorry spoink
no chance for you
oh there's a trainer I don't think I've
battled this one yet
hey yes
what
that's my favorite teacher at the
Academy is
oh oof I don't remember their names but
you will tell me afterwards right
press the left side okay no I'll do it
afterwards
oh cute
heart-shaped uh fish also
why is that make applying right now
normally it's just like standing
why is it flying
[Music]
all right
it just wants to
anyway I don't know what's effective let
me try
um a double kick
[Music]
thick
this feels like it okay I mean there's
ground right below you that you could
just stand on but I guess sometimes it's
less exhausting to fly than to stand on
one leg all the time
maybe it's trying to impress me so that
I keep it
oh now now it's standing
oh
[Music]
thank you I guess for low kick
oh wait
what this feels like it makes it really
easy to accidentally yeah
step on a lot of small Pokemon oh look
at yeah
if I didn't have a fire Pokemon
I might even consider getting you but no
no
here we are
it's just one of those stupid ass boobs
but
[Music]
as a group
does it bring me like NPCs
also it's planned right so I should go
in with um
these spots
[Music]
okay
what are you searching for you're giving
me NPCs anyway right oh wait there's a
link code
are you guys able to get in
[Music]
uh
I'm offline right then why is there a
link code and why is it searching
right here oh do I have to go alone
because that's with okay okay wait what
did this no okay good challenge alone
there's a wrap now you've got a full
party but I wanted to go alone
illusion of choice once again
I'm never alone no privacy for me
wow
not an interesting Pokemon I I will not
catch it but we'll just try to kill it
for the experience
[Laughter]
reflected is just
bugs bugs bugs bugs
[Music]
uh
oh my God
wow
head banging
[Music]
go styling go styling go styling
I killed it I did it
with a critical hit even
music is good
[Music]
don't want no thank you you guys can
have it
oh
so many yeah all right
all right I have like never used been
using the auto panel so I guess I'm
really lacking a lot of items anyway
so maybe this kind of makes up for it a
little bit
if I do it more often
[Music]
um
okay now we go to the arena which is
here
just like that
UMass
and
I don't know of course I just paint them
yeah
don't worry once I leave them behind
they will be
um brought to the next Pokemon Center
and they will be revived every single uh
enemy Pokemon yes yes I am sure
oh yeah
wow cute but what is the meaning of
fighting these by the way because you
don't get oh there it goes
you don't get anything out of it no
LP
oh that's the only thing
oh hello
oh if you want to catch it and it has a
different terror attack than you wanted
it to have
um
wow
[Music]
oh
just normal effective and one kick
killed it
shush
this bird is freaking strong
uh Luxio
[Music]
um
I don't know
which one should I go in with
that's electric okay ground would ground
be good
okay
then I resisted uh with my electric
Pokemon and pack of ground
big brain
I guess the crab would have been okay
too
wait it's level 18 why is it not
evolving
do I have to make it run around now but
then you guys say that first it has to
evolve and then for the last evolution I
have to run around I'm confused
after the battle
oh okay did it uh maybe that level 18
level up just happened uh after the
first enemy
okay okay okay makes sense
[Music]
hit it
I like this Pokemon I like look seal
[Music]
super effective
let's see Evolution time
foreign
let's see
what's will it look like
[Music]
oh
it's a bit bigger not much though
and it looks a little bit more like
Pikachu now
in terms of body shape
you the little the little yummy you miss
oh the fluff the hair fluff it looks
like my hair flop that I had when I was
playing tunic
it's cute
it's still cute I'm happy because most
pokemon when they look cute in the first
um form then afterwards they lose their
cuteness
thank you
part of me turns into power more and it
wants to learn arm pressed I'm pressed
uh let's see
no that's weak as [\h__\h] but this move
hits two times two to five times
ah I don't think we need it right and
now welcome back oh okay okay we can do
it right now
it's good it's stab oh okay I guess oh
was it fighting before or just Electric
then what should we get rid of nozzle
Maybe
you guys want this because of the
paralyzes
[Music]
um okay
look it's not that strong indeed but if
we get a stronger electric attack later
I'm probably gonna get rid of nuzzle
okay
uh
[Music]
a thousand steps how long does that take
shouldn't be too long right
[Music]
one two three four five six seven
six
okay while we do this
is it working it will work right let me
let me um
tangent
[Music]
let me look at my list
you know on the on the flight to Italy
[Music]
um when we were sitting in the plane
because I had my switch with me
I was thinking to play something with
Mommy during the flight so maybe you saw
it in the beginning of the stream that
right next to Pokemon was the Oink games
collection game right right next to it
which means I played it recently
yeah so I was like Mommy let's play this
and she was like no I don't wanna I
don't like like you know I don't know
I'm like yeah but you know let's play it
come on it's just a board game she's
like no I don't wanna no no
she kept on saying no no no no no no
but I Was preparing it and trying to
figure out how to play it multiplayer
and then eventually I got it to work and
then I just forced it onto her and then
she
actually
took it took the controller in her hand
and played it with me and seemingly
actually enjoyed it we played that one
game where you that we also played on
the stream where you go with a Sub sub
Subway sub machine
for you both you know
Marine submarine with a submarine and
you have to go down and then collect
some stuff and go back without dying
before the submarine
uh yeah leaves you because you have no
more air remember that one
it's a game about being not too greedy
but greedy enough to bring some good
stuff home
yeah and of course mommy was in the
beginning very greedy
I told her no that's normal oh everybody
is very greedy the first time they play
the game
I also died in the first round
and then the second round we both were
more careful and she was actually
enjoying it she was getting invested
into it
yeah
so once again I got her to do something
and she ended up enjoying it
yeah
yeah and then the second round we're
both
managed to survive I think
and then there was a third round
where oh we I think we both survived in
the third round
yeah yeah it's really kind of stubborn
yes she is
yes yes my mom is very stubborn yes
Force some things on to her
but at least in this case it was easy it
was a good thing to force onto her some
things you cannot
voice onto her at all
um
all right evolve a few little [\h__\h]
I'm running around
and you just do nothing you need to lose
some weight run run run run run run run
run run run run
he's so cute if it's tiny feet oh my God
it's trying to keep up
you can do it you can do it
dakuma on the diet
after the steps it needs oh you need to
level up well oh but if I stop now it's
like
uh and let's say I stop at 800 steps it
does not reset back to zero steps right
let's let's move on then buy a foot
I wonder if it's a thousand steps but no
there's no step counter
what it does reset it does not okay
it doesn't reset okay okay okay
we'll just fight a little bit
next arena is planned Arena so I will
once again sweep through with my
Fire Starter oh what the [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
um
found oh my God
ah my game capture card oh there we go
oh
shh is is dakama still there yeah nice
cute
just to have a companion on my side I
see wind ooh that kind of sounds cool
oh you don't hear it
[Music]
here with one one I think you need to
oops
just need to clean your ears
quiet for a moment
it do be like that sometimes
Oh I thought you were shiny but you're
the Taco Bell I love Tangled berb
oh there's a ghost thingy up there
there's so many new Pokemon oh yeah yeah
for these ones yeah what do I do
wow is that new
I'm not sure if I remember this one
hmm is that
shopping
I can't look at this it's dancing
that's me that's me
oh my God
it's adorable
have we arrived in the city
oh my God we have
[Music]
dancing fire verb yay
I want to learn that dance tango or any
dance really like any classical kind of
dance like I guess not classical but one
of those dances I want to learn one of
those dances I want to take a dancing
class but I need a partner a dance
partner
um
someone who is motivated to do that too
I want to learn one of those dance
oh oh it's the balloon Ghost Pokemon
drifloon I like that one too it's cute
I'm not going into the city yet I gotta
fight those trainers
it's just a little child but I'm gonna
absolutely destroy you
I've been so much fever night oh that
would be so cool too I don't know take a
class that's like 80s aerobics
and dressed up like according to that
that's happening looks huge right next
to you
[Music]
why is there so much time in between
you got anything else
um
nope okay oh I know running around cute
all right sorry for taking your lunch
money
[Music]
that seems so mean to take away from a
child that's young way younger than me
just for losing a battle
it's like bullying I don't want your
money I don't want your lunch money you
should keep it
it's so sad
yellow [\h__\h]
how dare you
and I have nothing effective against you
the cricket
you're cute though
kind of cute
you got double kick and yeah wow
that's impressive
I don't have to fight you but you know
what I will
whoa
it evolves into a common rider Pokemon
wow
this video sounds like myself routines
I think it's the base in the background
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah hear it a little bit
you can keep
416.
thank you so much
that is so sweet
are you still able to buy yourself some
lunch even if I take it are you sure
we killed it
[Music]
anything else interesting here should we
just go into the
into the city
I guess we'll just go into the city oh
wait I didn't fight you what's up
um
let me
put Connie onto the front row
and do you mind
I got Kinder chocolate Christina
oh
um
uh so ghosts are strong against ghosts
but I have I think actually I do have a
ghost attack somewhere
and what else is strong
against Ghost dark okay well then I
guess we go to the bread dog
okay okay okay at least I remember that
ghost Australians goes that is quite
amazing
but I remember that
I remember that because it's like so
unusual
foreign
[Music]
I guess it has no poison attack
in its move set
well it just has a stupid AI
that is a dark verb right
um
I still don't know
he
well
I still don't know what's strong against
flying and dark
okay I want to see the crystallizing
[Music]
making me time
oh my God there's a big crunch with
angel wings
[Music]
that is sour
cheesy
so cute though
so girly
Rock and electric good against flying
okay let me try to remember that
thank you
um
let's go
how do you make the auto battles does it
live wait
this
oh
gradually wrong
[Music]
oh baby a triple
just killing could you have had like a
critical somewhere in there
oh man
now let me try it again
um do I have to do the focus though
because I did that and it felt right
it's like you [\h__\h] jump on me like
that oh come back come back
[Music]
I want to throw you
go attack can you do it are you gonna
survive it
oh come on good job
we're gonna fight that one too
motivated oh better not fight that one
though I don't think you can make it
a lot of bad things won't evolve and I
just want to do it because
um
of the EXP
erience
hey you don't want to fight it why why
do you know you can't win the fight
oh hello hello
yes go go go go
where you going where are you where are
you good you're supposed to fight the
coming
here this one this one
let's go come on
nice I'm so proud I'm the proudest
document mother
s ever
I raced that child
I raised that child
what what
why does it not know where to go
oh we got a new move oh my God
do I have to wait for another level up
for the
for the evolution to happen
oh [\h__\h]
oh for [\h__\h] sake
I didn't know we were so close
thank you
my help
going
yes
there you go
and what about this one
yes yes yes yes
okay let's keep an eye on on the ESP
this time
okay nice nice cleaning up
now let's just do uh
I wonder if it can kill the makuhita but
let's try these ones
oh okay where are you going
we're almost level up again
okay now let's do a normal fight oh
what's right before the level up okay
okay okay normal fight normal fight
normal fight normal fight
see the final
[Music]
and everything's a [\h__\h] super
effective amazing amazing we got a big
repertoire
hit it hit it
[Music]
Pokemon Center and safety first what
nothing's gonna happen
one
please don't Court
polishes itself that's so cute
that's so cute
I bet it's not gonna evolve why would it
not evolve oh because maybe I didn't do
the 100 steps ah
oh
I feel like we did a thousand steps yeah
I feel like I feel like we did
simple
foreign
[Music]
you look funny
um
you look a bit funny but overall like it
looks barely have changed since it's
like first stage so I guess maybe that's
a good thing that it didn't change too
drastically
it still looks okay it's like
I would have maybe hoped for a little
bit more difference actually
um
very hairy very fancy hair like it's
using so much styling gel
trying to impress
the other Bears out there
Hands-On Pokemon we did
we did Revival blessing that sounds
really fancy what is that
[Music]
uh use the user bestows a loving
blessing Reviving a party Pokemon that's
fainted and restoring half of it it's a
[\h__\h] healer in an mmor p
that's amazing
I don't think I've ever heard of that
move before is that new Reviving another
party member
don't remember that
mama
it is new huh
interesting hmm
I don't think I would want to waste a
spot
but it's quite a special move
only this one can learn it wow
[Music]
that's foreign
how is this better than just revive yeah
right because
I mean you're using one move for it at
the same time you could use an item
the only reason you would use it is
because you're out of the items Maybe
or
it's good for ah if a competitive we're
not allowed to use items oh
oh true
oh [\h__\h] okay well maybe if we do
um
a competition where we're not allowed to
use items and I will put it in my
moveset
wow that's interesting I am I find it
very interesting that they put a revive
your party member kind of skill
into a skill
whatever I say makes no sense but you
know what I mean right
Reviving a party member
very fresh
foreign
okay
let me heal again
no comprendo
oh let me change the picture then
um wait for me promo and Paul what pom
pom
um
[Music]
I don't know
I want the pink one
[Music]
now it's already fully evolved oh man
I wonder if it will ever show up in like
the world in its final evolution
so that I can get it in in pink
[Music]
they grow up so fast too
I wanted and shiny
what I don't know what I'm so hopeful
for it now like in my previous Pokemon
flavors I wasn't so desperate for a
shiny because I did not quite see it as
a possibility but now I see everyone
getting
it again
[Music]
they're bikes yo
they got like a really cheap version of
my bike
gotta learn for him
[Music]
I think they need to oil
the wheel over there
because it's moving really choppy put
some WD-40 or something like that in
there
ah
what's up
what's up everybody new town what's up
they got like these sunflower Pokemon
here but they're just statues I guess
[Music]
Muhammad's whole line can swim
I never doubted it could not do that or
could do that um
what is that oh oh is that the final
evolution of fly baby oh I didn't see
that ever before
oh
it gets pretty big and quite pretty
wow look actually I like it
is
the first time
interesting what is that
what is that in the back behind you
weird
wow that's a cute
boy crap
oh my God what a paradise for a kid
oh that looks so fun the climbing walls
but honestly if the climbing walls are
so short like those you can't really get
anywhere they need to like make it
taller
that one's okay that one makes sense
but the other one is just like you grab
onto one and that's it
oh
to browser I I did for the airfryer
stream I saw I looked up like a churro
recipe thingy forever but it actually
needed quite more effort than I expected
it to
um I want to make it at some point
though
but that time before that was not the
time but I want to do it
I still don't understand these stats
but I really want to make churros
my brother recently had lots of churros
because my brother was in Spain recently
and he told me he was eating Churros
every freaking day
understandable right can I swim oh my
God
it's like a baby like like those tacos
that you hold above the water or
anything going well and they're playing
like that it's so cute
oh
[Music]
that's what it looks stupid though are
you ever gonna learn to swim properly
try throwing Palmer in the water
[Music]
it's like Mommy look I can swim yeah
Mommy come get into the one or two okay
wow cute swimming bear wow it swims so
much better than my bike
wow the water actually looks good
would it be nice to have some kind of
pattern
though like Mosaic pattern
on the ground
the reflection looks nice though and the
water movement looks nice
but if it had some some pattern there
that would look so good
every freaking pool has that I feel like
and then put like a Pokemon
uh art in the pattern would be perfect
in my opinion
oh well I guess I'm not part of Game
Freak so
what can I do oh yeah
[Music]
oh it's the gem
hi Jim
my name's kiwawa
[Music]
oh it's you again how the hell are you
here bye um
so welcome we ended up randomly visiting
the same gym at the same time again
I feel like she might be
part of my Discord group girl stalk
[Laughter]
what a weird coincidence
um I swear I'm not just sneaking ahead
of you so I can lie in wait what can lie
in weight
in line in weight
line can lie and is that correct
that makes sense
can lie and wait
and go
sounds so weird to me
okay oh wow weird might as well battle
now that you're here
we're in battle last time so you're
welcome to Bellamy now girl no seriously
look to prove it I won't even challenge
you to a battle or something
but I would like to
as much as I'd like to well we have the
same feeling why don't we do it but look
at you on your Pokemon why shouldn't we
have or where could we have bumped into
each other since the last time we met
because it sounded like the next time I
was gonna see her I was gonna battle her
but it didn't happen
where could I have met her
add this to the mix and you'll be 100
set to go no problem
oh we face
um
I'll go train
[Laughter]
20 20 Pokemon well you know you can only
put five of them in your team right
you're so motivated
hello please let me do the the thing
yes I'm kiwawa
and you are pretty
great now in order to face gym leader
professions you'll first need to pass
the gym test
here at the Artisan gym that means
completing a game of sunflower hide and
seek
as you may know Artisan is a city of
artists the artwork made by the people
here is largely inspired by nature and
the Sun that nurtures it since sunflower
embodied these Concepts we try to gather
them and take good care of them your job
today is to find sunflower located
throughout Artisan remember this Pokemon
look like sun shapes flowers
gather up 10 of them and bring them to
the sunflower floral on and you pass the
test I'll register sunflower Lawrence
location in your map app to get you
started when you leave the gym turn
right and you'll see two large sunflower
statues head for those
once you're at the Lamb's entrance the
staff are there will tell you more about
the gym test
now get out there and have fun
[Music]
ah INTP I think I saw a clip of that I
know what you're talking about
it's um
ridiculous
we shall do that
for the memes I mean but it's no
surprise like look at all the NPCs
where could they be I see one over there
does that count as one
not really hiding but
was it a statue
I guess that one's just a statue
they're like scattered in the city
though right
[Music]
yeah oh I need to talk to the lady first
oh
I thought we have started already wait
what lady should
uh
[Music]
her
hello you're getting really wet here are
you okay
you're soaked you need a
umbrella
I have one you want to share one
let's go that's so unnecessary I should
have just started the moment I stepped
out of the gym
okay
yeah let me move
oh
what about this one
oh my God it's already low FPS
now it's better
okay I found that one is it following me
oh
[Music]
so the big ones I guess are all statues
but is that one
no
no no
[Music]
how far
[\h__\h] did I cancel it no okay good oh
thank God
maybe one is over there hello that one
that one
that one could be one but it's not
really moving
I guess not
oh I can't ride corn I don't know
what oh
yes
need more sunflowers oh
by the way what the [\h__\h]
was it seriously just running away from
me you want some bathtub
uh should I should have put my my fire
starter in the front
um
it's some plants right
two of them will fight me
it's a battle one
interesting
one more come on one more nice
four times
wow
oh
no don't kill yourself back up that's
the cool thing about plant Pokemon then
being able to use that
I like that more I only had one fight me
well I hope they learned their lesson
now I hope this
this will be a lesson for all the
sunflowers
all over
they better
be smart
a hello there
don't don't don't you dare
what
[Music]
there's two and I'm getting the those
two exactly those two right off the bat
you had zero fight you
but some people don't even know you but
aren't they always in the same location
the ones that you have to find
or is it random
anyway no problem
just have to
you know
might break them and then they will know
what to do
and what not to do can they follow me
are you
oh you're not part of them
okay four how many was I supposed to
look for 10.
how about it back here oh
[Music]
kind of cute how they go like purple
when they see me just like my kitty cats
oh hello
[Music]
there's so many now
I mean
[Music]
just don't look behind
cute
it's pretending a great Pretender
you can't fool me
[Music]
why have we not gone yet ah in here
wow there's a big
big hands
kind of cool
oh
and
nine one more
[Music]
what was that
oh wait there's one inside I think
oh I have been amazed
[Music]
foreign
oh my God
I got them all I mean I'm guessing
there's even more but uh
let's go let's go so what me fighting
the two sunflowers is basically the
equivalent of me fighting the trainers
before the big boss
just two sunflowers that's kind of weak
yeah oh
no hold on
[Music]
all right there you go
take them out take them on me
[Music]
all 10 of them
surprise surprise surprise
who the font
well done in finding uh all this
sunflower you'll pass the gym test with
flying colors now please head back to
the lobby at The Artisan gym to report
yourself
okay
we'll do
thanks for taking these flowers off my
hands they were supposed to
kind of be like a
a way of telling you I love you and I
want to go on a date with you but I
guess it didn't come across like that I
thought giving flowers to a lady would
have that effect
honey honey
these flowers at the higher frame rate
oh you're telling me the low FPS
sunflowers I'm not gonna impress a lady
normally they wouldn't even be alive
okay people told me to give people you
know normal flowers now I give her a
live flowers and you're telling me
that's not impressive no matter what FPS
they are they should be impressive
am I ready
I guess
now I'm ready
[Music]
let's fight the dude
these flowers will live long as we go
hey
I recently you know I had one plant that
I've had for a while
um that got some like tiny tiny tiny
tiny bugs infecting it and I noticed a
little bit too late so
but when I noticed I saw that it was
getting really dry all the leaves and
they were falling out so I just thought
okay it needs more water but eventually
I noticed it was getting real so dry and
losing its leaves because of the bugs on
it like really tiny ones yeah that look
kind of like tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny
spiders or so yeah and they were making
some
tiny tiny webs as well
yeah right next Challenger
oh
yeah then once I noticed it was already
pretty late because like it lost so many
leaves and the ones that were still on
it were 60 just like
you touch it and they fall off really
bad so I I bought like a spray that's
anti-bug I didn't have one yet because I
didn't have this problem before
then I got rid of them I sprayed like
the whole plant and I got rid of all the
the leaves that were bad
and then the plant was basically
stripped naked almost
um but very soon after it started like
um spreading its wings again and uh yeah
new new tiny baby leaves were starting
to sprout and that made me quite happy
so right now it's sprouting and it looks
like it's gonna make a good Revival I
saved it just in time
I don't telephone
drifted yeah no I think it was necessary
all the Dead Leaves you have to remove
them hmm
it's looking good did Mama tell you
commented yeah she was happy that I
because I told her about the I sent her
some pictures when I noticed the bugs
and I was like Mommy what are those
yeah and then she told me to buy some
bug killer uh like food Coco but I
didn't have a full cocoa at the time
so no she didn't say that but
he doesn't like Pokemon but yeah and now
it's fixed and yeah I think it should be
fine yeah and another plant that I a
smaller plant that I unfortunately
killed
and for some reason it's also sprouting
again so
plants but I'm also
for not being good with plants I'm good
at Reviving things as the Phoenix so
you'd as well to come this far I am
Brussels
specializing in grass type Pokemon I'm
also the gym leader here at the Artisan
gym
I was observing your gym test from Atop
The Windmill you know the one that moves
into FPS
Junior displayed in finding sunflower
was truly
oh how shall I describe it
yes it was truly avant-gard
is that supposed to be a pun
I don't get an is it Maybe not maybe
he's just really fascinated by me
wow thank you you have a weird hairline
that's up
really weird hairline but I like how his
hair looks like a cacti somehow
I have Garden ah maybe that ah Garden
I only pray that you might demonstrate
that eye for beauty you know but it was
well
and after we must begin creating a
collaborative work of art
oh
he's an artist guys
I trust that you already it is time for
a masterpiece to take shape
wow
hot
oh
was that with me oh okay
you were challenged with your little
gracias
oh that's so cute
are just creation and destruction
struggle else you defeat will nourish my
Pokemon
I say burn and you say
faint
yes face
[Music]
now I'll burn it
roasted veggies
oh no no sweetie what what small lip
well I'm guessing it's a plant Pokemon
would be nice to have an evolved Pokemon
in front of me by now
well that did not have an evolution
there's so many plant Pokemon
give me something stronger so
no I love sudow
um
[Music]
I'm very overpowered oh
the last time um the gym leader the last
Pokemon was not of the gym type but the
Terra sterilization made it into the gym
type this time we have a plant Pokemon
but they're gonna use a personalization
that's not
uh
class Maybe
what you gonna do what you gonna do
it's rock type originally
[Music]
okay that must be a mistake that many
people do okay okay so it is a common
theme that the last Pokemon that didn't
trainers use is not of their type but
they make it that type but
terrestrialization okay so I can still
always be safe with using
what I'm just using until then
[Music]
whoa
whoa what's up
avant's guard what what does that mean
I've heard it so many times it's like uh
something you say about cool art things
right
I don't know
oh what artistic tactics you employ
the patterns of your moves the minute
details of your Pokemon's performance
everything you did was
hold to Perfection our battle was in a
word art indeed if we could not call
that a work of art history then nothing
else in this world not even the Mona
Lisa could be labeled as such as you
were more pretty than she ever could
have been if I were to judge your work I
could say I would say it should be in
the Louvre right now as the most popular
exhibition piece anyway can I take a
selfie with you because like I'm a huge
fan now
[Music]
nice cute this one is already always
turned out so cute
I like them one night
a little 30 okay
a TM trailblaze okay
my inspiration is overflowing as I've
drawn from a bottomless well
I will begin on a new piece at once you
must excuse me farewell
foreign
have you gone to your classes oh no I
haven't should I are there classes
what is there to learn
should I go
[Music]
is it worth it
oh there are classes oh yeah we are in
school I have the Hollywood thing I know
who's that person oh
are you the person from my phone
not away
Lauren basic knowledge your classes yes
I should exercise you can if you want if
you pass the midterms and fans because
you speak any um
maybe I'll do it off screen
pardon me
um would you be the killer I've been
hearing so much about
oh my God your eyes are terrifying
they kind of look like Stein skate eyes
the Mona had mentioned there was a
promising new facing the academy yes
indeed oh but I do apologize I didn't
mean to tell you by addressing you
suddenly
my name is Hasselhoff I'm one of the
Elite Four Elite Four
oh
of the Pokemon League
I also teach art classes at the Academy
big eyes man
so do tell me young kiwawa what
compounds you to collect these gym
badges and strive to be a champion
my friend asked me
I wanna say that just because it's
stupid
or for fun I guess I wanna
yeah cause my friend asked me too
[Music]
Ashton answered thank you
sounds like a bad answer
naturally there's no single correct
answer I'll pass later the great creator
of paldia as they say I was told I'm not
allowed to go there though
you know your friend namona is the
youngest Chief Champion rank in all
paldian history
it is entirely possible that such great
potential lies within you as well
[Music]
call that cute hair
it's like as if he has a
a seven-year-old daughter
who he tries his best because mom is
busy also to style his daughter's hair
to make her happy and send her to school
with cute hairstyles and then exchange
the daughter will then try to give him a
cute hairstyle and he has to wear it the
whole day because if his daughter sees
him without it then she's gonna cry and
be like Daddy why did you not like him
then you why
oh that's why he has those curls at the
bottom at the Little ponytail there
isn't that a cute story yeah
he's a good dad yeah he's just trying to
make and to to be a good replacement mom
should you continue to strive to reach
Champion rank you will one day have to
battle me and I really don't want to
lose because I have to impress my
seven-year-old daughter you know but
anyway that should matter to you he
would be wise to train hard starting now
I will save you from experiencing the
bitter regret of defeat as well as
divorce
um so come along to my art class
sometime I would prefer to have you
attend
laughs
don't beat him tonight when the time
comes yum
okay should hire me to find NPC bags
noise oh
what have you noticed there are lots of
students passing through here today it
has this restaurant started yep well you
seem to be the only one who's not
treasure hunting or who's not into
Pokemon
are my Pokemon's healed
yeah well the voice thing makes more
sense with him doing the hairstyles of
his daughter you know kind of divorce
him okay they're not hands but doesn't
matter so we did that
oh are there items hidden in the city
too
I don't think I saw any
[Music]
but I want to run around a little bit
and check to make sure because what is
that
anything
interesting here end of the maze really
I was thinking there must be something
to reward me
what
ready
on it
you give me something
you actually found your way here nice
almost no one ever makes it this far so
let's have to make it into my secret
base
[Music]
there it is poison tail oh
what is this way I guess it's art
this weird City in I was gonna say but
it's supposed to be an artistic City
also I like these these pathways they
remind me of old Pokemon games
and there was like a trainer here in
every freaking corner
and you were bicycling through and uh
underneath was water
right
oh there's another item
hmm what is this so this is it what what
is it
fling because I think this is Health
item in the Target to attack
I can't just say this famous piece I
can't say I really get it but I like it
well it's just like a flower no
just sounds one of my favorites design
wise
yeah I think I like the vibe I mean some
of the art pieces kind of look like out
of place but that's I guess the point of
like putting art everywhere
it's like it's a little bit difficult to
make it blend in light like this stuff I
mean
like hmm
it's interesting though
it looks cool
so shiny
[Music]
Okay so
can we leave the city already where
where where where where where should we
go next
should we check her out finally
I want to I want to mellow
apple Lady Red Apple lady
I love her I love her the first time I
saw her I [\h__\h] squealed
because she's gorgeous
chest she's so cute I love her fire
boots I mean they're obviously
it's so hard to walk in I can't imagine
myself walking in them
but she got style she's like on fire
can I go around here
yeah they're fashion it's a fashion
statement and she has like
a really good design in my opinion I
like her color theme
song
Sunny dang oh sunny day
when Jesus was when Jesus
foreign
what are those
[Music]
hey because they're together
I think I saw this one though like it
just becomes more and more mice right
I think
it's funny is it good
it's funny but it's weird it's
oh that's so funny ah the names the pun
names oh man I wish Ina was here to see
this
foreign
oh they get a couple unique moves really
what type are they
they look like normal type to be honest
I can't imagine them being anything
besides normal oh they are normal okay
that makes sense no more time you know
it's kind of boring
okay I'm gonna tackle you
why do I still have tackle in my moveset
what the [\h__\h]
they can learn dragging them
normal but good
um I kind of like them they're funny if
I ever seen them again in their
evolution
I might think about adopting them
and then I'll call them Casper's
plural
but it's a weird Pokemon because it's
literally just copy paste one Mouse and
make more of them
what's that
what city is that
well this one oh
it's wearing this girl
Fiona lives levinsia
[Music]
so shiny
[\h__\h] it's not shiny
I thought it was
normally
I got so excited
or maybe the pink is the shiny but oh
it's a seasonal version
cake
both of me like that
damn it's seasonal version It's kidding
me
so rude
he said something I don't know he died
so mean what other colors does it have
just so I know
to not get excited next time I see it
and like it's winter coat or something
don't blame your disappointed thank you
white
brown pink green and white well then
what's the color if it's shiny
charger can we pretend that it is a
shiny because I'm really desperate can
we pretend
then it is so shiny shiny makes a flower
with its head pink oh but then it keeps
its seasonal color and just the flower
changes color oh
oh that's hard to see
if that's true
all right we are exploring
yeah
we taking my show quick ball
just roughly
[Music]
oh
is that working from
bye
bumps into the pretty Flamingo burp
Flamingo that's what it was not Tango
right
oh it won't let me go
away
all right let me go out
a flamenco
did I just say Flamingo this is called
in Flamingo in German it might be called
flamingo in German that's why I said
that
happy awesome
maybe no never mind it's just Flamenco
Flamingo is literally the pink verb
I'm just it sounds so familiar
hmm I'm at the end of the world
[Music]
I don't know I felt like jumping
dear Lord
can I land on the layers before that
though I wonder
probably not even if I could then
there's nothing there are you shiny
the yellow ones weren't do they also
have seasonal colors because I think
they were green before
are they shiny
what the [\h__\h]
I mean it would be where the ball of
them were shiny right
they have multiple colors
oh they're blue
um
in it
hi Hopi oh what is that
is that a shiny
[Music]
does that turn green for real
or is it supposed to be pink
it's just the evolution
[Laughter]
oh never mind
this is terrible
this is just bullying
showing me all these different colors oh
hello are you a trainer you got a good
view
can I can I have thank you
but I wonder what level she has
one million polka dollars
to build
I'm challenged by Isabel devices no no
no I am charged by Isabella the waitress
for what I don't know maybe it comes
afterwards bye Doug
[\h__\h] that's water
level 17 okay no match but uh
yeah okay
now this is my problem I only have
nothing I need a
different electric move because nozzle
has a strength of 20.
only 20.
I just caught my first journey okay shut
up get out of here
and
what road to come in here and tell me
they got a [\h__\h] shiny
[Music]
so rude that Flex oh yo even of strength
20 it does so much against Psyduck
um
oh oh I should check them okay okay I
will do let me check the menu
[Music]
you got the map from yeah I think so too
um
not the right things
[Music]
you can't get attacked if you're in this
menu can you
it seems like it oh no wait what um
how do I look at it again
wait
there was a tower us
here this is the one
so we got wild charge oh
90 but it damages the user level
[Music]
um
nothing good I think did I get a good TM
in the meantime on the wave electron
I mean electrical is good
oh no never mind
the fast the user is then the target
um
Thunder Punch while charges good
I just work for now okay
okay
hope it doesn't do too much damage
that's a little cow
[Music]
all right
descending
did you guys watch my YouTube music
weekend thingy
today I was trying to watch it but like
I saw the chat move and like cheering
and so on but my YouTube was bugging no
matter how many times I refreshed it on
my phone it still said
um like first it's so sad like 60
minutes until the stream starts
so often and then eventually I kind of
broke it and I just could not like get
it to work at all even if I refresh it
what the [\h__\h] is that
what the is that
speed Dance Evolution
no way absolutely no way
no way
it looks like a character from Rick and
Morty now
what
what coins
no way it turns to spool right okay
that's kind of funny but like
it's it's weird it changed too much
it's weird it was so much cuter before
Oh but that's kind of cute when it's
together with the small ones
okay
funny
weird stuff
yo now that I'm finally catching up on
on my Pokemon
Adventure I can continue watching the
playthrough from dumptendo
I had to hold back oh yo look at those
fancy ah isn't this original form oh my
God there's so many
that was the original form right because
normally it's uh Brown I think
what happened what type does it get
oh let's go over there
I'm gonna be so mad if I run by a shiny
I'm gonna like Rage Quit
what is this
it's so hard to see what [\h__\h] Pokemon
it is
it the sunflower Pokemon all right I'll
check it out
all right baby
oh the the the after Club in the right
but not the final evolution in between
it was kind of cute
uh wait is this carrotype plant and it's
originally fairy interesting
I don't really care for it though
it's raining
oh no my attacks will be weaker oh my
God Chihuahua knows that her fire
attacks will be weaker when it's raining
oh she's a genius
yeah
I don't want to catch it
I don't want
what
oh because now it's Berry
[Music]
now it's fairy so my Fire doesn't do
[\h__\h] screw to cover the Bell
oh yeah it heals me too
please what a friendly Pokemon
um fairy um
um use metal claw
okay
feel against fairy still against fairy
still against fairies still against
fairies still against Ferry silgan's
fairy civil against Ferry silicon fairy
still a poison
against family still poison against
fairy stealing poison against fairies
this is wish
is that also heel attack oh my God
oh it's only so little you know what
I'll catch you
spam
the output is that actually like a thing
that Pokemon players use to remember
this
[Music]
which became true
what is this fight how triggering
they just look at the charts
[Music]
yo it's pissing me off
how dare you
just
let me catch you so I don't have to be
this triggered anymore oh you little
[\h__\h]
Moana
did not even consider it
insulting
I'll kill him
no I don't want to use the other balls
and seems to have learned an attack
snarl
55.95
hmm
it's only five powerless
five accuraciness but it also has the
effect of special attack yeah okay
or even get rid of tackle
then we have one physical and one
special
dark move which I never know which one
to use anyway that's even more difficult
for me than remembering the high Pikachu
remembering oh it's a female one cute
remember oh my God it's on the tree this
is
remembering the the element thing is
yeah yeah don't don't yeah
okay uh
is that a shiny no
I think I've seen that before
thank you
I just scratches the tree and runs
around the map
yo this bike is lit someone lost and spy
bike normal Dragon interesting
so
does the evolution of that one look
different from the bike that I have
free bike free bike
it's a weak bike though
catch the bike it's good oh it's a
dongle
hey doggle
um I guess I when I'm gonna challenge it
but wait what element will it have do I
know that beforehand
yeah wait the spark on the top right
right the top right that's a bug thingy
okay
I want snack
chocolate snack
how long have you been streaming three
and a half hours wow it's actually this
time normally it feels like shorter but
this time it feels way longer I feel
like I've been playing for five hours
cute
I'm still not gonna catch yourself
I'm just doing it for the items
chocolate
[Music]
yo he got a crocodile Pokemon
with a bug type is actually pretty
interesting
hmm
[Music]
I think one of my center of uses I just
got one too
[\h__\h]
wow
[Music]
that's not fair every shiny you guys get
while watching me stream
you know you owe it to me right you have
to send it to me
hi bye
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
bye bye
[Music]
um
now some piggy transformation but why
did it look different from the farm what
happened with its ears
[Music]
um
it does look different what the hell is
this female
hmm
it does look quite different I think
it's really cool when they have
different looks depending on their
gender
it gives them even more variety
see at that I'm not mad at the seasonal
forms I'm very mad at those
that is
acceptable all right what do we have
here
tomato Berry
you're so cute
little Leo
seasonal a left over from Gen 5 is that
a thing they just liked doing there a
lot what is that ah wait settle dog of
the candle
Bubba and it's type it originally is
Ghost but it's now dark
oh
my girl I might even catch this one
[Music]
I know you know
the dog has a busted move
a Gen 5 had different seasons every
month Ah that's why they did that oh
cool
oh
is it shiny can it be shiny in the rain
it's very shiny like in terms of okay
being sparkly
[Music]
all right I probably went in with the
wrong Pokemon uh
but it's dark now I guess my only choice
is instant
Academy hmm
Chinese yellow oh
[Music]
well that will never happen to me
anyway
take it down take it down
it has a move that's as strong as five
earthquakes oh my God but that's also
like kill you is it one of those KO
moves
[Music]
it's a shiny charm
I already forgot what we talked about
should I use a normal ball
I kind of wanna but if it fails or is it
a guaranteed get though
there
what normal will do it is 100 okay cool
then we can use the normal one
oh thick moves girl whoa what's
happening with
my holy [\h__\h]
I think
I think they used so much time
on this part of the game this this one
part
very
very detailed
[Laughter]
hmm
very detailed very intricate very
sparkly
this side of the dog but when I died in
the wild without ever interact with a
human was
oh
sorry
[Laughter]
oh
sorry
I will send into my box but maybe I will
join my team at some point
your Nintendo's missed you yeah you're
still playing Nintendogs
I did
I would even stream it if I could or in
10 cats or whatever the name was oh
there's a whole area down there
probably shouldn't go down there now
creep all those Nintendo
I think they're fine
oh hi
they're probably fine don't worry about
them
and we're sent to
someone to take care of them
that looks like the island I left
circles on oh
upstairs
[Laughter]
exactly holy [\h__\h] this one's 23 level
23.
[Music]
wow
holy [\h__\h]
my last level 27.
okay then it's good that we fight some
monsters here oh [\h__\h]
all right
that might be a bad idea I don't know I
don't know what this is it dark
what's good against dark
okay then maybe that was smart
spiking okay and apparently whatever I
had used it wasn't good on me so if if
it's fighting move was weak against
fairy then that probably means that
fairy is strong against fighting
the right Pokemon but it's still gonna
kill me oh my God
thank God it's only double cake and not
triple kick
but we survived
damn you know what I wanna heal
um my little boy and then we fight a
couple of those Tauruses work up what's
that
uh
what slam
come on and slam and wake up to the gym
or something like that oh 80 75 nah
a lot of pools new WeatherTech
see
[Music]
okay bye bye water gun
good I was hoping for a stronger one
attack because also we need water
attacks for Mela right
she's probably gonna use fire Pokemon
she looks like fire so
we have
water against that and
what else do we have
oh wait
no
[Music]
Rock oh okay okay okay
he's just [\h__\h] stressing me out don't
do that
oh maybe never mind fight fight normal
normal fight
so yeah they are bullish you may want to
level your crap okay crab will crush her
crush crash
Crush Crush Crush once before nothing
compared to a quiet aiming alone just
don't want to
do
I don't understand
this
holy [\h__\h] they're so
strongly evolve title do I just have to
wait
I feel like it's about time that fight
to evolves as well
oh level up maybe now
maybe no no no I guess not
okay
just wait level 24. bake it yeah it
looks uh Raw
looks like raw dough doesn't it
uh wait so doc this is probably also
dark so I can fight these two right oh
wait let me interact normally
26 oh okay
maybe I will remember finally the berry
is good again it's dark by doing this
continuously
cocoa
foreign
having a fairly fairy Steel Dragon
monster on your team is really strong
I have a fairy sealed Dragon monster on
my team
you do
do I do I
[Music]
need more physical pain though oh what
physical works better against this one
oh but look at that one hit nice
combo of planting some free programs
[Music]
m
I think
what is that that's new that looks like
that um the tentacle tentacles Pokemon
from the ocean but on land
is it a regional form of that
grass grounds
it looks funny and it's pink it could
work for a pink tea
it's it is
so it looks like it
is
okay the lion and wait so what did you
say poison plant or ground or so
uh
what did you say
grass ground okay but ground resist fire
right
well grass doesn't
so
what else what else what else is there
uh what's good against ground well
um water no
it's flying ice
use Amica
one is four times
ground does not resist fire oh
[Music]
okay I found the [\h__\h] because you know
if you throw some some Earth
[Music]
I'm thinking if you throw a bunch of
Earth against it it runs
it runs buddy
oh my God
it looks so stupid
well I love it Toad's cool that sounds
like
um a name Iris would come up with like
Iris so cool
oh my God it looks so funny it looks
like a joke
[Laughter]
man I'm so mean
it looks good though I like that it
looks like a joke
legs
uh off screen I went on top of one of
those towers and it had the the treasure
chest and I think they're up on all
these towers right but there's also an
item there even if you don't care
about the oh
are you oh
what are you wearing
superhero outfit or
yeah are you like did you escape from a
new Marvel movie recording
um let's find
Dragon Tamar oh [\h__\h] uh dragon
fairy
she's smirking
foreign
if it's if it's planned as well then
fire could work
dragon breath okay wanna try let me try
let me try
pretty good oh
good for not even being effective
just normal
nice
[Music]
nice nice nice nice nice
little nothing and you guys said the the
kanikani
uh will be helpful so I want to level it
a little bit but
um what is this
things
like who do I let it fight
cool which of these Pokemon are safe to
fight with my with my crab
maybe the whole bit
fire and birds okay let me try to find
some birds
because of flying right but then maybe
these ones would be good too
puppets
oh I guess that little thing on this the
hair on his head oh
oh
both effective all right
10 and let's take it down
train a little bit here
mohawk
hey it didn't look like fire to me it
looked like normal
type or something like that
oh you guys want to hear a story that um
make me super sad
foreign
you know on the day where I was
um working on the hollow talk recording
like subtitling it editing it and so on
when I was in the big big time crunch
something happened
that was
the most
scary thing I've had happen to me
since
years
[Music]
um so
I don't even like talking about it but
you guys you know I
I share things with you so instead of
is that a is that a shiny
it's like Pinker than usual I feel like
[Music]
not though right it's not shiny right
okay
I'm imagining things
um
shiny is bright pink okay
so
I was like
um in the middle of working on that
stuff you know
and but I I took a little break on my
balcony
and my my cats have been with me for
what four or five years or so now
and even when I lived like with my
roommate before for example
when I had a balcony there too no matter
what balcony they were on they never
cared for like experimenting
with it you know never at all
uh protect I don't care about that
um so you already have a feeling of
where this is going
[Music]
um
but I was out there with them together
and like really like I've I've spent a
lot of time with them on the balcony
in those years and they just never care
about like they don't look interested in
like jumping away you know
but yeah
um this so this one time
smoothie that little [\h__\h] you know how
I've been telling you Smoothie has been
insanely cheeky recently
jumping up on places where she should
not be on in the kitchen
trying to annoy the [\h__\h] out of me
you're such a cheeky little [\h__\h] yeah
she's so adventurous and so she just
zooms around
and the thing is well
she was zooming
she started filming on the balcony you
know when cats Zoom they just zoom they
just run run run
and she did something insane I was
watching her like my eyes I had my eyes
on her but it happened so fast like I
couldn't do anything
sushi
basically jumped on this super super
super super super thin
railing of the balcony fence which she
never even thought about doing before
ever before
in high speed she does that in high
speeds yeah
she only took one step on the railing
and then like just jumped onto the next
balcony
and my heart
stopped
I I was so scared to death
and I was like
[Music]
my heart stopped like really I was I was
that was so scary
because she could have fallen easily
like it was
how how could she even have known like
where to go from the I don't know man
she's insane
um
let me check this
to say five
should I switch it out or keep wild
charge
yeah she has I know cats have good
balance but they can always make a
mistake and then yeah not good
okay
so
I
I was like
I I I can't even
describe to you how [\h__\h] shocked I
was and scared for her I
so I looked over
to where she was then
and I it's it was like pretty much
impossible
to just like pick her up
and bring her back that was not possible
in this situation and I also did not
want her to try to do the same thing
backwards to come back to me because it
just seemed too dangerous if she would
slip and fall
these are not good
um
yeah
especially like
I don't know
if I would try to hold her and then I
make a little mistake while she is
trying to go back then you know that
would also be super dangerous so I was
freaking out I was so freaking out my
heart was
pounding like crazy I was like trying to
hold back my tears
and so for while I was just
um observing and trying to hold her back
from going back actually she did attempt
it a few times but I was actually
holding her back because I didn't want
it to go wrong I was just hoping for the
neighbor to notice and be on the balcony
and pick her up and bring her inside
but I waited and I waited and no one
would come out and she actually was in
the meantime she was just sniffing some
boots that were on the neighbor's
balcony
she was sniffing and yeah just having a
good time
exploring the balcony
so I was like okay good you just you
just do your thing for now and hopefully
someone will come out but I waited and
no one would come and the thing is like
if I had someone with me I would ask
like the person to go over to the next
apartment and ring their Bell while I
observe the cat but I have no one with
me I live alone
so
yeah I was like [\h__\h] I don't want to go
around and ring the bell of the owner of
the other apartment to see if they're
there and can help me because then I
have to
leave my cattle there and what what if
she does something stupid trying to go
back you know I cannot let my eyes off
of her now
but I waited and didn't know the
situation was not getting better so I
ended up running as fast as I could to
the other apartment in the moment where
I thought it looked like
um
it looked like this movie was pretty
occupied with sniffing the shoes of the
of them that were on the balcony
and she might be not interested in
trying to go back at the moment
so I ran over
your cat will be fine even if it fell no
it would not have been fine cats cannot
miraculously survive these high uh jumps
all the time they can't survive every
[\h__\h] jump
and you can't just assume it will
survive then
they cannot
cannot fake no they cannot
they literally cannot like there's been
many cases where they did not survive it
don't try to tell me some miracle story
my mom
when she was living with a partner who
brought in some cats
my mom was living in a apartment that
was like on the third floor so really
not very high at all and one of the cats
was you know
standing on the rail of the fence and
fell down and died pretty much instantly
so even if it's a low height if it lands
weirdly then it can die
if you think cats
cats then it's a [\h__\h] myth
yeah you don't want your cat to even
risk it
this movie is like
I I need I need her in my life and I
can't risk something like that that's
insane
and you don't know you can't even assess
that situation because you don't know
you know where exactly what kind of
place I live at so
I take this very seriously this is not
something to joke around about
it can yes but it's not a guarantee
it just makes me really really
worked up so we cannot discuss this it's
a fact that you should not let your cat
do this okay it's a fact
so I ran but no one opened the [\h__\h]
door there was no one home so that was
not an option for me to have the
neighbor bring my cat in
um I'm burnt oh [\h__\h]
I'll go to the center in a moment
um
yeah so
anyway
I ran back
and tried to observe my cat again why
are we going mentally [\h__\h] falling
apart because I was so scared I was like
already starting to imagine what would
happen if I was hoping
you know
I I couldn't [\h__\h] take the part of
them
he's gonna die
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right
um
yeah so
[Music]
I want him to get the EXP I'm gonna
revive them
um yeah eventually I just you know
we made it work somehow and I rescued my
cat somehow but
um since then I have it's a couple days
ago but since then I have not let my
cats on the balcony again and I don't
know if I can ever
time in five years or so but I
I can't I can't she's always been so
good but now I can never
again maybe with a leash yeah maybe but
that's like annoying too
but yeah
and that was in the middle of me working
on the whole talk stuff and you know it
really got me out of out of the concept
I was like
so
I don't know my brain is losing yeah
[Music]
little girl needs to be with her mommy
more closely
house arrest 10 years yes
unacceptable I'm glad you saved I'm so
glad to like I I hugged her so tight
time ever ever
[Music]
you or never ever ever getting on the
balcony
or never ever ever get an outside again
you must stop you jump to the neighbors
balcony
apartment
never ever ever
getting out again
stupid movie
I love her so much like she cannot do
this to me getting a freaking heart
attack from her
um
[Music]
foreign
or water right
wait never mind it's nothing oh it's not
my style
[Music]
it's the mice
and their Terror tab is still
this might actually be interesting
oh
steel fire
the mouse hole
iron iron Mouse steel Mouse
fashion sounds strong it kind of does
it's interesting
gonna cat proof the balcony
yes by never letting them outside of
again
decide anyway but I mean
I
um I have to think about it
obviously I love them so much and I want
to risk anything so
I have to think about it
[Music]
thank you
maybe you know there's times where she
Zooms in times where she's chill at
times when she's chill she's just
chilling you know maybe then it would be
okay then I have her under control
[Music]
double safe
no no no no no they can't easily go onto
my balcony
[Music]
like only if I open the door and I only
have it open you know when I want to go
on South outside which is never
especially not in the winter it's
[\h__\h] cold on my balcony
oh
the only times when in recent months
where I would go on the balcony it was
really just to you know
water their plants and chill with my
cats show them give them some fresh air
well it was mostly for the cats so it's
not really for me so if the cats don't
want to go outside then I don't want to
go outside anyway we caught them the
funny mice which they look they look so
simplistic
weird
[Music]
um
so I guess I'll call you
oh
caspers
I know Iron Mouse would fit too in this
case or stale Mouse
but I said I will call them caspers
and they would be an interesting
teammate though
who did I say I was gonna let go Amiga
right eventually and long boy long boys
come on boring too recently it just
looks funny but this one's more
interesting
who would you replace it love
uh uh who who would you replace this
with
um
yeah so maybe after afterwards but
longer longer long boy
I guess he's not very strong in the long
run huh okay but then after after Mela
don't go kind of weak okay
okay I know isn't it
so let's try to get closer this field is
[\h__\h] huge but let's try to get closer
to
foreign
to the city or like uh
a
Pokemon Center where the hell is the
next Pokemon Center I feel like I'm in
the middle of nowhere and I want to
fight the trainer but
[Music]
you
oh come on Santa is this a Pokemon
Central to my days
it's like this dude with
um
oh
it is okay then we'll go there
he looks so realistic his face
never mind from the side it looked
really realistic if it wasn't for the
eyes
oh he's got a strong Pokemon and that I
don't know how to fight
um uh what type is that plant fighting
this guy's a student oh I've seen
students in this game that are like 16.
the
um
age really doesn't matter in that school
system apparently
psychic fairy wait I want
strong against Perry dark
[Music]
I shut down by accident
a lot actually
even though it was super strong and
super weak it's supposedly
okay
[Music]
well then
go seal and poison okay poison against
Berry I think I can remember and still
still poisoned against me I already
ordered one
didn't see dangus what's that
what the [\h__\h] how does he have this
weird-ass Pokemon
what is that
normal
oh maybe ghost is good against normal
because Normal doesn't work on ghost
right
let me try no
oh
man I thought it was the other way
around
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
what do we want
haha
what did we bring in
I want to revive them
oh man
[Music]
I will revive
one
Red Dog
holy
[Music]
y'all I think this one's pretty heavy
right no no
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
oh my God what do you got next he's got
one more
but I guess that's a like a flying bat
Pokemon
uh you guys know what I should use
dragon flying
fairy
but Brent is not doing so well
[Music]
let's try
please
hope I can even survive a hit or get the
first hit
um
and that is not very defensive oh that
thing
the big ears I only got one more
um
use left though
[Applause]
first hits and one hit
[Music]
good job good job
so proud it's worth it that I revived
you
but that's a strong trainer he's got a a
good like choice of Pokemon
not bad
ah the Pokemon center is right in front
of that
thingy
we need to get in there right
doesn't it have a gate
no
okay let me
oh are you
I almost didn't sail oh my
God because I just look like gas
stations yeah I I honestly preferred
them when they were inside but at least
this way you don't always have to go
inside a building and it loads
because that always took so much time
so having it outside like that saves a
lot of time I suppose
um
[Music]
but I liked the way they weren't
buildings all the time before
anyway are you satisfied with me
battling the last one I saw oh [\h__\h] it
doesn't count for this
I need to
I need to go back to the other trainer
and the other dude
who said I need a couple more as well
but I will fight you now
[Music]
it only counts per area
I thought we found I thought we fought
enough of them
Slowpoke oh yo I haven't heard of
Slowpoke in a while
still comes local in such a long time
the person who controlled Slowpoke is in
check right now and wants to say hello
[Music]
this notebook was here today
what would he tell me about
he's slow sign up but it's been so long
[Music]
say something
say something I'm giving up on you
oh that's pretty strong I didn't even
super effective I was just hoping for it
wow I'm so proud
[Music]
answer nobody here hey what happened
my oh
you little [\h__\h]
enable my moves
congratulations
yeah that's impossible
a possible things
[Music]
indeed
what is that in the grass so far away
come on
do you think I'm ready for Mela
I feel like it might be a little bit
tough
[Music]
um
we would use Connie right honey and long
boy
honey let's find a little bit more with
Connie
[Music]
um
we both bread dog then yes
my hair maker is nice and sunny
oh
okay next up
one to two more levels were coming
Windows does cunning evolve
don't think I saw any spoiler on this
Evolution that had someone
it doesn't oh why is there so many
Pokemon that don't evolve
pythony's level up fighter wants to
learn battle with us what is that
honey
a normal move
you just wish this place with a party
that's a free switch
not really it's free switch because it
doesn't come with an attack
but it passes along any stat changes
so
interesting like I could buff me up
insanely and then switch but no
interesting move though you have to like
use it smartly
let's go
oh my God this is gonna look cute please
tell my son looks cute
oh oh
hmm it's like slowly turning into a
duck's hunt because it's kind of longer
um
I'm saying it and it's definitely baked
now
oh that's ah there you go I didn't even
see that I understand I understand yes
that was on purpose I guess
that it turns long it becomes longer and
turns into a ducks
doggle
a little bit less cute but it's not
unbearable
a pleasant Aroma that emanates from this
Pokemon's body helps wheat grow so
that's bun has been treasured by farming
villagers oh
[Music]
oh
the evolution that's good
um
[Music]
nice
I got spoiled on some Pokemon's
Evolutions unfortunately but this one
I've never seen so I'm excited
don't want to get spoiled too much
[Music]
look at its straight he's now even the
fire oh wow oh that's good against melon
too then huh okay and we're gonna We
would supposedly only use Connie and
long boy but in the worst case spider
works too
okay
you got bake
well I mean you could still burn him
so that is completely burnt that is
absolutely possible to do with a bread
so I don't quite understand the immunity
but okay I'll take it
I'll take it I should not be complaining
it's not like bread is fireproof
um
nice almost killed it almost
yeah the sound that Connie makes is
uh
it's a very easy to be found
very Titanic
Rock blast oh
a new rack move
25 five times in a row though
um what do you say
this one's ah
maybe better than rock throw
because
I don't know
same accuracy about 50 and yeah okay
agreed shake hands
[Music]
get rid of Heartland too
yeah if I find something else then I
might
what level are we uh how much how much
are you speeding about Connie
oh wait I I'm leveled up okay yeah
something happened
maybe long boy level up would be good
homeboy is so weak 40 HP what the [\h__\h]
who can long boy fight against
maybe that pig
he will soon
isn't there yeah there is but they still
get more exp when um
one day do the fight himself when they
participate as far as dinos
I think that made a favor no
[Music]
strong enough for team Stars I would
hope so like I've been I've been
grinding this shouldn't be so necessary
oh my God
this little trunk is taking you apart
you'll find it
[Music]
oh
actually I wanted to do Auto Battle
let me just switch
I was kind of like saving them for
Pokemon that I'm keeping on the long run
no
more North Fargo
I know but I want to be here
thank you
[Music]
hmm
this is kind of the problem of them
saying you can go wherever if it's
really spread out like that and I wonder
if I missed if I should have gotten like
a different route
and that's why I was on the level now
because just a while ago I was totally
over leveled and now I'm under leveled
kind of
um
I don't understand
and then if you accidentally do
something else
before the recommended route then you're
over leveled even though you don't want
to do it
for the things you were supposed to do
before that
um
I don't like it
anyway
[Music]
it's that thing again I have yet to see
it in the monkey form
all right I think
we should just go for it
oh but maybe that trainer I will fight
uh how is my
team looking
poison skill type
[Music]
okay one last
Air Trainer
before we go in to meet the pretty lady
oh I like this Pokemon isn't it like
fairy poison or something like that
um
oh that's not very effective but still
does so much damage
it's in the water
oh my
[Music]
God
oh flying Titan and jio Como first
it would that be the better order
is that what people do
yes
see like I thought
who is that person that you just said I
thought
you know so even
close to one another
if you just go to Natural path wouldn't
you
I don't know but who is who
what is this
tulip
what do you want me to do
it maybe
no
sounds very Italian
but I guess it's Spanish
okay so this is this is the one I should
be fighting
and
Earth Titan Maybe
or Sky Titan or the sky Titan
okay kind of a waste because like I
explored everything here but okay we'll
come back there
does it say
do this next
no
oh I wonder if I would have asked for
advice if it would have told me to go
here
um all right
[Music]
is that the closest
okay
the nurse somebody tells you what's the
closest you're not the Baseline levels
okay
I know people like games that are not
too linear but I would like them to tell
me what the most recommended order is no
in the beginning they only tell you what
which which gym is the one they
recommend in the beginning the first one
um
yeah I need some gardens made to me too
I would have probably with all that
grinding I would have been fine with
Mela now but then I would have been way
too over level for the other things
apparently
if they were supposed to be done first
so that I need to do that now otherwise
you know
so what's strong
against flying
I have no idea
ground Electric
yes
okay then we have our
um
finalized uh
um dakuma to handle that and I will Zoom
I will Zoom
to reach the destination
as fast as possible while also fighting
the Traders
I mean I think level scaling would make
so much sense
cunning would help too okay
wonderful oh he's handsome
he's a handsome one oh
Ah that's good for Connie but I don't
have honey
out right now
but level 14 oh my God I'm so over
leveled what
[Music]
how
are you supposed to go like left right
left right left right
like west east west east west east
is that the way to go
I don't understand
what is that
[Music]
looks new it looks that's a baby Pokemon
isn't it it looks like a baby Pokemon
of an eggshell on its head but I don't
think it's an eggshell
[Music]
um
I like that Pokemon
it's evolution is pretty nice too and
it's pretty strong
I am going to
look around that area of screen I think
let me look where is that
no no look uh
oh God what
happened
[Music]
around this area
Maybe
that part does not come to recycling
yeah but that's like lower than
the place where you started kind of
right so
you really only go left right
eventually you'll end up at the very top
and then you go to the bottom
I guess
wait oh that was effective no it's
working I'm just too strong
flashlight
I don't know what that is
it's an attack
it's really go far out of your way to
get to the cycling lady I suppose so and
then I mean if she's really that high
level then the Pokemon around her will
be really high level too right and then
you would you would supposedly notice
that you're not supposed to be there
but you know when you guys told me the
level of Mela it didn't seem too crazy
for me and still kind of made sense to
me that I should go there
I already have that one
he's a monkey monkey monkey
[Music]
and he does get super fast
but look at the too fast
[Music]
oh I hear a waterfall wow
is that shiny monkey
isn't it brown normally
this one's white
is that what it's supposed to be like
no
I mean it's not like I wanted a shiny
monkey anyway
I am enough of a monkey myself
I don't need anyone else to be a monkey
for me
I like the music here
nice instrument choice
oh the wind goes whoosh yes it does yes
it does and the and the pork makes oink
the pig makes oink and the cow goes boom
yeah wind goes whoosh
what are those splash
because you guys wants to collab on
cowie's Channel
oh
my God
turns into town flame
but that's a fire Pokemon right well I
have to fire starter so that
does not make so much sense
oh by the way so pickle that is um
playing a nice look right did she lose
her starter yet
I feel like the funniest thing that can
happen to someone who plays on naslock
is losing their starter
that Pokemon looks new to me that's a
light bulb huh
anyone that grasshopper hops away
yeah no no
oh
[Laughter]
but you would be so extra careful of
your
um starter so I guess it rarely happens
unless you have like really hardcore
rules as well
because just making it Nuzlocke
[Music]
right
but you can
find a bit more difficult
and then and then
and it's starting to be a challenge
[Music]
just looking for possible shinies you
know
but nothing inside
[Music]
oh I love this Pokemon is so fluffy
this one this one so cute fluffy blue
bird
Looper
[Music]
and I make that jump
so shiny I'm gonna go there but
I don't really care about it to be
honest
[Laughter]
I guess one more reason why I assumed
that Mela is next is because we did one
of the Titans we did one of the gyms and
I thought we'd do one of those
other things next but
okay I guess we're doing another Titan
we did two then oh right we did two and
no team start wait then it's really not
as balanced as I thought it would be we
did two gems and the Platinum you can't
tell me that we were not supposed to do
the plant gym
okay you guys have to control my
playthrough and tell me where to go at
all times
I thought it was equal in terms of
numbers
ouch
plays Pokemon exactly you play my
Pokemon
[Music]
you wanted to back to you you're already
doing it anyway yes
my Pokemon is always being backseated
always always oh you know what let me
bring out more boy
needs some leveling
hi there I'm hitchhiking can I catch you
a ride on your Pokemon you mean on my
bike and you should go find your own
bike what the hell
it's just about your own bike
caterpillar eyebrow man oh cute
that is so cute
[Music]
um
probably don't care for any of these
attacks
again five okay yeah it's probably
planned so or yeah the water was
obviously ridiculous
oh no dad I know
it evolves into a mogulu
what
manga train
[Music]
um okay
by the way I think the kid people who
are watching yesterday knew it as well
but it seems like that eggs on Christina
manzanita's food submission really was
supposed to be a chicken I
attack on my chicken when I see one the
people in the chat who are not kfb were
doubting me and we're probably thinking
that I am just too self-centered
trying to make it about me but no it was
a [\h__\h] Tacoma chicken not everything
is about a mogus
but the KFA in the chat they understood
they understood yeah now and the
submission was by Christina so there was
no doubt
[Music]
somewhere but it looked like a chicken
to me okay so
chances are it was a chicken
right thank you kfb you get me you get
me I
just look like look at your pictures of
the mirror is so obvious I look at I
look at you guys all the time
I have your looks burnt into my brain
I cannot forget what you guys look like
huh no no no no I want
[Music]
I wish that was a cute fluffy chicken
but you are
or maybe you're not yet but you will be
[Music]
it helps that we all look exactly the
same mama you wear different clothes and
different accessories
some of you got different eye colors oh
who the hell oh my God
capsa kids
huh
are you telling me about the air Titan
so from what I gather seems like the
Open Sky Titan lives somewhere up on
this mountain but there are all these
crazy Boulders raining down from the
mountain too it's gonna be a little
tricky sat around and look for the Titan
while dodging all those I think it'll be
set flying if you get hit by a falling
Boulder but maybe a good power your way
through top that brood of yours
hmm
okay Power
my way through a top
wait which way this way
[Music]
you mean there will be big chunks of
rocks flying at me
if you think I can go outside
[Music]
I don't think that's
working
yeah oh
no plan this is not the Fab I can take a
standpipe there's a path
you little
really a little [\h__\h]
you're the littlest [\h__\h]
wait here you can get on the roof
great
out skills
was I here before
[Music]
oh no
why are you so tiny and green
oh that's the way to the psychic gym oh
they're everywhere they are
cute
we have a sister I saw your sister
somewhere
[Music]
how come I know what's effective on this
one I don't think I've fought this one
before
interesting
Kansas where they're turning green why
not
yes I did
[Music]
oh
it's gen one Pokemon yeah but like
in this playthrough I don't remember
fighting this one
maybe I'll stream I guess I guess
I guess so
yeah
oh I didn't know that that was why they
taught themselves German human language
in that case it was German
in German it was German in German we say
in German
no in German we say Deutsche
um
anyway
[Music]
yes
I didn't know that
I never went up the other Tower did I
this one you can't even go up I guess
you have to
I think I saw a bird flying I guess we
have to go up that one by flying is that
what we'll learn next lying I thought it
would be climbing Maybe
but I did just see the Shadows
of big round
objects flying above my head
[Music]
no
is that a shiny Gosling no [\h__\h] witch
where do you see it Shine Gastly
[Music]
you see a Shiny Gastly
I was definitely not a shiny guy
I just passed it no way
it's just light colored hmm
no
no no I think I would have noticed that
one
because at least with gasoline
seen it a lot before
oh
Mama Mia
I have to cook today no more leftovers
you need to have your shiny dogs open
yeah
and your shiny glasses
you need to cook I have one more my my
brother you know oh God no I noticed
that no I'm my brother has uh uh uh who
was looking over my cats while I was
gone and
um I had my hellofresh delivery come in
on Tuesday
and
then the the recipe since I can't order
for one person the minimum is two people
so usually what I do is I I cook it and
then I eat one portion
what the [\h__\h] is that pineapple
I eat the other uh portion on the next
day and sometimes sometimes it's even
enough for free portions not often or it
depends on the
um
on the type of proof it is
that's bug oh
now I protected itself so
and back along
um yeah so two to three portions with
minimum two like it's really enough
my brother
cooked
two out of my pre-hellofresh recipes
and
said
we easily finished
one
like whole cooking load
in one dinner
just just he ate all of it I was like oh
you got any leftovers he said like no oh
what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
what did you do that
yeah
so not many left there was one recipe
that he didn't cook yeah but I expected
he would have some leftovers from
something he cooked
oh man
[Music]
normal stomach
he thought I would say he eats a bit
more than the average person
the average whatever the average is in
Europe at least in Europe average person
in Europe
not saying is fat at all no no he lost a
lot of weight recently no
he's really fit now
I respect that
yeah I was shocked that he ate all that
in one go
so now I only have one recipe left but
today is a Saturday
and my next delivery comes on on Tuesday
most of the time
I I like on Monday I make the last
recipe often
because there's there's just so much oh
hello
[Music]
so often I I struggle with finishing
everything before the next delivery
comes
I know it's the wrong way I just went
there because of reasons
to wear fears in the background
oh hello
boy not the right boy
I know I can guess this one
I would have guessed grass or poison or
bug or fairy or a mix of them
[Music]
but grass very highly likely
it's too empties
the more the wind comes in such like
pushes like
that's why it looks like that right
instead of it goes like
[Laughter]
chill dude chill
and don't wanna fight you
[Music]
[\h__\h]
up
let's go up this reminds me of I think
Zelda
I think
oh
can I can I see it
no I can't see it
this is no damage to me
surprise
uh oh [\h__\h] I should have changed Pokemon
home
ah
[Music]
what
is it a uh
it's a story yeah what what is so weird
that's right so flying oh [\h__\h]
um Electric
why does it have like a cut in the
inside of the pouch there there there
it's also kind of like a tongue
uh
watch out
don't hurt yourself
[Laughter]
okay so you're just gonna [\h__\h] off like
that wow it
oh man
that was easy
oh hi
your timing is impeccable as always
okay well well you managed to get the
Titan somewhere
I was one hit
so that's super scary Titan wait it's
deciding what's been dropping all those
boulders
I was lucky enough to be able to sneak
up here because it had all its attention
on you little bud it looks like it's
trying to power itself up like with some
kind of mystical meal power or something
oh [\h__\h] I have the wrong Pokemon in the
front again or do I continue with the
one I had
in the last fight
nope it's long boy again
[Music]
is it flying a rock type
that's actually cool that feels pretty
rare as well
oh I should have peeled before switching
it in maybe
flying dark
[Music]
wow
flat bird
come on can we see a one hit again you
did it once you can do it again
[Applause]
um how much damage though it doesn't
even show me how much damage I get from
The Recoil
yay looks like it's about to evolve
again but no we're done here I guess
oh long boy level up good for you
headbutt
good job
ah normal move
you know what I'll take it
I'll take it
I'll switch out yeah yeah
[Music]
let's look at the grass what it does
this time
it's way to go kiwawa yes looks like we
don't have to worry about any more
bullets falling on the snail huh
mm-hmm
I guess so and no bird poop Eva
there has to be more of that Urban
mystica it ate in here let's hurry and
find it before the Titan can come back
for another good with us
it looked Majestic though that big burb
struck Pokemon is a cool idea
if we're lucky there'll be another Urban
here
also a historic YouTuber would be funny
because stork brings the kids right the
babies
could be quite the funny lore
funny as lore I feel like you could play
around with that
I knew it
oh this time is green everything's green
now
really is here this is one of the herbs
make no mistake
yeah it's very shiny stands out a lot
sounds very important bitter
bitter Urban mystica
we did it thanks kiwawa
no no let's see what does the book have
to say bitter Urban mystica is great for
your circulation it really gets the
blood flowing and that warms you right
up nice and toasty even boosting the
immune system also it says
let's make another sandwich shall we
what are we waiting for it's time for
sandwiches Let Me Whip up something for
us lunchtime
what's up
and Bob's your uncle I have to by the
way make so many of these yeah
hey
hey sounds for
um
for counter counter strike counter sign
yeah so many
it was funny Zelda noises
[Laughter]
lots of fighting noises it was a bit
awkward recording that alone I think
that's um
I think I mentioned that in some three
more tweet or so after recording it I
said oh I recorded so much stuff today
and that was it was awkward stuff
remember something like that I feel like
I mentioned it
I did well now you know what I meant it
was that
because there was so many lines really
and some of them were a bit awkward to
record especially because they wanted so
many variations at some point I was like
oh isn't this like I am kind of the same
how do I make it sound different like
yeah and then they also wanted some
cheering noises like yay and yay and oh
a lot of different
different and Pops your uncle what here
you go my special Whimsical herb filled
super sandwich it comes with side of
Titan [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh oh they really don't like this one
well then I think we're happy to give it
to our bicycle bicycle
foreign
[Music]
yes please
take that away take it away this bitter
why would I want to eat that
let's try to say facts or something
um
a good thing I made extra
well you know didn't we like in the
photo we look so disgusted by it you're
helping me out a whole bunch with the
horses there's only fair that you get
more I definitely absolutely did not
make extra so that cool ride on could
have said why is he so knitted
why is it something that towards my
bicycle
whoa oh my god oh
no it's never climbing nor flying okay
but flying would have surprised me
because that seems overpowered
I'm gonna go stronger again
man these Urban mystical really do
pocket punch don't they
I mean they better or have some barely
up the creek huh what does he mean
[Applause]
maybe he's trying to heal his own
bicycle don't dare touch that that isn't
for you oh oh he's getting really mad oh
no
okay
sorry I shouldn't have Shadow like that
I guess I should at least tell you the
full story oh he's opening up
emotional time
oh
[Music]
it's a big old big dog
sick we need to help
this is my boys give my partner and my
boss
this looks funny those oh
[Music]
oh he parked too old
boy
old boy oh
[Music]
ah sad
[Laughter]
[Music]
slowly now take your time no
no it's a whole bunch of fine just too
nice and slow
[Music]
my body always hurt pretty bad a while
ago real bad in fact
he never really recovered
have you tried to put it's like asking
have you tried turning your PC off and
on again
nothing seems to help no potions no
Pokemon centers nothing
but that's weird like even on Pokemon
men are fainted the poker Center still
revives them so
there he is
the only thing in the world I care about
the only thing I totally get with what
you mean
so I promise I didn't make it better
whatever it takes
is he looking improved after eating two
different herbs
I searched online I read books I looked
all over and tried every curing remedy I
could find maybe because you keep on
feeding him those [\h__\h] sandwiches
maybe he
cannot uh process gluten and you need to
give him gluten-free sandwiches
I don't know man
I read books a little over the all over
try every Cuban remedy I could find but
nothing really worried I'd almost given
them hope but then I found about out
about the urban mystical
foreign
[Music]
however before we could harvest the
herbs were eaten by poltimum which in
turn grew large and strong we called
these Titan Pokemon
[Music]
it's just Pokeball it's this book full
of crazy stories and legends and things
stuff nobody'd usually believe
um but I believe it I think what it says
is true
and according to this book eating all
five Urban mystical can cure anything
that ails you case in point my
bullshit's Paws were Colder's eyes
before he ate the last group but they've
warmed up a little now oh
sure they have
[Music]
my coconut oil is broken though
and I'm impressed with the pretzel
is
like which dog is that
which that's an evolution no looks like
an evolution
of which Toko though not the one with
the candle right
Mischief I forgot what it looked like
oh you don't eating bud
oh
it looks so sad with those eyes even
though it's not his eyes oh bubble
oh
[Music]
your eyes open yeah
no it's crying
[Music]
it's been so long since he was able to
open his eyes
oh
[Music]
God
those fiery orange little eyes it's hard
to even tell if they're open or not but
I I know the difference yeah you though
the power of these rooms is amazing I
knew the book wasn't lying I'm gonna
bring my Buster back to full health I
swear
we also that's my story three herbs to
go let's find them together yeah
[Music]
what do you [\h__\h] all the other things
like what the hell gyms are so
significant now
oh
[Music]
foreign
has regained more of its original Power
while riding opponent it seems you
should now be able to move across water
it's finally learn to swim let's go
I'm relying on you to continue taking
good care of credence
okay I love you
oh man you can't do this to me
a dying doggle
you can be like [\h__\h] that I'm not gonna
help you nobody
um
and especially not
I think a lot of pet owners can relate
to that especially if you've had a pet
and then lost it
oh I hope
oh hello
fun I'll get to this point
I hope she was okay
it's just like so in your face
no she didn't oh
oh my oh that won't be painful Maybe
oh wait those towers that one has stairs
let's go out
I've lost one
more or less one kind of two pets in my
life
one on one one was when I was really
really really tiny
um so it was a kitten that was also
really tiny
and it came from I think I told this
before but it came from like a farm
so it came with an illness that a lot of
farm cats have
that you really you really cannot say
that
basically impossible have some solution
yeah and then another one
was weird because I was living in Japan
[Music]
and the cat that we owned
which I love so much even though it
hated me but it was my baby I loved her
so much I wish she loved me back
[Music]
um
while I was temporarily in Japan
my mom had some
one move in
who brought two
cats male cats
and somehow they were prioritized and
my mom sent away the family cat that we
had which wasn't even that old at all
and supposedly sent her to
someone who had a big big Garden she
said
but I never saw my cat again then
so I couldn't even say goodbye
when I came back from Japan she was gone
so
[Music]
anyway
well that's one of one of those cats was
the the one that died when jumping from
the balcony or like falling off the
balcony one of those cats that moved in
was uh the one that fell and then died
pretty much instilling well these
standings are so
they're so bad anyway where was that
Fountain thing I'm guessing they want me
to like can I zoom up that Fountain
thingy
is
yeah today is sad tangent day it really
yeah not not being able to see her
anymore
and this time with brown hair she got
the oink oink
black textbooks stronger than normal
what I didn't know that
I noticed that difference
uh I don't know what's strong against
you let me try
[Music]
and you have an NYC panels reviews
did you see me there
are you asking because of that
are you new
[Music]
oh fighting oh oh well are you not new
and Luxio
electric maybe ground
[Music]
s so yeah I'm thinking which one is good
again
two three
I need to go to an annual meeting
it's so big holy [\h__\h]
even though it's super perfect oh
what
what level is this one
huh no oh well okay because this type is
water well yeah but no I'm more
surprised about my attack not doing [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm gonna slap the face weak I guess so
God damn it
um
[Music]
it what happened
I didn't look
it missed
stand there we go wait I still didn't
see the level [\h__\h]
did you see it
[Music]
hmm 20.
amazing
okay I'll go on an animal meeting and
then I'll come back and we'll we'll we
won't talk about sad things anymore
maybe I'll pet my cat
[Music]
foreign
looking at me
what's so funny
[Music]
thank you
I just came in love
I miss a shot no
no I did no [\h__\h] it shut up
I did not miss the shiny
shut up
[Music]
no
no I did not Mrs sweat
oh God
no way
no no no no no no I feel like it would
still be here I wasn't gone for that
long
no
no no no
I don't believe what are you doing Trump
You Want to Stay With Me
[Music]
you're so warm
so warm and floppy
okay bye bye love you
okay
these are so cute
hi you want to play
it's huge
wait it looks so blue now
it doesn't look white anymore even on my
main screen
oh but from here in the sun it looks
White
ah
just like a dress
where where am I supposed to go now
I guess we can use the swimming
technique and swim along the river but
what am I really supposed to do uh
go to hell
dark type face okay
okay
[Music]
that's how it's watching me yeah
so cute
oh go for swim
Ming oh good job
oh
well we are flying on top of the water
then that's fine can you not swim
Amiga
[Music]
shocking
run right on the fish
yeah I can't swim now I am aware of that
yo
you're so much faster faster
I don't like items in the water I'm
guessing not
um
doggy paddling cute oh
sometimes
or maybe the sparkling ones but not the
pokeballs probably
here we have
purple
[Music]
no
I wanted to go up there with the
Pokeball ones
no
my Pokedex level what I don't know I'm
not really trying to catch everything
um catching what looks interesting to me
what I need to get out of here
um
[Music]
not where I want to be
why do I wanna go
I'm gonna call everyone watching the
Pokedex oh every time you put them wait
how do I see
and finally late
caught 18 Battlement doesn't give me
anything
oh and at the Academy press X
there it is
[Music]
what I'm pressing minus
on the bottom it says minus
[Music]
oh oh now okay that's weird I'm confused
okay
what ah there what
it's so confusing
is it about how many I catch or how many
I see
uh I think it's how many I catch because
I only caught 18.
okay you managed to motivate me to catch
a couple more again
[Music]
does it have to be separate ones okay it
also be the same
you shouldn't have killed it Amiga
different ones oh well oh well
gives me something to do off-screen I
guess
um okay we are here and we want to go
there
we need to go back up
um
okay I'll teleport here
because that seems to be the
smartest route
let me heal
[Music]
I don't know how long my HP are but just
in case
[Music]
plenty of candy some special balls for
it so it's definitely worth okay okay
I just you know I'm doing my own
adventure
okay
I'll think about it
I'm going this way
[Music]
zooming
all right
did I catch this one before I don't
think I did
maybe it will work
oh
[Music]
there's a there's no Pokeball icon
underneath you haven't caught it oh
oh
I wish I wish you know we have all the
battle now but in our chaos we have kind
of Auto all the catching
I wish we still had that
I liked Auto catching
oh
yes
I got to the other side uh wait maybe
that wasn't
[Music]
ah the the turtle
is this good
where's the actual path that you're
supposed to take
[Music]
let me go here
that might work because I just wasn't
able to get up from the water but this
just might work
as long as I can go up somewhere on the
left
oh no
[Music]
what
if you survive I will catch you
no you didn't
go back
[Music]
they almost spawned me back in the water
okay well
it ends here
okay back Pokemon Center
which one is this one
this time
we will really
choose the right path
turn around and jump backwards I don't
know how that works I tried it before
because I did see on Twitter
that if you walk backwards you can get
up anything
but I tested it and then how do you even
walk backwards
[Music]
let's see
jump and move backwards
mmm
let's do a red battle
that's the water spider okay I don't
care actually I don't want it
change my mind
oh let's go let's go was that shiny
I wish they would at least make a sound
they don't have to like sparkle but if
they at least made a sound
for the people who don't know which
Pokemon looks like what
uh is it over there
there's a base looking in place than the
Pokemon Center
[Music]
yeah at least the sounds
Mateo a Backpacker
with an Eevee
cute easy I saw like someone who I
follow on social media get a shiny Eevee
I was already mad at that and then the
next post they posted was them getting
another Shiny Pokemon when both without
trying
both without
crying I am so mad and I'm like so eager
to get one too like just without trying
yes yes yes yes
but shiny Eevee they're like silver it's
really cool
imagine if you have a shot
[Music]
Evolution whichever the [\h__\h] you want
choice and that is like next level
worth
that has so much value
[Music]
and what
Monday I'm in
[Music]
unlocking anything with you to the
shrine Logan again
um did she recently get a luck thingy
from the shrine
did she did see you
I should make use of it looks like
people are still using it
oh luxury ball
foreign
[Music]
yes I did
oh there's a wider angle like this
I have to get used to this but I I think
I like seeing more of my surroundings
does it trigger you guys
[Music]
full here
where does this path lead
nowhere really but there's truly great
items or whatever
over there
it should be explored
wait what what should be explode I
already forgot this this angle
that that area
short time memory
I'm on it
[Music]
I always run into a tiny Pokemon hey
with this camera even worse
really I think I think I remember Tinker
tank
[Music]
but I don't I remember and I also don't
remember
fly me challenge when it landed uh don't
have the right attack but let's give it
a try because I'm 10 level above
double
kick nice
[Music]
dude go back to school girl
back to school try
are you looking for a Pokemon well yeah
you're like we've seen this before but
you are
you're as small as the grass like in
comparison to me this makes still sense
you versus me but you versus the grass
is
worrying you might get lost in the grass
literally that makes me worry about you
going outside without your mommy
I do not recommend it
is that shiny
no it's not okay it's not it's nuts I
see the other ones
foreign
looks cute though that Pokemon
[Music]
if I catch one more Pokemon I'll get a
reward oh it's
desert area
I want to catch the Flappy Bird
[Music]
don't die when I do this when you die
don't die don't die
[Music]
I want to touch
the wings
[Music]
now hold on you can switch out the
enemies Pokemon I don't really care
about that
it's annoying when the enemy does it
but I don't think I would use it
[Music]
please don't die wait why am I doing
this again
it will not
get less effective
ly slow brain brains love brain slow
rental these are just too low level for
me
doshio
I can't even poke them
and poke them too
faint
[Music]
okay and this Pokemon here are kind of
boring
except that
one
no no no no ah
we finally getting notified about that
base
All About That Bass step I can still pay
you finally you haven't heard about you
oh from you in a while so interesting
when we were close to mela's base
he didn't call right
you're so close
or should I have gotten any closer but I
think we were close
so she only tells me about it
but I'm here I was not close enough oh
okay
I say it'll get in close to one of the
team Stars bases
I take it this means you've decided to
join my operation
uh yeah
because you're hot probably
uh thank you
it is officially a member of operation
Starfall
hold on a second Nani
what the f wait he looks familiar
for some reason his face looks familiar
yeah
professor
yes
or his son
doesn't he have the same face
is it same face syndrome
wait in a long time
Clive who's Clive is that the name he
had
is he just in disguise
no no he's this guy didn't get me I was
like I know this face but I just haven't
played in a while but you know I mean
you see that his eyebrows in his beard
or gray and but he just got a wig on top
I totally knew something was up
laughs
uh does this operation stop for all of
yours have room for one more member
well who is you
name's Clive
um
oh and uh how long have you been spying
on us
no need to get your hackers raised I'm a
proud of your mutual friend here isn't
that right kiwawa
so does Kiwa recognize him because
normally Pokemon protagonist and
generally game characters are really
[\h__\h] dense I could imagine her
thinking this is a different person
Pals
[Laughter]
[Music]
Shy's ever see
we're talking about going up against
team style here it's not something you
can join in for fun
um well where I just need to sort out
some Monster's [\h__\h] with Team start
at all such a tend to get the job done
well not that you can take my word for
it but it's true
uh
I suppose I'm oddly in a position to
refuse L welcome to the operation clean
oh great that sounds again
I think I heard your name earlier
costume who exactly are you
excuse
me I share some history and that's all
I'll say for now
I said cliff on purpose you little [\h__\h]
I see in that case I want to press it
further
I'm good and now back to business let's
talk operation
oh yes what do you what would you have
us to do
simply put I want you to read each one
of the steamster's bases then you'll
defeat the bosses of the team and put an
end to their rule
put into the world you mean we need to
ask these bosses from the world somehow
that's all right uh Teamster is made up
of five squads and each of those squads
has its own best you should be able to
see it as the front Gates of one of
those bases No in fact
yeah uh-huh I saw
oh yeah so I can see you over there
on the other side of this is the base
popper and somewhere within the base
lies one of your targets a squad boss
she's friends now yes
oh yeah I'm sorry if you had a good idea
well that's just the outline looking to
the old operation is the code that the
team has to follow if someone challenges
one of the squad bosses to a battle they
have no choice but to accept
and what's more if they just so happen
to lose that battle
they must forfeit their role as both all
together
I went ahead and issued challenges to
each base under your name
basically Declaration of
now all of teamstar knows that we are
looking for a fight
She's mixed hmm
well let's say we defeat all the bosses
and they step down from the rules what
happens next
the rest of the team crumbles with no
one left to them lead them and that's
what happens it's a solid plan but not
without wrinkles it's best as a bunch of
Pokemon inside to fend off Intruders and
the places themselves are considerable
size your garden China would be overrun
long before they'd get anywhere near the
boats
that's why your skills are essential to
this operation
defeat the Pokemon inside the place and
write the words out from where the
hiding hiding
first things first though you need to
deal with any guns that might be
guarding the phone case
and what will you be doing in the
meantime I will be chilling I have
history with Team stuff that means I
can't operate or in the open I'll back
you up from afar all right what will my
world be
sorry but I don't trust you completely
just yet for now I'd like you to monitor
the bases and access keyword support
your coaches won all right as respected
I'll be in touch again when the plan
advances to the next stage a good
hunting out there
you look familiar
I don't know what you mean what if
anyone asked you about me remember this
I'm Clive the normal Academy student
just like nothing more nothing less
he's limit love crisis or a really late
life crisis actually
it's just Clive uh of course it's just
not yeah yes whatever
no problem why did he leave though
wasn't he supposed to help me
I guess he's not being trusted yet
where did he come here
he may have a history too all right so
uh dark dark was his type was it dark
what's dark good dark fairy it's very
good or is the other way around
what am I gonna want to use Amigo very
inciting okay cool cool
is also gonna use dark Pokemon
[Music]
my soul
I don't think we really need to save but
[Music]
I really do but we're probably really
overpowered
but also good oh [\h__\h] is good against
dark wow
well
what hold you
over here's the base of the operations
before team Stars the crew you may
notice there's a decision squid
and we don't take your time to run a
little kid snipping around the tent
silly but if you're doing too and you
said around here Amiga Amiga
oh I guess
we'll have to send you back that kind of
confused me
why are you talking to my Pokemon
[Music]
's team star
no no no no no
I want to join team stuff talk about two
species what it is exactly what
someone's trying to sleep on the radar
with it or fight me fight me
uh you know what it doesn't matter who
you are you're not getting real what's
up okay first by me and battle kid what
it will be I'll take you on
thank you on take you on
oh will it be double bubbles
okay okay then I'll change the order
but for now for now we're good still
single battle oh wait it's just
effective I guess because he's also
flying flying dark
oh wow
kick it
burp kills other birds
gracefully
[Music]
next anything next so was that it
week
birthday
it has to be so strong no
lose
[Music]
well whatever's your problem now finish
uh finish up for me
[Music]
bye-bye
baby
she's new to the TV no might have to
have little chat every day about the
attitude
sucks but I'm gonna go into the base now
and get the rest of the head Squad heads
up
we're going to do in full folks if you
set foot inside so you might want to
consider turning tail either way best
luck to you amiga
I think as a child
in the school we need Austrian kids
often would say that every once in a
while just sound funny or cool because
it's one of the few
phrases
a non-german phrases
I think another one was um
uh
okay this was not foreign but another
one we I would say sometimes we'll see
you later alligator
assalamistan see you later alligator
I say you took care of the Gods and
that's okay
no hold up in the base in Teamsters dark
cool in season Squad the robots
pretty much runs the whole team style
and it also produced that Wild
soundtrack of this himself he's a sharp
guy even though Declaration of won't
have ruffled him in the slightest
is blind is probably to where you're
done with a wave of crunch then a finish
you of himself
no use trying to add think a strategic
attacks like him bring him down just
keep on defeating as many Pokemon as you
can until the big man himself shows up
ring the bell on the gates once you're
ready to kick off this face of operation
time the wife is a teaching Squad of the
map
cool
foreign
music
starting really weak though okay
um we want
what do we say
and Amiga wait how do I
no no no no how do I switch
I just want to switch
um it's in position
like this
uh these two right
no one would be spikes
but Sparks down really strong because
now come on okay
okay easy
why are we sneaking
why are we speaking
I'm gonna ring the bell anyway I write a
challenge yes
ah with the first free Pokemon everybody
aha
so I really only get those free okay
interesting oh Cliff is with me
okay well what he starts a unique way of
doing battle they call it stop a bridge
barrage marriage to get through it
you'll need to use the I button to set
up multiple Pokemon and have them
but at the same time
the Pokemon Get Low Health come back
here and I'll heal them up
easy mode baby mode once we will be
facing will heal up the Pokemon too so
stay sharp out there okay so as much all
the Battle Is Possible
[Music]
oh I can't use my special effects my
ghostly is weird
[Music]
she won't forget if you can defeat
Freddy about Pokemon in the next 10
minutes ah yeah
um our button
[Music]
oh God okay does that happen easily
help it recover HP by using a vending
machine can I also use the items I have
in my inventory or all those like gone
oh
it turns out too
[Music]
okay well that was super easy and they
didn't even take damage this will be a
walk in the park for over here
easy
you're sending bubble bubbles
okay and now I'm relieved I got the
right Pokemon for these
get the alligator alligator what are you
doing
[Music]
anyway we got 12 out of 30 and we're not
even a minute in
the grandpa
Peppa Pig
God
oh my God
but they got a Cool Base I guess
[Music]
and they got some variation at least in
Pokemon normally like
in previous Pokemon games the variation
of enemy teams felt like really weak
look here there's another new one
oh the castle I love the cattle
I don't wear a little Pokemon oh don't
hit me
first
what what are the others
there we go
[Music]
Snapchat oh but I really like this one
stop
where are they going
we're on the others
[Music]
there we go almost there almost done
anything
yeah
just way above the level we gotta get
the bus
oh what a flex whoa that Carl you must
have participant in in
exhibits pimped by ride on MTV huh
sick muscle car is
you've done a real number on this party
creation what was it I'm joking
about the device
call me whichever it's a Bible Way nice
to meet you and all but how about we
skip straight straight to uh you were
all true
wow don't worry I'll play with secret
wheel unless you crash and burn let's
cut this party started oh you listen to
Black Eyed Peas Turtles
he's got some good lines
well I mean his design is a bit boring I
must say the female designs are better
but oh Banger music
turn it up oh the mountains back
you don't really think things through do
ya declaring war on team star is a bold
move wait where's this Pokemon
wait what I didn't say a Pokemon
oh the thing up on top there
oh
there you are
what is it just there to impose me
[Music]
what am I supposed to fighting
all right
[Music]
don't tell me I'll end up fighting the
car too this big drop Will bus you is
open is your voice in the house
how's that when opening track I'll spin
you up good party Crusher
he's so hyper
[Music]
you've got nothing on me
Logan was hit only one time one hit
wonders what you are buddy
grab a broom what is that
time to help the temple this show went
over yet
oh what you got what do you got
[Laughter]
oh yeah that's what I thought actually
okay
but that's a Pokemon can you actually
like
get the Pokemon for yourself
it's not really a Pokemon is it
I should have done the other cake
because it's probably really heavy
oh
I'll do it next time
it won't look like that uh only a part
of it like a smaller version yeah yeah
yeah
squeak attack
[Music]
okay it's a weak attack but you're still
feeling do some damage on me I'll give
you that
engine is dead
oh my God
wow
I guess that's dead
there's Kelly Vibe of this guy I feel
like she did
if she saw him
um I can see her vibing with him she
probably asked him for a collaboration
[Laughter]
on my stream
guess what I said
she likes this is that I think it's
pretty basic but it makes sense for what
he is it fits him is this the past guess
that's it
ah
wow those designs he's the most basic
one look at those
oh my God
[Music]
I'm like staring at them but the my red
lady she wasn't funny so she really has
problems walking in those boots I think
um
damn he doesn't really fit in he's not
cool enough
wait who's talking what's up yeah come
on did something happen
number three bus just wanted me one of
my take on some stuff so we had a chat
and still run a few plans
[Music]
a few plans like a full month
a British Star first of all and also a
new code of conduct for the team
you know how tons of new members have
joined up recently well we figured we
gotta make some team rules like a code
so we'll all be on the same page
next you'll come up with a great con for
us once you jack them up
I have to think about the voices when I
see them again
oh no thanks way too much pressure
I mean yeah I used to be president of
the student council but you know
everyone ended up hating me after that
because we know you of course a ton of
Stuffy rules on everyone and they
wouldn't take it we got some other
narrative replaced you after like five
minutes
uh I could not hope to but conquer male
students hair but stray no further than
1.8 inches below the nape and so far I
forgot what that person looks like I
can't see them
can make a voice for them
vacation big manifest
my point exactly so you'll agree that I
shouldn't be lit anywhere near this new
code
[Music]
but you always know what's best for the
team jackomo you look out for us
[Music]
at stuck up student in the console press
isn't who you are anymore man
book written by Jacob I'm looking at now
I'd follow that any day
as would I
well friends with the ego boost everyone
I'll do it I'll write up the dunk
[Music]
I need the best I could I would decode
myself and there's no going back on it
now my days as a boss are over
so here take my star beds would ya
huh
his clothing style is actually he
reminds me of someone now
oh when we Face them did we just face
them whoa I'll give you this Choice dmu
Ernest fan Square
role play
not a Venus why would it be Elena
ah got that
foul play
um
so this is how the party ends
let's talk about those Pokemon of yours
they're crazy stronger you learned those
training jobs at the Academy like what
moves you should use and stuff is that
where he really realizes he should go
back to school
just say no actually no I didn't
oh okay lucky that's Academy having fun
okay this is I guess where
it's not the best no kidding definitely
[Laughter]
oh
Rubble I'm not a rebel I'm just being
honest
school didn't teach me [\h__\h] about
Pokemon fighting I did all myself from
previous Pokemon games and you with you
guys
so they're doing direct but are you Jack
come on
wasn't expecting a giant Pompa dude to
make a guest appearance today you get a
coaxial to style that up yeah yeah
actually I think yeah
I guess yeah wait does he have different
hairstyles if I choose the coaxial
I'm just after quick word would you mind
sure I can tell it's gonna be something
annoying but I guess I'm nearly freed up
for time are you gonna convince them to
go back to school
because I couldn't do it
thanks I'll get straight to it it seems
all of you and teams are headed for
expulsion if you keep up your current
activities so why won't you break up the
team and start attending class at the
Academy again
that's what you want to know the job is
we're actually waiting on a pearl though
we don't know if they'll be coming back
a close friend of yours are they
Casio
[Music]
it's probably Casio fail
literally the strongest boss in all
Teamster like how there's a job champion
who's the absolute number one trainer
you knew
they're the one who invited those other
bosses to front to from the team we call
them the big boss
why is the big boss of yours now in my
phone
wouldn't we like to do we haven't heard
from them in I don't know must be a year
and a half an hour it doesn't even
engender at the boss so that I don't you
know guess
female
what could be Ronald
before dead if we kept him still going
then they'd they'd be back in touch one
day
but the teachers keep pressing us to
call it quits and then we get party
questions like YouTube
sucks maybe the big boss did they just
they were talking about breaking up the
team before and all so teams teams died
and this big boss will be yours they're
really that important to you
oh
[Music]
let me put in the woods you Eggheads hey
hey at the Academy might understand
they're my greatest treasure
[Music]
sweet
called me Egghead though what the [\h__\h]
I'm I'm like I have I have
I'm wearing it self-conscious about my
egg hand okay
on my onion head
s
foreign
good job girl
oh yeah come on
ah sorry god let's just see now it's
really obvious
and got caught up in my thoughts for a
second now about you we both I'll
transfer some LP about to your phone as
promised
oh I got a lot actually
you can now make more kind of TMS yay I
took it's a little bit deal of adding
some new entries to the range of DMS you
can make at your machines these new
teams should help you improve your
Pokemon's battle capabilities even
further
in any case you did some solid work out
there so much so that you deserve an
extra reward someone from my simply unit
will be there soon to give you some
materials for making teens
send them off her post what you
[Music]
um
I'm Penny from the supply unit you
probably don't remember oh boy you got
me out of a tight spot by the school
stairs
remember I could not forget you
oh so you do remember
uh I'm I'm helping out with the
operation staff all as part of my
independent study you know
potassium
I'm good with machines and hacking and
stuff so I'll be working behind the
scenes
so here you go your bonus reward from
Casio bail
thank you
I wonder if they're related maybe it's
like Casio bear is
the big sister or so hmm
you should be able to make a ton of TMS
with us because your bear said you'll
get more rewards each time you take out
one of the team star spaces also um I
heard all about how you had your Pokemon
charged into battle seems you were
pretty amazing
[Music]
um over China as strong as you on the
outside I'm sure the operation will go
just fine
there's four more squat bosses left so
uh good luck
thank you
oh cute
cool kids
look at fire emblem
look at the upcoming Fire Emblem and
then this one will not bother you
kidding I have no problem with the
upcoming firebomb designs but it's a
joke it's amazing
there's a skate park now since they're
the they're basically in disbanding
nothing left here no items
oh
maybe I shouldn't have
this is what happens when you jump on
the roofs guys don't do it
I know you feel super overconfident
with your dragon bicycle
don't do it don't do it
all right
so we already did two gyms
uh two Titans one thingy there now I
want to do one more gym or something I
don't know
what should I do next
either
Mela
oh is this the order in one of these
things
Firebase melon okay let's go to Mega I'm
ready
[Music]
for girl
vamos uh
uh
here
come on
mama
's
[Music]
let's go
I hope she won't adopt me as her younger
sister because looking at my hair color
I think
she will find a liking in me
so let's um
mark
wow what's the best way to get to her
can I just jump off the cliff there
probably not
uh
such as destination where is the
entrance though
I was in front of the entrance before I
just need to figure out where the hell I
am right now
also I should probably heal
long boy for fire type
hello boys really freaking week though
even when he's
um
even when he has the better type
even when he's
he has the longer stick
also I need free Pokemon right
the catch another water Pokemon right
now maybe um
it will evolve well when
he's level 24 now do you guys know the
evolving level then I could try to aim
for it
two levels 26.
okay
[Music]
what where do we grind
catch the ground type in the desert
hold on
oh
[Music]
you're a rock yeah
I have water I don't
I have some rock attacks I guess
uh ground attacks because yeah where am
I going
you know what
I'm gonna do it
[Music]
I am
going to forcefully level up that little
[\h__\h]
how many do you need
oh way more okay
oh there you go 25.
foreign
[Music]
almost did the trick
oh wait I should have uh then on before
25 right because now I have to do
another
I thought it has to happen like
naturally okay
oh
okay
long boy evolution
red long boys
did he become shiny when evolving I
thought he would stay White
why why is he red
Rosie Red
this is normal tell me I got
I got just
to say it just say it
[Laughter]
even even if it's not churches tell me
shiny
well it's shiny oh my God the bones are
so shiny
why is it
oh it's hot pink why
why that makes no sense
did it like skin itself and underneath
was this pink flesh
this is shiny and luck Trio cute
the original form of it
did not change its colors like this did
it
anyway very interesting
let me look at it
funny
it's so we believe wobbly wobbly maybe a
better uh
um will I be using the ground attack
right I think I will
so it would be nice to have a better
attack than that
but also maybe one more ground or or
water Pokemon or do you guys think I'm
fine mobile
[Music]
what do you think
go check your machine okay
I'll be fine really oops not that way
if you say so I will trust you guys
[Music]
uh TM I've never done that before let's
see it if I have materials for whatever
I need probably not because I have
barely been collecting materials
um I want the tea I'm made
making materials okay we can look for a
certain type
we want
a good ground type there we go so my
stuff we already have that's power 20.
bulldoze would be leather but don't have
I have the material videos for this one
my shot
it's not as strong but it's better
and for this one I'm missing also some
things for digging
it's better than nothing though
what's special is that a problem oh
because he attacks physically
well but it's still better than nothing
[Music]
mud Bray mud and question mark how am I
supposed to know what question my
question Marcus
oh
[Music]
my job
do I have no water
I have to encounter the Pokemon first
[Music]
you might be gonna bulldoze from Ghost
Town castles
Bulldogs
nearby Beach
that's it's really worth that effort
we have to go
that way
oh
bulldoze is worth it
nearly honestly okay can you stop bye
bouncing into everything
near her City what is your city
[Music]
ah okay
so actually we will go here right
[Music]
can I can I ignore everything
that
comes across me
let's see
already fought this dude already
explored a lot here
and this camera is weird
I can do like
okay hopefully you mean down here
I wanna go to the beach
I can fly there oh wow
[Music]
it went straight down you guys did not
believe it I was I think
Pratt I did
there's sand castle
[Music]
um
he still only has 57 uh
wait what top is this thing anyway
this is ground ground ghost or so
then I might want to catch it
oh that could be helpful now
ground ghost
[Music]
try it oh because it's ghosts
uh
The Shield
we'll try this one
okay level 21 isn't even that bad
okay
um
ball time we balling
you little [\h__\h] what's your problem what
is your problem
trapped by quick stand
[Music]
it's great ball times
it ain't [\h__\h] time
[Music]
carry it yeah do you think it will also
give me those items that I need
cast
um
no because you're only temporary but I
will put you into my team
um well Sparks actually will probably
not be helpful right so let's get rid of
Sparks for now oh my God oh only
temporary
um okay
yeah I'll leave it here
buddy so who could be useful for
Auto Battle let's see
are you doing it
oh my God
[Music]
no it's the same I finally had like
because maybe because it's a female
um sand castle it has a ribbon noise
level it's just a shovel
does this work
it works Sunny gets sand
one about the other items
to try this one
bye I have to do more of this on a
battle
[Music]
oh is that that's fighting something
where are the water Pokemon
go into the water
donkey Pokemon donkey you mean the
horsey
to me that's a horse
can we find the shiny
the shiny Magikarp um
three of them already
are you oh dolphins
hmm
[Music]
do I want the dolphin these look new I
don't think I remember dolphins in
Pokemon
beautiful
should I get one of them
whatever you need to do co-op oh
that's annoying
look at this Evolution no I don't want
to spoil myself
so I killed it
it would be interesting if I didn't have
to like I guess trade it that's what you
mean
um
it's cool with someone level it up
[Music]
um
so I have to level it up why I'm
co-opping well who should I follow up
with now
oh Big Bub wow
wow
should I just get that one
[Music]
yeah
and yeah burp looks new
[Music]
I'll take it
it's a shot it's not shiny
it's not for XP no no I want it in my
team for the for the okay you can take
it down afterwards
um do you think little kick will kill it
maybe
um
ciao
well double kick should be fine right
yeah
yeah please don't kill
my bird
let's get it down a little bit
foreign
[Music]
um
which would be okay to use without
killing it
obviously not wild charge
yeah I don't want to use it
metal clock okay
maybe also I'm friends
two to five pounds
thanks kiwawa you're welcome
six and a half hours now
don't hit too often
it's so it's okay now you can stop now
or stop now stop stop
oh my God okay it stopped well it
stopped perfectly fine actually I've
read that couldn't get any better
hey you even get a great ball
[Music]
s
be like that
again and take a luxury ball luxury
it will be like a little vacation
no
you big [\h__\h]
how dare you how dare you
the netball oh okay wait a second let's
try this one come on come on come on
come
on come on
I'm not gonna run now of course not
um
I don't know
oh
he's a fluffy pillow
oh cute
uh
netball right
he's a
oh
what do you want
help please uh
[Music]
wait was it Nest phone not that ball
um
I don't want to use the Ultra Ball
she almost went into the great Bowl
let's try it again
look is it just because it's a catch
rape thing is so low
is it down low
it seems a normal one
I would have been funny if that one's in
double can you not swim
I want to see the Dax swim I feel like
you could
yeah I know that is but
I don't think I have anything
okay okay
okay I get it okay
[Music]
you better take this one
little [\h__\h]
[Music]
a lot of expedo
what the hell
all right now
uh who else do we not need for sure
during the
upcoming Mela battle
on point
hold on I
know I am
Sunny guys why did I catch Santa Claus
because of ground right
from one another I wanted the variety of
water
exciting
[Music]
one
are you guys confused
Sammy is for electricity Jim oh okay I
thought ground was good against fire
I was thinking that before huh wow these
birds are beautiful wings
wow
new burp oh hi
hello I'm a burp too
what's your name what name is this Bob
wow
[Music]
water pledge water attack should we
switch it out
all right I think I'll go back and we'll
just challenge my life it will be fine
hopefully
I'll be okay I'll probably be okay
[Music]
I'll just heal everyone and then we'll
go in with Gyarados
and long boy
and
who else
[Music]
fun I should kill it
because I'm so [\h__\h] mad
um
[Music]
and how you disrespected me
go back for the Train on the island it's
a good reason oh that was a trainer on
the island we're just from
[Music]
I did not see
yeah oh I like it
um
for the bread boy
what's something right there what
what you don't mean this one right
there's also items here
that's it I had some chicken nuggets
today
for lunch oh
it's shark
it's a shark that I've not seen before
ah is that though
is that still water
yeah it's new
cold water
[Music]
love this one really
that's already an evolution or does it
start off like this
I don't know if I want to kill it I want
to catch it I think for the open deck
it's not an evil oh
another single form what the hell only
kind of horns boring
if you will survive
then I catch you but
second game I played with the Pokemon if
you survive I will catch you if you
don't well then you just don't survive
so apparently there was a little trainer
here
for Courtney
ah yeah okay I was to distracted with
the Gyarados
[Music]
I can't find my potential anyway I
anywhere are you looking for potential
Ah
that's why you wanted me to invite him
yeah yeah yeah I saw this it was posted
in our Discord
and
this is how you think it's a reference
because Yago is a young girl seems to be
[Music]
just the name that's used in Japan I
mean I've never heard it besides from
our Yago
[Music]
well who knows maybe there is a fan
working
at Game Freak
[Music]
not necessarily don't necessarily need
to be but
it could be could be I mean Sims 4 even
had a reference to kiwawa
okay
[Music]
so
no it was like big games it's like
unbelievable you don't really expect it
don't expect it but
I guess
nowadays YouTubers are
quite popular
and Yago apparently had is that a shiny
is it always proud purple purple
it's not shiny
actually
um can I go first oh I might oh oh oh is
this Gonna Hurt
ah [\h__\h]
and that yeah yeah
uh had I didn't watch it I just saw a
screenshot but Jago was in 3D
participating with a 3D model
add um demio
yeah
oh I want to fight you
[Music]
um
I I saw oh my God my team is not looking
so good I saw something going on there
I'm just gonna hope that these ones will
work
did you guys watch it
the pot with Bianca
[Music]
ah
I don't know hello
oh that might kill actually nice
I haven't seen it not yet
it's only to watch it oh yeah I've got
something to do then afterwards
okay let's live up nice too that's very
good
get stronger before we
enter the base
you guys say she's level 20 or 25 it was
25 then
[Music]
might struggle a little bit fun oh we
gotta check out gotta those moves as
well
[Music]
check summary oopsy
he got
wonderful scary face Brian and Iceberg
oh my God a nice move but that's bad
against fire I guess
waterfall is all I need
we're gonna also put a Twista
I will add
just for fun
light
okay
I wanted to change the icon of vital as
well hmm
Ryan is not that good as well don't need
brine with waterfall
was there something you would want to
replace it with
[Music]
Twista
let's play Twister
My Little Brian
just to have some variety if we're not
gonna use it anyway
that's even worse
oh well I mean no
okay
I never trainer but where's the Pokemon
fender
[Music]
ah this one I already fought okay it
should be up there
uh-huh
and then I'm a little bit scared but I
mean last time we
did it so easily
so even if she's a little bit stronger
than us and
[Music]
no problem right what is this not to be
held by a Pokemon just those dice always
was a good number and holding one can
ensure that the holy smoking string was
hit more oh
oh yeah I should give them some items
right
I have uh someone with multi moves
got the arm press maybe I should give
that to dakuma
[Music]
okay let's see what we got
if I tend to hold
oh we're all day
okay
Laura dies
and then what about the other ones do we
have something
for Amica
[Music]
um let's hold the move first
occasionally reduces the weight of the
holder
wait I don't really have many
oh wait
Chris's base points where Pokemon's
attack stats speed stat
attacks like we're starting on a special
attacks that may sell the numbers give
them berries that's true oh wait but
these ones
these ones I use up but these ones are
to hold right
okay
no these ones are actually used up as
well maybe
oh okay I'm good
I don't have so many useful items to
hold I guess I'll give some berries
[Music]
um
I don't know what would be good
burn
Quick Lunch Berry
[Music]
I mean
um
a grandma friendly what the [\h__\h]
no I haven't seen any option to plant
trees in this game
rasped berries
yeah but we're not gonna really use the
verb right
I'll just give it Cherry Berry
and for you
I will give you
the raspberry
[Music]
and
I will give hmm
[Music]
a raspberry
cloth
honey floatstone
[Music]
okay
I got you
reduces the weight okay I guess Kanye is
really heavy
don't say it directly to clanido
now we got one more
okay I don't remember if you guys told
me what what my third member should be
did you
what do we bring who do you think would
be helpful
all right
honey
okay
oh finally I got some items was about
time
all right uh let me save
hello
[Music]
and oh wait no I don't save it what am I
doing
okay infiltrating the base where's the
entrance
[Music]
huh
was it on this side
ah is it all the way over there
oh
so far
so safe
out oh [\h__\h] uh huh
the other way follow the road okay
wow the one at the top I suppose okay it
means
I think that will be the last thing we
do
because I'm getting tired
even though I want to play longer
well I'm gonna play I'll [\h__\h] in a
Pokemon next week as well so
um
well as such a small verb I would be
very intimidated as well by Gyarados
it's understandable
foreign
dance
do I have actually something
effective against you
unless I use Iceland are you dragon type
does that work well
yes big rainbow
I remember that Dragon don't like eyes
fell for the tones and no problems
Bring It On
[Music]
dragons don't like ice oopsie but
Italians definitely like ice cream even
in the winter
[Music]
let me ask you too
okay let me go now I didn't want to
fight you all
right
I'm leaving
hey
seriously
Powers has the worst shining form it it
what color does it get
if it's pink then it's kind of
embarrassing for the towers
Red Bicycle let me fight you
no
[Music]
just slightly darker what
all right
yeah that's being quiet the normal
Academy student anyway I only won first
you have been accepted into a precious
thoughtful
oh what's your end game
I need answers that's all how do I
resolve the situation was team star and
what's causing its members of our
Behavior
team star is a subject of more than a
few nasty rumors swirling around the
academy you know
some say their bullying as close the
worrying number of students to drop out
of school others say they hold up in
their bases plotting to cause trouble
for the economy
but these are rumors the matter I
indirectly confronted with is something
else I'm talking about team Stars
persistence true and see
they've always been skipping class for a
while now five of them in Portugal are
the so-called bosses of teamstar are
having so much set of footage inside the
classroom for over a year it seems that
team teams rank and file have recently
started started stirring up Mischief as
well
um that's why I took it upon myself to
issue a direct order to team star to
this bed I informed them that they
should refuse if they should refuse I
should have no choice but to expel all
the students affiliated with their team
it's been a year you should have already
expelled them by far like way long ago
you're going way too easy on them
but I'm afraid there's been no response
and deadline I set for them to make
their choice between the solution
expulsion is not eye upon us so you'll
see when I overheard you talking on the
phone to Casio player I couldn't have
comment wait aren't you just a normal
student Clive how could you be able to
threatened them with getting kicked out
of school
don't even question it my dad my dad is
the boss he he would do it not me it's
casselbea can you hear me
be careful
I see you're coming up to one of
teamsters bases was there someone will
you just know why choose me
at least now
well we want that team star will have
have its got up after losing one boss to
you already this base won't go down as
usually as the last one will sit with
Extreme Caution I'll be in touche
she'll be in touche
touche
hmm
yum yum yum yum
I will heal
by myself
oh goodbye
I only need to heal a little bit though
[Music]
oh this time only one of you guys is
waiting for me
foreign
[Music]
oh
if you don't clear out real quick like
I'll have to come at you in self-defense
you get me
I'm not turning back
we're all right time for me to stop the
fence to snot right out of here
well we're so far apart go closer you
scared or what
I see you shivering and shaking I see
those Goosebumps on your skin
aha that is not fire is it is that fire
oh I guess it is
I'm surprised I'm actually faster wow
a dark fire okay
very fitting
very fitting Pokemon
for an evil team oh so evil aren't ya
man you crazy strong
wait are you that key to declare the war
on teams there
[Music]
whoa okay
thanks for the terrible news
I guess I should have totally subscribed
to you then I would have known that you
would come and I could have warned
everybody and I should have hit the
notification Bell as well to make sure
that I miss absolutely nothing
well I guess I'll subscribe now and then
I'll leave a like on your stream forgive
me for not doing that until now
just so you know I am already subscribed
of course I am big fan Casio bear told
me to scope out the fire crew space I
thought I'd come give you some backup
now that I've proved but it seems you
all said
what was that
oh
is that your friend
foreign
like Carlos
is that you traveled
what are you doing here
is that yours
this is Charles the chocolate
it makes so many zappy noises
he's one of the Pokemon the academy
takes care of within its ground
foreign
looks like he may have some connection
to the team Stars fire crew
I'd better choice after him don't worry
I'll regroup with you soon
oh is he gonna help them
motivated
who is this time
I see you there's a second standing God
Network
stationed inside the basis Teamsters
fire clue the shadow Squad
the robot smell is really [\h__\h] cute
and I love her but she will not you know
love me back so uh I decided to take her
down because of vengeance
our declaration of war must have made
her blood boil but even now her clothes
are hot at work inside the base trying
to keep her feeling under control
that means your best dude is to take
down all the cons nice and quick once
there are no one left to keep to help
help Mela keep Earth cool she should
come out to comfort you
ring the bell on the gate and once
you're ready to kick off is a face of
the operation
time to wipe the shadow Squad of the map
be quiet guys
I didn't save but it just did safe on
the top left I saw that
so I guess we can go uh wait let me
check
uh yeah
okay
[Music]
please don't explain me the rules again
I know how to do it
oh God of those why are you already
there
I'm getting logged out reading one of my
sister squads and now she thinks she can
take us on time to give her the boot
gang let's show this gay question what
teams are gonna do and if you're
listening gay personally know this
unless you can beat Freddy Pokemon
totally not to explain it again
yeah this just wants to get right into
it yeah
that was also motivated
isn't this cheating having my Pokemon
out already Kusa
I can do it just with one Pokemon
can I go for these ones
yo they got the Mega Man Pokemon
not so weak
pretty impressive wow
these ones aren't bad even like really
their choice of Pokemon isn't because
lame is it used to be always
same shitty boring ass Pokemon only in
other games
doing pretty good this space kind of
seems smaller
go go get a dog damn
oh grow lift in English in German we say
I think
let's go for these ones
where are you going longboard
he's jumping around in this in this
Stone
and eight more yes I can count
this one
[Music]
is doing it all
no it's not like saying fire dog
it's like saying volcano I think that's
what they're referencing in German but
even in English it would work
thank you finish it
easy peasy on the financial bridge is
all up to the bus now
Bring It On
[Music]
hello in love with you
it's happening
wow look at there's just got
new oh I just got the attitude bottom
team starts by cremella her makeup is on
fleek her hair is so cute
purple
what are those
so you're the dope who picked a fight
with Team star
I don't know why you do something so
stupid and I don't care you challenge
that song will beat you down and that's
all there is to it prepare to get messed
up
that's messed me up mess me up
four more
she was singing in her head right now
Crush crash crash crash crash yes
[Music]
yes play
I'm your biggest fan right here right
now you're going down
sunlight turns harsh please don't take
down my
oh my god oh level 27
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] that was a critical hit
this little there ain't nothing but ash
left oh
mystery let's take it from the devil's
got a body like another one singing like
a clock it's been another time before
they all running out I thought it was
mine
they're hot rain dance
um
finally said I'm free for that
crystallize
was the only one for me
[Music]
but I wear the biggest smile
now
[Music]
feels so good
second chances they don't ever matter
people never change once a whole nothing
more I'm sorry that will never change
sorry
there's a million dollars
innocent as possible to get to you
[Music]
without my attention
good job staying alive
huh Staying Alive is this uh car also
fire now
how much HP is 78 okay
so what should work
we'll be fine
[Music]
let's go
to shine now
nice
chill
how much does that how much does that do
now
beautiful that's what we like to see
hmm will we survive one more hit from
her maybe not oh
[Music]
we did at least finally I yeah it's
challenging
challenging too yeah
oh oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
should I switch
[Music]
yeah I'll switch to Connie
for the last hit
because I would have to heal otherwise
but this way I kind of gets some time to
shine as well
oh even though he was still crystallized
oh wow
okay kill stealer
yeah but Connie is an actual member of
the team galados is not so I think
he deserves
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
I guess I'll go back to singing for
Paramore Now
is this really how it's gonna end oh
what a hassle
love her I love her Marry Me Marry Me
Marry Me
man what a hassle these boots
can't freaking walking down but I just
want to look cool
welcome back Maddie which one is talking
which one is Eddie the small one or the
pink one
ah the small one
I managed to get a bunch of shark dead
to evolve that ought to be enough to
power the Starmobile and finally get
that hunk of metal rolling
I still don't see the article space I
don't know what to do Glad Tidings
indeed is it not so odega
I'm I'm just
I forgot the voice I did for this one
too
[Music]
um
surprised she's not oh no
I'm I'm just I'm just surprised she's
not all hot air no that was not a liver
[Music]
it's not comments if you can't even
decide on what voice you want to have
then just don't talk at all okay
as if you're any better Mela being rude
and being rude and saying mean things is
literally your whole deal
S at the Academy have always been
jealous of how cute Meli is she just
puts on a silly attitude so they'll stop
picking on her
even kiwawa is in love with her although
I guess you're not wrong to say that her
silly attitude is what people know her
for what what come on not you too Eddie
event
yeah operation style is finally
happening
uh and the big boss would pray is their
plan
they're already got in touch with all
the buoys and asked them to head over to
the schoolyard
it's finally time huh man I'm so stoked
the thrill's burning me right up
I love her I love her I love her
you weirdo in weird boots I love you
I burned for everything I had and now
I've spotted out guess this is where it
ends
look at those of yours
oh she's giving credits not to Connie
really let us have it but I guess gotta
just did the awesome work beating me in
battle is a huge deal so here take the
star badge and be proud of yourself
I love you I love you
is her her handshake so strong is she
twisting my arm or so
foreign
[Music]
I don't think Canada's will find use for
it also gyandos is leaving the team
after this
I came for now leave me alone
[Laughter]
let's just uh be happy and accept it
yamella from teamstore all right there's
your Pokemon I'd like you just see
huh could you supposed to be
oh I can imagine her being British
oh yeah you two look good together
shark attack that oh wait
if it if it ain't chalice what are you
doing here
it seems you came to this place looking
for you
it's very attached to you isn't it
yeah because I used to play with him
every day back when I was still going to
school
I can't even tell more or less what he's
thinking just by looking at the way his
Flames move
you have any idea why Charles wanted to
visit you
[Music]
oh look shut up Charles
to me it looks like he's saying that he
wants you to come back
shut it already won't ya
[Music]
I say team stars hold itself up in these
places to plot something against the
academy were you aware of this
first I've had heard of a stupid rumor
like that
nothing's changes back then everyone's
still spouting garbage
what about a modified car you were
motoring around and just now you don't
even have a [\h__\h] license what the
[\h__\h] ah I'm I it doesn't matter it's
it's not a real car anyway it's a
Pokemon
we made that thing a long time ago to
help us out with a big fight
but we never actually used it against
anyone before you two came looking for
trouble
we never used it before uh was just
about a big fight
you haven't heard of operation star
operation sure another version star full
this is the first I'm hearing of it
yeah I guess you wouldn't know
but for me and the rest of Team starts a
memory will always treasure
oh
interesting
nice to see she's she has like a
sensitive emotional side as well
waifu life full
of
um
[Music]
badges now in your position
I see now that there's no bus to lead
them the rest of the school shouldn't
last long
did she say anything about me uh never
mind sorry I got distracted for a second
there again and now about your reward
I'll transfer some LP over to your
fullness promise
oh 6 000 this time
oh
Morty I'm still arms use those nutrients
to strengthen your Pokemon even further
I'll add my supply unit wrap and made
you shortly to deliver some bonus
materials too
[Music]
is cuter now yeah
I have competition for melo's heart yeah
I guess I have to take her down
hello it's me again from the supply unit
what the heck
oh we have the same colors oh my God
stop that ew disgusting I don't like
being looked somebody help
hmm yeah I feel you
understandable
but why
what how did you get help why did why is
he sleeping now did we punch adios
what
it rolled all over me what even is that
Pokemon anyway
I have no idea what it is it's a bike I
guess huh let me see yourself climb with
a giant question mark of a Pokemon at
your side
[Music]
um but before I get I like that choice
though I like to put in some funny
choices just
this time
uh here's a reward anyway
thank you
your name your name's kiwala right
you're part of operation Starfall's
battle you know can I ask you something
what do you think of Team star
they're not all that strong
week week
no match for me you know some of the
rumors say that same style wasn't always
a bunch of delinquents most of them used
to be victims of bullying or they just
found it hard to interact with people
but then these Misfits and also they
found each other and banded together to
form team star all they wanted to do was
push back against the police they
couldn't face him alone
but that's just info I got by hacking
other students social media accounts
she's a hacker
that was a fun talk about some secret
Mastermind behind the five Frozen
someone who recruited them to the team
in the first place
I don't normally talk this much no my
throat kind of hurts same some good luck
we're taking down the other braces and
stuff
so I guess you said it before but it's a
week ago over a week ago
yay we did it it was the the the the car
fight was a bit difficult but we
survived and we thrived yata
[Music]
a bicycle
it's not a muscle car that I know for
sure
damn that we are are almost seven and a
half hours
um I'm gonna end it here
it's 11 P.M
doshio
I did want to write super trans today
but long stream this now
[Music]
we did so much
foreign
[Music]
yeah I have a shorter stream tomorrow I
think it will not take too much time the
The Reef building
it's my first time doing it but I don't
think it will take longer than an hour
so yum
oh
no oh I'm right in front of iono I did
two gyms two Titans and two basins the
next stream we will go to iono pretty
much straight away I think
hmm
[Music]
foreign
I did so much yes yes
I hope I was able to catch up too
a lot of the other girls
I feel like
we
bet through the game today speed
[Music]
that's terrible look I am angry
inacceptable but yeah it's okay I I saw
some evolution I didn't see before on
the funny team but we'll switch out
Gyarados again
uh and probably kick out long boy now
that I saw the evolution
and bring back of course
um Sparks obviously and then look for a
different team member that will plays
long boy maybe the rats and also the
sand castle for electricity Arena so
little mama tally kick out dakuma sorry
dakuma you're great
um
yeah no I mean I like long but look at
the HP it's like
um
dies so easily even though I feel like
it would be looking at the moveset you
know there's potential but yeah
awful HP awful defense
so squishy
and even though so cute
also oh my god did you notice
long boy has odakuma chicken face
oh my God
[Music]
you still just said no
the nose is the big
[Music]
how did I not notice until now kids on C
right
maybe it's actually chickens with a
really long neck ah
[Music]
triple
triple triple chicken
don't know why it's pink now though
maybe it's a really really embarrassed
chicken
today thank you for watching
with two streams yesterday
one Premiere and one long stream today
and two streams tomorrow I think I made
up for
the missing days this week where I
uploaded all kinds of things anyway
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
foreign
yeah no I didn't feel like I had to make
up for it also but I mean you know it's
weekend so
I wanted to make use of you guys being
available I guess
um now I hope
I hope that the food I mean it's
Saturday so the food should still be
um good to make
[Music]
I make a
um
I either will cook or if it's still okay
tomorrow then maybe I'll cook it
tomorrow and see what I have in the
freezer now when I probably should cook
it on the other side I'll see how it is
mmm
have a good food thank you more time to
cuddle with Kitty cattle yes I can
literally not say cats anymore I would
say kitty katos and chunky wonky it's
like the new official name chunky wonky
the date decides exactly you get me
I'm a good evening you too and join me
almost YouTube
pizza rolls
I say kitkats for mine let's move around
let's move around I don't really use
now I call it you little [\h__\h] because it
broke my [\h__\h] heart
I don't know what I have in the freezer
I have some things
hmm
I have some some sweet dessert dumplings
with like
um plums inside I think which is so
delicious because uh it's the dumpling
of the plum but also you you you coat it
kind of not really coated but like you
roll it around in a lot of like
um crumbs which aren't I don't think
it's really bread crumbs but it's also
not cookie crumbs like some kind of
in-between thing it's really sweet I
love that one of my favorite desserts
and they sell a lot of variations of it
uh that you can make
um easily at home by just putting it in
the freezer and then throwing it in hot
boiling water
um
it only has just begun exactly
[Music]
um
all that kind of stuff well not gum
noodle I mean yeah it's Vegeta
but Captain also is pretty neat yeah
if you guys ever go skiing in Austria
um you have to ask you know if you go to
one of the restaurants up there in the
mountains
my my old roommate ordered that too I
think we both ordered it we ate one
together so
um but one thing you should you have to
eat up there is a gamco noodle a hot
Camp noodle
it's like a big dumpling big dumpling
with
what's moon in English
how do I hit this crab
gamble is a fluffy yeast dough dumpling
filled with spiced plum jam and served
with melted butter and a mix of poppy
seeds and sugar on top it is
occasionally even though less
traditional served with vanilla cream
warm vanilla cream sauce instead it is
culinary specialty of Austria and
Bavaria yes I like eating it with a lot
of vanilla cream sauce
and it's hot so it's a warm dessert so
if you eat it on in the snow in the
mountains and um like as a break when
you are skiing or snowboarding
it's so good
and the plum gem inside it says spiced
Plum gem I don't know how to describe it
but it doesn't just taste like normal
Plum gem it has some kind of
interesting taste to it
um
you can you can also get it outside of
the mountain on the ground as well as a
dessert in Austrian restaurants it's
quite filling it's pretty big so you can
share it normally with another person
yeah that's how you spell it yes yes
yeah it's so good
yeah
we have all kinds of stuff like that I
also like oh yeah it's actually called
povido that's why that's why it's kind
of different than Plum povida is what's
inside poor beetle
poor beetle is a dialect word for hmm
fruit spread prepared from the prune
Plum unlike Jam or marmalade and unlike
the German flowerman moose who will is
prepared without additional sweeteners
and gelling agents for wheelers cooked
for several hours in order to achieve
the necessity sweetness and consistency
the plums used should be harvested as
late as possible ideally after the first
Frost in order to ensure they contain
enough sugar
in Austria Moravia and Bohemia who will
is the basis for bottles for little cake
and cake noodle but it's also used as a
sandwich spread never had it on a
sandwich
etc etc
it's special
we have some good Austrian desserts you
guys need to try them
um
[Music]
hmm
food
[Music]
you really seldom well
I should get a sponsorship for
everything for life because I everything
I talk about
I sell so well don't I
[Music]
mean that sounds good hey
got a sweet note on my list now this you
know actually
um there's one Austrian dessert that I
actually don't recommend you guys
getting it's just funny and people get
it for the sake of having had it once
um
it's from a region called Salzburg
and it's called salzburgen
it looks funny if you look it up
maybe let me write it besides program no
can
it looks like free mountains usually and
basically it's just fluffy
oh sure
it's just fluffy like a souffle
souffle is served as a dessert
in the a culinary specialty in the
Austrian city of Salzburg the Swiss
Supply is made from egg yolk floor sugar
and vanilla sugar
mixed into a dough that's it
and next egg white is granulated and
granulated sugar whisk into a maling
until soft peaks form
and then mixed into the dough with a
spatula finally dumplings of the mixture
are baked in an oven but it doesn't
really have like a real dumpling texture
though at all it's way fluffy and Airy
wait did you get the message in the chat
because I feel like it failed
um baked in an oven until lightly brown
on the outside and besides going up a
lot always freshly prepared and served
warm with powdered sugar sometimes with
raspberry sauce or any other fruit
spread layered on the bottom of the
souffle though traditionally served as a
dessert the dish is filling enough to
eat as a mangoes yeah but it's not yummy
at all it just tastes like almost
nothing
it's weird
it is also usually served in quite a big
portion as well so normally you can also
share it
and you will be very disappointed but
you might want to get it anyway because
it's funny and it's like wobbly
it's wobbly like jelly
um
what are you picking up what is your
opinion I love
it
seems so simple because it's basically
scrambled pancakes but no it's way more
than that
it's way more than scrambled pancakes
and you have to eat it with um there's
different types of sauces that people
like to eat with like apple
um mousse
and uh
and some other stuff
um
it's art yeah it's so good yeah they
also eat it with a plum sauce
and yeah
it's really fluffy and big and very
sugary
yes powdered sugar mm-hmm
you have to try it yeah this is also one
of the desserts you can easily get in an
Austrian restaurant
[Music]
um
also make it yourself I think Kaiser
schmann is pretty easy to make you just
have to make sure to get like a fitting
sauce like I think the easiest one to
get overseas would be apple mousse
it's like baby apple mousse for babies
okay
I've tangented it enough we're at over
seven and a half hours
almost eight hours
we should end it
bubble bubbles yes also a good Austrian
cake chocolate cake with some Jam inside
it's very chocolatey but I think the jam
helps to balance it and give it like a
little bit of a fresh taste
but it's like highest quality chocolate
cake ever it's so good like it's
chocolate
um sponge
but then outside it has a really
thick and good
smooth chocolate chip chocolate coating
and inside between the sponges is a thin
layer of GM usually I think it's apricot
jam
why are we talking about food right now
because I guess I'm gonna make food now
Danka
um
[Music]
because hungry yeah
um it's definitely good and very
recommendable
especially with hot vanilla sauce and a
scoop of ice cream you know get the best
of both worlds
um but not my favorite Austrian dessert
but Apple Store is very good yes yes
I'm very proud of the episode there's
also talking total another variation
that is without apples I like I actually
many times I prefer tops over at first
order
[Music]
ah
ah sweet soft Quark cheese
in Austrian German it's topven yeah I
think in German German they would not
call it Top Fin uh in German German they
call it quack so often when I say topven
and German people will not understand
unless maybe up there from Bavaria
um
there's also no story but I don't like
news total because that's with nuts and
nuts are
and desserts to me kind of boring yeah
it needs to be sweet and
juicy or creamy
yeah I'm so quick and then fights is top
from alcohol
can't you go eat
should I go eat should I should I
put yours
I'm really curious about that cake I saw
last night though at Cali stream the one
with the swirls with the strawberries I
want that cake
kick
I have to find a way to get it
no no no no no no pretty cool attention
no no
don't torture me it was sweet poof go
make yourself something sweet
calcium
yeah the cafe chicken cake was great too
why did that person make it to impress
me probably right
I was impressed
I want to taste it
it looks it doesn't only look good it
also looks like it would taste really
good I'm sure it tastes actually really
good it doesn't smell me it doesn't
really look good
mmm
Beauty on the outside and yum yum on the
inside
pumpkin pie after I flip pumpkin pie I
like pumpkin soup but I
um I also never had the pumpkin spice
latte from Starbucks
[Music]
is it good is it sweet
because I don't know if I want something
sweet then I want something really sweet
not something that makes you think it's
okay because I guess it works but in
reality
let's be real it doesn't work
pie Lisa being sweet in my mind
[Music]
but I wouldn't mind trying
well I'm on my giving it a try
but I've never seen pumpkin pie here
we're not a big pie country we're more
of a cake country
um good old yummy
fluffy
creamy
cakes rather than pies
apple pies awesome no again with a
vanilla ice cream scoop mmm
cheesecake
everybody always Praises cheesecake so
much but cheesecake
boring can be very good of course
but not in big amounts I say
um other cakes I will eat endlessly
in big amounts but cheesecake is like
boring
trust opinion
I am Banning you
into the usual room
you must agree with what kiwawa says
or else
it's cakes or what
uh if you have the choice between like a
Saha torte and a cheesecake I think you
would also enjoy the sakatoa more unless
you're a big hater of chocolate then I
just cannot be friends with you at all
anyway
no I've never been to the Cheesecake
Factory oh next time I go to America I
will go
do they only have it in America
Cheesecake Factory
let's go
Cheesecake Factory I've heard good
things about Cheesecake Factory
mm-hmm
okay okay I'm gonna go now guys
[Music]
Nutella what the hell
in the ice cream cake
[Music]
Bubble Guppies
and German we say
ah
dies
[Music]
I've talked so much that my my tongue is
already numb and I can't do the boom
boom sound so well
have I done an AM turkey yet it's about
[\h__\h] time
if I didn't did I
I don't think I did
I didn't
oh my God
damn okay
well they have it in Canada
Oh Canada
[Music]
Wrong song
tomorrow out in the Channel first
[Music]
maybe she already has the reservation up
I don't know and then after that later
and we make a wreath
[Music]
DIY
Christmas wave
water
[Music]
mm-hmm
no no no no no no no no
boom
and down
[Music]
honey
foreign
[Music]
Japanese
tweet about uh
[Music]
live to D assets that are Pokemon
related
I think my acids are fine
would not be affected
foreign
[Music]