[Music]
oh
13.
[Music]
me
break down
[Music]
yum yum
foreign
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
wow
[Music]
i'm at the ocean looking at the palm
trees
oh a dolphin wow let's ride the dolphin
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
can we just
she's surviving
where did my game go
wait oh let's see
yeah oh yeah okay sorry i'm tapping up
hello kitty king kitty
the first words to say should always be
kikiriki
kyoba kookyumi today we read the air
kooky yummy is a japanese is this too
loud this is too loud
to me to me personally it's still out uh
but i'll turn it down here okay
um cookie
is japanese word for air or like uh
atmosphere or yeah air
basically uh and then yummy
yomu is the verb for reading
so uh japanese people like to
use this word a lot
means the the thing to read
[Music]
and um
welcome to the new members thank you
guys for the super chats
um there's a funny um slang word
that i would like to tell you that i
mean it's not
not exactly a word but um
so someone who can read the air
will not be called this someone who
cannot
read the air uh japanese people on the
internet would like to call that person
okay why yes it's what i wrote in the
title
ky is someone who cannot read the
the room it's it's it's turned into into
a
what's the other what's the other thing
not a verb it's turned into you know
a thing okay
[Music]
no i can generally read the air pretty
well especially because this is about
japanese culture
um how to read the air in mostly
you know japanese culture japanese
situations although i think it applies
to
or i would wish that it would apply more
like people would
read the air more overseas and in other
cultures and other countries
as they do in japanese culture because
there is there's
just japanese culture so polite right so
um
it feels like a lot of cultures could
learn
a lot from japanese
but yeah people
what minecraft oh oh forgot to go
okay
i don't have the logo for that right now
so we'll just keep it empty over there
[Music]
like there's a lot of japanese people
here at this early time it's like six
a.m or something and then
my australian peeps are also awake
already
here it is 10 p.m
um ohio good morning good evening good
day everyone
what up what up
i woke up so early today and then later
i took a
comfy long nap because today i went
to check out uh my future apartment
and even though i originally planned to
go for
more than one apartment i mean in that
in that apartment blog i looked through
all kinds of apartments
that were just you know cut differently
it was really interesting
um but i think i've decided i have
decided already
and because i don't give a [\h__\h] about
any other apartments this one is pretty
damn good
it has a lot of things that i was
looking for and
uh the other is like i'm like
one thing that kind of annoyed me but we
might talk about this tomorrow in the
atelier riser stream because we always
talk a lot do a lot of small talk in my
rpg streams
um but uh it annoys me that
i contact these what do you call
um imobilian macla
in english the people who sell
who sell apartments in houses realtors
yeah yeah
not landlord yeah and real estate agents
uh
i couldn't contact these peeps and they
just
don't answer me and then i send them the
same email again and then they answer
and then okay i'm i'm like okay now we
got a conversation going
[\h__\h] off but then no um
i answered again and then they stop
answering again
do they not want me to get there apart
there
i don't get it hi
you're gonna make it so difficult i had
that with
uh two two different realtors
one of them was the one that i um
got the apartment from today like even
though she didn't answer me
three times i had to send several
emails i thought they were gonna
be happy about me running an apartment
and and answer me
like quickly but they don't answer at
all sometimes
yeah so weird on realtors
how inconsiderate exactly they should
read the room they should play this game
and then read the goddamn room
and
we'll talk more about that uh tomorrow
uh
i got a lot of topics also because
yesterday my family was here
so we can talk about that tomorrow um
okay so let's get started this game a
lot of the japanese members have played
it um
uh before there's three there a new one
recently came out
which is why all the japanese members
have been playing it again
and there is a third game of this
already out
right now but i'm starting with the
first one because i haven't played it
yet and hello
there is the english version
uh i'm glad i have it in english i was
going to play it in japanese otherwise
but
let's see there's a the language you
know is not so important it's mostly
just situations
that you look at and then you decide
what you're gonna do
um and then at the end i hope they will
give me
an english judgement of my
kynes uh as you can see
the japanese text is still there um
and we will take a look at the options
uh how to play
[Music]
look at this this is a space where you
are free to consent
consider things as you like there is no
one here to stop you from being as
considerate or inconsiderate as you
please
after considering the situation move the
red object on the screen
sometimes there may be thank you guys
for the memberships sometimes there may
be nothing to move
just do what you consider the
appropriate action by the way is the
music
well balance okay guys with my voice
you hear the music right if you wish to
stop playing just push
escape all of these situations by the
way are time limited and like they
end really quickly so you got to act
quickly and decide quickly and often you
don't even understand the situation and
then it's already over okay it's fine
okay okay let's go let's go
and there's like a quick one a cookie
but i think all the members have been
playing the full one
and it uh turns out to mostly fill up
one hour nicely
we're gonna we're gonna do this one and
once we finish this game
in the next weeks we're gonna do the
other parts as well because i love this
game already
let's go let's consider some situations
yeah this is the same thing and this is
a space where you're free to consider or
not consider
it um
the most considerate person on earth
number one okay so these people are
together so i'm gonna move to the side
so that they can sit down
easy number two
why are you pressing x
domino i fell down together with them
in in the right timing i'm so
considerate
a double dumbbell okay down
number four oh in tokyo
ah what was it
what was i supposed to do i couldn't do
anything i think i don't know
normally they all stand on one side
really like oh
what what what i gotta go there i gotta
go there
empty spot that was hard to see
oh plainly considerate okay cool
i am from for for now plainly
considerate okay number six
what does that even mean santa
i gotta sleep just acting
i'm home asleep dude yeah i'm asleep
that reminds me of the one time i got
robbed when i had my birthday and was
overseas on the vacation
and there was a someone robbing us
and i was acting as if i was asleep
because i didn't know what what are we
doing
what what what what what am i what nunny
what what what ah do i just order
something
what like i don't know what i went
around
i'll tell you the story another time
what what are we doing
i i can't do nothing
ah because she has no more drinks so i'm
gonna call someone for her
to take her next order i think that's
what was happening oh
a b c e what
maybe i didn't i go for her because she
otherwise
she's not chosen ah cause this is like a
dating part
party like in japanese they call it
gokum
if i get this last pin will you go out
with me yeah okay
what oh i was the pin i played the pin
okay then i pressed the right button i
thought it was
controlling the ball in some way or
another
consider it
[Music]
i am not inconsiderate okay
wait was i supposed to not drop because
she didn't want to go out with me like
she didn't really seem like she wanted
okay anyway oh my god what
what there's a foot up there
[Music]
what is this and we're just gonna
destroy them all
[Music]
i don't understand number 12. but i
think this is the funny thing like you
stand
huh kiddies lay
okay seat so what
how do i sit okay what was i just saying
this is too fast
yeah yeah the thing is like you're
probably gonna miss a lot of these
situations because
not because i'm inconsiderate but
because it's like
oh maybe i'll
go go somewhere yeah
[Laughter]
wait wait it might be awkward to look at
that what
a ghost
oh he wants me to be surprised
ah because otherwise his ghost would be
scared it would be sad
oh hey ah a little bit
wrong timing next one yeah a good timing
good
that was good i think one more
[\h__\h] too late but i think it still
hope it still counts
plainly is that better than the one we
got uh one before this
this was the same that we got in the
beginning too
oh
[Music]
ah because otherwise you know it's gonna
maybe bump so oh the cars were not
really happy with that
they would be beeping i don't give a
[\h__\h] about the cars
you got enough space over there okie
dokie
oh man i'm gonna go off at the next stop
oh okay
next is the final stop hit on the bus
terminal
uh wait i need did i maybe we need to
press a button
wait one what did i get up too early
uh i'm going there because there the
thing
there i couldn't go to the left because
then the thing would be in between them
we don't want to separate them yup no no
no
no how [\h__\h] considerate am i today's
our date
yay robocon and okay romance romans
romans romans for the girl for the girl
we don't
we want her to enjoy the date right
because i'm the guy in this situation
not robocop no it's for the girl she's
gonna enjoy it what are we doing
oh wait i need to go to the side yes yes
yes
yes yes to protect me lady
all right
hold on moderately consider is that
better than i see he presses the button
i should have done it i knew it i knew
it
[Music]
it's moderately better than the them
plainly i guess
i think so i think it's better we did
better than in the previous uh
five five rounds
twenty one
[Music]
stamina is weaker than the great elderly
okay
so what
was that okay
she's my girlfriend right or is she not
wait maybe if she isn't then i should
walk away
wait what what there's a robot
girlfriend wait who am i
who am i walking next to who was she my
girlfriend
was she my girlfriend ah today's another
day i guess i could think of them as a
couple now
ah they were heading towards an anime
when
suddenly they turned towards the romans
movie he seems one he builds up his
courage and takes her hand it seems like
they're really dating
oh i'm the girl i'm gonna lean over to
him
wait did he not did that make him i
don't know was i feeling like
oh no no no no no no no no go back
no
seeing people kiss in public is in japan
and japan is really
rare but i i actually i'm glad it's rare
because like i don't like singing that
much when people make out like
awkward move [\h__\h] i don't know does it
not make you guys feel
uncomfortable maybe i'm just too
sensitive in that kind of
area like when i'm
outside and i see people making out
it makes me feel so uncomfortable
i don't like it either awkward i agree
with you
a little bit um
yeah you guys agree with me nice but i
feel like overseas like overseas as in
perspective of japan and like
in japan they don't do that much but in
other countries i feel like they
at least like in europe and i guess
probably also in america
and and i don't know wherever
i feel like they do it a lot
don't you think it's illegal what i
can't imagine it being illegal in some
countries because some
some countries have really weird laws
[Music]
is pretty loot alright i mean hand
holding is okay
handling is not a problem let's continue
you guys say it's so innocent
oh so how who have we got for the yellow
ranger
oh i guess not me
i guess not me i don't know
i mean but no one's oh
[Music]
oh maybe or maybe yeah i just become the
yellow ranger
no i should have did that should i have
i don't know what
oh no i'm not good at tetris but oh no
wait this is his arm i give him this arm
right okay
ah fill the hole or give him his arm
that was his arm
so i think that was right yeah
close close oh [\h__\h] hey i got my
personality test pick what you want to
see yeah see what you got
um what
oh
oh wait i turned left i mean
i mean
well i mean that was difficult
for quick thinking that was difficult
okay
oh my gosh
did we did we get like worse again
we still have time we should have done
okay
how many are there barber bar
uh well i don't have hair so
i don't know i mean when are you gonna
barber with
right oh
thank you dude that's nice of you
scared this game is so great i hit a
home run for you
why am i dying
oh my god
[Music]
i think i did it oh my god
there's recently guys there's
there's a new wrestling move called oh
sorry did you see it
did you see it it's been all around the
whole live twitter tuesdays
uh down to my sponsors my last chance oh
my god oh wait wait i should dodge it
right so he can
go like i guess i guess i should have
so that i don't i don't know
moderately consider it okay there we go
i feel like we did quite well is that
the best rating you can get
in around i probably not probably not
probably like second
best oh that was a pokeball
oh i thought he wanted to shoot a girl
and so i shouldn't stop it
oh oh i was a pokemon
you should have made that more obvious i
didn't see that
oh man all right next one
this is so awesome i love this game
oh [\h__\h]
i was never good at jumping ropes never
especially if it's smooth more than one
oh
yeah yolo
oh what what are we doing what are we
doing
what oh wow wow wow you did such a good
job i went
what what i couldn't
i tried to move but i couldn't really do
anything not sure what i was supposed to
do
oh yeah sure sleep on me that's okay i
don't i think i could say
uh stand up in this situation or move
away
but i i want him to sleep tight so i'm
just gonna
let it happen
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
dammit
[Music]
what a big kusa moment 41 is there 100
and you want to sleep on me too i guess
that's okay oh
your legs don't maybe you should close
your legs close your legs
oh there's hundred problems it seems
okay
was that the right thing to do what baby
but she needs i don't want to buy is
this about
boys love but i don't know but she's no
one buying no one's buying her stuff so
i guess i just go to her
nice of me isn't it oh uh jump
do i destroy it or ah
okay i don't know whether what i was
doing but i think that was the right
thing we want him to grow big as well
well i don't know be i don't know
no no
is it just musical in here got it
but it probably shouldn't be cool like
or i should have turned it off
maybe because it was cooling
i don't know very vaguely considerate oh
no
it sounds bad
[Music]
yes sometimes i just don't know how to
i
should have turned it off
i just don't know how to
no i know how to read the air but
ah wait i mean yeah you can
stand there okay good
47. oh oh wow you want you're so strong
wow wow wow wow they are so strong
oh you pushed me down
i'm first can you get me a coffee got it
no problem this time uh okay
but she's feeling hot so she went but
she wants a coffee but
you know what i'm giving her a cold tea
because
i feel like that would help her she said
coffee but
she's feeling hot
oh oh yeah let me put that away yeah
because he's bringing us a new grill for
the yakiniku
let me eat that
he's changing the grill because it's all
like sticky and and
yeah no more oil on it um
you got me boy not whose hair is strong
plainly considerate
are we getting better i don't know this
seems
maybe better than vaguely considerate
plainly is better than vaguely
what would you guys say
he gonna
no yeah i think it's better plainly is
better than
banquet now we need something better
than plainly though
this is not good enough um i will do my
best
next round 51 oh we're going
for this quickly what's going on what is
this
oh no no no we're not looking up because
she has a skirt
no no we're not looking up look down
look down
is that what we're doing
yeah right 52
oh oh
wake up they're looking at us
ah plainly moderately vaguely mildly and
then consider it
oh okay oh no oh no
yes put it all on me that's okay
at least it didn't
yeah was that okay
big bro big rum so hungry before us to
do something
go slack competition finals the winner
gets uh only
okay good draw don't ride up to you what
what what ghost like what what
competition what
who's like what what
what what what winner
what you what what
what nanny what was they doing
i don't know oh no
this is out we fill the gap this time
because this looks like
something that won't fill the gap he
wants to pink
come on oh i should have gone faster
because he wanted to pee
ah i did it at the end
very very considerate oh come on
oh come on those were his
those were his panties
no i think he just wanted me to do it
quickly
the line one was okay what was i doing
with the line one i didn't understand
i'm not sure what i was doing did you
guys understand that
one the when i was drawing the line
it said something about ghost arm
oh wait was i supposed to draw him was
that supposed to be like
no no
[Music]
you were supposed to let your brother
win but like how was i was i didn't
draw one line because he drew
ghost ladder is that like a like a game
that people know
it's a ladder game you finish a ladder
or
something
maybe maybe my japanese viewers will
explain it to me later
on twitter like a pipe flowing
ghost like game never heard of it before
okay next next stop
hey why don't we check the personality
personality
what what what
what what
what
what that was the girl's hand
what what don't you think that's wrong
hey are you even listening
hey which do you think is better oh all
right yes yes what is it what
i want to talk to you what oh
no i wanna no i wanna talk to you
no no i want to listen to you
i don't think i was able to put [\h__\h] i
left
that was probably the worst thing i
could have done oh
but no one like people in japanese
trains are so quiet i love that but in
in my country people are so noisy
no one gives a [\h__\h] sometimes people
even listen to music without headphones
uh what um
okay i stay until 3 pm right
but no no i don't i don't leave until my
boss leaves
yep yep
yep
wait oh i was the boss oh [\h__\h]
oh okay she's a she's a cow we go eat
sushi not yakiniku that would be um
very inconsiderate
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] let me do it
no please please please give me another
chance
please i thought that was one of the
workers
[Music]
no
ah right i'm always the boss i'm
potential
makes sense it just makes sense now
ah super big kusa
next up i love this game i'm so glad
that i have more than 161 okay
um wait there's a chicken over there
oh if if chicken comes up i'm gonna eat
it so that
no one's taking anything let me let me
take one
i don't know
[\h__\h] yeah
he's heating up his bento i'm heating up
my bench so he can
he can buy something first
[Music]
yeah there was no way that no one's
gonna be the same again right
okay headbang hat bang headbang how do i
head bang
what what
[Applause]
yes of course anything you say
i love you marry me i uh oh let me throw
over my bra real quick
today is our date oh what is she
dressing okay she's a robot girlfriend
so this time we go to rubblecon
right it's a convention right
romans convention and robert
hi it's you guys
see you guys oh my god i was today
on twitter um i was uh asking
people like very spontaneously to draw
me in the style of this game for a
thumbnail
and the first reply i got was someone
sent me
this character as a picture
i was like why
but then afterwards i got a lot of good
uh a lot of good ones they hurt
everyone was so fast did you guys see
them
korean
i am not a chicken i am
not a chicken but yeah i got a bunch of
uh drawings thank you guys thank you
they're really cute i like this
simplistic style
top-notch thumbnail wouldn't you say
continuing
66. ooh we're getting closer to the nice
number
are you guys getting excited oh i should
probably
yep sit in the back
or sit uh there because no one's there
was that okay you got too much hair i
hate it when someone's
in front of me is taller in the movies
please write the robes in order
what red
what what
i don't know i don't know i went to the
to the damaged one
68.
what what was i supposed to do what am i
doing now ally
okay no no shoot no shooting shoots but
this one is no ally
[Music]
i was trying i was trying nice
hi hi hi hi wow amazing movie
who does that in motivator's club i've
had that happen maybe oh no sorry you
for you for you for you
i've had maybe it happened once or twice
in my whole life when i went to
futures that day
that they actually clapped it hadn't
happened once or twice
out of a million times hmm
they don't i was also with like with
with
airplane rides i've been like on
airplanes a million times
uh short uh distance and long distance
and i've had it like i personally think
it's kind of awkward when people start
clapping
unless really everyone claps but i had
it happen
um also that maybe twice in my life that
people clapped at the arrival of an
airplane
yeah that's why
but that that one i can remember one
specific time
where uh i was like really really young
and i think we were flying from
australia to like
um turkey or something like that
or even i'm not sure it's like ages ago
we had a lot of vacations
in european countries but it was super
hot
and the plane just didn't take off it
took them like hours
so we had like a huge delay and
no it was so hot in the plane it didn't
give us anything to drink so
everyone in the plane was dying so when
the plane actually finally took off and
finally arrived in that
country uh everyone was super excited
never everyone clapped because they were
like
woo-hoo we're still alive yay
yeah and then another time i don't know
what happened the other time
that's all next up
17-1 sarcastic club
what oh i closed it
so that he can focus on his test i guess
he was running a test
where is there why is there no food in
our pot we need to be patient something
will arrive soon
oh [\h__\h] no no
i was trying to i wanted to jump but i
pushed the wrong button
oh yeah oh [\h__\h] okay
i'm trying i'm trying i'm trying i'm
trying i'm trying
[Applause]
i was trying was that good enough please
tell me yes i've got a date tomorrow
tomorrow's exam could affect my whole
life tomorrow is a big day live at
budokan that's a lot of things going on
oh no
no no no no bye bye typhoon bye bye
swoosh
we don't need that a lot of people are
relying on that day it's always been my
dream to be saved by a handsome prince
what
uh oh you want to be saved well then
we're gonna go to the evil castle i
think
shrek style yes let's get yourself
captured
get yourself captured yo why not
oh very vaguely considerate
i wanna be considerate i wanna be
considerate
[Music]
okay
i wonder how taller tolerance the game
is
costume competition
we wanted him to to go over the bar
right
or ah maybe one maybe no
maybe not don't push me oh i'm pushing
you
ah it's such a hot bath oh my god he's
boiling totally i must be super super
super hot
this japanese game show have kind of bad
acting though
what what am i on the comedy show yeah
i can't do anything
oh wait
i love this game don't try this at home
yeah don't don't do this
whatever that is don't jump into
boiling water i guess
[Music]
i know i understand everything i am
a considerate verb young i am
next one we're going speed
20 left 81
[Music]
[Applause]
okay so ah
even though she's horrible [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
wait was that good or bad because
because she froze so good that i can
obviously not even hit it
are we doing that
maybe what what
triforce 83
okay nearly at the top doki doki doki
doki i like that they didn't translate
that one ah
when i was skiing with kelly going up
the thingy i actually lost
um one of my skiers while i was taking
photos on the ski lift
i was so embarrassed did i tell you guys
that i lost one of my skis
uh sleep maybe
i think i i think you did did i
sniff
yeah keep on sleeping i'm just sleeping
i'm dead i'm dead
was i acting as if i was dead
success i would say i think
what do you guys think textbook no no
don't look at him like
look at your book look at your book your
[\h__\h] hentai
no ow look at your book
i knew it from the start
this is such a good game don't need any
gaming skills for this game just need
you know social
skills which we all know i have
the mostest of even though i'm quite um
a shy person actually but social skills
i do have
although i'm not the type of person who
likes to go like
drinking and stuff and party and stuff
but like in like situations where we're
just chilling
or in a like
any kind of social situation yes i am
shy yes i am if callie would suddenly be
like
kiara kiss me kuso tully
kiss me i would be like
even though that was the thing i was
always hoping for i mean that's
something you could imagine right
me not not really i'm in such a
situation i suddenly
i'm like
that's just glasgow what is that glass
cannon
what does that mean i don't know what
that means
flirt i am flirts fluster me
ah all attack no defense ah
yeah yeah
86 let's go
oh seat belt uh we're gonna
yes come on quicker come on before
there's an accident
close your seatbelts
always close your seatbelts guys very
important
we don't want any accidents to happen
anyone know the answer
who am i um you guys can answer
what what ah i know
because he seemed like he knew the
answer for sure so
i want to discuss these situations this
is so interesting
is there a ufo why is there a ufo or
everyone's gonna look at the ufo
no no looking looking at the ufo
i wanna talk about these situations
it's so fast eh
ah i guess i'm gonna i'm gonna
i guess i'm gonna get abducted yeah you
guys just stay here
i'm gonna start new life as a alien
slave or
i don't know oh my god no yes hands up
okay put no hand down oh okay
okay cool yeah answer if you don't want
the world destroyed
yes he was human yes
don't want the earth destroyed
yes don't not want the earth not
destroyed
yeah what the [\h__\h] tomorrow today is
before yesterday
you lose weight no i guess not but
i can't even put my hand down right now
i don't know how to see it turn put it
down
you see here yes
your secret keeper no no no i want to
put my head down
let me put my hand down you have an
itchy spot
no no don't touch me
you hear you save realm yeah i guess so
[Music]
goodbye earth
no i don't want the earth to disappear
please
no i gotta save the world
i couldn't push anything
we're doomed no don't worry i'm gonna
save you guys i'm part that warrior and
phoenix takanawa i'm obviously going to
save you all
yeah yeah baby moments y'all be anime
moments be like night too long
help save me um
yeah i ran over to the situation right
in osaka yeah they stand on
um the right ah i think they stand
i think they stand on the right side and
in tokyo they stand
on the left like in everywhere in japan
they stand on the left one in tokyo
and osaka on the right or he's the other
way around feature of the band break up
vocals
okay i did the right thing i did the
right thing i did the right thing
[Applause]
[Music]
tonight we got an important answer for
you
so my grandma suddenly passed away i'm
not supposed to cheer right
we're gonna break up after today with
your emma
you passed away grandma
oh oh the band is going to break up oh
okay
oh
what's going on here ah aircon off okay
let me open this up
sorry uh well i mean
can't have everything
can't make everyone happy right that's
that's that's the lesson that we learned
from this
very wrinkly see i cannot pronounce the
word
wiggly vaguely vaguely
vaguely wiggly
this is like the other word that i say
kind of weird what was it
um
uh what was the other word what's that
other word guys
you know what i'm talking about visible
yeah visible
sometimes i say visible instead of
visible
wiggly visible today's
sun is weakly visible oh my god i sound
like that guy from
um from big bang theory
wiggly reasonable how do you say
squirrel i say squirrel
that's how would i say that wrong
wait oh that's actually also baby
speaker i guess
wrangling wiggle ball okay continue
before everyone leaves okay 96
is a scene what i didn't read uh
what i guess oh yeah cause um instead of
sitting right next to someone i guess
i'll take the
one of the middle spots here so that
he can continue sitting on his own
is he easy i'm bored guess i should go
attack a planet or something
heroes in she was in she was there let's
go there
[Applause]
destroy everything but oh no the hero
98 we're almost done guys
dead i'm dead i'm dead oh no you killed
me
you're so strong 99
no i want to play longer but hey it's
only been one hour but i've been
doing some small talk in between what's
going on uh it's been a while
oh but you came cooking your stuff but
you came
i really wanted to see you
[Music]
just hold my hand
raise back memories huh
[Music]
who sent me photo of that ghost what's
going on
maybe i'm not supposed to press the
button so that the
the credits can make it in time
because if i press the button the whole
time then
maybe not all credits will be able to
roll
i don't know
i don't know is that okay oh gosh this
is so lewd
the ultimate considerate move yeah oh
wait this is gonna be like super long
and i just
they're they're testing my patience like
how long am i going to look at the
present the credits i don't know i don't
know i don't know
anyway forget about me okay
just go find someone new
sorry can't stop crying what's going on
i'm sorry i couldn't be more considerate
was i not considerate enough
but i'm not strong enough
you always look out for other people
this reminds me of zelda music you're so
kind i really love that about you
okay is that a bad ending
even the times you didn't wait a second
i'll never forget it
there's no bad ending
i don't want to die
oh okay no stop don't
ah
[Music]
what
that's so smart that is so smart
i love it but i don't understand
i agree but i also don't understand wow
with us philosophical phoenix we are
very very considerate what was i doing
with that
with that text like
i don't know
that's okay now we should get our test
results
okay
okay your application is your best
quality postcard marker level what okay
we got there they're nation 62.
i think there's a lot of more detail uh
afterwards sympathy 68
ability to fit in 52 cents of duty 64 a
whole
uh i do have that yes quick thinking 58
yeah
pretty low i understand that application
17 that sounds good sounds good
okay cool wait that's
normally in japan you in japanese
language you got did they not want to
translate it
there was like way more detail
inconsiderate mode
oh there's a new option there's also
extras
chapter mode secrets let's look at
secrets
oh oh there's
what how do i how do i select something
or no i don't understand that should we
try inconsiderate or
quick or considerate
extras
[Music]
ah ah it's like a
endless one oh
let's try inconsiderate mode is it i
wonder if it's as long as the
considerate let's try give it a try this
is space where you can freely mess
around no one is going to hold your back
go ahead and mess around to your is it
going to be the same
problems though same situations
please because it's inconsiderate and
mess around there's no explanations of
just go nuts
if you wish to stop playing just press
press escape
okay number one
no i refuse
i do not want to fall no no
okay it's just the same things though um
all right we can do it for a while
can i take your order beer beer baby ah
i should have gone for beer there okay
but now you know what i'm not going for
beer
but okay now i understand because i
wasn't listening the first time
oh actually no i'm gonna go for the rice
set because then i'll choose drinks and
i'm gonna
go go for something to eat
number three how
ah okay shoot the ally shoot him
[\h__\h] no okay
still inconsiderate enough good enough
right
we want to be we just don't want to do
the right thing
now i'm waiting i'm gonna wait here and
you know what i'm just gonna
think about maybe i should choose
something from the front
options here no no
no she went there anyway
oh i'm not gonna pose no no i don't
wanna be part of this
no you guys suck i don't wanna
you guys know what that means it's like
in in
japanese comedy and bouquet is the one
who acts like stupid or like who who who
gets
um who's like
um but the fool yeah
yeah yeah yeah i'm
i'm good at that kind of stuff trust me
number six
big bro i'm so hungry big brother do
something
okay so i still understand this one
ghost like competition
okay so you
big bro ah cuz he drew one two three
four lines
and i should draw less or did he draw
two lines
anyway i guess we're going to draw more
lines than him
wait i don't know
why is it supposed to not draw at all
now to be
to be considerate okay i'm going to take
another one of those i'm not going to
jump
if i'm bigger and i'm going to stomp on
you
make you into a pancake
and then eat you
you cannot control me i'm an independent
double
i will not let you control me is it just
a cold in here got it no brown okay
let's turn it down
all the way down
[Music]
can't go lower unfortunately
unfortunately
nobody people people people oh no
this arm is not for you no
[Music]
hey no i'm for you today
i'm gonna live with what you have
moderately boogie
am i better at being inconsiderate on
purpose than i am and being considered
but now i know the problems i know where
the situation is now
so i know a bit better what was what i
was supposed to do
down to my last ball this is my last
chance
oh yeah okay yeah so this uh yep
i understand completely i am the pokemon
and i'm a free pokemon
no one can take away my freedom oh let
me look on your screen wow
sorry actually i don't like that no even
in the game
[Music]
you guys wanna you guys looking forward
to 3d kiara when
uh i'll show you what's under my skirt
because that's probably um yeah you
can't probably cannot hide it
the moment i the moment i
bow even a little bit or move even a
little bit
i think we will see it all
my first aid kit wait did i
oh [\h__\h] i woke up i didn't i'm being
considerate again you know i'm just
being too
i just mean being natural
naturally considerate truly my legal kid
all right didn't i say i have a first
aid kit under my skirt did i say that
before i feel like
okay no no
no
i don't need a girlfriend anyway today's
our day
let's go to roblox robots robots robots
robot m robot
i'm robert and robert
and sorry
did you guys surprise y'all oh i'm gonna
actually stay right here
i'm gonna stay right here no i don't
care if you're dating
don't look like i give a [\h__\h] i don't
bye-bye you can stand
if you want to be together that much
standing is healthier
maybe i don't know la la la
maybe disturb him can i disturb him
hello
we're doing the opposite right now guys
oh i don't even know what was the right
thing to do but i think back then i did
the right thing
did i should we do this up to 50
i don't want to do all the the same
things all over again so this up to 50
maybe
and then uh uh we finished the first
cookie i mean
look at him look at him oh my god you're
bald
beautiful though beautiful shiny very
shiny i like shiny things
mine nothing for you dude
don't give drinks to cowboys here no
you already have a hat i should no i was
being considerate
i was supposed to be not confederate oh
i'll hit a home run for you
this is so sad
i'm sorry i'm sorry
thank you for the membership welcome man
today what
oh yeah let me sit right here
you like sitting next to me don't you
don't you felt lonely didn't you
very very how come okay i was being
too considerate one time okay next round
we're gonna do perfect one we're gonna
do a perfectly
inconsiderate round trust me 26.
oh yeah let me in can i join
can i join
well get yourself a freaking room
unbelievable today is our date
how about we cook you make you into
yakimikou
[Music]
[Applause]
oh wait is this also an option
no no
i want to be different i'm different
it's not a face mom i'm an
edgy teenager
let me choose one of the okay this is
what i wanted to talk about in school
when like the teacher like obviously
chooses me
when i obviously don't know the answer i
feel like they're doing it on purpose
like they could have chosen someone
who's smart would they choose me to
answer
even though like why
okay let's give her some hot soup
there you go you like it won't you
but actually apparently like even in hot
weather you're like supposed to drink
like hot water
why is this not perfectly broken because
your
body adjusts to it better or something
like that right
right well like i don't even know people
tell me that
like not okay not hot weather red like
warm water
um because i don't know it adjusts you
to like
i don't know but i don't do it anyway
because even though people tell me that
that's good
i still want to drink something cold
because that's that's what makes me feel
like i'm cooling down right
um anyway let's get up to fifty
thirty one thirty one funny one
oh man i gotta get off at the next stop
doki doki doki talking my hat goes doki
doki
okay so this time um i'm just gonna walk
right away
because i know that the right thing to
do was pressing pushing the button
but this time i wouldn't do that why is
there no foot in our park we need some
sleeping patients something will arrive
okay now i just don't
don't jump at all
even though i hate mushrooms actually i
really didn't like that that didn't
taste good
out of five i'm too good for you guys um
i'm not i'm not i'm i'm a phoenix i'm
not part of you normal burps
yep yes we're looking at that guys
but guys that's slow we're looking at
i'm so sorry this is so
so wrong guys please don't do that okay
please don't do that please don't do
that
please be considerate no wait stop no i
can't don't do it
[\h__\h] yeah i want to be inconsiderate
freak in some way or another
bouquet
[Music]
stop being considerate i'm trying no
that was not my death that was my chair
okay why do you suck at being rude i
don't know just too nice
i can't believe i'm actually going to
meet aaron ah this is what it was about
ah and then i still i still know what's
the right thing to do though
okay so yeah i guess it's still the
right thing to go to bb because she
would be sad
that no one wants to meet bb so i'm
going to aaa
okay
wow you're stuck just kidding
that that sounded okay but still i'm not
gonna clap
no i'm not feeling it no you gotta try
harder
osaka you're the best you're in freaking
tokyo down
this is tokyo we're gonna break up oh
yeah
yeah see ya later
we didn't care about you anyway
let's freaking go they're breaking up
i refuse to move at all
okay now let's try to go right against
them
e i'm slower though i don't move as fast
as they do
okay so do we get ourselves eaten
no no wake up wake up whoa
yeah let's fight it's cuddle let's
cuddle
let's cover 40
and for the celebrity first miss miss bb
so what was the right thing to do here
[Laughter]
what's the right thing to do in this
situation and what's the wrong thing to
do in this situation
[Music]
think you're supposed to hit it if i
want to be considerate
you're supposed to hit it
hmm see i don't understand baseball to
begin with so
if this is baseball wave
what a question i take the question back
i take the question back
like if if the the person who throws the
ball
um froze so fast
that the person who wants to hit it
doesn't even get to hit it doesn't that
mean that the person who threw the ball
is so good that
like so fast it froze so well that you
can't even hit it
or do they want it to be hit yes yes
okay
there we go
so if i'm the thriller the best thing
that would happen is that
the the hitter will never hit it
cool continuing
i guess i'm gonna start a career in
baseball now because now i understand
the game completely
today is premium friday okay okay so now
we're staying
because now i understand that i should
have left because i'm the but i thought
i was the subwoofer
what was i supposed to do i didn't know
it was first but i
i should have known because i am the
boss always
they're looking at me i'm so sorry guys
typical kfb day oh no she started super
chat reading it's been already four five
six hours how long is she gonna go i
wanna go home and sleep
no i withstand your power
you've got nothing on me
sorry i'm having fun
oh yeah
look how cool i look with my pigtails
but we love your readings thank you i
know you do
i'm just no no
no no
you fall look at the ufo
what is all you fool doing there
what see you for doing
swoosh uh
i guess i'm gonna walk right into uh no
no no yeah you get adopted i'm not doing
that again
no way no way that was
traumatizing i'm not i don't want to get
adopted again
duct tape boogie
is that the perfect score yeah
well we did well my friends adopted up
duct tape
am i still gonna be abducted anyway in
the next one
no one but no
okay i'm not no no i'm not gonna answer
um okay i'm just gonna raise my hand
when they ask if i want the world to be
destroyed
if you i said don't want to you is human
maybe i'm phoenix though don't want the
earth destroyed
don't not want to i don't know what that
means
tomorrow today's day before yesterday is
three days ago
what
[Music]
i don't know you see here
no i mean yes
no i can't unraise my hand though
interestingly enough
you're here or say maybe i should have
kept it down the whole time
okay bye-bye earth anyway it was nice
being on the earth i'm gonna go to mars
next
it says you get to go attack a planet or
something okay let's destroy this world
it's it's a horrible place anyway
i'm living in the virtual world from now
on
where i've always lived there thank you
oh wait the people
um members are uh hatching
congratulations first in line
but i still don't understand this one
what's
what's i'm just gonna not go anywhere
i don't understand
take red what
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i hated that one that one made me so mad
okay we're at 51 let's do the full one
after all
oh oh it's only until 15. oh okay
incredible mod only goes to 50 okay
your quick thinking is your best quality
backstage juggle level
oh so this should be as low as possible
right
determination sympathy ability to fit in
sense of duty quick thinking application
my quick thinking was too good or is
this the
other way around like should this be
high anyway because
no way i think it yeah it's supposed to
be low as low as possible
okay
i think in the japanese game they gave
you like a more
detailed explanation
of why you're considerate and all that
or maybe maybe ah
ah no no that's all they show me
okay okay let's do number two next week
shall we i wonder how this one works
though consider it together
is it still the same problem the
situation it can't be
i wonder i want to check it out at some
point
maybe um also is this
okay one last check is this is the same
ones
as we already did
okay cool uncle
i wonder how long the the the the one is
though with the two people
all right it's the same one okay never
mind uh yes
okay yeah yeah am i low on fps again
yeah it's probably because it's prime
time here even even though i got my
my land cable going on um sorry about
that
but um anyway that's that for today
we're going to reach uh some super chats
quick
and conan
next week and then cookie will be free
the week after
hell yeah kill you this is so much fun
i hope you guys like the game um you can
get the english version on steam
um you can also get the game on switch
link in my description for steam at
least
it's called uh consider it in english
but you can also find it if you just
type out kooky yummy
in romaji by the way this is not
sponsored but i just think this game is
great
and then find out yourself how
considerate you are but maybe
maybe now you already know the
situations from considerate one
maybe by consider it too and consider it
free where you don't know the problems
yet
and then try to clear those ones and
then watch my stream
afterwards hmm yeah thank you guys for
watching
uh i was uh happy to have all of you
here we're gonna take
uh a two minute break for um
uh before we read the super chats
because i got a little loading screen
for the super chats
that i want to show off to you and then
i'll be back
in a second
thank you guys super chats in
two minutes
[Music]
do
i oh my god help
this is always so scuffed here
[Music]
you have seen nothing do you want to
continue
seeing things well then you better act
as if you haven't seen anything
[Laughter]
welcome back guys we're not going to
watch along we watched a movie together
with the members yesterday
that was fun we watched the hobbit
second movie
however let me change the title and
comment
chat
super chat
and pretend you didn't see it exactly be
considerate guys
did you like it uh
the intermission did you like it
uh james two made it james chu has done
like a lot of uh
funny and cute uh animations fan made
and he made this one a while ago and i
thought it was just absolutely perfect
so uh i finally started using it like
normally i don't really necessarily feel
like i need a break
in between but i just want to show this
off now so i guess why not
i guess why not
it's so cute it is so cute
so guys did you see that the kooky
opening game properly
for the for the first time today through
my stream
which i think a lot of you did which is
awesome
yes it was really good isn't it it's so
funny isn't it
i love this style and i think like
generally
like a lot of these things are
like people in japan really follow these
things and i feel like you would expect
people to follow
through with it in other countries as
well
but people give less shits about it in
other countries i wish they would give
more shades about it and would be more
considerate
but i think most of it was
understandable
right like i would be like yeah yeah
that makes sense to me even if
even if we don't really are that
considerate in my country
that makes sense to me i think that's
what a lot of you guys could
relate to you would love the us
why are you saying that because they're
not
not following any of these uh
kooky yummy things
uh wait are you guys hearing a btm
probably not right
let me play this one sorry i was a bit
too loud baby
okay let's read some super chats um
we have to read the ones from the
movie watch along yesterday and then we
start reading the ones from
this stream okay so first we'll read the
ones from the movie once long shouldn't
be in that minute
yes okay starting
[Music]
thank you you guys are so so sweet
busy i'm too loud oh okay but you heard
what i was saying right i don't have to
say it again
sorry for being so inconsiderate and
having the music too loud
i'm so sorry yes you heard it okay
thank you well well as i said thank you
thank you the love and
i'm uh after playing this game i'm
feeling a bit better
uh and actually yeah because of the
because of the apartment i'm feeling a
bit excited
yay use the other bdm please you mean my
other
track that i always use or you mean the
new one anyway i'm using this one now
i'm using this one deal with it
yeah um yeah i don't know i think i'm
gonna keep all these topics for tomorrow
because we're gonna have a lot of time
to talk
tomorrow and so not so much small talk
today
i have a lot of things to talk about
you next time you will accept a poem
words are double-edged sword but will
our sweet words protect you
when loving you is what we swore to
stand by you even when you are blue
to break your shackles so you can fly
and to keep that fire in your heart
alive oh my god
i may have only known you for a screen
but all i see is a person with a
beautiful soul and a gentle heart your
genuine personality
is i think ah that's um before that
that's where the poem ended i think
your genuine personality is what proved
me to you and i will do my very best to
show how much i love and support you
kiana
thank you guys thank you you may notice
that sweet
i mean i
i guess some people say that
one could be overprotective
and like like too nice like like kind of
white nighting white knighting style and
that might be bad but
i don't know personally i'm glad that
you guys are so sweet
and so so kind to me and
especially in situations like
the past few days that's exactly what i
need so thank you all
thank you christophe
brandon wilson duncan turkish duncan
no no it's disappearing
[Music]
men be right hello kiana i was just
watching the vlog of the minecraft
stream and i think you are focusing a
bit too much on opinions of people that
doesn't matter it's impossible to be
liked by everyone
that's why each person has a different
orsi pay attention to your core audience
i'm sure they love your cats
appearing on stream and don't mind you
saying
i don't well i mean um
i think one thing one thing that i
didn't get across
at all was it was it was more than just
the baby and the thing
it was way more than that that bothered
me
but i don't want to get too much into
detail because
it's just um
not gonna be helpful to discuss it
like i would love to discuss it with
only people who have
who want something good for me but
you know you know it's
it's never like a safe space
[Music]
um unfortunately even in my super chat's
reading and even in the members
stream it's never a safe space
yeah typhon duncan d804 dan kishan
and the outfit shadow duncan decibel
foundation
and the drinking game
do you guys are you guys over are the
members over there
uh hangover are you still hungover
i've never had a hangover in my whole
life guys i actually never
have been drunk in my whole vibe
i tried some alcohol but i don't drink
and i've never like gotten drunk
i probably never will be like there was
one time where i tried
to drink drink with my friend
um to like get myself drunk
just to have the experience once but i
don't think we actually got myself drunk
i gave up too early because it just
didn't taste good
[Music]
he did
yeah i don't think that's okay i don't
know i mean i mean i mean i think
probably once in my life i should at
least know how it feels
hmm is it gonna be worth it though
like obviously it's not gonna feel good
it's obviously not gonna feel that good
but
but still i feel like that's like one
thing i should experience at least once
um at some point maybe
but i would i just like the stuff that
gets you drunk
it's just nothing tastes good to me i
would have to drink like
a cocktail with like like
almost no alcohol in it like for real
like
where you guys when when other people
are like hey
can i try this cocktail there's like
barely any alcohol in it you won't taste
it and i drink it and i taste
it a lot so it would have to be
even even even less than when other
people say this is this doesn't taste
like alcohol
it has to be much less than that because
my
my like um
my standards things that i'm used to
it's just not it's not like that it's
not the same
but if it's that low then i'm never
gonna get drunk from it
anyway continuing
looking for the top and thank of 67
thank you in color
patrick
hello how are you once again since i
start work soon i will watch on the
archive
okay cool thank you thank you i wish you
my theory a being goddess and my fellow
cave be
a fun view and can i just say how cute
you are today
you lie and don't continue to be my oc
have a fun time everyone
thank you dusty
thank you i'm glad to be someone's
aussie thank you
and by the way uh do you guys want me to
play cookie on me too and free as soon
as possible or should we have
like maybe one month in between like
more time should we have more time in
between or should we play it
like super soon
yeah soon yes yes weekly
more time a week is enough
[Music]
soon is better weekly sunscreen okay
okay i think i'll do it then forever
sooner than later
is the third one translated i
don't know let me see
oh i think it isn't
i think it might not be translated yet
actually yeah because if i look on steam
it shows me only the
like if i type it in in english it only
shows me the first and the second one
oh oh how long is it going to take them
to translate
the game i wonder although but still i
mean
it's not the language isn't even that
important we could play it anyway
yeah we could probably play it anyway
and i could try but
i could try to translate but the
situations are passing and the text is
passing so quickly so i probably
wouldn't have the time to translate
uh but as i said yeah it probably
would be fine to just
play it anyway or
or wait
just just wait until the third one gets
translated
okay then let's play the second one next
week and then for the third one we just
wait
we don't have to play everything right
away we can keep it for another time
[Music]
just go time to turn just
got time to turn on my pc and join the
stream it's nice that i didn't miss too
much
a great sunday starts finally yay thank
you
thank you for watching the movie
together with me felix
thank you shane hope you enjoyed it
was it your first time i wonder hey
i think most people already knew the
movie
[Music]
thank you hope you enjoyed it mr casper
visible thank you soon for next
by the way guys this time frame
time slot for my stream
seems to have worked out for a lot of
you
interestingly enough a lot of people
showed up today so
maybe it's okay if i use this time slot
more often
because even a lot of the the asian
country people showed up too like even
though
it was pretty early in the morning i
suppose but
they woke up anyway yeah it's prime time
in
europe so who here is actually from
europe watching from europe right now
you guys all are you guys mostly from
europe
raise your hands if you're from europe
[Music]
me me me me me me
that's quite a lot i wonder if that's
the
um mere height
uh what's the freaking for that
[Music]
okay um but as you can see right now
uh i have a little bit of internet
problems that's that's one thing why i
was still not uh
i was still trying to not
go stream in primetime
because internet
uh but depending on the game i think
it's okay
like minecraft maybe not during prime
time
because minecraft still needs like a
little bit of good internet speed
but one thing i can tell you guys um
the new apartment that i chose
it has high speed high speed high speed
super good internet
because it's uh um like
they built it in there a new new
internet
thingy um and i checked with my internet
provider guy
and he told me uh that the same
um the same
if i would use the same tariff
just the same contract
that i have right now
over there it would already be much
better
but i will still get a little upgrade
and the thing is before
um i wasn't sure if i'm gonna keep the
same provider so i didn't want to
upgrade anything
and because that would extend my
contract but now that i know that i will
stay with the same provider
i think because we still have uh one
month left until i move
i'm gonna no it's not the three hundred
dollars no no
like the same one i have a like normal
price internet right now but really low
speed
but with the same contract
in the new apartment i'm gonna get
better speed for that
i didn't sign the lease yet though but
yeah anyway so
i'm still i'm still gonna get like a
small upgrade because you know
how he told me that i can get five a bit
more for ten dollars yeah
i'm probably gonna get like two or three
of those
and and yeah then we should have decent
internet
yeah how much is the speed how much was
it again i didn't do it
let me do a speed test
let me do a prime time speed test while
i'm streaming okay let's go let's see
good question let's see my internet is
really bad right now
but i'm not i'm happy that it's at least
good enough to
to stream okay download is like
33 mbps
that works that works
it's not good but it works
okay upload wow better than 9500 wow
five mbps four at four point
four point four four point three
four point
4.34 mbps
is what i get now but as i said
with the same contract with the same
provider if i just move location
i'm gonna get something better from that
probably just like free and i mean he
didn't tell me
how much but i i suppose it's probably
just gonna get up to eight or something
so i add a few more embeds to that
upgrade in a little bit and then we
should be good to go
i'm not going to go for the 300 option
but i'm going to upgrade it a little bit
my phone internet is 10 times faster
than that
wait flags but okay
[Music]
when you turn one book of like 300 pages
into free movies and there was so much
filler
damn mysteries thank you p1234
67 67
905 thank 905 uh general pickling that's
indeed
67 packages you may have told us in the
past but if you
did i don't recall ah i think i already
answered this
during the stream how did you get into
the lord of the rings movies in the past
you mentioned a roommate that was able
to quote them but was she the reason or
were you a fan before that
what keeps them your favorite yeah i've
known it since much much much much much
longer before that um because of my mama
i guess or because of my family
because all of my family kind of likes
that stuff
like fantasy stuff and and and
gaming especially like rpg games
mmypgs we used to play mmorpgs together
and then yeah we also liked lord of the
rings and that kind of stuff
so we my mom introduced me to the movie
i think
she really liked it she's a big fan
yeah whatever yeah we played world of
warcraft together
my mom loved and usually always play
actually no maybe not i think she played
both world and alliance
yeah but my sister and my brother always
played horde
and i was alliance until
the blood elves showed up then i was
like okay i'm gonna give the horde a try
because
blood elves are hot as [\h__\h]
anyway yeah i'm continuing patrick
chandagashin p1234md
ferris gt thank you and deal of 67
where are you where did it go
doomsday
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
hi guys wait let me give you a kiss
that was not for you that was for a fly
that keeps on following me
it was nice and having to watch along
with you and kfb but gotta head out for
work can we say hi
and give chocolates and smoothie a
cuddle for me
hope you had a wonderful time with your
phoenix family thank you we did we did
we did it it was nice
i got good food too thank you
for watching the movie together with me
even though it seems like
no i think you stayed until the end yeah
i was that was nice at least i didn't
fall asleep this time
i mean i didn't last time either but it
was i was close too
thank you
thank you for the and love the once
along
been a while since i saw this movie so
it's been a blast yeah it's always nice
to revisit some old legendary movies
that you've
loved before even if you guys all claim
that you don't love the hobbit
come on youtunda
it might not be as good as lord of the
rings but it's still great
to a certain extent bradley ninety-seven
misfits on christian
thank you for the pinky yeah thanks for
watching kiera you were extra adorable
today as always
thank you sweet
[Music]
another fun movie watch thank you again
boss you're going to play a co-op game
about dwarves
called deep rock galactic with my
friends drunk now
do you think we will ever see a collab
with you and resident whole life dragon
someday
ah or with phoenix mama ah
uh both yeah someday
possibly
uh i'm pretty sure yeah
thank you
hope the game session went well with
your friends
were you the only drunk one i wonder
how thank you soon hi rooney thank you
trevor g donkey rest for which one thank
you thanks for another wonderful
watching
mama
yes yes it is it just i went to sleep
eventually thank you thank you felix
i hope you got some nice and well
deserved sleep as well thank you for
your support
someone else is
and that's it for the members only super
chats
now we continue with the ones from this
particular stream
perfect looking for the top
lex casper defending
breaking character i'm sorry that
casper's goodbye made you sad kiara
maybe someone else will continue but i
didn't think it was right to keep going
when i started to skate since there was
not much you could do
my reason was that i hoped it would turn
into a source
of it would turn a source of your fear
into something that's more light-hearted
hoping it might reduce your stress
oh i don't think it's no it definitely
worked what the [\h__\h]
i because of you i had like
this feeling of of love
towards casper now
but i hope you enjoyed ghost casper at
least now you're with your babies and
casper is gone and no longer concerned i
so i once wanted to give closure to you
to the kfp girls no
i don't want closure because it might be
gone but i'll always be
around and support you just in a
different name and form
but then who are you give me closure
tell me who you are
casper says goodbye but see you in the
next stream
no
it's the final
[Music]
countdown
ah sad
sad come
[Music]
you thank you for all the cute little
super chats
they all shared me up every time was my
highlight oh it was my freaking
highlight thank you so much i was always
like whenever i saw your name i was like
oh my god guys
i loved it thank you
maybe maybe maybe maybe you start a new
character
you're funny you can do it thank you
thank you soon bye bye
i hate this
white moon wait when i never see
you guys we're super chatty
do i have to get myself a mouse so that
you won't come again
i will do it i will do it for you
um
have been causing weird behaviors in the
occupants
many have taken to become miss phoenix
we'll update oh okay they're really
going at each other
now thankfully i have the bear with me
this time and it will be
fine nakamura the second where did you
go
phoenix so that's keyblade let's follow
us up with
uh here too well they're just covering
each other and dipping sauces and
knowing so it should be fine maybe
might want to reconsider white piano
what's going on in the usual room
we come in phoenix we come as phoenix
become his phoenix
i can see that i can see how you guys
would
change that that makes sense to me
that's so fitting that makes sense
[Music]
back to sleep yes of course please to
watch the archive this is
a shorter stream anyway so it's all good
i don't know if you're still here but
please guys um i
even though i appreciate it very much if
you get up early for me to be there
live as long as you watch your archive
it's all good you can
sleep as much as you want or
work or whatever whatever you need to do
get it done
and then watch
hmm you don't have to be there always
sorry keira stop for the stream no
problem i'm done with the
super chats soon anyway and then you can
watch the archive thank
you soon
wait did they give you a kiss
crunchy three four nine tango some magic
tanks increased
brandon wilson and i got a book on
japanese
etiquette when i first thought about
going to japan so i'm wondering how well
it will help me if i played this
oh did you did you actually read the
book noise
people read books huh um
key archive wow that's so smart thank
you for the membership welcome
um i think but like a lot of these
things
are yeah just being considerate you
don't really
need to know much about japanese culture
for most of them
just try to be as considerate as you
could ever
be but the quick thinking might be an
issue if you're not really used to
these situations like i have had these
situations before
some of them like for example the the
one in the
in in the train where a couple comes up
and i would scooch over to make space
for them so that they don't have to sit
with me in between
so yeah although i think that's
something that would
happen in other countries as well
obviously
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow that typo
cabbage flashbacks do you remember the
cabbage
that usually doesn't happen trains in
japan are usually super clean
super clean and no no garbage
lying around so the cabbage was really
magical to me
it was like this must be a sign
am i does does the cabbage want me to
become vegetarian
or or should i take the cabbage and turn
it into a
into a like a carriage and become
cinderella
and ride in the carriage in the cabbage
carriage
and cabbage do i become
cabbage become as cabbage
become as cabbage become eggs i love
cabbage
i love cabbage
don't you wish your cabbage was hot like
me
don't you wish your cabbage was a freak
like me
what sorry i don't know where that came
from
ramsay dances down question skype here
is duncan
thank you thank you for the pinky i'm
glad i get to catch you when i'm not at
work
uh i'm just getting to see you live but
i still supporting the door you can do
thank you i'll try to stream more often
during this time
seems like a good time but you know you
know often streams during this time
and i honestly don't want to um collide
with her
so when i was making my schedule i
i purposefully put my own strings
at this time only when she wasn't
streaming
how how considerate am i towards the
viewers and towards ina
that is actually me being considered
yeah
um well yeah it will be
impossible to always do that because
inna like
always always streams at a time i don't
think she ever streams during a
different time
yeah it's impossible but i'll try to
oh get a good balance
a bit too considerate nah i'm i'm
personally fine with it i prefer doing
it this way
uh anyway continuing uh where was i oh
there
oh neither toaster three eight five
[Music]
why
thank you for the membership welcome er
oh there's a russian name i cannot read
it's a letter that looks like an
e a letter that looks like a b a letter
that looks like a p
a little letter that looks like an e and
a letter that's uh turned around
n with a scooby-doo on top
what are you someone who knows how to
read that tell me how to read that
i don't want to copy it's like every pen
pen every every f array
how do i pronounce that
sorry i wasn't listening it's like a
small e
it looks like a small e looks like a
capital b looks like a small p
looks like a small e looks like a
capital n turned around
everyone everyone cool okay
thank you soon there we go i didn't even
have to open google
every
[Music]
during the intervention i checked my
twitter
[Music]
i checked my twitter about that japanese
game
what was the name again now i forgot
again but i already checked on twitter
and i think i understand
how it generally works
generally
i think i understand
boy but i'll have to look at it a little
more closer
and but yeah now now that the people
showed me on twitter
i think like i've seen that game being
played before
just not as much in my
tour mario country tournament she used
that system
for deciding who like for
for showing who continues to the next
round
uh oh
i wish i could wear two hats like kiara
what stops you from that
follow your dreams with two hats we're
three hats we're four heads we're five
beds we're 100 hats
i will support you in your endeavors do
it
just do it
i love hats
gravity and hat shape you can attach
them with like
um what clips inside or
with uh um the the bobby pins and stuff
there's so many ways
yeah try
fist of the first ben thank you
are the most colorful and energetic
member of ian i know you had a rough
time last week and i wanted to let you
know
whatever you feel you should change or
not you are a mama and we love you
thank you
you thank you
i love you too that means a lot to me
thank you
motion thank you so much
there have been rumors that kfp is a
black company [\h__\h]
that makes employees stay for unpaid
overtime but
on the basis accusations we totally
don't already know about
everyone is free to go
whenever they want
and everyone is aware of that
so that's my thoughts
[Music]
and lord oblivion okay composite
thank you thank you love 67
pickled cucumber metro senpai
uh white muda duncan
thank you and hi kat
i heard you were feeling a little down
lately so i just want to say i love you
what you do
and don't let anyone shame you for
having fun thank you
thank you thank you
doll star thank you friends for our
kittens 67
thank you for the red super chat wow
can you say the longest non-technical
english words
[Music]
libidification or is it flocking
clutchy
[Music]
vacation
thank you so much for all the support
potential sorry
for being late for your stream today i
just got home and just opened my pc
hopefully i didn't miss too much and
i'll probably go over this again before
sleep yes of course just watch the
archive no worries as i said
a moment ago please don't don't stress
yourself just watch the archive
take your time watch it in bed before
going to sleep or whatever
and just relax chill there's no stress
no time limit
thank you for trying though thank you i
appreciate
it very much having a live audience here
is nice it's fun it's more fun to have
you guys here
um j m
s y t b e thank you
thank you story
[Music]
thank you for the pinky what i've seen
so far has been top tier comedienne
content
thank you and funny
and very funny i know thank you very
much
well i think really the game was
hilarious so i'm looking forward to
playing more
glad you enjoyed it thank you so much
bob business thank you soon slide on
kitchen just in the reinhardt function
looking for the top function
a cafe chicken hamburger old and cute do
you take chicken mom to the fryer
oh you're giving me you're giving me a
little kooky yummy moment okay wait i
didn't read the thing that's in the in
the
in the things so there's a
one grown-up chicken emote and then
three
baby chicks emotes and the baby chicks
say pvp
and it says i can't wait to spend
mother's day with mom
but that's difficult like if i have to
take someone
if i take it with your mom then they
won't have a mom to spend mother's day
with but if i take away your child then
what the [\h__\h] that's
messed up there's a carefree chicken
hamburger order and cute
do you take chicken mom to the fryer
oh no it does it only the question is
just do i take the chicken mom
doesn't ask me which chicken do i take
okay so i say no
of course because we don't fried chicken
at all it can be
in german that's called a fung fragi
what's that called in english a fung
fragi
a trick question hmm
i guess so
a rhetorical question maybe
something like that um mary do danger
and that be shrimp thank you
dead beach rim super jets with hatchet
moji
okay so i think you're being ky on
purpose
monkey uh
aokia is so considered that she had to
try so hard to be not considerate this
was extremely fun to watch looking
forward to part two thank you
me too me too is your blade dankeshen
romanian dead lift sankashan
in consideration's best danger thank you
hi
[Music]
nice short sweet and anna america
friendly timing oh very good
very well i shall continue streaming
at this time then we don't have many
streams at this time this week but maybe
next week
daisy thank you thank you for the red
super chat wow
no matter what the game says you're the
perfect bokeh and cali is the perfect
tsukumi
yeah but i feel like we're both both
things
kelly can be very bulky
very bulky she's like constant booking
especially with without me like to her
own viewers
i feel like like when she plays
minecraft
she's very booking she's often booked
she's both
cali is extremely broken kel's is switch
confirmed
yes
[Laughter]
thank you daisy static snake thank you
that rabbit and moon broke your heart
take the first shot and blow up
usakian headquarters
it would be hilarious if you start the
great piccolo do it
well that sounds something like um
something that a comedy hen would do but
i'll get in trouble if i do that so i
will not do it
[Music]
upon
oh my god there's a chalker is on my
floor
[Music]
it's so cute
so fluffy
it's so funny
[Music]
how loud he coming
baby
[Music]
still same guy hello cute under here
she's thinking
thank you
so she wants love right now points my
pedals
she's showing me her fluffy belly
it's like help me help me [\h__\h]
[Music]
i love you
she's so cute why are you so cute what
the hell is wrong with you
stop being so cute
she is so cute
she's such an angel such a weirdo though
she always like plays tag like whenever
like
like she comes up to me and she's like
meow meow meow meow
and then i then i want to like go and
pet her but then she starts running away
from me like really
fastly so she goes
and then sometimes she runs um
right into the into the bathroom and
there's like a
like i told you guys this before but she
runs really fast into the bathroom
and then froze herself oh my gosh she
did it again
throws herself uh onto the the bath
towel that's like on the
on the ground in the bathroom
she flops she just flops over
she runs when twins runs runs runs and
then flops over on the bathroom towel so
cute she flops over a lot though but and
she runs away a lot she always runs away
and wants me to follow her but then when
i follow her and reach her
she runs away again like this it's like
an endless tag session
she's like mama come get me ha ha
they just want me to love them
but she also wants to run away and play
hello
you think he's super cute right now yeah
okay i gotta get her one second
[Music]
baby
i caught her i got you
to run all the way over to the living
room
[Music]
oh
oh the muffled wolf was real
happy happy cat mom
[Music]
okay where was i out here
tomorrow where you can't send super
chats thank you taji for
sending it anyway in this stream thank
you
thank you
countless night dancers thank you for
the pinky
awesome new super chat loading screen
breaking up super chat since k-dog
ignores my two donation requests you
don't want any shoes for yourself
i give them to me you anyway
you can't stop me
is that sexual harassment
[Music]
i'm too strong i've got the power and
you can't stop me
uh sebastian lopez thank you
hello again i just want to tell you how
much i like your content with your humor
personality and bottom leftness
watching you is the full experience of
joining loves and never-ending memes
thank you so much and love you
thank you thank you that's so sweet
thank you thank you means a lot to me
guys
really thank you soon
you guys are so sweet trevor g duncan
mhm thank you for the thank you amazing
and let me refresh you
okay you're the sweet one thank you
thank you guys
where was i
oh thank you murasaki
thank you thank you
remember you wanted to write down topics
for tomorrow i just did
i got a few ones sorry i just
uh cracked my
leg
why did i stop oh
[Music]
thank you for the pinky my name is yoshi
kiara
i'm 999 plus years old why it's over 9
000 my hut is in the north face section
of chicken land where the coops are
and i want to get married i'm an
employee of the kiana fried phoenix and
i get home every day by 8 pm at the
latest
okay thank you interesting story
tell me more please i'm intrigued
suvitoni duncan
if i get spontaneously rich one day will
you attend my floating warship
brave party no
no
try googling and looking into it if you
don't know what it
is i have the same issue with alcohol
tasting horrible
no matter how light or mixed it is and
eventually discovered that was the
reason
super that sounds weird super tasty
hmm super tasty appears personal
experiences
this tends the sense of taste with far
greater intensity than
average with some studies showing that
showing an increased sensitivity to
bitter tastes
it may be a cause of selective eating
but i only really experience it with
alcohol to be honest
i don't think so but
um
[Music]
what
interesting stuff
[Music]
what yeah i just don't like it
i probably could like if i would force
myself to socially drink
i would probably get used to drinking
and to alcohol and then i would probably
end up being fine with it but i don't
even want myself to get to that point
i don't even want to be tolerable of
alcohol i think i'm
fine this way it's actually quite useful
because i don't at least i don't spend a
[\h__\h] ton of money on alcohol
sixth true magician danke sharon
raspberry alice danke soon
cody duncan
[Music]
you should ask where we are from on one
of those youtube messages
what reading from argentina
you should ask where we are from on one
of those youtube messages
wait you want me to ask the chat
is that what you want
uh sometimes i do
community poll but i would only be able
to get four options
how would i do i want to do a community
poll about that
[Music]
uh north south east west
oh oh oopsie
i cracked i i cracked
help
oh thank you thank you for the pinky oh
wait that ah sorry that probably isn't
even a pinky
[Music]
you here is it
i don't think it is i'll read it anyway
i'll read it anyway because this looks
funny oh
my cats are playing with a paper bag
that i used for groceries
it's like you can't entertain cats so
easily it's
ridiculous i love it okay the mother of
chickens
oh the you are the unforgiven unholy and
wicked place
there's always news there we all thrive
to become as you
as pinks be the flame kiara be the
lights that show us
the way i'm already doing it i'm already
on it don't worry become miss phoenix
everyone try your best your chickens
down but in one day you might become
feelings if you follow
my guidelines properly uh-huh
and don't don't even dare
to doubt that i am a phys
because then you cannot become a phoenix
yourself
you must trust and then
become
you must trust and then become
hashtag philosophical phoenix
black friction duncan
[Music]
thank you thank you very much for your
support and your generous
donation spanking on thank you also for
a red super chat
thank you for some reason jingle town
cat
is sitting here bonking you on the
screen i can't explain
this well
i am a bird so
yeah it's uh
why are you all writing among us and
that's and not
a mangas anyway
spanking time it's okay let her touch me
i'll let him touch me as much as he or
she wants
it's okay it's a meme
ah it's okay spanking um i want the cats
to touch me
let them touch me i love cats i just
can't get enough of them
let them bunk me
and they don't long straight thank you
thank you thank you please please don't
do anything that you can't afford though
enough spotting street
hashtag broke thank you 67 thank you for
the pinky
if someone were to write a thing where
might they submit it on twitter
thing is there a specific hashtag or
would it just be under the normal art
hashtags
uh think like story kind of thing uh
generally i would like the art hashtag
to be used only for art
art um
we don't really have a
fitting hashtag for that i guess
but um
i guess it's okay um it's okay to use
the art hashtag
just try to not post too much
not related stuff there
because when i go through the art
hashtag it's a bit like
ruining my flow
i'm going through that every day and
sometimes i skip some things uh not
intentionally
you're reading right yeah i don't know i
can't promise if i'm going to read it do
you love
i cannot promise it depends on how long
it is
new hashtag for stories no i don't want
too much hashtags
and you could also put it in kfp memes
but i'm probably not gonna check it out
i i checked that
hashtag very very rarely but if you
don't care
about that you can put it in kfp memes
as well
thank
[Music]
what's going on what
here you loud and clear as nick kfb
prepare to
fire our first shots across their bow
whoa we shall make a pre-emptive strike
here and now who are you fighting
love 67 nagashin foreign attacks
thank you for the rice attacks
kristoff's also thank you for the
donation for
the ryzen stream tomorrow uh which
cannot be monetized
register thank you thank you soon lord
evoke also thank you
for arise attacks thank you guys you
guys are so supportive thank you very
much
the stream tomorrow uh does not allow
super chats
so thank you very much sly danke
and let me refresh one last time
tomorrow thank you thank you thank you
again
for arizona big ba tata thank you
no hi my friends say you will never
notice me can you prove them that they
are
wrong by liking my last tweet or leaving
a comment no i i go through i pretty
much read
almost all of the replies unless it's at
a time where i'm very very very busy
but um even if i read it i cannot like
like everything and comment to
everything but you can't be sure
i'm probably reading it but just don't
don't i can't if you ask for it then
everyone's gonna ask for it
it's i'm sorry i'm probably reading it
but
i cannot promise to like
give everyone a comment but hey you
basically
got noticed now i
read your super chat
thank you for your support though and
i hope you enjoyed the stream oh you got
notice in the club that must be good
enough
your voice is so cute it's like a fruit
salad thank you
i love fruit salad doomsday soon crunchy
i missed talking to kiara's hand our
time together was short but it was
therapeutic to have someone to listen to
our problems don't let kiana slam you
on the table too much we wait for your
return
you guys are so stupid
thank you thank you who knows maybe
maybe my hand will make a comeback
tomorrow and
rise on again thank you
very much i set myself on fire now what
oh my god
oh [\h__\h] because you want to become a
phoenix oh dear lord
[Music]
don't set yourself on fire to become a
phoenix
[Music]
you know but that's like something a
cult would make their members do
oh no you're gonna turn into fried
chicken you're not grown yet
you gotta wait a little bit heal me
yeah also my cats are playing oh my god
what are you guys doing
good that you're you don't even need me
to play with you take it monkey
thank you for arriza super chat
and owed me a cookie also thank you for
rising super chat and that's it that's
all the super chats
uh also crowley c danke
for tomorrow thank you thank you sly
thank you just ask
ned for the fire extinguisher
oh man uh angriest angry artist duncan
guilty gear strike coming soon are you
interested in fighting games
uh depends like you mean like a fighting
game where you straight up just
like like bunk each other not so
much optimus prime thank you thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
so stupid i'm so stupid i'm so stupid
thank you for arrive attacks thank you
um that's where we end today
thank you guys so much i'll see you
tomorrow uh
hope you had fun
on
and good night everyone love you
thank you might not do an
after stream tweet
just tweeted me randomly it's okay
if you need to tell me something thank
you for a super chat
uh spector from behrend
what's this join kfp that's called work
your way up the ranks and eventually be
bathed in glorious flames since he was
sent to become a phoenix
thank you thank you next time
thank you you're cute too
okay and in german we say
[Music]
no one stupid question
stupid
[Music]
you