[Music]
do
okay welcome everyone to the stream
today
is on my second duty as the
tales of the rise official ambassador to
the english region
but today i am not alone today and you
know my inanes
is with me thank you for coming
oh thanks for having me of course is
as you can see she is already very well
very prepared with
her uh what do you call that thing
my pal and my brush your pants
no no don't you
dare even touch my hat don't worry it's
water soluble
that's not it is easel easel
[Music]
easel easel no ah i can't yeah i'm
guessing you put the canvas on that's
right that's right
okay chad don't mislead us don't give us
wrong information
well so today's theme
is all about i will
teach you i will tell you who is who
and uh and then we'll draw who the later
and we'll
draw all kinds of huddles but uh before
we get into that
uh i'll i'll do a lot of talking first
you know you just go fubufu muhumu
my dear student and then you will
understand everything
because i think as far as i know you are
actually you don't really know uh
much about tails off right i know
the characters but i don't know much
about the story
you you never got to teach me a lot you
never played a tales off game before
right
i have not you are missing out on so
much
i will teach you leave it to me
all right so uh to give you a little bit
of a
light introduction first um well tails
of a rise
is a new upcoming tales off game from
bandai naka
uh coming out on september 19th right
before our one-year anniversary
uh it will be on ps4 ps5
xbox one xbox xbox xs
and windows so on pc as well and
in this game you challenge the fate that
binds you um sounds deep doesn't it
right believe in fate i
i don't know maybe the maybe the game
will make me believe in fate but
the tales of games usually always have
this like kind of uh kind of a slogan
like that and that is
the slogan for this game specifically um
it's a jrpg
with updated combat but classic tails
off gameplay mechanics
with a tale of people from different
worlds and heritages
looking to change their fate and create
a new
future because we kind of already
learned about it
in my previous uh tales of a rice
related stream that happened on the 5th
of july
and where we got quite into detail
about what this game is about uh what it
looks like i i
gave you guys a two hour introduction so
if you missed out on that
and you're interested in it uh
interested in learning a bit more about
this upcoming game i recommend you to go
to my channel afterwards
and then watch that as a recap but today
we're going to dig a little bit further
in there already so
today everything is about
so who is huddle
uh i i didn't come up with that okay i
that was not i didn't call it that
either
let me change that let me change the bgm
for that do you guys hear the video
or is it too quiet
very very tiny bgm actually i think
let me turn down in a tiny bit and the
music up a little bit did we hear that
guys
[Music]
we hear it okay so
uh huddle is a dan and owlette and
rinwell's
loyal pet united by their feelings of
loneliness
whotel's bond with rinwell is such that
he takes an
immediate dislike to anyone rainwell
doesn't trust
that sounds like a good companion but
actually we also want to know who are
owls because
we we we burps
i'm not feelings but you guys are
chickens we we chickens i speak for you
guys
don't know who else apparently owls play
a key role in tales of our eyes
owls of all colors shapes and sizes are
hidden throughout the land discover them
to help return them to the owl village
every hour is unique featuring a
specific attachment
discovering them unlocks this attachment
for party usage
so the owl village kind of
reminds me of uh uh tesla symphonia that
had something similar there
um uh was that a cat village or
something like that if i remember i'm
not sure do you guys know
but i think it is something similar to
that you can imagine that
er for example if you were to happen
upon a
sophisticated owl sporting a cat's
village
that was that oh my god that is so
nostalgic
sporting a monocle you would then have a
monocle attachment you could equip to
any of your party members
so the same thing for example if it's
glasses and if you see a hoodle
uh or an owl with glasses then you would
be able to put glasses on all your
members it's like a like an item that
you pick up by picking up the owl
and sending that out to the village oh
that's the very first style
but here there's small small letters
here written the monocle is just an
example we cannot confirm nor deny
that owls with monocles exist in the
tails of her eyes
by the way that that reminds me i don't
think i mentioned this but
i think i have to mention this in the
beginning of the stream
uh this stream is sponsored by bandai
namco i forgot to say that
uh yes never guessed
surprise surprise but uh you know i have
to say it it is it isn't
true the stream is sponsored i i am the
official
taste authorized ambassador for the
english region and this stream is
sponsored
yes it says so sorry i forgot about that
but it's it's just everywhere else it's
pretty obvious
you should have you missed your chest
carry you should be like
i know how that one goes okay perfect
thank you so um to get to know hoodle
we first of all want to take one quick
look at
rinwell with hudal with english voice
over
now i might be wrong but i think this
could possibly be
no guarantee but this could possibly be
exclusive footage because
i didn't find it on youtube
i couldn't find this on youtube so this
might be exclusive let's take
a little bit of a look oh
don't worry about hoodle he's from
cislodia
probably just nerves is all he's not
really used to being around other people
this much
oh it is don't worry hoodle it's okay
here we go so tiny
hey is that owl beckoning us over
hey hoodle
how about we find more of your friends
and tell them about this
so adorable oh that was so cute
so that was ringwell that you saw on
screen one of the playable
characters one of the um main side
characters is that the thing main side
characters she's like one of the team
one of the
uh group that you go around with in the
game
it's so small it's an owlette and baby
owl
how cute is it i'll
yeah yeah you don't know i'm relying on
you here
i don't know i thought you were the bird
expert here ah
what not really changing with the sky
you know okay
it was also so tiny it was like a baby
so adorable
so cute and so they all already seem to
have a very wholesome
interaction going on there i think
like i'm so curious like will she be
with
huto from the beginning on when you meet
her first
time in the game wow why where did you
find
hudo how why did she pick up hudo who
did she steal hudu from
etc many questions that i still have uh
but i have one more clip uh this one
might also be maybe exclusive i don't
know
babe actually it wouldn't it might be
but but we will in this clip see
um how the owl village looks like and
how this whole
thing works um functions like when you
find
an owl in somewhere
and you pick it up yeah we'll see how
that works let's take a look
do you sense one of your friends noodle
oh found one good eye
oh there it is you guys see it
you're saying we should check the owl
forest
oh and there we put on the accessory
that we just received
from the owl that we sent off to the
forest
oh
oh we got something else too oh midnight
gardel grab wood i don't get it
why has it suddenly started giving us
things
ah because we're bringing owls back to
the village
as a thank you hey is that owl
beckoning us over i think it is pecking
people
we rescued before then maybe that's what
the gifts are all about
thank you guys for saving its friend
oh very lovely it isn't
something about it seems almost regal oh
don't you think
what if it was the king of the owls i
think uh
could be when you look at what they're
wearing the queen
oh perhaps you think so the king
what the hell they're clearly
self-proclaimed king and queen
[Applause]
[Music]
oh that was uh
in the beginning you were playing alfin
and
walking through the city and finding an
owl
then yeah we picked up the owl or
basically we sent the owl to the village
as i explained
and then uh we received the halo
so this one was uh wearing a hail very
very holy owl
ho ho cool
upstairs that would be a
you are the perfect guest for today
[Laughter]
yeah anyway we gotta look into the uh
owl village which i think looks really
uh
really serene and comfortable
with uh hopefully in the future hundreds
of hours
as you said you wanted 500 who knows
maybe that will be 500
at some point who knows
okay okay
yeah so let me show you a few examples
of what kinds of huddles uh there are
well for example someone who really he
doesn't look very uh
happy um oh no he's happy he's happy
i can tell maybe he's just you know
being um
blinded by the sun that's why he's like
squinting
no he's just like you you're jealous of
me aren't you
jealous of his drip exactly this
mug he's he's very amused mm-hmm
he's really cute i think uh i don't
want to get that whole i wonder where
that one is we also have a
devil hoodle with huge huge
horns hmm what are those
what are those kind of edgy very indian
still looks fluffy though yeah wait is
that two wings
yeah or like like two sets of wings
yeah devil winks
do you fly over to center wing do you
have two set of wings
me no not kawaii
none at this very moment but i
i could i could help them if papa would
allow me
anyway and there is also
so cute look at those eyes
adorable
wait a second there's wings on wings
that's what it is
but this one this one is even funnier
because the wings that it has attached
are also like
normal proper feather wings the other
ones were different wings i don't i
don't want to ask where
where i got them i got the wing
quadruple wings um
can probably uh you know sparkly eyes
hide a dark truth
but who knows who knows maybe uh they uh
did these owls have those wings because
they are actually
not good at flying and need flying
support
ah maybe maybe maybe you know how good i
can swim and therefore she needs
swimming support
anyway we have a she on hudo shion is
the female
main character of the game so this one
comes with like a big
red ribbon in the front uh to hide its
big belly
and uh
it's not a crown but uh she on has this
like
accessory on her ponytail which in this
case is
on this hoodle's forehead pretty
adorable i must say
[Music]
the male main character of
the game very handsome we saw him in the
key visual that i showed in the
beginning
and in the back this hoodoo has
outfits sword in a miniature version
it's literally like glowing
so cool i wouldn't want to get too close
to this huddle
looks looks like it's ready to stab
someone with alvin's sword
without her what without a moment of
hesitation
not even in one blink you gotta even be
careful with the scarf because it has
that dispatch and it looks like it could
poke its own eyes
out at any moment but what if it's made
out of cookies
the
that would be great but i think it's uh
oh the real deal i think it's
it's better than poking its eyes out if
i'm being honest
well well well so that was a bunch of
rules that uh i showed you there and now
i think we want to teach you how
to draw huddle and get into drawing but
before we do that
i want to tell you guys if you look at
the title of the stream
and the hashtag is doodle
i didn't i did not come up with that but
that sounds really i'm awesome
who was in charge of this stream
i think it sounds adorable uh it's a bit
difficult to pronounce for me
but you guys are welcome to use that
hashtag on twitter
uh to draw huddle with us together
make your own hodo and upload it on
twitter to show us
all
[Music]
wait i will show you our screen
sorry a very scuffed improvised titles
oh wow
eh let's draw who don't like it
music change okay uh
how do i get rid of this screen and can
i just
and then make a new one oops oh no
how do i make a new layer ah this one
okay
so uh oops no that's not it
this one okay that's it okay
we will be sharing this screen
together wait a second i'm having some
audio issues
do you guys hear the museum now i
switched bgm
i think it should be audible
that will come oh
[Music]
previously we used it
wait a second
bgm is okay wonderful
there we go okay are you on the same
h can you draw something
test test where are you ina let me find
you
oh oh my god you're drawing something
big i need to zoom out here
oh is this supposed to be an oversized
hoodle
that's watching over us be gym a bit too
loud all righty
i'll fix it one second
yo yo
[Music]
okay that should be better
yes you're good i think i'm good okay
so it is actually extremely easy
to draw hudo guys would you like to
learn
the basics of how to draw a hudo
we will teach you okay well maybe you
have no choice
you can do it together with me you know
maybe uh get rid of that big huddle
but that is a completely straight line
there we go no actually i love that big
huddle i love it
but we have to start small enough is
that straight
how do i draw a straight line there we
go
[Music]
there there is probably a two for that
but
oh my god you're making a statue of
oodles
[Music]
you're a plop here yeah wings now
okay okay i will i will however start by
teaching everyone how to draw hudo
and also here hashtag
who to
there we go use this hashtag so
first of all step one we draw
an egg maybe a prettier egg
no okay dragon egg is uh
we all know how to draw an egg because
all my chickens
have been in an egg before okay i'm
really struggling with an egg here you
know
oh you know i have a feeling you have a
better time understanding
what an egg looks like maybe this will
no way it has to be a bit more like
round
the egg comes first that's right egg
comes first
egg comes first oh where does the egg
come from
it from the tree did you not know
okay we we don't have to do this in one
stroke
you don't always have to do it in one
stroke oh my god we gotta
we can start uh with one stroke but we
can
fill it up like that wonderful okay i
think that has a perfect shape
yes eggs come from crease
okay so after
you draw the egg you add to
[Music]
what's made in english
fried fr fried fried that's yolk
sunny side up fried egg oh i guess yeah
sunny side up
oh okay okay so we do that uh in like
the not in the middle a bit above the
middle
hi everyone are you following ita is not
following
oh on my own way go ahead go ahead
[Music]
help
oh that seems no way that's creepy
maybe a bit more uh away from the border
this is my first time drawing huddle
okay i i i need
some practice uh yeah that's what you're
learning how to draw
for you know exactly i'm the one
teaching as well though so we have a
little bit of an issue there
uh can i can can i copy and paste
don't come back okay come on you can do
it draw a circle draw that circle
[Laughter]
yeah work that circle oh
i'm starting to see
i'm shaking you can do it i can do it
this is here for more support does this
look okay
yes okay so we have drawn
uh two sunny-side up uh egos
now uh wait actually no not yet i need a
i need one more
uh circle inside to make it an actual
uh wait uh sunny side whatever you call
it whatever you call it
um not exactly you know what we can do
this
uh uh no
i'll do it right now okay
almost i was so close to perfection
[Music]
so close
you're doing it i believe in you i know
this one is all right this one is right
one more come on you can do it kiara
there we go wonderful that was perfect
first try
beautiful thank you thank you okay
so huh it's not a potato
it's it's becoming a huddle give me a
break here
so next step you
burn the fried eggs you burn them you
left them too long in the frying pan
and therefore it turns into this oh no
yeah that is uh unfortunate
but it is what it is now we add
cheese cheese we shall add
yes yes cheese a slice of cheese
uh how about some gauda
gouda wait how do you call that in
english
or some cheddar i like cheddar cheese
what's your favorite cheese inna
swiss swiss cheese that's not really
hmm that's not
that's that could be any kind of cheese
no eh no
that's just cheese from switzerland no
no
maybe first like you know the classic
cheese with like holes in it
classic cheese what
yeah like it looks like cheese i'm
drawing right now ah
that's just that's just comic style
cheese
no it's literally looks like that chiara
any cheese can't look like that there's
a lot of cheeses that look like that
i think i think okay between chat me and
you i think you're the only one who
doesn't know what swiss cheese is
the looks of it whatever just a feeling
okay let me continue driving my hurdle
okay
you better be watching to learn
oh yeah totally so after after you added
the cheese
yeah this is supposed to be cheese after
that you add
uh two chopsticks
[Music]
like that chopsticks
my guide tells me it's chopsticks okay
my guide is telling you that it must be
true this is chopsticks what else could
it be
all right it's not my fault
so that was that was easy we all did
that
are you guys following chad are you
following are you drawing that down
hopefully well done the next step
is also supposedly easy you put the
fried eggs
on a plate so uh
concentration oh no
undo
like that and then on top
[Music]
didn't go too bad did you get that
i am making breakfast now we're making
it ow we're not making a breakfast we're
making out
we're making whodo who don't doodle let
me make this a bit prettier
what are you laughing there mrs inna
[Music]
who am i married to you what
you said missus mrs is for uh
well it sounds cuter
well as long as i'm married to you i'm
fine oh come on
yeah i did i didn't bring you here to
flirt with me although i do enjoy that
but i brought you here for
artistic input
you started it i didn't what i did not
call i tried to be professional by
calling new misses well you know like a
title
so i wouldn't i would like you to be
professional right now because we are
now putting this little uh hoodle doodle
on some
legs so that it can walk and and i have
noticed they've saved the private
matters for after stream okay god
that's better uh i've noticed when
looking at hudo hudo
uh kind of like like
duck duck looking duck-like looking
uh feet i don't know if i'm the only one
that noticed that but
so we're gonna be giving feet like that
so and with that we add a little
uh something uh what was that round one
it had there i think it was round so we
add the
the necklace thingy and then
all you got to do is add some color oh i
guess you could probably
do the wing thingy like it they are
they're pretty much like
like uh how to say
uh schmidt melting melting into
its body because it's so thick hey
my whole
doesn't look as i would have imagined it
gonna practice it yeah that's what the
stands for
exactly you could now go on and add all
kinds of accessories
like for example elephant's uh
scarf like that
get rid of whatever you had there i'm
sorry if you were drawing
traditionally and now i like what the
hell kiana there is no
proper eraser tool with what i am using
you completely completely effed me over
but i am sorry
that is just how it is we are using
digital tools
this one really looks like an egg it
kind of needs to be a bit thicker
there is no issue in correcting
what you have done yes yes
i'm talking like the expert here but i
would like to have a little bit of an
artistic input from uh miss
inna if you will yeah one if you want me
to call you miss
[Music]
mrs slime i mean to be already divorced
that was fast yeah
[Music]
what is your uh artistic opinion
uh criticism about
evaluation evaluation of my
little hood i want to add colors
yeah i think as long as you add some
color in it i think it'll be perfect
i see also i gotta it has no life in its
eyes right so
i'll add some life
there we go add a little white dot
and there it is there's life life
it just happens like that so
i want to add another layer underneath
your shawl for some
color whoa
is uh has like a what mostly
white oh wait what do you call it
you don't call it fur you call it uh
yeah one feta but what do you call the
whole thing
a bird
that's not what i meant
down down down down a phoenix down
thank you chad i can always rely on you
you guys are bird experts
excellent experts
[Music]
i am sorry um all right good luck with
the rest of the stream i'm out of here
hi hey white is not i put uh i chose
soft but it doesn't do the soft oil you
have to double click the brush
ah thank you oh there we go
there we go yeah it's a little bit of
like a purplish
hue there and then you go
a bit more into orange and
and then add another area here
and then we have the perfect hulu color
on its body and now for the
for the feathers we wanna
make it like blue a light blue color
that is a general color oopsie it's okay
to draw out of the lines
no one's gonna stop you you don't have
it doesn't matter you're the one to
decide where the line is
all right
your hoodle seems to have a bigger
mission
[Music]
it's uh it's called galaxy hood
galaxy doesn't it need
a space helmet nah
it's powerful but that would be another
great accessory
hmm true but i think it'll be kind of uh
not fitting the world
not necessarily but i mean they also
have devil huddles angel
hoodles all kinds of huddles yeah but
a fantasy setting like devil and angels
you know but
space helmet
[Music]
well if you want the hoodle to die in
space that's fine with me
i hope it lived a nice life
[Music]
okay i'm gonna give my huddle
the classical yellow eyes
because our noodle has yellow eyes of
course there are who will come to those
all kinds of sizes and forms and colors
but this one is the classic one and now
i'm just gonna i'm just gonna add
the color of the this thingy here
the sky supposedly elephant scarf not
sure about it
maybe not oh yeah and then the pendant
as well which is i guess it must have
some kind of
connection with rinwell maybe maybe not
i'm just theorizing here
i got a jaw cookie
cookie pendant ah i didn't i didn't mean
uh the cookies that we talked about
before
are you talking about those cookies the
one that
um on the skype yeah
no no i'm not putting those on right now
no no no no you're so you're stuck
okay i drew a little bit over the line
is that is that a problem
[Music]
a red a little bit of a red color
okay oh wait wait what's the color of uh
it's big
beak what was the color of the huddle's
beak
uh was it like brownish
i'm just gonna make it like a brownish
color
usual and there you go you could
probably do this much much faster
but this is how you draw a
and then you add two fried eggs and then
you burn the eggs and then you add the
cheese and then you add chopsticks
totally chopped six hundred percent then
you put it on on a plate
then you give it legs and yeah pretty
much you got a huddle
[Music]
take it easy just for a reference
let me show you
this is the guide
easy right use it as reference you're
welcome you're now
professional artist yata
okay so with that
i think i will delete that
just make a new layer oh okay i didn't
want to you know spam
layers but okay if you're fine with it
okay i guess you're used to
having a lot of layers yes
okay so now what we do next and i want
you to join with this one
ina okay we draw
all kinds of tales of uh hudos
so all right uh one thing about tail
love games i usually
always have some kind of um fluffy
mascot so for this game
it's huddle but for other games for
example for
tales of celia one one of my
favorite games we had
uh wait where is it oh yeah wait i need
to hide
this one we had tipo so we're gonna draw
people
first people looks like this maybe a bit
difficult but i think we can manage
so we're going to try to give it the
pink and purple diamond checker pattern
and then the ear and tail top still
yeah instead of instead of the feathers
and then zigzag teeth that's gonna look
creepy probably
and acromerene circle lens contacts
all right so also that color or we're
actually actually i guess we could also
one of us could draw people and then
another one of us could draw a reload uh
huddle
roller ah true i think you're gonna want
rolo
oh yeah by the way i'm gonna uh end
the screen sharing i don't think you
need it anymore right
okay do you have the reference for
people
[Music]
you can you can i have it up uh uh wait
i i'll send it to you
i'll send it to you
there it is don't worry i got the goods
okay then yolo tipa
out the world rumble is by the way from
tesla celia two
t-boys from taylor's celia one
you're sure then let's get rid of those
for rubble i'm gonna give it a great
face
uh emerald circle lens contacts whiskers
cat ears cat tails a cattail bell color
and a grey left wing
ah kudos left i see i see ah for the for
the paws i guess okay
oh wait rolla i just noticed well has
only one white pot all the others
all right um there we go you're already
on it
[Music]
we're drying we're drawing a hulu
version of cheapo and raw
yeah okay i see you are not
restricting yourself to the hoodoo
doodle guide that is interesting maybe i
should
do that too not restrict restricting
myself
i think that's all you called me even
even doing a sketch
wow professional i guess i'll i'll do
like a sketchy thing too
[Music]
and then the proper outline later is
that what you're doing
let me do that too okay
all right
which there we go so
we start out again with an egg
what's so funny
it's a purple potato i mean what color
was that like blue
it's just a sketch color what about that
[Music]
maybe with a thinner uh
final brush maybe okay
[Music]
okay small strokes start small
start big usual
okay something like that okay okay okay
get rid of that part wow yours already
looks so good you're so fast
yeah this is too easy for you we gotta
have a little bit more of a difficulty
level for you
it's way too way too easy
big potato don't call it a potato
it's an owl a dan an owl
[Music]
slow down ina can i put on slow motion
on your side all right i'll go slow
very okay
relatively slow lies
[Music]
oh my god oh my god it looks like it has
seen nightmares
you can do it you can do it
okay friday it's fried eggs but it
doesn't have to be exactly that shape
okay alien let's go
i'm trying to make it look a little bit
more like those cat eyes that
rollo had oh my god it scares me
it sometimes does that start we can do
it
okay okay and then oh yeah
i guess the beak can stay uh
but it will have whiskers
[Music]
cute and the thing about drawing
characters like in
in like a different kind of thing is to
pick out
their characteristics and then add them
into the
into the character you know yeah but i
think adding the
the inner eye made it much better now
okay
hmm oh wait wait actually the the
whiskers look like wrinkles
oh they look like whiskers it looks like
a baby seal
someone in the chat was just like
nedesil no
i'm not throwing this i'm not doing a
steal i'm trying a huddle in rebel
cosplay
uh okay a cat ears cat ears
okay like that okay
like that and uh oh yeah the
the bell color color
color co color
can you say both words please colored
color
i don't know which one is which
[Music]
here yours looks so good
i'm glad it's soakier
um
is so cute rolo um
was uh the companion of uh
what was your name again small small
little girl in desert cilia too
what was her name again
[Music]
she is such a such a cute baby
okay she's not all the mascots always
like
hang out with like the small like cute
character in the party
not with like a small character but
actually
you know what it might it could
is it's a trend it seems to be a trend
that they hang out with the girls
which is a choice that i can uh
relate to oops what the hell is that
uh you're sure
because the for example for tales of
berseria
uh there's this character called maggie
lou
she is the one with the mascot uh
bienville
was that one we're also going to draw
that one in a little bit
yeah okay tail oh my god that doesn't
look like an owl anymore
[Music]
i mean i i don't know what mine is
looking like i don't know is it
also doesn't necessarily look like an
owl anymore but
still wait you know what that looks like
a like a what what does that look like
like a squirrel yeah
but it has cat ears why does it look
like a squirrel
because of the wings um maybe but
how about i do the tails
the ears and tails has whiskers too what
the hell
but it's okay because this is uh tails
of her eyes right
oh you're trying you're really trying
ina i feel it
i don't want to have the whiskers above
the eyes but
it's kind of tough
how creepy does this look
[Music]
your answer to my question
is your tails one
no whatever or not it is cute
that's cute um
okay oh now it's kind of cuter with
filled
filled eyes it still looks kind of
creepy
what am i doing wrong
don't worry about this cute it's like
the it's like the pian
eyes oh wait it also needs a darker face
but i'll do that when i color okay
then i guess i'll just i'll just i'll
just
i'll just go with this needs feathers
um then you want me to add
those feathers
[Music]
i guess so we can we can have that
i damn it i went through around the
wrong layer again
one more
[Music]
okay so i will do the outlines now
this takes uh more time than i
thought it would flying is a long
long journey it's very
uh relaxing though uh
[Music]
do not draw on the wrong layers to lower
the opacity of your sketch like yeah
yeah should have done that
okay
it happens
it's kind of thick thick but whatever
yeah it's a beak not a nose does it look
like a nose
it's a honey it's a it's a cat owl i
mean a cat owl can't possibly look
normal
it's difficult to make a cat out look
like one certain enemy a an enemy
animal of course we're gonna have some
issues here
[Music]
cat owl cat owl
i mean honestly i wouldn't mind we have
a cat shark so
yeah cat
cat human shark it's not only cat shark
it's human also in there
[Music]
yeah we also wait we already have
something similar to a
cat owl
closer than you think i guess
uh i'm closer than you think if you
think about it because i am a bird
and i also have cat ears with my other
outfits
yeah you're getting closer dude i see i
see the cat phoenix that is not
not i don't i don't know whatever you
are thinking about currently
yeah i was thinking about cat chicken
maybe i was wrong i will
i will okay so what
once we get into minecraft later in in
one hour
i will i will i will push you off of a
cliff just kidding i love you
yes yes
oopsie
okay okay
[Music]
chad are you drawing all right you don't
have to draw the same things as we are
drawing by the way you can draw all
kinds of noodles
you can draw a chicken i want to see a
chicken
or what kind of you could go draw a gura
hoodoo like a
huddle with a gouda a hook dress hoodie
thingy
and a trident or you could draw
ina with tentacles you know
sore also translate really well to talk
about
why others becoming the flaps
they have a very similar silhouette is
that so
[Music]
i guess so hmm if you think about see
sorry guys i'm turning the canvas right
now
you can turn your head i know you can do
it chickens
i believe in you oh oh that's cute
oh that works but can you add like some
santa claus
just don't really have tentacles coming
in yeah but we want the tentacles too
for example
and probably with your
hey focus on your own drawing
[Music]
i'm just helping
if you don't finish i'm gonna move on
without you oh
sure sure i want to see you do that
okay okay i just need the eyes and then
some color oh yeah
oh yeah i'll be happy
uh there we go
we got a huddle quota to me true
little cooldown we want to do a few more
and be really sure
oh by the way today's bgm is provided by
tails of a rice
thank you uh that's actually
bgm that uh is part of the game
and the other tracks that i was playing
same thing there
this one is really fitting for our
little drawing session
it's really cute i guess you know you
can't hear it right now but it's really
cute it goes like
what is it called i can play it on my
end sometimes we need a break
sometimes
all right got it nice
isn't it relaxing it is i can't i can
imagine the the hoodles dancing
belay to this
relatable title you guys need a break i
wonder if this is
what plays in the uh our
little little place possible it also
could be the other one the
hidden owl one this one guys that i'm
playing for you now
it's very mysterious
i like this one too can you play this
one for a little bit
your i'll try to make the beak
look a little bit more like a big maybe
if i do that oh cute
[Music]
okay now we talking
do funny sounds
uh let's see
i guess i could even add the whiskers
here
is that better guys it might be better
huh
what do you think
if i add them here
oh yeah that means okay let's do that
it's better okay
one step closer to perfection
gosh let's add uh the color
you know i can i'm adding color now
you caught up eh
what caught up to me
[Music]
it so oh because
wrong brush wrong layer exactly wrong
brush
there we go okay
[Music]
can i select something from what the
hell is that
can i select something from one layer
and then uh use that selection and the
other layer is that a thing that works
[Music]
is there one i know there's a there's a
lasso tool
oh no okay
no need for that
a clipping mask eh no problem i i'm just
going to draw in the
layer below so let's do
like a brownish color for rolo willow's
tail rolla looks like a ragdoll cat to
me
i don't know what you guys think when
you look at rollo but
we're all looking hella cute
[Music]
so cute chunky very chunky like chunkers
oh those colors look really good
actually then those colors remind me of
you yeah
t-boys
what what has
has been revealed conspiration theory
conspiration and a conspiracy
english doco
english what's conspiration coco
is that a word is conspirational word
inna
oh
[Music]
i keep on asking you questions about
english language because i feel like
you're more
way more sufficient than me in that
language but you can't really give me
clear answers when people think i'm
good at japanese when i'm just good at
pretending to be good at japanese no you
are actually really good at japanese and
i will now
uh uh confirm that here openly publicly
for the people
[Music]
we like she likes udon i like ramen
gray left wing who does left
wait i did the wrong side
that's who was ryan
[Music]
but wait what the canvas left but with
romo's
right front paw is white
oh god oh it looks so good here
yeah i'll keep it like that
never mind why yours looks so good
it looks like people ah
it actually like harmonizes so well
thank you thank you
that's the reason why i brought you here
the expert
artistically i'm here
that's why you have a brush and then
a palette in your outfit
exactly
[Music]
if you could have a a cat
cat owl as a pet would you want it i
would want it
i love cats and i love owls i want that
[Music]
are you thinking about it are you
thinking of saying
no i'm just saying um i
prefer a normal cat because think about
all the cat
uh all the mess that cats make imagine
if they fly now
my cats don't really make much of a mess
not all cats but if yeah if they fly
then that might make quite some trouble
yeah exactly that's how i was thinking i
was hmm
no you're thinking you're thinking too
much
thinking seriously like a real option
like it's not like a passing by question
you know it's like an
actual actual question like wow if i
actually had one would i or would i not
wow deep stuff you're just gonna say yes
sometimes you know
you gotta think first life's all about
toys
you know okay
i'm i'm gonna get started i'm gonna get
it anyway
i don't know what i'm doing with the
eyes i'm just doing something random
you know we're spending too much time
eating for you
okay you can already start with the next
one uh
you can go um
next one if you don't catch it okay okay
you're just like i'll go ahead
okay i'll wait for you there no the next
one is uh this one i i'll you can do the
the bien fu one
this one this is for this of azaria
beautiful
with a present top hat i host red bat
wings ribbon necklace
and purple fur with cream belly and hand
uh
tips doesn't that sound adorable do we
have it or should i send it to you i'll
send it to you
i have it i have it okay so
we are drawing dad i'm gonna finish the
cat the cat owl
i'm almost done too though
[Music]
time goes by so quickly i wish i was
amelia watson
[Music]
can you hear her impression
these are her hicks did you hear them
did this quite even pick them up
nope i was i was doing an accurate
expression
and then and then she goes like um
all right number one detective
can you do her
i guess i'm guessing discord didn't pick
that up either
i picked up some of it
because if i if i do something in really
high frequencies like when i when i
yell or when i laugh too high uh on on
discord it doesn't pick it up
why all right all right let's see
yeah i can't do her like uh gremlin
laugh you can't
did you try and the discord didn't pick
it up because i want to hear it
oh i just i just can't do it
[Music]
are you shooting me the gremlins are
sure
are there any taco doctors in the
audience now raise your hands raise your
flip
flaps i want to know
if she's hiding something from me does
she have an inner gremlin that she ever
showed to you
there they are there they are does she
have a gremlin
that she's trying to hide right now i'm
just like i gotta be real
like i've been with her for a while but
i don't remember
ever hearing maybe not yes they say yeah
they're lying you know guys can you
slide as easily as they breathe
i need a clip as proof please i would
love to get that
clip she says you don't have a club guys
mm-hmm a little bit of yabby
no no gremlin only comfy hmm very
contradicting
the opinions hold on
all right i am finishing up this cat owl
[Music]
you know you're suspiciously quiet maybe
there is a gremlin inside of you
no i'm just waiting for them to still
proof i mean is there proof i don't
think so you can't just make up stuff
hey this actually looks cute now i'm
done
ah see not believe in yourself it's not
that bad see
actually let me add light
[Music]
i'm not i'm not 100 unhappy with that
it could be bad i don't have which one
is drawn by you
what nah it's already so cute
you're cute
okay next one
[Music]
here okay for me the next one
and the last one uh apparently probably
unless i'm go i go like super speed but
i wanted to look cute
will be none other than
[Music]
oh chatan
huh a orange body with a turquoise hand
and actually they're supposed to be on
both sides and turquoise
head sprig spree so the little feather
on top
and sideways of the eyes okay no so
no creepy eyes this time okay
and maybe a blush could add a blush here
yeah okay well
let's go oh my god yo i'm so so dynamic
how can you make such a fat owl look so
dynamic
oh it's like like it's like jelly beans
squishy jelly beans ah
yeah yeah that's right that's actually a
good advice for people drawing huddle
hashtag a little and maybe maybe draw it
like jelly beans yeah
i think i like bean bags and stuff here
hmm
[Music]
never thought of it that way you guys
are you drawing something you better be
drawing some hurdles
i will what will what will you look like
guys
[Music]
curious to see what you come up with
i i am curious as well
[Music]
um egg
yeah yeah i see this happening okay okay
[Music]
but actually drawn by none other than
you
i need to sneeze i think do it ah
do it now that i said it i i think it
disappeared
oh no we're waiting chad is waiting
always always waiting for your sneezes
you sure oh those are the v eyes
[Music]
okay
really looks like an ink fluffy fat egg
kotori is actually not supposed to be
that fat
[Music]
kotori works around hmm we'll see around
i know
he goes to the gym every day and lifts
lifts what have you done to his mouth
no no it does proper workout
i wanna i'm gonna do the feetsies too
okay
[Music]
which game is bien foo from tales of
victoria the
one that came out before it tells of a
right well a taste of res didn't come
out yet but it's the
most recent uh mod
i forgot again how to say it mothership
mother title
motherboard motherboard you know what
i'm talking about right
stop laughing i see you laughing
you could at least do an audible laugh
that would make me feel a bit more
comfortable
i don't hear
[Music]
yeah you do that a lot but i always
wondered maybe discord just doesn't pick
you up
no i just lost flagship that's what i
meant yeah flagship flagship why don't i
think motherboard
why do i have the motherboard series is
there also
a stereo profiles is there also uh
another word for it like mother or ship
or is that another thing why do i always
think of mother
something why
why do i do that what is that i don't
know what goes on in your brain
mothership is for aliens yeah
i'm i'm confused okay well
well yeah so that says of tesla bizarre
tesla bizarre i really recommend
um since it's the most recent one but
also
is that the one with the the girl main
character
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's actually
quite
rare for tons of games to have a female
lead
character um it was the case
uh kind of the case as well in tales of
celia
one but besides that
we all can't actually
chad help me are the tails off fans i
can't think of any
other tales of games where the girl was
the main character
actually it really doesn't happen often
that's why i was so excited about uh
tesla berseria
um because i i just love my girls
[Music]
and she was really bad as uh velvet
velvet was her name um she looked like
this i was like
that's exactly what she looked like yep
yeah
she's not or angry
[Music]
yay collaboration and she had this
really hot sexy outfit
that's like uh it had holes in it it was
like
red yeah yeah she was hot
she was very hot like big claw
she goes
she definitely doesn't uh because she's
not
not that kind of edgy teenager
she's really badass i love i love her
i love also her relationship
relationship friendship that she has
with the
what was the boy's name no i i'm really
bad at remembering names
from video game characters
same to be honest the chat probably
knows
luffy said yeah exactly because i know
how the like the main characters look
like in the tl series
or some of them at least oh i don't know
their name
oh do you just know it because you see
it on
on twitter or whatever i see people like
john there's like
this dude
[Music]
that could be a lot of people but maybe
maybe that's loins are you drawing
lolita yeah yeah
where's red yeah yeah red cloves yeah
yeah
but that kind of hairstyle is quite what
what there's also there's also this dude
but except this time he has a feather
a feather thank you ah he's from tales
of systeria the main character
having played tails off games you do
know some of the characters huh
yeah and there's there's there's this
little thing yeah his name is
long hair so it's already so hey
oh are you drawing another dude yeah
who's long hair
look that looks cool that looks familiar
wait who was that
it looks very familiar how the hell do
you remember that
could could be yuri oh yeah yeah yeah
oh my god
okay i know my characters damn
not bad not bad okay i think
there's kotori is really simple there's
not much more that i can do
without colors i think this just has to
be turned into colors
um but i guess we could make it look
a little bit more like a little bit more
like
poodle wait let me pick that color again
oh wait sorry sorry guys you want to see
that don't you
there you go cute doodles
uh okay
maybe should i add the fried eggs to
make it look
[Music]
this one or does that just not look good
with kotori hmm
i think i think you can do it i think so
[Music]
thinking chad what do you think eggs
eggs is good
ah wait there's not eggs that's that
that's the plate that's the place that
you put the fried eggs on
hmm you already freaked out
[Music]
it is a very defining feature yeah
that's true we can try
let's let's try let's make them the
outlines
okay you know don't worry
i'm catching up don't worry don't worry
do it
i believe in you i'm on my way
[Music]
oh wait why did i make a copy you show
your show
[Music]
okay i'm actually surprised that this is
the
the first time that we draw like
together
uh-huh because in the beginning when i
first got to know
you sorry by the way if i'm not moving
for most of the time it's because i'm
looking to the left side my tablet i
can't really place it
right in front of me at the moment am i
not moving most of the time chad
and i'm not even noticing sorry if
that's the case
uh but yeah and i wanted to say uh
because uh when i when i got to know you
it's fine i am moving most of the time
oh cool okay
i found out that well you you like
drawing
a lot and you're really good at it and i
was like damn
i i like drawing a lot too i don't do it
that much
at the moment i'm not very active uh
i don't do much drawing but um
i was like yo i could totally do like i
can totally see myself
doing drawing collapse with you but it
never really happened until now i mean
we had that five
five people drawing cool out but that's
about it
and you've been doing dramatically with
others but not with me i don't know why
that never happened
no more yeah although i don't i don't
have to say
you're so good that i just feel
a little bit intimidated
[Music]
you can't help it maybe that's
i don't know you're like you're like god
god of drawing
[Music]
your bob ross no
no no no no inaudible
chet agrees with me i think
nah nah you are you are better
you are god here oh yes yes
yes of course no no no yes yes yes yes
yes yes
yes yes yes yes yes okay
zip it and keep drawing kiara gotta
catch up
she zipped the mouth of the official
ambassador can you believe it
i don't know you're still talking
i gotta i gotta talk
um oh yeah guys
tomorrow tomorrow it's tomorrow right
tomorrow i'm doing um
a test play privately i'm so sorry guys
i can't show you but
i'm doing a test play of tales of
arrives tomorrow privately
i am so excited i'm so freaking excited
you know what i really like about tales
of her eyes yeah
the art style like in game i saw a
screenshot i thought it was a concept
art but then it started moving i was
like what yeah it has a very interesting
style that it's not
it's actually the first the first time
it's not like they have that style
all the time uh i think they're
experimenting a little bit
uh with this new game um
and that was yeah especially with the
art style it's very noticeable
it looks uh like watercolor yeah looks
really good
so i want to play i've seen it a lot in
videos too now but i want to
see it in action like when i play it the
game
so i'll see that tomorrow
i'm so excited i'll i'll tell you guys
guys
how how i felt about i can give you i
got permission to give you like a brief
brief uh feedback like
what i felt about it i can do that it's
just gonna be you
screaming for a couple of minutes no no
it will be
just on twitter like an update like a
screenshot and like yo i
uh this is what i thought about the game
so excited
we're gonna get your uh your fangirl
voice pack
yeah but don't don't worry guys i think
i mean i can't make any promises right
now or any any official announcements
but
there will be something like that sooner
or later
that that i will be able to stream okay
so don't let your heads down
yet i am the official test of a rise
ambassador for the english region that i
will deliver i mean i feel like i've
already been
delivering uh with this stream and the
last room and we only just got started
there's
many much more uh exciting content to
come
you guys and
someone said it to me in the in the
twitter uh replies after announced like
sorry it's actually private
um but uh someone said like
i i would probably be able to enjoy it
more
if if i was playing it privately and i'm
like yeah
that's kind of true because then i'll be
able to slowly take it all in
um quietly without having to talk all
the time
um and just yeah be on my own and enjoy
what's in front of me inhale exhale
yeah so that is true actually
i i'm excited to play it alone
sorry guys enjoy thank you
uh
[Music]
oh
belly so lucky
yes i am quite lucky it's a huge tales
often this is
really exciting because it's coming out
in september and we're still in july
i'm getting to play it so early but only
only a little bit it's not not the whole
game
uh but yeah super hyped up about that
so earlier than a lot of people i'm
really
curious about the fighting system how
that's gonna uh
feel uh
yeah is it gonna be a little
different than previously
[Music]
from what i've seen generally most of
the the
gameplay mechanics of the fighting
system
seems mostly like familiar
but i think there are like some some
features that are new definitely
[Music]
like but if you if you want to if you
want to learn more about that we already
did quite
quite a deep dive in another telesurface
stream that we did
uh on the on the 5th of july on my
channel
we did one where i did
an introduction of all the skills and uh
well what did we do we did so much there
it was a lot of information guys
actually make let's make that this shape
usually
think we need to uh
yes and we have 30 more minutes until
the next stream
uh but that's okay that's okay that's
okay that's that's totally fine um
i i am i am done with the the outlines
almost oh my god
oh my god
you you could probably uh do this much
faster if you wanted to
right you're pretty much done anyway
[Music]
let's go
okay we're almost there you know
yesterday uh we were doing
ttrpg right and in ttrpg i do have an
owl called
and at one point i tried to imitate owl
noises but i was
actually not sure how to do owl noises
but today in that video that we saw with
rinwell
uh i learned how to do all noises so
uh next time if i have to improvise and
imitate owl noises again
i am ready oh boy
when i heard your noises yesterday i was
like
something something doesn't sound right
that was just random bird noises yeah
okay i think that actually sounds pretty
good
this squirt didn't let me hear that come
on
all right all right i'm doing i'm going
in with the color
you sure you can do it i really like how
you
uh use like not black as the outside
outline color i like to i would like to
experiment with that
too at some point i tried it before but
it didn't really look that good
it really depends um
on the relative colors that you use like
if the liner is a bit lighter then
that's like then you have to use other
colors a bit lighter so it doesn't like
overtake
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that is true
takes a little bit of balancing but
okay
i'm just going to go over the edges now
and then delete it later
but if we do this thing should i have it
should it be like
whitish or like maybe this column
[Music]
okay yeah that's cute
yours yours no yours is cute
they're both cute yours is cute
i want to see everyone's submissions
though i'm sure everyone did a great job
drawing groups
oh yeah go check it out after after the
next year
afterwards yeah we don't really have
much time
but i i'm really glad today that i had
you here because last time i was alone
and in the future streams
no well maybe i won't be alone but but
having you here
gave me a little bit of a relief and
i it was nice telling you a little bit
about tails off as well i
hope that maybe it caught your interest
a little bit maybe
i feel like maybe you should try it or
give it a try at some point i was so
surprised to hear you never played it
before
you should i will definitely try it
or tails of a rise coming out soon 9th
of september
i'll be playing it 100 let's go but
uh if you are impatient i would
recommend you to start
um you could totally start with taylor
bezaria because it's the most recent one
but
[Music]
i probably shouldn't reckon
my well my favorite is silly one and two
uh-huh and press area too but
but maybe maybe that's not the best
tails off game to start with what do you
guys think what do you guys think is the
best hands-off game to start off with
before telltale varies comes out
afterwards of course it must be tesla
for rise but
i think vesperia a lot of fans of
brazilia i think brazilian was great yes
yes
oh i enjoyed that one vesparia it's
quite
quite uh i mean i wouldn't make it but
out of all the characters here that i
don't know which one is the main
character uh
from vesperia yeah which one's this big
isn't that yuri or am i mixing up
something
the sparial main character is beauty
right okay okay
that was a great game i started out with
tales of symphonia
which i also think is still a great game
to start out with but since it's pretty
old it's
uh yeah it's not as updated on on the
graphics as
the new games are but it really depends
on what what your taste
is yeah
[Music]
but all these hands off games have a
great story
and a really fun battle system and
really wholesome character
then group dynamics really great
character designs
and oh my god don't even get me started
i'm currently playing tales of hearts r
on my new ps vita
to get into the mood because tails
override is coming out so soon and i
just wanted
to get back into the world again so
that's what i'm currently doing
and oh yeah by the way i didn't mention
this on stream but guys there is now a
link
in the description uh i know a few of
you guys already bought
or reserved the game last time when i
did the tales of horizon you guys were
so uh interested that you guys already
reserved it but
if you haven't yet there is now a link
uh
which is kind of connected with my name
uh in the description you can you can
click that if you decided
like oh yeah i want to buy the game
then i would recommend you to use that
skill uh
link i can't i can't my brain right now
i am on on the it's like a ticking time
bomb right now
okay yes well we should
wrap it up yeah yeah yeah
just jump right into it no problem
oh problem almost done
[Music]
use pre-purchase well i mean i taught
you guys before what do you get what
what do you get with the
pre-purchase some pretty dope stuff
mm-hmm
i bought the i could have used my own
link but i already bought the i already
pre
purchased pre pre-reserved the
one of the ultimate whatever versions
the biggest version
the biggest ever version what was that
version
it comes with a lot of stuff a lot of
physical stuff as well
i just wanted to but does it come with a
accessory for yes
maybe not for food but for the
characters it comes with
outfits like dlc outfits full outfits
not accessories
but but i mean it might come with
something for who
collectors edition yeah look like the
ultimate collector's edition
the insanely big collector's edition
i i don't know the big one
okay yes eraser tool let's go
let's clean this up all right i'm done
you are yes it looks so good
could use it as official official art
official character
you're like oh you know my inaudibles
now works for us
thank you nina my name is for your hard
work
[Music]
so
while you are still waiting for me you
could quickly doodle um
[Music]
um
that's not me
are you saying you decide caught you
designed kotori thinking
of me i mean i mean i mean of course yes
you found it
is that supposed to be me
that's me it's me
i guess you don't remember when you were
when you were tiny little phoenix
[Music]
i gotta i gotta yeah for pictures from
my childhood for my baby
babyness yeah
i don't remember that it must be slander
i don't believe it
i will i will ask for proof well
are you saying that kotori is not cute
he's cute but i was killed as a baby
oh okay okay
okay we are we're done
let's look at this um i feel like um
with more time i could have made it
obviously as amazing as yours hahaha
wink but those are fun to draw
i hope you guys tried drawing some as
well
and i'll be checking the hashtag later
yes hashtag
doodle it's in the title when we
checking it out
post them there and thanks for your
participation everyone thank you tesla
verizon
for sponsoring the stream and bringing
ina along thank you very much
thank you i'll see you guys next week
for
another tales of arise
related stream something really big
might be coming next week
and yeah i'll tell you about my thoughts
of the game
uh tomorrow
[Music]
wait one second
i'm i'm sweating i'm playing
[Music]
was in the chat i missed out i didn't
see it
[Music]
well uh in the end i guess we'll say my
greeting of vida sin and i'll see you
guys in the next stream which starts in
15 minutes
oh okay
sorry yeah that that that's it uh
everyone
and in german we say
[Music]
bye
so
[Music]
you