[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
you can do it again you can do it again
i'll say it again
[Music]
12 times you did not show up in my
stream
i showed up no you were sleeping yeah
that's too late
okay everybody
uh welcome to our first collaboration
actually the first uh
non-id
senpai that kovo is collaborating with
and and we're gonna play portal two
co-op
i i played portal 1 and portal 2
last week and the week before uh
kobo has not really played this game so
i will we we will have to help her and
teach her
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
we will help you don't worry i will i
will carry you
in many ways
[Music]
hopefully afterwards you you will love
me so much that you will not ask anyone
else to be your mommy ever again
uh
i i already love you no
maybe it's just because you're excited
but my chat says that you're peeking
again please use your pinky really yeah
a little bit a little bit maybe i
already turned you down but uh
no no no it's mine like yeah
uh no no oh maybe she's just excited i
think she's just excited i'm sorry if my
my voice is speaking mommy
no i'm sorry no problem
she's just excited she's so energetic
you know you gotta this is this is like
with move ollie you know they just peek
you have to
do
guys it's so perfect because she's the
blue little one and i'm the orange big
one it's not perfect
yeah
yeah really we really complete each
other yeah yeah we do but we didn't
really start uh yet uh so we're starting
completely from the beginning guys uh
let's see uh it will probably be two
streams because i don't think we can do
it in one stream but yeah let's do our
best golf ball favorite animal yeah yeah
i'll do my best and the first mission is
to choose your favorite animal i think
your favorite animal is horse
horse i'm a juice horse
that's a surprise
wrong
why do i use the ridiculous
what what do i care about
these things i want to choose my
favorite animal there was a chicken
there
eh i don't even know what these mean i
think this one is sink i don't know in
english what are these which one is a
good one chad
do you know these
i don't know no
maybe
maybe i n or cu because it's like cu ah
i don't know
what are those a u a u means gold
apparently a g of silver
orange ah what are the other ones i see
cu is copper oh
so these are like medals i guess
i'll go with them
chemistry things yeah
okay i'll go oh hg is mercury cd is
cadmium
c set
yeah that's the only one i knew
okay let's go
gold uh use your pink tool oh
owl
really okay what's your problem gladys
resting choice
well serve your partner's interest
observe it
gladys is the weird lady cobal
you i hope uh
i hope you don't change your mommy
because gladys has kind of mommy
tendencies
yeah the lady who's talking to us she's
like a mommy
nah nah nah you're better than this
mommy
wait what did she
say what did she say i was listening
i see you hello
oh no
yeah
hello
oh why why are we separated now uh
i think we have to
uh
somehow figure out the uh
the game by helping each other uh even
though we're on different sides but
you sure ah i gotta use the ping oh okay
oh oh oh oh i made a portal huh
you made a portal ah can i make make the
plural too yeah with f like point at
something and then press f
ah
but how many i could only make two oh
there we go okay oh
huh
so uh i think we can both make how many
portals one two
ah we can make two portals both of us
so uh
you press the f in one spot and then you
yeah
shut up gladys
i was explaining it to her wow she's
such a
already triggering me but okay we have
the the gun now
oh yeah yeah we have the guns now we can
do it with left click
okay ah left click and right click oh
okay so we do can
we we are able to make two portals
you can make a dark blue and a light
blue and i can make a red and then
yellow cool
okay okay okay
wait i have to raise the
volume a bit okay done
so now
already next area
[Music]
oh yeah you press the button oh yeah
yeah yeah we have to do this
[Applause]
don't tell them my weight okay
okay it's open
right
come up here oh i'll help you yeah yeah
you can make another one
i made a portal on top of your portal
ah your ping tools are valuable
communicating specific locations to your
partner
oh we can use ping
oh
[Music]
can you make a portal over there
um
no no there's the glass
celebrated
yeah there's
the glass it's already oh wait i make
okay we almost had a little brain freeze
moment that would be too early no no no
we have to think harder koval let's see
how smart you are today i hope you're
smart
do you know your iq
i don't know maybe it's below 100
yeah um
my mine is 180
oh there we go okay so put the cube on
this thing yeah yeah yeah yeah
easy easy
[Music]
don't fall into the oh wait there's no
water on your side but that water don't
don't fall into it okay it's very very
ah yeah i see your water there
oh
yeah i think i have to
ah
nice catch orange shut up
but i can't um you know those barriers
if you put the cube through it it won't
uh
it will disappear but what do you want
from me wait i'll give the cube to you
for now
maybe maybe
nice catchphrase
okay
what
and placing it nice
hi
kobo we have to think with portals yes
yes yes
think of portals and with buttons i
opened the i think i opened
ah
yeah you you're barely i don't know yeah
barriers
i think i know okay yeah someone has to
push that button
oh oh no i didn't see that one
wow
for me thank you
yeah yeah yeah that's for you oh okay
i'll press the button
nice
oh i had almost given up
oh nice yeah
did it work
nice
well i think we did pretty well so far i
gotta go into the orange one i'm gonna
bring you into the blue one
yay
okay oh yeah oh oh techno music again oh
wow
what technology yeah
cute i like these robots they're so cute
yeah
but in the actual game you don't play a
robot you play uh a human
yeah you should play the game cover you
need to play if you if you're done with
this one you need to play portal one and
play portal two intelligence training
center human test yes
it's very fun
[Music]
actually yeah don't worry i'll listen to
her you don't have to listen
thank you mommy oh
oh they're counting our steps oh
no
okay so there's two buttons over there
oh
i'm going
you can use something i think and we can
stand on both of them maybe if that's
necessary
oh
where are we going
roller coaster
wow what
wow
okay
this
this doesn't look so uh clean anymore
no cars selected extra courses take
place after the main courses okay
art therapy
we're doing art therapy
art therapy that sounds good oh
sounds just proceeded that this
this assembly chambers
that sounds like they're taking us apart
kobold
what if i ain't in the blue one does
that work
no no okay
okay that's fine i like my color i like
orange
yeah
that's later that's the dlc what what
what what why why how did we get to the
dlc
this is super hard stuff what chad says
that we went into a dlc uh post game
that's really hard wait how do i go back
i don't know it has been 100 000 years
since i just assembled you for testing
remember those
humans found because they're all fine in
fact we solved science without you can
we not go back an artistic intelligence
oh [\h__\h] i wanna go back should i show
you my latest installation oh
we're
[Music]
can you press escape and then uh go to
hub ah yeah yeah
my fault the game led me to to go here
automatically yeah what
that's confusing maybe one day we can do
the difficult dlc but i think for now
for now we're not being brave enough to
the computer yeah yeah yeah
i'm small brain
so we're not supposed to press those
buttons can we just go in here
oh i thought if we stand on those
buttons we can open up this door
ah
okay
nice
now we're supposed to go here
yeah
okay
what's your favorite kind of game
like the genre
ah
moba and fps
[Music]
and from one i know you don't really
like fps games yeah that's true
i think you gotta go there yeah
oh
hold for partner view oh that's so cool
i can see what you're doing if i press
tab
um
i think i understand maybe
um can you can you stand on my button
for a moment
oh wait i need to open up
ah i come
back can you come back here
ah okay
and then
stand on the button
yeah um
[Music]
can you go here maybe there's something
here oh
wait no no no no
to your right hello
i came for the other side even though
the door was closed i'm thinking maybe
what does this do
i just opens that door yeah oh he's
opened it
go for my portal maybe
okay
and then go for the door
and then make it oh make a portal
[Music]
but come back here come back to the
original and make the other second blue
portal
[Music]
yeah that's true i can go here too
fps so much how did how long have you
been playing games or are you just like
new to games
i mean i play
[Music]
you know inside
i have my pc since last december you
know what so i
i started to play pc games
like since january
i've had my pc since i was like nine or
something
you have to go back i think and press
that one button
[Music]
what you had no computer before that
yeah
where
oh wait oh sh ah open up again please
i have an idea uh
wait wait wait uh where was it
orientation
you here
wait i'm confused i lost my orientation
can you open up again
okay ah
okay uh in the back i made a wait wait
open up one more time
okay
oh wait is that gonna work
ah yes ah yes it is okay go for my
yellow portal
okay
hi kobo oh
[Music]
hey you played games in the internet
cafe before
no no
chet says you played games in an
internet cafe
no internet cafe is too far away from my
home oh you guys are lying then how did
you get that info huh oh
okay the buttons will activate something
that's like time limited
and what is it oh oh oh there's another
bind yeah
that one does that one okay x and
dot i suppose there's probably something
up there
uh-huh
that one is
that one uh-huh
ah
yes the moon okay so
so i i think
when i press this
then i may be
[Music]
yeah you see you see up there there's
like loading ah loading
sign yeah something yeah we have to
maybe activate all of them at the same
time and then something will drop from
from above and then we can put it into
this hole okay don't keep that
crazy
i have the ball it looks like you kobo
yeah
thank you looks just like you that's
pumpkin
totally a compliment
that's cool but this will probably get
much more difficult
is your is your mom not gonna be sad if
you call someone else mommy
your real mom
[Music]
she's fine
she's watching us
right now ah
i can't use my hands but i'm waving back
totally
yeah i'm waving waving
oh wait
wait wait no i can wave like this maybe
am i waving
hello mommy hello mommy
i am
very very glad this is going good so far
oh
i was worried that because you didn't
play the game that maybe we would have
some problems
i hate them
i hate them what they're so cute but
they always shoot me
it can shoot yeah not for that one but
once you're like
yeah
oh yeah
so we have to eliminate them basically
you can pick them up if you press e
like
when you're right in front of them
but oh what is that oh cute
uh
but let's see yeah we first have to
oh okay okay
how
how to shoot them with this laser
i think
um
[Music]
are still there oh man
that was actually uh cobu's fault but
it's okay
yeah yeah
you were on the button and then uh you
left and i was standing on it so it
closed and it crushed me but it's okay
it feels nice sometimes feels like a
massage
oh
yeah i am so cute about that okay okay
i will figure this out
this this this is my um
what
oh you pray oh yeah yeah it gives us a
new one
i thought we can now we can only have
one
unfortunately we can only have one but
um how did you
how did you oh we can do it ah wait we
can do it through
ah total
through here
no
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait oh shall we no we will do it
through here
almost almost we have to change the
angle
a little bit
there we go
now
kobo you have to i think you have to
make a portal uh yeah and one at the top
yes
let's go
but the carrots are still in the way
should i just
run there and throw them over
oh then
we still need to get rid of them
otherwise if we walk over there we have
to we're gonna get killed by them
well we can try to kill them with the
laser maybe but
i mean what's the what's the point of
this button
that's a good question cool ah wait no i
know it's okay okay okay
i'm
yeah you saying what's the point of the
button um was important because
otherwise i wouldn't have thought of
that
[Music]
they went up in flames one of you yeah
nice very well oh please continue into
thank you gladys thank you thank you
yeah we did the kind of uh the other way
around normally you kill the robots
first and then you figure out the rest
yeah normally i don't know what you
think you are doing wow
oh that's cool
[Music]
do you know her
thing it's like she likes to do a rock
paper scissors and it's called tsunamaki
junking you know it
i don't know about it
it's like she sings
and she has these uh
streams where she plays
rock paper scissors with some other
members but she uses usually she always
loses
yeah
about that i don't really get it but
okay okay no problem okay
don't worry
no need to understand
yeah what if we stand both of them
i don't know
uh-huh
this looks complicated oh no
oh no what is this all
something like a cube will come out of
here me no no we came out of here never
mind
but
that cube that reflection cube that's
over there we want to bring it here to
the laser
so yeah first of all ah i understand
maybe stun where where i
wait okay
you just have to keep on pushing those
buttons and we'll find a way for me
thank you
and now
is it okay to go here
[Music]
oh
should i make just in case a portal here
i'll make one there
okay don't crash me
oh
[Music]
okay now back
oh maybe
yeah yeah make a portrait i can use my
portal and but now i need to go back up
oh
wait wait wait wait no no you cannot go
back you need to
wait can i shoot portal there no um
i think
uh
[Music]
well i can't really go up there but i
made a a yellow one over there so uh
sorry i have to go back again oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay
i did it i get it i'll go through
oh yeah thank you
yeah
there we go hi
thank you
genius i suppose we probably need one
here
but where does it go where do we want it
to go
uh here
oh
points huh
lou you just love too huh don't listen
to gladys don't listen to her
yeah i'm just listening to you
oh that's it that's good that's good
never had a daughter before this is not
a competition oh now you have one
lou would be winning shut up
it's not a competition okay
it's not a competition yeah
um however
we need um the laser to go to three
different places
also what is this
nice the same cube it's respawn again oh
oh
yeah
ah
okay in case we lose the first one
that's how we get a new one but
maybe we start by activating this one
oh
what the heck oh my god
don't get crushed overall
and no no i'm gonna be fine i don't
understand okay now i make the middle
platform move but i think you have to
jump over the laser
oh
wow
it was very dramatic it was very very
very good
okay let's see let's just get it
let's do this again i think um
a little bit of pain goes a long way
kobold now i oh [\h__\h] wait a bit higher
[Music]
oh now yeah we need a portal on that
side yeah
and the other one
i think you have to go back and i have
to go
uh
ah can you make one where the yellow one
was
here
here yeah yeah ah the other color yeah
and then
i will i think i'm able to go there
alone
okay you make the the dark blue on on
that uh exit
[Music]
yeah you're right okay
big brain
big brains
specified nice teamwork as a concept in
which two or more people work together
usually with a goal of not failing
horribly i don't know when you're trying
to say glasses but i think we're
succeeding
immensely yeah
get that gladys yeah take that gladys
yeah
you know gladys is uh she really likes
to test people it's like her favorite
thing to do so we're actually just doing
her a big favor she's playing with us
[Music]
when you find it we have to think
outside the box scroll
outside the box okay i think
so dark
with the box oh there's something there
down there ah
let's go
insert disk
i don't think we can do that can we
insert this
i think it's just
just a video that always plays
can i push this
oh there's two of them
hold for
done
and you have to press it at the same
time probably
uh okay countdown
what what is that countdown i don't
understand that countdown let's just say
it in discord uh
one
two three
oh
hold the f but
what
wait i'm sorry my my my mom
okay yeah yeah hello mommy
[Music]
what we should press
[Laughter]
three
two
one
um there was a portal wall over there
okay one more time
[Music]
that one's not the right timing oh
oh they did want the disc oh
okay do i have to go for this here again
nice and nice and nice
it's like a frisbee it's so big
well we can run some movies
the only way i can retrieve you is to
violently disassemble you
then carefully reassemble
[Music]
what
what what
why did she kill us
she disassembled us
we explode what the [\h__\h] why we did
everything correctly
it was so mean she didn't very violently
hey why are we back here
there must be something wrong with the
reassembly machine and we did it
correctly don't worry let's see what
happens
[Music]
that's that's not very nice but okay oh
we need to go to the second door
yeah over there uh f
oh
yeah uh-huh
we will learn some things about mass and
velocity
which don't worry i don't really know
what that means either you're not alone
oh momentum oh
okay
uh kobo you do you know the word
momentum
this course wasn't i forgot anything
about physics i will tip i will teach
you if you look at this picture
you see that one right
um let's say you fall
shut up gladys
let's say you fall out of that portal
at the top yeah and then you you fall
into that portal down here
um
that is called
momentum and the higher you fall
the more
um like like okay wait no let's say you
fall out of here and you fall into this
one let's say if it was a pretty big
fall then once you go through this
portal again
uh you will fall like this way
very very far away so that's called
momentum okay perfect explanation
[Music]
i wouldn't have been surprised oh if you
didn't understand it but i see
[Music]
i see okay okay i think let's check it
out
here we already have an example but oh
koppel can you go down first
not into the portal can you make um a
blue portal where my yellow one is
and a dark blue portal there where i
can't reach over there
okay and now i show you momentum
i will help you to get up to the top
you go for my yellow one
i am carrying my child and now you fall
and do the same thing fall for the
yellow one just fall okay
momentum
wow
[Music]
but it will get more complicated
like this is probably also oh no oh no
oh no
i see something here that's where we
have to
fall through maybe
oh dear aha
aha
i'll go there too okay okay
so i think first of all
can you make um
a blue one here
blue
and here one like somewhere uh hi ah
this one this one this one
i think yeah yeah let's see
i press a button i don't know what
happened
what happens
um
nothing happened wait wait um
okay you have to get to
uh
i have to get here wait i have to go
here
[Music]
come i think you have to fall through
this one
yeah yeah i know
i can help you maybe ah
yeah you make the dark blue one here
yeah and then the light blue one here
yeah yeah okay oh god
one
yeah
[Music]
nice
oh she's doing the hard camera workout
we did it we did it
yay you're not humans
robots
we're robots robots are superior anyway
designed to exactly fit okay an edgeless
safety cue next test
yeah since you
don't really
you didn't really play games until
recently you didn't have a pc until
recently and uh i don't think you have
much
experience
streaming as far as i know
but then how did you
just thinking of all the ways how did
you like find out about the whole
audition testing and
my friend just sent me huh like
yo kaboo oh
uh whole life is opening audition you
should try
oh i'm just a genius friend
yeah
that's a good friend
you try my luck
yeah so they they had a good idea that
you would probably fit into whole life
well hmm
what is this
i don't know
masks
yeah i'll jump through that again
are you getting dizzy
that was
yeah i hope you don't throw up
wait okay no wait do that go go there
again
okay just keep on falling
yeah yeah keep on flying
uh uh okay believe me
oh god that's so good
[\h__\h] that didn't work wait uh
fall again
yeah
i'm fine
i just wanted to see what happens but um
it's the right idea i just need to get
rid of these things happy
i come
don't be scared
we'll do it again
[Music]
that was that was funny
i was not on purpose okay kobo
i'm sorry
how do i get to your set what does your
button do
um
and what is this little button
it does the same thing oh okay oh they
just want me oh
oh
it's my turn yeah
boom boom boom
oh god i'm scared don't forget
[Music]
it didn't work i know
no i think you have to
get rid of the upper one
first
okay i'll go
that
[Music]
that was fun
it was like that was that's what you
call
a trust fall
a trash ball yeah you have to trust the
other person and just let yourself go
oh i trust i have to i thought you
spared trash
no no no
no
okay
the best way to build confidence is to
first recognize your insecurities room
three out of eight by the way ah eight
are from mass and velocity okay okay
on second thought we don't have the time
just done how much better is why than
blue
you are very good at being an example oh
[\h__\h] she's so mean she's so mean
ladies just compliment me
[Music]
i guess you would change it's a
compliment
yeah oh we have the same thing again
and i think we want to fall
oh dear
[Music]
oh
what is this
this is getting very complicated
uh
well
[Music]
there's something up there though
portal
oh yeah
good eyes
yeah yeah
okay i'm gonna throw you again okay
okay
[Music]
you press the button i make the floor
you run back maybe what did your button
do ah
oh but wait don't don't don't carry it
through there because the ball will
disappear
uh
i think
um
hmm
nice it's actually done nice okay wait
where does it go again i think up up
here
oh my god mommy kiara i can go up here
what
yeah yeah you can but with the ball you
can't go there because the ball will be
burnt and disappear
the door is open
that i can appreciate the desire to stop
us the eyes open you're done
[Music]
my daughter is so cute
very cute
what's your favorite food
favorite food huh
uh i like japanese food and korean food
for example
ramen
[Music]
oh is it spicy
yeah
yeah there's spicy one and there's like
the
uh normal one
also everybody in the chat says
shiloh si lord galore
hillary is uh like indonesian street
food actually yeah it's a good snack oh
i want you to look at that
yeah yeah
yeah
what is it made out of
it it's basically just a flower
floor i also don't know how to say that
flower
i don't know
that's why you don't know how to say
and and egg
oh that seems like something i could eat
[Music]
oh interesting when you fall
you will fall upwards and there will be
a button and i want you to push it okay
but when you wear the button yeah maybe
first time you just take a look no
pressure
no stress no no no i i i'm i'm looking
at your cam right now oh it's upstairs
it's up there
so you will fall from here like swoosh
and then you ah
okay let's try it let's try okay
yeah it was the wrong timing
okay one more time
one more time
oh yeah all right okay
three two one
oh damn it no maybe the other one
maybe ah maybe the other one
never mind okay i'll i'll do the other
one okay okay
okay are you falling
yeah okay i'm falling
[Music]
now where's the button
you need some orientation first okay
okay okay we'll try it a few times
and bounce and bounce and bounce and
bones
okay
um
three two one
after i push the button here you should
drop the powder we'll make the other one
right here
good catch kobo nice
teamwork teamwork okay
okay teamwork let's go
and oh god
[Music]
good job
there's so many balls
we didn't even have so many
oh
cool i'm so proud of you oh sorry you
can't bring your ball with you
i'll buy you a new one when we get home
really no yeah
okay
hey
let's go
so proud of my daughter i thought this
would be a disaster but so far it's
going really well
it's so smart
yeah
i'm happy to be here
just walk over it
you're like you're my object i'm
becoming gladys i'm just testing you
kobo oh [\h__\h] out okay
i always go first okay so that mommy
doesn't break her precious bones in her
body
oh yeah that's okay
[Music]
but ah okay okay i throw you again uh
yeah
uh leave oh [\h__\h] yeah yeah uh you have
to go back first we have to time this um
when you jump through
say go
uh when i jump okay yeah because i'll
make a different portal
two three
jump ah no jump uh wait wait
okay okay i'm stop stop okay i
now i jump okay
[Music]
let me think
that you fall for here but then you fell
for that one again
i think i'm uh i i i didn't reach that
height
make a portal
while you're falling
wait you would fall yeah but um
no no no i think we need to uh just just
redo
but
no okay okay oh
oh
yeah but ah
can you actually make your own your own
portals here
where i put them yeah
um
yeah and because if i walk through here
my portals will disappear now i make one
here and and where
oh
ah here i see it okay
[Music]
stop hurting yourself
but how do i get to you
now come here
okay okay okay okay
hello is there my hello i'm here
i am
[Laughter]
oh
now
[Music]
um
i think if you walk
through there
your portal will
disappear
um
[Music]
think
mommy brain hurt couple very hurt oh let
me hurry i can maybe i can do this i
don't know
ah
no because yours disappears the moment
you walk through but
maybe oh no now we need to retry the
gary do it again because i messed up oh
okay no problem
that's okay we learned oh maybe i should
have done something here first uh okay i
make the same portal up here
and you make yours over there
okay
and then you fall through
and then you're on the other side again
but then
then
i know how to go to your side too but
oh dear
ah
uh
okay
uh can you make a dark blue where you
made it before
here
no uh here i think i think
okay
or maybe
that's right
or maybe no no no no actually
i know uh i don't know yeah i'll leave
it like that
oh wait oh that doesn't work
okay
oh hello
um
is there something here on this wall
yeah yeah
that means
there's like a
what is that
it's like i don't know this target sign
yeah
huh
[Music]
um i can't i don't know
uh can you
oh
mommy
[Music]
thank you chad
thank you
all right where are we going this time
we're speed running oh oh oh okay i
think first step you go through my
portal over there
and then you will be catapulted over to
that button
nice oh
so much fun we have two people oh
okay but i can't do that no no
now i kind of put myself to that side
now i'm here ah
oh wait it closed again
bye
i think ah damn it ah
there's like two
two platforms where i can make a portal
one is angled one is straight
and
i think
if i know
i um okay ah but that can't be me can it
be me
um i'll i'll go
wait how did i get there before i'll go
here again
and then
wait this door
closes when you get off of the button
right
okay
um
uh go to the catapults
maybe no do we need to shoot through
two two two
to take that cue first yeah and i think
you have to fall uh and then you know
pick it up like when you push the
buttons in a different room yeah yeah
maybe
i think i know okay um
can you make
a
boo
a blue one
here
wait
oh uh
okay i don't know that no that won't
that won't work
yeah i'm probably overthinking it's
probably easier wait we have catapult
right
yeah oh yeah yeah okay
makeup makeup
uh a blue one here
yeah and then a blue one where the
catapult is
um
wait i'm dry i try it should work okay
why am i here then why am i up here
oh you have to clear i got i got yeah
you have the cube so you can put the
cube where the button is i think
but does it go yeah
but wait uh okay okay i need to oh i get
it i get it okay okay
i wait yeah but i don't think you can
put it through the barrier i think it
will disappear
oh
right no cobalt
yeah
yeah it disappears
can i can i throw it up again
throw it up there
um
i
wonder if i
oh glad that you could
um
or if i'm up there to to
to hold it to pick it up
that's how you do it
and
now please push the button so i i'm not
stuck anymore
yeah
thank
you thank you
i'm free
so yeah okay we have that open all the
time now but
i think like
how how how how how how can i
do this when you took no no never mind
we have to fall through this one to get
over to that side but we need a lot of
momentum
but this this barrier kills my portals
how do i do it uh the bear kills the
portal
um i want to
get the momentum to fall but now with
the port with the little catapult
is there any other
i think
and now we both have one of those
moments
i'll test some things
sometimes you have to
test things with your hands
yeah of course that's not enough i knew
that
um
what
and i do
no i'm not sure
but i'm trying
[Music]
ah
can you
yeah you look at it too baby
i'm thinking shooting a portal while i'm
falling somewhere when
[Music]
okay
is actually backstabbing me but i don't
understand what they're talking
oh your chat is backstabbing you
yeah i mean they're telling
yeah they're telling me how
not different things actually but they
tell me how but i don't use i i
don't really understand
ah
yeah you made a portal but i can't go
for your portal
i want to
i want the portal
i want to go huh
what the [\h__\h] oh no no no that's not
really what i why oh i don't want to
deliver
does it get rid of the barrier if i get
rid of the cube
no
no no no no no no mommy mommy
i get it i get it okay now
now it's my time to carry you oh yeah
this time carry me okay
so now
you need to
um
make a portal in your catapult
and go here and i make a portal here and
here and then you boom you you go to my
portal and boom
okay okay okay okay
yeah yeah yeah
cause i fall into yours okay yeah we
needed something like that
noise
yes
[Music]
and now you can come down here
in the red one and here we are hello
thank you kova
humans yeah that's what you look
together strong better than that
isn't it nice when you when you solve a
puzzle and you feel so smart
[Music]
yeah i feel so smart now if you want
more of that you should play portal 1
and portal 2.
okay you should play it solo on your on
your stream
i'm sure your audience will love it
okay that's a nice extreme idea though
yeah i'm sure you think i was giving you
game very soft i i i overcame yes
i already see something so there's a
catapult here
i'm guessing
it will shoot me into that and then
maybe i want to go out of here let me
test
you
and i might be uh stuck
but no okay i'm just investigating
uh okay i'm here hi
what does that mean
oh it opens the door okay
so
where are we
where did i come from up from here okay
here yeah it was a nice intense nice
reflexes yeah yeah
oh i must have almost gotten it
so wait i fell through
i went through the catapult to here
and
while i was falling i guess i made
another one
no i already made before that i made
another one here then i went to i went
over this i think
over that barrier the glass
and then
i made another portal there
i have to think with four portals i
think kobul needs to make some portals
on the other side maybe
maybe
ah
i see okay okay you you have a blue one
there and uh you make uh the other blue
one here i think
yeah i think i think so
now let me come to your side
you're right and then i will reach the
place where i can push the button
oh okay oh [\h__\h] i'm coming
yay
one more one more
oh yeah
we understand each other
are you ready
okay i'm ready i'm coming
swoon
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
we switch it around you do the portals
where i did the portals and i do the
portals where you did the portals
okay first you have to go to the
uh to the catapult first
okay
and then you make one where the
the sign is
yeah
and and another one another one uh no
the dark blue one needs to go kind of
next to the
uh
it should be like somewhere there yeah
yeah exactly
i got it right
did you miss the porno
yeah
it's not on point
um
yeah the dark blue yeah exactly and
there she goes
and uh uh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay we have a big room
oh no
don't fall into the water cool boy it
will kill you
okay
oh
differently okay
what else is there
there's another
nothing never there's another catapult
another one to go back i think
uh here
yeah
oh
oh yes yes yes
what why did you not fall
out
come back cube
oh it doesn't reach
oh yeah i think when okay um
the following thing is gonna happen kobo
you're gonna oh [\h__\h] oh well maybe i
will do it
maybe i will yeah
because i i understand it i think
and
when i fall
through
um when i'm on my way to
this yellow portal yeah you press the
button because i have to catch the cube
while it's flying
i get it okay
oh can't miss i can't just wait wait
wait
no no no it's not wrong
okay we'll figure it out we'll just go
for an endless loop
[Music]
where do i stop where do i stop
um
ah
beautiful
so beautiful
it feels like we're in a circus okay
you're coming here
wow i find something happening
consequence of death
is this even
glad instead this is love
this is not science
beautiful yeah chad what do you think
are we going to are we going too fast or
is this are we going at a good pacing i
think we're so smart that we're
running the game too slowly
yes
we're gonna make a new record
it's gonna be in the guinness
world book of records no in his book of
words
aperture science yeah ever continued
perfectly average that sounds um nice
and also not so nice thank you
okay
oh i think
we will have to push those buttons at
the same time by falling yeah out of
there but
oh [\h__\h] oh my god what what
did you
[Music]
okay you make the same portals that i
did but you know the dark blue one here
yeah
damn right which one did i use here
wow wow oh oh the phrase it feels good
what do we have we have a laser
what is this laser
oh
did i activate that because of the cube
i think i activated that with the cube
because if i get rid of it
oh no it just always does that okay
mommy kiwawa there's something here
here and here okay okay
yeah yeah
um
i i i want to place the cube the other
way around uh and then make it go
through ah portal i know
sorry reflect two cubes
okay we'll place it uh this way
oh [\h__\h]
what are you doing
i
um
this is kind of lower than i thought it
would be
i want it to be higher so i can send it
through
but can we like
lower or erase this platform
oh yeah you're right huh and then the
laser maybe will go through here and we
can send it to go through here
it will probably
uh raise or lower if we push this button
so we have to go through this
catapult
oh look there's the oh there's the
momentum
yeah there's a momentum
i'm not not this is ah
ah
with the catapult we can go through
that
uh
that portal
and then
we want to go
i don't know where
[Music]
what is on the other side i wonder can
we
walk here no
okay
[Applause]
i see what you mean now you probably
wanted to go for the signs
[Music]
oh
closer
we need
to touch
the catapult
oh
[Music]
i'm
i understand nothing but i kind of
understand the thing but i don't know oh
but even if we go for the catapult where
do we go from there
over over the
[Music]
over those uh crushy thingies
no don't yes we have the spirit
believe kobo
it will be like tilted and then shoot
maybe like that i don't know
ah
i think
oh
ah
what if i go for oh that doesn't work
what if i go through here that doesn't
work i thought that was portal surface
ah
yeah never mind i was wrong i had i
thought i had an idea but i didn't
follow my thing
why it gets so close if only there was
like a platform right there
where are you going
chateau
hello no wait don't help me i don't i
want
i want to figure this out
i'm scared of getting crap crashed oh ah
wait i have to hold it
oh
[Music]
okay we don't have much time though
let's see
okay okay
okay what is happening oh my god raises
the platform
okay wait what what what do we do after
it raises the platform i think uh i
think i need to
stand here okay
how high does it go
ah
does it raise you so you can jump down
and get momentum here you fall down here
and then you fall out of here so make a
make a blue one here
and a blue one there i guess
okay yeah yeah okay i get it
okay and i
oh i do something else i do this and i
do
that okay
uh
i wait for the
the crusher
the crusher okay
ready
go
go go go go
okay okay let's hope this works i don't
want to be killed i don't want to be
killed
can
but you think you can if you try again
maybe yeah okay
let's go
oh no problem i kind of saw it coming
but i forgot about it
okay you do that part i guess you have
to put a portal here
and a portal there
where uh
here and there
okay
and i will do the thing that you were
doing if i remember oh yeah yeah okay
okay
and suddenly crash wouldn't that be
funny and that would be funny
that would be something gladys would
like to
do you're so smart mommy phoenix
what did that do and that opens the door
[Music]
you make a portal mcportal here
there's no no nothing for portals here
we have to beam fast
or
what
[Music]
go here and then it opens and then
something
something with the ah
wait kobo i understand you're waiting in
front of the door you wait in front of
the door
i wait in front of the door we will
throw not our bodies we will throw the
cube instead and we wait in front of the
door
yeah i think i think hi is that possible
yeah i think so
we can throw the cube and um
but
i i will
make a portal here and here so i can
quickly move from the
box to
your side oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] that was good
but okay that's enough time
[Music]
display
we should take it i'm sorry
i don't
really much no it's okay and that was i
was supposed to carry you anyway
thank you
is impressed by our genius brains
wait let me listen to her first
totally boring and useless this is just
a thought experiment
just to see how much time you'll waste
thinking about these worthless documents
uh-huh
the correct time is zero seconds okay
i'm glad this tricerato
okay i i wanted to ask you while we're
looking at this
um
you've been
in her life
for one month now
yeah have you gotten used to it
um
[Music]
i guess
maybe maybe
is that yeah i need some some
[Music]
some things that you think are difficult
uh
not really
huh
everything if you have some questions
you can ask your senpai
yeah
and yeah i always ask
uh
from ollie senpai oh you can
ask senpai too
i i wanted to i i want to chat
other senpai's from other friends but
you're shy
i mean besides that i'm shy
what what
what what what what me what oh what what
did i do i pushed the button but what
how what did i do
oh yeah what does that do
you know
up
and then down
it changes the direction
you jumped a little bit later than me
yeah okay
two two or three seconds maybe
okay
go yeah
uh
now oh wait maybe
wait okay okay
wait later you have to jump away later
than that
oh
yeah you jump when i push the button
maybe that's the right timing
and go
maybe that was true
maybe
three seconds after i touched it
[Music]
very
close
i'm sorry i'm not maybe
me i want to i want to push the button
okay
yeah yeah then let's do it the other way
i'll i'll go for this one
and i uh oh yeah it doesn't matter well
down here it doesn't matter
okay okay okay i'll wait for you okay
okay i'll jump
one two
three ago
that was already falling down again when
i was uh
on top of it so i couldn't reach it yeah
i saw you so
also i
will be
uh i need to jump a bit earlier maybe
yeah
okay okay okay
easy piece of lemon squeezy koopa town
let's go
okay one two three
one
two
go go go
wow
[Music]
and now we have the reflection oh
yeah oh i have to hold it again
what what's happening
what happened
what does that do
um
oh it turns red what's happening
[Laughter]
all the fan stops
the fans stop how does that help us
so that you can fall for the fan now
or we need to go there
yeah
because we can draw portal here
[Music]
i can draw portal here but you can go
for the for the barrier and see what
yeah they are
tap
secret room
shut it down forever
wait oh mommy
i have portal here
uh-huh
but there's a portal deleting barrier in
between so
okay i'll try to go here what do we have
here
um
is that that um
shutdown thingy
is that um is that
something where a laser has to go
through because it kind of sucks can you
can you can you uh can you shoot with
her like here
through
the window
oh
i
can't go very high but let me
okay here here um oh here maybe i yeah
wait i have an idea maybe i can send it
for here
and then
oh
[Music]
okay i'm not quite sure
um i need to where am i standing oh
[Music]
i can't i can't angle it lower but can
you move the portal lower
oh no you can't ah wait
i guess i could wait uh
just drop it
it's not low enough
nope
okay no okay no problem no problem no
problem no problem
what about now
it's not coming through
we had it just for a second correctly so
it's shut down
oh
nice opening okay perfect i think i have
to come to your side now maybe yeah yeah
yeah yeah you should go
no
we have to push it at the same time
uh okay one go three two one
go oh
wow
are you
are you sporty couple do you work out
no i mean
no that's why i started working out okay
because when i saw those stairs i felt
like oh in real life if i have to walk
up those stairs i immediately get
breathing problems
oh that's not a disk
are we gonna explode again very good i
can't watch another movie
yeah i know it's gonna call me stupid
gladders
why
they always kill us like that but that
means we have like the second chapter
done how many of these are there chad
we did two of them
and trust me
six humans only have one five
okay we have two out of five or six so
let's do one more today okay
so uh this uh this three third level
gonna be our last around
what
uh
it is uh wait where uh uh how many level
again um chad says five and one uh dlc
and we have two now so if we do one more
then we have three out of six
so half which is perfect because then we
can do the other half next time
okay i see so this is our last level
yeah today it will be pretty pretty long
anyway yeah for today for today
okay okay i'm gonna get up there i need
to go here
[Music]
yeah he makes really good videos
you have a similar name
yeah
i saw our
uh our short video from him ah
yeah
[Music]
um yeah
i don't know if i can
if it's like smart to really buy you a
horse but
if
[Music]
a session to ride a horse at a beach
okay
yeah let's go riding together i miss it
too i went uh horse riding when i was a
child
for like one week but never again
it was only one time
so i want to go to i want to ride a
horse as well
by the way okay this is a bridge
that we can send through the portals
just like the laser see
yeah damn
you can walk through the portal and walk
for the bridge
yeah
wow
that was cute can you say damn again
damn
no the way you said it before so quiet
and cute
i think we need to
send it through
these ones but ah
yeah okay wait uh uh
let's uh stand should we really do this
together
i'm i'm kind of worried um
hi
oh it's close emma's closed
okay can you do that dark blue ah no now
we're too low
a dark
oh
oh yeah wait we just walked for your
light blue one
ah
holding one
that was easy
and we did it together
yeah now we don't think with bridges we
have to no we don't think with portals
we think we're bridges that's what i
wanted to say
okay we have a one here
where do we want it
and when do we want it now
aha there's a catapult
at all
ah doesn't that hurt i have an idea
oh you have to make the portal cover
you have to make one up here
okay and then don't uh later when i am
like up here
you make one down here
i say okay
but not yet stop now okay go
and now
okay
oh
i need a ball
where is that ball oh
you're going to get a headache if you do
that
i suppose has something would do to do
with that uh
i want you to eat
where is the ball is there a butt ah
oh there's a button there you found the
button uh-huh can you reach the ball
there's a button
i can't i am wait um
reach
can you make a border right here mommy
yeah yeah i have an idea i think
one needs to be here
and yeah the other one needs to be here
yes
[Applause]
this is so much fun
okay yeah now you have to help me to go
up
again oh
um
wait
i uh
i fail
uh okay when okay let's oh but wanted to
take away my ball
it will kill my ball
[Music]
oh hi
you're dancing oh damn oh she got moves
sorry uh
i will take away my oh wait what if i
let's leave the ball first
oh no yeah
[Music]
so we can test it out without the ball
so we need some more bridges um
we need a bridge that will stop me from
going uh up there it will stop the ball
from going up there yeah yeah exactly i
guess like that
and then
nah yeah no let's test it so for example
let's say i'm holding the ball
and jump up here in the bunk ah and then
i need
and i need one okay
i understand
oh thank you but i was gonna pick up the
ball
okay okay okay oh you're gonna after i
bunk the the first bridge you're gonna
make a lower one i guess yeah yeah
uh-huh i'll try okay
[Music]
so fast quick reflexes i like it yeah
thank you
[Music]
it's so cool you have a
you you
rode a horse before road ridden you have
ridden yeah
yeah
well a few times
a few times to fail this next test when
was the last time
uh it's
um
a long time ago
yeah i think it's like maybe like
10 years
six years ago oh so long time ago
but you really like horses huh
i like horses you can make a portal over
there
can you make one
um
and then
a a dark blue one
wait uh
i think we will fall uh if we do this
now
can you go back a little bit
yeah yeah
um now
make a blue one where exactly where my
red one is
oh
wait no not quite
oh that was a thinking mistake
i think i think i'll
come here uh-huh maybe
come here uh-huh and
like this
genius we just need the first bridge to
see the the wall where we can make the
portal yeah oh no ah
come on now i made that one we go back
again
oh and then
yeah
okay
[Music]
i think we have to do that again
but where
a blue one here
and a blue one there oh yeah oh yeah no
need to go back okay
you need to make these tests a bit more
difficult
there are no maps for us
sorry i actually have something in my
throat because when i was outside today
um you know sometimes when you when you
uh swallow
your own spit and then it goes into the
air breathing tube and then you go like
you die because of your own spit do you
know what i mean
i basically i couldn't breathe
and now for the whole day i i have uh
something in my throat now and test
plants we tried yeah
just sit there never shine is it hard
does it hurt no it just feels like i
need to cough the whole time
yeah
that's what else would mommy oh thank
you i love you
yeah repeat after me
repeat after yellow okay
are you laughing at me
frankie um
[Music]
oh
i don't think i even want kobo to say
like who cares about
[\h__\h]
we just need more how about your ara
um
wait my i think my
i want to turn on my echo but my going
so large it's not working what the hell
then i i will do it without my echo
can you do it again three two one go
okay
ah
three
two
one
[Music]
no no no no don't die don't kill
yourself because of my ada
stay alive okay i need you i need you we
need to uh finish this course
yeah indeed very much tesco what are we
doing here oh there's a bridge there and
a button
oh yeah yeah
okay
uh
okay i think we can fall down on the br
oh where's the bridge i am
wait i can
can you
can you jump
that was dangerous
okay let me let me push that button and
we see what happens
mama
you can go through my portal the one
that i made over there somewhere and
then you can catch the ball
or it should be
here
[Music]
is up there wait how did i get here oh
no
okay try today
uh
yes
now would you want to push the button
can i catch yeah i push the button i'm
better than catching you yeah
[Music]
okay one more time
yeah nice and nice yes i gotta be
careful but kobo where do i bring the
ball
um
we need to add they're up there yeah
we need a a wall
up
there can i if i if i put it down will
it roll away ah yeah yeah uh i let me
let me let me uh
let me attack the ball let me protect
the ball and you make a portal uh so
bridge okay
[Applause]
one here
and oh yeah that's it
that's it oh yeah and
oh nice
i'm not sure which one is your face and
which
it's okay we already have the portals we
just have to push the button again and
and grab the ball you want to grab it
you can do it
okay
don't drop it again
[Music]
maybe
you're the smartest member in whole life
indonesia
i hope so
now who do you think is the smartest
member in her life indonesia
don't say anything wrong otherwise your
senpai will kill you
i don't know maybe it's only senpai
because
mathematics loves nappies yeah
i hate math oh
okay i'll make a portal
um
can you make a portal here
oh yeah oh yeah
and maybe here
a bit more to the right i think
to the right
but uh angled straight
and go straight
yeah it has to be more straight so it
stops yeah exactly does that work so
okay
but what for
i wanted to go here but ah
can you make
uh the dark blue up here yes cool smart
cool
ah
i see
you know you say ollie knows mathematics
but you know how to program a website i
think that's really cool
it's not really a big deal it's just
it's not really advanced though
no i think it's a big deal
you're sure okay i think i need to uh
somehow
make one
so so that i can ah stop it stop you oh
[\h__\h]
oh wait okay can you make your blue one
the way you made it before
oh yeah oh yeah all right okay
and
almost
almost i don't know what happened today
oh no it's almost okay
wait if you had uh if you didn't get a
pc until very recently
how yeah when did you learn coding
before that
ah i have laptop i use laptop usually
how long have you been studying the
coding
excellent work
for completing or
for for the website i think i just
learned about
it like
[Music]
around
a year maybe a year
can you learn it that fast
i don't think it's fast though i'm i
mean there's still so much i need to
learn about the language
i guess so
but
when i saw your your debut stream i was
like so excited because you know there's
there's hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds of youtubers
so it's normal that some things are like
some people do the same things but you
did something that i've never seen
before
i've never seen someone do
a like a website for their debut stream
that was so interesting and i really
liked it it was very original
like from my point of view i don't know
how to code website so that's amazing
but probably maybe from someone who
knows a bit more coding
maybe it's kind of basic i don't know
but but for me it looked really cool and
it was something really original and
that was really nice to see someone try
something new for once thank you kobul
are you okay
we need to we need to praise each other
there is a japanese saying um
[Music]
to describe yourself uh you can say uh
homereva
do you know
senpai
she uh she lives by that model she has a
song in the original song it's called
home
and it's about
praising someone and then uh getting
better by being praised so she's all
about that it's a really cute song you
should listen to it yeah yeah i have
understood
my song
she's really sweet so by the way
i think
you have to make this portal
after
i
jump up like when i'm up here you make a
portal down here you know what i mean to
stop me maybe maybe we can try
and uh yeah after i'm
up there ah
oh yeah first of all
it kind of has to disappear completely
oh there we go now
yes
okay so far so good what now though
oh
was that even a good idea yes yes yes
yes yes yes
how do i bring how do i bring kobold up
here
uh by
um
maybe you can get rid of your portal by
sending it here
and then
i
ah then i get rid of your portal now
jump
and boom boom
we need one up here
the bridge i think
it would be the dark blue can you make
dark blue up there
oh yeah
all right
oh yeah we just walk through again
this looks like the same room
yeah
all right portal here
and maybe portal there
and then
another one
or we can can we fall ah another one can
you make a blue one
uh like here
and then another blue one down here
but but don't you
i'll drop my dark blue portal
okay
yes yes yes
yes and what yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
where are we now
and now
i make portal here
portal here
wow
and now
and now and
[Music]
oh no make one oh no
oh no i lost the portal
oh no
is that bad
i used the wrong color cobalt
can you make a blue one here
ah
okay and then we go back
to me go back and make the other blue
one here oh
here and then go back go back
this is funny
i like this puzzle there it's not too
big brain it's easy for two small brains
like us
hello hello hello
no no we went back sorry i've had an
optical illusion moment
at this one
ah
make a blue no wait not that that one is
not the right one either is it
draw a portal here in this side
and this yeah
[Music]
wait a minute
hey we're going down is that where we
came from
because the arrow says go down and there
is a portal platform here
ah
do you remember going here kobol
cause i
we haven't been there yet
yeah yeah i think
i think so
should we
should
we i'm scared to make a portal there
i don't want to mess it up
momenta oh my god
oh
okay
i want you to do we have to do that
together
yeah a light blue one a light blue on
the bottom okay
okay ah oh and then we just go
get rid of the portal and we fall
through it together maybe
yeah yeah okay let's try it
okay
[Music]
okay it's okay i i'm gonna die no
no don't die no maybe it's helpful if
you're all ready i see you hello
i see you
oh no because i just
hello ah
because i just um
maybe
maybe don't worry i'll figure something
out um
can i draw portal
i'm right here
um hello i'm already here
wait
no problem speed run
okay but wait did you actually make it
up there to the top did it work yeah
yeah yeah
was i just too fat to go through
nah i don't think we can
we in the portal fit
yeah
so
you
go first
can i
but
i wait here
i will drop the portal are you ready
oh yeah okay okay i'm ready i'll go
you guys remember that meme with that
that people made with hookah and me and
subaru's mama and subaru where where the
parent uh lets the child like tosses the
child and lets them fly can you guys
remake that meme with me and kobo i'm
the parent
yeah
did you just kick it ahead to get my
intention
to call it broken
of course i like this riddle
nice riddle and just keep trying
kind of different from the other ones
i like this one
so cute can you say it again
[Music]
something interesting here once again oh
yeah here maybe oh where did you go
you're still there okay 105
fall through my portal oh whoa whoa whoa
whoa
hello i have the bridge i have the power
of the bridge where do we want the
bridge
wait i'm trying to go here yeah
maybe
what are you doing ah
can i make a bridge for you to catch you
no there's nothing
we'll figure it out
i love him
i can go up there
is there when you jump up there did you
see something where you could build a
bridge in theory
was there something for portals i forgot
what i saw
okay um you go again oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah there's something okay okay
so um
i make your flying portal
or i could i guess you fly too damn it
uh but uh
i make the flying
i dammit we have to get the portal again
we okay we made one bridge
yeah
i'll get the portal again
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i think i understand what
you're doing i wanted to try something
simple similar i think uh
[Music]
we're both so excited to share our ideas
waiting for your timing
i think oh [\h__\h] i know oh okay
you know
you get it what i want to do yeah but uh
i think
i think we can't do it at the same time
uh
and we have to order a little bit of
wrong probably oh there you go see
you're up there now
okay okay
just a little bit of adjustment and now
we make one here
no uh your light blue one goes here oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah hello you're right
okay
oh can we make that jump
okay one two three
we do everything together
all right all right we're gonna make
this
this looks difficult but together we are
a big brain i believe i will first of
all
see what's here
wow
that hurts
uh
not at home
there's another platform here oh
oh oh oh
[Music]
okay
oh
you're making some bridges
i want to
fall through there
where can i make this bridge go here oh
yeah i can but i don't think
i think you're supposed to fly further
not walk through the bridge
yeah i have an idea
i have tonight
okay we just walked in here we can take
some time think slowly slowly slowly
we had something similar before
i'mma try something
oh
trying always
is good
ah
i see
when you're up there
maybe you have to help the one who's
flying or so i don't know
okay well of course there needs to be a
portal here what if um
[Music]
huh
i don't know
i go here again
oh
we
have
had a feeling that maybe we understood
something but
we're getting closer so when i fly in
there you probably
make
a portal but
do we need the bridge i don't think we
need the bridge but you can only make it
with the no no no uh get rid of the blue
one
make it somewhere else
yeah and
now the other the light blue one too
like put that here
the light the light blue one
yeah uh
not the both of them
both of them but i have all uh nah i
will you won't fall
and then because i don't think i want
the bridge instead
you
uh need to uh when i fly up there you
put like for example the light blue
portal
on the platform
and then like
like where
and then yeah
but no that doesn't make sense either
because i can't directly fly into it can
you go up
here
yeah i tried but uh the wall
you know it will stop me here
i can't go higher
but ah
[Music]
ah okay that's for later
on
[Music]
wow
no that's not it
thinking noises activate
yeah we're probably thinking too
complicated
so this is
if i go here
it will just get rid of my portal
ah but
i don't
no i don't know i don't know i don't
know
light blue portal
somewhere
chat maybe do we need chat help
i'm blind
we we we solved so much on our own maybe
one time we can
we can get chat help but
backstabbing time what do you mean by
stabbing time
you mean backseat time
i'm sorry
yeah i know this is this is gonna be a
jump um
this is gonna be a jump and that one is
gonna be a jump but we also have bridges
so what do we do with those bridges how
do those help us use portals to go
around the field
ah
so you go there here
oh use the caterpillar
and momentum here
here like so
you're flying to here
yeah that's what i want to do
but that's what you're gonna do but i
can't make a portal there okay
um maybe i can go there
i i go there to make a portal no but
wait wait wait wait wait can you wait
yeah can you make one there and and on
that side and i just make a button how
do i fly through here ah
why
can you oh do you have to do it while
i'm falling like let's say
no
no no no that doesn't work no i don't
think so wait what
wait um
[Music]
not quite
um
where are you going cooper you want to
make one here
oh yeah
i see i see it okay
now he can't come too
yeah because then i don't go through the
barrier
[Music]
did you get that from the chat or did
you know yourself
i know
[Music]
uh
okay yeah
ah
now i make one here
and
i want to put it where the catapult is
we probably just have to do the same
thing again
like put a bridge here
um
uh
so that i would go down
yeah yeah
something like that but i think with
your i need your like i can't do both so
one person has to make the bridges and
and come up here
can you yeah yeah come come up here to
me here
okay probably
[Music]
and then
i can go back down to the catapult thank
you
thank you
now we need it a bit lower
oh
you need to go back i see it i see
uh okay okay uh yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes
the only problem is will i be able to
use the right color
yes okay
i think you can use the oh no
no i cannot
but i can make the bridges for you from
up here i think i see everything where
so just stopped yeah i just made the
bridges i just tried to not fall down
or we did it in the wrong order um
did we
but i can make i can do the same thing
uh probably
you will
go
do what i did and i knew what you did
go to the catapult
for now uh-huh and i make one portal
here and one portal here
and so now the bridges are mine okay
and uh you make those yeah
uh fall through the first one
yeah uh uh go through the first catapult
yeah now you're there and then can you
go on where are you running below me
are you able to go on on the bridge that
i made
the first one
here yeah and then go here yeah okay
stop stop stop stop and now we bring you
here
i mean i'm not waiting no wait no wait
huh
wait
ah the catapult the catapult
uh back back back
you have to make a portal
and one at the catapult and one like
down down there you know
okay
and oh yeah now we bring you back to the
catapult you go back again wait wait
wait uh
now
yeah and this way we're both
understanding this riddle
because we both do the same thing yeah
now you jump
you ju
yeah should be fine
jump and then you make make it here
yeah yeah that's that's what i did
before
okay okay okay and now
uh make the portal over there first
[Music]
one color
and then come down here on the bridge
carefully
okay
let's go in here
no i get it
it should be dark blue yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
i think we did it a little bit over
complicated but
oh it's
it's okay hard i understand
yeah i think
we could have finished it earlier if you
would have jumped first i don't know the
chat was saying that you should have
jumped first but this way we both
understood both of our parts
yeah
oh yeah
how are you
are we done with that or do we have one
more okay
this is a bridge building i know we have
ah a few more two more flip this
okay
bridge
oh
that was still
turrets are there again okay um first of
all can you make one here
okay and then one here
because now with my bridge we are
protected from the turret
[Music]
they still can shoot me
yeah
we'll find a way
hold it
fine couple i don't know how you died
there come up here uh okay i think just
wait for the timing okay okay yeah yeah
i think you gave them too much time to
shoot you uh wait wait
okay
drop your portal again yeah the the
orange one
ah we need
i i
think we need another wall
one more
can you make a one here
and mommy
yeah
escape escape abort mission nice
ah we need we need one
we need one to block them
there is more bridges up here
maybe
[Music]
no no don't deploy turret no no
uh
can you come back here
and um
where
actually maybe i oh we don't need
we don't need mine anymore do we
so
i put ah
oh
okay but uh
no i wanted
how do we walk over there though
if we walk behind it i know mommy i know
i know i know yeah i know i know you
know i know
i know you know like this
yes
it's michael yeah
someone has to push the button kobo
apples for you mommy
okay i'll i'll get rid of it
yeah yeah yeah that's cool it's cool and
really
at first i'll go here okay and now
you might die
go back
mommy mommy
behind your back
hallelujah
[Music]
no we're just getting smarter kobold
we're learning now we're learning to
think of portals
yeah yeah we're getting genuine um
[Music]
look away look away just go somewhere
else stop
stop shooting
we need to speak
we can feel the wow if you make one here
or here somewhere here
maybe yeah maybe it won't oh you're
right oh you're right like okay okay
and oh
i make one here
and that way we can go up here but then
it will see me
it's okay it's okay i go
[Music]
yeah that's true gladys it's okay it's
challenging i like it yeah we need the
protection
again yeah
it's about timing okay
and
ah we can maybe just
go
let's go let's go go mom
[Music]
mommy just go up here i'll protect you
reassembly ah come ahead and burn for me
yeah yeah
just go up there again
i don't i don't i'm not sure if i
understand
come on just just go let's go let's go
let's go let's go okay
i don't mean it sorry sorry uh the
food is very annoying
once we're up there can you change the
the
yeah yeah that's what i'm gonna do okay
okay
nice
okay okay
and now okay we can
make one here
and one here okay
okay
oh my god
what
happened can you push over the
turret oh no it was the other one of us
huh where are you
and you're still there wait ah i pushed
it over when i flew here
i thought i thought you you're the one
who died
mommy doesn't die mommy is a phoenix
yeah yeah you're immortal yes yes
okay
don't get caught and
we will
figure this out
uh is there a bridge no
it's upstairs
oh i didn't see it how am i so blind
i think it needs to be higher
no yeah
on their height like here
what but still
let's do this
one yeah
yeah
yeah that was one higher
maybe no
no i can't
can you can you push them with the wall
try making one here
i guess
not not a whole door
it's just inside of them
okay
i feel
like
ah is there there's more in the back oh
no
but they look the other way
what even happens if we push that
button
think think
think
think whoa pink
i wonder if you can
send it to somewhere where we can like
splice the bridge
i get two of the bridges but i don't see
anything because there's i can't make a
portal there
yeah
i think so
uh thinking
thinking
let me get that i want to try it
um
what oh what is this
[Music]
we're just putting
i'm just putting the portals wherever
and hoping that it will work
but um
what if i put it here oh
no that's for later i suppose because we
have to catch the cube or the uh
circle later a circle
ball
ceiling there's nothing on the ceiling
then can we just
push that button fastly
you can try we can try uh
do which one do you want to be protected
from
oh hey the other one didn't even see you
that quickly you pushed it what happened
i
don't know
i pushed it again maybe it was the cube
maybe it dropped the cube
enough ah it opened up ah
oh i can hide here i can crouch white
crouch
that thing opened up over there
can you make a portal there
or
uh here
[Music]
oh yeah i can
so
ah walk through it
will you be able to push over the turret
from there where does it bring you wait
i'll i'll test that
no leave me alone
better than you dying
wait we both died okay
because you died your poor girl also
died
uh i wanna see like through that portal
and see what i can see when i stand
there okay okay
oh okay they can't hit me
ah
if you jump down there can you reach the
button maybe can you make a
portal there again up here
don't get killed
yeah
run
[Music]
and i
think i know what to do with that
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait wait uh uh stay
there
yeah
there we go
drop the uh drop the balls again
uh-huh
adamant oh
higher maybe
one
more
oh i see
wow
no no no
not quite oh
i was thinking to
stop them so that you can pick up one
did i pick the cube
too
i mean we can still get it later i
suppose but i don't even know where we
need to bring it i'm kind of still stuck
there ah we just want to kill those
turrets first otherwise we can't do
anything
yeah
can we
drop it on them or throw it at them
when this one goes
ah
can we go for the portal
yeah
i know
push push push the button
[Applause]
i want to get the second one oh there we
go
[Music]
push button again please
okay i push the button
i'm so sorry i am so sorry i didn't want
to do that
how do i get to your side
ah maybe with a bridge
come come here come here oh my portal oh
but
okay i'm sorry can you do it again i was
trying something yeah your portal okay
and now we don't have to ah but it
disappears
oh when it closes ah we need one of our
oh i'm sorry oh my god oh my god maybe
it works
right
okay it stays okay
oh
[Music]
broken easy tests
oh are they broken they seemed fine
gladys
don't put yourself down like that gladys
if you play the game um solo one day you
will
understand
the that voice that keeps on talking to
us much better
yeah
there's a lot of banter and
she's a very interesting character what
a security dvd
[Music]
and then we're done so
yes
okay okay i'll come to you just a little
more
oh
what
what you know that that city in bahasa
is actually a
fan fish
what pet pat
pa papa
pig sauce
um
yes
okay that's interesting do i have to go
through this hole
no way you can't go there what no you
can't
okay
ah
[Music]
we have to bring this ball
ah i think i know if we have to stop the
flow of the laser
by putting a ball in between
oh yeah then maybe the door will open
but the question is uh
if the portal is ah do you see anywhere
to make a portal oh yeah
yeah
i made
[Music]
yes
flying around okay what is this overall
okay we need another ball and put it uh
here again
where the laser is
yes guys guys you guys guys guess what
is this
or flying
online
all right still the bridge maybe
oh yeah bridge
oh
what
can we catch you
oh it goes ah okay we'll catch it here
you can't catch it from there okay
okay i can i can make portal from here
but
it won't fly through there i think
there's another one here
another wall
oh yeah
i see i see
make one here and one here
yeah okay
oh
where'd it go i think you're well you
would be able to catch it there maybe
see when it comes out of the blue yeah
yeah yeah is it close to you
not quite sure how it looks like to you
okay okay
oh eyes are very fine
okay
maybe i can stop
it
once it's uh there's just one one more
thing
maybe
ah mommy mommy mommy yeah mommy mommy
or maybe
you're right okay that that's more
simple
okay
did you think of a more complicated
solution yeah yeah i think more
complicated
oh my god
you think we can do this at the same
time again
okay
count down
three two
one
go
yeah
[Music]
oh wait there's a little bit more a
little bit more
bridge wow thank you for telling me that
it's a bridge i see
what do we have here
exit is over there there's another one
here
ah
oh
what if you walk through there
for the
yellow one
well i can go over there too even
without the bridge
i don't even remember yeah
all right where do we need the bridge oh
oh maybe
like
maybe because
yeah but we need to like fly fly from
here
yeah
and go there
wait where was the first one that you
pointed at the first one
like from here
and we
yeah
i don't know
where do we start ah maybe
ah
hello
okay i see where we're starting that's
what the bridge is for
okay kabul
i think you need to come up here
here
um can you make a blue portal on on
[Music]
and okay
oh yeah and then i guess i can get rid
of
the
we'll have to test it out
but you better go back for safety oh you
can fall down anyway okay
oh it just brings you there okay uh how
about how about
uh
i stop you somehow
you stop me i will stop you not stab you
stop um
perhaps
make up make the bridge uh
sorry can we go back once
okay but then what ah we need the bridge
first here though for the momentum
what if i'm making like what happens if
i do this
oh no that's not it i want to stay there
huh
i know i know you dropped once once you
are up here
once you are up here you drop your
portal here so the bridge will stop you
okay okay yeah
i believe i can fly
i believe i can
touch the sky
oh sure
i'll just make a portal somewhere while
i'm flying
but i'll jump after you jump
okay you
just make the portal and the one there
right okay
okay oh
it's two it's not enough
space
i was not gonna oh
[Applause]
we'll figure it out we'll figure it out
like what i bet oh wait i think maybe
maybe i know
maybe i know maybe
you know there's two platforms oops [\h__\h]
that's the wrong one
backpack
there's two platforms right
two um back here uh number one and
number two
one is for you one is for me
one if we jump at the same time meet in
the middle and stop each other
that's crazy but
uh you yeah you wait there because
when i make
uh i'll make a port yours is fine yours
is fun you'll just fall into your blue
one and then and you get out of the
light blue one i will
have to be faster than that are you
ready
uh
wait you're ready just believe in me
trust fault trustful
okay mommy just fall into your hole and
everything will be good at the same time
okay
just stand stand right in front of it
then stand right at the top of it
because the the bridge will disappear
three
two
one
[Music]
there was nothing else that we could use
to stop us so we just used our own
bodies
[Music]
he's going to kill us kobold
okay at least i got time to watch
together with
you before we die yeah
and we'll be reassembled gently anyway
five thirty three forty one eighteen
[Music]
did you like the game
yeah yeah yeah it's very fun mm-hmm
[Music]
maybe i think it has a very big
satisfactory uh
satisfactory
satisfying effect
if you play it alone i think it will be
a bit more frustrating
but i i still want you to play it um
one day when we are done
i i i definitely gonna play this too
to uh you know practice my small brain
yeah yeah
it does make you feel smarter after you
finish the game then you're like oh wow
i did all of that i figured that out
damn i'm so smart mama
yeah and if you need help you'll always
have chat they love back seating or
backstabbing they love both of that so
you can always get help from them but
don't play it alone before finishing the
co-op with me now because we started
this we have to finish it
[Music]
maybe we can continue either next week
or the week after that we will have to
see how
our scheduling works but let's do it
soon because otherwise we will forget
how to think of portals we have to
remember
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah so happy that i i was able to
collaborate
yeah
you're so cute
i love my friends i love you
the first time i'm voice chatting with
yama senpai i'm crying
yeah she i'm really happy the moment she
came into the voice chat channel she was
peeking and screaming so loud
i'm sorry for my broken english no it's
fine we completely uh communicated fine
i think completely perfectly fine
everything was fine i understood you
and as you know
as you know my english is
not the best ever because my first
language is german did you know
ah
[Music]
no that's french what this is
is
sometimes you make uh mistakes and i
make some mistakes like that too
sometimes
okay what is that again
thank you
wow i'm a german it's actually when i
read super chats i always say the name
and then i say thank you so i say uh the
game recruit
and so
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're so cute i i don't know how to
kobo kobo have you ever been to europe
before
my what have you ever been to europe
rap
up you're rub
rub
what can you spell it
rub e u r o p e the continent europe
euron
how do you say that in indonesian
uh europe oh oh
you're saying europe indonesia
in indonesia we call it europa
oh it sounds like it's very erotic um
come to the erotic continent
wait to have you have you been before to
europa
yeah i haven't been
outside my country at all never
at all i even have a
passport when
planned just wants in my life
oh but within your country inside your
country
yeah
would would your mom allow you to visit
mommy kiwawa would your mom say yes
you are the
does your mom not let you go alone
can you come to me
i want to i want to come to you i mean
yeah yeah my mom should approve really
really
i'll take good care of you
i'll protect you yeah yeah
i i
asked permission that she have to say
yes so it's okay you have to travel
around the world you have to see
everything kobold and you have to go
to see all the horses all over the world
all the horses yeah
yeah yeah
absolutely one day because i i want to
meet kobo one day it doesn't have to be
in my country we can also i can fly to
uh your country i can fly to indonesia
i can go i wanted to um i went to i
wanted to go to a body
bali yeah i haven't been to bali though
i want to try
cali
let's go let's go yeah
i think it's a good idea uh yeah yeah
yeah oh my god i'm so excited
yeah yeah yeah
when you're like
embarrassed or excited you
act uh very strangely but um
funnily
i'm sorry
let out that yelling aggressively very
good let it out let it all out very good
you need to let those emotions go
otherwise they will be inside of your
body and you will explode one day yeah
[Laughter]
kfb what do i do she's so cute can we
adopt her i want to adopt her how do i
adopt her
i want her
okay
yeah i will i will let you go now but we
will see each other again to play more
portal too okay promise brown and pinky
promise
miss pinky i promise
let's do let's do something here
everybody for watching us uh kobe's
channel is in my oh
cute
kobo's channel is in my description
she's a new member joined one month ago
so if you um if you didn't subscribe
yeah you should subscribe to her channel
okay okay
okay yeah yeah yeah and subscribe to
mommy kiara
so
[Music]
can you
help me say my ending greeting in german
do you also have an ending reading
my opening is also my ending oh okay
okay okay
yeah how's your ending my ending is and
in germany we say alf peterson so
there's a german part again i say
goodbye in german
yeah i want i want to try yes it's alf
auf
exactly so i'll say and in german we say
and we say together auf wiedersehen okay
wait wait wait wait wait i still uh just
just out
yeah you just say auf wiedersehen
auv doesn't okay like that well yeah
exactly
and in german we say
[Music]
thank you for watching
thank you thank you
more importantly soon
yeah more portals yeah
okay okay i'll go to my ending screen
now you can also say you're ending
ending greeting if you want
okay hey
[Music]
do
uh
guys do you know
uh if we leave the game now will the
progress be lost because it says exit to
main menu your partner will be
disconnected in progress for the current
test chamber will be lost what does that
mean chad
what does that mean it will save
it's saved yeah okay because that text
is kind of misleading they mean with the
current test chamber what does that mean
it auto saved okay okay thank you guys
thank you
see you i think tomorrow is a day off
for me but i'll see you guys the day
after
[Music]
bye bye love you kfb
bye bye
[Music]