[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
audio check audio jack
um I'm listening to Mariah Carey
Christmas Eve oh baby yeah that's what
you're listening while talking to me
yeah
this song
all right getting in the mood it's
already Christmas time totally give me
some of that jingle jingle dopamine
Mariah yeah it's time it's very fitting
indigenous I I mean I still have a
Christmas uh what do you call the round
the things you put on on the door on the
table the wreath yes I still have a reef
but it's like really dry and so if you
touch it the needles will fall off
what's wrong with you why why is it
still there because cute and I'm at the
face well I um I made it by myself with
fresh like a tree part
and and so I then I decorated it it was
all on the stream it was really nice it
was so much fun to decorate it yeah I
mean it almost this smells amazing too
now it's dry but I I thought but I don't
want to throw away the whole thing I
just want to take off the decorations
before I uh throw it away and I never
got to do that because I'm a lazy piece
of [\h__\h]
no you're just prepared for next year
you're gonna be like see
it is I'll just um some add some
tree Refreshers
no please don't hang those
you're gonna touch it and all the
needles are gonna nobody will post it
and they're gonna fall off no nobody
will be allowed to touch it it is it is
Untouchable
um scent of car Pine yummy yeah wow
hello by the way everyone hi welcome to
my bed's still made from the last time I
was here
it comes often here I have prepared
slippers for gouda I've prepared uh
snacks for good I've prepared a bed with
with the cat toilet uh let's go smells
like me here it was so it's just since
the last time I was here there wasn't
that much time until you
yeah with not much time to work
did that come out I feel like I had
trouble with English then I feel like I
was just here it still smells like me
but maybe it does maybe I smell like you
know maybe what do you maybe smell like
uh dust I don't like dust I think I
think I must have had this like hoodie
on the floor and now I smell like dust I
mean I'm not wearing a hoodie I'm
wearing my hair
it smells like let her smell your cat's
tail
eh and they like you know when your cats
they walk around and they they stick
their tail like all in the cobwebs and
the dust and stuff you smell it when you
smell you're like oh you smell you smell
like a Dust Bunny kind of like that that
doesn't make sense to us but he liking
Sims they have dust bunnies in Sims 4.
but no no my cats don't smell like dust
no oh oh okay
weird
going on here
we got the game to work guys we prepared
preparation what did you ask me even
before the stream got up what's up
it's so obvious
picnic
no no it sounds it sounds like an
onomatopoeia onomatopia
no it's a Pico Nicholas picnic in
Japanese
no but I've always wanted to
I I want to go picnicking again we
should do it we should do a cute one I'm
yellow bean by the way yes she is she is
yellow should I write that I should
probably write that down somewhere
otherwise you guys will have no idea
I'm the creepy yellow
beanies
[Music]
yellow and red
and this game I know maybe you guys
don't know what it is well we just you
know we're just hanging we're just
having a picnic I guess in this game
and we're we're trying to get through
the world
and we have funny legs
[Music]
wait how do you kick again this
I love the sounds I said okay guys this
is baby okay
you're stinky
no no just kidding just kidding
[Applause]
kick
how do you kick why is your leg so long
ow hey how do you how do you do that
[Music]
you can't even tell me how you're doing
it
is
we're playing with okay wait help me get
this box oh how would I do that
let me jump on your face
[Music]
why do we need a box
is there something here too
there's nothing high up there too I just
saw it up up left
oh this way there's something there
what's there
I'm so bad ah you this is
so wobbly
wait there's nothing there anyway okay
but then I'll take the comfortable way
what the
nice fall I bet you I could walk up a
wall like this oh oh okay what do you
mean ah egg is the payback for the
kikori kicks yeah
last time I was able to kick this but
now I can't how'd they open us do we
need both maybe the time it double kick
okay double wait okay let me jump in oh
not me
Moana
ah I don't think we can kick it at the
same time
[Music]
um
um oh maybe we yeah
I won't hurt you maybe as ball no
wait maybe we have to use the Box
now we have two boxes and one stone when
we do that we're hoarding now we're
Hoarders
um
it is no never heard of that no no it's
called it's a thing it's a thing isn't
it guys channels would you say your
hoarder
no um
yeah if you don't like me as a hoarder
I complimented you thank you
minimalism is to do anything I think
oh did I like I maybe screwed us do we
need the boxes
no
let's go this way awesome yeah let's go
up up up if we can because maybe huh
it's better wait maybe do you want to
jump across here jump up my head
no no
I said jump on my head cause you gotta
get up here I wanted to help you get
over I thought I could just let make you
jump kick me in the chin
bling
I think the problem is actually keyboard
is more difficult thank you
keyboard's difficult yeah
can we make a jump
no follow me this way oh
[Music]
yeah yeah
button of course that's why the button
is there button oh my god oh
obviously close it
okay okay I just wanted to see what
happens okay I thought they would smash
it but I guess again the game is too too
child
um child uh what what
sorry
I don't die here either okay I'm gonna
go for a swim woohoo
oh wait have you been playing Zelda yes
do you like him
is it good uh the thing is I never
played breath with the wild have you
played breath of the Wild
um for a moment right
um I only watched like full playthroughs
of it
um so I knew the story and everything
um and now it's like tears of the
kingdom and it is quite fun yeah yeah
overwhelming a little bit but fun
you're like familiar with all the
controls though and the maybe the
environment as well
are you gonna play
no probably not why not I don't have
interest you are you scared of
commitment for such a long game I don't
know 999 corks
look at those I'm not getting those
either I don't know whoa
what x that's for for a controller right
let's control it I'm so good at this
game
what's my input
[Music]
it was
me good I had to say
c a r i b b e a n Caribbean that's how I
say it too
but then if you're saying the title the
movie title pirates of the that's the
Caribbeans
oh no I also say Caribbean there but you
know I noticed I was watching
hotels hell from Gordon Ramsay oh good
taste I love that show I got so deep
into that and then like uh there's like
this hotel that has the Caribbean
Caribbean uh as a theme and so Gordon
Ramsay is like
your your hotel is themed after the
Caribbean and she said yeah the
Caribbean and he says the Caribbean
but apparently some Caribbeans also say
Caribbean so I'm confused now I thought
it was like a British thing I was just
like well he's British so let's take
what he says with a grain of
it so you watch
so too right
yeah oh my God have you noticed there's
a what is this problem with Gordon
Ramsay and always wanting to show his
butt
uh
um I've noticed this English chefs do we
have any chefs here today maybe you can
oh
do chefs want to show their Bots
generally they have big eagles chefs are
always so like have you noticed uh
speaking of who
maybe it's just a a product of over
dramatized television made for America
what's that so many of the chefs on the
Gordon Ramsay show Kitchen Nightmares
they are so I'm right and you're wrong
even though you're here to help me and
that's final it's like why are you like
that he's there to help you nobody I
feel like that's more like less the
chefs in in hotels lesser chefs it's
more the hotel owners who are always
like I'm doing everything right and uh
the people who are in the wrong are all
my employees even though I come to work
uh drunk or even though I waste all my
money on big luxury cars and no money on
the hotel
Etc it's the yelpers they're they're
they're they're targeting Us in in uh
yeah something like that I don't know
yelperson in the review writers
oh yeah maybe Yelp is just red no no you
can do Yelp reviews online yeah thank
you sorry thank you sorry
we're playing a game oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh
dab I'm sorry
thank you
uh yeah anyway I thought it was really
funny and and Gordon Ramsay it always
shows this freaking butt he always they
always include a scene where he goes
into the shower of the hotel
and is it a European thing
no no it's a Ramsay thing oh wow how
does this open up I don't know why
didn't we go up here anyway when oh
we didn't have to did we
I guess not weird how did you fall down
there
oh without submarine moan you're back in
the water I'm gonna submarine
man
I oh my my life to distant let me revive
it
hey what color Xbox controller do you
have
I don't have an Xbox
[Music]
should I have it because it comes with
Uno
and I have Uno so I mean I should get
the Xbox One
no I was just I just wondering
I use PS5 controllers when you play with
controller uh yeah usually ah unless the
switch that I've used the switch
controller well oh yeah
the other day uh it looked like it was
your colors like uh peach orange and
tealy blue
welcome
thank you I'm in the intestines of the
Beast it was pretty cool though
the intestines and that that's the the
what's it in what's it in English
you know everything looks to me like
um like uh
in a lot of games I always say a uterus
do you have this problem too
[Music]
a what a uterus
a uterus you the best part of you
I see a Universe like everywhere but
like I feel like you know my viewers are
like making fun of me for seeing one but
if you if if they would be honest with
themselves I think they would agree with
me that there's a uterus like everywhere
[Music]
everywhere
[Laughter]
oh
this is just one of the things that we
will have to talk about in girls talk
next week
uteruses yeah for example whoa girls
bangs yes so good I will be on girls
talk next week thank you
because of the ball there we go I heard
him too harder
oh [\h__\h]
I have to do it on the other side now
yeah uh yeah
yeah good I was really excited to be on
girls talk just I am turns out you are a
girl so believe it or not
true
this is true I talk about like
brands uh like yes we can talk about
anything
bags and stuff like that okay I have
stuff I want to talk about I'm gonna
skip you guys can talk about it too
didn't you open this thing up here
before for me how did you do that
the upper one didn't that open one I'm
sorry I'm distracted
but I feel all the way back
uh where was that
[Music]
this one opens the blue one yeah this is
not open maybe I go this way
no that's too far okay
what's with the ball
or something
okay can you open the blue one again
take it away
okay
want to go up or down
you go this way okay
this is satisfying it is
reminds me of Poptropica up or down what
you go down wait I have to go down to
there's a ship waiting for us and we've
got two little holes for us
for the beans
is this a sign that we have to eat more
of those jelly beans sorry
[Music]
amazing 15 minutes
fine no I think that's pretty bad
high five with legs cute my toes
my first impression is also funky wow
[Music]
um
I guess one of us has to go because how
else ah maybe you can get the ball from
the top so you go first
wait
I'm still confused with these new legs
yeah
what yours open
s you well I get your ball
oh thank you thank you
and also ball here okay
oh the music
okay
[Music]
yeah run
me run go go go
sorry Buddha short-term memory
very short time memory
[Music]
um
send me the Bowl here is ball
take ball
you Coulda did you ever hear about my
plans of
um becoming the now we come in the
German or Austrian act for Eurovision
song contest
while that you just mentioned that I was
just thinking about that
apparently uh right when we started the
streams when Eurovision song contest is
like uh going in its finale today
oh
uh yeah so I was thinking about it
because last year I attempted I signed
up for the German one
because I fought you know in Eurovision
song contest people who don't you know
know it they won't understand but it's
like the crazier your act is the more
successful it will be and uh I thought
then why not oh why not go for v2 bro
that will like be absolutely crazy and I
don't even want to win you know it's not
about winning it's just about being
there and and maybe
at leaving a big impression getting us
on the big news but so they didn't take
me and I couldn't sign up for Austria
because
uh it was too late they kind of did it
privately some countries do it privately
and some do it publicly oh there we go
there we go
on an incredible opportunity yeah
[Music]
really cool they're not ready for it yet
that's what I think it is I feel like it
would have been also a little bit
embarrassing and stressful so maybe it's
for the better that it didn't happen ah
thing have they ever had a digital act
before
yeah not like that so I thought it would
have made history exactly
you know what's really crazy
um the last time an Austrian won the
Eurovision song contest was Conchita
Worst have you ever heard of conshita is
it worst like uh
sausage yeah
is this you know lady who sang as their
Eurovision winning song
Rise Like a Phoenix
yeah that's that's the song and
that's unconnected that the next winner
should be a phoenix
after that Austrian winner
I mean yeah of course it's fate it would
have gone Circle no full circle baby I
wouldn't have won probably but maybe
oh well I would have the entirety of
home alive backing you up yeah maybe I
will try signing up again
um for the coming year
maybe sometime they'll come to their
senses and realize what an amazing oh
sorry opportunity it would be oh I don't
even know what we're supposed to do with
this ball
I think we gotta land it
uh up here left wait what song would you
have sung
we would have done do you because like
Kira the producer even already made me
like a short version because the song
has to be under three minutes so you
sent him like you have to send in like
an audition and everything no not really
just a demo or like a finished song
um yeah
something no video done
yeah oh oh okay wait what was the left
button for again
is it for the water on the right side
because then
if we just turn off this water
wait how did you turn on
[Music]
turn off oh is it just is it that button
it's this button it's this button wait
what
wait wait
how do we get the very right water to go
there's a
little bit
somewhere else
I thought we had to uh
uh do that
and you get it to sit here
and then somebody
yeah
ah okay okay
[Music]
no I don't understand though
kick each other no I did any ball kick
the ball and then you go
maybe six I did the kick
I don't want to kick it too much
yeah but that thing the only thing that
that button does is turn it turn that
thing around the teeth no
yeah
why do we want that now wait maybe we're
missing a button did you check oh yeah
we did oh yeah I saw that button I
thought the if we get water sprouting
out of the very right one then we can go
over there
but
I think that wait I don't get it
[Music]
we're missing something
oh
okay wait we're doing some sick jokes oh
oh oh oh
what is I'm trying what is your end game
you thought that we could kick it up
here to this other one oh wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait yep
no
wait jump on me
jump jump on the one who's on the ball
we're like in a circus now
okay wait
wait wait wait Release Me oh wait
release you
and then I'm gonna push the ball in you
want the ball there
I think you will just have to push that
button yourself no with a kick
wait you have to kick it
[Applause]
we will try to get the ball up there
let's do it or or you try it try your
you first
and give it a nice kick
firm cake wonderful
oh my God that hurts
oh no no no
ah yeah we need the ball I guess
Frank is in the bowl push it up again
heavy it seems weighty oh yeah please
open up again wait
oh
is there like a what is that
a soft block
I do anything wait keep going to the
right
ah there is this but no that's not
related
oh
um
the problem can we restart the level
should we yeah I mean
I can
I mean we did pretty quick
oh no
let's not do that again
Let's Roll
I I get ball I think please fetch me
ball I'll bring ball oh you know maybe
maybe it's good you're not playing pears
of the Kingdom why because I saw your
cans even you can't pet the dogs
oh and they have cute dogs
really cute dog but you cannot pet the
dog but it's it's like it turns around
on its belly and it's like
and Link just stands there looking at
the dog with such cold eyes like he does
not give a [\h__\h]
Nintendo
what you're doing 10 dogs
oh my God yes it was my first game that
I had on the Nintendo DS
uh but I also played it yeah which one
did you have uh the labrador doodle One
um
which one did you have I had the
dalmatian one oh
Dalmatian and Friends
even though I wasn't even a dog person
but wasn't there a nintend cats but it
wasn't so good as the Nintendogs I think
so I think it was it was not definitely
not as good wait it's funny you
mentioned that because sometimes I'll
just listen to the the walkie song when
you take your dog for a walk in that
game and it's really quite nice
[Music]
it was a wacky song
away if your dog starts eating garbage
on the side of the road
ball number one
what do we do with it uh
not the not the thing that we did before
because that would be a problem
[Music]
it's like a like a logo from a certain
website to me
anyway not anymore
sorry that was me possibly
wait so now we
[Music]
um
we keep the ball over here and then
one of us first must go up with the help
of each other that almost made it yes
I got it I'll go up again okay okay
no
keep on balancing wait you know we look
like what what we look like those beans
that we ate the jelly beans good that's
what I was like when I when I went into
this form I said uh you know with the
boat I said we will have to eat more
jelly beans oh
I didn't oops sorry it's
um
people that that is totally why I chose
this game because I saw the reference
that is exactly why I thought we have to
play it
I think I sent you the somebody made a
really funny edit of all the the parts
of that stream I think
I saw it no
let's go oh
it was a good stream
good one very exciting very much
throwing up was you telling me okay
after that
I think so but I think my breath was
pretty horrendous
as long as you don't uh
as long as you don't follow up on that
kissing a prompt I will know it will not
be a problem right you know
but if you and I if we if we I mean we
would smell the same so anybody it may
as well be somebody that also smells
like vomit and dog food
[Music]
wow it's not working wait maybe we need
balls hold on release
I'm not going
simple game design must be easy right
we had it no no it's staying open
already though
don't you need the ball to I don't know
is it how do you come up here oh there
you go oh it's already open oh oh my God
sorry
what is this how do you keep on pushing
it a test of strength of which neither
of us have
this time how about you go forward and
and I will do the other stuff
huh why are you oh you someone yeah you
you go on I I try I don't know whatever
else
oh dear okay aha yeah okay I think
someone goes up with that thing huh okay
turn it up
[\h__\h] turn it again
turn it again
amazing
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm sending the ball but where to where
to oh oh oh
uh what the [\h__\h] where did that come
from
are you supposed to get it all the way
oh maybe you're supposed to get it all
the way oh dear okay
[Music]
no
um
no I will send it up again no worries
[Laughter]
I
disable Unthinkable oh my God it's
amazing what
okay okay so I wait no that is maybe
really just no I realized that the ball
doesn't have to go anywhere it just has
to go away from the button well you have
to jump
okay the worry was for nothing you still
did it though you got it all the way
back
I'll become a soccer player now
are you able to come up here I am you
made it right for me oh wow
you sound like Mario oh God
no did you uh
[Music]
waiting to watch it with the I'm waiting
for it to be on the streaming services
forever no go watch it in the cinema I
will otherwise I will go over and and I
will triangle you
actually want to laugh with some of the
memories
movie yeah because I wanted to laugh at
it nicely respectfully of course it is
so good I liked it so much
do you like Jack Black
I guess
you will love the special scene that he
has in the movie you will love it
he has he's Bowser yeah he he
prized me he surprised me I'll just say
that
um I'm trying to figure out what I'm
gonna do here
I'm exploring wait what do we have to do
ah there's a ball
I guess oh
oh
okay yeah I passed now what do we do
about you though
ah wait some tells me
yeah
and now I'm here
was that huh what we wanted
what how do you how do you uh-huh
let me check again
it must be
um
maybe to the right
oh that seems pretty far
with
no there's nothing here
huh
it's probably very obvious
oh wait
oh
uh
show us your big brain skills
wait what is it with
the emcee of your your school show hmm
so you should that's smart
no that's actually exactly the reason
why I am the MC so I don't have to do
anything I have problems
[Music]
by the way are you ever gonna do that
show again
uh yeah because I want to tweet I can be
there too
absolutely I wanted to tweet because I
hadn't I've had like so many ideas to
like for the modifiers but I feel it was
kind of kind of scrambling like I had a
good base but I just needed to
tweak it a little bit more
let me show you how smart I am
not are you smart no no
I think you could do it I cannot pretend
to be smart anymore ah but maybe if we
figure this out we can be a little bit
smart
well I got through
um who didn't get through so what does
that mean that I have to leave you
behind
no maybe I can slingshot myself can we
like hold hands
[Music]
no
no oh
there's nothing to the right
I'll check out some more
oh no I just I swim endlessly what the
hell
what is this
is that do you know the switch game yeah
it came with the it was like the first
switch game clip you're like scissors
um
cute I mean the style yeah but the
gameplay
um a check chat uh balls the blue button
let's get get the ball to the Blue
Button can you do that because it's blue
oh God I get it now you get it the wall
is blue yeah so the blue oh
God okay
so difficult okay
[Music]
yeah sometimes the very obvious things
are not so obvious for the people who
are supposed to see it streamers though
streamer eyes we need glasses get so
chatty everything else kind of just
mushes
[Music]
okay okay what are we dealing with here
huh
we have a blue two buttons two blue
balls three blue balls oh
freeze free balls uh okay easy
[Music]
that doesn't matter you just need some
weight on them
you just need weights oh nice nice
teamwork okay
next
um how do we one of us has to go up
do you want to I'll try
you can do it
kick me oh the accent I'm still
unfamiliar with the controls trust me
believe me
why am I sending it there why am I why
am I doing that I sent it to the left
but you can you can set it to the left
right yeah yeah
yeah yeah
[\h__\h] no we can get it back don't worry
don't worry it's easy
okay
put that my screen from laughing
oh
my God so I'm getting in your way I'll
let the kickery do it no no
no you're kicking you do it
you got the controller the Xbox
controller it's blue
do you even ever use your Xbox do we
have an Xbox or just the controller I
got an Xbox but I found that Xbox
controllers are just easier to use PC
I've heard me
oh yeah
come on
I'm so sorry
that was really good you can bring it to
the left or to the right your choice
um
I'll bring the next one meanwhile
take your time go to Taco Time ah [\h__\h]
Taco Time single time do you know who I
look like
have you ever seen Gumball that show
Gumball Gumball no I think not I look
like Darwin
Darwin from who is also a fish
that one is unreachable no maybe from
the very top what the hell
first go through is that necessary yeah
you stand on there I'll check I'll check
what's up
bling bling bling
a gift box I checked
I feel like there's no there's no
present here Gordon no no there's
nothing here you're serious no no
oh well I guess oh what is this
wow wait it's not a hat we don't get
hats no no
[Music]
okay next time I fall in a way that I'll
fall to the right side
be easy I was gonna say something
[Music]
that's difficult
ah
the present I think you're right after
well it is Christmas
oh thank you that's why there was a
present
for sure all right well when I want to
talk about Christmas when I say
Christmas what's the first smell that
comes to your mind
ah I guess the tree scent tree what the
[\h__\h] I can't wait
me wait jump on my head jump in oh okay
I have an idea
yeah that could work oopsie sorry
actually okay when
um
[Music]
wait you try
what
wait John
I am honestly impressed wow that was
incredible
all right all right too many there's too
many it's like circles that clown sounds
you're like clowns but clowns I don't
speak to that personally but oh they're
all right I guess okay sorry I'm getting
confused with my legs
oh I brought it back okay sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
also I think of gingerbread cookies oh
yum yum yum yum
[Music]
no come on
be the ball
like
I'm sorry you got excited that was cool
it was really cool it was cool and I
ruined it I'm so sorry no nice headshot
do you know what do you call this in in
soccer language you don't call it a
headshot do you
coupler
yeah
wait is literally just a header
well it's pretty much the same in German
so I guess that makes sense
okay okay
this is enraging I use the bath bomb
last night what is it a gingerbread bath
bomb no it was pink it made the bathroom
pink but there was like a rose in it
that was supposed to be like oh pretty
roses but it was like jelly consistency
and then it didn't like dissolve fully
in the bath so it was like it looked
like big what I would imagine big thick
skin flakes or scales that were squishy
so like as you would sit in the water
because they didn't dissolve it would
like tickle my back
you continue
music yeah it was just uncomfortable
because it felt like there was big
flakes of something squishy floating
around in my bathtub that it could be an
itchy it's kind of gross but anyway is
it from large
yeah I think I know what you mean I've
had a bad phone from Lush before that
has this like squishy stuff inside yeah
it's kind of weird it is
enough
[Music]
[Applause]
we go Happy Beans let's go it took us 20
minutes even though it was always like a
run through okay that's okay maybe it
counted the first one too
oh what is it it's so quiet here
it's omnius
music
oh I'm hungry buddy money money money
money
what okay
but now there's no music again
this is this is like dispensary the game
Mario card
oh
it works at first up first I'm gonna be
first let's go Mario
the music
all right go find it over this way oh
[\h__\h] oh oh six friends
bye-bye
[Music]
I'm leaving you behind
see you later
the only thing that's left is a blue
shell
[Music]
our fun how fun for you
almost flipped over oh another loop on
your side hello
you like you like Loops though oh you
didn't I do what the hell no you take
the lube no you take the loop you take
it smelly
[Music]
cute what a rematch
no rematch no this is this is it I win
no you lost bro
you're lost you're lost you have to
accept it hello I'm fine
[Music]
oh that was the whole level wow we did
that much oh sorry wow
wait do that much faster than the other
ones
Racing's in our blood
[Music]
gotta go fast
because we did it under three minutes
maybe Sonic
yeah yeah hi
fun with the leg we got you know what
we're gonna do that let me twins
high five oh whoop we can do that
we're twins we're connected by the music
oh that already feels like a mistake
oh
no what is this
I saw something up there that I feel
like we should have pushed I want to
touch it okay okay okay
it's a playground for us whoa okay let's
check out uh together
all the way back up
you jump on me
I'm sorry sorry oh
do you know this like Japanese
um
politeness
joke meme thingy real life meme where
you know Japanese people they'll be like
because they're very polite when there's
something to do something to take or so
they'll be like those are those are
those all right
okay yeah and then when there's like a
group of people and and you want you
don't actually want to do it
and you go like those those well then
the other person is also those are those
everybody's like it's just an endless
those are those are those all
endlessly
so feel free to use that I saw it when
you talked to Coyote the other day you
used book A book on Easter again
literally all of all the Japanese I've
learned in my time the one that yours is
you taught me the most yeah you
is it it's so in your brain I think
who's again
what are we doing I think we just jumped
away I think
oh I saved you come back up here
we gotta I think I saw a ball or
something up there we gotta go there we
got this thing over there too this way
okay okay
oh
no oh okay sorry forget it let's go up
again wait is this a Japanese game
pikuniko I think so because yeah
Japanese
I don't know maybe not because it was
published by the Volvo digital so that's
not very Japanese publisher
oh maybe they just picked a Japanese
cute name
Maybe
down honestly
come on come on I'm dead
let's look
please
oh there it is there's a ball oh man
what do we do with it though send it
down send it down it needs to go on the
buttons
thank God thank God okay okay let's
stand up here maybe
there's something to test out can we
reach those uh up there no somehow not
oh
Mount me I don't know why we would do
that though I will Mount you gouda Mount
me I'll jump and now
why though it's kind of useless for fun
oh wait press C oh
eels we're like switched out oh wait can
I press the the bigger why
for one purpose right
I don't think there's a purpose but
should there be always a purpose
or maybe we're supposed to do something
with that ball we toss down yeah oh
we stretched out the
the
cable not cable our flesh connecting
Earth
oh wait yeah there's a big red button
there
really that's why I wanted the ball push
the button oh
no better you I spin the ball that would
uh can you wait I [\h__\h] help
oh now what oh mean become Mean Bean
mold always
do you know the sheldons wouldn't have
them that meme
like actually Kobo told me about it it's
like
sounds like German I guess so somebody
was making a video where they talked
what the [\h__\h] did they talked
[Music]
um
yeah so there's like stray cats and they
want the cats to look at them and talk
to them and come over so they use all
kinds of languages like uh uh any any
language and and call the cat in each
respective language and it doesn't work
So eventually they say it in supposedly
German really aggressively stop and pull
the Thousand box and then the cat looks
at them and comes over to them but it's
obviously edited okay because everybody
knows that the real language is
no I don't know
I don't agree I don't agree no I don't
know a lot of people always go
it's just
known
do you really do your cats
doesn't like you Coulda what no I think
it's more personal reasons than that
person what did you do personally
honestly
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
I can't reach
oh okay
okay let's go down
have you heard of the game fortunately
unfortunately no that sounds like a name
that I came up with
unbelievably believable wait it is
unbelievably believable
no no no it's not it's not it's um oh
okay let's make new balls
you like you started a scenario you say
somebody's fortunately and the other
person is unfortunately like fortunately
uh
I made an ice cream sundae today and
then you would say but unfortunately you
spilled it all over yourself and then I
would say um like fortunately I was
wearing a hazmat suit so I didn't
actually get any of it on myself and you
said well unfortunately your hazmat suit
was already contaminated so regardless
you still can't have your ice cream
sundae and then I would say well
fortunately and then it just goes on and
on and on until somebody gives up what
I've heard of that
ow what is that a game or what yeah
play that because I don't understand it
negative and somebody has to be the
positive in whatever scenario I think I
think that's how it works okay how would
I apply that now
think of a scenario uh
uh uh oh wait no no would you rather be
the positive or the negative I'll beat
up positive
okay
so a scenario
yeah
give me a scenario
uh wait sample sample scenario
fortunately
I don't know your cat comes to sit on
your lap
uh-huh scenario
unfortunately I guess now I'm the
negative unfortunately
the cat uh just had an accident on the
toilet
so it stains your lap
fortunately you're wearing an
adult-sized apron
all the way down to the bottom
no no no aprons are normally adult-sized
wait I change my answer fortunately
you know so there's actually nothing to
it for the bathroom to stick to your
cat's hair unfortunately okay
okay this is not your cat
uh
fortunately cat has a name tag
with names and numbers
it's uh in a language that you can't
read like it has its own writing system
like Korean or whatever so well
fortunately I've got translator on my
phone
personally your battery of the phone
died
well fortunately
fortunately I remember I plugged my
phone in to charge
ow now you plug it in now I guess now
I'm plugging it in unfortunately
unfortunately
um you didn't pay your electricity bills
so
unfortunately there's a cafe nearby that
I know has free wi-fi
Unfortunately they closed down because
of lack of business
uh
playing this is making our struggles any
easier but but it's fun it's fun
I like ruining your story
no
wait okay so it closed down
unfortunately the cafe closed down uh
okay uh fortunate
[Music]
oh man fortunately I found a perfectly
reasonable foam charger on the side of
the road like a miracle
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're gonna go home back to charge it
or what but you didn't pray your
electricity bills Where Are You Gonna
it's not a problem
oh leave it
all right okay one second timeout
timeout let's fix this problem okay
it's up there what do we do
somebody has to go maybe we don't even
ah Winnie the bowl and we don't need it
no we don't need it listen we don't need
it
you are you saying our friendship alone
is enough yes
will get us across this Gap because
that's all we need to do right get it
across the Gap okay let's let's check
out like where we would need it because
we do need it
sorry
lift
oh
okay
[Music]
what if we need the ball there too okay
we got wood ball cookie we didn't need
the ball
I think that's our Barrel yeah
[Music]
but it's closed actually it's not
supposed to be there can we kick it to
break it it's ah it's a barrel after
World possibly possibly
excuse me
what the [\h__\h]
the barrel okay keep it there no no no
no no no no no no
I had it
[Music]
push it all the way yeah
I'm a helping steam it's rolling did you
get the achievement too no because I
guess you don't have the games
no says you're not helping but it meant
me probably
not every let's go down go down go down
what did you
do oh we have to go I up
oh but what about the bottoms
screw the buttons I guess it's just a
trampoline help
[Music]
um
you're so weak
oh
follow me
pepper beans amazing
[Music]
I thought that was gonna be a lot harder
yeah
[Music]
oh
test oh no oh you're fine
no blood allowed let's go club music
buying
what was the button for though what did
the button do
okay now
this is very spiky oh oh
oh
they break oh it could then regenerate
maybe with the button ah yes the button
regenerates them
damn okay can you not destroy everything
no
maybe one should focus on on going all
the way up first maybe there's a
surprise I don't know mine okay we need
both people there
but I'm almost there
oh you you no no no no no oh not yet you
go up and then I push the after pushing
the button for you and then I push the
button and then I restart and then here
you have to come up now hold your skill
issue until I prove you right please
wait one second platform what I can't
see
oh oh there you go there you go
[Music]
join me
three two one yeah
one got stuck
that's your ball your sign me
all right
[Music]
behind do we put them on uh-huh
I think aren't we down here though
ah
why are these buttons maybe yeah maybe
it will open up the blue door maybe the
button out the buttons are red though
uh true
[Music]
well we might as well try they fell down
for a reason right
yeah I guess so
[Music]
how do we
triggering me go
go
eat the ball before you do it I guess
let's both stand on this at the same
time
and see what happens
well then
get your ball into your hole and I got
my ball into my hole
[Music]
I saw wait I saw uh on in a stream oh
you know Ina never swears right very
rarely she said one more oh I didn't she
said one word
um can you give mine yeah it for me it's
not even a swear word what does she say
but like everybody was like so shocked
and oh my God what did she say what was
that like yeah damn it was damn she's
really yeah damn them
for me that's like in my normal
dictionary I always say
um damn I say [\h__\h] hell more often
than damn even I think Ian must keep it
really clean then yeah
I don't know even I let out every now
and then something
[\h__\h] I guess she just was raised better
than we were going on
she's raised as a proper
I don't know she's well mannered with
speech-mannered and weird
from from
where what are we
what are we
we're just a couple of beans bouncing
around in an unfair World why are we
bouncing the other way right
oh thank you give me a box
[Music]
don't mess it up uh
we're just clowns yeah
internet clowns lady Ina
but it's true even in real life I don't
think I heard her swear
I haven't heard her I don't think I've
heard any of you guys say anything
incredibly Really Gonna you don't have
to lie about
it anyway because he already used to
about how I talk
it's funny though because you say that
and then whenever I say
swears in German you're like
hey yeah cause why would you swear in
German
because you taught me switch in German
and then when I said them you were like
this is very this is wrong to my ear of
course it is wrong to my ears
swe swear to me
I've forgotten him can I get a refresher
uh shut them
um better uh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] is if
perfect
I like that one
you're so good at saying things
confidently thank you I want this nut
[Music]
I got the knot
it's actually a nut no way
oh God
Jose what does this happen
what is it
and then what does that have to do with
nuts
wait there's the blue what whoa blue
it's blue here how did you why are you
so fine
yes
I'm lost in the belly of the Beast
it's a maze dude I'll bring the nuts
oh sure nuts
I don't have to share the nuts oh
acorns yeah it's an acorn wait do you
even eat corn
I've never had Acorn before yeah I don't
think you eat it unless you're a
squirrel
Lisa
no we don't really need the nut right
maybe there's like an extra achievement
if you bring the nuts [\h__\h] the nuts how
do you say
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm sorry
you have to ignore what I say and then
it's not so bad
[Music]
that sounds like you're gonna break the
nuts oh
oh okay uh moving on moving on where
does this hey dude
where it is did you come outside
Grand Theft these
um
I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
the other ball you mean
no yeah
[Music]
the ball and not the knots
could have left the the knot there on
the button true
okay okay thank you for joining me in
the next things
wait no uh ball ball or I mean it
doesn't matter no I'll I'll leave them
no no we can bring balls
no we need one here because we need the
door to be open
oh right I think maybe the
I mean why is it enough though it's so
Random
because it's round
okay okay let's bring the nuts
[Music]
don't shoot the nuts back we don't want
this whole thing again
[Music]
be nice to the nuts
and you say
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
Dexter noise
I'm not the nuts don't kick me
kick the nuts if shaped like nuts why
not nut it is nuts
it could also be a human head with a hat
on
that's messed up looks like but also
correct yeah
[\h__\h] up
stupid nut oh oh nice cake now don't
mess it up oh well whoops sorry
wait let me stand on you stand on the
very edge
ah there there there
you're so cute when you're being
[\h__\h] I'll show you
what maybe better if it was a ball
because then it bounces
yeah okay see that's that's why I say
[\h__\h] the knot
[Music]
no not no
[Applause]
oh okay okay
see so much better already apple is the
way I protect this path so the ball
doesn't go oh no
[Applause]
oh
is there are we making this harder for
ourselves
probably
oh man we're like we're literally clowns
with all these clown sounds whenever we
kick each other I feel like we're we're
clowns
if the shoe fits
sorry
yeah now do that but do that to the ball
yeah
[Music]
yeah real game of strats
just gently rub the ball with your bean
heads and lift it yeah
I didn't know
warm it up yeah yeah
wait
I'm pretty sure hold on you keep trying
that one there's a ball oh wait we need
that one we need this one never mind
[Music]
it's okay it's okay uh if we just focus
for one second
but that's hard
[Music]
I've locked this path okay I will block
this top
sorry
I will block this stuff
let's go back oh take it back take it
back
[Music]
yeah yeah work it work it
I'm gonna I'm gonna uh
is there like a are we missing a button
or something
no
no no oh
get out of here
I deserve that how do we how
are you
this this is a disaster
you just gotta believe
[Music]
it can't be this [\h__\h] ball that will
make us great quit right
no is it the payback for not trusting
the nuts
you offended the nut gods
AKA 82
Lisa heard you say
[\h__\h] the nut
okay okay okay if you you haven't met at
least to Eva right
In the Flesh
no Lisa and
um
there's like two or three members of ID
who I haven't met yet only two whoa
wait is it
[Music]
I met
yo they're all so cute they're so fun so
cute
I think this remember you're talking
about them you're like they're so cute
and then you were like
these are cute and there's a small and
they're so cute I was interesting
because I I thought she was a manager
really to me she gave me this like
Japanese manager uh Aura somehow
oh that's what that's what you know Ina
was saying that as well about herself
yeah she likes to pretend to be manager
yeah yeah
together
and she believed it because energy I
guess she's in this situation I feel
like it must have been a little bit uh
naive or or gullible
because
it was all it was really absurd the
whole thing was so absurda
wow
soccer is the way all right I'm sorry
why is it kicking that way I feel like
you have to uh push the direction where
you want to kick oh yeah
[Music]
oh God I'm gonna make a miracle come
true yo
yo self-sabotage
sorry
[Music]
cannot I just become the ball
why no I cannot I be the ball
is this is this level supposed to be
this hard or are we just having an
exceptionally hard time because we are
exceptional what is this is difficult so
far
I'm diving this is difficult
okay
uh maybe yeah maybe I need you to walk
away can you be on the on the protection
side here yes I'll try my best
I believe
[Music]
bring it bring it back bring it back
bring it back
nice and easy
gosh these things are so cute
you're doing a great job as a woman
you're making your reputation become
true
I am the toughest piece of plywood that
you ever make
oh [\h__\h]
why does it always go to the [\h__\h] I'm
sorry sorry I want to do that
maybe maybe
[Music]
you can be on standby like when it's
here in the air to kick it to them yeah
okay okay so you gotta come in a bit
further
yeah and then you have to jump when the
ball jumps
that's gonna work that's gonna work
that's gonna work
come on come on no sorry
yo okay see that that was basically the
same strategy
it's just timing it
okay
um you kicked the ball
[Music]
oh
oh man
don't give up don't give up don't give
up don't give up
what would we be if we gave up too
easily
this is literally our job
we can't go home until we solve it oh
sure
then we're gonna be the best ball Pusher
beans they've ever seen we're gonna be
balling we're bawling
[Music]
I feel like the more I do this the worse
I get though
at this point
I I can't man
my my fingers are
nice wait is this
is this where it started yeah
no yeah maybe maybe there or maybe
somewhere around here yeah
um
I was wondering maybe we should like
reset to the ball is somewhere easier
but if it starts here then uh huh
come on
for what purpose
[Music]
wait let's not send it back again wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait what if we made a wall
and we just kicked it yeah okay
oh not me
you mean stand on each other yeah yeah
when I'm on you I don't think I can kick
well no yeah I feel like it
automatically kicks you when we're like
[Music]
wait does the same thing happen then if
you stand on
[Music]
okay
also like I I said to you so smugly that
just push the arrow button sometimes I
feel like
it really doesn't
um push or kick towards the direction I
wanted to it's just
right sometimes chicken I'm pushing to
the right and then kicks to the left
right but I think that only happens when
you're right like right next to
something and your right leg cannot be
even extended
I guess that's silly no
they say leave the ball alone
right we need the ball
is there another ball closer
let's check again
um where does we need the ball
oh no I guess wait if we needed the ball
how would we even get it across this
water
I'm kick it
all here up here
wait maybe we didn't need the pool
no wait wait
[Music]
not much time do we waste on that then
it's it's okay it's bonding time well
yeah but there must be it then a
different ball
if we really needed a ball oh [\h__\h] oh
wait wait I feel like I know where there
might be another ball
another yeah because there's two buttons
there I just confirmed there is two
buttons and we have one ball there we
need another one so I just saw I can
hang up here
see oh but there is no ball here
but no that is oh
[Music]
the ball
we're so stupid
[Music]
it works it's true we can be stupid
together still stupid a good time no we
were
oh wait you need this
yeah we need it over here
everybody watching this is rubbing their
temples right now
sorry the new Bolton Bros oh yeah
because we're supposed to be like what
kind of dumb bone-headed brothers yeah I
guess I need to be added to the Bone
Bros I'm the new member please welcome
me
please
bring the ball
oh yeah
you know
topic change because you don't want to
watch
um the Super Mario movie you don't want
to watch it right not yet no yeah no how
about the Dungeons and Dragons movie
that's also in the cinema right now
I've watched that one yeah go watch it
before it's gone it's been on the cinema
for a while now I think
what's it about other than DND well you
don't really see them play DND at all
it's like you're immersed in the world
but it still gives you the DND like the
dorky D Vibes like crazy things happen
they come up with crazy Solutions and
all that but it's like a whole adventure
and and the the actors are really good a
lot of laughs like really I laugh so
much
everybody laughs so much in the cinema
they they left holy [\h__\h] they were like
crazy I felt like they were on something
um but yeah do we have to
um have this be the same sign like
everything
I think so okay what do we want which
sign oh
um if we kick once it stops
pick it once yeah oh oh
time it riots unbelievable is there
something here did we check this part
out
[Music]
I think I saw like an ad for the day
what is this oh wait that's what we need
to do sweetheart
[Music]
see you're already smarter I didn't
understand
no no no no yeah so please watch the DND
movie if you if you don't want to watch
Super Mario then watch the indie movie
you have to watch it it's so good
well if you recommend it but then you
also like to catch the movie so maybe I
should question your taste in movies
what wait what why are you lying to me
on Twitter you seem very interested in
watching the cats movie I'll watch the
catch movie I actually thought of a
funny response after we had that back
and forth and I got upset because
but yeah if you thought of it within 30
minutes you could have edited your
tweets no this was before I think oh no
no editing what did you think of them
I think what you thought of something
funnier
I don't remember but it made it was
[Music]
I don't wanna know half an hour
yeah this doesn't feel as bad as you
know no it did it felt worse it felt
worse because we were stuck in the same
spot for half of the time yeah oh my God
okay good now let's leave the game but
good let's play Let's play another round
of uh unfortunately
fortunately unfortunately yes
okay that uh you are fortunately then
fortunately do we do you start but
fortunately the word fortunately
uh
uh somebody who starts with a topic or a
situation
um
fortunately we finished the level no way
then we're gonna keep on talking about
that personally
uh fortunately
um unfortunately
fortunately fortunately for fortunately
fortunately you've got a being stuck in
a forbidden place
uh unfortunately uh-huh
are you it's a dangerous place
you mean on your body
who knows maybe the dangerous place is
like a electricity socket for
fortunately
uh wait what did you say it's a
dangerous place right
yes fortunately you know someone who's a
professional Bean remover
unfortunately
you are unable to reach them by phone
silly you know the address of the
painful
um
so you make your way to the bean remover
that's a vein remover
um unfortunately hmm
the bean remover
has acquired an allergic a deadly
allergic reaction to beans yeah I
thought you were gonna say that oh my
gosh he's what
he's uh well
um fortunately
this Bean is an anti-allergic a
hypoallergenic or whatever you call them
Bean
hmm
oh
why do we choose to stop it why did I
choose to stop it why beans could I like
beans
fortunately hypoallergenic beans
unfortunately
you can't afford the bean remover's fees
[Music]
how much is it
it's now fifty thousand dollars USD to
remove your beans
ridiculous
fortunately the bean remover AKA Cara
Bean owes you a favor and therefore
we'll do it for free
bring
her over
unfortunately while traveling to your
location Cara beans plane crashed and
Caribbean uh yeah her plane crashed in
the Caribbean oh my God
[Music]
fortunately she uh was able she traveled
with a uh what do you call the the
the things that go poof when you fall
out of a plane a parachute yeah she was
traveling with a parachute
unfortunately when she went to open her
parachute there was no parachute at all
oh my gosh God a bean attached to some
strings
[Laughter]
then worked as like a bouncy
thing to save her from the from a deadly
fall and bounced her and she was at
least not dead
this was an inside job
wait what relation does Carrie bean have
to the original Bean remover no she is
the bean remover
not the guy this is a friend no no the
Caribbean is the bean remover I gave her
the name
it's it's it's a it's a lady called
Caribbean it's different it's different
being removable though I tried to kill
her
yeah
wait so unfortunately for Miss Caribbean
this Bean oh that she bounced on was not
hypoallergenic and when she bounced the
force and gravity of her coming down to
the Earth watch The Bead Lodge the being
deep within her skin and which she then
had an allergic Bean reaction
that happens very often in the Caribbean
uh since there's many beans and many
many carrots so they immediately treated
her in the hospital because there's many
Caribbean Caribbean specialists
and she was fine you soon after
what's that game that we played uh for
that like first Christmas with myth that
you wanted us to I think it was you oh
like a Mad Lib
it is it's like a
rapid
yeah
yeah okay so she was fine she was fine
are you do you give up is that like how
do you win the game
I think you have to completely stump the
other person oh well I don't I don't
feel like I stomped you just yet but
we're getting closer to my goal of uh I
guess fixing the beach
um
um unfortunate wait fortunately so she's
healed but unfortunately
The Bean Is Still lodged within her
somehow the symptoms may have been
healed but the bean is the largest
within miscarriages
[Music]
prohibiting her from boarding any other
aircraft so therefore she is stuck
stranded in the Caribbean
[Laughter]
you're such a bullshitter fortunately
um because we didn't specify uh the
protagonists uh who originally wanted
this Bean situation to be solved
that just happens to be one of the
doctors no she's already there
so yeah the uh yeah I I
believe that that for you try
she doesn't have to lie she will not
remove this bean I won't Rebecca video
[Music]
unfortunately she cannot get inside the
residence of the the person in need of
bean removal why
why because she can't she has no arms
she's become puppy
she has become the one that she was
fighting the beans it's a side effect
fortunately
[Music]
uh
uh the name of the protagonist
is
Carrie
now
Benjamin and and he and Carrie fell in
love with the bean form of Caribbean and
they marry and they become Caribbean
but how
because Carrie Bean couldn't get inside
because she is a queen she has no arms
and legs so she's gonna knock on the
door we don't have to get inside because
he fell in love with the bean form he
likes her as a bean but how did she win
unless she was at the door
he's in the in the hustle to save her
and it went wrong I guess because he's
the doctor oh he's doctor
thank you so so now they're Caribbean
and it's love and a happy ever after
they are Caribbean together
no Bean was removed after all instead
they all became the bean
[Music]
exactly
that is our lesson of the day
I guess what the hell I'm saying to the
fitting to the game too I think if we're
ever in a situation where we're like I
don't know on a five hour train ride or
something like this this we can use this
as a travel game thank you for teaching
me this game
the hard part's gonna be keeping quiet
though because I feel like the further
you go the more you yell no no
you just come up with ridiculous things
man that's amazing and made for for this
game we made for each other thank you
for being with me today and balling and
nothing and
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't forget to watch Dungeons and
Dragons though next time I talk to you
you talk you talk to me about Dungeons
and Dragons okay that's your quest let's
do your homework okay watch DND
and then next week is gonna be on girls
talk but yay it will be unfortunately
unfortunately uh fortunately Google will
be on Girls Talk unfortunately it's
without fauna fortunately it's okay we
can rotate you know maybe
maybe we can get some input from fauna
if she can't be there but we can still
get video message does that make sense
or pictures or something a video message
so yeah I'll see what I can do yeah
[Music]
will be in her place that's okay I will
momentarily stand in yes all right
sounds good so thank you guys for
watching
thank you thank you kfp for having me
Yay good night everybody
good night
and in German we say
[Music]
yeah
wow that is I didn't think of that
that's amazing
[Music]
oh
Muto
[Music]
foreign