[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
voices
all right everyone welcome to Halloween
cup 2023.
[Music]
[Applause]
like this
[Music]
you guys
all right all right thank you thank you
okay
um as you guys know oh wow this is the
second year of Holo ID card 2023 and I
would like to say thank you to all of
you guys who've been accepting to play
with us
and trying all the games that's been
setting for this year
um and also
um I would like to say thank you to
ollie and rainy for being the MC today
yay
[Music]
and also thank you for birthday with
theme and Shri candy theme for do a lot
of practice so yeah it's really helpful
for me too and well that's all I just
want you guys to have fun for today
foreign yeah
[Music]
we'll be emcees today
yeah so uh we'll be watching all of you
guys
[Music]
will be commenting on every one of your
moves
secretly
yeah and after this what do we have
after this rainy
well we're gonna be having a captain
speech from each of the team
so if we can get the leaders to come up
here please
what if I shift shift all right
let's go have fun today
[Music]
it will be it will probably be chaos
chaos
let's have fun today
[Music]
thank you
and that was Zeta and next we have risu
[Music]
are you ready to game
game
so yeah let's let's have fun today
[Music]
thank you I love you too
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
ERS and then it's now time for the full
introduction of each team we can start
with free candy second team please
[Music]
Amelia from Amelia senpai
hello everybody
let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Laughter]
moving on uh
bae up to you hey do you want to go
first oh okay what's up it's it's me
this is
[Music]
uh
okay hello everyone I'm Anya let's have
fun today
[Applause]
[Music]
all right
next would be uh
candy let's win
[Music]
your service
oh my God
episode today
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
nice nice
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
it's time for Team for TV to introduce
himself
[Music]
thank you I will do my best
ie
thanks oh sorry
and next we have Kyla
oh hello hi everyone my name is Kelly
[Music]
thank you
let's party I'm energetic Yankee
yeah thanks I know
next next next we have Kiara
[Music]
um it's currently 6 a.m
and I am gonna be at badminton and
soccer fighter
[Music]
we have fauna
it says
English Council thank you for not
putting me on the soccer team
it's fun though
what are you participating in for now I
will be in capture the fort and also the
potato sack rays
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yay next Lunas I'm fine
hi
hi everyone
my name is
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign oh yeah
I will participating
today
wow
that's for that's all for team for TV
right yeah yeah but you know other than
like introducing the members I kind of
want to hear something more don't you
think yeah
all right everybody come up with their
own team cheers oh
yeah
I'm ready I'm ready
are you ready
oh let's do it let's do it okay okay
fertility team and so let's do our yeah
yeah okay so after me I'm gonna start
okay okay
three two one
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
that was so good yeah
thank you
let's go let's go okay okay okay okay
[Music]
two one
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
then wow
[Music]
so the even today
um we're gonna play a lot of games
starting from capture the fort or we
call it bending on and after that we
move to the puta de sacres and after
that we go tug of war and then after
that we have badminton uh from the a
side and then badminton from a b side
and also after that we have soccer and
that's all
[Music]
yes
that's all I hope you guys having fun
now it's it's time for you guys to uh I
think it's back to the interview should
we interview huh yes right so in English
[Music]
foreign okay
[Applause]
games games games
soccer there we go
we're we're sitting on YouTube
okay
[Music]
come on
are you winning
are we winning are you winning oh yeah
we just go straight to Ben 10
okay okay okay let's go
okay
[Music]
wow okay
interested
[Music]
very positive positive vibes
Big W
are you guys scared is there anything
that you're afraid of from the other
team um
nothing nothing scared no it's okay
nothing scary big
we have Puffs in on the team so that
fits
wait who's who's playing the capture the
four on the other team
[Music]
um
no it's okay
good luck
okay hi okay okay okay okay
thank you thank you thank you
I don't know
um I think uh until we're getting told
to get ready
um
do we move to the general yeah where do
we move or the training
oh no no we don't we don't move to the
general
oh so we just stay in the CC everyone's
even the place is staying in the VC
even the other the other three candy
team are they staying in the PC give me
one second it wasn't in the brief so
yeah
okay
yes
like my life depends on it please
defending it with my life
[Music]
um
but I've got a reply so basically we're
supposed to stay in the VC and everyone
else who is not playing will stay as
well to cheer for oh okay so everyone is
amazing yeah we're all in the same PC
okay let's pick Team all right
um
thank you
lady are you ready
[Music]
okay
we got this we got this
[Music]
okay
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
oh yeah
let's move okay okay
win
okay
[Music]
uh
okay okay
try decided if we were red team or white
team so we yeah both so we'll try
oh
damn
we also had another strategy in case
everyone went to prison
prepared
[Music]
wait why why I didn't do anything I mean
I protected the base
literally uh all of them went out no one
was protecting the base at all so I was
very impressed
sucks in this it was all part of the
pictures
according according to cake plan
[Laughter]
easy
bye
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Laughter]
happy with it
yeah
that was fun
since we are already playing the Ben 10
apparently depending on it's only for
like one time playing so we want to do
another game
muscle
hello
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
thank you
okay what's the Finishing Line
okay
Play-Doh now we wait right yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on
[Applause]
all right let's watch
okay let's hear it
[Music]
so fast
[Applause]
um
[Music]
last night
I thought she wasn't on the other lap
yeah
yeah I thought she was so fast
I was like okay she's
so fast
is still right here
it's fun I somehow winning despite
taking the outside of the lab
oh
surprising video
[Music]
wow the timing was
part of the timing was success
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
okay okay
hi everybody
[Music]
foreign
but next time
uh I think if there's connection issue
or someone disconnected I think uh we
will keep uh continuing the battle
because also I think to make it fair for
everybody as well okay okay thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
I'm gonna go to this thank you thank you
so we're lucky we got a practice round
we used to watch Pretty we're pretty
lucky yeah I'll make this up I I will I
will I'll do my best let's go
okay we can do it um
[Music]
[Laughter]
the waiting game let's go let's go let's
go
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
that's really cool
um
[Applause]
[Music]
come on
one more
[Music]
time
I'm looking forward
[Music]
um
wow what are you guys made of
idea oh my gosh why are you all so
cracked what thoughts
[Laughter]
yeah congratulations congratulations
[Music]
the winning line was mostly on uh Amelia
Senpai as well how did you feel
uh I felt like I was slow
but because you were the uh the last one
to actually finish the race you were
kind of like the winning spine
you held the key you clutched it yeah
let's go how do you guys feel do you
guys think you guys got it got
everything in the bag
you won twice you think you can win the
next one as well
[Music]
you guys
thank you
[Music]
go back everyone
oh my God
I will be cheering on you guys
I want to discuss a strategy okay okay
so I think the key is we need to spam
click
uh
just uh sometimes
[Laughter]
we don't get tired uh early okay okay
um yes
[Music]
already
you can do it yes
[Laughter]
gravity let gravity
bill
fingers
[Music]
faster
thank you
foreign
[Music]
it was pretty close it was only like um
I think it was 100 difference I thought
we were the white team yeah it was a
static one yeah because it was we're
there yeah
double click
oh
[Laughter]
okay okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
yes yes we got this we practice we got
this oh I'm excited
this time I will not make a strategy
anymore thank you
it was a spam
pink
okay overcome the pain
can do this
okay let's go
[Music]
who is playing for the badminton on the
opposite team I wonder
oh
let me check so okay
no no
three candy so three candy team
no no yeah yeah foreign
[Music]
this is violence in 4k
guys
okay so I think so from badminton team a
uh is
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
because
[Music]
yes
but whatever we're ready
[Music]
ready
yeah okay okay
[Music]
come on
oh
yeah
what
thank you
[Music]
so hard to see where if it's out or not
that's it
yep get it get it get it
awesome
do you
know
um
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know
[Music]
that's it
people might come back
[Music]
okay you got this
next week
[Music]
now I'm hungry we bring
all right guys
that's really nice good luck guys you
can do it yeah
ready ready
okay ready
you can do it
come on
okay yeah
go come out nice nice Circle nice okay
I can see you see it's hard
maybe you can change to third person POV
yes but I think the hardest part
either way yeah it's hard as well yeah
already
yeah sometimes easier
[Music]
yeah
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
it's okay
what do you mean
if you hold quick more power more power
more power more power
look in the direction
oh
my God yeah I think you might not have
enough power like in your clicks so you
have to hold it longer hold when you
click hold One clicking
[Music]
does that count as two wins
oh it's 20 20 points for each winner so
they got 40 points
wait so you count the total
wait yeah
we do
but also other games
this is the Turning Point team it's
soccer next
[Music]
are we Thai right now with party no
we're 70 80 but if each one is 20 points
if we win we beat them oh okay okay
let's go
okay okay
[Music]
we haven't decided
should I play goalie again
I'm a keeper yes
okay okay
[Music]
I'll do it
we got shoes
okay how do I get one two three four
five
[Music]
70 to 80 right now
17. you define the best angle yes angle
it's just this
sucks
yesterday yeah
we have offense we have defense we have
goalie
yay
oh my God
last time in practice we couldn't score
wait I don't know if anybody on either
team scored any
we'll try we'll try as long as we score
on our own goal at least one's right
that's a good thing
our own goal s
the green this
oh
[Music]
nice is nice
let's go let's go team let's go let's go
do we get to see oh not yet maybe
you need to turn on my hype Man music
some goals
[Music]
she's chanting the chant right now
we just need to do the the channel once
again before the match
sports team probably do that before the
match
should I play offense or defense
um
we'll figure it out in the field
good night
offense
front
means
[Music]
foreign
uptown
yes
fun
let's go aggressor
okay just be aggressive
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
um
okay
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
position
okay
yeah I'll be in the middle
[Music]
really good
I don't know
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okay okay okay
[Music]
go okay
dude that was so close
time
[Music]
what's your name
red cake red cake
[Music]
oh God
foreign
[Music]
okay
yeah
here because there's so many people here
[Music]
oh my God
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
nice cake nice nice nice
foreign
[Music]
fancy
[Applause]
[Laughter]
videos
[Music]
seriously
what is
okay
it's counting up I've just been uh okay
okay okay
okay
I was so close
okay okay
[Music]
give it up give it up
no no
no okay guys
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
amazing job on the defense as well your
defense is great the pressure is you can
really feel it you can really see it
they're doing a really great job
you guys can do it I'm a crack goalie I
know I know
that is so good I miss sweet yeah I I
noticed while watching
um without a few ball hold it gives like
the team the other team more time to to
like run back so that one time that you
instead of ball holding you just kicked
it out of your goalie area gay pickled I
sent by that opening to then score
afterwards so that was a very very big
brain play
oh yeah I'll keep that in mind yeah yeah
[Music]
mind game
what do you mean like a chat oh yeah
oh wait nevermind they can't hear us
[Laughter]
now another thing to keep in mind for
the second meeting you guys are up 2-0
so just keep the ball out 2-0
um
I've been playing like before she'll be
good too though I think all of the ovens
and defense is like really really
balanced yeah
um
[Music]
indeed
[Laughter]
mental destroying play
okay they recovered to break it's okay
don't let it get in your house
[Music]
wait can we do that can somebody's
making a drink
[Music]
doing it
everyone ready
come on
foreign
[Music]
okay okay
[Applause]
sorry
[Music]
positions
okay okay let's go
um
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
um
[Music]
daddy okay
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay
when you stand by
okay okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
okay
oh
[Music]
it's okay it's okay okay all right all
right okay okay all right all right you
have one
let them have one
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go let's go okay
let's go
[Music]
five more minutes you guys can do this
okay okay
Madden
okay
Central
okay okay
come on
[Music]
okay
let's go let's go let's go let's go
okay okay
nothing
thank you
foreign
three more minutes
[Music]
they're learning
okay okay
two more minutes
that was close
that was close okay let's go
okay
[Music]
come on
let's go let's go
one more minutes
okay
okay okay that's it
nice nice nice
Center Center
okay okay
[Music]
all right
foreign
[Music]
two three
[Applause]
oh my god
really nice comeback first amazing we
have the legend being birth
for the two games and then you guys came
back up with soccer that was crazy
what's the secret to your teamwork pessy
um
yeah wait I heard that you guys only
practice like once like what what did
you guys discuss during that practice
round
um literally nothing
wow soccer results
soccer tensa everyone in Sri candy you
guys were very aggressive and
coordinated and then you guys have three
goals from usada pakora right and then
one go from Kobo
was that revenge for tug of war like
what's happening
yeah yeah
[Music]
teamwork was amazing the passes were
amazing you guys did so good
everyone was so good it was so fun
everyone was so good that was so fun but
if I had to ask what was like the main
struggle what was the thing that
actually
um made you guys sweat bullets
my vision
oh I think putting pressure on the other
team
are we back in Maine Hall yeah oh yeah
blood pressure keep kicking the ball in
their Direction make eye
contacts kept getting better like at the
second half like it was really hard to
score a goal yeah
foreign
[Music]
awesome
when did I look cool yes I was watching
from above
we should have been cheerleading where
are your pom-poms
hearts
you mean in front of your heart
[Laughter]
yeah
how strong are you now though getting
punched yeah she likes it though Kelly
don't you know she likes it you sure
about that just like back in the day
I'm not abusive
yeah
[Laughter]
Emma did you play soccer in real life
before or what I have I have oh
that explains everything
[Music]
are you announcing your wedding with
someone
yeah
delicious
it was intense and well after all of
those intense games will be announcing
the winners
yeah so first of all from the bending on
the capture the fourth
the winner
with 40 points
[Music]
and then we also have the attack race
with 30 points yet again three can you
win so that brings us to a total of 70
points
[Music]
what's the next one
the next one was
tug of war
in which it was a blue versus pink team
OMG
four how many points
40 points yeah
and then badminton again two matches
both won by partially so 20 plus 20 so
another 40 points for per TV
[Music]
after three candy was leading pretty we
managed to catch up by 10 points and
then that's where soccer came in and
became the deal breaker yeah
Watson too strong and we are happy to
announce that the winner of the whole ID
cup is the
subtle
[Applause]
too
[Laughter]
[Music]
I am number one in Elena's heart
[Laughter]
spicy
we are going to be awarding the medals
right okay
team captain please distribute the
medals to your teammates hi I'm gonna
distribute
all right
oh yes
I sent it please distribute
[Music]
[Laughter]
let me see hey what if I just put on the
gold medal anyway
yeah
[Music]
foreign
if you want it
it's my medal now
thank you I'm ready
[Music]
does everybody have their medals
[Applause]
yes okay
yes oh looks so good
yeah
this thing is heavy
just like the opening we will be asking
for a few words by each team captain
starting from three candy teams
[Music]
that was it that was really fun really
really fun and
um
can we go oh can we do the
um the the yellow together again let's
do it again
let's do it again yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay let's go okay okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
everyone did
um everyone did their best doing the
games
thank you so much for being such a good
leader thank you thank you
for playing with us as well
[Music]
we can we have a little bit of
riddles from the captain of temper TV
please
hi baby
[Music]
first I would like to say thank you for
all for today team to uh to actually
make time for this and also I love
birthday theme because they are all
um hardworking so they practice too and
they like oh my God I just I just love
the team so much I love you too
yeah
[Music]
So yeah thank you so much everybody
thank you so much for inviting us
this year was really fun thank you
next year again
please
guys yeah
one last time
foreign
[Applause]
thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
[Applause]
lastly
[Music]
pictures
everyone welcome go into the podium
please let's go let's go
baby
you can be on the top one on the spruce
okay okay
[Music]
three two one
okay
thank you
thank you one more time
look at me look at me okay okay uh
okay okay
[Music]
the time good fun times
thank you
if you guys want to take separate the
adventures you guys can do it now in
your own free time it's fine
um
[Music]
okay okay
um
wait wait wait wait
yeah
oh wait this is the wrong room oh God oh
God oh she's all gone
wow
wow okay okay
oh I'm haven't ended yet I also haven't
ended yet
um I'll probably end after we take photo
okay okay
okay when you want to take it okay let's
take it here right
um below the building
I guess we can do it we can yeah
foreign
can
perhaps anyone help me with taking the
screenshot because my Minecraft is
broken uh okay oh okay
please please please okay
come to the front come go to the front a
little bit more okay and then to your
right
too many
people
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]