[Music]
do
you
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
ticky
wait wait
wait
there we go oh there we go
oh
hello everyone
good evening good morning wherever you
are
you have come here today to watch
a kiana stream and i must say that is a
good life choice you
are making good life choices
congratulations
[Music]
thank you for the membership and thank
you for the super chat funding of
additional membership
you guys want new membership emotes
uh yeah i should make some more but i
can't seem to find
the time to make more
and i don't really want to commission
anyone because i i kind of i'm like i
can't do it myself
i can't do it myself but it would be
much easier if i would just commission
someone yeah
[Music]
so
oh yeah i guess that's an idea but i
feel nervous when you guys are watching
me
thanks for the membership emote contest
oh interesting
oh axel axel you drawing something
what are you drawing this time around
well everyone um
right i'm having water cooking right now
water is cooking starting off the stream
with a nice
tea chamomile tea
i want more expressions like we have uh
we don't have a crying kiara we need a
crying kiara
we need more chaos we need more faces
right
caramel milk caramel milk tea
crunch is bad nah nah no
sometimes you could you could use it
when i cry out of happiness
[Music]
netflix can i do that i wonder
i have no spoon except the spoon that i
used for my ice cream okay
i i ate some hog and that's ice cream
before the stream let's use that spoon
for my tea as well
just lick it queen
[Music]
now the spoon is clean enough for my tea
okay i love hugging nuts
okay so how are you guys doing
sorry for changing the
slots today was supposed to be super
mario sunshine some people
might think that i am just trying to
escape from super mario sunshine
well
[Music]
i mean in some way maybe but that's not
the reason why i
changed the slot
it's not the reason but i oh
it's not exactly the reason but there is
a problem
there is a problem that i want to
mention before
before we get into asaku now so
it's now uh a little bit after 10
10 after 11 p.m at my place okay
10 after 11 p.m now let's say
we play sakura for three hours that's
like two o'clock
after two after midnight two hours after
midnight and then we do
it's like two hours of super chat let's
say it really goes that well
then it's already uh four four o'clock
and i have uh i have to sleep somewhere
early because i
have to get up somewhat early not for
the super mario sunshine stream
but because tomorrow i talk with fubuki
senpai
12 or something so yeah
i can't stay up too late too late today
either
which is uh also
i mean staying up until five
is already too late but i always stay up
until
five or six oh god yesterday i stayed up
seven a.m or something like that
it's horrible it's absolutely horrible
but yeah worst case ah
we will just reach the super chats after
the super mario stream
because then we can go on forever i
don't have to go to sleep early or
anything after the super mario stream
but yeah
we will see how it goes okay let's see
[Music]
i have a weird headache right now
interesting
also guys i ordered let's go over let's
go to the street and gain though i
ordered
okay okay okay kiana keep some topics
for later
keep some topics for later okay sticky
notes sticky notes write down
kiara talk about what you ordered write
it down
remind me in an hour
thank you where are the kfb sticky notes
remind me in an hour to talk about
what i ordered and now
before this tangent before going into
the game
don't cry babies don't die
so one more thing uh before the stream i
played like
uh 50 minutes 50 40 minutes of sakuna
to uh yeah do
do a tiny bit of progress so basically i
stopped at the point where
uh uh someone where it seems like story
is continuing so here we are
there we go yeah yeah so murder just ran
up to me after i came home from
fighting some weird fishies
telling me that i think kai mata is gone
so we are here now
don't worry you didn't really miss
anything i just went uh ahead and
started uh tilling my field
and i got entranced to a new area where
there's like lots of fishies
flying fish actually but story-wise you
didn't miss anything
don't worry don't worry oh my god
no voice acting from me right now
because it's main story
are you guys sad oh oh that's it
wait so the baby is gone wow you only
brought me eel and salt
what the hell why
what's up
oh where did the baby go okay by the way
i did
i did hundred percent killing i did
extra work and see again
i mean this is not as good as last time
foreign as well there we go
spread it spread that sexy fertilizer
let's go uh working really hard
on my rice fields hoping
to be the very best rice farmer out
there
eventually let's scoop some poop
scoopy puppy which
i say what do we mix in the poop
ah
[Music]
what does the amber do i don't really
see anything changing when i put in more
amber
does that does it matter how much amber
i put in there
i never really see anything changing
thanks for the membership
and what makes the triangle bigger oh
oh really i didn't see it changing that
much
i was putting some bamboo some set some
cook tree branch
some moisture some more cooked tree
branch
oh there we go looking good
okay anything else i gotta get rid of so
wait i'm gonna prepare for the baby like
where what should i do where should i
where should i go
is it maybe just like on some kind of
roof or something
[Music]
oh oh it's not kai mata but someone is
on the roof how the hell did i know that
[Music]
okay
thank you
yes
you cannot go to the mystic terrace or
should we go right now
[Music]
isn't it night right now i should
probably sleep for it what is this nice
music
[Music]
yeah right it's too late to go outside
now
also she's referencing see food goes
rotten fast it is a great waste if we
have
ice food goes red and nuts of it she's
referencing ice am i getting ice cream
get talk wait that was not his name
what's he called again timeout
why did you write takamata
the baby baby
[Music]
let's go
i don't wanna i don't wanna waste or
already eat all of my
all of my rice i worked so hard for that
[Music]
okay
and then from tomorrow
we will uh there's someone missing
where's my big big boy
[Music]
tomorrow we will go and find
so i've been waiting to process that
right rice because i only have one left
and i want to eat it normally
is that a weird idea
oh the fishes can give me oil
go find the baby ah he's trying to fight
ah
okay okay i don't know
[Music]
by the way
wow what a nice spring day and double is
here
if dogo is here there's a big boy also
[Music]
let me spread my fertilizer
see it's so green now looking really
good
okay preparing the next i wish i could
dash around
what if already no no no no no
not yet why would i need water already
welcome to the membership
[Music]
it's not so many
and i don't know what to add
[Music]
yeah oh lord of the rings on the weekend
yeah i'm looking forward to that
all right let's go exploring shall we
you guys ready to go on a date with me
where are we supposed to go ah dare
okay no problem first of all though i
want to
dispatch murder oh i can't
oh because he's dispatched
oh yeah let's go here get jade
defeated
what is this
[Music]
wait what's going on
am i supposed to go in there how do i
stay in there
oh spam jump in the water
oh
[Music]
wow a nice mountain climbing time
come back
[Music]
mission avoid mission avoid okay here we
go again
hey sugar we got should we have gone
down maybe
are you guys tired you guys seem very
tired
what are you guys up to what time is it
where is this where is this going
where's the bubble going nowhere
ah how'd you stand you guys are tired
while you're working can you even focus
can you see this beautiful woman in
front of you
8 a.m good morning good morning
from
where are you at 10 pm you went out one
dollar behind
[Music]
oh my good food kinda ore
eli grass machine is kind of what tell
them
everything oh thank you oh my god uh
merchant food king.org
me to choose guys uh
write it down every time i ask you tell
me again
sticky notes sticky notes employees
[Music]
sorry
1 a.m what where where
is it 1am right now
cool almost
oh
personal information wow
well where am i ah at the beginning
again
no no no no
[Music]
here we
yeah the thing is are you stalking the
employees no it's just because if they
said super chats i
can kind of guess where they're from
what is that
yo fishies how come you can fly i
thought finch camp line
what did you fly i thought i was
something special because i'm a bird and
now you take that one special thing
about me away from me
oh
are you trying to escape
banjo
there's no way fish can actually fly
like for real maybe they're just jumping
there's no flying fish what
[Music]
is
glide okay see that's something i can
agree with
possibly but i finally doubt that they
can fly
come on come on don't don't stop
[Applause]
i believe i can fly
am i the only one who's like really bad
at the spiderman thingy
swallow flies
[Music]
oh i got new story
i got some new skills overwhelming
affliction
what okay but i don't have the thing
that you just talked about right
swallow slice i don't see it
oh i want to change my attacks
oh swing around furiously wow
[Music]
oh i'm already using that
let's use some of these new attacks
shall we
oh my my i'm already getting hungry
wait i wanna i wanna go over to that
side and i
couldn't manage to get up again okay and
then now
now now now
okay okay chill chill
oh
you guys you gotta show me those flying
fish to keep on talking about
otherwise i will not believe you
wait wait i didn't want to do that
attack goddammit
okay
let me out of the bubbles
[Music]
using skills more often and create some
other okie dokie
wait are you still alive i think you're
still alive
i imagine that a bit stronger
[Music]
before
i need to concentrate and dodge again
i'm busy
oh last second on the last second i did
it
hell yeah but i think i'm not really
done
god damn it
[Music]
oh it was done i did get until the end
did i
did i miss any anything because i also
got a treasure so i feel like i didn't
miss anything
yeah the bubble was interfering
[Music]
good evening the goddess is back
bow to your
[Music]
um
i don't know what you're talking about
of course i can fly but the fish is
no no no no fishes don't fly
[Music]
um
can i keep it for a little while i
wonder how long it takes until
[Music]
they uh disappear
you can kill the crowd to get kids and
light up the way at night
the frog which rock the frog which one
the one i killed before
[Music]
foreign
it's already looking pretty good don't
no need to be worried
keep on making that pretty like
a chad is lagging
right
[Music]
but the game didn't tell me about
planting the rice
[Music]
but it tells me about it it didn't tell
me to do it
[Music]
well i mean at least our field is um
um it's not too late it's never too late
our field is looking better now too
too late no
[Music]
need more amber wait no no no wait wait
wait wait i wanted to take this
toy that is slow for me as well
hmm
let me see
okay everyone say hello
[Music]
everyone say hello oh there we go
there's no lag it's just everyone is
sleeping
everyone's chilling keeps on stopping oh
[Music]
really
let's look at my beautiful straight
lines
first line looks acceptable
[Music]
oh oh oh oh that one wait i can do two
at once
did that just blend through it once it
did yeah i just learned it
oh my god that's amazing
[Music]
really bad camera
okay that oops they're too close
goddammit
wait that's amazing
i'm a dual rice planter now
[Music]
wait that makes everything much easier
but i hope they're not too close
[Music]
is this very bad
can i also just plant blendo like
[Music]
going backwards is really confusing
really hard to go straight
can i just go like straight forward
no can i undo something by the way can i
undo
like
can i undo this
well usually she always tells me in the
end that
um my rice is too far apart
well there you go now they're on each
other
on top of each other
usually i'm always criticized for having
it
spaced too far there you go
you're happy now wait 300 i have so many
seedlings
okay maybe there's no issue in having
them a bit closer
wait farming simulator
yes
[Music]
nice tips thank you
and i want to look at the chat but i was
also like super focused on the
on the seat right now
[Music]
my rice field looks like [\h__\h]
i want to put it in between but now
that's only really space for one
[Music]
can you do it
no not there
okay how about
[Music]
no okay
well let's go here
it's okay we have so many seeds
we can [\h__\h] up a few times
[Music]
how far is uh enough with this game by
the way does anyone know
is she already [\h__\h] am i already
behind even though i started earlier
or is she behind me
[Music]
oh god no you guys behind okay i would
have been surprised
if she wasn't because i mean i didn't
even play
off screen a little bit you're pretty
ahead okay okay okay
i feel like generally she's probably
better at this game than me
but i started much earlier
stupid rice
[Music]
whatever
no blaming the rice
[Music]
okay let's go from the
hey japanese viewers are telling me i'm
doing a good job
well now that actually gives me some
[Music]
confidence
it's a joke i love this i actually love
this i absolutely love this
i love planting rice this is why i'm
playing the game okay now this is just
horrible
this section is just horrible
[Music]
how do you like my rice everyone
i have by the way for for after the
stream
i bought some chicken curry rice
chicken katsu curry rice
at the convenience store so i can eat it
if i'm hungry after you stream
it's great it's waiting for me
in my fridge
oh my god it's already nice did this
really take me the whole goddamn day
wait i don't have space for so many what
if i have too many seedlings i don't
have so much space
hey what if i ran out of space
[Music]
i have to plant them even closer then
well i will try my best to fit
every single rice coin on my rice meal
so that all of them can one day be eaten
[Music]
not on the grid anymore is that okay as
well i wonder
who knows there's game mechanics that be
playing does someone know
there are fewer spaces here
welcome to the membership yokosuka
[Music]
it doesn't matter okay
i wish i could see where she's about to
plant it
in
[Music]
it's already turning night
well whatever wait my rice looks like
fireflies
i am planting fireflies
nah almost
yeah wait i still have so many
comments
you have some space on the sides
how relaxing is this
what a pain watching this as an actual
farmer wait why because i suck or
why why are you saying that
am i doing such a bad job that it hurts
you as a natural farmer
i'm sorry
[Music]
oh come on not everyone can be good at
this kind of stuff and
like if they didn't learn it no one know
what
you can't just be a natural challenge
[Music]
one more here
we almost got it
if she still tells me they're too like
spaced
from each other then i don't even know
wait
i need to stop
my mama
what do you think
[Music]
that's good that's not bad balance there
you go
doesn't this look good pick up frog
rocky frog
and my my my soil is looking pretty good
too
we're doing a good job should i let the
water in already
little let me see okay
should be pretty low though right
what's a good water level guys oh wait
oh it's open on the other side
[Music]
15 to 10 that's pretty high though
quite a lot
[Music]
ah it's very high right now okay maybe a
bit more
there you go
[Music]
okay oh wait so it's too late to go
casper it's too late to go
uh exploring i guess so let's sleep
wait if i if i didn't go exploring today
but have like stats from the dinner from
the day before
and i didn't go exploring do they still
apply on the day after
you know what i mean
wait why do i have so much soup stuff
but can't make any soup
where's all my food
i have so much soup stock
and i can't make soup
no soup for me
[Music]
let
you me didn't hear that that well that
was that was a nice one
[Music]
do i restart yeah i need probably some
mushrooms and stuff
[Music]
wait that's a full triangle
what is my
[Music]
oh yes oh yes oh yes
rice felt looking hella sexy to me don't
know about you guys but
i feel like it's looking quite sexy
[Music]
wait do we even need any additional we
don't really need anything at this you
know anymore right but okay let's throw
in some rabbit food
[Music]
that's it and some more
self-esteem somewhere
uh remove confidence what
that's too much
[Music]
ah
my rice is getting sick
my rice is getting sick no but but the
soil is looking so good
it doesn't look good
second tap
oh oh there's more
disease
than
can't really tell you i'm laughing at
that name but i have a reason why i'm
laughing at that
but so that looks fine that looks
fine to me
[Music]
well before it gets dark again we should
probably go explore a little bit
and can we send someone out no okay
where is he where'd he go
we got another mask here
a new mask i want a new mask on you ooh
what is that gonna fly over there
nope i could i could not
what's wrong with that
[Music]
okay that was not bad
you know when i played off-screen i
played without my
uh pro controller i played with the
normal
switch thingy uh
the court affordable in the portable
version
and in my when i fight my hands would
really hurt like actually that design is
really not
good so i realized getting a pro
controller was a good
choice because my hands would really
start hurting a lot
by playing on that normal
controller you know what i'm talking
about it actually hurts
after a tiny while already
[Music]
[Applause]
yes i did it without falling into the
spikes so what is that
[Music]
how do i get do i do something here does
it
it drags it down
[Music]
okay
let's see where it takes us
finally the maps are looking a little
bit different they they all kind of
looked um very similar to each other
in the first well okay so i don't want i
don't really want it to drag me down so
nice one
boom
[Music]
speaking of papa recently my papa
hasn't been around much
i love how the baby always reacts when i
speak of babies and stuff
oh like mama and papa a baby always
sends a crying sticker
i'm worried about that baby
i need some i need some closure about
the baby like what if one of the 30 days
are over
what will happen i need some closure
okay so how do i get up there i
you never wait for me
yes i am stupid yes yes
i am
what's down there
what let me go to that bubble
i want to go to the bubble
is that a new area
[Music]
come here
now you can carry me i like these
bubbles
and platforms he's watching nana i can
actually see that yeah
wait what do i do got them
yeah that's so difficult here
okay
delivery thank you you made my order
thank you is it happening it's only been
an hour you are on time
damn yeah
[Music]
where am i this is really a really
confusing map am i not just going back
now
at this point
i feel like this is where it came from
this is not where i came from probably
oh my god
this map is really confusing
i have no idea no imagination of where i
am right now
okay i wanted to talk about the order
right
so um before the steam i finally ordered
uh a gold xlr the big one
it's like if you don't know what that is
it's like a mixer thingy
uh it's like a pretty pretty fancy
expensive one
and i wanted to buy it already ages ago
i wanted to buy the mini one
ages ago but where am i going
where am i but back then it was sold out
everywhere so i couldn't buy it
anyway and now i finally bought it but
it was kind of overpriced
it was kind of price but i bought it
anyway because i want it
because the good thing is if you have a
mixer like that then
um there's no delay in the voice and
also i can just
give myself a reverb through the mixer
instead of giving myself
a real instead of
this
[\h__\h] instead of giving myself a reverb
uh in obs which uh one time
bugged out so bad that you guys had uh
lost your hearing if you guys remember
i think you all remembered where am i
going
rip my ears yeah i'm sorry
[Music]
i'm sorry for what it did to your ears i
still can't hear
i'm sorry but yeah and not really
not really in order to prevent that but
it's an extra effect
what
[Music]
and now it's now it's not and now it's
like already like
cotton i gotta add some hot water wait a
second
my teeth
wait i waited one hour for my teeth
[Music]
gotta make some hot water and add it to
my teeth
okay sounds good sounds good to me
throw it in the microwave now it's
downstairs
[Music]
what did you order last time what do you
mean all the last time
what do you mean or the last time this
is one of what i wanted to talk about
though the order
did i go down before
no okay
if i come back here next time i'll have
no idea where i was already and where i
didn't go in
hmm difficult what the hell is
that stupid face
that like was helping me
[Music]
i'm gonna die
i'm gonna die no let me kill your face
okay it's over i gotta go
[Music]
no i do not add milk to my teeth
yeah i know i could just microwave it
but it's downstairs and i'm upstairs
i don't want to go downstairs okay
water is done
[Music]
here we go
you guys are so quiet today
are you still not awake everyone
what kind of tea are you drinking
chamomile tea with lots of honey
because streaming for hours every day is
really straining
on my voice i really don't understand
how
all the senpai's are doing it
i don't understand
that's a lot of weeds
almost dripping asleep sleepy then cozy
game
you're way too energetic
i'm trying to entertain you guys
sleepy chickens
[Music]
your pain is my entertainment
well that's good to hear is there some
fertilizing there okay i'll i'll spread
it tomorrow
tomorrow round long day and sick as hell
hope you'll get better soon
please take care of yourself everyone
it's getting
it's turning winter so
everyone be careful of your health
oh no let's not eat the same thing
basket clam
do you guys like clams i think i already
asked you but i didn't really get your
answers
[Music]
i want to keep those clams are good
clowns are pretty nice
[Music]
i don't like seafood absolutely not
never try not a fan yeah
times are okay muscles are great so go
to
goat means good
wait it's already been in hours i feel
like i accomplished nothing
okay i need water
[Music]
a game of the year um you accomplished
making us happy
that is adorable i love you guys
and don't go waiting there sitting here
with a cutie patootie
[Music]
one day i want to get a dog at the snowy
to my cats
but i would i wonder if i can like make
them
like get along with the dog properly but
if i get like a dog as a baby
then i think my cats would be able to
[Music]
oh my listen to this music my cat bully
my cat
eh you mean your cat phone is your dog
[Music]
no hey i want
they need like so much care for their
fur
because they're like really fluffy and
they lose a lot of hair to shed
so much hair but they're so fluffy and
too sweet i want them
i want to summon i want one
what are we gonna do we go here
[Music]
reach the exit will i ever reach the
exit
[Music]
yeah they're huge fluff balls so so she
looked there
but i also i would ask i would also go
for a courtney
or or as shibanga
although i know uh they are kind of like
um
they do whatever they want to do they're
like teenagers
i kind of prefer like bigger dogs i
don't really like the super super tiny
dogs that much
like uh what's a tiny dog what's a tiny
dog i mean pomeranians are cute
but i don't know
hopefully you can go there again
they kind of creep me out a little bit
i'm sorry for all the chihuahua lovers
out there
but the way that their eyes look like
they're popping out of their heads
creeps me out a little bit you know
small dogs are more aggressive that's
funny though
that's
ah
[Music]
in japan i see like outside i barely see
any dogs but when i see a dog in japan
outside it's usually a really small dog
at least like in tokyo
outside of tokyo i see more more people
uh
walking around with a bit bigger dogs
i guess it's just because in tokyo the
apartments are really really tiny
which actually now that i wait how do i
how do i get over there oh okay okay
i didn't fall all the way down how do i
get up there
how do i get there oh wait wait wait
wait
yes yes
yes we got the treasure i was thinking
there must be something special over
there
moscow
enemies drop 30 less amber oh increases
that money expense skills received
look at me
just fitting for a bird like me don't
you think
oh hey hey buddy are you going
for a swim swim or for a fly fight
i want to thrill you on a stick in the
fire
see that's like that is so simple
but already so enjoyable don't you agree
fish on a stick grilled in a simple
fireplace
isn't that delicious
i ate that for the first time in my life
i think in one of these um
festivals that i told you about remember
the salt is very strong here
[Music]
now
yeah okay so i've been here before
should i try to go down i don't want to
go down it wouldn't go up
let's go down let's go down
back attacks i learned something new
well that was worth it i suppose
nicely whatever that wins if you have to
take a look at that eventually
schnauzers are pretty cute ah i think
you mean the dogs now just
yeah i think i've seen those before i
think i know what you mean
yeah they're cute
don't fall
seasonings damn we're getting all those
treasures right now
okay do we just fall down now
orange super chat to the fella michael's
flowers
it wasn't really my idea but i'm glad it
helps you
the birds are bad the birds are bad
mean birds very mean
uh by the way guys oh yeah by the way
guys
wait first i wanted to say something sad
but now i tell you something happy
uh my pc my new pc is arriving
tomorrow or like or the day after
tomorrow
[Music]
[Applause]
yay
and you know i was thinking okay
how do i know what's coming there how
would i know
so i was thinking now that i have a now
that i get my bp
i would want to of course you know play
a game that actually like
test the power of pc because these are
switch games they don't test the power
of the pc at all
it really doesn't matter how strong my
pc is mostly
for these kind of streams
the only one i could think of was yakuza
but turns out
we don't have permission for you
you know how the statement for siga
recently
sega recently came out and i told you
that i fought and think that this is
separate from sega america
and i checked with my management and
that was indeed the case
yeah so i cannot continue yakuza
just yet maybe some time in the
future
oh my god
i don't think we have permission for
that because cali would be playing would
be playing it already i think she's
waiting for that game
to be approved
for a long time already
definitely looks amazing though
i guess the games that i'm really
interested in don't really need
that much of a beef pc usually it's more
like um
it's more like all the games that i like
are like on consoles
jrpg yeah they're all on they're all on
you know
parcels mostly was i here before
gta is not really my type of game
doom also
no phoenix rising see that's actually
my mom my mom uh greetings to my mom
she's
sick at the moment hope she gets better
soon but she
she uh emailed me with a link saying
this could be a nice game for you know
and send me a link to
phoenix rising i was like yeah
actually i know i know that game already
and i was thinking the same thing
but then again isn't that also console
game
so again the pc specs don't really
matter for this one either
and uh
i was thinking if i play phoenix rising
or whatever that name was
then i could just play zelda
or would you guys be more interested in
seeing me play that
phoenix rising but um i don't even we
don't even have permission for that at
the moment i think
we would need permission for that as
well and
that could take a while oh wait but
that's
isn't that playstation 5 exclusive
i would have to buy a playstation 5. and
apparently
in japan right now i wasn't trying so i
don't know but apparently in japan right
now it's a little bit hard to actually
get a ps5
because they're not restocking oh my god
i was legit dying
scalpers what are scalpers
um monster hunter world ah
do we have permission for monster hunter
well
oh but one thing wait i remember some
one one thing i could play
with uh the bfpc oh my god
is a final fantasy 14
right wouldn't that be a good idea
i don't know if you guys would enjoy
seeing me play
an mmrpg
[Music]
because final fantasy 14 is the only
final fantasy game that
we have permission for at the moment
the only and i actually i really like
mmorpgs personally i
love mmrpgs and ina wants to play it as
well
so we were thinking of playing it
together
me and ena
final fantasy uh julian
[Music]
would you guys watch that maybe try one
stream but it's hard to say a long time
it would i i would want it to be a long
term project
to be honest
renewing my ff14 membership right now
yeah you would watch it really i always
was wondering how you guys would react
to a mmrpg stream
the thing is i played final fantasy
before a long time ago
uh and i i leveled up to the max level
that was back then level
60 or something like that or 50 i don't
know
and then everyone who i was playing with
who was already max level and just
waiting for me to reach max level
they quit the game because they were
already playing for ages and then
then i finally reached maxwell thanks
guys for the super chats i finally
reached max level and was like yay i can
finally play with them
and then they all left and then i was
all alone
and i didn't know anyone else in the
game and you know how it's like pretty
hard
in a huge game like that with already an
established
community to actually like be part of it
you have no chance to be part of that
community
at that point
so oh fire resistance i want to keep
that
does the spring water go bad does that
spoil
[Music]
that's why i usually prefer to play
mmorpgs
on the first day when they come out when
they launch
because that pretty much guarantees that
i am always part of the
community that's how i used to do it i
played so many
so many mmorpgs i played so many
so many i love them so much audience
fear oh yeah i love audience free but
that's not an mmorpg
spring when it stays good oh okay good
okay
such as well it started out with
wonderful crafts
and then um i played i played like
lots of anime style mmorpgs like
fly for fun uh trickster online
uh aura kingdom and eden eternal
and a bunch more
i love them so much
and i i used to always play like from
right the beginning so
enter your curry what about my curry i
don't want to eat it right now
can't be the guilt yeah let's make a
cave video
so yeah i really missed playing mmorpgs
but eventually
mmorpg's in like a style that i like
start
stopped coming out like there was a
phase when
a [\h__\h] ton of anime mmrpgs came out
one after another um
[Music]
but eventually they they started like
goddamit i have no fertilizers i forgot
eventually like
double the developers started making the
games for
smartphones instead and i
i really don't like the idea of playing
an
mmorpg on the smartphone
[Music]
i really don't like that
do
finally what the hell
what the hell i don't understand why it
does that sometimes
[Music]
here i am here i am once again
i fall into pieces can't deny it can't
pretend
[Music]
you won't have to see the tears i cry
what were you saying a lot i don't know
man i was just saying i'm glad you guys
understand what i'm talking about
[Music]
have some nostalgic kelly clarkson
okay so that's that wow it looks so
fluffy
you can't even see me
[Music]
no playing around
no playing around i gotta go
i gotta go by the way when is the baby
and the dude coming back ever
when are they coming back okay we have
to we have to defeat more enemies
i have to reach the exit wherever the
hell that exit is and we have to
question my question my question mark
you gotta oh they are in here oh
[Music]
what on earth is going on i'm not even
doing anything
but in order to fix it i just
activate and reactivate it in obs uh
streamlabs
is this a obs thing
[Music]
it's not like i'm doing anything i don't
really have to
to feed all those enemies again do i
probably an obscene yeah
no no no i'm not pushing any mute
buttons i have my controller in my hand
and that's it
wait a second
let's go up again come on come on
you've been playing ffx14 for
five years i still love the game but i
had nothing to
burn out to the lack of content i enjoy
i've been raiding regularly but i prefer
to take breaks
oh it wasn't here before what is here
oh that's where i wanted to go
but i have to go down again no
just keep swimming does it happen if you
stop speaking nope
even when i'm in the middle of speaking
i don't know i have no idea why it's
doing that maybe i should really switch
to obs instead of obs streamlabs because
i'm using obs streamlabs
should probably switch
[Music]
you accept uh banner of course i do
there's a whole fan art tag that you can
use
go ahead draw whatever you want to draw
wait wait wait wait wait wait
whatever get some some of those fishies
for lunch
let me grill you fishes and bunnies ouch
what the hell
how dare you leave me alone
he's not gonna reach at this point what
you mean the end again
i used to enable noise reception from my
mic
and i consider my own voices noise
ignore the enemies okay
where do i go though i don't know what's
the right direction this place is so
confusing
[Music]
what role class did you prefer to play i
was often the healer
but sometimes sometimes i would play dps
but i was never the tank
i didn't want that responsibility on
myself
whenever i was dps i would i would do
some kind of
mage class though oh finally i made it
over here finally that's the first time
i made it over here
health powder okay that's it
where are we now
[Music]
i was told to ignore the enemies now but
they're kind of disturbing me
uh excuse me what the [\h__\h] is going on
what why is this happening
can i get a healing please don't do i
not have any
natural healing going on right now well
this is really bad
[Music]
young
you think my microphone doesn't like
mmos
do i have anything i can eat that will
heal me
is it health powder
i can't eat that
[Music]
i will die
yep yep and once again i
have not been able to find my way
on this map my last name
do you guys know where to go
[Music]
i don't understand the game you don't
need to understand the game
just watch no problem
no need to understand anything
i'm just making rice living my best
life
i'm just trying to
get some more ingredients before i go
[Music]
home
and let's go back
i'm watching with my cat on my chest oh
my god
i want a cat on my chest as well
he won two did you kill the deer yet oh
no
oh josana wasn't weren't you the one who
last time
gave me so many tips was that you
i was like literally looking for your
comments
without you
[Music]
water only four percent oh my god
what got you on your chest
[Music]
well that would be lovely
pick up brad skill what red skill
oh
[Music]
george strength counter acquired
it what's that
i'm gonna spread it now i know i should
spread it in the morning but
i'm just gonna make another one right
now
i'm a first time on your stream oh
welcome
thank you for coming thank you for the
subject
how i can infuse items
with those skills
that's cool
[Music]
what do we add maybe a bean
that does the green dough oh okay
okay
rotten food salt and spring one
you mean i should add the spring water
to the rice fields
what do i eat tonight bee lover that
sounds amazing to me
someone coulda would like that
[Music]
sounds like a delicious dinner
i don't think i have salt at the moment
i use it up already
be larvae
some oil by the way i never used that
oil
lamp light thingy before the fish oil
what was that where you can um continue
to explore in the night
i never used that one before oh yes
[Music]
oh i don't really want to play a dollar
game but i have so many games going on
at the moment
fire emblem sakura super mario sunshine
minecraft and every now and then i want
to do
karaoke i want to
[Music]
spread that fertilizer give me the best
price ever
come on a busy bird yes
very busy so much to do
so much to stream
oops oh my god
oh my god oh yeah let's add some springs
oh my god okay wait wait a second wait a
second
uh oops two rounds and food
bamboo hemp sets oh
okay branch what does the roots do
let's add what does the fish do for
okay what else will now
[Music]
i don't even need the spring water at
the moment
what should i end
[Music]
what helps with the pesticides the salt
right
but i don't have salt
[Music]
garlic i also don't have garlic
wasabi garlic goddammit i have nothing
like that
oh well hello
should be good enough
[Music]
start harvesting i could already start
harvesting but i will not
[Music]
not yet i will wait until you guys said
last time
autumn right i should wait until autumn
was it
[Music]
try to talk to tamar
you mean the fat guy
he's not here no wait who was that
again
i thought why is the dog i should talk
to the dog
i
[Music]
yeah my spirit dog is called tom and now
it wasn't dead okay well
oh you're right
sorry sorry sorry it's been a week i
forget
names okay now how
oh god how do i get okay
ignore all of them
how do i get to where i want to go
this is a labyrinth like literally oh
god
leave me alone i want to go up here you
can't catch me
there leave me alone please
where is the right direction
[Music]
your path was correct last time i have
no idea where i went last time
let's just try to continue going the
right side eventually we go down or we
go up and then
then we go probably in another direction
i don't know i don't know where i'm
going
do i go down
don't play game
oh now that's okay i was already there
down i should go down oh okay
ah the fishes again
they're like slicing themselves up
making themselves ready for me to fill
them
they're making sashimi out of themselves
nice good species
taking the workload off of me thank you
thank you
self slicing fish what
that was good that was good i didn't
even see where i was going i still
went for it very good very good piano
japanese 101 so
all right let's go over there i don't
know what is there
[Music]
but
there's nothing here find your way do we
go down
give them some good sparks we're gonna
go home with some meat as well
can't just go home bare-handed
[Music]
i don't think there's anything here and
i'm not gonna ignore them
yeah the time just flies i'm gonna
wha okay i actually i wanted to go
i always forget like in the middle there
when you fall down there and the middle
point
i want to try to go to the right side
but i keep on missing it because it goes
down way too fast
okay how do i continue here
go down just go right oh okay ignore it
wait do i have to fight them no okay
well here i am now
bubble thank you for helping
but these aren't really in the way i
gotta kill them
i never really used that thing and
during the fight
but i see people doing like really some
cool moves
using that the spider-man theme
i don't know how to use it properly
uh
[Music]
tough
oh what on earth
why why why why why why it keeps on
happening today or not
[Music]
give me a [\h__\h] break
am i going in the right direction after
look on the whole
maybe it's maybe obs is censoring me
because i'm cursing i feel like i was
here before though
oh spring
am i getting closer
now right okay down here
thank you guys
ignore those edx oh i think i have to
fight them
starting off very well
come on
um
i saw what you were doing there piggy i
know you wanted to
ramble me
not this time
[Music]
what's wrong with you guys
come down here
what the hell is going on with them nani
it's turning night come on no don't [\h__\h]
around
come on come on come on i don't want to
do this again who's next
go right oh can i already go
am i so late all right jackson
oh is that
thank you guys for helping me that was
so
good
that was so big
do you guys know what a kappa is i know
that in that slang i don't know
culture whatever kappa is used in some
different
way but do you guys know what a japanese
kappa is
foreign
i thought because he's a baby he's just
not speaking
[Music]
hmm
he probably couldn't find his way back
because it's a
really
m
rice on her back like rice uh
grass thingy what is she going on
it's a cup
i
m
[Music]
him
he's one of us now
[Music]
you're safe now don't cry
i bought the go xlr that's what i wanted
to tell you guys the go xlr and my pc is
coming
my new pc is coming today after tomorrow
set it up
why are they so quiet
[Music]
i just realized i can make a new sound i
didn't realize i can make that sound
wow i didn't know i can do that
i just discovered something new about
myself
[Music]
bird noises yeah i can make crown noises
now yeah
mating call
[Music]
or
i'm driving and i heard a cute sound so
i pulled over
shouldn't you be pulling over constantly
then because i'm talking constantly
[Music]
yep seems about right
summer is already over no
that's not
keep on driving my friend but drive
safely
[Music]
yeah you're really something special
thank you that's so sweet of you
damn you guys are also charming
i really wonder why aren't you all
already
married
secretly dissing you
well although i do think many of you are
probably quite young
as well
it's harrison i'm waiting for autumn
apparently it's better if you wait a
little bit
more
by the way i saw people keep on uh
sending me the video even though i
already saw it uh the video
of um alexander reacting to
me reacting to the baby and then
recently they also uploaded another
video where the parents
were singing my opening bgm melody
to the baby and the baby was like
it's so adorable holy crap it's so cute
my baby i love you mom
even the wife uh humped my melody
it was very cute
the baby looked much more excited when
the when the mother was
humming my bgm though not as excited
when the
when the father was humming the video
[Music]
what does that tell us the mama is a
better hummer
how did my father and mother meet on
this island
oh i haven't done these voices in a
while
uh oh so you are finally showing
interest in the story of the romance
is that astonishing you may have
forgotten but i
too am a blast summit blossoming maiden
i do give thought to matters of the
heart from time to time
and if it regards my parents i have all
the more reason to wonder
there you go see that's the food that
see that's why that's that's that's my
kind of food that's why i that's the way
that i
thought it was meant that's why why i
translated it that way
he was not laughing that was kind of an
angry food
that's how i thought that was okay
[Music]
how dare you mock me
you're talking about your mom pop
or was it a different i don't even know
any much
i went here too it is a long tail
i will start at the beginning
it was a doubtful yeah that could also
be it long ago
this island was mostly inhabited not by
demons but by the ashigumo tribe
i have heard that they preferred not to
live in groups but rather
excelled at making a living as
individuals
yet even so one day a terrible disease
began to spread
for the ashikumo it was an unmitigated
disaster
one after another they fell
then lady toyohana appeared along with
this house
so ladies okana's mother brought only
not only herself from the lowly ramen
but his house as well
the power hitting within my divine
raiment
is incalculable indeed
why are you laughing
at first there's actually cool mover
very rarely up there and even tried to
kill her
but lady toilana paints their suspicions
no heat
and instead began to care for them
a medicine she infused until the water
from this past worked like a miracle
the icy groomer swiftly overcame their
predicament
owing a great death to her the icy girl
appointed her as the princess
and vowed to aid her throughout her life
here
wait is that all you have not so much as
touched upon topic at hand
i told you it is a long tail i will
continue it some other time
what oh god she saw somebody
the moment i get super excited about
seeing a cat
it mutes me again why would you do that
finally we got the cat oh
yes i was waiting for this moment my
whole life
[Music]
a cat
you do understand that we are living day
to day here yes that our future remains
utterly uncertain
we simply don't have the means to care
for useless cats
cats are not useless
it might do a good job of catching pesky
mice in storehouse yeah my setup called
casper
mice you say i have not seen any in this
past
but if it can make itself useful
she's already planning to get
then i'll shall allow it even if i can
see the merit
in having another tool an hour even i
can see
the merit in having another tool at our
disposal
[Music]
thanks for the super chat oh look at
this cutie pie
[Music]
nice usage of what i have taught you
consider yourself fortunate cat from now
on you will earn you keep
oh yeah where's the kitty cat where is
it where is it where is it
where is my where is my cat where is it
[Music]
where is the kitty cat
right that's the dopamine
honey where is this drawer
is that this where's my cat
[Music]
hmm
the cat where is the cat
very realistic just like cat in real
life
that is true okay whatever ignore the
cat for now
it's autumn should i harvest that oops
yeah i actually just started
i wanna wait
[Music]
should i spread fertilizer before
harvesting or does it not do anything
now anyway
but i can't do anything i can't i can't
do that
no i drained the body
[Music]
won't do anything oh okay
okay draining the water
let me get that rice
is it drained
[Music]
okay
look at me oh wait
i can start right i can do it right here
[Music]
i hope i didn't have to wait to dry the
peelers and then that comes afterwards
right
cali look i'm a reaper i'm a rice reaper
you may be creeping stones but i am
reaping lives
uh i'm reaping rice not likes
pretty close
[Music]
funny are you eno or something serial
killer written as
c e r e a la
really good
you know i'm somewhat of a reaper myself
yeah i gotta tell that to cali
[Music]
i like this music
wait could i couldn't i have done this
at night
and gone exploring instead during the
day
oh wow
[Music]
we did it guys
you should have done this at night right
better to harvest during your day really
oh is there a reason for that
yes oh okay oh well then i don't feel
like i wasted my time
i just feel like i should go exploring
every day so that i keep
so that i don't um
run out of food you know
ah pick up the rice and dry salt it
wait did i have one before
[Music]
all right i don't have enough places can
i do it
oh you can place it on top as well okay
okay
wow we have so much now we started i
think the first time we started out
uh with only like putting it on three of
these things
we barely had anything to
[Music]
i told drive i guess it was true i
wanted to say two first but then i was
like
oh yeah there was only one wrap ah yeah
one wrap per side right
yeah we've come a long way from that
after the rice is dried it must be fresh
but using the cookie bush is such a pain
oh are we getting an upgrade
if i fresh too quickly the husks will
not be fully removed but doing it fast
tediously will take eons
always never very skilled i did myself
that's why i would first take off the
husks
and later remove the extra leaves and
stalks like we're cut with them
oh is it easier that way why did you
teach me this sooner
well it may be easier for it
if you're fine with doing it that way
then why not just make a tool that
speeds up the process
oh do you have an idea for such a tool
oh uh i don't know how well it will turn
out but
i'll give it a shot i'll give you a
materialist so get it gathering
if it will lighten my workloads i shall
spare no effort
[Music]
hold up a quinta's voice i always do it
differently
oh you can trade rhymes for other items
what or where is tama
where is tom um i guess everyone is
sleeping now anyway
but where is he usually
guess i have to wait until tomorrow
right
drying by the rains yeah awesome ah he's
in here
i can i go up here oh i didn't know i
could go up here
you've obtained an old droplet now you
can venture out at night
oh no nocturnal demons are much fiercer
but you may make some
surprising discoveries if you can defeat
them
[\h__\h] i didn't know i could go up here
[Music]
there's a room behind what
what i did
[Music]
magical
in my room
oh
[Music]
the game didn't tell me okay
i'm running out of my rabbit meat
i'm running out of it
we basically have no food we have to go
exploring the next day
oh there we go so i continue my tail
yay hey waited
at least addressed my question this time
around the time lady told you honda was
exalted by the ashikumo as your princess
my master lords take me was expelled
from the capital
what did my father blow up the garner as
well
he had a great crawl with the previous
lady kamuhiki it wasn't uproar
immense enough to overturn the capital
whoa
lord's talking we wandered from lands to
land
eventually arriving here at hinois
island the ashikumo tribe was in the
habit
of eliminating all outsiders but in the
face of
the mightiest war god they could do
nothing
uh as a shrugged of their attacks he
realized that they seem to be guarding
the princess
it was curious what a furry-faced
ashikuma
princess might look like and so he
headed to this very past intending to
have a good laugh at their meeting
i like this guy my father was impulsive
indeed
as he tossed one asi kumu after never
out of his way he finally arrived at the
pass
but as soon as he laid his eyes on lady
toyohana
right here in this house he froze
that is how breathtaking lady told you
hannah's beauty was
for her apart lady toyohana was
similarly
taken aback they stood there for what
seemed like an eternity
staring in awe at one another
wow it was love at first sight ah
so wonderful
getting tired
however they could not reveal what was
blossoming in their hearts
as an excuse to remain here lord talk
and if he began
exterminating demons a useless effort in
everyone's eyes
does he like my whistle i'm not a good
whistler
ugh how awkward can one man be
i think it's cute
it was around that time when
disorienting spell began to enchant
his past the days passed peacefully for
a time
some were faded and the mountain was
dampered in splendid shades of
red and yellow
and that is when it appeared in the
northern welling
i will resume the story from here on
everyday
once again you failed to cut to the
height of what i actually had hope to
hear
[Music]
whistling excuse me i know but you
should say i'm good at it anyway
i'm not whistling those are my bird
noises
boot calls is it giant
no it's flying it should be right soon
okay wow
we have to go exploring
damn hold on voice acting oh bubbling
sandbar
what that sounds amazing that sounds
like fun
okay what was the talent where do i send
pokemon where's the
best area to send talemon to
like he's uh what was it meat i think
what's the best area for him
can we send him in here
i wonder if he can fit in there in that
hole
he does everything a little
let's send him to the forest
anna let's send them
[Music]
in 120 seconds
no not today
what
this gaming host is so relaxing thank
you oh my god look at that beautiful
scenery
left oh god i didn't see you right there
wow
[Music]
very low what the hell i didn't want to
go here
oh my god where am i where am i where am
i
wait wait wait wait wait what the hell
is going on here
yeah that was totally on purpose of
course
oh god oh god
oh god oh my oh god what is that bubble
doing there anyway
[Music]
am i too weak
what is this pokemon
[Music]
i was too weak for this mom
i think i'm too weak what the hell oh my
god
at least let me clear those moms
in the first area stupid [\h__\h] bubbles
oh my god okay but the turtle is like
really [\h__\h] strong
i'm on the level right i i this is uh
incredible
uh really wait am i
like supposed to have different
equipment on
how about strike weapon
maybe that helps a little bit
you could start polishing the rice oh
yeah i guess
i guess but i have
but i like want to go home without
anything
[Music]
i want to bring home some food
okay actually i feel a bit stronger
right now
come here fishy fish don't fall down
i don't think we can ugh too much
against the
turtle right now trouble seems
incredibly strong oh yeah but now i'm
making much more damage
does the turtle have a weak spot or
something oh my god oh
oh what was that hello
okay [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] your chill i don't
wanna i don't wanna [\h__\h] you
sorry but i'm done with you
i want to get something out of this
before i go home
yeah when the turtle was flipped
probably that was uh
a good moment to kill it but i don't
care about the turtle anymore
i don't care
[Music]
come back bubble you have to flip the
turtle
yeah it seems so
oh nightfall what could that be
hello fishies
the birds and the fish are so obnoxious
i think this is the first time i ever
used the word obnoxious in
my streams here here i am kiara using
new words
are you impressed about my vocabulary
not as impressed as i am
smart bird very smart wow
is that what i was supposed to do
there's another cello there i don't
wanna i don't wanna go there
i don't wanna talk to the turtle
[Music]
did i tell you you can talk to me
i prefer to eat chicken not fish give me
the chicken where's the chicken
wow
it's not cannibalism no
you are wrong
very good very good i don't like it when
i don't see where i'm jumping
i don't like that feeling
[Music]
there's a lot going on here as well
oh my god i just want to explore a
little bit
[Music]
hug me again stupid face
no one is allowed to hump this majestic
phoenix here
oh my god please make it stop
oh my god oh my god this is such a chaos
moment
they are so strong
well as long as i'm not dying you have
to have the
bird i just i just felt it in my
controller
the bird i call it a bird it's official
it's confusing me they're manipulating
me
they're making me think if they're one
of me one of us
but they're not you can't fool me i know
you're not a bird
i know what birds look like they don't
look like them
no no no no i just want to know what's
going on here you know
just let me let me just let me pass
perfectly
nice
[Music]
did you guys see that oh my god okay
oh yeah i shouldn't be the one laughing
do i still have some natural healing or
no
is it open how
just be stupid that's the thing you can
do the best i think
just be stupid these stupid empty scenes
don't you know you can do it
ah oh no okay going home bye bye
caribou
[Music]
you always got to know your limits guys
it's not a bad thing
to like like take a break
and you know
don't overdo it you have to know your
limits if you feel like
it's enough and you can't do it anymore
you can't go any further
don't feel bad about it just take a
break
don't force yourself to do things
well we got a lot out of that
grind more it are you telling me to
grant more like
foreign
[Music]
why why does it keep on happening
anyway my reaction was chicken excuse me
how dare you say that to me
[Music]
i am a phoenix and i'm scared of no one
and nothing
let's see what our new techniques are oh
look there's so much
use yeah i thought i can use something
new though
i still have to use that i thought we
have a new
you haven't made it yet you need to talk
to kinta oh god damn it do it
but that's so much no
i should have talked to quinta
let's go we can do it
yeah bye yoga
ah that's going to take live 35
oh my gosh should i let someone else
load up all the save
uh wait uh
or do i should i let someone else handle
it and then
whatever whatever i'm gonna do it
grasshopper no welcome to the membership
don't i'm just gonna damn it
foreign
[Music]
hello what i was just getting angry
about is that someone was translating
what i was saying
in english in japanese and as my name
they wrote birth
i mean it's true but
bird says how about kiana says how about
phoenix says
huh why is it just bird accurate
translation
yes i am a bird but i'm more i'm not
i feel like you shouldn't put me like
actually i
don't i don't like being in the same in
the same
category as those other birds i'm a
phoenix okay
i want them the queen the god of birds
and i'm the legendary birds moltres
i'm a pokemon okay if anything what is
your pokemon
[Music]
but still birds well um
well i suppose
but look how fast i can do it
how much more how much more
do i have something new for halloween as
well from kinta or do i really have to
do that myself
that's a lot of hauling to do though
that was so exhausting
oh god now that's really exhausting
okay it's gonna take a while ah actually
wait is that
it doesn't feel like it's more than
usual
i guess that doesn't really get more no
matter how much
rice you have
60 is a good balance
verb said it's exhausting
i am phoenix same amount of time yeah it
seems so
all right then i'm going for a hundred
percent
nothing less for a majestic bird like me
sixty percent is not enough i am ten out
of ten till i'm going for a hundred
[Music]
says i'm a physics
shut up shut up
what do you want there we go we didn't
have
[Music]
oh wait she said something different
than usual
she said something more positive i
didn't hear it well because i was
clapping
but she said something positive
improvements i think
see i was doing the tilling off screen i
had 99 very good but
very good turn time period early
yeah you guys were telling me i'm doing
it too late
it says early
i could have done it even later than
that
what dried no what do you mean dried no
damage from wheat's large no
[Music]
well i don't care looks good enough to
me
[Music]
didn't do mid-summer drying oh
ah because i dried it in oh look at
those two cuties
because i dried it in in autumn
but i thought it was better to wait for
adam
when you like stand for a while it gets
longer
wait wait wait i think though i saw it
in the video
don't you get longer i thought you get
longer
[Music]
doesn't it turn into a long cat
maybe that was a different cat
oh my god
do it again
love it oh my god it's so cute
the way the paws are like bouncing
oh i'm happy
how do i let you down though i can't let
it down i have to carry it forever
okay well um does it make sense to
fertilize the field before winter comes
or does it only make sense to do it
after winter is over
[Music]
foreign
okay so before winter
no need now you need the triangle max
out
so i will try to max it out after winter
that's usually
what i actually no off screen i was
um fertilizing it every day
anyway what are we doing okay what that
means though
do you have something yummy no
okay maybe uh
fat boy now he's gone got them
but he wants to tell me something
[Music]
yes chad do your thing do say what you
want to say
yeah yeah yeah
you're happy now you're happy now
but then that's a lot of rice damn
[Music]
yay
we can do so much now
actually no there's not much choice
[Music]
let's make some
oil thank you for the super chat nice oh
[Music]
nice rice 69
how funny ha ha ha ha nice super chat
do we want some vinegar
[Music]
we want some malt do we want some mochi
we want all of it
that was the disgusting one though right
i don't want to make that unfiltered
cloudy white socket
oh you can make amazing i drank that
before i mean i don't like alcohol
alcohol at all but
it was all right
[Music]
let me check the menu mascara
isn't that a dessert though
well i might that looks good to
[Music]
oh sorry by the way tama as you are in
no doubt aware these shiny stones called
amber fly out of demons when i defeat
them
what in the two realms are they oh i
want to know that
uh a very specialized spiritual
energy energy that has been accumulated
by the tree of
creation its forbes changes depending on
the density of spiritual energy of crude
and
can range from fragments to magatama
jewels and large orbs
ah so that explains their shape
additionally
because amber is the crystallization of
divine power you can increase your own
strength by gathering it
this is all in addition to it being used
as currency in the capital
huh verbal boy there exists to
counterpart to amber known as a spirit
bowl
it is also a cluster of spiritual energy
but it does not crystallize or otherwise
take shape
instead it has the ability to resist
resid reside in objects
if you manage to obtain any it would be
in
wise to infuse them into your equipment
man this hurts my fruit
amber huh
thank you thank you for letting me know
tips for committing to learning to
comment
tips for committing to learning a new
language
more in japanese i'm struggling i say it
again and again
communication is key just talk every day
use the language every day
and then it should be quite easy
actually but
motivation and passion is also very
important and it's winter
why you you why okay so you guys say i
don't have to care about the
about the soil just yet
look cute today oh thank you
[Music]
ask what is your first impression of the
second uh indonesian
ah i already talked about that in my
fire emblem stream
uh so i don't want to get too deep into
it i guess but
i think they're like really cute they're
designed they're really cute
and i'm really curious too there's a
i'll be watching all of them of course
oops
[Music]
yeah and actually uh the zombie girl
is rigged by the same papa
kefi papa the same as me so obviously
oh obviously um she moves very nicely
very smoothly
and i love uh lam sensei her designer
i love i love the art of lamps and then
we got we got the hand pressure
why do you get to name it that's such a
dumb name
you understand nothing it's paralyzing
what it does not in what it is called
there's a weird fly flying around here
[Music]
potential volume low
really should be pretty high
oh there we go i got it i can't do his
voice i never know how to do his voice
we've done great working dog
yeah you're so good now let's try
putting this hand pressure to the test
yeah it's too late now
[Music]
thanks for bringing me into here but i
already did everything by hand
[Music]
i already didn't
yeah my papa seems to like lamb sensei
and love since it really seems like my
papa's art
i don't know if it's why i'm using
demonic materials or what but my
weapon's got strange powers you can
imagine
being a goddess and all you know
wait let me drink something a hydration
check everyone
[Music]
did you hear that water
damn i just drank water but okay yes
always listen to piano
jade sledgehammer what
attack power 100 free oh [\h__\h] yes please
[Music]
damn son what do you need for that hemp
jade okay
i'm gonna get it for you
[Music]
thanks bro
daily special meal deal
double phoenix burger
double phoenix burger comes with two
slices of pineapple
um ah yeah okay there she tells me the
things that someone told me in the chat
today
i wish i would have known that before
murder focuses on food kaimao goes for
fertilizer oh what he goes for poop
[Music]
she's not wearing them right now i think
but
yeah wait is that
i haven't talked to him in a long time
does he have anything to say to me
i am adapted to your parents but
therefore to you if you are in trouble
do not hesitate
to speak with me i'm always in trouble
i'm always in trouble please help me
i'm a damsel in this dress please help
me
pineapple goes past that's with
pineapple
yes i agree
okay so merida was food right where do
we send does it matter
where i sent them
[Music]
let's go to the goddamn bubbling
sandberg and i should be
i i'm stronger now right
hey i was wondering if you were
what
wow that's a
interesting comment
i have no idea what you're talking about
absolutely no idea
you're giving me a little bit of an
aggression problem here i'm
getting a bit angry here with these
enemies you're pissing me off a little
bit i'm not
safe honestly a bit annoying here
but oh i'm scrambling i think i'm
stronger
what okay here comes the turtle how do i
put you over like a pancake how do i do
that
okay you really got me okay
[Music]
[Applause]
what used to round up raymond i don't
even know what that is
i don't know the names of my skills man
i don't know what you mean
how do people remember all the names of
the skills
[Music]
what does that tell us everyone
rice makes you strong food makes you
strong
everyone eat your rice rice is awesome
you can make so much
yummy food with rice i love uh
like oh all kinds of food you can make a
rice i love it i love i love
curry i love everything that you make
with rice i love it i love it i love it
rice is powered
very much
again
are there bubbles here to only to
distract me or
they're also here to help me in any way
because it feels like it's only there to
annoy the [\h__\h] out of me
[Music]
whoa what was that explosion oh are they
like
letting their bombs fly again
i don't even know where i'm standing
anymore
i completely lost track of who i am and
where i am
pain pickle
the close trips are back with revenge
i've eaten too much rabbit
there they have now come to eat some
phoenix burgers
well i guess that's what i deserve
okay chill piano try to try to not
fall down so fast maybe there's
something you want to
play there's something here what
oh see usually in these types of games i
never find
these kind of secret spots but now i
found one
but that was not that it's not that hard
anymore
[Music]
yay that was actually the first like
hidden treasure that i found i'm sure i
missed like a [\h__\h] ton of them
probably missed all all of the hidden
treasures until now
sorry i'm pressing way too much and the
baby is watching i forgot
baby sander is watching and i'm cursing
so much
are you guys not worried about the words
that he would be picking up
like i feel like parents are usually
always like really freaking out when
someone is swearing around their baby
even like
even when the baby is still like in the
stomach
they're like oh they understand
everything
i really freak out about it but maybe
that's only the the parents that i see
in sitcoms
maybe only on netflix maybe in real life
their
parents are not that crazy sorry maybe
you guys were the same way i'm sorry
not judging you oh my god what is
happening behind this bubble
i don't even see what's going on
oh but it's turning up let me kill you
first come on birdie
you're a
what if i want to continue
how do i turn on the light thought i can
turn on the light now
the whole thing
oh i'll just tell him it's bird language
and hope they never go to
bird sanctuary with school
so you guys don't seem to be too worried
about it now oh l1
whoa whoa
what okay how strong are they
[Music]
i'm leaving i'm i'm still too weak for
this i think
[Music]
bro for like the late game to be
fighting during the night
is that more a late game thing
it i don't know i saw
that she uh proposed to uh
not tulami but lamy was just confused
about it
[Music]
turtle meat
turtle meat well okay i'll take it
summer magic buff should i drink that in
summer
let's drink some spring modding
[Music]
everything i have seen here differs from
the teachings of enlightenment or shinto
formers are also different of course
i'm sure the gospel believed in the west
is also different
yet wilder interpretations may vary it
seems each teaching has consistencies
regarding the local realm
an extraordinarily large tree created
this world
acceleration lies within its bows
according to foremost eating sakura and
tama
not gods
what but my divinity is self-professed
wholesale god does not make god if i
human but
say i got then what
i suppose you have a point
i think you're amazing but i think
different from god
well rude okay hello
you realize i'm doing all this goblin
work for you
and now you're telling me you don't
think i'm a god
hello
angel okay that's good that's cute
that's cute
i'll take it
but but i'm a goddess a goddess you hear
that sounds like me telling people i'm a
phoenix i
should be a goddess no
am i not
princess get a hold of yourself meredith
has said that every religion believes in
the tree of creation yet
then that confirms to the divinity of
lady kawahitsuki the tree of creation
itself
then kamuhitsuki ah
not god but archangel what the hell is
an archangel
said such impertinence do not expect me
to turn the deaf ear to such questions
however innocent huh
oh dude melter first thing the matter
will not accomplish anything
why you avoid talk i do not understand
i don't get it either is it cause she's
making sense and you don't like
questioning stuff
no no
a higher rank of angels ah
whatever we believe we have no choice to
accept what we see before us
now is truth everyone is confused you
need to not
rush to a conclusion murica i understand
[Music]
wait i wanna try some food i'm gonna try
some food please
phoenix is an ark bird
i'm a dark bird is there even such a
thing never heard of that before
[Music]
no i want to drink it
morty
[Music]
okay let's sleep everyone good night
oh we're not in minecraft here that's
right
by the way did you guys see the
community post for uh
questions for holotalk for bookies i'm
fine i already
went through a lot of questions already
scroll through a lot of them before my
stream
i have to already present some questions
to her tomorrow that's why
the deadline is um very soon
and i think like i mean i like
everyone's questions but this is um
and i'm gonna use a bunch of them of
course but still i feel like that's not
exactly what i'm looking for
but it's so hard to get the questions
that i'm looking for
uh it's like um i
i know i could just like i mean i would
love to just come up with them myself
but it's hard because
the kind of questions that i'm looking
for you would kind of need like
some really deep knowledge about that
person in order to be able to ask such
such a question so
[Music]
senpai would be the right people to give
me
questions
but i think for that i should be asking
in japanese
some some japanese voicemails
because i i like the questions that you
guys gave me
but they are very general like um many
of them
are i'm grateful that they're quite
serious but
they often are like how did you feel
about reaching 1 million subscribers how
did you feel
about uh being a senpai
to so many pohais how did you feel
about the whole life blowing up so much
like there's so many questions like that
and of course that's also interesting
and i'm gonna pick some of those as well
but it's not exactly what i'm looking
for and it's kind of hard to
um get the right questions
that i'm looking for if uh
the people who are asking them don't
know that much about the book
so really real i realized there is a
flaw
there is a flaw in my in my um
strategy of getting these questions
[Music]
huh
how long have i been muted now i've been
talking a lot
how long about a music i think not not
so long
damn it
so basically um if i
i i could just like if i was gonna come
up with those questions by myself
uh i would have to watch hours and hours
and hours of archives of each guest that
i bring to whole life and i just don't
simply just don't have the time for that
so i think it would be best
to just ask the
fish to ask the general
um viewership the fans of who came by
for questions
because they just know more about them i
i wish i could just do it myself and not
ask you guys but that's that's the
reason why i'm asking you guys for help
because
i thought maybe some of you um are big
fans of people's empire maybe some of
you know a lot about her
and can't help out with these questions
but it ends up
still most of the questions being very
um very superficial still you know
they're good questions interesting
questions it's very general
so i'm thinking maybe
i'm thinking maybe next time when i'm
asking for questions again
maybe next time i just ask in japanese
for questions i asked
because the japanese bros most of them
know
uh most of them watch fubuki i would say
they know some stuff about her oh my god
where the [\h__\h] is that
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] sorry i'm getting a bit of
residue
[Music]
oh thank god we finally found a
checkpoint
yeah do you guys understand
my struggle i really like all questions
i really like your questions and i'm
using some of them
but it's um
because i i'm asking
the the wrong people i think
the people i'm asking mostly don't seem
to know much about fubuki senpai and
therefore i don't get
the deep questions now um
it's kind of hard like some oh there's
something here
i found another secret
[Music]
how did i find that um
could someone someone in the i when i
was checking for the
questions today
before the stream i was i was looking
for the questions there was one comment
that was like hey if you don't like the
questions that we ask
how about you just think of them
yourself well yeah
i could do that with someone like
piccola senpai
where i have watched literally almost
every stream of her
for for peculiar standby i could come up
with the questions myself
but i'm planning to interview every
single member in her life
i can't i can't watch all of your
archives
i can't it's just impossible for me to
get that deep knowledge about all of
them so i kind of have to
i kind of have to rely on the viewers
for that
party
[Music]
is
well yeah so that's that next time
oh my god oh my god
[\h__\h] it
mushrooms is there anything here
is it where do i continue
to kill yourself yeah
[Music]
let's play tennis come on oh my god oh
my god
this is really dangerous this is really
dangerous
okay bye-bye that's it that's it
you could probably use the fan the skirt
of the interviewee
i don't think i can join the fan
discords
i guess that would work but i don't
think i can go
[Music]
there
you can drag the enemy it
what with my spiderman power
damn i forgot to dispatch someone
that's rude
sakura just chilling there
[Music]
oh
all right there's so many there's so
many good comments right now okay i
think asking that your pampers for one
question is a great idea we'll get some
good questions to engage the
japanese yeah i think generally
i think it's a good idea to ask because
last time when i
um did the when i asked for questions
last time for madden senpai
and i i ended up also making a post on
twitter
asking the the japanese fans if they
also have a question
and then i got some good questions
like instantly they seem to
like all have a bit more like deep
knowledge about
whoever about every single member so not
saying yo guys questions are bad but
it's not except
not exactly what i'm looking for ah
start a new holotalk subway
interesting
just join the fan discords as ana annan
so
no one knows you're joining speak
speaking of questions for fukuki
yeah but i would have to be like hey
guys can you give me some questions so
then they would know who i
am because they speak mostly in japanese
we don't pick up as much about streamers
yeah exactly exactly
ask the guests to make a community post
treat themselves so that they can catch
their own audience
yeah i don't wanna like uh i don't want
them to
go through too much preparation and
travel i want them to just be the guests
and chill
next time i guess next time i'll just um
make a japanese post on twitter
and oh yeah you know what i can ask the
talent
to retweet my twit tweet so their fans
would see it
and uh i think that would work good
that's a bit better than the community
post
asking them to make community post their
own they only have to retweet it and
then
their fans can answer to my tweet and
then i get some good questions
yeah i think i'll do it that that way
next time okay
but anyway thanks guys i'm still i'm
still going through
the rest of your questions after the
stream today because i gotta put that
present them to fubuki senpai today at
o'clock which is in about 10 hours and i
have to sleep in between
well i hope you guys are not mad
i just want to get the right kind of
questions i i hope you guys are not mad
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i still really appreciate that
you guys um
um like thought up some nice questions i
really appreciate that
oh mustache that's a good topic
actually not wait i'm being aren't we
now banned from
[Music]
i think muse dash is not a thing anymore
that we complain
but she did participate and she gave her
song to
mustache
never mind dad but her song is still in
there i think
all right never mind let's continue with
the story
there's a bunch of topics that i would
love to talk about with her
but we can't really talk about at the
moment yeah
unfortunately a few a few topics are
kind of ng right now
i have a request huh what is it
please gather the children i want to say
something
she's picking up from where she left off
before right involving me might just
make everything race
does she have some secret plan this time
fine i shall do as you ask
what why am i saying stick around for
this lecture too
to set a good example for the children i
am an adult adult you hear i shall only
linger as long as it suits me
sorry sorry
before i make you listen to things and
not want to hear
i am salty but only sometimes is enough
i want to teach you study i have thought
since then
if this continue i hate it more maybe
but it much much better for you to gain
power to live
so in exchange i promise
i mean each time very interesting
and it's kinta's day i also study yanato
language do you not think that receiving
a free education is a blessing for
children like you
and from an overseas scholar no less
quite a rare opportunity i would say
yeah i guess you're right then it is
settled
myrtle promises to make it interesting
so approach your lessons with open minds
and perhaps you shall be surprised
if the god is
splendid work princess
did you see us all right
how about it
[Music]
very slow chat are you guys dead or
something
thank you everyone now we start with
17 horses
a riddle huh this is a chance to plot my
superior intellect
yeah i'd like to see you trying just to
watch i'll teach you not to understand
underestimate an avid reader
this is fun i teach kai
more simple thing later
long long ago the king had three
children
you're alive
mom nice that's nice to hear
i i can't accept this this cannot be the
answer
[Music]
i guess you're not so good at this
goddess
okay interesting thank you well well
well
wait did we just come back from our
exploration
i think yes what should we do what
should we do
baby nothing to say by the way where's
the cuppa
we're all meditating and trans by talk
to your voice
thank you thank you
i really can't make much many voices i
can't
imitate voices unfortunately i wish i
wish i had that challenge
there's a copper here by any chance
[Music]
perhaps you got my hair done hey i also
want to go to the
hairdresser oh a hot
who can do boys school in her life maddy
and senpai
kuboki senpai poka senpai
those are the ones i can think of right
now
they're pretty good at making voices
ah lisa yeah this is really good at
making many voices
i saw a clip of her doing all kinds of
voices a long time ago
[Music]
ah oh yeah kind of doesn't buy also yeah
yeah yeah
oh i wish i had that talent it's so
funny
what's my goal at the moment anyway
[Music]
actually i might eat something else
mushroom broth
you make great big guy voices
thank you oh here we go again here comes
my big guy voice
would you tell us about your hometown
oh i would like to hear about it as well
i enjoy exotic tales
right thomas yes i would also enjoy that
many light ships also many kinds fish
fish meat so good i raised in monastery
by ocean i love to read many books
that come to harbaugh oh so
that is where your first knowledge stems
i myself have been known to eat i
i actually i myself am also quite the
reader
we ain't talking about you you must not
change your subject
it's so inflexible can i not indulge
just a little
bentania and janato very different
it's best big building made with stone
castle and church bigger than yamato
building
a giant stone castle does shogun live
here
there greatest inventana
bigger country empire thank you for the
membership
greatest in empire is kaiser he's in
different country
i got no clue what she's saying anymore
i suppose some words are difficult to
translate in other languages
kaiser may be like
then this empire thing is similar to
yellow to itself
and when daniel can be likened to a
fighter's domain
winter river and lake freeze slide on
top is fun
everyone laugh
oh god i hate doing his voice
cause i still don't know how to do it
even the lake freeze
that's one crazy winter yes yes
fascinating very intriguing
julie do you wish to know how the people
of ventania adorn themselves
yeah i do who cares about that stuff
a hammer swinging door like you will
never understand
maiden's height why do you call me
inventania people there
thanks for the meal
voice actor kiara i really want to like
um i know i'm not the best voice actor
at all but
i wanna i wanna i want to um
like voice act a character for a game
for like an english dub or something
maybe for a tails off game that would be
amazing
you still can't come to the fan discord
service
you can't tell me what to do
can you do a deep voice i was literally
just speaking in a deep voice
i can't go deeper than that and even
that it's kind of weird really hard for
me to
go that way literally i believe it is
about time
to started this year's rice grub oh you
tell me
this is what is winter already oh yeah
it is oh
now maybe if i continue playing rpgs
like this maybe one day someone will
notice me and
ask me to be voice actress for their
game maybe
ah so it is we have more seats than ever
so how about we try sorting them this
year's
new ah we're doing a cinderella thing
what do you mean by sorting each rice
seed
is different some will grow to hail and
hearty plants where others will fall
during will
poor seeds will be just susceptible
[Music]
to disease so sorting them out ahead of
time is in our best interest i can't do
this goddamn voice anywhere i'm done
so it says it describes
too much for today
oh the one my mother wrote you mean all
right then i shall give it a try
where do i begin come to the storehouse
you guys remember the cinderella
[Music]
start using mods
now as i've explained
[Music]
making them heavy or to put it in
another way
bad seeds or light
that is why we use the mud in the pot
over there
if we mix this but i can't do it anymore
oh i'm done
with the water containing the seeds the
water itself will grow heavy
and eventually the light or in other
words bad seeds will float to the top
oh so that's how it works sorry my my
throat hurts now
i can't do it anymore
naturally that means you will not be
able not be using the ones that float
so if you aim for higher quality crops
there will be yes yield that year
oh i think that makes sense i shall use
this question
go ahead and give it a try wait wait
[Music]
what sorting separates good reds from
the bag mixing mud or salt into the
water makes the low quality rice
float to the top adding more mud or salt
raises the rice's quality at the cost of
a smaller
yield
okay how much do i want to put in there
[Music]
all of it next use a stick to mix it
oh it's moving very slowly
oh they're popping up oh
why is it moving so slowly oh oh there
we go oh you know we go fast
wow wow wow okay by mixing it the water
will grow heavier and the light seeds
will flow to the top
whoa and now repeat the process until
you have your desired ratio of quantity
to quantity
oh don't don't i want to put in more
months have you estimate the bucket also
contains a small amount of amber
oh okay
once the amber starts floating that
means you have a good ratio
once you have reached the side ratio you
may stop sorting
okay but it's not floating up there yet
so the the amber
is not floating at the top just yet
so how much longer why am i done
should i how do i how do i
how do i put more mud in ah there we go
[Music]
mmm that looks yummy
okay and now we mix it again
[Music]
mix it mix it mix it um welcome to the
membership
too much yeah but other said i should
put all of it in
oh there we go it's floating i'm done
okay okay okay well that's a good number
now then let's just get straight to
swing the sword price
daddy let's bring it out to the field no
wait a minute the seats are not sold
into
in the field but into ceiling bugs
and why would we do something like that
the seeds have only barely begun to
sprout in a word they
are very babes until they are big enough
they might so it's
a lully rice right now they must be
protected from the seas and pests in
this box
oh i see how should we sell them
i don't know does it matter
quickly finley
[Music]
i went with thick please leave them here
and be patient until they sprout into
ceilings
hold on you have not finished uh
chilling yet why not work in the field
until
yeah okay i wasn't gonna do it yet
anyway okay
thick lowly rice that's what we are
going for
wait was that uh before telling before
telling i want a fertilizer
oh there's a skill there
and time of true strength this thing for
integrating strike wait i actually
should have um
i think i have fertilizer ready what's
going on
oh yui speaking of loonies
oh what's wrong with her
use empty fertilizer for chilling empty
what do you mean with empty fertilizer
is she looking for the cupboard
cute you mean don't add anything
at all or i can add some amber rain
i have so much
just do it really
[Music]
since there are no plans to absorb it
but
really can anyone like
confirm me then
[Music]
oh okay
here okay
[Music]
but
but then my my triangle would won't get
all big
[Music]
foreign
can't tell this oh i'm definitely
telling it
i can tell it's telling you
[Music]
okay let's go i'm really good at tilling
okay
i'm really good at it by now i've been
doing this off screen uh
for like two times by now trust me
if there's one thing i can do it's
chilling
um all right it's a bathroom
and about five percent of water will
help really
should i add some water smash
it's smashing time
sakurai is already complaining
thank you for stream thank you
nice super chat is it still
that is uh 6 900 uh
watching viewers and that's why you sent
that super chat
i'm not look i haven't uh been looking
at the numbers at all
i have no idea how many people are
watching
i know i know i can i look at l
i know i know i do it at the end
six thousand eight hundred we gotta get
it back to six thousand nine hundred
come on
come on why did they leave
why would you leave and destroy such a
beautiful number
come back to me
no no no no we're not done
we are far from being done
and not for piano and thank you for
[Music]
watching
by the way uh it's almost
uh four hours of streaming and i said i
i can't do too long today
so i'm probably gonna end it soon
[Music]
maybe we can um
maybe we can do another uh a planting of
the rice
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
yeah i'm not sure about that
i gotta catch up on some but
i still feel like it's not that much
the past few streams were i'm not
complaining but they were not that much
so i feel like it's not too bad
but i can't even see it it's getting
dark
[Music]
so i feel like if i do tomorrow like two
hours of mario sunshine
and then three hours or four hours of
super chat
then it might be quite well
did she say yes we're done did you say
it yet
[Music]
like normally she gives me a comment
that it's pretty pretty much done
she would say that i really can't see
anything right now
it looks done to me yeah it looks
perfect to me
i think we're done
ah she did say it oh okay i didn't i
missed it
and then we're done what are you worried
oh sure that was exhausting
[Music]
why is it always 99 why does it never
happen
thank you for the super chat
thank you what do you think about it
never mind good night
thank you for the super chat
yeah where does the one percent always
go
nothing is 100 100 is tricky to get it's
usually some places inside the corner
oh
[Music]
thank you i appreciate it
very much thank you thank you thank you
i actually do want to read them but
i think i gotta i gotta go for the
questions
some more
[Music]
and then try to sleep uh before 6am
preferably if that's even possible for
me at this point
oh nothing to say today thank you
yeah super chat for sunshine sounds good
to me probably i'm gonna get like really
angry at super mario sunshine tomorrow
anyway and
don't have the patience to play longer
than two hours anyway
and rage quit eventually and just go to
super chat reading quite early
then never play super mario sunshine
ever again
what's that daredevil
what are these oh what are these skills
where do i use them are these like
actual like skills that i use as a
tactile
is it something else is it like
um i don't know how to explain
now you must finish go back to 64. no
over my dead body and that will be hard
because
i'm a phoenix i'm never dead for that
long
i revived way too fast so that's not
gonna happen
it's not gonna happen my friend it is
not going to happen
um i mean maybe in a few months i might
go back and revisit
from super mario 64 but at the moment
now
[Music]
can i add an amber now i have so much
or is it still too like i guess not i
guess it doesn't
make sense
[Music]
i guess it's
at all amber really
after that oh really okay if you allow
me
then i shall do it
[Music]
i have so much water i'm not gonna add
too much stuff though all right there we
go
you can but not an advisor
no ah you mean the amber
oh okay well okay what are we gonna do
actually i think i want to quit here
sorry i'm kind of exhausted
[Music]
oh thank you there's another question
for jacob
with the new year coming up my
resolution is to learn more japanese
have you decided what yours is going to
be
no
[Music]
new year's resolution my new year's
resolution is to go
home and be
completely happy with my cats
because then then i think i i can find
pure happiness at the moment i'm quite
happy thanks to her life i found quite
some happiness
that i didn't have before um
but there's still something missing and
that little thing that's missing
is my cat welcome to the membership
yeah i mean i will miss i will miss
kelly and i will miss the opportunity to
to like hang out with japanese whole
life members i will miss an opportunity
but i can go
back whenever if i want to visit i can
just go back
and you have been holding it back for
four hours holy [\h__\h]
you okay thank you for the membership
well so yeah that means uh for today
that was sakura um
[Music]
i might i wonder how long this game is
does someone know like
a percentage-wise where i am does
someone know
can someone like guess roughly
[Music]
i feel like i'm like really still at the
beginning
[Music]
five push it you read one person
wait everyone's saying something
different forty percent forty percent
[Music]
ten percent ten percent done [\h__\h]
for ten percent
uh i think i am going to play off screen
a little bit more you might miss some of
the story but
uh i don't want to
like play the same games for moms and
months and months
on my stream because the thing is with
streams
i just i try to keep um
a week kind of like with variety i don't
want to play
one game every day the whole week
i would be able to make more progress
that way
but that would probably not be so much
fun for you guys because
not everyone wants to see this game and
then
it would mean for a whole week i would
have no viewers or whatever
and so yeah don't listen to them you're
at 30 40 really
[Music]
i think with variety for my streams is
better
but in that case the games are going to
go on forever and ever and ever
[Music]
bless me
thank you thank you
oh
[Music]
so yeah um if i'm really around 30 40
then okay but i think i'm gonna play a
little a little bit uh
off screen get a little bit of um
progress going
thank you thank you
oh my gosh
[Music]
wow wow wow
oh i need i need to i need to blow my
nose
i need to blow my nose i have no tissues
here right now triple c
combo
kelly is thinking of me oh yeah oh my
nose
[Music]
use your clothes use your shirt
thank you thank you
yes take my bacteria take it take it
[Music]
lick lick my sneeze
[\h__\h] lick it
drink it
never mind
[Music]
thank you spread my bacteria
it's positive bacteria it's good
bacteria
just accept it
oh dear lauren okay uh
[Music]
it was fun thank you guys for hanging
out with me we are playing super mario
sunshine tomorrow
uh i hope you guys are going to be there
estamos super mario sunshine
um i'm going to check uh
go through all those questions uh and
eat something and then hopefully try to
sleep somewhere early so i can talk to
fubukki senpai
uh in the noon time
can't wait for the public club yeah oh
my gosh oh my i'm actually
ah i'm still um
trying to go day by day because there's
so much to do every day
so i'm not quite realizing that the
collab is
getting closer and closer so i'm not
that nervous about it yet i'm trying to
not think about it i'll probably be very
very nervous about it
[Music]
right now i'm just focusing on each task
that is right in front of me because i
have a lot of tasks right now
yup so
everyone thank you for watching today uh
i'll read all the super chats that i'm
missing out on
tomorrow after the super mario sunshine
stream
sorry for keeping you waiting
[Music]
mario sunshine
bye bye good night
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] i just had
a really weird really weird dizzy
thingy felt like my
my head was turning itself inside out
oh my god night
love you all
[Music]
you