[Music]
oh
hello what the how did I get
here what is all this the crispy Gator
wait can you guys hear me chat can you
guys hear me
hi wait what what what is that over
there what's that huh
wait who's that playing a tune over
there it's so
cute loud and clear okay okay okay okay
okay
good
hello
it also sounds sorry okay
okay okay thank you everybody for the
birthday wishes I guess we had a pretty
wild night here at the crispy Gator
Saloon I got to stretch I was just
passed out on the
floor wait what is all this stuff did
you guys gift me this new new wait a
second look at my look at my
hat what do you guys think I'm uh you
know I'm missing something though like I
have this bullet belt but you guys
didn't even get me a gun for my birthday
what the heck what what am I supposed to
do then what if I saw I saw some some
creature standing outside did you guys
see that some some type of Beast outside
in the in the desert and stuff
anyways
no
gun are you sure may wait a second wait
there's a present wrapped over there
there's a present
[Music]
wa what is this okay it's a little
scuffed I'm still uh perfecting my my
holding gun
technology
ta see it's got there's like some candy
or something inside do you guys hear
that there's like some
uh some maybe like gotcha inside maybe
we should test it
out do we shoot some stuff I got
telekinesis wait wait guys take some
cool screenshots look look look I'm
holding it right it's working it's kind
there we go wait I'm kind of holding it
like a like a missile launcher take
cover
I
[Applause]
got now it's all
oh all right I'm still perfecting my uh
my telekinesis Powers as you can see I
don't know is this a is this a western
is this a Cowboy is this a
fantasy
anyways what is up to the
[Music]
chat I was uh today just you know
cleaning up this Saloon I guess I don't
know I uh apparently I own this place
now you guys have given me everything
you gave me a roof over my head you gave
me this
Saloon and now you guys can uh you know
enjoy enjoy some activities here what
should we do I don't know do you guys
have any ideas I'm just kidding I have
some stuff planned today uh so thank you
for coming to my birthday party
party yay yipp
yipp you guys see it I can't
tell
okay uh thank you so much for all this
support all right well since we have
this bad boy
here I think we got to test it
out it sounds like a piggy bank it
sounds like there's coins in here all
right let's take a a
look oh there's some magical
cans they're they're they're little
scuff too okay don't mind don't mind all
right well can you guys see it look you
can see what I'm aiming at can you look
at my C look at my gun cam who's that
I'm just kidding no violence we use this
for and this is a BB gun by the way just
in case anybody's wondering it's a BB
gun
yeah so the the cans are a little
scuffed actually I haven't really tested
this but they are actual cans and it's a
good thing you guys left all this trash
here so that I could practice with my
with my new my new
present my new
present it's it's got a gold tip okay
the orange tip okay okay all right oh
wait actually I forgot I got to take off
my invisible gamer
headphones they're not actually moving
targets it's just a little SCU
make sure the gun is loaded can you guys
see you guys wait maybe if I move the
camera you guys can see me better hold
on this is not to say if I'm holding it
in between my leg wait never mind okay
hold on let me adjust
this it's homemade okay it's
homemade oh look at that cute little guy
back there
look so cute he's taking a nap
you guys can hear the bgm right the bgm
played of course by look at this guy
he's the Piano
Man the piano
man all
right okay good you guys can see me from
here hold on I'll just crop it just a
little bit
[Music]
more there we go okay that's you oh
watch out I'm just kidding okay I
haven't tested this yet don't worry I'm
wearing safety
glasses okay let's see if it works I'm
aiming at the can
okay oh holy
[\h__\h] that was loud that was loud wait
can you guys I was going to point the
gun in my face you could see the see me
in the point the POV but I'm not going
to do that that was really loud uh hold
on I'm going to turn down the mic just a
little bit one
second I hit it first try let's go
all right there we go okay sorry I know
you guys can't see me you can see
me hold on I think it's a little too far
now oh that's right cuz this camera is
attached to the can I forgot
oops all right there we
go continue our activities
[Music]
hello hi
okay the goal is to knock them off and
also to waste like another 20
minutes cuz uh we're going to have some
cin yay we're going to have our first
customers to The Saloon you guys can
hear me right okay hope so all right
let's
[Music]
see oh [\h__\h] it's really loud those cans
are thick those are some thick cans ah
my eye I'm just kidding I'm wearing a
safety
glasses
okay again wait there's like a smaller
can you know the blue can that one's the
smaller one so I'm going to try to hit
that
one oh
[\h__\h] wait I think I actually made a hole
in that one that was huge holy [\h__\h] it
it's actually gone I it's not tracking
anymore but it's because it's gone hold
on let me let me
adjust camera one sec second is this
working no that one's Frozen um what
about
uh okay I'll just turn this one
wait oh there we go it's like selfie
mode
hi
okay yeah this one the the BB gun that
I'm using it's
springloaded hold on let me check let me
check the can really quick hold on one
second I know where it
went thing is oh wait I see
[Music]
it
oh I think oh I hit one of the one of
The Trackers on it so it's not going to
track properly now I made a hole in it
all right well that one that can is gone
that can is done let me move it
out uh
done yay we got it
woohoo hold on uh so yeah we're going to
have some uh Callins uh some people are
going to come visit the
saloon I mean not just cins okay
and um yeah we're going to we can make
some some drinks here we're going to get
behind the
bar but not for another not for a while
only two people oh just some Ian members
just some Ian members yeah yeah
yeah okay we have more cans to shoot oh
yeah this is my I forgot this is my
selfie wait does this
work hold on I attached the camera to
the can cuz I was kind of I was like
what should I what should I do this do
look cool wait wait wait
guys
my oh
wait yeeha
the floating gun and this is heavy okay
happy birthday thank you thank you wow
welcome to my Tik Tok stream guys
welcome to my vertical
stream isn't this cowboy hat looks so
cool I'm so happy and this is not a new
outfit by the way in case you guys are
Wonder away let me fix
this uh it's not a new outfit or
anything okay it's just like a little
just something I put oh oh look at this
look you do you guys notice anything
different here do you see anything
like like a little oh oh oh look you
guys see
[Music]
anything okay okay okay um I'm going to
we're going to shoot more cans cuz I
don't have anything to do for like the
next 10 minutes until we have some
visitors some scheduled visits
here all right wait let me adjust this
again all right let me try to shoot this
can hold on let me set it up I'm going
to try to shoot wait is this working oh
no the only can I can shoot is the is
the hand cam this one I guess it'll work
this will
work okay I'm going to shoot my my
selfie
[Music]
can this one there we go okay can
you
uh uh wait should I step back further
okay even further we step back even
[Music]
further [\h__\h] I
missed
okay good thing I have all these bullets
here my
ammo
damn it I missed I should be careful cuz
I have my computer to monitor it's like
right over here and I'm shooting like
right here and then I have I have a I
have like a glass of water that I I
forgot to
move so hopefully I don't hit
that ah shoot I missed again I think I'm
a little like too far to the to the
right definitely not thing to
extend the
stivity yeah nothing could go what could
go wrong I mean I have my computer right
there I have my phone my my monitor my
other phone it's fine it's fine all
these cameras around here that I could
hit by accident it's
fine hit the wrong
Cam hold on let me move that one away so
I did not hit the right can cuz you see
this this one did it wait which one
there's a can where did this can come
from there's a can over
there
okay I'm reloading with my mind
[Music]
Powers I missed I missed again hold on
hold on I'm going to get it it's going
to look so cool and you guys are going
to clip it and stuff right
oh wait wait wait did the camera move
did it wait oh oh I what the [\h__\h] I shot
the marker off the tracker and now now
my camera doesn't
work just the uh the can doesn't work
anymore okay well that was
fun we're back here with
my well close enough yeah good aim my
ears are ringing after that that was
really loud and I have the microphone
right next to the can
so all right so we have a few more
minutes until until
Callins but uh oh yeah I wanted to do
like U I don't know maybe a song or a
dance maybe both let me put my cool epic
gun
down and yeah we should do dance
actually I do have a dance that I it's
this hold on
you guys know any like country country
song or dances there's like the square
dance
or um H wait I had I have an idea it's
kind of something on the fly but I think
it's going to work give me a second will
you guys wait for me is that okay no we
can't do Country Roads no we can't do
Country Roads
s hold on let me check
something
[Music]
one
moment just doing something don't mind
the weird motions that I'm making pay no
attention
okay all right let me check something
really
[Music]
quick
okay you see that fella over there wait
you see that fell over there we're going
to dance with him this is totally
possible I thought about doing this
earlier but then I didn't but now I'm
going to do it
anyways and it's going to work and it's
going to work trust
me trust me okay uh let me do
[Music]
this uh uh and then we do this and then
we do
this one second it's going to work
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's going to work oh
[\h__\h]
wait where is this fella there it
is
and
ah maybe it's not going to work okay
well I tried I tried to attach like a
gator to this other prop that I have but
he won't move he's stuck
oh I see why I see why ah I see I did
something wrong wait wait wait just give
me a second you guys are listening to
these Tunes I mean look at this
guy look at
[Music]
him
okay
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] okay I got it working I got it
working now I can see the chat all right
look at this
guy
Tada I'm
[Music]
I'm wait I could even put I could even
attach like a like a gator POV this is a
HK stof Gator by the way pretty modle C
cool okay okay okay this
you I'm just
kidding wait how
do okay okay okay let me fix something
really quick you see how he's like
floating all the way over there I'm just
going to move him a little bit closer
all just a little bit closer in these
few minutes that we
got and then I have I have a dance that
I wanted to
try I'm becoming a genius wizard at this
stuff
guys okay we now we can dance we could
do like a like a a square dance or
something we're going to have a a ho
down yeah hold on hold on let me play a
song I know there's one playing but I'm
going to play a slightly different
song
Oh you guys hear
it there we
[Music]
go
okay
wait how do you do how do you do square
dance
[Music]
uh I can hold it like a baby wait it's
too big to hold like a
baby
[Music]
can't when I dance I automatically
resort to like
[Music]
skanky yay all
right we'll set him right here
I just wait I haven't been moving around
lately so I also haven't been drinking
any water today you guys want a sip of
water here
[Music]
here all
right
that was F all right you move out of the
way you go sit down or
something hit him right
there stay now
sit it's so cute head Pat right wait
maybe I'll turn him
around where' he
go sorry just
hey hey
hey like you
wait oh shoot I messed up the [\h__\h] okay
anyways he's there now permanently kind
of all right so we're going we're going
to do uh as you guys know usually for
birthday Callins and stuff we're going
to have some visitors at the saloon here
and also
um what else are we doing oh yeah we got
us I have some announcements for you
guys
yay I got some announcements um that
we're going to do very soon but
first but first um yeah we're going to
have some uh visitors come in I
think all
right here we go we're going to have
some uh people hopefully show up here
some uh customers now that I own this
here establishment oh [\h__\h] start here
hello
hello uh which way do I turn oh this way
hello Kara welcome early no it's fine
it's fine you're good I've been watching
oh thank you I'm I'm first of course
because I couldn't wait to say happy
birthday to you
oh thank you thank you thank you happy
birthday Elma you look so cute in that
outfit yeah it's killing me you're so
cute you come here
often I I I I think I should come here
more often now that you're here uh yeah
underne management M
oh okay well can you do me some favors
yeah
that the the the the gator that you can
move can you put him so that he looks
into the camera oh hold
on I can do that but just give me a
second can you stall for me for like one
minute oh wait I I want you to take some
Memorial pictures with him like give him
a kiss on the cheek and maybe on the
mouth and then do a PE sign next to him
why are you trying to give him a hug
into the camera just you know we need a
lot of cute pictures yes and I will
print them out and frame
them you
will I think all everybody will okay
okay okay uh give me one second while I
create something really quick yes H oh
yeah girl for how long how long were you
setting up
everything uh well I I started I started
preparation for for this like a week
like a week
ago yeah um so yeah just setting up Beau
stuff you're so amazing
am
no like the previous View that you had
where the you you put the gator in front
of the camera for a little while that
was I think a good position oh here we
go okay he's working
now it's kind of hard to get it like oh
like this maybe can this looks like can
you sit him down can you sit him down
like was before and you can pose next to
him easily okay I I can hold him right
here how's that okay oh
pictures
uh only has one
eye uh me and it's hard to
orient give him a kiss do I have to
yes that was that good that's pretty
good pretty
good can you stroke his
tail what the [\h__\h] what's wrong with you
just trying to think of things oh yeah
that's good he he feels happy I put
something can you give him a pet a pet
on his on his and either his beak or his
hat or just Pat him a good
boy can you say who's a good boy who's a
boy who's a
boy I am I am that's
me all right security can you get this
lady out of here she's she's making
weird requests over here and no no no
this is I get the terms of service of
this
Saloon can can we do a role
play okay where um I came into the bar
and I'm going to get a drink and you're
the barkeeper oh okay sure are are you a
sheriff or a cowboy what are you uh I'm
um I'm a I'm a bartender yeah okay I own
this salon now oh okay oh hell hi nice
to meet you oh you're a new owner yeah
welcome to the crispy Gator Saloon what
can I get for
you uh I don't know Whiskey on the Rock
I guess please all right well we got one
of these bad boys how about this here
you go you can take this home with you
it says a souvenir
plushy okay I'll I'll take it that's not
what I want but what happened to the
previous owner uh don't you worry about
that
Missy okay oh wow you secretive W oh
yeah we have we have milk I I think I
guess milk yeah fresh Gator milk that
sounds
weird fresh Gater milk M yummy what does
it taste like is it different from cow
milk uh yeah it's like apple juice oh
what that's really weird okay I'll have
that please give me like a bottle guys
br Apple just wait wake up hey wake up
hold on everybody's passed out right now
I think I think they might have gone
through the reserves Miss but we have
this uh marketable plushy for you to uh
take home how much how much how much uh
it's uh five gold bars five gold oh okay
I'll I'll I'll give you I'll give you a
spit in the
bucket that's what you do in the wild
west right yeah yeah yeah here I oh
do you have a bucket I can spit on into
yeah I do I'm holding it here you could
right here right
here Jesus what was in that
thing can you spit into the bucket for
me too it's like a bonding spit what are
we making a potion here it's is a cowboy
bonding moment all
right okay I put a little bit in there I
didn't hear it I didn't hear it it's
this cold Discord cut it out okay I will
check the VOD later okay all right then
I'm it I love you happy birthday thank
you you're so you're so cool I respect
only heart work you look adorable you're
the best I will forever respect you best
am in the world come thank
you oh thank you our first customer our
first happy customer wait Z oh hello
hello oh there it goes oh you just
appeared here
hello oh why should I not be here should
I get out of here no no no it's I got
get out this is good this is good you
just you scared me you like a you're
like a you came out of some pocket
Dimension you just kind of you're just
here anyways hello that's that's a me
thing to do I know I know what you doing
good looking
oh uh well welcome to the crispy Gator
Saloon and I'm the new manager yeah new
management and welcome yeah oh this is a
new management oh okay cool You' been
here
before um
honestly not really this my first time
but you know like that time travel watch
what's that about oh that oh that oh um
no I don't I don't know who put that hey
who put that no don't worry about it
what what's for what's that for I'm just
curious what are you talking about
there's nothing there's nothing there
there's there's a fella staring at you
weird you see that you're going to let
him stare at you like that oh oh oh
sorry oh must have been the wind my
bad wow okay strange yeah is it okay for
you to you know bring your guests around
like that you are so strong Sheriff this
is my this is not a guest this is my um
how do I say my my compadre my uh he's
here willingly of course yeah right
isn't that right
really it looks like you're holding him
at gunpoint or something are you sure no
look shake your head see he's fine he's
fine he's got car having a fun
time oh what what happened to your other
compadre uh that one he's he's taking a
nap I let him drink too much Gator milk
and he's passed out so yeah we have we
have gator milk here in these barrels if
you're interested you oh yeah sure well
what's it made out of um well we have a
ritual with the Gators where uh wait
this is going a work
direction oh he seems eager he seems
eager all right well
you know it is my birthday today and uh
you haven't wished me a happy birthday
yet what's with that come
on oh oh sorry yeah I didn't know
if I didn't know if you were the Watson
having the birthday or Watson the new
management it gets
confusing I'm both I'm both but happy
birthday thank you AIA Watson the real
one hopefully what what do you mean by
that what who else could I be
I mean I don't know if you're the second
one or the third one who
knows you're the OG right where are you
going where you go I had to check
something in the back rooms yeah I'm the
OG there's nobody back there don't worry
about it that's uh that's uh that's kind
of sketchy I'm kind of getting worried
already hey than
you wait no you got to explain the gator
Gat milk what's the gator milk
about uh well you can have some fresh
from The Source right here he's he keeps
it in his hat and uh it's kind of sweat
actually um we're kind of short on
resources out here okay over here in
this desert area it's you know it's we
don't really have too much so oh so you
guys have okay that's really Barren okay
yeah there's nothing there's nothing
here I guess you have a
Gatorade ah oh my
God why didn't I think of that that's a
good you know that's a good name I think
I'm going to I think I'm going to
copyright
that
really yeah you're going to just switch
it out like that yeah yeah next customer
I'm going to offer them some Gatorade
and they're going to immediately be
excited really I think Gator milk sounds
a lot more questionable and now I think
about it it sounds a little
uh size just a little
bit yeah just just a little bit Yeah
Gator milk yeah nobody would ever think
that it's you know Gator sweat just
saying Gatorade I feel like you really
get an idea of what it is it's like
the comes out yeah but then when it's
like gator milk it's
like you know do they produce
milk
um I think you know that's a good
question biologist in the chat in the
saloon
chat uh give us your
verdict I I'm pretty sure they just lay
eggs and say peace no no they produce
milk from their
mouth oh like birds oh didn't they bleed
like bleed like they have like blood or
something like red like substance or was
that a penguin I don't remember remember
you know we'll just go with that yeah no
I think you're right yeah penguins are
the ones they got like stuff that comes
out of their
mouth yeah right it's like red reptiles
are related to birds so maybe it's
true um maybe I don't
know yeah but anyway main point is Happy
Birthday detective Sheriff detective
Sheriff I'm the only person in town so
I'm Sheriff
here really oh you're going to have such
a big competition with uh sherff the
sheriff
kopy oh that's true well I think she's
one town over so we'll have a we'll have
a gang battle okay okay that that's not
too bad then well love what you've done
with the place and I'll be coming for
that watch it's overdue now there's I
don't know what you're talking about
there's not like it's long overdue you
know I tried to turn a blind eye but you
know you know what you are look I'm
missing it too I I I lost it not yeah
yeah yeah sure sure yeah go talk to your
other
detective what whatever happy birthday
oh thank
you
[Music]
bye good thing she didn't check behind
the mirror I just had to uh take a look
oh
hello a couple of animals coming in here
on the
counter we're going to Violent stuff up
H you're you should be glad I like dogs
so head
[Music]
P
wait
oh but assum we be giving and because
it's your birthday instead bir oh that's
true oh it's okay I'll I'll just here we
go oh my want part for your
birthday feel so good thank
you happy
birthday oh thank you thank you amazing
here thank you I like it yes this is the
crispy Gator Saloon here we sell a
Gatorade and
spit oh we heard something about Gator
milk yeah yeah fresh from The Source
right
here
oh I think though I'm not a big fan of
milk but I think Gator milk sounds like
a a yummy bubble tea no no no we we we
rebranded it's Gatorade now Gatorade
Gatorade rebranding yeah
no it sounds a bit no it's got a dash in
the middle it's not exactly yeah
yeah see we were thinking like it would
be probably yummy if you had like uh
bubbles in it they could be like a melon
Flav like Boba or just like like oh ooh
okay I'll I'll add it to the to the
[Music]
recipes oh but we were wondering where's
Bubba the yes well we have a typo here
it's a print uh you know it says Wanted
Dead or
Alive no no we want him
alive uh Bubba's fine he Bubba's like
yeah he's good he's
good I could bring him in here I can
bring him in here right now but take a
second yeah too many do not missing
that's okay yeah you guys are going to
bark each other then it is never
ending
yeah that would be bad yeah can't have
too many dogs in one place at one time H
that's true you know P sometimes goes
missing too but dead or alive I don't
know I find with alive for
p you guys alive I'll keep an eye out
I'll keep an eye out just in case any
other dogs are not allowed on the pr on
the premises only you
guys yeah it'll be good maybe maybe
maybe maybe much violence wait a second
you guys aren't Outlaws or anything are
you well we're innocent we're Innocent
but we did spend a lot of time in
the oh I remember yeah you know you guys
need to be investigated or
something for your
crimes there's no crimes we have
fun is just a good
thing okay you know it's the past what
right yeah all right if I see a b out
here for you guys you better watch
[Music]
out there's nothing of the sort we're
good
puppies you guys have yeah good puppies
we just wanted to say big big happy
birthday to you always helping us always
taking care of us too I didn't do
anything thank you we hope we can spend
more time together yeah we should play
more games together yeah mod was a lot
of fun last time and Among Us that was
really fun too yeah among
us we definitely need to play more among
us thank
you wow we got a couple of famous
criminals in here the the crispy Gator
Saloon is moving on up in the western
Society
all right I'll take a drink
[Music]
too
okay wait who's that looks like we got
another
visitor hi guys it's me I'm a I'm a do
I'm a I'm a
[Music]
do all right we had some pretty good
cins so
far where's my gun oh yeah I disabled it
accurate representation one second let
me fix something really quick while we
wait this
one
yay oh wait what time is it oh shoot
okay I have to do actually I totally
forgot that's why I have to do
announcements I almost forgot okay
perfect timing
actually oh thank God I don't have to
stall
okay all right let's go back to
this one this
one all right thank you guys for uh uh
hanging out so far I think we might have
some more visitors to The Saloon but now
it is time for a special announcement
you guys
ready you ready is the music too loud is
it bgm okay by the way I saw somebody
said it was too loud and I turned it
down a little
bit announcements yeah I know the soda
can don't don't look at that I'm I'm I'm
keeping it floating with my with my
mind okay bgm good okay I'll turn down
just a little it should be
fun okay special
announcement
ta oh wait
oh
yay look at this design wait doesn't
this look kind of familiar the cowboy
hat the bandana the neck Chief or
whatever you call call it in my my
Shaw all right I do have some merch to
announce for my birthday as you guys
know tradition of
course
and birthday merch
yay and part of this birthday merch set
you can get a rubber mat with this
amazing art look look look it's it's
doesn't it look look just like me look
oh with the gun and everything with the
gun and everything see look look the gun
the gun is it's the same thing anyways
and we also have um I'm a milk
bottle not not Gator milk I'm a milk
bottle and with small Alit on there a
nice item to you know keep as a
collection or or just to drink out of
and then we also have this Poncho
blanket cool right actually I saw I got
to see like a merch preview of this and
um um it looks really good it's like you
know it's a blanket but also it has a
hole in the middle so you can wear it
like a poncho isn't it
cool isn't it cool isn't it cool and
also we have a limited bonus postcard
with Amilia Watson my signature on it
and these are limited edition um limited
Quant
to uh so these are going to go on sale
and they might sell out so if you're
interested in getting one of those you
should uh pay attention to the link and
yeah here's the closeup of the art so
this is a rubber mat and yeah look look
look
look oh it's just like the it's just
like it what look at the look how look
at the gun H it's movie
Magic and yes the art has the mo oh
thank you Kiara thank you um so yeah
this is the full illustration looks
really cool maybe we can uh zoom in a
little
bit fastest Slinger in the west rubber
[Music]
mat and thank you to this wonderful
artist who did this uh amazing art it
looks it looks so cool doesn't it it
looks awesome okay and then some
close-up on the other a small alond milk
carton uh so it's not my milk small on
his milk I mean that's I me know that's
good right that's good that's
good um and then what
else and then we have yes the Poncho
blanket hold on let me zoom in let me
zoom
in a design to resemble my Cape yeah
it's got my coat design on it and and of
course uh it's got some tassels you
can't have a Pono without some
tassels and yeah you can use it as a
blanket or you can wear it so I'm really
looking forward to I hope that um so
maybe there's some cosplayers out there
they could wear this Poncho blanket and
do like a western themed Amilia Watson
that would be cool you want it you want
it well luckily it's going to be on sale
in 8 minutes uh as well as the uh sorry
I forgot my manager is going to be like
I I mean I told you what to save for the
limited stuff uh so yeah there's a
complete set purchase
bonus hold on it must say it here
somewhere uh yes birthday merch complete
set limited edition postcard with
handwritten autograph birthday merch
complete set postcard with uh duplicated
foil stamped autograph so it yeah it's a
limited quantity of the real thing and
if you don't make it you will get a foil
stamped one so I will be signing a bunch
of these postcards and put little
drawings and messages and stuff and yeah
there's don't worry there's a you know
there's quite a bit of them I W say but
uh yeah this is going on sale so it is
um a limited quantity I believe MH let
me make sure I'm not being yelled
at
okay okay so that's the announcement yay
hey what is this a bundle bundle bundle
yes you could get the bundle or you
could get individual item you know maybe
you don't want you know autograph though
that's fine that's fine don't worry
about it but um you know if you just
want like the rubber mat or you just
want the Poncho you can get these
separately as
well
yay all right we'll just zoom in on this
for a moment I take a I take a sip of
water okay come much
sh
[Music]
M all
right
successful that was a successful merch
announcement I'm now back to waiting for
my Saloon customers so that we can um
increase our output of Gatorade with a
dash it's Gatorade with a
dash what do you guys think did you the
the art looks so good doesn't it
oh how there well hello there fancy
looking Miss welcome to the crispy Gator
Saloon do you guys got any uh Johnny
Walker Blue Label oh
um sorry we don't we don't we don't take
kindly to around these
parts all right give me your strongest
give me your strongest whiskey double
shot of whiskey on the Rocks uh all we
got is a fresh Gatorade is how about
that are you right from the source
establishment are you running here it's
the crispy Gator
Saloon crispy Gator Sal can you make a
cocktail with that at least um I mean
yeah we can mix it with some uh
moonshine we got back here
all right you're really busting my chops
but I'll take some moonshine how'd you
make that moonshine though do you mind
if I ask first um uh nothing is
uh what are you the FDA huh this is the
wild west sherff from the town over oh
well you're you're this is not your
municipality
okay well it's going to be I'm going to
I'm going to raid this town one of these
days you're the sheriff you can't do
that darn it you're right okay how about
a duel a
duel yeah okay all right we got to we
got to have a duel uh go you and me go
outside at High Noon so I'll be back at
High Noon um and then and then we can
point our guns at each other and then
shoot all right M it's a du kick me out
don't don't kick me out I wanted to say
happy
birthday all right wellth thank
you Watson oh thank you
Watson wait are are you Amelia Watson
right now or are we are you are you do
you go by something else at this exact
moment well I don't have one of those
fancy uh cowboy names but if you gave me
one you know that'd be nice all right
let's see
um hold on I'm I'm thinking I'm thinking
I I can be creative I do creative
writing for a living okay um West uh the
the the the W Witch of the West that's
that's freaking Wizard of Oz hold on a
sec the words that start with hold on a
second all right I got this Google um
mean words that start with W um I know
these are all bad I don't know I'm at a
loss guys what do you think chat what
does chat
think oh chat Amelia Weston that's a
good one Amelia won I'm a Weston come on
dad I'm I'm sorry
I'm yeah yeah wild Watson dang it missed
opportunity I'll get them next time but
speaking of creativity this is real
creative I wanted to say thank you this
is cool nice I love that Western bar but
I will say one small critique if you're
going to do Western Bar you're going to
need to sell some alcohol here ah know I
know I ran out of I killed all my props
earlier cuz I shot him cuz we had a
gunfight in here it was vicious darn it
oh really man I got to see that you're
too late Sheriff you should have arrest
like arrest this guy right here you see
him arrest that guy oh oh hey there
buddy looks like you've had quite a day
what's this did you smash a bottle over
his head jeez it's the only it was the
only way to subdue him all righty hold
on hold on let me handcuff him all right
I'll take this one off your hands
Watson oh thank you thank you you're
welcome we'll get him out of
here yeah you got it and also a very
happy birthday to you Watson um I feel
like oh wow I just noticed that I have
my my top hat on I guess that kind of
fits in the west people kind of
wear top hat yeah that's true there's
like the fancy especially like doctors
or something you know
yeah they did have top hats Okay cool so
maybe I do kind of fit in but not really
be fitting of the sheriff anyway anyway
doesn't matter um am a Watson I hope
that you have a fantastic fantastic
birthday um very nice merch I'm going to
I'm going to be very quick on the draw
teammates on getting that exclusive just
so you know you're going to have to
fight with me if you want to get that
so thank you so much K thank you sheriff
for stopping by
my neighbor not a problem not a problem
all right well let's let's work on
keeping this small part of the West safe
how about that okay it's good thing
you're arresting that guy take him away
take him away yeah you're coming with me
buddy you're coming with me see you
later am bye
byee peace
peace what a nice Sheriff I tried to
kill them but uh they're kind of
impervious to uh my bullets for some
reason almost like they're some type of
Shinigami
ye oh thank you guys thank you hold on
should I bring oh
oh no oh God no
scare
cowpoke well hello there shrimp creature
welcome I heard quite the commotion
coming from these over Saloon do cars
here had to come in and see what was
going on well we were having a a
shootout a fight but uh the sheriff came
by and clean it
up oh how nice so how's it going uh
pretty
good I got this fella over here and so
far everything's going smoothly
so at this nice Saloon
opening what is what is the top seller
at this Saloon if I I just want to know
what what do you have to drink oh uh
here we s
Gatorade Gator with a dash in the middle
Gator Gatorade Gator Aid Gatorade yeah
so do you like is there like a how do
you harvest the Gatorade oh well it's
the sweat and um I got him back in the
back uh in the back we got him hooked up
to ma je and ping yeah sweat where how
what is the science behind it it's a um
a sweat machine it's got like artificial
tongue and it's um licking their skin
like on their you know on their body and
stuff and it makes some
sweat can I get a farm tour do you offer
that here uh well I can give you a tour
of the saloon if you like no no no no no
man I want a tour of the I want I want
to see I want to I want a behind the
scenes tour of this Gatorade all right
all right just for you strange shrimp
thing all right take Co over here uh can
you see that oh
God and we got a whole bunch of nothing
there's um out there there's some
strange mechanism that crashed
here and it looks toxic it looks like
it's it
kind of a toxic Wasteland if you will
and and then we just got the saloon here
and all the other buildings they're
they're just they're
fake not a whole lot of clientele it
seems out here no just just a a whole
ton of gators is
all is there any water in this town um
we got a well we got a well out
back the Gators just just they live
under around sometimes they crawl under
there to get all moistened up are they
socialized yeah I mean he's looking he's
perfectly perfectly domesticated he
looks
sedated no no no no no no no no no no
he's
fine um okay I okay who am I to
judge ah I saw your poncho by the way I
want your Poncho thank you yeah it was
just kind of like a spur of the moment
thing I was like you know what I want a
poncho
blanket it needs tassels mandatory it it
has
tassels I saw yeah but they were too
long so we had to we had to send it back
and now that we they're like a little
short cuz they were like too
long two was like too long yeah now we
got the shorten version pepperoni
tassels okay can tassels ever really be
too long though yeah they become a
safety hazard you trip on them they get
stuck and
stuff no if you can the correct length
for a tassel is one that you can
like helicopter you know oh that's true
o and now I want to see somebody wearing
the Poncho like do a oh ballerina
spin
SP I'm spinning like Arena
like a
puncho
cowboy I'm
tangled the cowpoke is tangle quick chat
this is our chance Dive Dive over the
what is this
countertop get the triple xx and head
for the door I'm going to rankle you I'm
going to you know like uh when get a
baby horse and you got to teach them you
going to you you got to Wrangle them you
going to ride the
shrimp you're going to ride you're going
to ride
me like a like a big
worm wait oh my God I am the worm I'm
the worm that's just
arrived
get too bad you're glued to the
counter I am glued my entire body I lost
the other half when I crashed here with
that sun
fish out back I did oh it's all your
mucus right
it yes I'm a mucusy crustation never
mind I don't want to I don't want to
touch you you're you're getting slime
Trail on my bar stool oh oh forgive me
shall I Slither back to the crevice in
which I came from you live over there
you live I do
know well that's fine it brings some
life some diversity to this town you
know there's nobody
here I am that's true that's true that's
true that's true so wait you could be
the sheriff you could be the mayor you
could be the sheriff mayor yeah I yeah
there's nobody well this this is the
only building here so um it's like my
town
[Music]
yeah well happy birthday thank you happy
birthday cowpoke would you like the
marketable plushy I would love a
marketable plushy GM wait never mind I
ran
out I was promised a marketable
plushy maybe next time we'll have that
as
[Music]
merch okay happy birthday thank
you have a wonderful rest of your stream
and day thank you you
[Music]
too oh who's GNA clean this up all the
Gaters are leaving one by one there so
hold on let me bring back this other
fellow over
here here we
go bring him back all right I think we
might be
um oh
oh hello oh
hello welcome to the crispy Gator Saloon
Miss what can I get you can I get you uh
um um can you get some you have some Dr
oopsy oh I already knew you were
stopping by actually I I I uh I got one
right here for you what it's as if you
already saw the future how could this
be oh well I do have um a couple of
gators who are
psychi gave me a palm re said a a nice
little taco Nai lady would be wandering
in today
ooh what what is this place you kind of
look familiar uh uh my name is uh wild
Watson yeah they call me wild Watson
here wild wat Watson are you related to
a detective by
chance uh perhaps but uh you know that
that person has a bounty out for for
them so it's definitely not me oh oh are
are you
sure miss you're not a bounty hunter are
you with that innocent look no
definitely not all you're missing is
like a mustache what kind of Disguise is
this um it's it's it's that's not it
that's not it I'm not a foundy hunter
I'm just I'm just I'm just I was just
going to the the convenience store and
then all of a sudden there was this
strange door and then I opened it and it
was like the desert and then I I was
like you know what maybe they still have
Dr oops oopsy you know well you came to
the perfect
place oh it's this is this where Dr
oopsy's
made um why yes it is yes
oh mhm are you sure uh well you know did
you know do Dr oops used to be called
Gatorade with a Dash in the
middle oh g g Gatorade but we recently
rebranded to Dr
oopsy oh oh what what's
Gatorade um it's like a sweat from their
glands and uh we ferment it and leave it
out in the sun for a little bit and put
some salt in
it oh that's why they say you can get
like you know like what's it ions and
stuff from drinking G oh electrons
that's right yes
electrons oh it's from the swiat salty I
get it
[Music]
wow well oh I got a I got a I got I I
just have a feeling I should say happy
birthday to you is this is it your
birthday by chance I don't know it is
wait it is my
birthday oh I was my my little my little
flaps STI They were telling me you know
someone's birthday here today these old
things here oh please don't touch them
they're very they're very sorry they
were calling to me
okay I know you want to touch them but I
mean maybe maybe some other time right
now no all right well you come back
again when when I can touch those things
okay or else no entry happy happy happy
happy happy happy birthday on the merch
looks so good oh my god oh thank you
yeah I can't wait to yeah yeah I'm so
happy it turned out really nice yeah
super nice I can't wait to get the
blankie or the Poncho Poncho blankie and
then the bottle looks so cute oh thank
you I want I want lots of it but yeah no
not thank
you oh you're welcome I keep saying like
thank you like close to how you say it
it's just it's just so nice thank you
no it's cuz I I gave you that Dr oopsy
you know that's on the house oh oh will
I start hiccuping too yeah yeah it's got
to it's got some uh hiccup stuff in it
oh no I'm going I'm going to have to
talk to sheriff about this but it's kind
of su sh anyway Thank You by mind thanks
for the drink happy birthday you a nice
nice wonderful day wonderful
year thank you
[Applause]
byebye and she she's going to take the
Dr oopsy with her right
[Music]
oh oh oh oh there it goes T I guess it
teleported with her okay all right I
wonder if there's anyone else I think oh
oh H there little lady oh hello there
hold on howy you're so quiet there we go
howdy my name is is Babel the kid and
I'm an Outlaw in these hair
Parts this a safe establishment for the
out those who avoid the law well as a
Outlaw myself uh I just got rid of the
sheriff so you know it's pretty safe
here but hey are you are you old enough
to be drinking here at the crispy
Gator um Above the Law you're oh oh I
don't need the law to tell me whether or
not I can drink I will do as I please
well we don't I'm Not Afraid we don't
serve uh whatever you're eating whatever
you're ordering here Rock milkshake or I
don't know whatever you got
there that's fine I'm thirsty I could
use some sort of drink here is this a
bar or not what do you have well we got
uh some uh Gatorade with a dash in the
middle Gatorade I heard there be milk
where is the milk well the Gatorade is
actually we rebranded for uh for reasons
cuz Gator milk cuz uh but you know a
growing kid like yourself needs some
milk so um hold on I got some I got some
fresh from The Source right
here
wow all right I'd like a nice fresh cup
of milk please o wow hold on Wow from
The Source a
getting milk live
wow I can see where my drink's coming
from amazing it's from up here not
anywhere
else it's h stored in his hat here you
go there you go oh wow thanks I'm going
to take a sip right now just here taste
this milal I'm in gorade
yeah it's tasty right M refreshing I
give it acceptable acceptable I approve
of this establishment here you're
running a very nice place I like it oh
now I can put uh a review you're going
to leave me a review right uh oh yeah
I'll leave you a review on the do is
there a Yelp out here RW something
Yeehaw we call it Yeehaw instead of Yelp
yeeh oh yeeh okay Ali you're five out of
five on Yeehaw don't worry this is going
to help my establish thank you soon soon
this place will be hustling and bustling
and you you can attribute it your first
review from baby the kid yeah I could
die happy
then I can't believe I had a famous
Outlaw here I need a picture of you on
my wall you know how like when you go to
a restaurant and you see we take a
picture together I I'll take a selfie
and then sign it I'll sign it too so
that way people know that I actually was
here amazing I I got a picture I'm going
to oh thank you thank you I'm a big fan
big fan yeah now not only did I come
here because I heard that this was such
a good establishment but I heard that uh
you know this was today was someone
here's birthday and you know be with the
kid you know comes I'm so famous but I I
visit for birthday so oh it's me who
birthday is it it's my birthday is your
birthday wow happy birthday I wish you
had an amazing amazing day thank you
thank you that has been pretty cool
especially since I got you here well you
know I've been I was watching from
outside and I saw some shooting and I
would like to say that I was mighty fine
impressed by your shooting from an
outlaw I think you could survive out
there oh thank you will will you kiss my
gun please oh yes
sure there oh I'm good this is a family
heirloom there now now you can save baby
the kid kiss your gun your gun has been
blessed may your shots never all your
DS oh thank you
yeah very nice gun by the way oh thank
you yeah I need to get that merch with
that picture on too because I like that
gun so much very nice oh thank you very
very impressive not as good as my gun
obviously but yeah where's your gun huh
all I see is a couple of rocks well you
spit them out your mouth or something a
true outlaw never reveals their weapon
until the time is right you know we're
not duing right now so maybe if you want
to if you want to duel later on and we
can we can I'll show you my G all right
I'll schedule in after after I have my
duel with the
sheriff yeah it's still it's still
dangerous in here I don't want to break
stuff there was a fight in here too much
stuff broken already I don't want toover
it yeah
yeah all right all right well have a
happy birthday and I I bless your
establishment with five stars I will be
coming back again for another drink soon
going to get addicted to that Gator very
nice well thank you thank you for
stopping by B Boo the
kid thank you watching of the way wait
was that was that your name yeah close
enough yeah was what wait what was it
wild wson oh W wild WatchON sorry my bad
I
I I will remember it now okay have a
good birthday happy birthday Yeehaw this
tell ain't big enough for the both of us
so I'm getting out of here byebye byebye
thank
you it's so cute what a cute
Outlaw yes there's a lot of Outlaws
around these parts huh in
Halloween all right I
uh I uh I think I might be closing up
for the day
possibly let me take a look I think it
should be good yeah all right looks like
the the line outside the saloon has uh
diminished we've served all the
customers I'm pretty
sure wow thank you thank you oh
yeah do you guys have any questions for
for me the uh Saloon
manager I uh I wanted
to oh actually I saw that some Gators
left me some presents and I haven't
looked at them yet but I thought we
could look at them
together oh
[Music]
oops okay wait hold
on last call when's the last call on I
was just fixing
something there we
go oh okay
[Music]
um last call last call no I think that's
it closing time time to close up
guys look at these guys over here
they're still
uh still playing their Tunes wait is
this working still playing their Tunes
all right give me one second guys while
I thank you thank you for all the
birthday wishes thank you okay I'm just
going to fix something really quick and
oh sorry I forgot I duct taped this
microphone uh give me one
[Music]
second all right the saloon is closed
this is after hours now thank you guys
for um stopping by wait there's some
type of video can I show this let me ask
my apparently some type of video that
some Gators
prepared oops one
[Music]
second I hope the music wasn't too loud
I I saw somebody said it is a a little
loud happy birthday thank you thank
you here we'll play uh the image
slideshow for this the merch while I sit
here and uh prepare something that thank
you you guys are so nice so many
birthday messages thank you thank you
thank you it's usually so oh was loud
during cronies oops
oops um okay I can show this
one and let me set this to
automatic
okay one
moment uh chat you guys are so sweet all
all the messages is filled with happy
birthday thank you thank you yeah if you
guys missed it here's this birthday
merch merch of course you know in hallai
we always have merch with our birthday
so uh we got some stuff here if you want
to look at that but uh I'm going to pull
up now a
video that um some nice sweet Gator
prepared I have no idea what it is so
and let's take a look it's like 2
minutes
long I didn't prepare this before stop
thereit I can't hear it well if it isn't
you bosen I should have known yes yes
you would dare come into my city with
all the crimes that you have committed
or we know about you becoming a vampire
jumping around on top of others property
cheating in the arena and worst of all I
can't hear it a carrot from an innocent
father right in front of you let you
guys watch you won't get away with that
in my city your stolen goods and your
stolen carrots are now
forfeit so what will it be oh wait it's
the guy from Oblivion or serve your
sentence what then bosen you must pay
with your
blood oh you f fetcher wait wait what
wait I
understand it is your
birthday it's my birthday yes
am your birthday said my name it is I
Wes Johnson and the Imperial Guard both
of us are putting down our swords to
wish you the very best of happiest
holidays that happiest of holidays your
birthday I hope that you have a most
wonderful birthday and as sh gorth would
say I hope you celebrate it with cheese
for everyone cheese for everyone said
cheese for No One just as good a
celebration if you don't like
cheese but remember next time bosen you
shall I've been murdered I
st what that's so cool that's so cool I
don't worry guys I had audio I could
hear
it thank you guys so much that's so
sweet thank you to the Gators who set
that up thank you that was really cool
everybody gets cheese so Cheese party
Gator cheese wait a
second that was cool there's also um a
digital birthday book but I don't have
the means to uh show it on the screen at
the moment cuz it's I think it's a PDF
and uh I have too many things on the
screen in my computer right now to show
it but thank you guys I'm going to look
over it and thank you thank
you gator milk now gator
cheese all right well I will be wrapping
up this birthday stream wait my face
stuck I'll be wrapping up this birthday
stream um and thank you so much support
thank you guys thank you wait what
birthday are we on now is this like my
fourth birthday or is this wait uh one
and two three four wait a second
this is like the fourth one we've
celebrated that's crazy that's
insane I I can't believe it's already
been four four birthdays my goodness my
goodness well I feel like the merch from
this one I don't know and you know we
probably shouldn't compare but you know
if we did this one's kind of like the
best I mean it's kind of freaking Poncho
blanket how you guys are so sweet thank
you so much for all the birthday wishers
in the chat thank you thank thank you
all right all this stuff is on sale
currently so you know if you guys want
to check it
out but also I did want to give um a
shout out to uh you know the modelers
who helped actually this this uh asset
this Saloon asset didn't look this nice
but um SEO boys usually does the uh you
know some 3D modeling stuff that we use
on stream uh they went and like fixed it
all up and added these Gators and stuff
in the back and you you guys see these
Gator paintings they're so cool hold on
maybe I could show you the uh other
side uh let's see wait wait here it
is take this
[Music]
camera and okay now we'll rotate it okay
perfect there we go now you can see the
the other wall too and um yeah it turned
out really cool it turned out super
cool here we go and of course look at
the look at all the effects and stuff we
have oh thank you oh apparently the
limited edition merch uh bundle sold out
in like 2 minutes that's insane thank
you guys so much oh wait am I supposed
to say that I think it's fine okay thank
you that's huge what the
heck oh thank
you oh it was crazy I didn't realize it
would go that fast I'm not going to lie
is oh sold that less than a minute what
the
heck you got yours hey lucky
lucky uh okay yeah so as I was saying oh
yeah so this the saloon you know looks
really cool so thank you SEO and also my
my props that I have on uh was hoft
thank you hoft for the props doesn't
look I don't know I really like how it
turned out I was surprised actually cuz
I wasn't expect like I thought you you
know oh it's my look you know e i I
asked very last minute it was like I
think the day before New Year's Eve I
was like I started
messaging I was like hey if you're not
if you guys aren't busy you know I'll
compensate you for your time oh my
birthday's coming
up uh so you know pretty last minute as
always so thank you and of course no for
pro who uh helped set all of this stuff
up I had a lot of fun um I'm the one who
set up uh you know all the cameras and
stuff and the ability to do stuff like
this which is really cool um be able to
control all of this stuff and yeah
hello um but yeah n referee pro really
helped a lot too with the a lot of the
scripts that I use and stuff so yeah it
turned out really cool and it's I don't
know for me it's really satisfying just
to put these things together you know
what I mean even though this might be
like yeah I don't think this will be the
only time we use it but sometimes it's
like a one use type of thing but I
always learn so much when doing it so
every time I do it I feel like you know
it gets better so I'm still improving on
uh you know my implementation and stuff
so yeah I had a lot of fun working on
this stuff it's really
cool this was fun oh thank you thank you
oh yeah which reminds me so uh in in uh
commemoration of uh you know this merch
stuff I want to this month we're going
to get back to playing Fallout New Vegas
and uh Red Redemption 2 which actually I
think was uh C playing recently or um
yeah yeah we're going to play and uh
streams are going to be still like a
little spotty but for uh for the next
for the foreseeable future we're going
to focus on those games and yeah yeah I
I have a lot of stuff going on at the
moment so I'm kind of busy but
ah I want to stream and I want to play
games so yeah ah thank you thank you
Callie just started the other day oh
nice nice we're going to join we're
going to join in on the uh what is it
called when you got like a like Oregon
Trail you know what I mean it's like the
you got the the wagons and the
anyways Red Dead to Sharpie let's let's
see maybe maybe if I ask my manager
manager please can I can I use this you
know this cool props and on my outfit
could I use it for my stream maybe oh
yeah we're going to join the Caravan
that's right let's join the Caravan
yay all right well I'm going to head out
now but thank you guys for watching my
birthday stream and thank you to
everybody who called in and thank you to
everybody who helped me put it together
so uh thank you guys so much H goodbye
Gators I I uh all my trackers kind of
broke right now I like peaked the mic
really bad uh all my tracker kind of
broke so I can't pick up the gator
anymore but uh thank you guys they
didn't break it's just they they fell
off damn you really fell off for real
for real H here we got this fella we got
this fella over here wait can you guys
see
[Music]
that there he is sleeping away all right
I'm going to go now thank you guys again
for all the support for the birthday
this is really fun and I'll see you guys
soon for continuing a game and I also
have a collab coming up uh with a senpai
what am I what a JP Senpai you guys
might already know and yeah thank you
guys for all the support for last four
birthdays what the heck and I'll see you
guys soon thank you thank you thank you
all right I'll see you guys bye-bye wait
I don't have a button to fit
out
[Music]
bye-bye
w