​​​ ​᠎I love you always​. Take me in your arms and kiss me​​​ ​​
​​​ ​itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I cannot forget this precious memory of mine​​ ​​
​​​ ​wasurerarenai kara boku no daijina memorii​ ​​
​​​ ​If dorayaki cannot become my main diet,​​ ​​
​​​ ​dorayaki wa shushoku ni narenai​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll just have to overwrite it my way​​ ​​
​​​ ​naraba uwagaki shichaeba boku no omoidoori​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm always watching by your side,​​ ​​
​​​ ​zutto soba de miteru yo​ ​​
​​​ ​so leave the backup to me​​ ​​
​​​ ​bakkuappu wa makasete​ ​​
​​​ ​From left to right, events pop up​​ ​​
​​​ ​hidari kara migi e to dekigoto ga​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, there, and everywhere​​ ​​
​​​ ​acchi kocchi docchi​ ​​
​​​ ​Where are you right now?​​ ​​
​​​ ​kimi wa koko ni iru no?​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't your birthday still some time away?​​ ​​
​​​ ​baasudei mada saki desho?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm reasonable enough not to believe​​ ​​
​​​ ​iikagen ni koyubi kara​ ​​
​​​ ​in the invisible string of fate​​ ​​
​​​ ​mienai ito shuchou shinai​ ​​
​​​ ​The sound of a parched heart​ ​​
​​ ​and the shallow mutterings​​ ​​
​​​ ​kawaita shinzou no oto awai uwagoto​ ​​
​​​ ​are getting on my nerves​ ​​
​​ ​precisely because they bother me​​ ​​
​​​ ​shaku ni sawaru nante ki ni shiteru kara ni kimatten jan​ ​​
​​​ ​Still, we need to have faith, be mannerly,​ ​​
​​ ​and polite to become happy​​ ​​
​​​ ​soredemo shinjite shiawase ni naru youni reigitadashiku​ ​​
​​​ ​For starters, how about some small greetings?​​ ​​
​​​ ​mazu wa sasaina aisatsu toko kara​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you ready?​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me​​​ ​​
​​​ ​itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I cannot forget this precious memory of mine​​ ​​
​​​ ​wasurerarenai kara boku no daijina memorii​ ​​
​​​ ​If dorayaki cannot become my main diet,​​ ​​
​​​ ​dorayaki wa shushoku ni narenai​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll just have to overwrite it my way​​ ​​
​​​ ​naraba uwagaki shichaeba boku no omoidoori​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want to wake up from this dream​​ ​​
​​​ ​yume kara pipipi samenai de samenai de​ ​​
​​​ ​This warmth, please don't go away​​ ​​
​​​ ​nukumori nigenaide​ ​​
​​​ ​The morning is still young, so please​​ ​​
​​​ ​mada asa wa tappuri aru kara​ ​​
​​​ ​give me five... no, ten more minutes​​ ​​
​​​ ​ato gofun iya juppun matasete​ ​​
​​​ ​If this goes on for a hundred years,​​ ​​
​​​ ​hyakunengo tsuzuku nara​ ​​
​​​ ​then let's compress our promise​​ ​​
​​​ ​yakusoku asshuku shite​ ​​
​​​ ​To the text I sent to the wrong person​​ ​​
​​​ ​machigatta meeru kara​ ​​
​​​ ​comes a quick and mistaken reply​​ ​​
​​​ ​kanchigai no tekipakiteki​ ​​
​​​ ​Aren't the ways we drink​​ ​​
​​​ ​sutoroo no kuwaekata​ ​​
​​​ ​from our straws slightly different?​​ ​​
​​​ ​sukoshi wa chigau desho?​ ​​
​​​ ​If everyone pretends not to notice,​​ ​​
​​​ ​mite minufuri sareta​ ​​
​​​ ​then the world will explode!!​​ ​​
​​​ ​sekai ga bakuhatsu shichau!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I get carried away, but then​ ​​
​​ ​immediately get shot down​​ ​​
​​​ ​choushi ni noridasu demo sugu ni hekomidasu​ ​​
​​​ ​Who will put a stop to my​ ​​
​​ ​magnificent rampage for me, baby?​​ ​​
​​​ ​kareina bousou dare ga tomete kuremasu ka beibee​ ​​
​​​ ​When I bump into something,​ ​​
​​ ​I discover some new knowledge as well​​ ​​
​​​ ​butsukareba mata atarashii chishiki hakkutsu​ ​​
​​​ ​However, I'll only go as far​ ​​
​​ ​as my stamina can hold out​​ ​​
​​​ ​demo chikaratsukite shimaeba soko made​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my god!​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me​​​ ​​
​​​ ​itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Will the stars grant my wishes for me?​​ ​​
​​​ ​ohoshisama ni negaigoto kanaete kuremasu ka​ ​​
​​​ ​Carry me to the other side of Earth,​​ ​​
​​​ ​chikyuu no uragawa made boku o hakonde​ ​​
​​​ ​and let's go on a search for the most beautiful flower​​ ​​
​​​ ​ichiban kireina hana o sagashi ni iku nda​ ​​
​​​ ​Your burning passion turns into tears on your cheeks​​ ​​
​​​ ​mada kimi no atsui omoi wa omoi wa hoho ni tsutau namida​ ​​
​​​ ​I will hold your tear drops in my bosom​​ ​​
​​​ ​shizuku wa mune ni tsutsunde​ ​​
​​​ ​and send them into the sky​​ ​​
​​​ ​todokeru yo sora ni​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you ready?​ ​​
​​​ ​GojimajiP feat. Kasane Teto - Ochame Kinou​ ​​
​​ ​(covered by hololive English)​ ​​
​​​ ​Lyrics, Composition: GojimajiP​ ​​
​​​ ​Mix: Angelina Fuji​ ​​
​​​ ​Arrangement: Akatin​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: hololive English​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me​​​ ​​
​​​ ​itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Will the stars grant my wishes for me?​​ ​​
​​​ ​ohoshisama ni negaigoto kanaete kuremasu ka​ ​​
​​​ ​Carry me to the other side of Earth,​​ ​​
​​​ ​chikyuu no uragawa made boku o hakonde​ ​​
​​​ ​and let's go on a search for the most beautiful flower​​ ​​
​​​ ​ichiban kireina hana o sagashi ni iku nda​ ​​
​​​ ​Your burning passion turns into tears on your cheeks​​ ​​
​​​ ​mada kimi no atsui omoi wa omoi wa hoho ni tsutau namida​ ​​
​​​ ​I will hold your tear drops in my bosom​​ ​​
​​​ ​shizuku wa mune ni tsutsunde​ ​​
​​​ ​and send them into the sky​​ ​​
​​​ ​todokeru yo sora ni​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me​​​ ​​
​​​ ​itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I cannot forget this precious memory of mine​​ ​​
​​​ ​wasurerarenai kara boku no daijina memorii​ ​​
​​​ ​If dorayaki cannot become my main diet,​​ ​​
​​​ ​dorayaki wa shushoku ni narenai​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll just have to overwrite it my way​​ ​​
​​​ ​naraba uwagaki shichaeba boku no omoidoori​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want to wake up from this dream​​ ​​
​​​ ​yume kara pipipi samenaide samenaide​ ​​
​​​ ​This warmth, please don't go away​​ ​​
​​​ ​nukumori nigenaide​ ​​
​​​ ​The morning is still young, so please​​ ​​
​​​ ​mada asa wa tappuri aru kara​ ​​
​​​ ​give me five... no, ten more minutes​​ ​​
​​​ ​ato gofun iya juppun matasete​ ​​