[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
n e
[Music]
[Applause]
get it C
[Music]
I am in my white night
outfit yay I I think I did I even use
this
before feel like I didn't but what
what like I revealed it and then did I
use
it maybe Maybe for One Final Fantasy
[Music]
stream finding the right window size oh
there it is
perfection oh Grand blue right yeah
after Final Fantasy ah right right right
right
right okay so I think I maybe just
changed
colors oopsie there we go
there we go
okay hello good day I kind of want to
watch P's new
stream but uh yeah oops my stream has to
[Music]
start never mind this black armor maybe
then we can change it once once I have
it uh Kyla uh
is not streaming right now I think
but she got the template I watched her
Vault a little bit she got it pretty
easily
surprisingly from what I've seen she
didn't even put up much of a
fight and she got free of them she found
them so
easily uh good good I'm glad because she
was
like Bastion alone n but even with you
it's might be really difficult she
nearly died it like the parts where that
I was watching nobody was attacking her
maybe she already killed all the piglins
that were attacking
her I don't know it looked pretty chill
from what I've
seen uh a lot of close calls
really it didn't look like it maybe I
tuned in too late in the
vault uh junus what are you
doing what are you doing
what are you
doing no hold she's leaving the room uh
but she got several templates and she
got herself her own full nevero armor
with Diamond trims oh my God and of
course a sword too from what I've seen
so I I uh I'm I'm not going to be the
first one that's okay I mean it was kind
of um you know it's Destiny that Kyla
gets it all
first let me make my window a little bit
smaller
[Music]
though I still hope I still hope I get
some
reactions that's really all I want I'm
not doing it for the armor I'm doing it
for the for the
chicks yeah before she went to the
Bastion she got had all the all the
ancient debris that she needed too
apparently I checked into that too in
the VOD how did she do all of that I
mean she did stream 12
hours M I got it too
already I should not have slept I should
have stayed up all
night she stayed up all
night I
know why did I why did I go to
sleep you snooze you lose man
man not full but three out of four
okay so okay another
hold well I'll have a full armor and a
sword so okay I'll be like on Kyla's
level but I don't think I can do like a
diamond trim I don't know what it takes
to do that what kind of shms can you
do what
uh uh six can i r one is cool can I do a
never quartz
one I think that might look pretty too
you need to find a trim T yeah but I'm
copying it from Kyla right
I mean I don't mind just having a normal
never right
armor quartz is good that works how much
will I
need that's
different can but I can cop it yeah
that's I have the diamonds you guys
didn't watch last night's stream where
we discussed all of
this quartz sounds cool right and I got
so much so might as well use it how much
do I need 35 pieces one P oh one piece
of quartz or one piece of quartz block
or so I have plenty okay okay not well
uh the diamonds I'll have some more
diamonds wait where my blocks where are
my
blocks beautiful ingots that I worked on
so hard
yesterday I got pretty
lucky yeah she got free trims free
templates I'm not sure it's like what
the [\h__\h] where's what is what I'm
confused but uh let's see how many
diamonds I got if I already got
[Music]
them 40 diamonds yeah cuz I did pretty
much every Mission except the one that
wasn't available to me one of the new
missions I get ender pearls ah makes
sense because this is preparation for
tomorrow
uh five diamonds for ender pearls two
diamonds for uh just killing one
Enderman uh wiz ah being part of the
withy 10 diamonds and make a golden
apple fre diamonds okay these missions
are not very rewarding but I mean
tomorrow is probably the last day
so doesn't have to be rewarding right
all
[Music]
righty uh let's go e was it that way no
was the other way
right no
was what I think it was that way qu I
don't have my bed I don't have my bed I
don't do I have my bed
no
bed
bed oh bed oh oh God I don't think
you're really supposed to do that but
I feel like the they like said before
like ideally you shouldn't log out maybe
this one of the hardcore
rules are we done already
okay voice chat not connected what do
you mean it's connected I see my
microphone popping in and out oh guys I
forgot okay really
simple has a [\h__\h] road
now oh I was a v I'll run
um I forgot to say okay you probably
don't care but yesterday before the
stream I took like
M two or in total four but there like it
was two pairs two pairs of like Little
Wall tiny pretty tiny wall shelves that
I've had lying around for probably like
years without mounting them
um first because I thought I couldn't I
wouldn't know how but one of them
literally really just needed Nails the
other one needed screws but I could
still do it with nails so I did it with
nails but the other reason and later on
was ah I'm moving so whatever and then
it was like I don't know where to put
them and bl blah blah and then I would
forget about them for several months so
yeah but yesterday I finally did it I
found a nice place to put them uh and
nailed them onto the wall
it looks really cute and then I put a
few little um decorations like gifts and
other stuff on
there looks
cute good job right yeah
[Music]
Kawa you did it huh you did
it I watched the VOD a little bit and uh
it looks like you had an easy time
but maybe I didn't watch the hard Parts
because when I was watching it looked
like nobody was like fighting you the
pigs were just
chilling like when you were opening the
chests and everything but I guess you
already killed all of them two
bastions oh so it was not just
Sebastian yeah I I I watched the last
one I think hey yo how does this
work do I uh so I copy from this one I
have like diamonds to copy it how do I
copy it
though that this is word crafting table
[Music]
[Applause]
door oh oh I it's in the
ground I didn't see it uh how what what
uh do I just type in smithing template
ah it needs oh I forgot neck damn it do
you have some extra
neck she can read my mind probably she
already started running the
moment the moment
I thank you thank you thank you did I
pick it up yeah okay so let's
see upside down is pants and no what
what
what I need different one uh
template wait what so how many do can I
should I make do I make do I make uh
four five out of
this four out of the same thing same
patter so chat confused me that I maybe
have to do it
differently five I make five okay uh
okay but this I get two uh do you want
this one back KY ah okay cool
uh uh-huh uh uh-huh uhhuh uh uh
[Music]
four uhuh uhuh okay I have five thank
you six to have one left over to give
back oh she said I can keep it
but I wonder if she has
more ask for trims uh
KY uh uh I never I never did this before
but uh how I can I put Trims on as
well how if yes how
we need one more
okay wait
um trims is the other thing
yeah is that something I can copy
too
oh what do I need for C
[Music]
I'm
in not for I thought this was Kyla and
this was another person we never four
trims that I can pick where are
they does one one trim apply to all of
my armor or is it like if I use one trim
it's gone and I need another one
one for each
part one trim for one armor but I can I
can I can duplicate it right okay H uh
uh but what where can I see it what what
parts do you which ones do you have or
does he have
it so
[Music]
confused I can send you link on Discord
ah okay ah do you show me a link how it
looks like okay
trims are easier to come by oh yeah cuz
you can get get them in the desert and
stuff too right in the jungle I think
that's that's the thing that you get
there
O Okay Minecraft
trims
yeah uh and and which which of the four
which four do you
[Music]
have typing
Coast ho host wild
snout ah
uh
close poost armor ah it's the ah it's
not the color it's the the pattern of ah
I thought this was about the color
already uh the one that I use is this
snow Co Coast wild wild armor
trim I mean I I think whatever whatever
is fine uh why Coast it doesn't show the
coast one here say can't find it
what
[Music]
snout the color from the yeah
okay I
think
whatever what whatever whatever what
anything anything's any
anyone oh they all look fine Co is this
one oh
co oh
co uh w
m i I'll just go for let's say let's say
wild
why went online that means she's going
to read the Diaries I
think oh
o okay okay
[Music]
aha Mossy
cobblestones wait does it like depending
on which template you have they need
either mossy cobblestone or something
else or mossy cobblestone That's So
Random what do the what do the others
need cuz I don't I don't have mossy
cobblestone
[Music]
who has losty
Cobblestone let's see what the others
need thank you oopsie
uh oh smiing temp template Coast armor
trim needs normal
Cobblestone not a uh oh she gave me four
of those girl girl girl thank you thank
you
got thanks
okay uh I thought I'll just do it with
never
quartz I know because I had a lot of NE
quarts uh lying
[Music]
around where's Red
Stone no but redstone looks red it's not
orange there's no real orange quartz is
white yeah I know I think it looks nice
especially if the armor the rest of the
armor is so
dark well from what I see there's red
and like a pinkish color but there's no
orange so I don't know
man yeah let's just do white the
quartz makes it white I think or is is
it
yeah copper is that's probably a pink
one right
no no quartz is fun quartz is fine
quartz is
fine
[Music]
are copper is close you think that looks
like
orange that looks
like brown if anything brown or pink is
that is what that looks like to me
wait but let me let me I want I think I
I'll I'll try to make it um so you can
give me the quartz
back also your Shield it looks like the
freaking twitch
logo it looks like you're a twitch
streamer even the the shiny effect damn
you can check each color here in the
table oh this is what I need okay
wait do I make it into nether ride first
and then I put the trim on I suppose
look I look much cooler without my
armor
sheesh
okay
uh add smiing template
s sne sne sne sne
sne okay let's try I'm so
[Music]
scared
wow wow oh should
I uh should I heal the durability first
or does it not matter anyway
really okays
boots never boots oh they look they look
nice hot black boots high heels
hopefully
nice uh
uhuh what was I doing oh
little shortterm
memory maybe pick I can see
it she's streaming right now so maybe is
she reacting to my
achievement let's do my sword too I got
to watch the Pico Senai
um uh archive
later she's reading Diaries ah she
probably can't see it
it's like oh okay I'm going to make my
Never Never My Sword also into never
Rite
then you can still add enchantments
after it turns into neite
[Music]
right probably play seeing something
well not to me uh I think let me
[Music]
check yeah not not to me guys not to
me okay I think I'm done with that so
now uh same thing for the
trims yeah oh so I can see it before I
do it
huh oh now hold on I think that's cool
cuz it really stands out
much yay let's do it let's do it
[Music]
yay crafting a new look wow
last
one yay can you put a trim on your
weapon
too not that I need
it I look so
cool w we should take a picture together
later maybe with M with everybody who
has never arrived at the wiow fight we
should take a picture together
yay DP wait I want to look at myself
outside
I'll never get outside there we go
oh oh okay bye-bye have a good
dinner okay now the shield looks even
more
lame damn oh maybe we can enchant it to
be shiny shiny like uh Kyla maybe that
can be our
next uh goal
oh
here oh I have an idea
could put a banner yeah I don't I don't
remember how to do that you guys got to
help me out with that I don't know can I
do
it am I capable of doing that Shield is
no lame Shield is functional no it's
really
lame you can use mending and then
breaking enchant for shield yeah but
what about the banner
I look like a burglar fief Jo is
back by the falling I have I have the
enchantment already I just didn't put it
on there yet but yeah that's
definitely one thing I want to put there
Banner using loom do I need like
wool right I remember making one once a
long time
ago just wool and a stick
okay and the like on the color right uh
that I choose from the
wool yeah I S she has a loom so we'll be
back but
first I need to get some iron too
probably to exchange some
more uh emeralds because that's what
I'll need if I want to buy more
enchantments
people will call oh you think they'll
look at a person in neite and
immediately be like a
[Music]
kylo she's not
here she's not
here is she reading them somewhere
else I just want to stand there
[Music]
menacingly maybe she's last time she
went down there so that's she's not in
the
way damn
[Music]
she's muted in game right now
but did she hear me did she hear me I
wonder she can't hear here she had her
speakers off too
[Music]
no
no I said I will protect you
today um
no but why did she come out she was did
she see my
name I
text it no it's okay I'll say it again
later
maybe
nice shiny yeah I think the white is
cool kind of sad though that they have
like two reddish colors but no orange
and I don't even see a yellow in these
pictures yeah even though gold should
probably result in yellow
and maybe they don't show it in the
picture because it's the everything on
gold no it's okay I'm happy with
this okay
[Music]
so we want to enchant
everything um I have some ingots that's
nice and I guess I could also change
with the
bamboo it's two emeralds
and the feather falling and silk touch
no need oh a stick and wool right that's
also one thing we got to become even
more o
goodlooking handsome beautiful
sexy oh for all my armor the same thing
protection Flor Unbreaking free mending
for
everything I wonder if there's shears at
the PO Farm to borrow for a
moment she has yellow pink
[Music]
white
shears guess I can make uh a pair of
shears yeah yeah yeah
yeah maybe there's some wool
like
here why did I saw Ida stream a moment
ago what what what is the meaning of
this ah to kill some
cows
oh somebody somebody's kind of naked
looking there
H
uh
okay oh there we
go he
it's not many
colors she looks impressed
really she read my diary now
y y you need to
die well I'll just go with what they
have when we uh
enchant or I thought we couldn't enchant
The Shield why was her so
shiny Kyla's Shield was so shiny
oh she just realized now that was never
right she didn't realize
before she's asking for never I have no
more but I have no
more she should ask KY well no but okay
if anything I would want to do it for
her damn it but there's no time there's
only today and
tomorrow hey
C hey
heyle nobody's going to sleep huh or not
enough people at least
not wait you guys said something was in
the
chest ah
M black and
white or there's only one black we can
take gray and white because that matches
my my whole look
right yeah
Banner
uh now I've got the shei for
[Music]
nothing oh oh now
now my house is right
there seems like they really changed it
too everybody has to be sleeping after
all
okay um maybe what was it uh
Loom needs strings two
strings I think I threw them
away is there anything else that I want
to bring to Kyla place
um my nice
axe I don't know do I need something
just in case
books oh I don't have any oh I do nice
ah first Iron get some more iron if
there's more the iron was ah no you guys
said the other way after all when I went
all the way over there then you guys
said oh it's the other way and I went
the other
way today we're playing a little bit of
a Japanese style music but I have some
others if you guys get sick of it let me
know then I can change
it but I think it sounds
nice oh yeah I won't have enough XP
right now huh I had so much
yesterday got to go get some
more how much is there o yeah o yeah o
yeah o yeah seems like there's no no
need to worry about too few
too few uh uh
irons 41 LS thank you
d d
indeed check the second ah no need feel
like this is
plenty okay I you a TT
to
really which way the
[Music]
it was this way good
good Flex to Ena I saw the beginning of
her stream where she was making a plan
and ah
she also wants to get never right if she
has time but she wants to go strip
mining any you got to go chaotic mining
uh are it this way this way no no
no this
way chaotic mining is the way to
go no actually not what did I get out of
chaotic mining in the end I think
nothing besides a broken picture
uh I hear no other no no no no I
heard uh Kyan heard me and she just had
her mic
muted and I think I
heard a tiny bit of a kind of
noise from someone
else yeah no no no should be fine can be
pretty inconsistent though at times
I can't believe that I would find so
much when I was just making the path to
blow something
up like I wasn't even strip mining
really just making the path to blow it
up and I found stuff as if I was St
strip
mining oh hello hi
hello wow old th down yeah yesterday I
was like I Min for so much uh ancient
Dey I went overboard and I shared some
with MAA and Ollie and then I gift also
one to Kaa and now I look like
this so you're going to tank the Wither
right uh yeah I was thinking actually
like for real like the ones with never
red armor should go into the front
lines I was really thinking remember the
myth one or not the myth one the I one
yeah it was so antil climatic and fast I
don't think it will be a challenge
honestly when I think back that was we
see that I think the
biggest I guess like the biggest um
difference is going to be the audio the
audio because everybody will be
screaming yeah yeah but only for a short
amount of time
probably yeah I think it will be easy
see we're we're pretty prepared so you
know you never know though like you
never know if like there's going to be a
10 butts at the same time you know make
spice things up you never know put simp
[Music]
I'm I'm I'm welcoming
it yeah anyway yeah y I'm doing my prep
hopefully I make it in time I'm making
some potions and
stuff hopefully it'll help what what
I'll be I'll be supporting you from the
back line oh thank you yeah shoot shoot
with your aim go for it I'll maybe I'll
get some milk too milk is really
necessary right I remember yeah yeah
definitely have a couple on on hand
especially if you're tanking
yeah
come okay
fight to war with the
Wier you know the Watchtower yeah and
normally I would totally prefer you know
I don't I like shooting with my bow I'm
a ranged Warrior ideally even though my
even though my design is with a sword
and a shield
that's not really my preferred way of
fighting you might want some better food
than potatoes for
tanking well yeah golden apples I guess
um we recommend it I just need golden an
apple
right I need to see if I can find apples
apples might be a bigger challenge right
now shoot with sword and B no okay see
the ideal thing would be Trident which
is kind of like a sword but has free
like thingies um and then shoot it
because that's what you do with a
trident wouldn't that be the best like
in between kind of
solution I just need exp right I'm not
trying to heal
anything but might as well
we're level 12 now I wonder what level
we need maybe 30
[Music]
40 good luck getting one getting a Trent
I don't need luck I don't need luck I
would like to remind everybody that I
got a trident without even trying and it
was the first drown I
killed therefore it was called first
Trident I like to think back on that
memory it's a nice
memory no TR it's actually no
Trident no try no cap I don't even know
what that means I don't know what no cap
means explain it to
[Music]
me try
lant no lies oh then and it kind of
fits maybe I should stream today in this
PO just so that everybody's aware what
I'm wearing I'm so proud guys I never
got never right in the normal Minecraft
server after a million years
even I'm so
[Music]
proud mommy is proud too
okay this is kind of hard to
hit you made your
pickaxe never right you just never Ed ah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that's the only
thing I did but I never got armor and
never
right dual wield now it's full so I'm
going to put it away hopefully
everything goes to me then
[Music]
oh yeah there's some chests around now
huh I wonder who put those there oh I
know I
know I am aware it was most likely
Kyla really convenient though now to
have those two
we'll try especially cuz the the uh
challenges are not that much and they're
not that difficult looking we'll try to
fulfill them all either before or after
the weather fight maybe some of them I
can do
before what what do you think is the
best way to get uh an Enderman I think
there's some that spawn uh in one boming
in the uh never right quite
L why is nothing
spawning
[Music]
hello yeah the fight is in like 2
hours warped Forest oh
yes Ana I hate you go
away farming exp
now oh oh uh I yes I
do I have one that she could
copy does she is she
making well does she want one armor
piece cuz I think she doesn't have so
much uh ancient
debris
okay will you let her go of
course can't be like U greedy about
it of course in the end I copied it from
Kyla
[Music]
so I have it with me but I am in
TT fake
hater yeah maybe I should just just not
give it to Ana I would give it to
everybody but not to
[Music]
Anya I guess I I should change to the
dark
armor but it doesn't even make that much
difference from this
POV and the white armor i' I never wear
it I need to wear
it so if Ana will be wearing it too then
we can all take a picture with Ana as
well
Ana mik by me I wonder maybe someone
else will manage too until that
time you have quartz your in fits yeah I
think so too the white black monochrome
monochrome
Paladin
sexy looking so good right
the
beds the freaking beds
man I can't go to yeah then come
on
okay I was also thinking maybe I should
just go get some
Endermen I get exp from them
too
[Music]
for so
yeah sorry one one Japanese bro was
saying he thinks it's nice that I hung
out with mikoi and I was like yeah I was
actually I was I was happy about that
because I was so happy about it that
after the stream I sent her a super long
DM of gratitude and emotions and all
that like why why I'm so happy that we
could hang out because I just generally
have not been doing much with Japanese
senis or not senis in the past one or
two years and
just perhaps felt like a little bit
isolated here and there and so it means
a lot to me thank you so much you're so
sweet I told her all of
that it really meant a lot to me it's
crazy how like just one one day of fun
interactions with a lot of senis and
other members can really help you get
back on
track what do you think guys about the
idea or no Ena what gold Ena Diamond
Ena which which ore for Senai you have
to be a bit more specific
or or
no good on thank you thank
you only Ena will get this but which
order no if has going to be confused
that's a cute
Emoji that's so cute Japanese emojis are
so much better than Western ones what
the [\h__\h]
so wait what do you think about my idea
of just going instead of going here
going to find Enders
Enderman I'm kind of scared of fighting
them honestly Enderman are still one of
the kind of enemies that I'm most scared
of because they're like whoosh whoosh
whoosh do it this is probably faster
enchant ammo first you can still die
okay well I can still also die if I
enchant it but
M
okay ah yeah the hidey hole I forgot
about that yeah you can
like make yourself a little baby for it
SM SM protection house put
house
not water repel ah yeah red water ah so
I need to bring oh but in the in the in
the
never it's not going to
work but lava probably repels them too
right but it repels me as
[Music]
well unless I have the potion on
me just spread some [\h__\h] lava all
over hardcore
repellent Ana yeah didn't she say hey
she's got to do something
first yeah in a bit she
said I'm here she knows where to
go I like the boat start I don't think I
really know the boat Strat do you just
sit in a
boat have them come at you and then sit
in the
boat she's coming with some company
[Music]
he will sit in the
boat walk into it and I'll force you sit
like he's I'll just stand on the boat
but he will go there and sit in there
automatically oh
no once I have the argro he follows me
so he'll just get stuck we place a boat
in front of
them I used to be really bad at doing
that with villagers is it easier with
[Music]
Enderman
yeah okay
[Music]
maybe poor Aqua logged in to see
everyone in never right not
everyone also like who who what that's
fine just so just not
everyone don't let it be everyone I
don't I want to be
special it's Overkill anyway we'll
protect everybody else okay
the side quest encouraged it it's so
overkilled like our group also like we
were pretty much like Ollie and Mauna
they were just happy with getting
one but I was like I need to get a full
set now because it's going so well
oh they're dropping really fast one by
one that's nice more please more more
more more
more Ana's coming
okay oh I see her what if I do a joke
and I jump down the moment she comes
up no no I'm too lazy
[Music]
go away go
away it's okay it's not like I came to
meet you for a one-on-one collab I just
need the template and then I'll I'll go
cuz I hate youse you should have brought
someone else together no just kidding
what wait what
did okay we still hate each other wants
to sell uh the tote them and and five
red oh no she's buying it or she's
selling it no she's selling it right for
diamonds a total of five gold apples
yeah she's selling it she's selling it
wait red red no wait it's not a golden
it's a red apple wait that's stop 200
diamonds yeah 200 diamonds for a totem
and five red
[Music]
apples what kind of scam is this oh no
she okay she freaking 200 diamonds she
did make a mistake she does means a
golden apple oh oh Golden Apple okay but
still still though I think I think that
was a mistake I think she was trolling
yeah all right uh the trim I have the
trim how much ancient debris do you
have um I have one Ingot already
netherite inot you want to get enough
for
everything um not everything cuz I only
have one I don't know if I still have
time to like farm for more but I I'll
have to see I saw your and vam ism
strip mining result I went there and it
was like tingling in my fingertips
because I really wanted to blow it up
cuz I was blowing everything up and I
was like making you know these long
paths and then would put the TNT there
and then blow it up but every time I was
making the paths I would meet so much
lava and all that and you guys already
made so many paths I was like oh what if
I just blow up the paths that they
made I had to resist cuz I didn't know
that one wasn't even that was um it it's
flares yeah it's actually it's actually
flares she told us about her place ouch
oh and you just like extend told us
about her place and then yeah we just
extended it
a okay well let me give it to you I I
got like thank you uh here this one I
got it from Kyla
anyway thank you you're welcome can I
can I use it here oh
uh no uh you first you need to copy it
oh yeah I need I need I need to do it at
the blacksmith uh yeah uh no you go in
you can use this the the normal crafting
table and then type in template normal
crafting table template and then see
there's a smiing one just make more out
of this one so that at least you'll have
one left over so it doesn't disappear
okay okay okay okay okay gotcha gotcha
thank you you're welcome
thank you thank you later after the wi
fight or at the wi fight we should take
a picture with everybody who's wearing
neite oh I'm I'm probably only only
going to be having one neite but that's
okay that's okay with you yeah thank you
thank you
[Music]
byebye you can just jump into the water
just jump from here or so true jump from
there and go and
[Music]
go everybody has to go
wee you thought I would kill
her W well wow I'm just trying to get
her to think that I like
her and then I will kill her just
kidding it's all a strat
can't believe K pushed
her one could possibly turn it around
and say that's that's what happened
yeah yeah
[Music]
25 now
H they want to
[Music]
sleep how did this an arrival rest start
M it's really just like we we would call
each other at the Callins for like
birthday or anniversary I think she was
the first to like reach out to me to
call her in hers
so I did the same the other way around
because we we did get along quite well
in that call and but besides that we
didn't really talk you
know
um and then yeah I did it the other way
around and then again she calls me it's
like you know once or twice per year
okay it's probably the amount of times
that we spoke is probably more than uh
once or twice maybe three times a year
or so thanks to these
Callins um but we would never actually
collab we would always say yeah let's
collab
sometime let's totally collab
sometime and then we never never do it
and then eventually it just became a
joke and it was just funny that we keep
on saying it and never do it we never do
one-on-one collabs I think did we
do a collab where where we were not
oneon-one we must have done one
right
uh uh yeah it's just a joke
obviously uh ah okay was it literally
just
AOE that's the only one and that was but
but that was just like that was a six
people collab and we didn't really
interact much
either we weren't on the same team
either
she shees but we still got along well
and I also met her IRL like uh two times
now once in Indonesia and once in
Japan I do I do like her
actually I'm just scared to break her
she's like she's so small and and thin
feel like I'm going to break her
arms yeah but no cab yeah and now we're
just like both laughing about it all the
time
and uh I sent her like fan art someone
made this like fan
art oh where is
[Music]
it
wait can I show it
there this is us this is literally us
yeah we're enjoying the
meme we're enjoying
[Music]
it which just trying we're just
pretending but it's hard to pretend
because I like her but I hate her love
hate all the same if you know play the
game I'm Lo up up I know I can fight the
faing and I won't
try love all the same if you play the
game you decide if you want me can shout
it out right
now is just a game I can't the oh do you
do you this is just maybe do you was
written for me and Anna
wouldn't it be funny if I did like Ana
and me dancing do you uh in in one of my
freed lives but it's too late now the
coming one is already planned
out also she's so tiny it look so weird
the size
difference well that would be
amazing uh
[Music]
oh
hello can buy golden
carrots yeah I guess golden carrots
would be no they're not they far not as
good as the apples
[Music]
right and a short or
something
yeah could you wield her as a weapon
probably she's tiny enough and maybe she
can transform back into the weapon that
she is the
dagger I
learned there was one time where she
invited me to a collab um that it would
have been like a four people collab but
I think the
time was really bad for me or I was also
not even available because I was was
just like traveling or so I think that
was also an
issue so I had to turn it down and I
said yeah maybe another time but now I
think I
think I think she ended up doing that
collab with someone else like replacing
me and now that became like kind of a
friendly group that has collabed a few
times
already so now I'm like
ah ah ah pain
pen ah missed out on something but it's
okay it's okay I'll make my own
groups did you get a date for H not
quite yet almost still waiting for one
person's reply to confirm the
[Music]
time was it Leal comp
uh possibly
yeah oh yeah cuz I think I said you know
yo um I might I would maybe be open to
do it but time kind of sucks but
generally lethal company I think is
really [\h__\h] boring I played it a few
times and with myth and and so on and
now I'm I'm like done with it like it's
so boring I don't know why people keep
on playing it it's so
boring but for I think for Japanese
members they were were kind of a little
bit late to the hype for once it's the
other way around you know um so they
were still enjoying it while Ian was
kind of already done with
it was kind of delayed
fotm for Japan members so yeah then Ana
did a collab with like two of them and
another person and another person should
have been me it should have been
me the other the cont
I don't know nah don't care don't
care if I get invited yes did you read
the Reddit no not yet I didn't have time
to even look for it or think of it if
you post it like you didn't post it in
kfp Castle
right so I normally I don't go to Reddit
like just you know on my own anymore you
have to post it on kfp so then I can
find
it I want to see it
I've noticed you're in the chat for all
of my Minecraft streams I've noticed
taking notes
huh how long is
it it was posted yeah I didn't see it
what the hell I need to see
it I still find it fun but I get
it I don't know if it's
[Music]
fun it was fun maybe to play it once and
even in the first time I already got
bored of
it you guys maybe quote retweet it with
the hashtag again so I can find it in
the
tag maybe also use kfp
[Music]
hashtag almost level
30 maybe when I'm 30 I'll go for once
I'll I'll put the actually I can do that
right
now better falling I can do
now
yeah
wow shiny
boots yeah yeah
yeah now I'm 25
and then I wonder what level I need for
everything else uh maybe not that much
maybe 25 30 is enough this one just cost
me
four only four
levels yeah I got the right look at
me look at me now Look at You Look at me
now Look at You Look at me now Look at
you that's a black pink song
Sorry
Flex I should have Enchanted it normally
before what before enchanting with a
book H what how what what do you
mean on an enchanting table thingy I
don't even know where one would
be why I did it
wrong it's fine
[Music]
but then I don't even know what I'll get
out of it
[Music]
right cost less if you have good enchant
I don't think we even have one yet not
even KY made one
right well you'll be okay since this
yeah this server we don't need to
optimize and min max everything This
Server is ending tomorrow I
think I just want to look shiny it
doesn't matter what enchantments I have
really I just want to make your shield
look cool I just want to look good on
camera in
4k server is ending
soon like it would be cool to have an
event like this that revives everybody
but on the main server so that you know
everything that we do actually has longl
lasting
[Music]
purpose but then everybody already has
stuff on the existing server something
like that should be done when a new when
a server is being wiped or so and then
re started but we have haven't done that
in a while and I don't think we'll be
doing that in a long time either
should be a this should be a f hole
server I wouldn't mind like having a
hardcore server just uh continue to
exist but once the event is over people
will just like yeah stop playing I'm
pretty
sure even if it were to continue to
exist I feel like it would be nice if it
existed and it just like somebody would
update the missions we could even like
have a mission
gotcha just have like a roulette of
missions so as long as there's daily
missions I feel like it's at least a
little bit of a motivator to continue
playing on this
server then it'll be no it will be the
hardcore version of the main server
[Music]
needed to be a bit more
automated yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I mean so far like when diamonds
are being put in a box nobody's stealing
them either so we wouldn't steal
anything I'm pretty sure so if you can
just put like 5,000 diamonds in a in a
chest and then we just take our rewards
on our own would also
work Diamond leaderboards
oh yeah all kinds of leaderboards that
could also be motivating yeah
[Music]
yeah people I was just saying people are
really
busy people have become more and more
busy Japanese members too so like this
only really works because it's a
short-term
[Music]
thing maybe some people would continue
playing even if it was long term but
not as many as now it wouldn't be so
focused it wouldn't be so you
know you
know you wouldn't be like this sadly the
golden times of Minecraft with whole
life are
over sadly and I thought pal world was
the one why did P World dice down so
fast it had so much
potential oh but also P world we didn't
have shared servers we were like oh Ena
just went
to the Fortress I
suppose um what was I saying yeah I
think the thing is like we were we all
had separated
servers yeah and then we got busy wait
was it like why did we get busy I got
busy while everybody else was playing
but then everybody else stopped why was
this a around firstest
[Music]
time was it around
Fest I think it might have been around
Fest lack end game really really there's
no content really I didn't get so far so
didn't I didn't have that
impression
m r was
like kind of even more long Las Ming
them pal
world but it was also like you know
seasons of it so Rost is not really
something I would prefer Minecraft you
know and I would prefer power world and
I would even prefer
GTA yeah R was just replaced of other
fotm I don't know Minecraft was just so
strong for such a long
time and
then can I put should I put Ming on my
sword
oops fall 76 I thought that was maximum
four people
[Music]
it's not the
same
[Music]
oh
eight you should really push for whole
GTA why me why do I have to push for it
actually I think originally cie was
pushing for it and then
and I think they were going to make it I
don't know why it stopped it's just like
you got to keep on
pushing I don't know what happened
[Music]
ohuh saai wants to discuss I think in 40
minutes together where to do the
Wither uh and asking people if they want
to discuss it if they want to be part of
the discussion to come to the house in
the
beginning I mean I don't really care
where we do it but I guess I'll go there
[Music]
nice middle of the
Town it would add to the drama and if if
the Widow was after the Ender Dragon we
could totally do that and just in the
middle of the town because everything
will be wiped
anyway maybe we should have done the
Ender Dragon first and not the winner
[Music]
yeah the only ones who responded were
Ana and me we're so diligent
diligent I think okay I'm going to fill
up this one level and then I'm going to
[Music]
go can be summoned to wipe the town no
we'll do it classic
[Music]
way mat it's the mat
and my music is already telling you it's
a
festival we use hyper boost I don't
think so maybe she'll boost the Wither
but I don't really think she's
considering that actually
[Music]
okay one more come
on come
[Music]
on come on come
on getting impatient come on come on
come on just one just one just one enemy
just one enemy you might want to stay
you're a bit longer
why why
why
what p is going to
[Laughter]
T that's
[Music]
why
well let's get my level up to
30 hey but I'm
shy I'm
shy oh hey wow actually that went up
fast you should punch her off of the
ladder no she'll HTE me
forever you can deliver your Ling oh
true okay I'll do that and then I'll go
maybe unless you have something to say
to
me do I look good
that look
good look
[Music]
good on the ladder
already is that her down there oh dear
oh God
[Music]
okay reached level 30 y I'm ready to go
I'm ready to
[Laughter]
go okay I guess I'll go
[Music]
for
nice
for okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
byebye she asked me if I have any gas
tears I don't think I have a single one
because we killed some gas but they just
like dropped their droppings
elsewhere in in the ocean of lava I
think and then she asked me if I have
any more never right but no I don't
but I said I said yo I I said this to
you when you were muted so I'll say it
again but I'll protect you today with my
never red armor and she was like oh okay
I'll use you as a meat Shield then and
I'm like
uh didn't want to go that far to like be
a meat Shield so to say I was just going
to go to the front line but yeah sure
okay I'll be here meat
shield and then she was like acting it
out standing behind me this is how we'll
do it I'm I'm like okay and then she was
like okay that means I don't have to
prep anything for the wi fight right I'm
like yeah don't you don't have to do
anything no I think she'll still do
it what does she need the tears
for the gas
tears they're so hard to get if you kill
them when they're far away and all of
the [\h__\h] gas that we were fighting
they all stayed so far
away don't know what's their issue
for potions what potion do you make with
that LE
[Music]
for
yes yes yes okay okay okay okay thank
you's
[Laughter]
I said if you want to blow something up
in the never you know you should use
beds I recommend beds but then I said
it's a joke it's
joke she seemed so naive that she would
do it
so uh we're
going
actually I can exchange some of
my wait was it the other way it was the
other way some of my uh I and I'll try
to exchange here because it might be
cheaper she knows it's a joke yeah cuz
at the end I said
usoo she seems pretty por so it's
probably
better if she does strip mining although
I really thought it wasn't really that
difficult once I got into it once I
wasn't scared
anymore oh oh it seems like
[Music]
they're I don't get
up okay this
[Music]
one you don't have it you have
it
26 I think just that one
more oh
nice
Tas okay I'll go
to
Kyla should have more yeah but they were
like always at freaking six and then up
to eight these ones had
four of course that by still wearing the
Wither head but AKA
Senai she's been like protecting and and
working for Pula Senpai this whole time
but now I'm her meat Shield perhaps
maybe I don't know if we were that
serious about about it I don't know if
we're actually going to do that if she's
serious about it I don't know
either I'll just try to be in the front
line I'll try I think I don't know maybe
I'll change my mind
spontaneously oh yeah Kyla's not online
right now right she's having her dinner
so nobody will be
tending to it but it's
okay W what's up Ana
oh hey oh 15 we should sleep oh hello we
should sleep yeah we should sleep sleep
with
Anya Oh I thought she would slip with me
in
here
no hate
those all right did you did you cool
thank you I'll get cooler even more but
did you use up all the the iron
thingies no no I did not okay it's still
six oh my God it's so
expensive so expensive oh this one's
Fuller free bamboo free
bamboo on the right side the the tall
bamboo trees oh this this one oh they
there too tall
okay take the bamboo and
sell how
[Music]
many oh as in the sticks wait you
get maybe I'll do that too oh I don't
know how much will I need is this enough
maybe it's enough can I join your server
no no unless you can DM P Senai is this
dude supposed to be
outside are you supposed to be outside
[Music]
dude oh okay
so should I really put like Unbreaking
and mending on all of
these
mending do we even need
mending because it's ending
tomorrow stop looking at me
[Music]
yeah feel like we might be able to skip
mening
now cuz it's ending
tomorrow
Unbreaking
Unbreak
one two three
and uh what
else
protection oh I guess I could put
Unbreaking on boots as well
obviously oh it's cheap
now I already have Fe falling what
protection
[Music]
five what is the work Fus on a
s
oh that's
[Music]
interesting
okay Action Four is most
important uh it's five
[Music]
oh no it's four sorry I can't
read well it's
Latin but yeah I I I I know how to read
that uh should I combine the books again
or is it like
whatever um I love
books
oopsy no
books no books don't
[Music]
un books
oh
on uh-huh we still have some
books oh I have um two books I can give
you one
really yeah thank
you thank you I'll probably have to make
more anyway
[Music]
huh n should I return the template for
you cuz I copied I copied one oh I guess
so I guess so thank you maybe I'll give
it to
stand H
bookshelf
41 bookshelf uh bookshelf bookshelf
bookshelf like you probably have
nine emeralds for one
[Music]
bookshelf no how do you
make
uh oh well yeah with books but what how
do you make a book oh we can't make a
book we can't make just a book letter
and paper M I'm too
lazy okay I guess I'll go get some more
[Music]
iron okay
speee
[Music]
[Applause]
speee
she reacting over there
what they got
do telling her it's not that big of a
deal
unless she spawns like five Withers or
but she can't God you yes finally I was
called God
too yay I have I have ascended to God
I've been promoted to
God
yay yay
I am God become as God
woohoo Phoenix God
strong y KY and Ki the Minecraft Gods
isn't that beautiful doesn't that sound
great
[Music]
another villager
farm she doesn't want to be called
God what I'm sure she enjoys it deep
inside
oh listen listen oh hi we
[Music]
okay OHA I was going to tell you the
joke that I F
of what joke cuz you were um you were
being called oroa by for and several
times and then I was like I said or or
you know which ore gold
Platinum
[Music]
diamonds or preferably neite
neite well you're looking more like a
diamond to me but that should be that
should be a compliment
actually
okay or of the or yeaha of the Ora of
the or
Ora I wanted to write it in the chat but
I thought for this sen I might get
confused so that's
true okay well I guess I'll see you at
the are you going to the meeting U not
sure maybe yeah was that uh ReRe it 9:00
p.m. jst I guess in 20 minutes I got to
hurry
[Music]
yeah
ohai completed the challenge cover me in
De
wait she would she was already oh ah she
just made herself the head or so cuz she
was missing the head I
think uh what did I come here for
wait this is not where the iron is
right oh the freaking opposite
side always the opposite okay we'll need
to change PGM
[Music]
now really calm RPG the Calm before the
storm this this this
Co she's shining too I need to be
shining too but damn she looks cool in
that really
cool my problem will be I'll have no
potions and stuff but I feel like some
people might give it might be giving it
away for free maybe
maybe wasn't that here
guys I'm lost again was it the other
[Music]
way the wiow will get absolutely
destroyed for real though maybe I don't
need any potion okay maybe not potion
but at least milk milk is
easy and I still have two fire
potions turn left ah
yeah God why am I so
fing I'm so
lost milk milk in bowls was it
or how do you how do you
milk how to milk bucket ah
okay got to check out the other one
[Music]
sheep oh whose house is
this oh they're they're
sleeping wait if it gets to
six
ah sleep sleep sleep sleep go go go go
go
go have we done
sleeping yeah
okay you like the VM it's very RPG like
right I
know
oh okay I hope this is enough
[Music]
wish I had more
books but the books I can buy with the
emeralds I just wanted to get more iron
so I can get more
emeralds
yeah that house is cute
too ooh
K oh what that's
cute yeah I like it nice aesthetically
[Music]
pleasing this one's
interesting quite interesting not
bad m
[Music]
M this way this way for
KY dangerous well but there is water
down
there so I should be
safe okay hello again hello it's
me I've been
wondering
six anybody who's cheaping
four
than much
obliged come here you're too far you
don't have it
okay oh nice okay 52 more
[Music]
emeralds the iron farm has to go high
speed
please but otherwise I'll I'll mine some
of the I'll Farm some of the
[Music]
bamboo oh they're just talking about the
upcoming fight kind of and Mei says I
will protect you to to S Senpai and
telling her to also fight
[Music]
you got to go get some milk soon but
still an
hour so
oh wait I'm I'm done with that
uh wait do we have the Unbreaking enough
Unbreaking we need protection like three
more
ideally
okay so expensive I should be the
farmers
[Music]
got cheaper thank you for your mercy
wait one two
three four one
more fin I already have
it okay I don't need to combine them
[Music]
right I don't need to combine the books
right
[Music]
[Applause]
does it save
[Music]
exp I guess so
[Applause]
breaking let do it right yeah un
breaking
[Music]
protection uh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah and then we'll
put some stuff on the feather falling
boots
[Music]
too maybe after the
meeting
oh I wanted to try the The Shield thingy
run out of levels after all
okay uh
Noom here how does this work again uh
[Music]
paper how does
look need to make a banner
first banner and you
[Music]
Banner put the banner here I guess
somewhere
[Music]
huh
huh die
[Music]
I do have some squid but not here with
me right
now
[Music]
oh she has blue dye no a blue lapis L
life uh
die how much G oh
10 ah here
I'll take some how much does it need
I'll give it back but she has orange too
let me see how does it look how does
this
work and then what's this
part it should be white honestly
[Music]
yeah white
D
pattern so but first for example I do
black and then put it I put it in again
and put the white on
it what what should I
do to make it look good thanks for the
membership
gift like I don't
know the gradation looks really smooth
[Music]
graduation white do su Tri
I don't know how this is going to turn
out but wait what if I do this again
does it get darker oh layering
[Music]
huh I don't want to like accidentally
make some sign that means
something like I feel like that could
accidentally happen
[Applause]
lightning
I how did Kyla make it look so fancy
[Applause]
huh these don't look so
fancy she had a pattern pre-made
oh okay
[Music]
thank I become a wall
no I got to go to the meeting soon I
need to
decide she asked permission from
twitch
uh I don't know these don't look that
good look like a mirror
I can also just leave it the way it is
maybe that looks cool
too it's simple but it might look good
try Orange
[Music]
[Applause]
it doesn't look so
good I should have had some kind of
pre-made pattern let's leave it
[Music]
simple how do I put it on the
shield how does that work I forgot it's
been a long time
she another yeah
maybe like I don't know how she made it
look shiny but I have a feeling if I do
another gradation gradual
gradation in like blue for
example how was hers like shining it
feel like it was like like shining like
it was enchanted oh she did I thought
that wasn't
possible but you might want to do that
too
then just okay how do I we can still
maybe change it afterwards too I don't
know how do I how do I put it on there
just like
this
okay that's better than before for real
M so much
better okay meeting and then level a few
more levels although P but is still
[Music]
here
luk
Y strong laa cool laa God wa
[Music]
for
okay okay
[Music]
we have confirmed the plan so it seems
like a
plan seems like I I become her meat
Shield oh need to get it's okay we still
have like 1 hour until the actual fight
uh we can get some food and the milk um
but enchantment wise I'll just I guess
finish up the
boots the rest is okay like it's hard to
get levels right now maybe by the end of
the day I'll have even more levels and
enchantments
[Music]
the first house is which
one this
one oh portion of strength a [\h__\h] ton of
them and slow
falling strength and slow falling and O
the apples I'll take like a
few maybe few pumpkin pies
[Music]
I'll make them into gold apples on my
own I
think three diamonds in
there
y everybody's like uh uh those are those
those are
those those are
those 42 diamonds
fre okay
[Music]
uh oh let's put this in here
too did you get milk no yet the fight is
not starting now
[Music]
she going to idle
meeting oh does that mean I'm being
[Music]
heard
protect I have been hired as a meat
shield for p Sena she's AFK by the way
are you here for the
meeting yes yeah okay she was like is it
only us too but it's good that you're
here stay here stay here there's more
more
[Music]
okay this Y where are they yay
hello fore
[Music]
I'll log out
y p is like what why is there only so
few people we're going to die with these
people but we're not going into the
fight right now we're just discussing
where to do it Kyla will come for the
real fight for example I think more
people will be there for the real fight
did they make it oh
nice for
[Music]
not
for for
[Music]
a for
oh
I don't know how to let go I'm
[Music]
sorry for
[Laughter]
how many people were we six seven
maybe for
foree
okay
[Music]
okay for
t
okay so basically the discussion she
first asked who like uh fought with wiow
before and in that group it was only me
and Ena
and then later uh like we told her we
fought it outside and we fought it only
with five people and
even and even then it wasn't so
difficult but I guess with like they
have I didn't know that was different
difficulties um so yeah of course it's
going to be a bit more difficult then I
guess but we're also more people now and
also we didn't have never ride back then
and now a lot of us have never right I
think we're we'll match the difficulty
um hardcore with a built different I
suppose but I still we I think we're
matching the diff the
difficulty will I think other people
also will join at 1 p.m. a few more
mikoi Senai also was not at the
discussion but I think she'll be there
for the Wither fight so I think it'll be
fine what I need now is buckets so I
need a bit more
[Music]
iron but yeah and then yeah she also
asked okay so who the ones who fed
outside how was
that yeah just basically sharing our
experience with that and they were like
hey really is that
easy like yeah I mean yeah
H looking forward to it also yeah I
recommend it uh we should fight it
outside like further away from the
village and she was like yeah I agree
and I said cuz she said we can also find
it underground but I I said that's kind
of boring right because it's just too
easy and kind of it will be cramped
[Music]
also where's my bed anyway I just left
it at home
[Music]
and I think when it's cramped it will
just also not look so good on
stream yeah I I I I suggested a desert
but no one has found a desert
yet I don't think we need to spawn more
than one if it's actually more difficult
and hardcore then I think wait I know
where to go this way I know I remembered
now for once PLS biome yeah anything
flat really would be helpful
it's the damage it will do on Hardcore
yeah yeah yeah I know I know I guess
it'll do more
but you
know oh wait I don't need that much huh
how many buckets of milk should I
prepare I don't even have that much
space
it oh wait they stack never mind at
least for now they stab at least three
three
four I'll make
10 I'll make
[Music]
10 yes yeah when milk they don't stack
it's okay I just right click the cow and
get the milk
right and then we'll try to make some
more golden
apples but there's a lot of strength
Potions there and the falling potion
slow falling but what do you think is
best should I if I use a potion should I
use one of the strength FS or should I
make a fire I don't think F did much
with fire did
he fire wasn't much of an
issue I
think oh the milk at rid of the potion
what for
real strength and region of best okay
then I'll bring a few strength potions
with me especially if I'm really ending
up in the front
[Music]
line actually I'll bring those back I
don't need them anymore
[Music]
uh these ones remind me I'm still
putting them
on did I get one protection too
[Music]
much I guess I did
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] wait more
gold golden app
Apple
ooh
what only so few it needs a lot of gold
but maybe free apples
is enough cuz they add more Hearts too
right it's
like extra
Hearts
plenty blast protection would be good
but did Kyla have that
[Music]
you can buy those golden apples that
would be a deal yeah I can get a few
golden
carrots perhaps where is where was a
chest with the
[Music]
wool I was my own but I'll donate it
okay little
cows why do I have all these eggs
oh I can't take it from the same cow you
don't run out of
milk hey y thank
[Music]
you yeah the cow
packing oh she has uh her new outfit as
her Minecraft outfit that looks cool oh
the white color looks
nice what if I shoot the Wier with eggs
wouldn't that be funny just create a
bunch of little chickens as
distraction maybe somebody will be like
who the [\h__\h] is shooting
eggs
me who
else Cy as a weapon let us fight yeah
I'm summoning you to my Army
m i mean there's enough time to maybe go
mine some gold in the uh nether to make
a few more apples I think I have time
for
that I can go into existing tunnels I
feel like there's a lot
unmined um a lot of
unmined
material but let me put this away for
now
[Music]
yeah don't want to die don't don't want
to die it's just mining a little bit in
peace in a
tunnel that's all I'm going to do wait
pickaxe is at the end the chest I
think yeah I do have a gas deer oh one
yeah I had a feeling I feel like I saw
it what do you think she still needs it
I think she went that way is she still
[Music]
there it will please
p regen pots
regeneration well oh
[Music]
see
okay I wonder if she comes
here I'll come to you or you come to me
evil way is
fine no need to wear gold no
so I was thinking just taking a few of
these potion of
strengths
maybe oh
okay okay this is her house
right and where's chest she said put it
in a chest I'm going to put it here but
it's like a little bit hard to
see is it okay to enter I saw this place
exploding once I'm kind of scared
[Music]
hi not this one oh was it not this
one uh okay then I'll go into the ne get
some gold oh my Aqua Z also wants gold
golden apples I
guess you're not going to enchant The
Shield I want to B uh we'll see maybe I
get some
ah maybe I'll get some
levels and then I can still do it we
have 40
[Music]
minutes all right if I die I'll still
have my never right uh head in the inner
chest and imagine dying now I would not
make it in time for the fre fight
[Music]
probably voice is so cute wait I went
the wrong way huh
ah
ah mine quartz yeah I can mine some more
quarts
[Music]
to protection four on the I know I know
I do you see my level I ran out of
levels I'll be working on that I don't
think maybe n no I could make it for the
weather
might make it for the weather in
time
okay bgm
change I think I'll go this way maybe
even to my
tunnels
um I have a few things I have a fighting
music on the playlist too but I used it
before
oh yeah mining it in tunnels is safer
cuz no one's
watching let's do it this way
we're lurking fief thiefing the
underworld from its gold well it's free
range
gold cute music right I like this kind
of music and it's so lowkey
too scoozie coming back to the place
where we spent several hours last
night hi I know you will want to kill me
once I take some of the gold but please
don't need some building blocks to get
up
there okay 60 already
okay I can shoot him from up here safely
I
think oh he's
gone wait how do I already have 64
golden
nuggets I'm I'm surprised every time how
uh
quickly you can gather
them
nice there's some over
there there's a lot man
[Music]
okay ni how much is this already in in
blocks in in englands fortun oh yeah
right cuz oh it's the
fortune being useful for me
now just getting some EXP
you're not mad if I M this one right the
quartz is beautiful too why do you only
care about
gold or or
or my manding pick is
oh oh
well that is true but it's
okay oh I totally forgot about but he
didn't
care he didn't care at all I see now
it's going to me cuz now the pickaxe is
mended maybe they don't want to attack
me because they see I have full never
right armor you're going to have an
issue with this
m nope he didn't see it he went in there
he's going to come back and be like he
where did that gold go am might loose
ating hu Halu
much I don't need that much more levels
right I'm just trying to enchant the the
boots but it's okay I'm still looking
for gold
too you don't get AGA from
zomi oh these ones don't care oh those
ones over there care I
think o ink
oink
you
nice level
six are you guys excited for the wi
fight I hope but I I I really hope that
my experience will be proven wrong and
it will not be so easy but also not so
so difficult that everybody dies just a
nice in between so that there's
some some
drama but not too
much P She f it before right but
underground I'm pretty sure she did but
she didn't when she was asking who did
it before she didn't mention herself
yeah with Mo right I I I feel like I
remember like watching a clip or
so
okay pretty good I think this might be
enough in terms of
gold what do you think for a few
apples definitely
many nuggets I have oh my God so
many I need at least 11 levels oh wait
ah I fell
down I don't have a fire potion with
me it's
okay oh wait I might be able to get to
it oh
nice okay
level 10 oh this is so much faster than
TT should have done that the first time
but then I wouldn't have met one time
oh I forgot about you I stay calm I'm
calm go
away okay level
11 Japanese Bros cuz I'm streaming at a
rare time I think there's some more
Japanese Bros than usual
I'm am
goofy I want to play a game that would
have a bgm like this sneaky cute
stealthy game but like cute okay cute
some kind of cute game like I don't know
like that alligator game although that
wasn't sneaky or so but I feel like it
would still maybe have a Vibe like this
alligator game was cute I can't fix
that I can't and I don't want
to where are all my other PS I can't see
them oh oh that's not one this is one
that's one short one
though just a bit more exp for good
measure for safety
go back
now okay okay okay okay
okay where's the exit
here heart's pretty good for X for real
it
is
God quartz is called I love quartz it
looks beautiful too I wish it had a few
more
uses besides just looking nice for
buildings and I I think yeah there's
surely a few more uses that I can't
think of right
now um but I wish it had more it's just
not really that
valuable yeah
observers yeah it's just niche
[Music]
everyone using your pathway H you mean
the never path that we built as a
group you mean them the
pigs I thought you meant the Japanese
members using uh the
paths they they did though they totally
did
[Music]
everybody using the paths that we have
paved to
get all kinds of good
stuff like ancient debris making a
achievement gallery on the journal
place I achievement
Gallery
[Music]
n you walked so they could run I I
didn't even walk I like
crouch
crouch uh what's slower than
[Music]
walking I crouch
sled craw
I've been
crawling placing those
blocks
[Music]
yeah okay uh gold
Ingot ingots for the apples right
mhm uh
apples gold
Apple I have a gold I have an
apple o gold
Apple thank you thank you thank you I
appreciate it love you guys you're the
best yeah
ooh eight apples eight apples good
amount I
think just got to get um these I think
these are pretty uh filling
right decently
filling maybe I'll get a few
more wait just put them El it's too full
get my books
get the blocks in
there and oh yeah my buckets need to go
back does it also heal any HP at
all
oops
maybe yeah we don't need that many
buckets in the task in the
bar right not
immediately if I run out of them in the
bar I'll go back and then try to
organize my
inventory it removes the weather effect
I know yeah only the debuffs
okay hey if the rther is stronger in
hardcore I guess the Ender Dragon is
also stronger in
hardcore stronger as in it just hits
harder or how is I guess that's it
right get some health arrows what the
[\h__\h] is Health
arrows does less damage than the Wither
oh okay well then we'll manage but it's
just I think it's still harder to fight
because you need to hit all the
towers and H the bed explosions oh
that's why we might need some more beds
I don't know if we're doing that are we
going to do that is it like
you can do it without the beds too
right but I wonder what the Strat will
be maybe we'll have another meeting
where we decide to
Strat fix the time a I already why do I
you guys keep on making me repeat myself
today already said I'm still waiting for
someone's reply but I did get uh like
reminded from you guys last night and
then I messaged the group and said hello
can we fix the time so waiting for one
[Music]
reply okay this is pretty
much the inventory that we're going to
go with well the Torches are
also not what we
need torches let's put them
away I still have some more leftover
apples but not enough gold
maybe I can make some more golden
apples maybe there was some more gold in
that free chest I'm guessing not at this
point that upper fire turn oh it's
really nothing I just it was on the day
when I was um doing dance uh
recordings and I think I might have also
just been generally doing a few other
things too where I was using my f a lot
but I recorded two dances and then I was
like H actually I kind of wanted to do
the uh narissa say my name
challenge
oh
and there we go that might be
good but I was watching the video and
it's really not like a proper
Coral um so I tried to I tried TR to
recreate it there's a lot of
like what do you call them like the
drops do we call
them what what what do we call those
drops I'm sure there a proper name I
don't
know
oh oh oh my helmet I think it's in the
end chest I get it um
yeah uh so this there
um and I was trying to recreate that I
was trying to learn it but I don't know
it just didn't feel like there was much
there like I don't know I didn't feel
like a proper
dance so I already did a bunch of those
drops the SLO drops yeah I did a bunch
of
them and then am I missing one oh my God
Wonder
three 1 2 3 4 5 6 78 I'm missing
[Music]
one maybe I'll
find
um yeah
[Music]
and for
okay yeah yeah she's asking everybody if
they're okay if something here gets
broken she does want to do it like
around there I said oh it's probably
fine
M my house is pretty close to it but I'm
just going to put my important things
into the Ender Chest I
guess yeah anyway so I was doing some
many of those drops and then more and
more I noticed my my FS were like
dying and I was like y b this is like a
work out what I'm doing because then I
tried to come up with my own
choreography still kind of trying to be
inspired by the original so to say dance
and include some of these
drops
um sorry I can't
multitask and it got even worse like
yeah eventually I gave up just because I
couldn't come up with something
good and yeah the only thing I got out
of it was pretty damn weak and sore f it
was a legit workout
play with fire take me
[Music]
higher may my
name with fire take
me my
name am I just going there because I
need an anvil I feel like an animal
could have been elsewhere too I just
realized that now
I was tricked into doing squats
exactly she it it I felt it the whole
following day and partially even the
following
day if you know play the
game you want me to get golden carrots
I'm out of emeralds bro I don't think I
need
them I can exchange my diamonds for
emerals
but uh what did I come a for the
Anvil
okay you protection oh wait then I let
me combine the books first
protection Unbreaking
cost mine there you go well El was I
going to do am I fine the the the sword
is not perfect it could use some more
stuff but it has sharpness
five
so wait oh okay I was going to say wait
I'm not shiny but yeah I'm I'm kind of
shiny I wish it was more shiny though
[Music]
if you had levels you wanted the shield
with Extra Protection
oh oh wait I can put protection on the
shield ah then maybe I didn't buy it by
accident
ah uh oopsie uh
oh
oopsy how
much
oh only Unbreaking and mending ah damn
it
Unbreaking I wish I could
like exchange the book maybe somebody
needs protection 4 and can exchange it
with a different one they they'll buy it
for
me ana ana ana hi are there any books
that you still
need um I don't know I I honestly don't
know because I have an extra protection
uh protection 4 book even though I need
Unbreaking
free
oh you don't need that one yeah I was
going to like exchange it or I think I
can make use of it I can make use of it
if that's okay with you my let's go do
you have the Unbreaking free
then Unbreaking I use them for my do you
have any more Emerald so you can make it
and I it be like just do a fair exchange
of me giving protection for I have I
have one more Emerald but I'll be
exchanging for more okay okay please
help me any I'll me yeah yeah yeah you
will not make any loss because I'll give
you the
book okay okay hold on
um Kyla joint Kyla is
B is she in her house
[Applause]
KAAL you need don't don't don't no
nothing else just a book Kyla oh just
just a book okay here you go oh hello
let me give you my book yeah thank you
wait hi K wait wait I think the book I
didn't pick the book up oh oh oh oh oh
hold on hold on wait no you did that
you did I don't I don't have it I don't
see any more book any more empty book in
my oh you gave me the empty book oh no I
thought you were going to give me the
Unbreaking book oh Unbreaking book hold
on hold on let me let me let me can I
can I can I have the book back I thought
you need an empty book okay hold on it's
going to be a get one for
you
Kyla let me update you we're doing the
Wier fight outside uh around the uh the
courthouse we'll probably meet right
there at 9:00 p.m. uh in oh in 15
minutes yeah okay can open it y thank
you here you go here you
go
CH thank you but I think I'm missing sh
by the way we do we do I think I'm
missing one level though we do we
totally do okay um no I've accepted the
right amount of levels
y woohoo can I upgrade this
one which one which one will be better
to upgrade shiny sh shiny
[Music]
shieldin some upgrad as
well
K can I sleep next to you
yeah yeah yeah yeah you can you you can
use the bed yeah okay I'm sleeping next
to you I need to show you something when
we wake up not appearing okay
okay M why the game is not appearing
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
okay KY do you have some spare gold just
like a few
ones let me check okay because I'm
afraid that I turn it into Golden Apple
yeah no problem no problem I think I ate
apples is maybe enough for
me probably
enough
sleep
[Music]
sleep I'm waiting to sleep okay okay
okay they sleep they sleep
finally okay good morning
look now I'm all shiny
nice I'm in didn't have a cool pattern
but at least it's shiny that's all I
want Shin yay yay we're shiny
together yay we're the most decked out
out of
everybody let's
go let's [\h__\h] go and I exchanged the
book
successfully it was a fair exchange I
think cuz uh it was three versus four
M let's just now put our
uh oh you shooting at
me let's just put our important things
into the end the
chest just just in case I don't think it
will go that far I remember we did move
around quite a bit in the
desert but mostly into One Direction so
if we managed to push the uh wither into
the direction away from the
village I forgot my
gold what do you mean I forgot my gold I
don't have enough what do you mean I
forgot
it
what from Ella no she said she might not
have enough so I'm like okay whatever
fine
oh this is the stuff that ladin left
behind can I smelt this back into
gold I think that works
right guess
yeah she's done did she did she die or
was she just there for one
day one nth of
gold
uh I don't have
[Music]
anything no no
okay the helmet
[Music]
too well if she still needs it I'll make
it for her again this is easy stuff wait
no oh it's falling off no uh wait what
where did it go did I get the six
nuggets out of that
[Music]
wait went to the
box I
here just one
[Music]
let me make it somewhere else
though one freaking nugget but I think I
want to see how the PO maybe maybe we
can make it do I maybe have more nuggets
in
here
I that's also the extra bed
I kind of need to go to Idol meeting but
I'll fight through it probably through
the
Wither the it will give me more
tenseness maybe that will be
good gold
nuggets I always have few nuggets up my
sleeve
yeah okay I mean we can still smelt it
but uh let's smell
these and make gold
inot now I can make one more Apple Gold
Apple nine
apples just one more would be nice
though I don't think I can make it no no
no no there's no
way also she gave me ah here's a regen
potion so wait is that's one 30 doesn't
mean I get dot
[Music]
regen is that what that
is oh nice should I drink it right in
the
[Music]
beginning why not burn this why not
not okay let's put this away let's put
this away ah wait I wanted to put my
important things into a
chest okay this is important maybe
although I don't think I'll get to use
it this is important this is
important that's pretty much it
[Music]
use apple first before
potion riding a horse I look like a
commander oh that would be cool if I
show up on horse but
nah ex important
[Music]
fore okay
I don't want to like talk too much
around them I feel like I'll be uh like
bothering in their stream like talking
English to
myself idle meeting time okay I'll go
really quickly if somebody talks to me
tell
[Music]
them I'll be right back
spee
[Music]
it's good
okay I give smoothie a hug too because
she was like looking really cute oh MAA
went online oh where she
revived MAA MAA will be helping too see
I think we'll be plenty of
people yeah 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 hi MAA hi
MAA hey hiy
MAA L hi
hey hey hey hey oh my God I sound like
her don't forget to laugh yeah are you
ready for the fight because I think
everybody prepared quite
well oh yeah what do you have wow you
got some I have look at you oh that's
right wow yeah I worked hard on this t
nice also looks like this
oh thought it was Japanese
members I made it
shiny I don't think I've ever been this
prepared for anything in my whole life
really
yeah shiny G yeah
g it's about time
[Music]
ah wait did I put it in
there
yeah so we have some strength potions
first I'll take the region potion maybe
early on but the Apple first Apple first
and then regen I thought we were
supposed
to go to the another gate and yeah right
yeah but I think wasn't that only when
we thought we were going to go through
the ne to fight him don't
know guess we can go there I thought
because it's also next the The Fighting
place is next to the courthouse where is
there's also the neate there so oh I see
guess we can go there is it that way
yeah we can go okay I always
forget me
too oh they're sleeping again I didn't
bring my bed ah
on there's a bed near nearby I
think yeah there's a blue bed nearby
okay yeah I saw it somewhere ah
here 7 out of
10 8 or 10 n
Yoo we're doing
it okay we're so ready dud
to war with the
winner we we we just going to wait here
right yeah yeah yeah yeah around here
we're going to fight here next to the
courthouse we
[Music]
just let's look strong next together
much much better we're the
strongest like
[Music]
heaven which which side that I should be
anywhere this
this
okay thank youe
[Music]
[Laughter]
power power
will if the wi comes
[Music]
I'll
for
protect but she also protect
[Music]
did call
me future name
no no I'm not strong I stronger
[Music]
very good
purple you let's ask
Ana yeah I like red yeah I
like did you hear me was tank in
Japanese red red it's okay this time I
blue I can't hear her red
stone why the [\h__\h] can I here red
[Music]
stone
Wasing yeah red stone blue you and me
Brew
yeah yeah yeah
yeah you brw okay
okay okay okay I R you R We R no Brew no
Brew no bre red
red oh we're getting even
more I'm quiet well for you guys but I I
lowered the desktop audio a little bit a
moment ago should be a bit
better I didn't I didn't go cuz like
there
was we need to be on time you know
[Music]
J
for okay
[Music]
for
okay I was telling that we might be able
to lead it like away but then again Pai
probably wants to lead it towards the
buildings to create a big
[Music]
disaster you
yep yep yep say
something say
something didn't really impr much oh
well we just got to go
[Music]
away I'm glad together we represent Ian
Strong
[Music]
did you guys hear that did you guys
catch
that I can slightly hear
[Music]
you what is going
on going on
honestly she's actually making in the
middle I was going to suggest it like
why don't we just make it right in there
but it might make it more difficult to
fight she's making it in the in the
fighting
ring wait she is yeah we're going to
start in
there oh
[Music]
[Applause]
no oh no yeah
[Music]
for you should eat it now
I had his
argro where is
[Music]
he let's go
he was so stick
[Applause]
right oh I don't have a bed
I'll just log out for a
moment oh they were sleeping for the
night
already nice tanking right that was I
told you it was going to be fast but he
was totally on me right I saw him inside
of me
[Music]
it's so
fast it was so
fast I was toally
[Music]
tanking you're truly a tank now yeah I'm
embodying my sword and my shield
did you use your bow you the SW have
enough stuff for the dragon easy easy
easy that
was I was just laughing because it was
so
short there was so
many
I it was going to be easy
[Music]
one more one
more one more one more one
more she wants to spawn free of them in
the
village which which
[Music]
Village she wants us to find
it she says find it
[Music]
yourself which which one should we stay
together let's find it together it could
be
anywhere we need to find it yeah she
says she spawn free of them in random
places oh really separate places
[Music]
theya reload on
milk is she still here no
I don't know if if if she's going to
spawn free in the same place or free in
separate places I
don't okay it will be where we live
that's for sure so let's go there let's
go
y got to hurry we to search it yeah it's
somewhere where we
live so it's randomly yeah yeah kind of
random I'm going follow you car
[Music]
okay I only have my bow and
swords stay strong I feel like I should
my ma you can get some free stuff here
potions and stuff might be
[Music]
useful he do do do do diamond diamond
we had a enchanting room
[Music]
ah I hear
it
what
[Music]
wait I'm so stupid I thought he will
ah I can't shoot like that wait
[Music]
easy easy easy
e no problem
[Music]
I still got
it no my house get away from my
[Music]
house no knock the house out
only house only house
[Music]
no no you're leading it towards their
houses
people no
no we have to protect
I want to hit him with the
sword oh God they're all on with a
bliss oh they're still only at half no
no stop stop running around the
[Music]
houses I'm shooting to hi
oh my God I'm my aim is
[Music]
d a
bur wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait oh ah
don't worry we'll take it
easy let's drink the potion where are
they I'm not
again oh he's right there in your
house it's okay fight fight stop fight
oh okay I got one hit and
y okay okay good
hits this is for my
[Applause]
house y my my God what a mess next
mission rebuild everything
what oh [\h__\h]
okay there's more all right
[Music]
hit oh he's dead I'm he already dies
when I'm in the
[Music]
inventory the war is
[Laughter]
[Music]
over she died as an honor full night
I couldn't become her Shield because it
was all over the
place she was tanking it for a while
[Music]
there is it her first death we can re
reive her until tomorrow
[Music]
maybe wait was she protecting the f
why just the why just the
cows why does the Wither hate
[Music]
cows oh she can't be
revived y
[Music]
[Applause]
she'll be revived good good good good
how do I get my milk but I don't think
we'll need milk for the Ender fight
right we'll got to we'll have to gather
everything for the Ender fight
too but can you
[Music]
imagine if it's going to go too easy
with the Ender Dragon 2 she's suddenly
going to spawn free
like if the one fight is not too easy
yeah not too difficult she going to end
up spawning more and more to satisfy
everybody
[Music]
okay oh I picked up so much
dirt I can fix
it I can fix
it picked up all the dirt it's fine
oh the chicken chickens are chicken it's
okay I have eggs I'll revive the
chicken nice we're we're fixing all the
holes nice I'll have some in my chest
I'll fix the
chickens chicken's gone no we we'll
bring them
back all the animals why do they not
place a flower for the
chickens no the wi also killed all the
the cows too oh I see but they only put
a flower for the for the cows not I'll
put the flower do I have a I have
flower sunflower is nice for you guys
everybody was only thinking about the
cows but you know I always think about
you guys therefore I plant this for you
big sunflower oh it will need some time
to uh look good
but this is for you my beloved
kfp I'll remember you as the true
Warriors that you are even if others
don't see you like
that even a big ass sakura tree there
you go
[Music]
she's laughing she doesn't have voice
chat on
but I told her everybody is talking
about the cows but nobody noticed the
chickens being
gone so sad you guys love chicken don't
you love to eat it then why don't you
why don't you feel sad when there's no
more when you're being forced to be a
vegetarian HH oh this was fun there was
like some did they already get rid of it
there was some lava here everybody was
like oh my God be careful of the
lava sudden
[Music]
lava yeah yeah
we have to fix
it yeah did ena's house get
[Music]
destroyed see I didn't call her Senai
this time so
proud solo okay Ida is going to the solo
server to get seven diamonds in 30
minutes good
luck yeah I guess it was her first
death okay wait where's what where am
I where is supposed to be ena's house
where am I can I try
to take out my armor and try the boat oh
keep talking hi I'm curious what are you
saying no what do you want to do I'm
trying to find something to do because
I'm confused what to do what what are
you planning to do after this oh uh I
think I'll complete the missions there's
some missions that we have to do uh in
preparation for the Ender Dragon um
there were like I think four missions
yeah we have to kill just one Ender and
we have to get free I think free ender
pearls and some other stuff we can do it
together I mean I I think I finished the
missions already though did you do it
today or did you do it yesterday you
have to do it
today I mean I do it in the morning
right when the new missions were up or
was it before oh no no no no no no you
just did it without the missions right
you didn't even think about the missions
yeah yeah
well but where would you recommend me to
go if I want to do the missions if I
want to fight Enderman um I I found the
I found the Enderman in the Soul Sand
biome in the nether okay yeah it's like
a lot there no no no not not sorry not
in the Soul Sand in the Crimson Forest
you know the greena thingy red forest or
green forest red Forest right yeah the
the the green green Green Forest red
Forest they they might be there yeah
I'll find it okay yeah War Forest oh War
Forest
but this one is this this one is already
pretty much we free to do whatever we
yeah yeah you can do whatever and then
tomorrow I'll probably around the same
time we fight the Ender
Dragon okay thank you you're welcome
good luck you
too okay so what we're going to do is wa
shouldn't their houses be
there what I'm so
[Music]
confused huh
where am I the other side but this is
Pam wasn't the ah wait over there I
thought they really just
disappeared I like was it that bad Ena
is
homeless homeless Ina
the first fight I feel like I was able
to help more because uh the Widow was
like you know mostly staying in a pretty
visible space but like spawning it here
we were trying to follow
it and we were in the water man she
chose a good place to create chaos
don't have the Red Blocks
[Applause]
[Music]
but big teacher
she was a teacher to
them now I can use up all of the shitty
blocks that I have maybe to fix this
[\h__\h] but is only not
online may use the priest of Kyla's
house only oh P Senai ah she Senai yeah
she's watching as a ghost she's
streaming as a ghost I
think what's Ena doing is she fixing her
Place hold
it
oh oh no it's
Anya Anya oh yeah what are you doing in
here
yeah this is my house this your
house
yeah good
love girl you live like this
okay okay I'll show you my actual house
okay okay you have an actual house I'll
will show you my actual house I show me
I hope it looks better than that I don't
remember the direction but it's
okay I was shocked Anya I thought it was
just like storage room from Ena or
so I like her
love where's the house hold on it's gone
maybe you never had one on yeah no no
maybe you never had a proper house I
have one H stuck at a house take your
med I'll show you I'll show you take
your
[Music]
meds I have one I swear to God hold on
well how come I've never seen it
an cuz I've I've never shown you that's
why maybe you never showed me because it
doesn't exist
[Music]
I didn't show you cuz why would I show
my house to someone I hate
right now that you're showing it to me
you know I will burn it
down I live with someone else so you can
oh well then if even if it looks nice
can we really credit you for
that well I mean it is technically my
house oh did you build this the bom is
in my house did you build it
yeah we live together yeah but you
didn't build it too I know it's pretty
but it's still my house
technically see there's two beds we live
together see there's two beds we live
together and no other Furniture this is
my house but I really actually really
love the uh effect of the falling petals
yeah I know it's really pretty damn must
be even prettier with
shaders damn yeah all right an I don't
have shaders so
I'm going to continue fixing the town a
little
bit okay yeah got to get some blocks
good
[Music]
luck can we reunite with with M Senai
and
Ana together oh B also coming Haim also
coming I just want to be with Miki and
Ana
she just asked like whoever wants to go
uh fight Enders and all that we're
gathering at the minute 40 so I guess
I'm not fixing the town anymore for
now U maybe later but the missions
they're not that rough really I'll check
it one more time but it's not a big deal
let's leave let's leave this stuff
behind and my house was totally unharmed
but it was kind of close to the action
it just went the other
way I forgot to put on my battle
music damn it just kept on playing
this I had I had this
tomorrow but there were also so many
screams maybe would we wouldn't even
have heard
[Music]
it yeah
tomorrow anyway
[Music]
that's also nostalgic I used it a few
times okay um yeah
uh if we go to the ne oh I need one
golden piece of
armor
[Music]
and yeah just that little bit of
food should be fine
right oh the Fire Res potions I think
they're in the Ender Chest got to hurry
got to hurry they're going to go in 2
minutes Fire PS maybe there's some more
also in the potion station oh no firebts
nothing's going to happen guys yeah I'll
take
one I don't think anything's going to
happen
okay I yeah my
pickaxe
maybe uh n this way or that way that
way torches nah we're enough we're
enough people they'll have
torches and also we're just going going
to the we're probably not even digging
any new tunnels oh somebody needs to
light
the the portal
[Music]
again I saw
one saw it
[Music]
somewhere h
oh what about what
about
no damn it that doesn't work maybe a bit
more ah I'm I'm setting it on
firey what the
heck
[Music]
for so we
pray fore
[Music]
[Applause]
it was my fire
[Music]
arrows no
it's it work mik Senpai made my my fire
eror
[Music]
reality fore
okay
okay we're not scared of anything
[Music]
I don't know what to play what music to
play maybe this one
beacons oh they dropped that stuff huh
[Music]
oh
for for
[Music]
oh they want to do the boat strp
okay
okay what was the rest of the missions
the other ones um it's the Wither the
Wither missions so we have them just
killing the Wither okay um make make a
golden apple oh okay okay nice nice make
one Golden Apple oh easy then we did
half them that's all for today's
Mission we have do we can extra diamonds
for fighting four
Withers
[Music]
please for
no where
where dead oh I think that was a kill
for me
right but it doesn't matter we're going
to kill a bunch of
[Music]
I'll go from here
oh
one there's one
here go get him go get him
[Music]
there's a few here quite a few
nice
Dro does she have a
[Music]
boat it's so easy
oh
[Music]
oh oh we're bullying them
oh
nice oh no that was a
fast there's one
there oh there's one I'm going to go get
that one and hopefully oh he's the boat
though
[Music]
oh I can't get him with the
bow I'm trying to get him with the
bow oh sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry they Dodge
arrows he's mad okay okay I think that
one's lost cause
yeah um Let's ignore that one sad it's
too
smart everyone else go just going to
chill the dog she not need the boat
anymore what did they did they try to go
there there was a and a man over there
[Music]
but they went pretty far
yeah let's
see where is
everybody
[Music]
oh
Panic no
[Music]
I'll try to maybe I
find oh there's one there but it's
difficult
[Music]
[Laughter]
just stare at oh yeah wait maybe they'll
come
[Music]
over oh I got in my eye bro I I I think
I looked at him he's coming over is
he I hear
him
where he was looking at me he gave up
though
[Music]
give me Pearl give me
Pearl damn it no pearl
[Music]
cuz they're so
far slaying
[Music]
I heard him
yeah I don't want to get caught in the
lava oh yeah that
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
for where
go fore
[Music]
I got it mission
I always regret my actions I look at
them and they come over and I'm like
yeah it it
it okay I have an extra one if someone
needs one
[Music]
yeah I have an extra one
now yeah I think everyone everyone else
has it I don't know probably we can just
get more and
more yeah I hear
something oh wow
easy oh he just needed one
hit oh okay I didn't even look at him
though
[Laughter]
[Music]
where you going
no did I get that one why do I have
[Music]
free we're too
strong the one you shot earlier
what I shot
somebody oh there's a few more there but
I think we all completed the mission at
this
point where' they go
[Music]
thank
you
[Music]
okay Bet
that sounded like someone put a bed
[Music]
down
exposion it's burning there so
maybe wait I thought it was a bed but it
might have been a ghast actually the
impact of a ghast
explosion with nothing
here that would have been funny
[Music]
oh he's
angry oh he's
angry why am I always so hungry
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah okay
[Music]
we're looking
for but she's disappeared and she's not
replying I thought he was kidnapped
[Music]
okay
let take a
[Music]
[Laughter]
picture
[Music]
[Applause]
fore yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
she's so
careful
[Music]
[Applause]
fore oh
[Music]
my mik also got
[Laughter]
[Music]
it this way
[Laughter]
[Music]
for he'll be there forever
[Laughter]
niceeeee
fore
fore speee
got to catch
up fastest runner in the
never Tak also known as t
[Music]
oh we're leaving someone behind
we'll find the End
Dragon one way or
[Music]
another
okay for
[Music]
[Laughter]
she saying
tomorrow nobody should die hopefully
we'll do our best to stay until the very
end yeah but today only one person
died and she'll be able to revive too
right nobody else died I
think today felt fast for real yeah it's
only been 4 hours hey there you go there
you go
wow I should
[Music]
even I don't know I wonder if I can buy
groceries probably not if I'm
reading um superjets but I kind of need
groceries because my hellofresh box was
not
delivered same time tomorrow an hour
earlier I'll first I'll wait for the
announcement I don't think in terms of
of prep there's much more that needed to
be done if if today if
tomorrow also there might not be any
other missions tomorrow either right I
still write my diary and all that don't
worry
but I think tomorrow might be pretty
short
too but I mean at least not longer than
today I feel
like oh it seems like a course Senpai
seems like she's hunting for uh ancient
deis because Picola Senpai is wondering
if she needs more
TNT maybe you can read suas
tomorrow I feel like I might be able to
do that and yeah for Preparation
tomorrow I mean we'll get everybody's
ender pearls together that should be
enough to find the the what do you call
it again the stronghold or so she's
reusing my mind my mind it's freaking
chaos there I don't recommend
it they're
using bu strip mine it's not really a
strip
mine using my
mind what's a [\h__\h] mess I feeling bad
but that's just what it looks like
normally it's so Bal
Bal then I made that stupid like chaos
strip mining action how many people are
[Music]
online all these all these people
stomping on my [\h__\h]
roof screaming and stomping on my roof
I'm so sick of it no just kidding I like
it but it makes me feel awkward cuz when
they're talking while they're running
over there I feel like I have to be
quiet noisy
neighbors by tomorrow it will be over I
can move out of this house I I never
ended up making a new house and Ollie
Ollie also didn't I I hope she'll be
there tomorrow cuz she wasn't here
today it would be nice if everybody
could make it for the final
fight someone at your window no I don't
think so that's just like a tree or some
something is there right or is that me
even something's moving over there all
the time but yeah what's Ena up to do
you guys know what is she
doing cuz did she do the missions yet
she she probably she finished oh didn't
she want to do like uh didn't she want
to get some ancient
debris did she do the missions at
all she finished missions early oh okay
okay but she didn't do the ancient
debris huh well she doesn't really need
it
anyway well are it it's in here right
yeah tomorrow maybe before the fight I
can try to uh repair this but I can
repair it with diamonds right and I
won't need my diamonds anymore so I can
just use them all up to repair
it
and yeah I don't know I haven't fought
the Ender Dragon in a long time maybe
there are some slow falling potions over
there that might be
useful in the starting
house yeah it might even last for
tomorrow I'm not going to get mending
it's a waste because cu the server is
being wiped tomorrow after the fight
guys it won't be it won't be that tough
I think I don't need
mending that's probably the only fight
I'm going to get into tomorrow
anyway man it's so sad that it's
ending when when is going to be the next
Minecraft adventure probably not for a
while stuck up on golden
apples yeah I have a few left over I
only used like three or four
I had nine yeah so I used four for
fighting four
Withers I think these five
apples
are yeah five apples and a bit more good
[Music]
food see I didn't need the potions
either I'll I'll use maybe the strength
potions
tomorrow I I think we'll be having a
good time are the next major updat since
that'll add a new stronghold like
structure I I will definitely I would be
open to getting back into
it but I guess everybody will go to the
Japanese
server aren't you glad P by yeah uh so
the things I probably would not have
participated if she didn't realize that
I sent her a message even though I
deleted
it cuz I was feeling feeling so
intimidated and like ah never mind I'm
deleting my message hope she didn't see
it I'll just I I just won't
join I mean today there was not that
much actually cuz the missions were so
little and our group was so big so we
didn't interact that much I guess but
it's okay I still
cherish every every day that we've had
so
far I'm guessing someone's probably
writing the diary right now but let me
check it out if someone's writing um
yeah actually let me
change happy music for ending was no
need to be intimidated you got over it
yeah I don't know I mean I think it it's
you know I really just didn't have that
much connection with everybody anymore
so I think feeling like that should be a
little bit
understandable Andy no one's using
it
okay maybe I'll just copy paste from
someone yeah cuz I did
everything did I make a potion
though I can make one
quickly oh no it's not potion it's
making a
uh making a golden
[Music]
apple yeah that's all the
missions copy okay
hi any did you write your
missions not
yet you write it yours I'm done it's I
just copy pasted from the others oh
[Music]
nice what am I looking at I don't
know actually let me carry this around
now
don't oh let's go
is she
[Music]
here is Ida like pretty good at
Minecraft I didn't
know yeah she's really
good good at
Minecraft yeah every time there's a
Minecraft event she always makes
St I don't
know wait is my
journal oh you know what I'm looking
forward to watching P Sen's uh
vud oh yeah me too cuz I want to see
what she said about my my journal
he or maybe let's write it at
home there's so many people here
[Music]
I think we all thought that overall more
people would die
today but I told I told you guys it was
going to be easy I told you I to pick
what a sire and even when she upped the
difficulty we were still
fine
yeah everybody's just old always way too
worried even the hardcore version of it
wasn't so difficult because we adjusted
our you know our power triple NE River
was fun yeah I think that's it's good
that she did that because otherwise it
would have been like it that's
it that that's
all okay I'm going to keep it short I
think again
[Music]
wa change
keyboard I guess tomorrow we won't be
riding one maybe because there will be
no stream
after you
hat free dragons I was saying like if
the if the first dragon is also as easy
and fast as the Wier was then she might
spawn more but I'm not sure about it
because I think it generally will just
take more time because we have to shoot
the towers and everything although we'll
probably going to be at least 15
people well okay
[Music]
oh inste
k
k k k m
not H hin henin the transformation henin
is the same word but different Kani as
henin the
reply word there's a word henin that
also can be used for replying to someone
[Music]
that's a star but maybe the the empty
one looks
nicer
[Music]
yeah oh that works in
oh using the sparkle emote in Minecraft
makes it also into these Sparkles oh
it's so pretty
wow then after that the only thing I
really did is fight the Wither right
after getting my never right
[Music]
armor what what was the material called
again uh that I used for my trim
uh what was
it brain empty
quartz H quart oh hello Cat did you go
to the toilet huh smoothie showed up
[Music]
and and I I wrote with the quart trim I
became even more
elegant and
then
uh do people want to
sleep you and then I went to the Wier
fight and
well oh I hear the toilet turning yeah
she really went to the toilet why does
she always feel the need to greet me
after she went to the
toilet I think it's because she woke up
and then she already generally feels
like greeting me after she wakes up but
first she goes to the toilet it's not
like she wants to greet me after she
went to the toilet it's probably just
she wants to greet me after she went
after she woke up right
[Music]
otherwise it would be so weird mom I
poop no generally I think you know cuz
her butt is wet like you often often
it's just like her having
peed are we not
[Music]
sleeping she's like ah people are not
sleeping huh Anna Anya running over my
roof
okay uh up up up up
o oh are we trying
again Anya is in my walls she's
Casper no I didn't I didn't I didn't pet
her this time
[Music]
good kids good children I supposed to
sleep come
[Music]
on now Ana is back again she's just
leaving the game hoping that people will
sleep ah now it's 9 out of 11 Ana yeah
go go go away
[Music]
Anya come on just one more now now I
think just one more
no is there someone AFK
[Music]
oops I never know which one's the right
key one more for sure there's someone
AFK ah an if you leave okay okay
okay oh finally
oh okay where were
we okay and
[Music]
yeah I'm riding after making some golden
apples we went to the Wier fight and I F
it before so I was very confident half
confidence
[Music]
what emote would fit well let's make it
pretty maybe sunglass I don't know if
that will work
[Music]
in in the diary
oh it
works okay
[Music]
nice okay have confidence oh I look so
cool I look so cool
[Music]
for
foree k
[Music]
okay well uh it was too easy so the god
spawned three more in the middle of the
village
yit uh but we somehow still managed to
uh protect the village safely wait I
want to put a thumbs
[Music]
up
here I'm realizing all the things you
can do let's go and then I road while
all of the all of the cows died and
everybody was sad about it even though
right next to it all the chickens died
as well and nobody even notices it eh
crying face
[Music]
pick what wait wait I want to put one
more comment
[Music]
uh I'm writing like in all of the chaos
today in the in that like free wither
spawn
situation it was not
really it was not really a situation
where I could have become her meat
Shield after all
okay
okay ah my copy P didn't work no my copy
paste didn't work what why
not no is it because there's too much
written here wait a second okay
M let me add this
[Music]
here and let me put this
here okay and then iate this so it's
threeee pages
and today I logged in uh in the in the
noon time and uh uh for me noon at least
and worked on putting the neite onto my
armor Sparkle Sparkle and I Enchanted it
a lot and then I became a sparkling
night
Hing and the white quartz on my trims
made me look even more elegant
wow and then I prepared some um golden
apples and went into the wiow fight and
but I fought it before so I was very
confident have
confidence it was so easy that the God
decided to spawn three more in the
middle of the village y h in all of that
chaos I I wasn't able to even be think
about becoming her meat Shield P
senpai's Meat
Shield but we were able to protect the
village
properly from up and all of the cows
died and everybody was sad about it but
the chickens next to it that were also
all dead were completely unnoticed what
the
[\h__\h] so and then after that we went in a
group to the nether to get the ender
pearls and and whatever else and that
was also easy
maybe maybe my never right is a little
bit
Overkill is this
comment I'll do my best tomorrow
[Music]
K the
end nice Flex I became
overpowered but I think yeah a few of us
being in never right uh has obviously uh
motivated AKA Senpai and P Senpai to be
in never ride by tomorrow as well I
wonder if they need the
template if they need
it I can give it to
[Music]
them some of
this you're sure
they got template from Ka oh okay okay
[Music]
okay
okay time to go I guess I did the
mission book I did the
[Music]
diary good stream y
very
successful very exciting with the wiow
fight I hope ena's house did not take
too much damage but it doesn't matter
actually it looks pretty fine from
here doesn't matter though but ol's
house is ol's house okay I just want to
check for a moment she got a she got an
award for her house you know
[Music]
it was the award-winning house after
all maybe I should use
Stone well
XP yeah I'm bringing some
blocks it was first place yeah that's
what I'm
saying first place needs to be protected
I almost thought they were running
around that area on purpose but I guess
you know mostly the argro was on her
doing that right and then she was just
trying to get away from it but damn did
she have to run around all the houses
there she
it's a bit different but it's
fine okay
[Music]
this feels good this is so satisfying to
fix this up I
know you guys feel the same way actually
we oh we need to stop this
here there we
go and
then like
this it would be a bit more satisfying
playing it the match wow well this is
afterward times that we're talking about
we cannot be picky about
it let's fix the leak over
here and did that work
yeah like this maybe or can I still got
proof oh oh it where oh here
what what oh wait it's starting there
isn't it there we
go I'm running out of
blocks oh my God look at this
[Music]
no wait her house though was
actually wait what a close call look at
that and then
the house itself is actually
[Music]
fine aena fixed it
ah I'm trying Ollie I'm
trying I want to make this look nicer
again
right I want to bring some more
blocks didn't I no never mind I have to
stop I have to stop this is my intrusive
faults I have to
go I was going to go but okay I fixed a
little bit more yeah this oh
wa this path is also walkable
[Music]
again nice
nice fixed of course it's
fixed beautiful I stopped a lot of the
water leaks
okay that's really all it
needed the eggs maybe I'll spread the
eggs tomorrow eggs eggs
eggs look
[Music]
X
xeg wow I can't believe it's ending
tomorrow so sad
but it will be worth it in the end for
the Memories I'm happy I'm being part of
this
I'll do my best tomorrow this white
knight will show up with her full power
and protect everybody from the
dragon together with everybody's power
as well we're also strong many many
strong Knights together we're an
army an army of
justice and in German we say I'll be us
in Super Chat reading hope tomorrow
sorry my hello fresh box didn't get
delivered those little shits stole my
food I stole my food I have to buy
something I don't know what can you guys
send me ideas
so no I might just like buy some like
pisto sauce I don't [\h__\h]
know this is my problem when I'm when I
buy groceries without you know like I I
don't know what to do what to cook
hellofresh shows me the the
the the
recipes wait I wanted to make curry with
the curry paste from
Thailand I'll make curry I'll buy Curry
ingredients all
righty I need chicken
meat chicken meat bell peppers like
that's the way we make curry that's the
way my mom makes Thai curry yeah bell
peppers Maybe maybe the Tuukka shorten
the the the crunchy
beans
M maybe some corn
even do you keep the recipes yeah I have
them there's so many I have like big
stacks and then I bought folders for
them there's so many I have insane
amounts of them I I'll eventually be
able to just like look at the recipes
and see what I need to buy from them and
then just I can already do that honestly
I have probably like 400
recipes yeah just need to organize them
properly they're in some folders but I
don't know the system is kind of
weird oh well okay see you
tomorrow uh probably going to start
according to schedule if not even a bit
later we'll see we'll see we'll see I'll
see first what uh the plan is if we
start at 10: p.m. again
uh fighting the Ender Dragon yeah I
think I'll probably go by
schedule a bye-bye in have a nice day
bye-bye Al go M Curry
[Music]