[Music]
hey guys
hi yo welcome back
to takamori playing it's takes two
yeah finally we get to play it again i
was i was worried we were gonna forget
the story but actually i remember all of
it yeah i also remember the story but i
wonder if i remember the controls
yeah that's the main problem isn't it
it's always those those darn controls
yeah i'll tell you what but yeah we're
going to be fine
probably
you're not really saying that with a lot
of confidence it's okay we'll we'll
figure it out we always do
yeah we're pretty good at this game i
would say i say that but i'll regret
saying that in a moment i bet it'll get
much harder for us and today we're
actually playing in casual
yes way more comfortable way more comfy
my first regular stream in the casual
outfit yay
i'm happy to see you like that with the
ponytail it's super cute
thank you it's it's fun to to whip it
back and forth
we can we can talk a little bit about
the outfits uh today i guess
uh while going to therapy
and talking to the book of love or
whatever that was
oh not again please
everyone is the audio is the audio of
kelly fine guys
you guys hear her well just one thing i
think is
uh that um the audio of the game is like
super quiet now but i
can't adjust it uh on this screen right
now i'll probably
adjust it while i'm inside the game
audio is good yeah you can do it in game
okay it's fine okay okay then
i guess we shall continue guys and uh
if i hope you guys didn't miss out on
the first part we did that on kelly's
channel if you missed out which i don't
think you did but if you did
then maybe watch it after today after
this stream
uh what's the first part and uh yeah
we're probably gonna play like
two to three hours let's have a fun time
and let's do it let's go i think you
need to
start the game okay yeah i'm taking off
my hat for this one actually
we can we can change
i can but i don't want to yeah you know
you don't have to i mean i mean in the
in the game we could
we could change characters now oh we can
if we wanted to yeah i mean
i personally i think that i think that
the
the um the mom character um
her personality is a bit closer to mine
but i've just grown so endeared to dad
yeah yeah i think we're i'm fine like
this
okay what did that did that
yeah is that yeah now it's maybe still a
bit too quiet isn't it
guys do you think
what you think what you think you hear
that guys
hey what'd you think what'd you think
the beach i mean it's just a quiet
decent pgm right now but
tiny game audio is fine and low i'm
still low
yeah okay one second let me try and like
i'm gonna do this if you can add a gain
on it um in obs
gotta give him a pointer but the thing
is right now i have
like i have like you and the game both
in desktop audio
but wait i'll just i'll just make you
more quiet and then lower everything on
desktop here again
can you speak again
hey hey hey hey hey hey mike check one
sue one sue hey hey
okay i think now you're loud enough and
uh what about the game bg i'm still too
quiet i feel like it's a little bit too
quiet
[Music]
is it better you guys hear that game's
still quite okay okay a bit more maybe
i'll lower you a bit more uh get that a
bit higher
and then do this
speak again please check one two three
unique new
york new york's unique you know you need
unique new york yes
red leather yellow leather um oh tongue
twister
theater tents okay i think now it's a
good balance
sick um obs it looks
okay sick bars
audiences you guys like my not freestyle
the the game btm you hear it decently
right okay let's go
perfect so how does this work again okay
ground pounds of that
okay that's uh nothing that's that
okay
fps oh really as in outer space
let's not discuss that again just saying
wait let me let me see an obs maybe it's
because
my resolution
don't worry guys it's fine i'll scream
into the mic oh
turn on v-sync
[Music]
it's always the thing with v-sync some
people always tell me to turn it off
some tell me to turn it on ah but i see
it
yeah dude let me see options
um queens don't scream you got it boss
it's not planning to it was it was a
joke
maybe what
they say that i'm just a bit low i'm
sorry you got to deal with this
sorry really yeah i know how this
is when oh it's too loud and then oh
it's too low
it can't be helped okay well i made it a
bit higher okay okay so uh
let me see can i do this in here i there
is no v ah no there it is
so it's on guys should i turn it off
you guys always tell me to do the thing
that it is not
let's just see what the difference is oh
it might be better right now i feel like
it's better
only watching when it will be on screen
i'm watching on stream and it it seems
it's like a little choppy but it still
seems better
i think um changing the fps let me see
if i can do it actually
options i can find it and then i'll i'll
tell you where so when
you can go to the display graph i think
we have different settings
yes maybe we might let me see
i don't even wait frame rate unlocked
what does unlock to do though
the game itself is fine it's just on the
stream
where it looks kind of choppy yeah
true yeah it looks better on my screen
leave it unlocked make it 60
try 60
i mean i mean it doesn't look horrible
on the stream it looks good enough
yeah we just roll with it smooth now
okay okay let's roll
nice really whoa baby
nice okay i'm down i like this one
oh sweet check it out it is haze boys
boys what's that do you know that um
so it's like i think it's um it's
referencing like a game boy
lob grenades that may are too
okay okay probably okay
oh wait is that me is that like near
automata hacking
[Music]
hey look wasn't my
you got me there got one
no you got one
the master of destruction oh master
destruction is me oh
no i'm in trouble no
you got me what a nice game i'm gonna do
it again it's bad
yeah i'll play another time
don't stop saying things like that not
you winning okay okay yeah i didn't say
anything anyway
i'm just making sure i don't want to
hurt your feelings oh no problem
you could never do that
why you're not shooting huh you're being
careful no
i'm just playing strategically
[Music]
you're really quite good at that one
yeah
okay all right if you don't want to do
it again we can continue i guess
sure where to
next what's this oh and it's when you
call those things that you can buy them
on amazon
yeah and then have a really like nice
sleepy dreamy night
yeah it like projects stars on your
walls and stuff there's like really
cheap ones which are really bad and then
there's some really nice ones too
yeah yeah i noticed that i bought a
really cheap one a long time ago and it
made me never want to buy one again
i could get another one disappointing
but i sound like in
i feel like in tokyo i saw that there's
like a show
flashlight on um where they have that a
planetarium
style thing like a huge cinema um
in like huge dimensions like that's
that's worth going to i think
well yeah that was cool that was like a
piece of art kind of thing yeah
oh what's there oh yeah what the [\h__\h]
where's that reference to a way out
oh my gosh it's our it's our boys
no freaking way it's so cool that they
include that
lines where are the boys did i go too
far yeah you're somewhere else you're
too fired
i want to see the boys my favorite up
here
i'm coming let me see the boys
that's so cool
you think you're gonna get away with
what you did to me come on leo
you're still pissed about that just drop
it already
are you crazy i'll never drop it you
just wait and see
oh yeah oh my gosh is this because i is
this because i i i oh my gosh
is it able to sense that we played this
game before and it
took the ending yeah maybe
i see him i i can see how they would do
that because
i bet yeah that that would be really the
same
[\h__\h] i'm i'm bugged [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i can't
get out of here
i can't stop running eva no no
yeah account integration i thought so
too because we used the same uh account
to play i can't get it
i'm not even running i'm not pressed and
like even if i press buttons
oh no come on i'm gonna try and break
you out oh
oh gosh oh are you stuck too oh
i'm not stuck i'm just desperately
trying to get you out yeah i'm i'm done
with
i'm done with oh can we like restart
like somehow
i wonder we start from next point oh man
i didn't get the fire anyway
we couldn't find a way out wait i can't
move it
huh i can't move at all though oh
wait no mike yeah you're completely well
let me try off keyboard
[Music]
we need to exit the oh oh with the
keyboard i can move
oh no no no no no now my thingy my
controller works as well okay must have
been some kind of bug or something yeah
what was that
i wonder enough
what pun did you say i said you couldn't
find a way out
oh that's
appreciate it i stole it from hey do you
prefer
doing it doing playing this game with
lights out or like sun
what's the difference i i i don't know
do you prefer
seeing everything clearly or do you
maybe not want me to see you that well
i mean i can do either oh okay
i like i like dark um yeah me too me too
let me let me turn them off i'm just a
bit yeah you know me i don't really like
the sun very much chiara so you know
what my answer is but
you don't you don't you don't like the
sun very much
no i i've said that many many times my
dog
i started my debut actually i don't like
the sun
but what about me though well you're
like
you're fire though and you're my friend
so wasn't that
like the the sun tarot card down in you
yeah but that's that's
a tarot card that's not like the song
okay okay you know that's not like the
the
the star in this guy okay you know yeah
just a little different rose is on the
other side
the gate is don't be sad stop getting
stop getting sad
a video game i collect it
yeah i i get it because it's a different
thing i mean i i might
be similar to the sun but i am not the
sun but but but but
but but i give you light and and and a
good good kind of light
not not the sunlight i mean i know that
can't be a bit too hot you know
[\h__\h] the sun yeah my oh my hope yeah it
sounds really annoying especially during
japanese summer
huh game another game is this gonna be
just gonna be the mini game collab i
wonder i like it
it's not complaining oh wordplay lovely
it's got something to do with capturing
ride over
override i think it's meant to say
override in some way over
because clearly it spells override
oh we have to connect it here oh wow
this is a little game oh that's cool we
have to connect
okay so this is
horns i don't know would it be this
angry one or would it be this little
smiley one
or uh wait i don't get that
we want to give him a smile snowman oh
oh okay
oh wait we have to press the button yeah
what's happening wait was that actually
not a minigame but like a
i think that was a puzzle yeah where are
we going
we've been abducted aliens exist
conspiracy theory on youtube
oh my god oh my gosh my name
traitor space museum
nice who's had picked me at the space
museum
and commissioned me for a special
mission
i am the only one who can protect rose
from the
dark side of the universe is this like a
buzz lightyear situation where moon
baboon thinks that he's like the real
surreal mvp of space but he doesn't
realize he's like
a dollar
there's been a misunderstanding that's
what you called on animals you need uh
to get a few teeth yeah
you won't squeeze a single teardrop from
rose
you'll be stuck here forever no it's not
kanata senpai this is a baboon
get it right are you saying that kind of
this is a gorilla and not a baboon
ever
that's right everyone knows that i'm
stupid but audrey everyone knows that of
course
where are we listen rose and i have
played with her space toys so many times
i just need to find them
oh here they are
oh buzz lightyear
but i don't know what it is in english
it works oh is it
is it um you mean the the buzz lightyear
to infinity and beyond to infinity and
beyond
big strikes from pixar on us do you want
to get out of here i love
toy story and we need to use cosmic
inflation and oh my gosh
are they making each other oh my gosh
defying the laws of gravity
oh oh
well that's kind of cool wow mom is cool
hey i've got some new shoes on
yeah everything is feeling everything is
going to find a way out here
so you can get bigger and smaller and
i'm
with the boots yeah yeah and you paid
for i got your voice
and the voice changes too [\h__\h] again
dead
you would be if someone threatened to
hurt rose yeah well we're not
hurting rose i mean we just need her
tears so she can have her parents
breathe
did you ever watch like part of my sims
4 stream
a little bit i tuned in for a little bit
okay because like do you have a problem
with
what voice i gave you in sims oh my god
people have been complaining but other
people have been very happy
i gave you kind of a low voice which i
think it should be low but
but people say it's too cursed
to infinity i mean ma
i was fine with it but wait i think it's
because
i couldn't voice myself yeah that would
be good ah wait i can only walk up here
i only own specific
ah okay okay it always needs to
some row some path to get to the other
side and then i can walk around there
normally
and you're down okay where are you i'm
down here i'm just trying to look for
something to do like if i change to a
different size
oh maybe i can access something yeah i
have to help
but i have to do something here i think
and i'm moving something did you see
something move
can you figure that portal yeah let me
try
nope there we go i mean that's that's
how that went well i guess you're not a
phoenix huh fire hurts you indeed
nope hey you want to get down here and
try to do that yourself yes
wait oh wait wait we're around there we
go
i'll show you how it's done all right
show me
i'll show you
there you go how you doing ladies and
gentlemen how it is done
but i revive okay at least i arrived
like a fiend because i mean
i believe you my dog what is that
connected to then because i pulled
something down
you did i didn't see anything i wonder
was it this little oh
hold on hang on i might
i might know what to do
oh wow you're getting really like
acrobatic over there
yeah the umbrella i wonder what came to
maybe was it this
see um i the way that i'm standing on
this makes me feel like i'm not supposed
to do this in the game
um i'm just running out of options man
what oh wait i'm hanging there i see
myself on your side
oh you're upside down yeah
so you can do things upside down um
i'm wondering what you pulled they say
go for the door while being small
oh yeah there's a little little little
slit
slits down there oh i had no idea that
that was there
using the big word yeah
i thought my idea was so good i was like
look at me doing
acrobatics all right let's see what we
got here
i think it's a ground pound
i guess i got to get big big yo
i'm on your side again you're so big
can you carry me uh no thank you
i mean you can try that
[Music]
my ground pounds are especially powerful
now
we have liftoff
exploded on me is that a mini game big
brother i wonder
let me get smaller itty-bitty
again no battery battery let me fix the
battery
okay here we go yay
fix the robot oh
we're technicians now yeah it would
appear so
whoa what's going on all i did was push
the battery into place but i felt good
to do
let's ride it oh yeah
[Music]
yeah that's right the ss it's a rocket
yeah the watson rocky
i want to try that in real life
he really needs to take a chill pill or
a snickers
look at this day stuff like that dad
please
oh my god what was that was that this
nuclear fusion
can i break more cameras i like doing it
let's see which portal now
oh let's try things
wow
that's fun now that was one hell of a
ride
all right it's time to do the tarzan
thank you
crash band oh i'm still alive what oh
this doesn't lead
i wonder if we need to jump off at some
point oh [\h__\h] this stuff again okay
you were a lot better than me at this
game stuff
this road but this doesn't lean anywhere
huh
yeah you gotta jump on planets and stuff
oh oh i didn't know you could do that
um they look like chocolate you know
that planet chocolate
yeah oh man
[Music]
oh there's a donut over there let me
jump into it
oh no that's good ass swimming support
thingies
floaties yes yeah girls floaties
oh speaking of good ass floaties
[Music]
a lot of people are already in the
waiting room i i saw since like
yesterday yeah
what happens waiting forever
yeah so exciting
it's gonna be at 2 00 a.m in the night
for me
but i think i'll still be watching yeah
[Music]
because 2 a.m days normal time for me to
be awake
yeah you want to lift that oh oh cute
yeah do it as big boy
yeah yeah i guess you could call it that
big daddy oh yes
oh okay all right i'm gonna now i'm
gonna stop doing it in that way
[Music]
aiming straight for your face
come here oh [\h__\h]
i was just describing what was happening
on the screen okay
you want to catch me callie no what are
you talking about i said nothing weird
[Laughter]
now i wonder although maybe i should get
small i'm i'm trying to figure out what
i actually need to do here
because obviously i can't really do
anything with those i can't move them
unfortunately so slow
oh my god but even i feel like yeah you
feel slow but when i'm running next to
you i'm the same speed
yeah that's true
[Music]
i'm asleep i'm gonna keep slapping it
slap it again
yes slap it am i supposed to
oh maybe i have to get
[Music]
maybe you hop onto this one this big one
and then with the
the big one we slap to ah
i was not ready for that jump
it's all good oh there's your back smart
they're so cute they look like marbles
and chocolates
yeah i want to go to a candy shop oh i'm
still on it okay okay
maybe maybe if we slap it ready it will
go like
further uh it actually slows down before
i can slap it again
oh okay try be on the edge try to get on
the edge of it okay
okay i'm gonna do it again here we go
perfect so sorry i always get too
excited
you're fine thank you it is okay because
i know i don't mean i don't mean that
one i mean the when you
press the the moving button the joystick
oh then you can run faster okay
one more one more okay ready next one
more yep
here we go okay
okay ready here i go
i don't need to go close up no problem
no
we got this take two because it takes
a shot
oh there's a robot here we can climb but
i guess i probably need you for that one
again
i'll just move it now and then i'll look
down here
[Music]
oh oh what do we have here buttons
good ah maybe i have to make a
path for you yeah what is happening down
there when i do that let me sleep
oh the drawers are popping out oh
and i pop out that one we're getting the
hang of this
and this one and you're almost done
there you go very good nice job
[Music]
there's a robot up here i'm gonna go fix
it yeah i already pushed
the the button that i needed to push
okay
let me get it yeah you have to go inside
again yeah itty-bitty yeah
[Music]
all right employing my master technician
uh abilities
teamwork push the recording battery back
in
and we're done mm-hmm on it
huh i mean cancel pulling do i have to
hold it
oh push it i guess all right press y
oh hi we go
yay
we're back we're back that was nice very
convenient you'll go into another one
i bet it'll take us some respect
one portal down two to go just kidding
okay
we completed
[Music]
yeah the one with the the space slug on
it cute
that looks a little bit like a shrimp
yeah
oh oh those are
space shrimps shrimps space shrimps
isn't that shrimps maybe like a little
sea monkey
like a space sea monkey oh do we have to
run over those
uh like balance on those balls
what you're cute again
did you really have to get that huge i
didn't
pay the price oh you you uh
you were spelling maybe on the other
side oh my gosh
[Music]
i'm gonna wait for you because clearly i
have to push this one again
thank you for waiting yeah
come back to me there we go okay
cause i'm so small i have to run way
more than you when you're big
that is true getting that leg workout
to fit into my to fit into my new hot
pants where i can't even close the
button did you see that my pocket is
open
yeah i saw that i really feel like maybe
you should have picked ones that like
fit in that case but you do you well i
mean no there was no other size okay
papa got my nose pants
hop on top of the screen hooky papa
needs
[Music]
this button up here see this button so i
need you to get on top of this ball and
i'll roll it
on the on the ball on this ball like you
can bounce on these little things right
here
oh okay get on this ball and i'll push
it
okay jump there we go
okay now be careful cause it's gonna
roll
right now we're going over the button
oh it's all right just just just
remember no need for panic
also kelly yeah did you notice um
did you perhaps use me really quick did
i notice what
did you notice that i um
got cat ears
yeah i mean i i definitely noticed you
said before that
you kind of heard one of the cats so i
turned into a camera
i want i want a a cat not a not a
phoenix cat
but am i not good enough for you
i did this for you do you want me to
answer that seriously
yes um
[Music]
i don't think i want to answer that
seriously
i don't want to hurt your feelings i
think
i think that you should want the cat
ears for you i mean do you like cats
don't you yeah i wanted them for me too
but i also wanted them to
just because you said you wanted to get
a cat so i was like okay i'm going to
become the cat
big bro i think it's very cute kiara i
think it's very cute but i'm not going
to make you my pet
i just won't do it
no hard feelings i won't make you much
it doesn't have to be like permanent bet
maybe sometimes when you feel like it we
can
act as if hi
but feel free to be as much of a cat as
as you feel like but i will not be your
owner
okay meow have fun i
like to have fun do you at least think i
look cute as
a cat meow yeah i think it's a cute look
hey cats are cute you know day i day i
i do love me a cat i'll be your cat
anytime you can pet me do you want to
touch my ears
you can be a cat maybe like a stray cat
that lives in my neighborhood and like i
see sometimes and i i give like
i give like food occasionally um like
little like
lunch meat pieces like ham slices and
whatnot if you're cool with that
yeah oh i mean if you're hungry you're a
hungry looking stray cat i mean yeah i'm
gonna feed you
i'm not i'm not that hard where the hell
am i
i need you to let me to the other side
i i don't know where i'm at right now
i'm going to kill myself
[Music]
no i guess that's fine uh no that's not
fun uh
yeah [\h__\h] it's bumpy all the way back
over here
yeah it's okay uh we're just gonna go
back to the floaties okay
[Music]
wait and hear me out there i have to i
have to use the one on this side
i have to push it through the gate oh
man okay no no here's one floaty over
here you don't have to
go okay excellent
i'll turn it around okay i'm coming back
i'm almost there
sorry for that i was kind of lost oh
you're good
it's fine we were talking about cute
things it's all good
yes yes okay that is a good enough
excuse in my opinion
yes i always want to talk about cats my
life is all about
[Music]
okay i'm back up here but what do i do
here i i turned on that thing but i need
you for that and then there's this thing
that i can do
you need to find a way to let me up
there what about this thing can you use
that
oh nice yeah let me try this ah get on
i guess yeah oh
no how did we get here we need to be
smaller no wait no yeah stay there
now i can move it and then you should
[Music]
oh perfect oh nice okay
excellent oh well done
[Music]
if you offered me a high five now i'd be
able to give it to you without you
having three hands oh
really yeah because we're not holding
game controllers
all right just one portal left high five
let me can i raise my can i only if i
have a mic
well it was a nice dream maybe next time
sorry about that i hate to leave you
hanging killer we're just too far apart
maybe next time
okay maybe next time
maybe in the afternoon
perfect you want to go in there yeah
let's go this green one
let's dig in
sideways that was
[Music]
oh smite the game
i want to point out one smart thing
about the game like when i'm
when i'm down here
i go left right with the stick and then
it turns around
and now i now here at this point it
switches to control so i
turn i don't know it doesn't mean wow do
you guys know
here i get i get what you're saying you
know what you're saying he's pretty dope
yeah i would say that is good smart i
didn't want it to be
inverted that would be very confusing
oh but turn around turn the ship around
oh get small it's fine i might
have nothing next time we avoid the
laser shut up wow
what an idea hey dad said it not me wait
how do i avoid it now
i jump oh jump jump jump
and now okay duck
um i think it's you hold down
oh but i spawn here no no it's easy as
long as one of us is alive i think it's
fine
yeah would probably be useful though if
i remember how to dunk on it
[Music]
oh
oh there you go
[Music]
oh you can't move that one oh no i can't
really how about i get smaller
i didn't know i had that power in my ass
whoa okay maybe that's one way to put it
oh
[Music]
there we go noise where are you you're
so tiny i don't even see you
very small cute
like i i always see you as a really
big woman because of your size like i
mean
i mean that sounds weird i mean you're
trying to see you trying to say
something
what are you trying to say
hold on no no let's re-examine what you
just said right there
is that something that you say no no no
that's because
english capabilities i mean i meant
height height height
because i'm joking i'm joking
i understand i
you being so am it's really cute dude
what the hell did we do there
i have no clue
maybe if i'm small if i'm extra small
yeah this seems like it's broken on it
right now as is
it can't move one
do we need it at the same time oh
three two one
yeah it was a little off but we still
managed to do it oh my god
yay this is so magical here
no right i really like this stage hold
it
i think i'm stuck again here maybe i
need to do something to help
um something with this thing here okay
platform i guess
here i need to move this
oh yeah you've got to move it you move
and look
you got the movement are you practicing
i like to move it move it yeah
move it yeah but why are you putting it
back now
maybe i have that but maybe that's right
maybe all the way
as far as you can get down uh-huh
and then maybe i can go over that wall
because here it doesn't really do
anything for me yeah okay
let's try that kiana is having a bad
english day yeah i have a bad english
day every day oh you can't go any
further
no i can't it looks like a spring so
maybe i released it i release it i'm
supposed to release it
but the problem is you got to be careful
because there are lasers at the bottom
okay okay
okay avoid them okay ready yes
i was
that born have been too much i'd say so
well yeah it really hurt me because i
have like uh
i have um since since like yesterday
morning i have a a and um
one of my nerves is like in my spine is
um how do you call it it's
[Music]
it's uh oh it's like it's uh it's
pinched you have a pencil
and when i laugh my spine really hurts
and that was oh
maybe i should just do it a little bit
yeah that was too fast maybe about
halfway is fine ready
yeah oh okay okay okay
the moment you do that i i jump maybe or
all right maybe
here we are ready okay
oh okay nice perfect thank god i didn't
die again
yeah well done okay i'm away i think we
puss it
yeah yeah will's greatest thing is dead
nice oh cute this is cute but it's it's
uh it's mother's day on the weekend we
should have a cup of that too
oh yeah girl's green is mama that's a
good point
it's my world's greatest dad mugs so
relax
won't you buy me another one you broke
it
can you get over here somehow i'll just
maybe side jump well jump
oh good point yeah
and here we go
[Music]
i'll hang on to you
wait was it oh do i need to be bigger i
wonder
let me try oh yeah maybe that's
it no i can't hold it when i'm bigger oh
okay
okay i don't think we're we're right as
close as possible
wait what's up sorry i i i'm always like
wondering if it's the big r button or
the smaller button
it's okay
[Music]
i released it again oh it's okay
we'll do it again i guess we gotta do
this a couple times huh all right oh
oh no that was my bad not bad here we go
okay i'm hanging on to you
whoa gravity oh my god what's going on
oh this is nuts this is bonkers
oh oh okay okay okay can you hang on to
that one too because
it's got two two of those
hey let me see i think you have to yeah
put it
yeah let me put that down let me see if
i can swing
so cute
what no oh my god uh jump i guess all
right now let's get off
oh okay wait which way is that i'm dizzy
what the freaking club
oh my god hey robot we're done i guess
[Music]
okay let's turn this [\h__\h] on
yeah there you go
oh we went through a lot of stuff huh
yeah yeah
nice we did it that should be all the
three portals activated
excellent nice
very well done now let's blow up the
[\h__\h] universe
yeah that sounds like a plan it sounds
like
my dude ah do i
turn the other one around yeah that
might be it hey
[Music]
okay
what's moving though oh
oh i really like being weightless yeah
being in real space this is fun this is
not my idea of fun
okay oh dad come on you were having a
great i'm time
okay throwing up is not fun hey yeah
yeah yeah i mean that's true throwing up
is really nice
we are focusing we're just trying to
find a way out of this damn place
you'll only do that if you collaborate
yeah
[Music]
eyebrows and mustache do not compliment
your color scheme
and make you look really tacky oh
should we just go up all the way up
always aim for the top
[Music]
please come out and let us explain why
do the things we buy try to kill us
it's cute though how he's trying to
protect our daughter
that is pretty adorable i do
i do like that it makes moon baboon a
little bit more of a likable game
hmm i enjoy a likable villain
so what's up here this kind of reminds
me a little bit of this game that i
played in two collabs called
uh foggs it had like i'm supposed to
play that with someone soon actually oh
oh yeah what kind of game is it um
yeah yeah it's like a co-op game where
you're like stuck
you're both dogs and you're like stuck
to one another
and have to solve puzzles like this oh
and there's a level where it's like
pillow forts as well
yeah are they are they hard puzzles
[Music]
not that hard i mean i would say about
about as hard as these ones are oh okay
oh maybe you need to be small for that
one oh i'll turn i need to oh yeah
you're good you're good that's a good
idea
yeah wow it's like amelia nice
personally
yesterday that you guys did yeah i was
sleeping and i wanted to enjoy
i really i wanted you to be there it's
cool though i think it was like
like three or four a.m for me or later
yeah i don't know
i woke up and it was like that's really
great so much
fun oh that's okay we got a collab
coming up soon again
yeah so what are we doing here
look at the question maybe try it maybe
he was big can you ground pound when you
bake
probably not huh yeah i bet i can't oh
you can't
oh i'm probably also gonna fly into
space and explode though
no oh okay i'm fine perfect hold on now
we're bringing it down
oh i can't move that much more though
okay let's see oh can you can you now do
a ground pound on here i
tried to put it generally
while it's down and then oh it didn't
that's weird
i'm too oh i'm this on the paddle on the
paddle where i am
and then you'll get me up there too if
you do that but then you'll be done
yeah ah but we keep we keep doing it in
rotation to get it lower and lower and
lower
ah getting you up and making you bigger
while you're up here
will make it low enough so i can get
back up okay wait so then i jump
down there yeah ground pound
perfect
[Music]
[Applause]
one brain cell plus one brain cell is
five
brain cells oh yeah what you said yep
five of them all five
okay what are we doing here ah hanging
on to those things again okay
oh yeah hey what the [\h__\h] more ropes
swinging
i love the ropes i don't know
earth look see
maybe i go first all right and then oh
if i go
then one appears for you to grab oh it
did it did
okay now what
and the next one the other one's kind of
far away yeah we can do it though
i lost it oh god damn it
i'm still gonna watch these things
because i always i'm not sure if i am
allowed to
let go or i don't know oh yeah it's it's
rough the timing is difficult
and jump okay i'm on it
now next it's my turn okay next one's
for me
that one's far away ooh it's okay now
you can okay
you died at least i'm here and i spawned
here it's
no wait maybe i can't get it it would
have been hilarious no that was probably
oh wait i'm just kidding yeah we did go
all the way back you got to come back
sorry
no okay it was it's okay that was fun i
like the hanging thingy
yeah we're pretty much in sync usually
mostly sometimes the respawn like
oh oh i respond here again i okay i'll
go back this way
sometimes the respawn helps you and
sometimes it just brings you all the way
back where you don't want to be
oh my gosh all right i'm coming oh it's
okay you can you can go back
okay we can both go back all of them are
activated
so we can just go back like this you
didn't have to come back it's all good
homie
thank you though looking out for your
boy no problem
okay i'm doing the doing the moonwalk
yeah
oh [\h__\h] not again no no no
at least we we got a checkpoint
look at the earth though i see it i see
you
amelia over there and good afternoon
yeah oh you see what's it girls in the
ocean
yeah drowning though okay good you stay
alive you have something coming out
today
please
i'm sure a girl will be fine i always
forget that you're the girl i wonder if
she's nervous i was like so nervous for
my reveal it felt like
uh you stream all over again yes
same my heart what is it maybe eighty
percent as nervous as david i was it was
maybe even like i felt like maybe even
more nervous but i don't know maybe it's
because it's
really like a long time ago but i feel
like for both of us there were there are
more people
uh peeking on [\h__\h] our new outfit
streams in our debut
i'm not sure about that from my case
i think it was because i recall you
peaked at like 70 or something like that
and that was more than your debut so i
don't even remember how many i had
at my debut yeah it was kind of a while
ago huh whole seven
months yeah
[Music]
gosh it was so long ago oh we're done
here
all right one second
here we go good question chad the first
one the first one
oh yeah that's right haven't you had
three um
three or four i think that you've broken
the record for
uh a whole live talent with most babies
i think that record goes to you thank
you
i'm proud i'm glad
you should get um a special medal for
that maybe i'll make foreign um
i feel like it fits because i'm a
phoenix and i revive a lot you know
that is true oh my god guys you want to
claim the title
yes all right let's see i mean today i'm
a cat oh i get tired
of the king i don't know you really like
the
okay fine that's payback
for you know that time where you killed
me a million times in that
thing i don't even know what to do
though
maybe i'm supposed to get big let me try
getting bigger
no i can't uh toggle walls
maybe i have to jump so remember before
i get it okay
i toggle the ones like that oh i see you
gotta go over there
okay
[Music]
i realized at the very last moment that
i can toggle that one too
probably yeah yeah
yeah i'm sure victory okay let's go this
is fun i love this
yeah i like this one and go
oh um
you oh
and the last one now it's free
yeah and can you visit home get in the
car kelly come on
cody you're supposed to avoid the
obstacles didn't you naturally
okay was it too small i i thought it was
i thought it was
a bad thing you gotta
get it you gotta aim for the whole cali
okay let's go got it
yup i'm good it's a little late here i'm
fine here there's the hole i see it it's
beautiful
oh my god it was meant to be you
exploded anyway that was the most
painful
pinball i have ever played and what we
have to do
oh dad you sacrificed yourself for the
greatest goods
goods yeah exactly yeah greater good
greater gold
reference to umbrella academy anyone
is that um a show
what oh he's uh he's a musician
no no he wrote the comic oh
what this is fun what the hell it's so
sparkly too
oh you're bringing me over there go back
there and drop me there maybe
we're here no no
you direct me uh uh uh
to that on their other umbrella other um
up up up up up up and then wait oh this
one
okay gotcha yeah okay okay drop me
please
thanks oh i see that's how that works
oh yeah you are a fan of my chemical
romans aren't you
yeah i used to listen well i mean i
used to listen to to them quite a bit um
in the reaper school days and i sing
karaoke a lot
didn't you sing one song and and you're
on i got kind of good too
uh many actually maybe about five
hoping to make it seven that's probably
like comparable to me singing
a lot of paramore songs and ever living
songs
yeah yeah that's true though mcr is just
you know special
it's hard to explain i need to try and
climb up
very early if there's a way that we can
get these
uh to not be on fire yeah yeah i think i
did that once wait let me do it again
uh there we go nice
thank you nice
[Music]
no problem i'm on the water eyes
sorry what oh my god the robot spoke to
me i had to answer
oh but of course all right there you go
you gotta speak to it in its native
language i didn't know that you knew
four languages
i know i know a lot actually i already
that's actually five languages because i
speak
german english japanese but also uh a
bird language so that's already full
oh and now we've rolled it that's fine
i can speak a bunch more too i can speak
cat
yeah you got ah that's
that's a cat sound all right oh yes i'm
your cat
[Music]
well i thought that was already the
second one confused
i didn't know that um that like chickens
and roosters are constantly cursing at
people
until instantly i mean you got pretty
angry before
right when i was and you said why are
you cursing at me right
well that made me realize chickens and
roosters are constantly cursing at
humans then
right
[Music]
and they have normal sweet conversations
with me too
right yes of course but i mean chickens
just like just
regular chickens that aren't yeah stupid
chickens yeah those stupid chickens
they're not they're always cursing yeah
yeah what is this
it's an electric body puzzle oh no oh
no what do we do here here first let's
fix this
let's fix this i can move it
oh just kidding where would i want to
move it though yeah i can
i can also move that too so either one
of us could do that but
the question is oh maybe
oh heavy yeah maybe that's for later
oh yeah that looks like later there's a
small hole for you
yeah i certainly can't get in there but
i get on the other side and then wait
stay there stay down okay now maybe
oh nice yeah very good
okay it's tiny again
so what happens over there
oh here we go
[Music]
where are you going with that rocket
only out there okay
to infinity and beyond meet with ahmed
do you have to jump down
oh here i got this oh that one
now you do i also have to get up there
probably
um should i come down or should i stay
up here do you think maybe can you make
yourself bigger
while holding that i can't hear i can't
but let me put it down and make it
and then hold it and then come down oh
you can't hold it
okay okay it's got to be this size
yeah maybe come down for now okay
oysha but i'm sure there's one up there
too and it's probably made so that
i can get up there because yeah i guess
yeah
you just have to get big now and get on
that side
i'm gonna set this down really quick
okay okay
all right there we go you ready i'm
ready
oh there you go yeah that was the right
thing to do
so probably one has to go over here
close enough
and then one in the middle somewhere and
we can probably move them a bit more
to like here maybe and that one a
bit further i think they don't connect
here
but maybe oh [\h__\h]
let's make like a circuit i guess okay i
see so maybe it just needs to be a bit
closer
close as we can get it to be try and
pull that as far as you can maybe
yeah here here is another one
there okay then just leave that one
there
there is maximum
yeah that's maximum hey that's not
enough maybe there's more
yeah there must be more what's so like
we haven't gone over there over here
that's something for me to walk on oh oh
god i'm getting dizzy i
want some food i'm hungry and there's
one over here
hey do you need my assistance to get in
there
probably yeah all right there's no
opening here
i'm on the way oh you can do something
on your side nice
nice get mom some cat
yeah can we poof please feed me huh
food i mean i don't have any on me right
now what kind of food do you want
anything is fine bacon bacon bacon
okay i mean i'll fry some up a little
bit kind of in the middle of something
but yeah you
you got it that's great that is not my
cat but it's still cute
okay oh wait i forgot my chance to say
milk please
god damn it yeah i was i was dreading
you saying that well
missed opportunity yeah you know
we were welcome but my brain wasn't
because i'm actually hungry i was
thinking about actual food
yeah but did you do anything on your
side because i still can't get it
oh there we go i'm about to
[Laughter]
[Music]
that rocket does nothing yep it does
nothing but i just felt like taking out
some
okay you've got one but i still don't
know how to get in here
maybe i can't get in here until
no i'll help you oh you're down there i
actually can't go wait
maybe i can ground this
thank you you're welcome
i knew i knew all i needed was you
yeah yeah no problem got your bag
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm bringing the last one over or is it
the last one
i don't think so these these are kind of
acting up maybe one more
okay i got it
nice on kelly where did you get that one
from didn't even round
over here there's like a weird puzzle
going on okay place it here please
okay don't die what the hell
what what oh i told you not to die
listen i'm trying to figure out how to
get back oh we'll figure it out
go callie go count me i'm your
cheerleader
oh i was so close go callie cool kelly
okay cody you can do this yeah dad you
got this
go go go count no problem go kelly yeah
we did it
when did you pass me
what happens oh we can activate the
ribbon
there we go
perfect smile
yes sorry that's super noisy i know
i mean it sounds kind of it doesn't even
really sound like a typical robot but
maybe it's like a colloquial thing like
maybe it's just an accent like a
specific type of robot yeah yeah yeah
that's definitely what that is a nice
nice robot accent
good job
uh guys i guess you guys don't watch
lucy lucia senpai huh
oh i'm sure there are some fans yeah
some people are used to it
the last one or only origin is also one
of those people
who makes your ears bleed who
uh only only oh yes that's uh yeah
lucille oh yeah if you if you
hate your ears and you want to get rid
of them watch all your
odyssey and if you're feeling really
really ballsy do the same time
oh my god they're ever streaming at the
same time golden opportunity the day
when they collab will be legendary
offenses defenses
probably we can handle it i'm not sure
if i want that to happen i wouldn't i
probably
i i treasure my ears too much especially
my new cat ears
yeah it sounds funny to laugh about
right now but definitely not it's like
one of those things that sounds fun to
laugh about but you wouldn't
really want it yeah unless you're crazy
we don't shame here to each their own
yeah no problem no you don't you
if you hate your ears okay yeah who am i
to tell you
to love your cute girls more important
than ears
i can kind of see it all right battery
activate
i think it might might be on it
can i do something with that why does it
say the battery isn't
cause it's definitely in there um maybe
maybe something else first cause there's
maybe
something else okay
[Music]
eh
ah
okay now let's connect this to there and
then
oh okay good yeah but then you keep
pushing that one one more
okay so it's connected now wait oh this
one but then that way
that one stops being connected um so i
have to turn it around again
you can okay i get it come over to the
other one
because when you stand on it that one
stops turning okay
and now i move move the that one yeah
and now it's connected there
we go nice nice observation
hello there's no i in teamwork no mom
that actually was pr
no problem i mean no dad that was kiara
figuring that one out
oh i see the current isn't making it
through
that brain your cats are smart actually
smarter than you yeah
they ain't very smart but also they have
very stupid moments too
especially my cats that is awesome
it does depend on overall happiness of
our child
she's very sad right now it started out
happy it went
all the way down i don't like this
analytics
that's sad okay so uh this is creepy
yeah moomba boom kinda knows too much
i'm i'm feeling a little creeped out
tracking her well-being yeah yeah still
super creepy yeah i'm kind of dead
i mean i know they're they're friends
and all that and you know baboon
you know she stopped laughing right i
mean she
she laughs at least a few times every
day but it's not enough anymore i've
been
arguing a lot recently yeah okay
but what about her uh her worry huh
oh what no that can't be right
it's critical sorry are you two really
that dumb
okay that sounds harsh i'm gonna reel it
back for a second like
you guys hold on let's let's take it
back both mom and dad
you guys remember what happened
[Music]
i mean yeah they aren't people connect
the dots
they're a little dense you can probably
connect with dogs
traitors what did you tell your child
before this happened
all right battle time can i just
beat down the ship like this
how do we can't get very fast maybe we
should try dashing i feel like we
weren't quite dashing
very much
[Music]
go oh the hole over there is that a hole
is that it why is this happening to me
as long as i'm up here it's up it's like
up here
can you get in there
[Music]
okay
nice oh my gosh yeah well done
nice thinking okay oh not great
oh jumping ropey
[Music]
oh wait get over there it's that one
i'll push it there we go
get behind it oh necessarily no yay
and jump
[Music]
oh my god is he aiming for me
specifically
i think that he changes who he likes
just keep running just keep running
kiara i probably
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
there we go okay
all right let's go beat him up okay oh
my god let's go beat up confusing
hey
oh that was very close to your uh
yeah yeah i was gonna say that felt
strange
[Music]
i'm back uh what are we doing
i can jump on them yeah we jump on them
to make them explode
maybe we gotta do it near him
we gotta do something with the rockets
because they kind of
oh oh oh
i can't oh nice you can ride it okay
let's try that then
i i did ride it but i guess i'm not oh
my god
i'm not i'm not good with that mm-hmm
yeah you're better with that maybe not
oh it's inverted i see i see
i see i see it controlled
the controls are inverted so basically
that means if you want to go up
hold pull down oh we don't start from
the beginning okay
[Music]
oh there we go okay we got both of them
there we go
where do we go we gotta explode into him
right okay okay yeah the controls are a
little a little funky
[Music]
oh
nice good job oh yeah okay
we both get did we both ride i don't
know if we both can't actually
oh [\h__\h] it's all right
was one following me while i was writing
it oh [\h__\h] i
just woke up
okay
good send some more rockets
coward yeah coward haha
you're a big coward
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that how you greet you
customized
stupid monkey yeah he's not very nice
not really
i just wake up and you explode me
give me some time to wake up
[Music]
for people who think we're drunk these
are in vertical controls okay
these are inverted it's fine
it's fine they just don't understand oh
what's he doing now i'm hockey anymore
are you
cody you must finish this
oh i get big
oh [\h__\h] what the hell hey moon baboon
and you're taking up with a monkey
you're right you guys love it very
all right you got this am i just
supposed to like run away from me while
i'm
supposed to do something and and i'm
supposed to like give you time right
yup just buy time for it okay how much
does it cost
um great i'm totally
[Music]
he's getting rather warm up here
i'm almost there i'm almost there oh my
god
okay spend some time here
power
hey i found something i think we can use
it
don't touch anything you shouldn't yeah
just trust me
keep him in sight
oh
a couple more shots should do it yeah go
get him he's over there
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] nice one nice one
i'm all for beating up boom baboom but i
really don't want to hurt the dude
yeah he's been like a good friend to to
the little one yeah
oh remember how do we get back to rose
i can't let you harm her we're not
trying too hard come on
hello she hasn't played with you for
years
oh okay you've been monitoring her come
on just pay attention
happy we can help you become friends
again we're telling him to pay attention
we need to pay attention
yes i can ask rose to play with you
again
but you have to help us get back to her
he's so cute two rows
that whatever happens i'll always be her
best friends
look she's over there oh clarence
claire oh rosie's your name is her name
is rose ocean
oh my god it's mom and dad
rose we need your help
look oh she literally doesn't see us
she she can't see us
sweetheart we need to talk
bum bum get in her
she can't even fail us
how can you draw on a bed that's a
really good question chef not
comfortably yeah it's probably gonna
make holes into the paper
that's smart mom is smart
[Music]
maybe if she drops a pen we can take the
pen and we can draw something on the
paper
did you see that huh we can write a
message
stuff around yeah get her attention yes
that's perfect right let's
let's destroy something rose loves to
make her cry
what oh my god mom no
just take that freaking pen and write
something down
don't make her cry like that make rose
cry
no just write something down oh my god
it would be so easy
great idea no dude you guys are so
dumb you guys are idiots why are they so
stupid
no offense why are you so stupid
well at least i didn't buy her a crazy
space monkey that nearly got us killed
oh check your clay face
my nose is itching oh that's the yeah i
feel that
we must remember to clean under her bed
hydration check everyone
yeah noted
all right uh can i ask the chat do you
guys know
how far in we are now
like do you have an estimate of how many
more hours it would take
should we stop it here because it would
be good to stop here but
we can also continue
[Music]
okay let's do one more than i guess okay
she has so many toys yeah yeah exactly
one less would be a good thing whoo
really loves that elephant though
you have to buy a replacement yeah yeah
maybe we should have so much fun here
from that point of view
it's time for a new friend
she has
dude who has a whole ball i don't know
why that's awesome jump
into it she did no why not game
please i'm attached to it again i don't
know why
okay destroying my dreams
hey check this out oh i can make a
bridge
oh i can make a quick block stick
what's over there let's see
how do i get over there
[Music]
oh there's a fireball here
hi if he dies at the same time
brought five up and it goes away
oh
[Music]
what'd you find nothing
oh that's how you run i can't believe
we've got how to run
i love that
these fives do that again maybe yeah yep
yes mate it's the last time you were in
a bar
oh that was the time rose pushed me in
you should jump in
it would be fun yeah you should go for
it
oh wait how do you [\h__\h]
grab on i forgot how to do that oh no
wait wait wait how can we grab on again
uh just just uh run into it just hold on
to it
just kidding that was a lie uh jump into
it and press maybe the
jump button again or square
or circle try try all of them
[Music]
oh it's not square it's not circle it
must be it is square
i just did it right now okay what oh
maybe that's another surface i can hold
on to
oh yeah that's probably it we need to
maybe flip them all right let me see
what i can do
[Music]
let us pick up there we
okay
okay i'm on it you ready you ready and
go okay nice all right next
and go [\h__\h] and
nice you see something coming up thank
you
four blocks
how did you do that kelly are you drunk
no i wasn't paying attention again
i was like i was peeking at bread it's
like a little hole like do we have
mice in this
looks like casper made it i mean with
how irresponsible these two have been
i'm sure that they have a multitude of
issues
i wonder if the mice are in some kind of
grand run
maybe they're friendly and actually help
us in this world
i mean the squirrels didn't want to help
us
yeah they definitely told them
the whole war that's going on where
their alignment is i suppose okay
it goes one two three for turning okay
one
two three
[Music]
why don't i have these skills in super
mario sunshine [\h__\h] okay i messed it up
but
i wish i had those skills in super mario
sunshine
wait wait wait wait wait
no damn it the camera around here
even as i said it i went right towards
it i was on the road before what
happened now
maybe i go to the other one
[Music]
what
no it's always the three i got it have
you ever played super mario sunshine
oh no i have no plans no
try it you would love it
okay so this is the mouse mouse goes
and this goes it has a horse and horse
this is pink it goes oink oink oink
and this
is way better than this yeah i mean
yeah i'd have to oh way more accurate
all right you need to hit
so when you hit the piggy it goes up
okay i need you to stand on the ones
okay
i'll try my best pig i'll call out the
animal to you when i see it
okay melt lion
there's a lion you got a double verse
uh mickey mouse nice i'm looking at your
screen as well uh
jump over to me oh
we had both of those possibilities okay
no problem
okay let's go pig this time okay no no
oh [\h__\h] sorry i was i didn't know you
were ready all right here we go
okay okay next up
mouse okay of course
what i guess i do have to actually be
careful okay
here we go this time this will be it
mouse to show up and horizontally
i'm sorry right
and mouse here we go okay
and horse
okay and now then mouse again and then
we had two choices uh pig okay big go
for pig
that's a big pear that is there that is
a bear they're the same colors
oh nicely done oh there's more
let me can i just do my frog noise for a
moment
my thing is i want to try after you
i'm proud how do you do that
i i um i i
i just become a friend is it a sound
clip is it a soundcloud
no what the hell hang on i don't want to
try hey why are you on there i want to
try to
hey
[Music]
i feel
[Laughter]
i make one of my cheeks puffy or both of
them
and then i i like it's hard to explain
but i
um when they're puffy i like uh-huh
swallow no trying
like
sucking in your puffy cheek
i don't i don't know
holy [\h__\h] i don't i don't know how you
do that i don't know
oh my gosh that is crazy
that is witchcraft someone in the chat
some people in the chat understand how i
did
it now damn frog i'm happy with my
version i'm happy with my remix
okay anyway go be frustrated okay let's
get me into the other side thank you for
trying to give me tips oh [\h__\h] uh i
think it's just a special oh
i think it's just a special technique
that only you can understand yes
because i am zoo after all well next
up is
oh okay uh sheep
no problem go be frog again um
[Music]
i did all of those videos already oh i
need to do live
next huh gotta be lying next and sheep
next and frog again just recently
actually i made a new one
uh uh yeah i'm lying
um
the classic thrilling prequel yeah i was
actually you're thinking prequel
i didn't look cool i did that because i
was moving right and i needed some
content
and then i was thinking i am cat would
be easy because meow was just easy
but then i was like wait i'm getting cat
ears on my debut reveal and
my outfit reveal so i should just wait
until i get my cat ears and then do mcat
so that's coming soon we're all looking
forward to oh
why do i do that why do i do that it's a
review of mcat
okay let's go yeah uh
and dog dog
[Music]
and that's it whoa
yeah nice all right my turn now oh all
those children's
boys are so cute oh wait i only have
cups i'll be the only one
we'll just chill on cow though oh
sorry just stand on the couch for me
okay and here i am
let's see where to next if you're ready
climb in the abacus ah yes oh great
long have i dreamed of scaling its peaks
oh yeah mom is like the smart one i
think the number smart one
yes i am yes i am but people say i'm
bottom left i might be
bottom but i'm not that left okay yeah i
don't think you're very left
thank you i think that was i think
you're about like in the middle-ish
thank you because you're very creative
you like come up with some sick ideas i
wish i could i need you all the way you
can
that ability sometimes huh i need you
i'm i'm trying bounce faster
every time i hit that whoa what was that
that was like a blackout sounds high
i'm trying bounce bounce
daddy's a bit closer i need to try i
need to stop i need to
stop trying to like press the jump
button when i hit the
that like back
i keep thinking that it's going to make
me bounce higher because sometimes that
happens in games yeah
if you jump on something and you press x
when you hit it no
why is this so difficult for me
you gotta let loose focus everybody lose
control
[Music]
yes it makes you lose control use it
make you lose control let's put
what are we doing now oh my god what's
happening
a classroom it looks like
wait why is
[Laughter]
oh no this is this is not a game that
good i should play probably uh
seven yeah but me neither
we can always just do one something plus
one uh okay maybe not six plus
uh
they're two please how about a nine and
a four
wait one yeah i know eight four oh
there's a timer we're at nine nine okay
eight plus one
[Music]
there's a few little prisoners a good
thing zera isn't playing this but
actually we're boned because i'm playing
this
eight nine seven twelve thirteen
fourteen eight
is sixteen okay oh
this is embarrassing yeah it is
wait wait wait wait what what
maybe one person picks a number and then
the other who's better at math okay i'm
gonna be at nine
[Music]
something
not my strong suit what what
should we have looked no it's a matching
game what let's see we played this
before
[Music]
okay what do you mean six what what do
they want from us uh cherries cherries
and cherries okay
okay oh we're not
playing against each other i guess we're
playing yeah with each other
or
you're mixing oranges no okay all right
let's see
banana cherries it only counts down when
we're playing okay
okay oh we need to okay i see yeah we
can't have two uh then
okay okay and then aubergine
aubergine orange
all right so here we go eggplant
oh god do we still have time
okay how should we do this i wonder i
feel like there's like a mess
okay uh we need to not turn him over at
the same time
pierre my turn strawberry
orange okay strawberry blueberry
no wait what's the strawberry the first
one here here here
there we go okay orange
oh dang it it's this one aubergine was
somewhere else
here i know where pear is here good
okay what's yours let's see
anna oh wait you know banana's here
right no that's wrong jeffy here we
[Music]
baby to stick to turns okay you go first
aubergine
banana my turn orange
strawberry okay i was the other one okay
i'll get it next time and now
go ahead there we go okay
pear strawberry cherries
orange ah
jerry jerry ah oh damn it no [\h__\h] my
memory
and banana banana yes
nice okay quick orange do you know where
it went
damn it was it this one it's not a timer
it's how many misses we get i see okay
you go first oh okay
that makes it a lot easier and maybe
here
aubergine okay
strawberry strawberry cherries cherries
here
okay i'll remember my aubergine was here
strawberry strawberry this one right
yeah
okay
okay pear banana must be here yeah
okay oh okay okay okay orange
banana okay banana banana again
[Music]
like a little piece of art at the end
through what's that one two i'm gonna go
to two three is up here
and then four is up here and then five
is down i wonder what we're drawing
what did it
[Music]
you guys see what it is chad can you
recognize it
i don't recognize it yet who gets it
first
uh 19
down down down down
[Music]
this
that is a cat ladies and gentlemen that
is a cat
[Music]
don't tell
thank you thank you for announcing my
catness
you're welcome
[Music]
oh yeah you love the the little mousy
huh
[Music]
wonder what happened i need to put my
mouth down
oh it's supposed to eat come on cheese
where's cheese
you have to leave it through some kind
of maze
oh maybe it's too early for that
oh is that cheese
what the [\h__\h] oh
so alive what
i don't get it
are we supposed to lead the the mouse
through the maze
what the mouse is over there i would
write them down i wonder how we elevate
it maybe we can
both bring it up um but over here it
opened a moment ago but that was
probably you controlling something here
oh
uh we have to move that ball over there
oh that's that's
very difficult
there we go it's okay it i don't think
it has to go it has to go
all the way over there yeah not into
that hole
come on come on come on yeah okay and
chill chill chill
no no no no no no no
yeah yeah down there probably on careful
camp not too fast
oh that's difficult oh yeah that's
pretty rough
okay okay okay weight distribution
weight distribution
all right there we go
see over here yeah
nice and oh we're pretty close to
getting it right straight down you can't
do much more
wrong here and up
the cheese has been captured
[Music]
well done we got another one coming up
oh okay okay all right over here
i was looking at the wrong camera okay
all right let's do it round two uh oh
that one has bigger holes
oh yeah yeah okay
okay that's two extreme
movements happening just staying around
the middle
staying around the middle until times
like this feel it
yeah feel it out all the way to this
wood block should be fine
all right now we need to be careful yeah
in the middle
come with a ball cheese ball come on
[Music]
next this way yes
yeah well that wasn't that difficult
that wasn't too bad because we were so
careful nice one
so now something you activated up there
once
opened up the the cheese hole so if you
do that again
here we go let's get that mouse to
cheese
and then can i have the mouse after it
ate the cheese and gets really
thick can i eat them
told you the mice are friendly
cute oh you won you want the ball huh
you want it you want it you can't have
it you can't have it
wait is it just gonna be like that
that's
torture it's so sad can't we let it
maybe we can let it free oh no i think
it's just over
oh that's a shame um bye bye mouse
you're never gonna get the cheese sad
it's very sad
oh [\h__\h] probably shouldn't have yeah
sorry i just wanted to go where you went
but i have to jump on the other one
no problem
it died you okay yeah did you did you um
i'm frog too many times okay jump
i'm ready
[Music]
how does this work it's like a one two
so i step on one you step on two
um wait i should i'm gonna join you once
two comes up i'll come in okay
okay here we go ah okay we're gonna do
this fast against cool
together
what
[Music]
yes speedy we are speedy
okay we're doing fine
[Music]
what do we have here hold it this way
oh it's so colorful i love it
oh my god very slowly
oh [\h__\h] nope still have time okay
oh
oh you can jump over from that side too
okay
okay i'm just gonna be happy here you
can do this alone too right
it's okay yeah i can go back and do it
actually you don't have to run left
kelly you can just jump over straight if
you do the dash jump
oh really maybe you're saving some time
um i mean uh yeah you did it again but
no no no
actually in the in the very beginning
before you go left
you just go jump straight over to the
yellow platform from there from right
there
yeah yeah oh okay that might save a
little bit of time
yes it does what huh oh yeah
it's very confusing i'm gonna try on
yours okay
uh no that you can't one has to be on
one side because there's like two
two buttons to press again oh i see
okay well let's get let's try and get it
to work then i'm sure it's fine
i just need to oh gosh dang it no you
can do it i don't need to
get the hang of it i just get the hang
of it it's okay we got this
no what
let me see what you're doing why is he
not grabbing onto the wall you have to
do the wrong jumps
he won't grasp okay i see
ah oh
okay you did it i see i got it now
i don't know why i thought i could just
do it without pressing a button jeez
just light it up oh
another door opens
are you gonna pull the finger i don't
wanna okay stupid fights the jokes
alright probably fine
oh wait we can't blow it we can make it
really what bart jokes are the best
no dad come on i don't like them i don't
like them
it's like that uh that that adam sandler
humor man
well that's what what are we doing like
help us with anything
i have no clue
i guess i guess we really have to pull
that finger
ah can you blow up that
fart thingy i guess i'll jump on it that
one i'm
this yeah over there oh
like with this thing yeah and then
to do yeah okay wait i have to dash
[Music]
i keep on yeah being confused about it
maybe
maybe i'm just too far what oh you get
really close to it i wonder if you have
to get on the other one
oh which one there's another thing
that's really close
yeah the one with the blue cord that
goes to it all right
oh this one ah yeah maybe ready yes
give it a try oh yes okay oh my god yes
it did something but
it happened too fast all right here you
go
okay i'm hanging on it oh and there's
some someone fired but it was not me
oh my gosh this day what now
i'm hanging here don't like those ghosts
can i get up though no i cannot i guess
i have to go down though but will those
go away
dude i have no clue can i jump up oh
he's moving back yeah
okay brain not working anymore it's okay
you got this so it's coming back grab it
all right
now maybe there's got to be something i
have to do down here
um maybe we have to be fast maybe you
have to get already in position
to jump over there and i will jump from
the room
okay so here's right i think i get what
i'm supposed to do
yeah not this one but maybe maybe this
one okay i got it i have to do it myself
and then
and then run really fast oh dang it that
is way too quick
i think you have to wait on that part
bag
and whatever that is wait cushion the
right the yeah the right one
yeah the one that i didn't use no no the
other one
the pink one yeah right here i jump over
there from
my side from from the rope i'll jump
right on it
and then it should still be in reachable
distance for you okay okay three
two one [\h__\h] i got the wrong one
[Music]
i got the two things wrong it was that
one right
okay okay i jumped on the wrong one but
that is how we do it
oh [\h__\h] sorry it's okay we got it this
time
we got it we've cracked the code yes yes
yes yes
okay and then you get in position and i
will this time jump on the right thing
yes ma'am
oh come on i mean isn't that something
you could do without swinging though
[Music]
yeah well let's just see let me let me
get over to this side and see what
happens
okay all right now we can control
this one oh
oh no it gives air to that one too
hey but that's still too far the thing
is
how about this one you can do the same
thing that i did
both of them
yeah do the same thing that i did okay
but first i have i have to finish the
blue one
yeah i have to bring it back first so
and yeah now oh
it's okay i get how it works now i see
why all that was necessary when you pull
the finger thing
oh [\h__\h]
yeah yeah
cause you call me kusatori i need some
real weird nickname for you as well
you got some time to think up something
rebelly
blurry yeah spinning wheel game
oh boy
did you don't get in there how did that
happen tell you what
splashy i don't want to use that on the
pool side
nice that was sick very much
[Music]
i'm getting really hungry come on that's
it
i am don't i need a teddy bear or
something i am water can
what can i are you inside yeah that was
oh we're both inside can we get out
okay what is that does that mean that
was
well that was really that was something
uh-oh
what is this crouch
jump three times crouch we didn't ah
where's the price give me something
useful
yeah and i guess that's it okay all
right so
you got that
two colors and now it's only one color
of balls dropping down
why am i going crazy now it's just
yellow yeah before it was green as well
balls that are coming down
oh wait there's another one here
you want to pull it out enough for the
yellow ones yeah
rotate it carry it thanks times for the
yeah thank you guys thank you
bless you too guys i'll consider it
it's been a minute since i heard a blast
oh i didn't really do that
in the underworld a bridge was created
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
nice nice safe oh my
[Music]
oh my god we have to drive together what
about creativity being stifled and all
that i think we need to come up with a
common common idea here guys just wait
that's way too different
it makes something great does mine just
ah mine goes up and down and yours goes
like right and left huh oh
well no i can't i i literally cannot
wrap my brain around that that is
impossible
mine used to have a pen my thingy
yeah yeah but a lot of those i guess
many of them just had the two knobs that
you could turn
and they'd each go a different way
really
vertical and horizontal what's up piggy
is that just a thing you saying to that
pinky
no i just randomly said what's up piggy
and then dad repeated me it's a little
creepy to be honest i kind of wish he
would stop it how did you do it i have
no idea dude i don't
know it's dead i loved playing this one
too that was freaking creepy
like getting out the tooth
okay oh my god that's so cute mine was
mine was a
not a frog what was the um hippo
crocodile oh yeah hippo hippo maybe it
was a hippo
oh oh are you okay nice all right all
right
sorry munch
[Music]
wait no that's kind of wrong it actually
goes
yeah i mean this is great and all but i
actually really prefer coco senpai's
version so
it's being popular
what do you mean baseball batting oh
there oh
oh no i'm not okay wait actually yes i
am good at brewing
football i'm good at throwing games
so yeah people have recommended me to uh
uh yeah play baseball i think you have
to press
uh watch out man okay there we go oh no
i know how to bat a ball yeah dad is
naturally good
how do i which button look at it go
next oh rubbish
i see oh
boo you're out of here
oh are we doing it right
yeah we're doing it right it's all about
timing yeah
oh damn it
i'm confused but i think we're doing a
ride
yes oh missed that one
oh
[Music]
come on face it oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] no all righty
that's right
you're hitting it real good kelly oh
yeah for a minute i was
ah that was pretty scary
did it for dad cool do it for dad
[Music]
okay dad loves the baseball i couldn't
let him not win any
two on the three i'm not messing around
yeah
[Music]
that's next focusing oh
there we go okay
he's good at the crazy speed beast yeah
no no
no props
okay
[Music]
that's right
are you letting me win right now all
right no
nothing to it easy
whoo are you sure you did a change i'm
not happy about it i felt like you were
trying to let me win
weren't you no i wasn't no i was trying
did you see how fast i was going
no you would jump chat was she was she
letting me win
i feel like she was going like really
slow was she letting me win
nah nah i just had a bad i just had a
bad game she wasn't i mean okay
okay it happens to the best of us
oh actually no there's no camera but
this is so cute
what's this the toy toys and the hair
what's written over there a little red
riding hood and a big
wolf and the big bear wolf
well there's the wolf of theirs already
that's cute it's
it's piccolo and we don't have a tur
turtle
uh yet why not
question maths three how about that i
don't we don't
we don't need that book we don't need
maybe a really extroverted turtle
give it to give it to good off
we don't need it i kind of need it to be
honest
you know
[Music]
itself it's the people that fidget spin
no offense to anyone who fidgets
this in the chat it's just weird
[Music]
yeah well good for them they seem to be
having fun
okay where am i jumping to them mom and
dad having fun
always that waterfall here we go walk in
the water
let's find a way to shut it off okay i
think
these pipes balls
that's fun wait there's a there's other
where do you turn it off
i found one just randomly
is this one right here oh you found one
yeah this is the second one i found one
too there should be one more after this
okay good oh no
and two i need to stop it i need to just
jump is it stopping them
the red ones yeah the red ones are gone
now we need to find one more
i guess there are some fidget spinners
oh no they're completely gone now i got
it
[Music]
nice although i would love to go for a
shower
of of those balls
we can't jump into the ball pit at least
so there's a shower through them
yeah exactly that does seem kind of fun
if they were very light
not super heavy look at that slide
it has holes in it though oh i'm getting
some serious flashbacks to birthday
parties
in the underworld you know reapers we
don't really have birthdays so everyone
chooses a day that they like
to celebrate something like that yeah
and they have this kind of stuff in the
underworld too
little bounce houses and stuff what the
[\h__\h]
is it supposed to do jump like that what
am i
oh i saw a good question in the chat if
you in the underworld don't celebrate
birthdays do you celebrate death days
hmm well that's it well since reapers
don't i mean reapers don't
die so yeah but do you celebrate the
death days of the people you reap
oh that's a great question there's just
so many of them it's it's kind of it's
kind of tough
um but because i have pieces of their
souls i'm always reminded
get a nice ad on the head you do
sometimes like
like become friends with the people you
reap
that's confidential information oh my
god we're doing a whole
do you want to be on holo talk one day
you're
inviting me questions to answer
questions
we need to understand what's what's in
the mind what's going on in the mind of
a
reaper so how the hell do you get over
there
i messed up ones um so get all right go
yellow
yellow pink blue on the beach balls but
before you first
okay on the right side yeah
by the way these are holes in the bounce
house which makes it a lot less charming
they're not little footholds
what i don't get it why does it do these
mini jumps did you do that too
oh yeah you just have to use your fidget
spinner
get onto the yellow what the hell yeah
yellow
perfect uh blue oh what yeah okay
excellent
[Music]
[Applause]
fun oh my god does this suck us in or
does it
i've just been avoiding them but okay
i'm pretty sure they provide wind to
make a fly
there's a whole beach here yeah we fly
we fly even higher
i need to put on my straw hat and my
sunglasses for this beach location yeah
it's beach time
but no time for that gotta we're gonna
gotta fidget spin
that's right we're on a mission and busy
spinning
a fidget spinner i feel like amelia
would be the type who plays with fidget
spinners
yeah i can see that but you probably
wouldn't tell anyone
um i waited until the bananas were far
out of the way that'd be time for the
jump
okay i don't think it'll kill you
um if you if you miss if you get hit by
one i'll definitely find okay
it's very forgiving yeah i don't know
what i'm doing
i actually have a melon in my in my
fridge right now but not a watermelon
i have uh the one that's kind of like
white inside oh i've never heard of that
before
it's yellow on the outside and white on
the inside
what's that one called in english yellow
on the outside white on the end
oh yeah it's a honeydew oh honey
okay it's really yummy have you eaten
that before
yeah i think they look a little
different
for me at least there's also scratches
not purple uh orange flesh what's that
one called
in english a cantaloupe it's the worst
fruit uh on the facebook
oh that's the cantaloupe in english
and it doesn't taste good it's terrible
it's not refreshing it's
the worst
[Music]
okay okay i won't mention them anymore
it's fine it's not like it's a sore
topic for me or anything it's just oh
not a dog
[Music]
because you keep on calling me i should
be calling you cantaloupe
all this time i mean all these million
times when you called me
to tease me i should have been calling
you cantaloupe okay can i love chat yeah
you're gonna miss that
all right fine i'm not gonna let myself
get anything
i know that's what you want i thought
you were already in front of me
no are you no i'm still i'm still
waiting to time this perfectly
all right here we go hurry up
yes i'm on my way hey
as long as i can still call you
acoustitory i don't care how can i
think of this earlier i just didn't want
to tease you the way you call me because
i just never thought of doing the same
thing to you yeah the viewers kind of
forgot about it too i think they traded
it in for dad
and now it's back i don't really mind
it's bad yeah i mean i guess but i don't
think the dead thing will drop
deadbeats really like it yeah whoa
here we go
oh man
yeah oh no there you are
cantaloupe you late no i'm on time
now we're just constantly calling each
other with our stupid teasing names
and we're going up we're going up
he's like a collider oh no
oh here we go yes same you guys working
you like each other more now
i bet this is the villain there are more
things to learn and new challenges to
overcome
let's keep on going we got a
relationship to feed
[Applause]
i like the book of love still what the
[\h__\h] is going on here
what oh my god
what whoa kaleidoscope nice
that's such a neat idea for a level
freaking crazy in here
that is a good idea an illusion that's
how polite
wait where's our fingers finished i'm
about to throw up in here
oh they're gone give them back they're
so fun
took them away from us that's scoundrel
what the [\h__\h] that's oh my god
oh no that makes oh my god oh my god if
you look at that
oh my god that makes you really dizzy
that makes me this is it doesn't make
you this in
what's going on
yeah what the hell is going on oh there
we go i'm alive somehow
head toward the light i don't like this
head
i don't like this
can we play twister instead please yeah
i'm down for twister any day god
oh uh what is going on here
this is so weird what
was serena oh
maybe when the floor changes we're
making ah
dang it i thought maybe something would
appear like a leap of faith
get it i get it uh
can you uh we need to connect those
wait can you go on that one and then i
go to that one
nine that was i was thinking
and here we have to connect again callie
i think oh
i'm just kidding vanish to the void for
that one okay
go go in doubtling here
yes thank you guys thank you thank you
finally finally i deserved that a long
time ago
oh boss fight
two of us oh my gosh doppelgangers
oh this is huge fight connect them
uh yeah we did it oh my god what the
hell
we made a hole
oh my god this is not what is this still
an illusion
what the [\h__\h] anymore
what oh maybe not oh finally
what is this place
that's this is where you move it to the
side and all that ah
we need to try and get up here so maybe
we bring the we bring that over to
ah to the stairs okay okay oh wait
there you can kind of twist it around so
that i can get on perfectly
all right next my turn to twist oh wait
it moves after i let it go
yeah it does okay i need a twist so we
can connect
oh here um wait can i get up too or
oh yeah you should be able to are you
able to come here yeah i did
oh now i go for the yellow one
i guess yeah next up i need to try and
use the yellow
uh where do i bring it ah so see
look look at this where the pink extends
outward
okay you can bring the yellow there
here yeah it's not so far okay
okay can i bring you to the other one to
this one
yeah blue oh there you go
a little bit okay perfect come up here
okay i'm here let's go together
yes nice
all the way to the top
oh and now we do it together okay which
way
what's going on no stopping
getting started is this the usual room
yeah it looks a bit similar
oh yeah is this yeah i don't want to go
back i can imagine
i like to think that the usual room is a
place of existence you're a doll
cody you have nothing to throw up like
like horrors like not the typical
you threw up callie oh that's cool i
guess yeah it looks like clay
oh look there she is the elephant
ah that's easy we just have to get to
the magic castle
which i built by the way you built them
wow big ups to you
dad you're not the only one in the
family who can build cool stuff oh
really
yeah stop fighting that thing right over
there
yeah i know i kind of wish they'd get
along a little bit yes i am sure with
you just
so annoying we'll try thank you
it's just come on let's clear the way
for the handcart be nice
oh we have to lift the barrier first
do those dolls control it dolls
dolls which don't wait
i cannot tell let's see we can scale the
walls like this
oh bouncy
here's a doll by the way the the things
we did
since last time was that one level are
we still or are we still in
like one level sure
i still do you think it here where do
you put the dolls
yeah i wonder
okay okay oh i guess so oh on the star
yeah i mean
oh no that bounces it star is kind of
bouncy i feel like this is the plate no
stop doing that this is probably the
place to put them
do that or bring it with you
okay um maybe we need whoa
maybe we need it down here
yeah here's like a yeah maybe a round
spot there we go that's better
all right let's find the rest of them oh
there's
yeah one there and one there but he's
does he stay here or do we move
him too looks like he's working i can't
remove him all righty we got three
another
oh this is probably in the wrong
position ah okay okay
see i mean maybe not okay just kind of
weird i don't know who you're trying to
smooth me
okay what but nothing happened
maybe maybe yeah maybe maybe it is the
wrong let's try the other one maybe
yeah am i the other way around
yeah maybe we're supposed to use this
somehow we can combine forces on here
we can't get going with this barrier in
the way oh
what's up with those dolls eh
what oh so you're telling me stop trying
to do that okay
heard loud and clear baby i'm gonna try
putting that over there
i'm searching for more dolls all right
wait no we got all the dolls so
now we need to try and
i think maybe we need to reposition them
yeah
oh okay so this guy looks like an
engineer dude right
so maybe this dude is here
where the gear is
oh you know the tracks are correct here
booing did it got it did it do that
trick
the thing is still up though
you go here really
[Music]
maybe there's a dollar missing you know
but there's only five spots
little boy i'll bring him over what's
that by the way
what is that
what what does that do
i can zoom i can look at stuff okay the
castle looks really nice
hmm you built that that huh
nice dad i made it myself where do i
i only see three spots to put dolls down
though
oh wait dude i need ah the boy and the
girl have the kiss baby
yeah oh all right i would just like
someone to work the gate
ah and then he goes me the conductor
no no not you got it okay
i live you live your dreams
those dolls might come in handy nice
okay now we have to do teamwork again
what we don't move it there we go now
it's moving
oh i told you to trust me where is that
oh my god what was that a dinosaur yeah
and it takes us straight to the castle
there's lava on the ground what the [\h__\h]
did you build that no yeah definitely
i didn't put the dinosaur there oh
whatever
let's just find a way to clear the track
what
how you
you got a long neck like a giraffe
giraffe giraffe
giraffe yeah do you want to control it
up here
okay this one's mine
oh i take the red one oh the red one on
the platform red one
red one red one
check it out there's a little one right
in front of you
go up how do i get up there
can you move your neck maybe i do it can
you
use me perhaps i want oh i can here i'll
help you
yeah maybe i need to go up to your head
how
how low can you kill me i can't make it
any more down
oh okay
can you get on board
[Music]
wait let me try to get on top of the
head
no uh maybe we need to go to a place
where you can jump and then get on the
head
okay
any kind of higher ground
what about these boys can i not use them
no hold it
i like the music here though it's very
chill huh what is this
i know maybe
ah can you try
i see there you go i did it oh my god
what did you do oh you went down there
didn't realize the white stuff okay oh
cute
what is this oh my god what is that so
i think you have to grab a bone again oh
yeah oh okay
is there a bone where i am
there's not one where you are but you
guys do this one again no
there's one on the other side but you
can't get to the other side can you
oh no how about this one
no i can't um
maybe i can maybe i need to extend
ah ah wait now do the bone thing again
okay
ah cause i can turn it around with those
thingies oh
ah thank you nice you're welcome
i'm just passing through wattle waffle
waddle well
and then i'm i bunk with my tail [\h__\h]
something turns around oh yeah you can
make me awake
big dinosaur jaws there we go here you
go
i shall lead you safely across i grant
you stay fast
and i bunk again no problem what moves
now
oh yeah hop on board
well now there's nothing i can bonk
got it oh oh do i have to go down
ah while you're grabbing it yeah take me
down again please
while you're still grabbing it i bunk it
again so that it can't move or
turn around yeah and now we go up again
and now i can pass all right
huge brain yeah this is a little bit
cute
it's very adorable
and i go back up
thank you thank you yup
ah oh yeah okay next bone please
okay you
and then and then bring me up again
maybe no did that do anything yeah it
did
yeah i did yeah i did you just gotta but
now you can't grab me like
ah yeah grab that so it doesn't move
now you can come back to me yeah and
bring me back up again
because whatever you grab won't move
when i when i
tap it with my tail that's the way
[Music]
you gotta bring it back to me please got
that one
cool i got you lunch here you are how do
those bones taste huh
taste you like them well since they
tasted pork dough
full of calcium is that like a snack in
the underworld eating bones because
you've got a lot of them down there
yeah sometimes they're pretty crunchy
usually demon bones though
not human bones it's like potato chips
for the underwhelmings
sounds kind of healthy though don't
worry humans are spinning oh
yeah i totally saw that coming i want my
baby back
what do i do here oh
and make sure you don't die thank you so
if i fall down there um
that would work oh [\h__\h] oh i
know that was gonna happen can i grab
onto something i wonder
maybe you grab onto the wall hold on oh
yeah oh yeah she does grab them
okay all right now you're sick
now we can go to the right side
thank you okay this is safe zone
and well down uh
something's here can you do something
all right i just fell down i guess okay
oh uh
i can i forgot i can grab on to just
hold on to the wall only hold on
no you need to jump i'll just i'll just
give you a ride
okay oh wait look at that
wait okay i'm on it
oh nice
[Music]
that's not good that's not good that's
not good it's cool hopefully
sorry mr dino i don't think personally
mr daddy
he looks very nice though ever friendly
whoa
oh no dude let me try a mint okay
just out of courtesy all right coming
through brushing your teeth is very
important well at least now we can get
fit
thank you sir i smell smoke smoke i
don't smell anything
your nose has always been sick something
burning oh yeah
why do i see fire ahead uh-oh
this kind of reminds me of the nether
yeah it looks a lot like the cave update
that's coming for
minecraft
oh really cool i'm looking forward to
the cave update
you should do a collab for it yes yes
we haven't done a minecraft collab in a
long time like you will
remember in the very beginning we kind
of wanted to make that our thing
look at this yeah everyone just kind of
feels like they're okay but
i'd be down the bridge anytime at least
all the toys i bought rose are finally
coming in handy
huh yeah
oh no he listened again yay
silly toy i don't know ancient
ones yes the ancient one's dummy
oh my god we're both cute
wow this is fun oh my god oh my god
they're shooting who's shooting at us
here's straight man
oh i'm am i shooting can
[Music]
i understand
but this is like the toy version
[Music]
well now we're double strong yeah
double strong we just really got to try
to be heading in the same area okay okay
okay pretty clear easy you go to the
right first
yeah make it rain taco takoyaki
[Music]
epic music closed
hey guys we don't have to do this we
come in peace
hey i don't like their cannons neither
do it
is
thank
gotta look a little oh unlucky without
position
yeah okay let's go to the ones on the
left first they seem more open
by the way one second um i wanna i feel
like the music right now is like
overpowering you let me
um turn down the music okay
maybe like that oh god
it's so loud what it
still super loud
oh maybe i should just
okay maybe i'll run down
okay all right guys maybe it's better
careful don't think
are you saying that to the keys because
they don't care they are ruthless
he is calm and chill and still are
talking that she's here
um until now by the way speaking of taco
that is
outfit was so adorable it's so
cute yeah the ruffles kind of moved like
like tentacles
mm-hmm i liked how her little taco still
has like some
all these dark colors like mine is super
bright but hers is like pretty dark and
chill but still
cute it looks very comfy
i love the the palette that she can use
in her hands mm-hmm
which is unfortunately not a big perfect
for her
perfect for her okay i probably
shouldn't have done that
i just really wanted to blow that up me
too
oh [\h__\h] actually my my viewers asked me
before which
outfits from all the halloween girls i
like the most like the new ones
and i said enos and almonds because ame
is like something i would personally
wear
and i said the same as you yeah really
oh yeah
i saw that i thought that too when i saw
amy's outfit you it you would personally
wear it
hmm yeah but i mean no no no that i
thought that like you would personally
ah okay okay and then it's like i mean i
would wear it
too probably it's not exactly 100 myself
it looks very comfy and i just think
like inna's outfit fits herself
so so so good it's so cute straight into
the ice pockets
penguins i think enos is perfect
wow this is pretty there's freaking
penguins here
frosty oh
what where should we go right
why are they saying spoilers did i spoil
something oh
maybe viewers don't know what you would
wear in real life
yeah i mean when you're not being kfp
manager so
they're number two oh my god oh we're
almost done
but they're gonna revive us with full hp
i guess so it's okay
even if we die oh we got it okay
are we going straight open the gates
oh see it's the final showdown
time let's go stupid ugly octopus it is
not
ugly in real life it is super cute and
huggable
yeah believe that yeah go with that one
you are
super cute super cute
yeah that's how you got a compliment you
got a compliment
lay on those compliments we don't want
to eat this yeah i didn't buy it
we angered them we angered them
real bad oh my god
they're sucking us in
he's on all right oh okay oh we need to
turn around
[Music]
do we aim at the tentacle and the face
or the tendon
let's try and turn like towards the taco
okay but if a tentacle appears turn
towards this
like this
[Music]
so rude
wants to hug us sorry taco dashies we
wanted to
be in peace but you are choosing to
fight take them away
oh my god the ducks
takodachi is now in collaboration with
oh gosh there are too many characters
here we got
we got marine senpai here too in the
whole setting
ahoy mother efforts mother f wording
ahoy
you got the whole cast the whole crew
we were turning already though
you all right my head's spinning
oh there's something done on the right
side do we shoot do we shoot it let's
kill it yeah
before it shoots us i guess yeah there
we go like a landmine or a water mount
yup oh right in front of us nice thank
you
easy nice
[Music]
maybe we should have ignored this small
things the bump yeah maybe
okay oh it's gone now okay i feel sick
tentacles gone too
much let's beat up the taco almost done
for
the big taco da team
[Music]
oh my god that no that's how they think
they look like
they're like they think they're really
buffing all but they're all tiny and
cute
with more than two arms again okay yeah
let's go with that real world
and did not try to kill me
exactly and the real word takatas are
cute
in the fantasy world exactly they're
super strong and can kill people
why did i leave it you left what do you
mean
i'm rejoining oh you left in the game oh
interesting
i have just quit no no not in the game
oh you also ah
there okay yep yep yeah only in the room
okay i'm waiting for you the place in
the dimension
i hope you come back at the same spot
debatable
well i went back in oh probably takes a
moment
yeah let's wait a second do you see me
nope oh yeah but i don't usually see
wait maybe oh wait on it maybe it's
uh on my side the problem i know i see
you now oh
ah wait i'll bring you into position one
second
okay
and then i i'm so hungry after we're
done with that level
we need to take a break because i need
to eat
i mean yeah sounds good to me i need to
sleep so okay
how late uh how late uh how late is it
in the world
um it's almost 1am oh
i would like to get some decent sleep
because um had to wake up at six for
for you guys uh new costumes
not your fault that was so sweet that
you got up for us
was hashtag worth it but thankfully uh
good as is it no
an okay time for me as long as i don't
get too crazy actually get eight or
seven hours the only one i can't watch
is amen probably because she's at four
am for me four oh geez damn
that's nuts by the way i'm ready to go
you're back in position
thank you for bringing me back no
problem
[Music]
but the good thing is even if i can't
watch i'm alive i already know what half
it looks like so no problem
[Music]
oh duckies oh my god doggies overload
hey this is kind of like that haunted
house next time i visit
you over there we need to go to
disneyland
maybe yeah next time we'll probably be
well next time when i visit japan we'll
probably be when everyone visits japan
maybe yeah let's all go let's all go to
do disney stuff yeah
i love roller coasters but i'm really
bad at them
creepy balloons oh yeah yeah now we
can't get to the other one
it kills me to lower that bridge
i can understand that though hey there
hey
the bridge is only lowered for visitors
to the cash
oh good we are visiting the castle b are
you here to see the coin
doesn't she look creepy to you as well i
don't like her elephant
yeah not a big fan oh rose's best friend
cutie
the elephant over there do we have an
elephant youtuber in
the world oh no okay
maybe not yet
but i think she can do the clown thing
if she wants to do the clown i guess so
yeah she can do anything
senpai is like overpowered circus things
yeah
ring mastery i guess worthy of an
audience with the queen
well if if polka isn't a clown then i
want to clown youtuber
no thank you yeah the clown v tuber
would be dope
i mean probably already exists outside
of her life
yeah i'm sure i'm sure
everything there's like literally
anything you can imagine now
yeah yeah any youtuber that you can
imagine
oh oh i can't do that alone
i think the moment you you you have that
there's limit there's another one
got it okay
quick okay yeah oh that was too fast
oh
okay is there more no okay
now that side which goes where oh
it goes on its own it opened the door
look at all those blocks wait didn't we
just finish a level i guess it's time
for some hamster action again i have no
idea
you just had that tackle boys
this is a whole nother new thing yes we
did okay
because we just then we can stop yeah we
just finished a boss battle i'm super
hungry you want to sleep
poor sleep this is fun yeah it's super
fun and we're doing the last part
probably next week uh-huh yeah we'll
probably finish it i think
yeah next week awesome maybe maybe we do
it one hour earlier than today then we
can probably finish it without problems
sounds good to me all right then
thank you everyone for joining in today
again um
i might actually after getting some food
i might actually start a super chat
reading
in an hour maybe maybe because i i'm
i'm yeah far behind now and i don't have
any other
any uh anymore time at the rest of the
week probably
so i'll think about it though guys i'll
let you guys know
oh yeah one more thing if you guys uh
didn't i feel like everyone who is in
here watched it already but if you
didn't
i just uploaded a new song covered with
good ah on my channel
i could buy free so if you haven't heard
it please listen to it
and like naked and heart challenger is
getting very close to one million views
it's like a million a million a million
million i don't know
i don't know how far i think maybe 50k
or something please
give it a listen so we can get to one
million please guys
i know you're always supporting me a
little bit i know i always say it stream
heart challenge um please do
please do uh and yeah and then later on
as good as outfit for real
which i'm sure everyone will check out
tomorrow is ammon's outfit for real and
after that we have a full member casual
outfit collab where we are playing a
pomo
pommel pumu pumu
[Music]
yeah it's like mario party supposedly i
never played it before
but either it should be fun ryan kelly
yeah word on the street i've never
played it myself
i'm sure we'll be fine because every
once everyone in the whole english is
back together it will always be fun no
matter what we play no matter what we do
so any anything callie wants to say uh
cantaloupe
ah it's funny
i always ignore when you call me
crusader and i call you cantaloupe when
you get like
really because you got used to it this
is a new thing
yeah the new thing about development for
me
forget about the only thing i wanna yeah
i'm i'm sure i feel like cantaloupe was
the thing that everyone used to
to poke fun in the beginning and then it
kind of died yeah
yeah but hey feel free to do what you
want my man um
sometimes for me uh guilty gear stream
tomorrow had to be moved for some
for uh to make room for me to get some
other stuff out of the way
so it'll be at 23 o'clock
jst which is 7 00 am pst
15 o'clock bst
uh come join in i'll be playing and
maybe fighting dead beats definitely
fighting deadbeats
and then i'm playing pokemon snap as
well and then
collab is the next day
so look forward to it and schedule might
be posted a little earlier
um members get to see it first so if
you'd like to join membership you get
access to the schedule about
uh usually 12 to 24 hours earlier so
yeah
uh check out my my staff if you haven't
i think everyone everyone already did
probably well you never know
i mean i think everyone who watches
these takamai streams
is like already like deep into the
takamoni fandom
you never know you never know
i prepare oh well thank you guys for
watching hope you guys had fun
see you um with this game next week and
otherwise see you soon
anytime i would love to welcome you and
see you back next time
i'll show you guys my straw hat again
glory wait i forgot do we have to save
in this game what was this auto save
yeah right yeah okay probably probably
hopefully
all right bye bye guys thank you and
germany
[Music]
yes and peace goodbye
peace freedom in german by the way
em oh wait what freedom
freedom yeah yeah freedom
[Applause]
[Music]
bye-bye
you