[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
food
[Music]
[Applause]
but
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm so spooked again hello can you oh my
god can you hear me
hello uh uh uh uh uh
[Music]
it's a nice very nice to see you again
hey let me
[Music]
just leave some back sleeves are back
catboy this microphone is new
uh
i don't know
uh what it sounds like it sounds a
little bit um
uh
acoustic
like if i would yes meow yeah yes if i
were to play
ukulele
with this it would sound probably really
good hello hello peace
[Music]
did you hear my cat i hope i hope the
microphone doesn't cancel out my cat's
meows those are really important i don't
know why people like used this hand
movement last time
but to make some funny memes and stuff i
really liked those kfp memes um
so
uh
the
this microphone is a blue yeti
microphone i bought it just to upgrade
the cooking streams um
and uh
i feel like you know it's supposed to
pick up everything around it but like
the more if i speak it directly it
definitely picks it up better i hope i
still hope it's fine
and uh
the cool thing about it is i can put on
headphones i can stick them into the
microphone and i can hear myself
but
it's crispy
doesn't sound okay doesn't sound better
than last time i'm not sure about it but
it has definitely it definitely has a
different sound to it
[Music]
oh um
yeah so uh where do we start like
there's so many things i want to talk
about uh so first of all i got a new
cutting cutting board i got free like
this is the biggest size and i have
smaller sizes because
i was using really really really really
flimsy cutting boards um
out of plastic but this is made out of
bamboo so
[Music]
[Laughter]
a new new cutting board beautiful bamboo
is going to be used today for the first
time then i did get cooking gloves uh
oh my god wow when i touched a
microphone it's like an asmr microphone
what the hell it's so sensitive yeah i
bought cooking gloves but i actually i i
didn't i didn't realize that
there there were specific sizes and i
accidentally got l size
and uh it's they're
too big i put them on and they're like
way too big they don't fit at all so
that is number one problem and the
second problem is that they end like
here
so you you would be able to see like
something here probably every once in a
while that is problematic so i am
sticking to my beautiful fancy black
gloves made out of cloth before i find
any other cookie cooking plastic gloves
latex gloves that go
further upwards because otherwise it
ends here and they all end here they all
kind of end there so that sucks
i did buy them but i can't use them
i bought a hundred hundred uh pair of
pack hundred pairs of gloves for nothing
yeah number two
uh of things is uh
i have a little bit of a little bit of a
um
uh
and paint i talked about it yesterday
actually it got a little bit worse so i
will be drinking tea and this is
actually
the
tea mug that nana senpai
[Music]
um
certain brands uh
furnace
[Music]
she got me too um as a goodbye gift when
i left japan so
once the tea is finally finally
drinkable i will make sure to drink it
where do i put it i'll put it
here
yes um
yeah uh
then we will be cooking
and well okay let me clear this up
because some some germans my dear
friends my dear neighbors a few of my
neighbors
were
mad at me
for claiming that what we are cooking
today is um
australia well let's just say it the way
it is today austrian okay i don't want
people to get confused and think i'm
actually cooking something from
australia which is it's obviously not
from australia so let's let's be a
little bit more clear today but so my
dear german neighbors the thing is you
know austria and germany used to be like
one country kind of yeah
i think
most of us know that and
since austria is in the middle of europe
uh
we take we we have a lot of we have a
lot of
food
that we
um that originates from other countries
like hungary italy etc we mix it all and
sometimes we'll make our own version out
of it so anyway what we're making today
is um uh well the german name for it
would be casey
cat the a with the two dots on top is a
you pronounce it as a
so it's ke
batsler quezo spatzler
you don't have to think too much about
it you just you can just say it as a e
but german pronounced e
most of the time it does a trick so it's
a cassette okay but i don't i don't
really usually i don't really say like
casual i say like kansas bracelet yeah
so anyway um that is like the german
name because the the case is the cheese
and the spatula is like the the things
that look like noodles or potatoes or
whatever you thought that was
um now with special you can make all
kinds of food anyway that originally
comes from
not only germany i want to say that
because i had some you know i love i
love germany okay we're neighbors i love
you i sleep with this buddha man but
then you're okay loving me
okay you have to kind
we just have a different version of case
of special in austria and it's i think
the the biggest difference is that in
germany um they make it with uh they
make it in like a
uh
oh
i think they make it in an oven like
they
they kind of put like the spatula and
then they put the cheese and then they
put the spreads and then they put the
cheese i think and then i put it in the
oven so it gets a little bit crispy i
think
but um it's like a little bit like a
casserole i guess and but in in
[Laughter]
something's in my eye in austria
in austria we make it a little bit
different we make it in the frying pan
and uh it gets a bit more creamy
it gets a bit more creamy by doing that
so um there are like specific types of
cases that originate from austria and uh
i am from
a straight i don't know man i don't even
i'm okay today
i am from austria
and um yeah if you look it up and you
see that there's different variations
from from where i'm from you know and
then and and and and and they actually
we actually call it actually
in dialect we call it casino
yeah so kaze spatzler became cast
yeah
so we even changed the name okay we're
making it differently and that's kind of
like uh the way that um my mom i always
saw my mom making them
so i would make them like that and i
think i think in germany they when they
make when they make the spatula the the
the noodle type thing yeah they they put
the batter in like a like a like a press
like a hat like it looks like a hammer
press like
from the outside looks like a hammer but
it's like a press or like a almost like
um
like the the thing that you use to crash
uh
garlic
shield senpai
so once you put it in you press it and
then out comes
long long many many long noodles which
are not really noodles though but i
guess you could call it that and then
they cut it i think but i'm making it
different and i'm going to be careful
because this tool that i have
mirrors
is that where did i'm supposed to use it
it shows things that it shouldn't be
showing so that would be really careful
but i'll just want to show you what i'll
be using oh you can actually kind of see
it from here
um
it's probably okay yes i think that
looks fine so
um this
these holes
yes this is where it will go through and
then directly into
the cooking water
and in here
in here
we put
uh the batter for um
the spatula so and then once it's in
there you gotta be somewhat fast uh
because you go like shoo
shoo shoo shoo
shoo
understand
understand so now i put this thing away
because it's cursed okay
um once the batter is on there i'll
probably be able to show
because uh when the batter is in there
it's gonna be all messy and there will
be no more reflection i would i hope so
and
yes i know it reflects a lot it likes it
likes girl goura so much i do too i
can't help it so i like to reflect a lot
and
that is also the reason why
i got this new microphone i hope it's
nice because it's way more expensive
than the other microphone that i used
so it better be better it better be
better uh is my tea drinkable probably
not huh let me see
um the dish itself
is not so difficult and i think i'll
even be fine
to make it without a recipe it's the
first time i'm making it all on my own
but
it's really not that difficult so let me
drink some tea
[Music]
oh my god okay i just explained it
i'm making okay okay let me be clear i'm
making an austrian version of your
sacred dishcase especially okay i'm
making cosmic i make it differently okay
so i'm not like not claiming something
as my own okay i understand
yes so
i'm gonna try to drink this tea although
i'm very very uh
[Music]
and i'm too scared to drink
i'm too hot
impossible to drink
okay so um
before we start i guess we can have
another talk because otherwise i'm gonna
be too distracted later on
um i went to the doctor today finally
finally i went to the doctor it took me
only a million [\h__\h] years to go
um i went to the doctor okay finally uh
we have a little bit of a special system
in
in the german speaking countries where
you go to like a general doctor called
house acts
looks like a house doctor he doesn't
come to your house but he has his own
little like office and he can do like
general things like if you have a cold
or whatever he'll like prescribe you
medicine but if you have some more
specific problems you go to him and he
sends you to a different doctor where
you would usually not be able to go to
if you didn't go to the house doctor
first understand so that's what i did i
went to the house doctor finally a new
house doctor because i moved recently
and i didn't have one in my area so
eh
yeah and he looked oh my god it was so
embarrassing because um so i was really
nervous yeah and um
i am a bit shy okay you might not
believe it but i am shy so i went to
went to the doctor's office
and i walked in
and i
sat down and i had my list of problems
on my phone in front of me and i was
looking at it while talking to him
and i started with the the i had three
problems without three three here
numbers three
three problems that i wanted to talk
about with him
and um
one of them was uh the back the neck the
back neck problem that i've had for many
many years including the injury from
very recently
and um
uh
i said that he had really good uh
reviews
and i'm sure he's nice and all but like
he did seem like he didn't want to spend
too much time listening to me and it's
like
both the receptionist and him seemed to
like when i when i was at the reception
and when i was on the phone on the phone
the receptionist was like asking me what
issues i have and i said i have very
very very very many many many problems
and she was like what you're so young
how is that possible
and then i come to the reception and i
give her my my my uh my insurance card
and all that and she's like
oh so where are you insurance and i say
well i am uh i'm i'm a set standing i am
independent so i'm insured with the
independent thingy the places where
independent people are insured and she's
like what you're so young
what are you doing
it's like
because i'm supposedly young
all of these things are weird to them
apparently being self-employed
independent and having pain and lots of
problems for many many years so then i
go into the doctor's office and i as i
said i started telling him telling him
all my problems
and uh
i was not done talking not at all i
didn't even get to the point of the
injury that i had in my vacation
but he already interrupted me and he was
like
blah blah blah and then i was like sorry
can i finish my story please
i actually
reinterrupted him because i needed to
finish my [\h__\h] story i'm not gonna
have people not listen to me anymore
so i finished my story but it still
seemed like kind of rash like he didn't
even look at me much so i felt like he
wasn't listening much it made me really
nervous but then
after i was done after i was done
telling him my stories
plural
uh he told me to get up and get
undressed and i was like oh
[Music]
because he wanted to touch my upper body
like the back side of it okay but i was
like wearing i was wearing a dress
i was wearing
uh like a
somewhat long dress
that's like
and i had i gotta be honest i had
nothing underneath
i mean yes panties but um you know the
other thing no so um i was like this is
my first time
do i have to have nothing underneath and
he was like yeah i don't care it doesn't
matter to me and i'm like yeah
can i still like um
keep it on because like uh
so i insisted on keeping my dress on
and he was able he was able to you know
touch my back anyway so
we were fine yeah but that kind of was
weird to me if it was a doctor that i've
been to before and was able to
you know trust a little bit i'm sure
he's not a weirdo i mean who does maybe
he is but for now i don't want to say
anything yet about that but but you know
can you can you judge me for feeling a
little bit insecure
i know i know he's a doctor and he
doesn't care much but you still like
to touch my back a little bit i had a
really thin dress on so it should have
been fine too you know
i think i think you can i mean
there's people who give massages through
massage clothes like you get like
clothes to get massages in at massage
places and they can still like really
get in there they can still really get
in there so excuse me for being a little
bit shy okay
um anyway he was able yeah if
yes if it was a female doctor i would
probably have gotten naked
but anyway um he was able to
uh touch me that sounds so weird and uh
he came to the conclusion that
my body is weird
he was like he kept on saying like what
did you do what the hell did you do what
is this what did you do
and i'm like i don't know i don't know
[Music]
i don't know what i did and he's he
keeps on saying i love it what did you
do like what that's like what um
just by touching my back a little bit
and my shoulders and all that he was
very confused no he wasn't able to give
any kind of diagnosis yet because that
was just a general like touchy touchy
feely feely but he did send me to go get
an x-ray and a blood test blood test for
like other reasons like you know iron
sufficiency or whatever or or like also
um related to the topic of me having um
baby asthma so
he also said that the headache probably
comes from
my back problems so
yeah uh we will be looking at that that
was just the first visit and then i'll
go get an x-ray and blood test and all
that kind of [\h__\h] he also gave me
he gave me um
yes he prescribed me
and
uh a medicine
uh
that
is called
uh sid sir dalut which
apparently
relaxes my muscles so much
that i will be absolutely dead and not
able to move so they told me to take it
before i go to sleep which might help
to
make me sleep early tonight
you know i always have these issues to
fall asleep and stay awake until 5am so
tonight i'll take that
um
yeah i'll become a noodle yes noodle
phoenix yay
yes yes yes i'm not i didn't take it yet
they told me to take it uh before going
to sleep at the very very last moment
because uh yeah it's it's uh
yeah i know i i will not take it for too
long only until the pain is gone so
because the the the pharmacy lady said
you can get addicted from that
oh dear we don't wanna get addicted from
that
uh
thing
so okay um now i told you all my little
stories
now i will cook for you no for myself
um let me just i'm trying to fix my
gloves right now
come on
my sleeve keeps pulling wait one sec can
i just one second
you also
undress the sleeve
[Music]
ah
i saw that clip i saw a clip of her when
she had that sleeping medicine
and was streaming i think she was
streaming ark or something and she kept
on talking
so much weird stuff
that was funny
yeah she didn't fall asleep downstream i
think right like if if yes and only like
low-key
yeah it's not gonna happen to me i'm
gonna take it before going to sleep
don't worry about it
okay fixing my sleeves we will start by
making the batter
yes
the batter consists
of um
[Music]
flat floor flour
floor
floor probably float floor that's is
that how you pronounce it did i get the
right floor is it floor
floor
is it floor
flower oh it's really supposed to be
like flower really
okay um floor a flat flower i have here
and um
uh vegan
eggs
wait
i think it was free eggs
they're difficult to get out of the box
[Music]
one egg
vegan
don't worry guys
two
three
tamago
[Music]
and let me look at my recipe
just to see how much flour we need
and
400 gram
see i do have a scale a cooking skill
but i have never used it before so i'm
gonna use this because it says
yeah here it actually says
uh
flour
here so i'm gonna put 400
flowers
400 grams of flour in there but let me
try to fix my camera a little a little
bit maybe
[Music]
a tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny bit higher
only a tiny bit
yes that's probably
okay so 400
oh wait i don't see it where is it hear
it hello asmr anyone
uh
[Music]
sorry
it's definitely so noisy right
[Laughter]
i got you gotta be careful when i get
close
i will uh whisper then sorry i will
proceed to
get in there what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
you
oh sorry sorry
sorry sorry for yelling
[Laughter]
[Applause]
is this an asmr mic it's like weird like
oh
no
or something like that
i think that's enough uh
[Music]
uh oh no it's a little bit less than 400
wait i need a bit more flowers
[Music]
no it's still not enough
i just don't want to have too much in it
okay what about now
[Music]
it's still a little bit not enough
and
well finally finally i'm using a bow my
[\h__\h] flower
i've been having this in my in my closet
for
ages okay
it's a little bit uh
[Music]
uh what is the best tool
maybe maybe that
i don't know i'll try to use this
uh
to mix it maybe in an income
nation like this but it's gonna be a
very thick
a pretty thick um
texture yes
let me try to drink my tea again i'm
trying to take care of my throat today
and
i have to say though simply by being
able to hear myself through the
headphone which i was not able to last
time simply by doing that um
that's a fork it's not a force
since am i doing that i am able to
control my voice better
therefore i don't have to yell so much
and
i can catch my breath as well somewhat
so i'm feeling better than last time
already
[Music]
what
will you mix the tea through this no
we're here you're fine okay
[Music]
okay
um
let me just quickly
check if i got any messages from manager
son
no okay
nothing
nothing happened so far that i would get
scolded for
we're doing great guys
okay so we uh wait a second let me see
uh we also need 200 milliliters water
free uh eggs and a little bit of salt
um so wait
[Music]
okay
so
that was a little bit of german er
we put
we am supposed to use uh
a c
a c for
[Music]
what
ah
[Music]
i see what it sounds so similar
a sieve yeah but i don't have one at
least not some one that's that big i
have like a tiny ass
okay this is i have this but
too small
um
should i use it anyway it's so tiny
nah nah that's for like sugar anyway
i'll throw it in
and uh
should i do this like
maybe this is well step by step
because it will be a little bit
difficult to mix this
egg
okay i want to
for the next cooking stream
egg in the flower
i want to figure out some setup where um
i can
um
uh really have the camera
above
but this is what i'm doing right now
i will figure it out eventually
eh no it's vegan chickens
don't worry vegan chickens not you guys
egg number two
um
[Music]
let me already start
by mixing a little bit
[Music]
yeah i want i need
oh god
i need
one of those mixers man
oh man
cooking
mixer is that my sister no
those are not real eggs nothing is real
the egg is a lie guys
have you not heard of that before now
great my fingers are ill disgusting
hey look look uh you don't really see
anything here anyway okay okay
[Music]
great now my gloves are wet this is
wonderful
oh god
yeah
don't worry don't worry
don't worry
ah
don't worry don't worry
don't worry everything everything is
daijoubu
let me just throw all the flour
and then i need uh 200
milliliters of water
yeah and i'll mix that
into the batter slowly so you currently
it looks like [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
i have this trunk
here but it will hopefully get better uh
after a little while
uh after mixing in some water oh god
oh god
[Music]
why is it all in there
yeah this is already a pain yes
i need i can get it out of there
get out of there this was the wrong tool
this was the right tool
[Music]
ew get out of there
get out of there
ew it's all inside
yeah yeah get out of there
[Music]
yeah you know what i could actually do
it by hand with my cooking gloves
i'm thinking about doing that
maybe i'll do that
[Music]
but i almost got it
out of the
thing this was a mistake this was a
mistake
[Music]
please don't make it please don't do it
like me if you have one of those mixer
machines use that
or use your hands i guess
[Music]
uh
learning by doing guys learning
by doing
okay
i'm i think i can
give up on the rest
that's in there okay
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
i'm switching to cooking gloves i'm
probably gonna turn off the camera
for a little bit
uh cooking gloves let's go
oh
oh jonkers i wish i could show you
junkers but she's
you know we don't want to show on camera
because she's not wearing any makeup
right now but she's currently
sitting in front of the kitchen counter
on on the [\h__\h] cat bed that i got her
i'm so happy she's using the cat bed
yeah so adorable
she's just looking at me
normally you know when i stream
in the beginning when i started
streaming they would always like be in
the same room but
um i think at some point they got sick
of it because i'm so loud for so many
hours
so they um decided to
not
be in the room anymore whenever i stream
and only like check in every once in a
while
because i'm just too loud and they want
to sleep
but right now she's right here that's so
cute hi chance hi baby yeah
judging me and my cooking skills okay so
now it has
here i told you they're way too big
but i will use that now
i will use that now let me turn off the
camera to give me a little bit more of a
safe feeling
okay
and i will need
neat
need
this
stupid batter
oh yeah that works oh that's so much
easier but it's also disgusting at the
same time wow
wow
disgusting
oh
ew ew
shut up
dell
are you
and they're so big my gloves are so huge
optimize your pc i don't have time to
optimize my pc right now don't you see
i'm busy
you shut up no drivers and outfits i
don't care dell
i don't care i'm streaming right now
give me a break
you add some more
water i got my sleeves
[Music]
add some more of that water
step by step
ah i'm losing and the batter is so heavy
i'm losing my gloves almost because the
batter like
tears tears down my gloves one oh my god
okay i didn't think i was struggling so
much with the batter
but it looks better than the other two
that i just used i feel like i'm making
bread or something
[Music]
i'm not saying the bad i used to have it
from my new life and saying that that is
heavy for my gloves okay
[Music]
this is [\h__\h] batter what the hell man
what am i doing wrong
i need that mixer
but you look
more water
[Music]
yeah okay get really in there i'm always
always too like too
careful when i
do stuff like this
i just really gotta get all in there
like i'm making like some pizza
or something like that pizza batter yeah
oh yeah
get in there get in there
yes
it has an interesting
thick texture it's like a slimy you know
those slime balls the stress
stress balls it's like similar to that
don't
i want to keep all my gloves wheels hi
jokers hi i just say hello to me by
rubbing herself against my legs this is
cute yes me i'll hang me up hi baby
sorry i'm making better right now
i'm busy okay
i'm massaging the batter yo you can get
your massage later
chances no not now
no no massage no junkies not now
yeah sorry
i can't
i need
[Music]
way there's so much [\h__\h] on my gloves
maybe i should wait a second what if i
use
my own hands i'm not showing it on the
webcam anyway
oh
that
makes so much sense now
wait a second i need to get all that
batter off of my
gloves somehow but it's sticking to my
gloves
[Music]
yeah
meow
maybe that was a wrong choice
[Music]
wait a second i'm trying to
get a little bit of the batter off of
the gloves and then i'll take them off
and i'll do it with my own hands
as my mom would probably do
my mom's probably angry at me for using
gloves in the first place
but i have to them generally i have to i
can't help it okay um
these gloves
belong into the trash
[Music]
but i have to say the batter smells
uh like batter is supposed to smell like
surprise
you you you you you you
[Music]
what
what is it
you're trying to say hi to my viewers
did you hear that
no
what is it
no hey baby
baby i love you too
i love you too
mama is busy right now mama can't give
you pets
okay [\h__\h] these gloves
okay wash my hands
one second
um i'll show you
uh
i'll show you in a moment
okay
okay wash my hands
[Music]
okay come here baby
okay
add the rest of the water
yeah
now mama is cooking
you disgusting i hate this i hate this
feel you
[Music]
hey it's denmark let's go yo do you hear
this
ew
[Music]
unintentional and smart it's not like
i'm trying to do asmr
[Music]
oh my god dude disgusting
i hate this this is why i don't like
making schnitzel
because i don't like the all the all the
breading batter on top of like in
between my fingernails and everywhere
it's disgusting
okay
okay all right mix it real good
quicksand mix of mac and cheese
that's a good um comparison yeah
okay
[Music]
sorry sorry
i'm so sorry the microphone is very
sensitive to movement
[Music]
it's
exhausting yo
um
[Music]
sorry
is gordon ramsay saying something i
can't see because my fingers are covered
in batter i can't see gordon
what did he say
meow
oh this sorry it started feeling good
actually like the whole bad end first it
was disgusting
he got banned
what
i think oh yeah this is a really
really nice consistency but it does look
like a little bit clumpy here and there
i wonder
if that's going to be an issue
[Music]
why is this so exhausting the
the battery is so heavy
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh wow this feels funny
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is a workout workout for my
little arms let's go
[Music]
okay i think this is enough i can't make
it i can't make it much better than that
this is like the best i can do
what are you doing
cat
trunks
stop playing near the kitchen
okay now get all of this [\h__\h] off of my
fingers
[Music]
she's playing with some piece of paper
on the ground
easily entertained cats don't need cat
toys
just need a piece of paper
one of my cat's most favorite toys
is
a scrambled up
ah
chocolate wrapping from um
very specific type of chocolate
there's no chocolate sticking to it but
she just realized that piece of
paper uh
kinder chocolate so
when i scrambled that up after eating
the chocolate
she um i throw it
she actually sometimes uh fetches
i throw it away
somewhere in the room and she follows
she runs and plays with it a little bit
she jumps around and attacks it
and plays soccer with it alone and then
she brings it back to me sometimes
it's so cute she like jumps up to my bed
with the with the
uh
scrambled up piece of paper in her mouth
so cute like half sticking out of her
mouth i can't get this batter off of my
fingers
oh wait i forgot the salt oh [\h__\h] i have
to mix it again
now let's just put more salt into the
mixture later when i when i um
i put salt into the cooking water and
then salt when we mix it with cheese
later because there's gonna be a lot of
cheese
okay can this [\h__\h]
leave my hands right now
oh my god
it's so sticky
it's so sticky i think we got the right
texture so even though it annoys me it
is
the way it's supposed to be
i just can't get it off of my hands i
don't want to waste it i don't want to
wash it all off
get off of me
ew
[Music]
okay
a little bit
[Music]
more
flour
no that would ruin it
sticky fingers you're sure okay
um this is disgusting
this is disgusting
[Music]
okay i think i'll wash my hands now
ew
chocolate
[Music]
it's everywhere
are you guys hungry
are you guys ready
for cooking
[Music]
yes
i see your comments
[Music]
that should be good enough
okay
now
put on my gloves again i don't think
i'll need my hands anymore i mean yes i
will always need my hands for cooking
but
not for not not my bare hands
[Music]
which side is this
very hungry
what are you making and a german slash
austrian dish when i'm making the
austrian variation of it
we discussed this already in the
beginning of the stream
it's very cheesy it's like
very like mac and cheese but
better
i know i know you all love mac and
cheese i know it's unbelievable but i
would say it's better
[Music]
glove number two
wait it takes a while because
when i took off the gloves all the
little fingers
of the glove
went backwards
inside
so now i have to
make it proper again
okay but not the not the plastic glove
the club club cloth glove clap club club
club
now smoothie is playing above that thing
okay
sleeve number one
slave number that's impossible no you
have to give it a chance same problem
with you guys and pineapples on pizza
you just don't you don't even give it a
chance
okay
um
and now we have
camera
cha-chang
look
[Music]
look the way it very very very slowly
goes down
it is very sticky
very sticky
it barely moves
yeah it's very thick
so so soft okay
so
[Music]
i need a big pot
oh let's get
that one
[Music]
shut up
okay
[Music]
hmm
i don't know
see i could have i totally could have
just you know
um
uh i could have
just
bought finished already ready to throw
in there
uh you know the noodle thingy i could
have already done that but i decided to
make it myself so that i can spend more
time with you guys
that was totally the reason yes yes
just wanted to spend more time with you
guys
and
and show you how it's done
because that's the very important part
here
showing you how it's done
so
sorry it's very noisy with this
microphone
we i will put some water
into
[Music]
the
pot of water
oh that's a lot of lot of salt
well that's okay we need a lot of salt
and uh i'm i'm um i
i am decently nervous but i'm under the
camera
[Music]
wait why is the camera not moving that's
so weird
did it like deactivate itself
activate
come on where are you
ah did i like disconnect it oh
did i locate disconnect it also
hello welcome
activate
where is it doco
hello
[Music]
camera
hello oh oh oh there it is so smoke
since when is that thing there why is
that so tiny
what happened with the resolution
[Music]
uh small
what the [\h__\h]
what is this what happened
let me reconnect it
that is so weird
[Music]
i'm so hungry i'm so hungry hungry
hungry
okay so uh let me see
let me see actually let me hide this go
to studio mode open it up again let's
see what we see when i do this
i'm sure
okay that actually
should in theory be fine for now
[Music]
let me get the tea
and
drink my tea while
putting this
okay so pop up
hooray
[Music]
so
um
carefully microphone moving sorry sorry
sorry
okay
now i will turn on the heat
yeah
right
let's do it to the
maximum
[Music]
and yeah when i will start putting in
the
the the banner into the cooking water i
will have to turn off the camera for a
moment because uh you know it's very
very reflective
what gordon what's with gordon gordon
lives
let's see
gordon i can't even be banned in peace
with all these bad cookies
oh man
oh this eric dude is also one of those
people right yeah yeah
let me drink my tea while i wait for
this [\h__\h] to cook i could also
cut onions hmm
[Music]
ah tea mmm
finally i can drink it
okay
so
i wonder if it's a problem that the
camera
is like next to the
plate like
stuff plate thingy that's gonna get hot
but it's it's like it shouldn't get hot
over there so it should be fine
[Music]
gordon's alive
did you hear that the way she like ran
and slipped
oh my god that wasn't loud meow
yeah we probably didn't hear that i kind
of heard it in my headphones but that
might just be
my dad might just be
me actually hearing it because i'm in
the same room
cook cook faster stupid water
don't waste my time
should have
started cooking it early on so the
recipe um
it says
it says to
put a lot of a [\h__\h] ton of
uh
salt
into
the water and make it cook
then
slowly put the
uh
the the batter
into my
spatula seed
and spatula sieve
and then
and push it into the salt water when
it's cooking and then i let it cook for
only two minutes and then i uh put it
into cold water and that's it and then
we put all of those
into
a frying pan where i first cook the
onions fry the onions a little bit
and then i add the
the specimen the noodle stuff then i add
a [\h__\h] ton of cheese and then i add uh
schnitzel what should love again in
stop running around so much
what schnitz loves in english
i forgot
i have forgotten
[Music]
i'm sure you guys know that
spring onions no that's not spring
onions
no
chives chives yes chives yeah
chives
chives i love chives
yeah well
that will give it a fresh
taste by adding that i bought fresh
chives so i have to i have to cut fresh
uh my chives and the onions actually
i could do that now uh
[Music]
i guess i will i guess i will um
it's a little bit of a mess here
uh i guess we can
in that case we can
[Music]
okay
so i actually also um
i bought a single new onion because i
didn't want to use the old onions even
though they're still here
i found a better onion
a white onion yeah fresh one
and chives
and i also got salad because
this dish is very filling at
hq
very filling and very cheesy so
combining it with a fresh salad is
really good so i bought salad but i i am
not going to make it on stream i
actually already have a finished
dressing i made a salad dressing
yesterday so i'm just going to throw
that over the salad and that's basically
it yeah but i i recommend eating it
together with um
you know
the salad so the water is getting close
to cooking and i will cut this onion
no i'm not i'm going to wash the onion
that was such a oh wait but i don't ugh
with gloves we did this last time okay
let me turn the camera
[Music]
the water is not cooking yet no
once again i'm taking off my gloves
because i don't wanna
i'm gonna cut these onions with
my gloves on
yeah so let me get rid of the first
layer here
[Music]
cook the water yes
yes
i am waiting for it to cook
also i finished watching uh this netflix
series that i was watching recently i
finished uh
i finished um
hey asmr appealing asm
i finished jane the virgin i have to say
um
all in all
it was a
great show
um
but i found it kind of ironic at the end
there was like an episode where all the
actors
talked about the show
for an hour and um
they kind of said like yo
there's so much going on in the show one
moment you laugh and the next moment you
cry and then yeah it's so emotional
there's so much going on and yes there's
a lot going on and there are a lot of
sad moments and a lot of funny moments
but but but
i have to say it never made me cry and
i'm the type of person who cries
constantly
it about any anything that goes on in
the show like anything makes me cry so
quickly so easily
so
i don't know it just the show never
really gave time to the
moments where you could cry
to really give the viewer time to
feel it
that is my my
my
feedback
like normally i cry so much when
watching movies and stuff
yeah
trying to peel this onion what the hell
man
why is it sticking here
yeah but the show is good so if you guys
don't have anything else to watch i i
recommend it um it's good but also
frustrating
they did something really um
not cool to one of my favorite
characters in the show
yeah my favorite note by the way petra
and michael
so
yeah
did anyone else watch the show
[Music]
right i'll check the comments
when the delay is
ready to show me the answers there it is
yes yes
no petra
what show it jane the virgin it's on
netflix
okay
i didn't get fart
cutting the onion okay uh
water is pretty much
cooking almost like it's cooking
slightly but i want it to cook a bit
more
[Music]
blue
baby
[Music]
let me drink some water
can you hear that
i hear it loud and clear
well
let me show you
[Music]
wow
have you ever seen that before
i will now proceed
to do the most important thing i'm gonna
make this better let's go okay so i know
how to do this
put this thing
on top of it yeah baby
oh it fits so nicely
it like kind of locks in place that's
nice
so and then
i use this tool oh yeah
i am a confident cook
i'm chef
chef
chef chef with this
okay
okay take some of the batter
take that batter ooh it's so sticky
so sticky
oh it's so sticky it won't leave the the
thing the mixing bowl
sticky sticky sticky sticky sticky
sticky sticky sticky
[Music]
wait if it's gonna be such a pain in the
ass to get it out of there in the first
place it's gonna be difficult okay okay
okay let me get another spoon to help
you here
oh it's really sticky
[Music]
okay okay maybe a bit more we need a bit
more a bit more what the hell is that
what the hell is that
what the hell is that in my batter
get out of there the [\h__\h] is that
where what is this
did it come from
yes me i'm busy
[Music]
okay
okay and i'm gonna already stop here
okay it's a little bit difficult to cook
when there's like a microphone right in
between me and the pot
and the camera is right next to the plot
okay so
oh this is hot well let me i have this
really cute thing really cute um
thing
[Music]
my oven mitten is a crocodile
yeah
oh this is so hot
what the [\h__\h]
oh it's so hot how am i supposed to do
this over over the cooking water when
it's so hot what what how the hell
oh it's so hot what the [\h__\h]
it's absolutely
it's so hot
hot
but it's working it's so hot though oh
ah it's so hot
it's not hard for me it's not hard for
me what the hell why would it be hard
for me
oh wait from this angle it works better
okay
i kind of want to show you a little bit
of that so
camera um baby should be fine yeah you
see that see what's going on there
yeah i cannot show you much but
[Music]
this is you basically you keep on moving
it on top of the cooking water
and it will drop in there and
immediately be cooked but i kind of
lowered the temperature a bit too much i
sure
i made it a bit higher again
[Music]
yes
good stuff
yeah it drips into the cooking water
really really cool tool
really useful see there's different ways
to make it i explained it a little bit
in front in the beginning of the stream
uh why are they so long now they're
supposed to be like
whatever it's gonna be fine they don't
really have to look pretty
they don't have to look nice
[Music]
technology yeah the other thing is a
preset i don't know how to say that in
english it's like
yeah you crash you crash the batter in
in a container and then
really long noodles get out of it as
nice but i prefer this tool because it's
the only tool i've ever worked with
and the way my mom always used to do it
and there's other dishes you we make in
in my country with this
type of noodle it's not a noodle i hate
calling it a little bit the only it's
the only comparable thing
oh yeah wait it's just a press oh say
more than english basically
okay
uh i think yeah it's time to put some
more batter in there
[Music]
more
still have a lot of batter
this is by the way for four people
portion wise with my lasagna i was able
to eat that lasagna for like
four or five days
it was a lot of lasagna i'm not a big
eater but
yeah for for big eaters it would
probably have been enough for two days
you okay super chat why super chat what
happened with the super chat
i will check
later on
i should
stop being such a sticky mess
oh god
all right let's put that
batter into the container
nice okay
and i continue
sliding
slide
out
this is the workout guys
[Music]
slide
and slide
why is it so heavy what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
my mom made this way faster like when i
she was like
whatever my mom made these why why the
the batter is so heavy though maybe i
have to oil this
this
thing tool that i'm using
noodle arms i wouldn't completely
blame it on the noodle arms okay
my batter is extra sticky and heavy okay
um now it's kind of faster okay i don't
know why i that it's hot hot hot hot
hot hot hot hot hot as [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
ah [\h__\h] what's happening there
okay
okay okay all right so hot oh my god
[Music]
and i think one problem is the angle i'm
doing this at so let me try to move this
a little bit you guys can't see it right
now anyway so
oh sure okay how about this um or how
about
how i move it like
like this
[Music]
okay yeah because i was mostly doing it
with my right hand right now and i am
left-handed so
yeah with the left hand it's a bit
easier
[Music]
how much more better okay we need more
batter we need more batter in there guys
more better
me me
i have a bit more i'll add this and then
i think
i'm mostly done
i hope that the noises are not too loud
guys because i know it's it gets a
little bit loud sometimes but
um
this microphone i don't i i have to get
used to it
there's like some noises that come out
really really loud
sounds sounds perfect really
it's all good
are you
no i will not do asmr
i am
i don't like asmr
good for everyone who likes asmr but
it's not my thing
i sure
okay
that must be the last
part of the batter
i sure
okay
okay a little bit more sliding
yeah
what a [\h__\h] mess this
[Music]
oh no
moving the microphone a little bit okay
ah yes
is this really cooking of course it is
what do you mean
of course it's cooking wait i think i
can show you a little bit of that
process
one second
[Music]
i hope it's okay that i have them in
there for more than two minutes
i think you're supposed to like if
you're as slow as i am i think you're
supposed to like in between
take out some of the um
[Music]
noodles
and then put them into the cold water
and then continue
but it should be fine should be fine i
don't really think there's an like i
don't think you can overcook
this type of noodle
probably
[Music]
and now i do the thing
what
hot
[Music]
hot hot hot
hot hot
[Music]
i can't do it anymore man
it's a it's a tough job out here
okay i'm done i'm down here
[Music]
i still love it but it doesn't go out
because because it's like so sticky like
i think it just wants to stay there okay
that's fine turning it up
[Music]
oh i'm so hungry i'm so hungry
okay
now get it off of their issue
and then
i know it looks a bit disgusting but
that's how it's supposed to be
[Laughter]
i i did it funny
i did it funny
oh wait no it's just not right i'm
supposed to go there probably hmm
[Music]
okay
um at the end
right this looks nice let me show you
[Music]
don't cook again don't cook again
this is what you get
now i throw this into cold water
okay
[Music]
looks nice huh i think it looks nice
okay
i'm going to rinse it
[Music]
nice
that was like the
most riveting part of this and now now
we go on to the next part and i need a
frying pan
[Music]
and
i will quickly cut the chives
one second uh i'll take out my gloves
again
to cut the chest real quick
give me a little moment
i'll make it quick i already throw the
uh
onions in here
[Music]
into the frying pan
yeah
oh my god microphone i'm so sorry i'm
i'm more sorry to the microphone than
them to you guys but sorry this must
have been really loud i'm so sorry i've
adopted the donk so sorry i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry was it really
loud i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
i'm bulk
i'm so sorry microphone
here i'll pet you here a said bar the
only asmr you'll ever get with me
[Music]
lots of chives
actually
i could have showed you this i didn't
really need to
take off my gloves right now
fresh
tea
[Music]
okay kiana is on a blast
i don't know about that
i don't know about that man
i want to watch the tribes
[Music]
but there's so much in my sink right now
okay
that's
that's all right are you guys gonna try
cooking this too i saw some people
tweeting at me that they want to know
the recipe so that they can cook with me
and sorry i didn't reply i saw you i saw
your comments but i didn't reply because
um
i didn't know until very soon to the
very close to the stream uh which recipe
i will actually be using
so
yeah i couldn't give you much of an
answer um but now
maybe at the end of the stream i will
add the the recipe the um
amount of like ingredients and stuff to
the description of the video
yeah that sounds like a good idea okay
i'm cutting shots now
cutting drums funny drums i love chives
you know it's really good um a simple
bread with butter
and chives on top you know what i'm
talking about guys
but like a dark uh we have like um
uh schwarzkopf it's like a dark
dark type of bread
and i think overseas like in america and
so on they don't have much of that like
i think it's more white bread
[Music]
but we have a lot of
really good bread and ah
really good bread with butter and chives
it's so simple
but it's so good
i i'm glad i see some
people in the
chat
yeah right rye bread i guess that's it
like
yeah just a darker type of bread
usually
[Music]
it's good that you don't see how i'm
cutting these right now because i am
again
not doing a
very safe way
of cutting like my fingers are
all out there
my fingers are like hi guys how's it
going
i want to be friends with you nice
yeah
my name is finger what's your name oh
knife oh cool
i never
never saw you here before are you here
often
well that's a lot of
a lot of chives it's gonna be
[Music]
okay
done
i'm gonna throw them in at the very end
though
i want them to be fresh
and
uh kind of like
i don't know not crispy what do you call
that
[Music]
okay
wait do i need to put in oil or butter
let me check my recipe oil i think it
was butter yeah three three spoons of
butter i think
yeah yeah yep
[Music]
yes no two spoons of butter
get some butter
[Music]
the writing for butter in german is the
same writing but we pronounce it
differently the more you know
okay
so
yeah butter what
[Music]
okay i think that's enough
a little bit more
okay
[Music]
you know this is really cool like the
cooking streams make me cook more
this is almost been a year
since i've joined her life almost next
week it's gonna be a full year
but
in this whole time i've been so busy
that i've barely like cooked stuff on my
own
and uh
yeah
it's just sad
[Music]
and now now the strings motivate me to
cook for you guys yeah and try new
recipes because i mean i've i've seen
this uh this recipe um
before like my mom made it many times
when i was young many many many times
but uh this is the first time i'm doing
it alone and once i know how to do it
properly i'm gonna make this every
[\h__\h] week because it's so yummy
ah when i need the cheese ready okay i
have 200 grams of a specific cheese
called a bag casey it is quite
quite the strong cheese very um
aromatic
uh it's it's mountain cheese basically
translated wow so if you want to try
making this just get some a nice
nice cheese not the boring type of like
gaoda and so on normally i would go for
stuff like that too
but
this is not the right
one to use in this case so now let me
actually you know what i think i can
show you
um
okay that's fine but let me put on my
gloves again
[Music]
gordon
chatting again
[Music]
nice slice cutting oh are you admiring
my onions
yeah i can cut onions
[Music]
okay
gloves are back up ready to go alrighty
[Music]
today i'll actually show you this
process last time i didn't because i
thought the whole um
um this this uh
this this stuff here
is gonna make it difficult to see and
the all of the heat is gonna be like it
stressed me out anyway it already
stressed me out more than it was
necessary so i don't want to stress
myself out anymore and break any of the
equipment
but
yeah it's fine it's fine today it's fine
[Music]
i want to show you some stuff you know
you hear that sizzling
yeah they are quite
chunky yes yeah that's okay it's okay
they're allowed to be chunky
you're also chunky chunky you're allowed
to be chunky as well
just like chunkers
i was just talking about you i was just
talking about your baby i'm so [\h__\h]
hungry
meow i need to open this bag of sheets
yum yum
oh that's quite stinky yeah that's the
way i was looking for you need really
stinky cheese
oh it's stinky
oh very stinky
okay i'm gonna throw in
um
not sure if i'm supposed to throw it out
i guess yeah but not all the cheese at
once okay
[Music]
some of these are kind of long
oh that's that's a lot
okay
so
i know it all just looks like one color
at this point
it's like almost overflowing i want to
be careful
to not drop it
ah
be careful
mix it a little bit usual
i already dropped something never mind
it'll last forever
looks delicious well this is nothing
just just yet
nothing the cheese will make it
delicious it's so simple it's such a
simple recipe
you don't we really don't need many
ingredients too
what did i need flour eggs
and salt
um butter
onions
cheese
and chives
that's i think about it that's all
for sure
okay
so
now i will start adding in the stinky
cheese
oh it's something else
but it will taste so good
trust me
oh by the way i got i got roasted onions
to top it with you have to top it with
roasted onions i bought them though
because i don't i didn't want to make
those myself
yeah
see now if you were to make the german
version of this you would put it in the
oven
uh but yeah here we don't do that we
don't put it in the oven
all right so stinky
[Music]
stinky stinky very stinky
okay
okay more cheese
you don't have to use this exact type of
cheese so no worries if you can't find
it but
yeah just some kind of stinky aromatic
aromatic uh
cheese will suffice
so chisel don don
still not done you need 200 grams of
cheese
oh my god my hands are exhausted
standing is so exhausting on its own
i'll turn it no no i think the
temperature is probably fine
it's okay to
get it a little bit crispy here and
there
that's fine you can go for like a really
creamy
finish or you can go for a little bit of
a crispy finish i i have eaten both
versions and they're both delicious yes
no pineapple no no no pineapple in this
one
oops i dropped a lot of onions there oh
well
oh it's so stinky
okay
and
more cheese
i just put all of that in there yeah
lots of cheese oh yeah it's just yellow
the camera is like
it makes it too bright
damn
i need a bigger frying pan
[Music]
more cheese
so i talked about this in my member
stream but there's a version of this
dish i mean it's actually pretty
different so uh
yeah it's just a different dish but you
still you still use these kind of
noodles as the base
and make you add spinach in it and then
they will be green all of these noodles
will be green and then you um kind of
uh
you make a cheese
sauce to go with that and kind of
um dunk it in there like really top it
up with all that cheese sauce
and some ham in the cheese sauce and
actually the ham is i guess with the
with the noodles
with the spinach spatula
yeah and that is called should be not
knocking with cases
i love that like i hate spinach
but this is the only the only food
that's made out of spinach that i will
actually eat
well these are so heavy oh my god and it
really when you eat this dish it feels
just as heavy in your stomach
spinach eh
what do you mean
should be not
spinach
okay i think we're pretty much done here
and
we will serve it we will add some color
to it in a minute just wait
okay
i'll turn off the heat because i think
it doesn't need to be in here much
longer
it doesn't move it just wobbles wobble
wobble
let me show you
wow
yeah that's better
it's not too dark uh not too bright oh
look at that
look at those specs left
you can try to roast them a little bit
um with if i had like a different frying
pan my mom said that i should try to
like
roast it like yeah but with this frying
pan it's difficult
i'm fine with the with the with this
kind of finish yeah i'm fine with that
okay
[Music]
okay now
i will take a plate
[Music]
yeah
and sorry i'm moving the microphone
now
i put
some of my cheesy ass
spatula
onto the plate
[Music]
hell yeah
oh very cheesy
[Music]
cheesy
cheese who doesn't like cheese man
so heavy okay
and
wait i will show you
i will show you
[Music]
and then
a lot of
chives
[Music]
yeah and
one of the ingredients that i didn't
show you yet
i just bought these uh
[Music]
rest sweet bell
it's a
roasted onions and
they're really nice
they only had it in these huge
huge packages for some reason
um but it looks like it looks like this
[Music]
so we sprinkle that
on top of it as well
to give it a little bit more taste as
well
and
voila although i like yeah it's crunchy
yeah
maybe more
can't have enough of that
i'm going to be a few more chives
voila
easy
you can make this much faster than i did
i wasted a lot of time here
but there it is there it is you see that
beauty
[Music]
yes
see the the creamy cheesy er special
topped with some fresh colorful chives
and then
enhanced with some crunchy roasted
onions
it's a ducky mess
and now i will taste it
here
can you not like
cats
i'm streaming here okay don't make a
mess out of my apartment
i will give it a taste now but i will
finish eating it off stream if that's
okay for you guys because i cannot calm
down uh while i'm streaming so
let me
take a little a little taste i shall
ah
you see that
wow
you know those uh those japanese or i
guess not only japanese but i know them
from japanese programs where they give
you this really close close-up of the
um food but it's like shaking always
let's dig in
mm-hmm
[Music]
could use
more salt
[Music]
but besides that
i think
um i basically nailed it
let me eat a little bit more i'll add
some salt afterwards
[Music]
okay
now this with a salad with a fresh green
salad yeah let's go
[Music]
yummy but definitely needs a bit more
salt so
i hope you guys
can give it a try it's really really
easy as you have seen
um
yeah i mean making the spatula you need
a special tool for it but i think you
could find it even overseas i think or
you can find maybe something similar i
don't know um
yeah yeah good luck with that i crave
foof hello then go get some food
[Music]
a cheese grater
i guess that that could probably
somehow work as well but you don't have
this little container that i had on top
of it right to slide it from one side to
another but you can maybe even make it
yourself i don't know
if you're crafty like that you could
probably make it yourself
but it's really yummy and it's really
filling so even uh somewhat small
serving will get you very far believe me
it is very very filling and just to be
clear again i explained this a million
times already but i don't want my german
friends on the other side of the border
to be angry at me so
i will say
that uh they're this dish casa spezza is
german but i made an austrian version of
it okay it's called actually kazna okay
cast nothing
here we call it cast note when we make
it a little bit differently okay it's
not if you go if you google it on
wikipedia it says it is yes indeed from
the very land but also from uh to all
and for ibag and saxbook and so on so
please don't get mad at me okay i love
germany i love you i love you guys over
there you guys are really cool yeah
especially
sharing is caring okay
so
um yeah
yeah thank you guys for watching today
tomorrow we have minecraft i will read
all the super chats tomorrow and let's
just have a chill stream tomorrow um
also oh yeah on sunday sunday one
schedule uh uh one stream that's not on
my schedule currently will be added to
that before the unarchived karaoke
therefore i will move the unarchived
cuddle get to one hour later so i have a
little bit more of a um you know breva
breathing time in between um but yeah uh
if you look on my twitter i i wrote the
times there
and it will be at i think 9 a.m est um
10 p.m jst
3 pm my time gmt plus 2 there is a
somewhat big collaboration
with mostly japanese members and i will
stream my point of view on my channel i
will not give out any more details
because
i am not the one organizing it
but i was invited to it and i was really
excited i i had to squeeze it into my
schedule even though i already have a
really really full schedule this week
and but i had to squeeze it in there
because i cannot say no to that no no
way
so
we need
[Music]
and yeah
so tomorrow oh yeah also megacon not
megacon uh uh fan expo boston
is the next one this week i'll be on
phoenix for boston
on saturday
with ina
er ame will be with ina on friday and i
will be with inna on
saturday yes so if you happen to be
there it's yeah it's basically the same
thing as megacon and like a q a but
uh this time with inna together
so like a dual q a you can even ask both
of us the same question or you can give
us
yeah different questions per person
if you're there then please check it out
it will not be streamed it will only be
for the people who are at the convention
yeah
okay double travel yeah
it will be
fun because like uh last time it was uh
45 minutes and i think it will be only
45 minutes this time as well so there is
not much time um
uh and there is two people
that you can ask questions so
[Music]
both me you know i'm gonna do our best
to answer as many questions as possible
i hope yeah
okay so
i will i think
leave it there and try to enjoy my food
in in peace but i think we already made
progress
with uh the cooking stream the whole
uh you know setup and everything i hope
you enjoyed it i'm gonna do more it will
not be a weekly thing but maybe like
bi-weekly or so and uh i will try to do
like more austrian food but we don't
have so many dishes that are from
austria
originally anyway because austria
basically
you know
uses
so many dishes from all over the place
europe just you know is a big mix of
food
yeah
so i'll i'll try to
do some other dishes as well um dishes
yeah foods as well
maybe try to make japanese food as well
sometime
thank you for the stream thank you for
watching
thank you thank you sweetheart
ah yeah right that's a
quite a
popular
austrian uh dish sweetheart is like the
favorite food from my brother
not my favorite but it's definitely
yummy definitely very tasty
[Music]
yeah thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you oh oh oh schnitzel one day
i want to make schnitzel um because the
real schnitzel comes from austria see
this is this is how like you know
schnitzel also uh you can also get
little in germany and they
eat it with different sides and stuff
but if you want to get the real deal you
gotta
you gotta gotta get potential to cook it
for you hey
yeah
yeah so
yeah being a
yeah i love you too i love you too thank
you for watching thank you
thank you
so
i hope it's okay to leave you guys here
thank you wait let me let me wave
[Music]
let me wait
oh my god stay there
like the queen
[Music]
bye bye bye bye bye bye
i'll give you a hug by the way because
cali did that too at some point
[Music]
that's difficult but here there you go
uh
yeah if we were in skyward sword right
now then they would say this is a bomb
but no it's not it's a heart okay
anything else you want me to do
um piece one here numbers numbers for
your memes number one
number two
number
three
number four
number five
okay use it however you want to use it
it's your choice
[Music]
but i don't know how to like you do like
oh
[Music]
bang
my baby shut me down
how do you do jiu-jitsu
thing
i can't do it
i'm i'm not naruto
i'm not sasuke eva
i'm none of these people
[Music]
come
yeah i could do that one oh here
ah you look through it haha do you guys
see that overseas too or is that one of
our weird cultures
like children here in this country like
to show each other these holes and then
when you like when you get the other
person to look into it you like hit them
and you're like haha you looked into it
got him
you look this one i got you you looked
into it again didn't you
i got it
let me show you hide a heart again
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah
yes
potential improves
[Music]
good
okay guys i hope you had fun uh got em
you'll know what to say in the end
we all know
and enjoy what we say
got him
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know how to wave like this
who waves like that who waves like that
no one does bye-bye
[Music]
double gobble
bye
[Music]
wait it doesn't look so good because i
have to like bend my
bend my whole arm like this
ah there you go
you guys know this kind of light that's
a high too okay
[Music]
wait can i show you something
okay one second let me get it
[Music]
foreign
okay okay again
okay i will just i just want to flex i
just want to flex here
hi too
whole live version
no no
no it got they're really good i love
high to hygiene is a japanese snack
and so it comes inside it's not only
but i see this is a
this is
[Music]
all the way around this way
cute
this is a
sky berry oh taste whatever that is it's
really yummy though
and then we have
[Music]
mogu mogul
which is a blood orange taste yeah all
of these are really yummy yeah
wait that's it right yeah yeah three
pretty different
tastes yeah i just wanted to flex real
quick
[Music]
you