[Music]
[Applause]
christmas
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
i i'm i was confused i thought i had no
more time
which i was actually hoping to have more
time because
um i wasn't even quite ready to be
honest because i just got back
uh
from outside
and i still had to censor some photos
that i'm going to show you
um
i did it now and while while we were
doing the loading screen maybe that gave
you guys enough time to
what
i i tweeted the wrong link
what link did i tweet
[\h__\h] what what link did i tweet
i didn't accidentally tweet my
what the [\h__\h] did i tweet
oh that's
oops [\h__\h] i'm so confused
i'm so confused
okay
started already
uh
early start
whoopsie doodles
please come
i'm i'm i'm like
uh
oh i s oh i see what i did
like and normally i retweet my tweet and
then copy paste
the link from that tweet and i see i did
the i did the one from yesterday
oopsy doodles
i'm so confused i'm so
all over the place
i am a scrambled
phoenix right now not in the scrambled
egg i'm scrambling phoenix
[Laughter]
okay oh my god so much to talk about so
much to talk about so much to talk about
someone to talk about so much to talk
about so much to talk about
where do i start
well uh i have photos so we'll talk
while looking at the photos i guess
[Music]
story time
oh yeah and actually oh [\h__\h] i forgot
how do i do that or maybe i
maybe i keep it for another stream
because um uh today i went to
um
as you may have seen on twitter i went
am i not lagging today
wait i just noticed i'm not lagging am i
not lagging
i'm not lagging on my side
oh my god
let's go i don't know how i did that i
didn't change anything from yesterday
then oh is not accurate
then um i don't know
it's a lie let's
get that out of the way
okay so i was saying that actually
um i was at
uh aniplus in seoul today you know where
they have the collaboration cafe
and i will talk about that if i get to
that if it doesn't take me too long
but
um
uh they gave me besides
besides giving me
every single piece of merchandise even
the ones that they didn't have in stock
because they're doing
it so that every day i guess maybe not
every day but like
you know every once in a while they
change what they have in stock you you
remember how many different
items they have there
um when that when they first announced
it i showed it off
they actually only have like a really
relatively small part of that um
available each day
uh not the whole
like not every item is there so they
they update on twitter like what they
have every day
um so anyway they gave me everything
though and i was prepared to pay for it
but they gave me everything for free
whoa
and uh
uh what was i gonna say oh yeah and
they also gave me
um some like snacks korean snacks i
suppose
uh as like a sashi ide like a sweet um
welcome gift i guess
now uh
i'm thinking because i wanted to take
pictures of them before i eat them
to let you know what i'm eating i was
thinking of doing it during this stream
but now i forgot so maybe i'll probably
stream one more time
before i leave so we can just snack
uh
in the next stream i guess
and then one more thing i wanted to say
just in the beginning because we might
not even get to the topic of any plus i
want to but
just in case we don't get there um
someone
i i was signing things there and someone
stole a post-it that i signed because
there was a wall with like post-its you
know and before i left i was like wait
can i try writing a post-it too and we
put it at the very very very top left i
couldn't even reach it i had someone
stand on a stool
like
not even like the the male staff members
could reach it without standing on a
stool which is why i'm wondering how did
someone steal it someone must have
gotten on the stool in order to take it
um or it fell down because post-its are
not very sticky aren't they um but
whatever so i put at the very very very
top left and
um
uh someone took it apparently so
uh what i wanted to say is like
maybe
i will give the person the benefit of
the doubt that no it's not it's okay
don't don't be sorry i will give the
person the benefit of the doubt that
they did it
thinking that it was okay maybe because
whoever finds it you know uh do we have
a saying in german i don't know how it
is in english how you say it but whoever
finds it
uh owns it
[Laughter]
maybe you know maybe they went by that
principle um
so i just want to make it easy for the
person to return it
by saying oh yeah find the skippers
i just want to say
it's okay you can still make it right
and i can understand that even if you
feel bad about it now that it's
difficult to return it directly so my
offer is that you go to the cafe
and then you know
when you eat something there maybe
slip it under or on your tray when you
return it or you know just slip it
somewhere you don't have to directly
give it back and then you know feel the
shame you know
when they are angry at you just maybe
you know you slip it somewhere where the
staff will find it you know
you know that would be cool
and and i i forgive i forgive okay
uh if that's
if that that would be nice if you if you
i don't know that will even reach the
person but if you're listening
please
do it
and
yeah i mean i can rather never post it
but
uh i don't know when i can
get
to the store again or if i can organize
having someone pick it up from the store
so i don't know it's a bit complicated
so it would be easier if you just give
it back please thank you
yeah
so
and that was that that's just something
i wanted to say before we begin
it's okay i'm not mad just a little bit
disappointed
because oh i didn't think this would
happen
so
uh but i'll take it as a
compliment that i am popular
[Laughter]
thank you
for
um
not stealing it to everybody who didn't
steal it thank you
well who said maybe they didn't steal it
you know maybe in their head they didn't
steal it maybe they
won it by finding it
so
okay
besides that
um
so um part two this is part two
basically because yesterday i didn't
have so much time
the reason why i said i had to leave
early and sleep soon
wake up early
was because today this morning
very early i went to annapolis in the
morning before the opening time
they picked me up they sent me
um a car
and
with a staff member from anaplast and
also
actually one pro-life
english staff member
is uh
was there too so yeah so
yeah i was well
protected and then yeah i arrived there
i did this and that and then bleep blue
will get there maybe um but uh i have to
start from the beginning
let me get my notes
[Music]
and turkey
um
[Music]
it's okay stop apologizing it's okay
i mean i signed a lot of other things
and those can hardly be stolen
so it's okay
it's okay not really
that job if it comes back if it doesn't
then
oh well maybe i can sign another one and
they can like i don't know nail it onto
the wall
or i don't know
we'll see we'll see
so yesterday i talked about
everything up to the arrival
at the hotel right i didn't get very far
uh
[Music]
that's where i got so okay
uh okay okay here we go here we go story
time has begun are you guys ready
are you guys ready it's gonna be a long
one
let me make some space for photos i'll
be in
here
ready okay
i feel awkward
oh this is good it's good
this is good i wish i had my
i mean i'm probably
i probably do have my
usual layout somewhere but
time to set it up again
busy all day
making the most out of
the days that i have
okay very good
that looks like a little bit like the
drink from
gouda that i got color wise
okay
i feel awkward because i i'm not even
wearing headphones
or earphones it's so
when you're used to streaming every day
with a feedback in your ear it is
incredibly weird not to have that
i don't know you guys can probably not
relate but
yeah
so
okay
so we arrived at the hotel
and actually i had a i had a little um
souvenir for nabi mama and i've recently
discovered that
i have a go-to souvenir now because
everybody who gets it loves it i used to
bring people the mozart balls most of
the time
because they're just a classic
but
i personally don't even like them that
much so
more than the moza balls i feel like the
sakha the little sakha cakes
um have proved themselves
to be even more popular
well i mean it could be different but
you know um we have a famous
cake yeah in
austria it's called sakha torte
oh thank you hank
i roommate super chats once i'm back
home i think
uh just so you know
oh [\h__\h]
chad already died here okay no hyper
chat this is what happens
it's like a chocolate
chocolate cake with some jam apricot jam
in between but the chocolate is so rich
and
it's really good so
um actually there's like
at the airport in austria there's always
like these uh saka cakes small ones that
you can bring as a souvenir and it's a
chocolate cake so even when you travel
like 10 hours they're totally fine
afterwards you know
so
yeah i brought three little
pieces
the same ones that i brought to dana by
the way i brought them to nabi mama
and we ate them together actually
because uh
i i gave them to her when we were in my
hotel room and she was like wanna eat
one too and i'm like hell yeah thanks
for asking
i think i was really hungry too yeah it
was oh my god i was so hungry i remember
now
we were we were starving or i was
starving so that little little piece of
chocolate cake
saved me for the moment
we had it with my japanese friends in
the hotel itself yes yes yes that's
where the original is from i mean you
can get it in other places too
but yeah the original is from the sakha
hotel which is why it's called
saka
but even the non-originals that you get
in austria are usually pretty damn good
too so i wouldn't say that this is
something where you have to get the
original but
especially because they are also kind of
overpriced i guess
but yeah
uh anyway
so we ate that and lovey mama really
liked it i was worried you know i asked
her before i came to korea if she likes
chocolate
um and sweet stuff and she said yeah
she said i'm on a diet but yes
and i'm like you [\h__\h] [\h__\h] diet is that
fat noise oh yeah sorry that's my laptop
is it too loud it's [\h__\h] loud man i'm
sorry i'm sorry hope it's not too
bothering
uh but yeah
where was i
let me make the btm a bit louder
[Music]
i kept on telling her that she
uh shouldn't be dieting
it's like
i feel like every
japanese and every korean girl is always
on a diet
[Laughter]
i told navi mama in my whole life i've
never been on a diet before
[Music]
i couldn't i don't even have the
discipline for that
anyway so she ate the chocolate cake and
she loved it
she was like fascinated said it was
really delicious so i was really happy i
was glad because saka cake it is
pretty
strong
chocolate taste
pretty rich
and very view you eat a few bites and
your mouth feels like
it's overwhelmed with chocolate
yeah but she liked it i had a
a good one too
so then actually i think right after
that
uh you know i told nabi mama that i
wanted to get a massage after the flight
um
and originally she wasn't gonna
get a massage
too but
she
spontaneously decided to join me on my
massage so
hell yeah it was like evening time like
i think it was like 5 p.m 6 p.m or so
no i didn't go to gym children
no but we found a nice massage place
that had really good ratings and even
apparently was on tv before
um
what
i'm scared because obs problem or wi-fi
what do you mean my connection is fine
isn't it
you should if you can
i don't know what they mean
okay
i don't know i'm confused don't confuse
me i'm already confused
okay
that reminds me before i forget it
because i didn't write this down
i i was outside today and i found
like at least
four different koreans who are like
uh irl streaming on twitter wherever i
don't know where but they were talking
to their phones and i saw the chat on
their screen
four different and four different
occasions today there's so many irl
streamers here i've never seen that
anywhere else before
like not not in that
amount
holy [\h__\h]
yeah
lots of irl twitch streamers i guess
but they were all in the same street
though they were all in hongdae because
i went to hongdae again today
yeah
i actually
i probably was
uh
behind them like on the screen
probably
in several occasions because i was
walking by that was like what is what
are they doing on their phone what are
they doing
um
travel streamers no i don't think they
were travel streamers but
they're really hip yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes it started early i'm so sorry
i'm sorry i forgot like i don't know i i
wasn't sure when i'm starting
uh
yeah photo bombing i was probably photo
bombing
so anyway
uh where was that oh yeah so we got a
massage at this cool place and uh they
were really really really nice in there
and the dude he even was able to speak
the reception she was even able to speak
japanese so we were talking in japanese
and and yeah it started with a foot bath
and then we got the massage in the same
room and
uh they they it was like a um partially
oil massage but not quite
um it was so good because i was also so
tired so i was so relaxed
oh it was so good that was one of the
best massages i've ever had
amazing i wanna i wanna go there again
before i leave
it was really good
oh my god
yeah and oh my god actually
lobby mama
said that that was basically
the first massage in her whole life
besides once when she was like nine
or 11 years old or so
but since then she said she never had a
massage and i'm like what the hell
you probably going to get addicted now
and want to do it more often
i've gotten like a million massages at
this point in different countries
yeah i hope she enjoyed it too like i i
for someone who doesn't normally do that
you know must be quite nice too oh nice
experience i never had a massage before
never go i never had one oh my god yeah
once i started getting massages
i couldn't stop anymore i was always i
mean i also have well um
chronic pain so
that's why i get so many massages
partially not partially i guess that is
the reason
[Music]
yeah
so
now i can't stop anymore always thinking
about massages
yeah
mush my muscles until they're nothing
until i have no bones left break my
bones please
okay so so we did that and then um i was
so hungry so i just wanted to eat
something close by
um
and then just you know i just wanted to
rest
um so we didn't think too much about
what to eat i just really wanted
something something anything
[Music]
so
we got
now this is not really korean food so
i'm a bit ashamed that the first thing i
ate wasn't even korean food i'm sorry
but nabi mama did say it's like a korean
version of it because
it's not so common in japan probably
because it's japanese food but like a
korean version of it so please don't be
angry
why am i goblin
i i like to gobble gobble gobble gobble
[Music]
it's katsu my favorite food
but with a [\h__\h] ton of cheese inside oh
and apparently that was
you know i think i've seen katsu with
like very very thin
layer of cheese before in japan
but this
that was so much
cheese
that was a lot of cheese so that made it
more korean
[Music]
okay
no well there's no ham inside so
not really no ham
cheese counts as korean food
yeah i guess uh they like cheese don't
they
um
korean katsu is a bit different you had
legit korean food oh
i'm okay i'm happy to hear that because
nami mama also said that like i was
worried like oh my god i come here and i
eat japanese food i'm so sorry but
um i couldn't wait anymore i need needed
food and nabi mama did say that it's
kind of like
koreanized i guess um
oh and it also didn't come with the
typical
tonkatsu sauce it came with like a
different
sauce
uh that was a bit more on the spicy side
but like not
like fiery spicy um
yeah yeah yeah
okay so that was that my first first
picture
get out of here
okay and i think after that i just went
tried to go to sleep yeah i i took
actually oh i took a shower already
while navi mama was in the hotel room
because i couldn't take it anymore i
felt so stinky
yes i took a shower before that already
and then i went back to the hotel
and then i
i
i don't know i don't remember everything
is blurry after that
i think i just went to sleep after
watching some
some stuff on my ipad
yeah
okay so
day number two
or kind of number one if you don't count
the day of my arrival but let's say day
number two
uh
in the morning
or like around around i think it was
around noon time actually
navi mama picked me up at the hotel
[Music]
and then we went uh with public
transport you know i gotta use up
all the money i put in that [\h__\h] card
um and we went to the palace what was it
i don't want to say it wrong what was it
again
go
kill
different writings in the chat even
young
palace
i'm still very
uncertain when i pronounce things so i
feel um not so confident have confidence
but no no no competence
[Music]
yes so we went there but
um actually so uh because uh
a viewer told me that there's a palace
that where i go when i go there in a
handbook the entrance will be free and i
mentioned that to nabi mama because she
didn't know and i was like do you know
do you know the palace you know uh where
you can enter for free if you wear
hanbok we should do that so that's what
we did on that day
ah
palace ah
the gong is
oh you didn't know
it's true
yeah you can enter for free
so uh we went to the link the closest
station and then
when you arrive there there's actually
like a lot of
handbook rental places
and they're all
so cheap i remember
in japan when i did uh
i think it was in asakusa
asakusa
yeah uh where
i did uh a kimono rental before and it
was really expensive
but then
here the hanbok was so cheap
big difference man
there was a big price difference yeah
and you even could enter something for
free so hell yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah so we entered one
place and then we actually
we got matching
handbooks yeah i chose something first
and then navi mama chose a matching like
the same
um set but in a different color
variation
yeah
but we got matching ones
and i think it was the prettiest
combination that they had like first
they make you choose like the the skirt
part which is like a really long
really long dress pretty much that
starts under your boobies and then goes
all the way to the bottom
first you choose that and then you chill
choose a matching top
and then the lady helps you to put it on
and she was so fast oh my god it was
also much faster than putting on a
kimono
but they have she like first
she makes you like put on this big big
big um
like a ring skirt
kind of like a
petticoat but
uh
not quite because it's
just completely empty inside it's just a
big ring i don't know what's the right
name for that anymore i don't know
anymore
like a ring skirt i don't know you know
what i mean the hoop yeah hoop skirt
and then on top of that she puts like a
fluffy
uh frilly
um
skirt and then script and then on top of
that she puts the actual skirt and then
on top of that
uh like some kind of top to where
underneath the actual top so it's a few
layers but all the layers are really
thin
and
uh
it's actually comfortable like not
uncomfortable definitely not
uncomfortable
um
and i thought you know the fabric would
be a little bit
more uncomfortable or thick or
or hot but no it was
fine pretty airy airy especially the
the
the skirt
it was really airy
and
it was just a bit weird to move because
you always have to lift up the huge
skirt when you
go upstairs or if you pass by someone
there's no space it's kind of awkward
because you bump into people makes you
so wide at the bottom
yeah the weather forecast so far has
been wrong every day
today as well it was supposed to rain
the whole day or and then it changed to
rain the half day and then it didn't
really it didn't really rain at all when
i was outside and i was outside pretty
much the whole day i think it only
rained once when i was in the train
maybe because when i left the train
then i saw like puddles outside but so i
maybe just
absolutely dodged it but
no no not really
raining so thank god
yeah i was right chill
[Laughter]
i was wide
i think that's because of you
thank you yeah i really hope it's um
it i i hope for the best for tomorrow
because tomorrow is where it actually is
the most important to me
that it doesn't rain but we will see
so we wore the handbook yeah and then we
went they also they also did my hair
because there's like typical hairstyles
that you get for
a
hamburg so they did my hair in like a a
braid one braid and they stuck all kinds
of accessories into it
uh and they kind of
extend your braid your hair length
with like a ribbon
that's not quite a ribbon
i don't have a photo of the handbook for
you guys sorry but maybe you can look it
up what it looks like normally um
so and then we walked over to the palace
and
it was so big i will show you i have
pictures of i took pictures of the
palace it was by the way so humid and
pretty hot
um
[Music]
wait where are the pictures
okay here
wow
so
here we have the entrance the front
entrance it's in front of a big street a
big like
crossing
really big
wow
so cool and then maybe we can see
uh if i zoom in again
do you see
[Music]
hold on this picture has it's not really
well captured but you see um in the
middle of the entrances you see some
like the one the guy in the blue thing
with the flag and then on the middle
entrance you see someone in red
right you can roughly see it actually
these people were like guards and the
one had a flag but the others had uh
like spares
really
badass long spares with like a blade
spares spears
britney spears
sp spears spares
yeah they had weapons anyway in any case
they had long
long cutlery
really long weapons wasn't sure if they
were real but i guess they were probably
real real
spear space
you know what i mean
long knives
oh some of them are actually korean guys
fulfilling the mandatory conscription i
don't know what conscription means you
mean something like military or so
is that part of it
is that part of the job that
they have to do for military
[Music]
so maybe some of the korean bros who are
currently in military service who said
goodbye to me
maybe maybe they saw me here
[Laughter]
not the guards the guards are full-time
soldiers
so what does the military people do
oh well
more similar to halberd yes that's what
i mean
getting to be a ceremonial guard while
conscripted yeah cool
[Music]
so we walked past them and went inside
and i didn't know what to expect because
i didn't look it up before but
this place is huge
so big oh my god so you you right after
that gate what you see is this
okay
an insanely big square which in the
middle basically is empty
and
[Music]
you have to go over there to the next
gate and there were several of those
areas until you came to the main part of
the palace
uh on this like the problem here is
it's a lot of walking if you want to
look at the whole palace and there's not
much shade you will go through a lot of
areas
with
blazing sun on you so i was
getting at some point a [\h__\h] heat
stroke i was so dehydrated because
uh there was also
not a single
a place where you could buy water or
drink water or ice cream or anything
there's no food no no water you can buy
nothing while you're in the palace
but at some point i was really starting
to feel dizzy and so weak
because i had no no no water left
um because i left my bottle of water in
the hamburg place because the bag they
also gave us a little bag
um
that the the the water didn't fit into
the bag so i just didn't bring it
i thought maybe i can get some water
there i i expected there to be something
you know
yeah i didn't think i would suffer that
much but it was really really really
really bad i really thought that i was
gonna faint around the end
um
yeah it was crazy we even we took little
breaks and sat down here and there
because there's some nice places to sit
down
and and look at the the big stuff i'll
show you some more
but it was really painful nabi mama was
suffering too but
she didn't seem
as much in pain as i was
so the main thing i guess was probably
this i assume like after you pass for
like two or three of those gates
you come to this oh this is flipped
oh nanda it's not flipped in my
preview
oh [\h__\h] that's the wrong flip
[Music]
180 there you go
what what wasn't it just the right way
there you go okay
okay so this is
uh
the side view
was the side i think it's the side view
we were sitting like on the side uh
uh in in some shade
here there's shade on the bottom trying
to chill
trying to cool down
and um
yeah impressive architecture naturally
flipped
yeah
it was so cool
like i like the the green
the greens
green architecture
really cool like roofing the under the
structure of the roof like on off the
bottom of the roof you like see
oh oh my god it's so cool
do you see this
yeah they had that kind of like
architecture
in in like all of the small buildings
like there were a lot this this whole
it's like a whole garden like the whole
palace grounds
have like several smaller buildings too
it's all connected and yeah blue sky wow
yeah impressive uh incredible
it was actually good weather
so then i went and i went up there
and uh
inside i took a picture of inside i
didn't go inside but why is it flipped
again
why'd you do that
[Music]
so yeah you can like
go this close
let's see what's done
without entering
and wow
look at that look at that roof what look
at the ceiling
oh [\h__\h]
that was so cool
look at that
what are those
[Music]
phoenix wrong
is it actually called phoenix front what
no way
ah so this part i think is
uh past the entrance where you would
have to buy a ticket but i got free
without because we have a handbook we
had a handbook so we got fruit for free
and actually on the way
um
i guess because we looked so fabulously
beautiful and cute we were actually
asked for like pictures from uh
from some foreign girls some foreigners
asked oh can we take a picture of you
guys you guys are so pretty i'm like
i look at nami when she looks at me
we're like looking at each other like uh
uh
i guess
kind of like
we both didn't know what to do but but
i i figured that they probably you know
just you really really wanted just a
picture because we were looking pretty
and they have no idea who we are
definitely no idea who we are
uh and then afterwards they asked like
uh because i asked
no wait the thing was like i heard from
their accent when they were speaking
english
that they were german so i asked them
where you from and they said germany and
then i uh talked a little bit with them
in german
german tourists yeah and
then they asked me
where i got the hamburg from and i
explained it to them and because i
didn't know
where to get them i explained it maybe
they got themselves a handbook
themselves yeah
what are the odds yeah i asked
we talked to actually like a lot of
foreigners while we were there and i
asked everybody where they're from and
uh i got a lot of statistics now
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
their english was actually pretty good
i'm not saying that their english was
like all so obviously german
um but i heard like a hint a hint of
you know and also looking at them yeah
in combination it felt like they they
might actually be german so i asked hmm
[Music]
that's my seat hell yeah
that's a really really cool
why does it do that oh look at it
sideways then i guess because it fills
up the screen like this
yeah yeah cool stuff yeah
it's a good seat it's very comfy
okay i'm gonna delete that yes
and you know the more we walked the more
i was
melting away and dying
but the stuff we were looking at was so
cool and the place was so big oh my god
we were like for we were walking around
for an hour
and we didn't
we probably only saw half of it and
there was a place like this
uh
yeah just um there were some like little
lakes
in the
area
of the palace grounds
it's really cool
this place was very
serene and quiet
shade yeah
a little bit of shade
oh sometimes they were like uh older
korean ladies walking by and they were
like oh you puyo and i'm like i
understood that that means they told me
i'm pretty
so i said come on
and navigable was like oh my god you
understood it i'm like hell yeah i
understand
okay
so you saw that and then
and then uh this is just like a nothing
special but i thought you know just to
give you like a bit more of a feeling
of
everything what they'll turn it around
like you know they have this sick
architecture but they also just have
like it's kind of like pretty park area
if you walk around with like a on the
left side even though it was like a day
after strong rain
that little
supposed river was no more river it was
still like making those river sounds you
know there's a little bit a tiny bit
like this
water stands
yeah
a cattle canal canalia not river it's a
canal
so doesn't it
yeah
yeah it was really nice we walked around
that it was really nice but i'm also
[\h__\h] dying at this point and i'm like
[Music]
that was really [\h__\h]
terrible sick and dizzy kind of wanted
to throw up
uh so i was like nami mama
i know we didn't see that much but i
can't do this anymore i'm dying i need
to turn around i need to go and get some
water
immediately
and wow but we didn't go yet uh we still
went further
and we saw stuff like this
really cool
just like this is like they were like
it's hard to explain but they were like
after the big big big building that i
showed you
they were like smaller
um
uh walled in
areas with smaller buildings like that
yeah maybe like living quarters
and the gate
you can't see how small that is probably
because there's no comparison
but
i was standing under that and
my my head pretty much reached the top
of it
so
really really tiny were people so small
back then i wonder
the gate was tiny
really tiny
no that's less than two meters
that was probably maximum
if not
more like 165
[Music]
meters
more
[Music]
maybe they were really small back then
yeah no 164
centimeters 1.65 meters probably
probably something like that
[Music]
yeah but this was so cool so like you uh
we we would walk by these kind of like
um fences walls uh to get some shade and
look at these little little
buildings here and there
and i i love the the color combination
of like this turquoise-ish green with
the pinks and reds
and then
this was nice
so
this was another big lake actually in
the middle there's this thing and then
in the back mountain
and it was so nice
and then we took um
like we got somebody to take a picture
of both of us
right here i asked um some a foreigner
couple a tourist couple
and they took some really cool pictures
i was thinking of that they would take
uh it so that we're in the middle
uh of that you know where that building
is but they took it so that we were
right under the mountain
with the building next to us on purpose
it was a cool picture
i know i'm streaming from my hotel
not from nabi mama home
my oh you like my photos
i tried to make them look somewhat good
while dying a mountain is rare in korea
no navi mama told me that 70
of korea is mountains
i'm like yo for real what i didn't know
that and actually
so one thing i noticed once i arrived in
seoul which i also didn't really know
is that
uh
seoul is like
like surrounded by mountains
it's like i i expected something more
flat less mountains but there's so many
mountains i look outside my window from
my hotel and i see mountains surrounding
the city
[Music]
yeah and they're all very very um
uh foresty mountains fluffy foresty
mountains
yeah
really nice
so i thought the scenery was so cool
with like the
the
nature
behind with the mountains
and then here the the traditional
cultural
uh buildings
historical buildings um
it was so cool and the whole area was so
big like you can do
endless walks in here
[Music]
and we took a picture and then i took a
picture i took a picture of the couple
too and i asked them oh where are you
from one of them was
the lady was mexican and the the guy was
american
yeah they were really nice i took some
pictures for them uh yeah yeah we help
each other out you know
love the scenery yeah
i would have enjoyed it even more if i
wasn't having a heat stroke
like for real holy [\h__\h] oh my god that
was terrible
[Music]
i wish they had like at least
one
small like it doesn't have to be modern
you can hide it in one of the
traditional buildings now like a little
little shop to to buy water
or maybe just like a drinking fountain
i didn't find a single drinking fountain
there were toilets
but i wouldn't assume that that's
drinking water in there so
what comes on thank you for the super
chat
so when we reached this point i said
nabi mama it's over
if i don't go back now because we
already walked for like 30 minutes or so
imagine we have to walk that back and
i'm already dead now if we don't walk
back now
i'm going to die i swear i swear to god
i was really not feeling well
i was like mommy mom i'm serious i need
to go
so we walked back
sweating like crazy and i was not
feeling well but i was still um excited
to be there so i was still jumping
around
while dying i don't know how i did that
um
we finally made it outside
oh no by the way i want to tell you one
thing you want to know on navi mama pon
moment
[Music]
at some point
like you know we were sitting somewhere
in the shade
taking a little break and then we walked
away
and then
uh we walked up that big thing that i
showed you the the big building uh this
one and this one
right there
that one
we walked up there and then we spent a
few minutes up there and then we walked
down so it has already been like i don't
know three four minutes at this point
and then
a foreign dude comes up to navi mama in
the right in the moment where nabi mama
says to me
you know where my bag is and i'm like
and right at that moment
right in that moment
a foreign guy
uh he was a british person
i asked him comes up to her and gives
her her bag
[Music]
absolute perfect timing but like he was
probably like she saw like a bag that
was fitting to her dress
but it was like where she left it it was
like at least
40 meters away so it's actually a
miracle that a few minutes later
we were uh we received the bag hmm
we're really pulling i'm like holy [\h__\h]
thanks dude
thank you
thank you very much where you from oh
england oh no i see interesting and i
was like
he's from england and she was like oh
sugoi
she was so impressed by me communicating
with um all the foreigners
she was like oh i don't know how you do
it and i'm like you'll be able to do it
too your english is good too you should
you should not be so shy and you'll be
able to speak better in english
eventually don't worry when you go over
scenes but yeah she was like really like
yeah yeah my social
skills are too good
so then uh we left the grounds
i wanted to stay longer but holy [\h__\h] it
was just too
too
hot and then
we were walking back to the hamburg
place to you know
undress
and
i just need to mention this because it
triggered me so hard
right in front of the hamburg place
there was a a traffic light
[Music]
where
on the other side there were like 30
people waiting on our side there were
like 20 people waiting
for
it felt like 10 minutes it was maybe
seven minutes if i'm realistic probably
but it was way too [\h__\h] long it was a
huge it was a huge like
crossing
it just didn't it just didn't there was
no shade though and me and nami we were
like
i'm going to die if i don't if i don't
wanna go we're just crossing right now
i'm going to die there's no [\h__\h]
shade i'm dying it's just didn't turn
green
what the [\h__\h] was going on we were like
eventually we were like is this [\h__\h]
broken it's unbelievable we've been
waiting for like 10 minutes
why is it not changing
oh my god
did the sun wanted to kill me so once
again i'm telling you guys
we have to take down the sun
the only sun you need in your life is me
take him down
chickens
take down mission shoot the sun
shoot it
the sun and maybe the traffic light
while we're at it
[\h__\h] that traffic light [\h__\h]
absolute [\h__\h] traffic light
[Laughter]
oh man
oh my god i was losing it i was losing
it
at some point finally
it decided to
have mercy on me
and turned green and we went over the
street and um i was like
like the hamburg place to undress was
15 meters away
but
i
was at
i was way past my limit i was so
dehydrated so i was like now my mama
wait before we go inside i have to eat
an ice cream because there was like a
little store like a little tiny
convenience store that had ice cream i
was like i can't i can't i could
15. one five meters
i was like i can't i need an ice cream
now so we got ourselves some ice cream
uh watery not creamy
and we
consumed it
as if our lives depended on it
[Laughter]
and it was like my mouth
was freezing
but even by the end of it
my body was still overheated i i was so
weird like i couldn't cool down
until i undressed and was like done
with you know
all of that
actually even after undressing and being
in an environment with uh uh low-key air
conditioning even after that i was still
not cooled down enough
so then in order to cool down
we went to
uh a close by
starbucks because i just needed to go
into
a room with air conditioning
and
sit down and just cool down
so that's what we did
and i got a drink that we don't have in
our starbucks so i'm happy
why do you always turn it around
what's going on what's going on
why you do this
[Music]
so this is
uh what was that something with
tangerine
i don't remember but some it's not
greater
it was really good the bottom the green
stuff with some kind of jelly
i don't quite remember but
lemonade yes lemonade
tangerine lemonade something like that
that they have on the menu there
and i was happy to drink some korean
only
starbucks menu
so
we stayed in that freezing starbucks
until we were both
cooled down
and we were thinking about what to do
next
um
navi mama actually had everything
planned out
so
next thing we did we wanted to go for
lunch
at this point it was
probably like
3 p.m or so
so
a close
by relatively close by
i think i think i think we walked
did we
did we walk or did we take a train i
don't remember but we went to this big
big big big big shopping mall that i
told you about the department uh
shopping mall
with a
[\h__\h] ton of stories there the biggest
one
[Music]
the biggest one in all of korea yeah the
hyundai
the big one um so the plan was to go
there
and even yeah have lunch and then
take out some food
to eat it
uh
at the river later
uh i think that was maybe the plan
but it took us so long like uh
to get there
and then choose something to eat because
we just could not decide what to eat
uh
yeah but we ate something small
where but you know everything was so
freaking crowded and we couldn't decide
what to eat so we actually didn't end up
eating anything
um
korean there i i said okay before we you
know buy stuff to uh take out and bring
it to the river
i just need something small right now
like a salad or whatever it doesn't
matter
and then i see a place that has a salad
and now me is like okay that's good i'll
take something there too i'll eat
something there too so we go inside and
i order the salad the salad is huge
the salad is huge it was like enough for
two people
and nabi mama ordered something too
but when both things came out we
realized holy [\h__\h] this is a full-on
huge
huge lunch so we shared both
and then
nabi mama was like actually the like one
thing that she really doesn't enjoy
eating or can't eat well is salad so i
was like
okay
so i had to eat most of the salad alone
[Laughter]
but i love salad you know but but yeah
um
so the problem is i didn't want to eat
too much because we were gonna eat some
stuff by the river but after eating all
of that
i was kind of full but i think navi mama
too
no maybe not as much as me though
so
yeah
that was a problem now but
also i showed you these pictures on
on twitter
but i'll show them again and the egg
[\h__\h]
the egg [\h__\h]
yeah this is just to give you a feeling
of what it looked like in there a lot of
different uh
places
yeah to get food ads this one says i'm
not a chicken
which is also apparently both of these
stories apparently uh exist or come from
america
interesting but you know korea loves
eggs and chickens so
they have a lot of places like that
[Music]
tonight
this is just a general
vibe
general picture it took while we were
getting
on the left side you see those
banana waffles which were
navi mama said that these are not normal
waffles she said she loves these she had
these before and she really recommends
them uh because they're not just normal
waffles they're like i don't remember
what what she said but um
they
uh have some like korean pancake kind of
filling
not not pancake filling but there's like
these korean pancakes
that uh
koreans like but
this is a like a
like a
waffle version of it
[Music]
yeah cause they're inside there's like
this this um
um
filling of like nuts and
not hot dog but
bro yeah brown sugar and nuts and honey
mmm is the filling inside it was so
good so we actually got that to eat that
at the river
um
i have a picture
i asked if it's okay to take a picture
you know while while they were um
caramelizing and i don't know roasting
the bananas
like that mm-hmm
yummy
yeah
fresh
all fresh
and then we went to the river now
i'll show you this first
so this was the lineup we had like two
really yummy banana puddings
and waffle
and the banana
[Laughter]
food porn let's go
i love sweet stuff this was really good
it was really yummy
we're the other half now we ate this
together
i was really full at this point already
so
yeah
censored
navi mama tried her best to be cool
by
um you know cutting through everything
and making it um
easy to eat
yeah with with our plastic
cutlery
yeah yeah yeah yeah so this nest so we
ate that but the thing is so we arrived
at the river okay we walked it's right
at the department store actually so we
left the department store navi maman's
phone was dead at this point already and
of course it was like it always was
um so we used my google maps at this
point thank god that i got the pocket
wi-fi
because her phone always dies halfway
through the
day so we used my google maps but the
thing is i have a question maybe you
guys have a like a similar experience
but ever since i got my new phone the
samsung phone
um
i didn't have this problem with my old
phone
i'm not sure what the problem like where
it comes from but um my google maps
always shows that i'm looking into a
different direction it's not very
accurate
what um
what does that have to do with does that
have to do with the tracking from the
phone or internet or what because like
wherever i am
it's showing me kind of wrong
like how do i fix this
i need to calibrate the compass
[Music]
calibration oh
i thought google maps don't work is that
why it's acting up so weird for me not
only and i don't mean like the the
direction but you know what's actually
acting up for me is um when i look up
directions to go to a place
is that what's happening
um
it shows me for example
how to get to a place with a train but
when i choose
um just to walk to somewhere
it doesn't work like it doesn't give me
directions how to drive or how to walk
it only gives me directions how to take
public transport
interesting i was like i wonder why this
is is that is because google maps
doesn't work there oh
it's okay so far um it's been helpful
anyway because like for public transport
it works
it's okay i actually
even without the
root route the map itself works so
the only other problem i have is that it
shows me that i'm going in the wrong
direction
no matter if i'm in korea or not it does
that everywhere or maybe i need to
calibrate it okay
i don't know how but i look into that
navel map cacao map
[Music]
thank you now i know why that was
happening good to know
i didn't know
nabi mama didn't know either because i
showed it to her and she was like hey i
wonder why
um
okay so
we were walking
to the rhythm
uh it was quite a walk because even
though we were like already at the river
at some point nabi mama kept on wanting
to
walk
further
onwards
uh down the river
and she kept on walking and blocking her
walking she was like soon soon soon soon
and i was like never mama i want to sit
down and she was like no a little bit
more we're gonna walk a little bit more
there's a place i want to go to
i'm like okay
and we keep on walking i'm walking and
walking at some point
we reach um like there were some like uh
parts of the river that were like
uh like with trees lined so you can't
really see the water much and then we
reach a part where you where the trees
are gone and you like there is a little
like there's a ship
uh that you could access normally and
buy stuff there like drinks or whatever
there's a convenience store and stuff on
some of the boats that are right at the
river
and then the trees are gone right and so
we look at it and navi mama says oh
this is where it's
supposed to be and she's like
really like confused and
like sounds disappointed
and
and like confused and i'm like it's okay
we can just sit down here there's like
tables there
and but yeah um
she was looking at this
uh i think she wanted to go down here
close to the water
but
um
so this is uh the aftermath of the
flooding
uh this is the only place where i saw
any
aftermath of the flooding
um and
i mean i was aware that this was gonna
be the case but nabi mama said let's go
to the river so i thought she was aware
of it but she looked at it and she was
in shock she
did not think that it would be like this
and she was in shock she wanted to go
here i guess like down but this is i was
taking this photo standing right at um
like a danger danger danger caution
um
like thingy it was fenced off
you can't go any further than where i
was standing i was just putting my hands
over it to take the picture
um but this was
all along the whole river
and uh
normally
you know until where you see the fan
fence in the middle
is where still you could sit on grass
but all of that is
water as you can see
[Music]
but
yeah i i that that doesn't look like
something that would be fixed in one or
two days so that will take
quite some time you see on the left side
there's like
yubby
yeah
and then maybe you can see a little bit
further ahead
there's like a ship or something with
like a cafe and stuff so you can go
there too to get some food
and yeah
there's several of those boats there
normally
so navi mama was like kind of like
sad
after that
i think i think she was probably like
sad that she couldn't do this because
she was
she really wanted to do this with me she
was also saying like oh we can we can
order or like buy
uh some fried chicken and we can get
that ramen there's this this fun thing
where you get this instant ramen uh
and you eat it by the river everybody
does it
and i'm like okay cool like
naomi likes to do that so let's do it
together and we couldn't do it but we
sat down there and ate uh the waffle and
the banana and we talked a little bit we
had some fun talks
but i noticed that nabi mama seemed
generally like down after
after seeing that so i was a bit worried
um
yeah and it was actually still pretty
early as you can see
uh the sun was starting to come down
after we arrived slowly
um
but then it was like
after it got dark
we were like okay maybe we should go now
it's kind of late um
and
i don't know
yeah i'm full
i wanted to eat something proper for
dinner but we we
just
had like
you know that that weird awkward lunch
where i didn't want to eat so much but
it turned out to be too much and then
the the waffles i don't know
we should have had like uh
a different system here so
we wanted to order chicken but then
we kind of didn't do it because we were
both um
relatively full and uh
yeah i wanted to eat like later it was
like i think
maybe 8 p.m or something like that
so
uh after a while it got dark and i have
a picture of that too where
you know there's flooding but it's still
it was a beautiful scenery anyway
yeah that's the right side first the
first picture was kind of the left side
and this is kind of the right side
and on the bottom you see the flooding
there's not supposed to be water there i
think but besides that it's
i think it looks pretty
i couldn't take a good picture
yeah i couldn't take a good picture
because
the the night camera from my old phone
was better what the hell
yeah yeah i'm sure that like navi mama
wanted me to see it in its normal state
so that's probably why she was a bit
sad
but i thought it was nice anyway because
then
um
navi mama was also confused because
there were no people
where we were she said there were always
people there and they were hanging out
and i was like i guess probably because
of the flooding there's no people there
because of that
um but then we walked back
we walked all the way back to the
station because we were pretty far away
at this point
and
right at the station
there were a [\h__\h] ton of people
there were so many it was it was pitch
black it was really dark but they were
all sitting pretty far away from the
water on a big grass area
everyone was like eating stuff and all
that so this is probably what nabi chan
actually wanted to show me
um and then there were a few
a few foot food stalls like this
yeah a few ones um that those were
upstairs
uh you have to like go downstairs there
to reach the the sitting area where
everybody else was
but this was cool i really like the
atmosphere here
um it's kind of straightforward yeah
kind of like street food
it kind of gave me gave me matsuri um
vibes uh
festival
vibes
yeah and then you go up a few more
stairs
and then there was that thing that nami
mama mentioned to me that i i did want
to try it but at this point i was really
full you know
so i i still want to try it maybe i i
can still try it
so let me show you let me turn this
around let me explain this to you guys
because when nami mama told me about
this i didn't quite understand until i
saw it
um
but so what they do apparently what they
like to do
it's not the normal they buy instant
ramen but then there's this these
machines there
where you heat up the instant ramen in
this in this form thingy
and
yes instant ramen machines i've never
seen that before
and and the people they stand in line
there to heat up the instant ramen and
eat it by the river i thought that was
actually pretty cool
and then there's like um there's there's
this like a tiny shop right next to it
that sells a million different types of
instant ramen
that you can choose from and there were
some non-spicy ones too so i was gonna
go for that but maybe we'll still do it
i i i still
what
i still want to do it
so nabi mama if you're listening to this
let's do it okay
before before i go i still want to do
this
yeah
it's cool
i know ramen what's good so nobody's
i don't know it's such a cool atmosphere
like
such a chill vibe
um
yeah
i don't know kind of cool stuff i never
saw that before it's a funny machine
[Music]
she says that
a lot of korean people like to do that
to hang out in the evening
so it's kind of a cool hip thing to do
be one with them
very
cool so
then after that we separated
uh after looking a little bit more and
that was not everything because like
actually there were a lot of more
um little
um
food street food stalls there um
i want to try them out
but then uh we left
and now went home
and nabi mama went home to with a dead
phone she said it's okay i have a book
with me
[Music]
good
i was a bit worried but
yeah she's fine
so
day
number three
oh [\h__\h]
it took me one and a half hours to talk
about one and a half days
okay
day number three starts
now
um
how was your money i did i did i was
able to get money
um
uh i was able to
use shinhan bank
apparently mastercard is barely used in
korea
especially the combination of a master
debit card so uh
that's why most atms didn't and all of
the restaurants didn't take my card
so
i went to shinhan bank
with the
whole live english staff that was there
and i was shaking and nervous in front
of the atm but then it gave me my money
and we were like celebrating like
let's go i got money
[Music]
thank god so thank you guys
for
uh
recommending shinhan bank
yeah let's go out
and then you showered everything in
bills yeah pretty much
because afterwards i went shopping
pretty much
so okay now we talk about day three
which is yesterday
okay
yesterday
[Music]
we
uh i told nami mama
i
i was unlucky again i i woke up again at
5 00 am and
needed uh
some more sleep because it took me hours
to sleep again
that was the second day in a row
so i said nami mama can we meet
afternoon
so we met around like
uh
3 p.m
in
where was that mata
yesterday i didn't know now i had navi
mama tell me
uh
[Music]
i guess it was on it
oh it was home there yeah yeah yeah that
place
was home there
hongdae and we had
to
be
okay
a little bit like a like a hamburger but
korean style
we actually wanted to eat
uh i think bibimbap
i think but then the store that we went
to
here's another pond moment navi mama
looked up the store and then we were in
front of it and it was closed
uh so
instead we went to tokkayabi
like a place that was right next to it
that was actually also pretty popular
apparently and had really good ratings
and good good place
yeah so
uh they were like grilling the tokkari
right in the middle
look i took a picture
on this big grill
looks like a hamburger right
yeah so it's actually i'm glad i found
this food because that's really easy to
eat for me there's like a lot of foods
that are too spicy in korean um
cuisine
but this was not spicy at all so very
easy to eat for me um
so he was grilling that there
and then what you get
is
this
yeah so um
there's like on the on the you know we
have some rice and the next day we have
a miso soup kind of soup and then next
to it we have some pretty spicy sauces
for the meat i think
and then
a salad and some
kimchi kind of stuff and the on the very
right the very red looking thing at the
top
was uh
i think squid
in this spicy sauce like
kind of kimchi style sauce and then
something the left the greenish one
from the second from the
uh second from the left at the top i
don't know navi mama tried it and she
was like you're not gonna like this
and the very left is just a daikon
radish
and like a sour
uh
it was sour radish and then yeah the
long green thing i think
we all know what it is
it was not spicy though i was able to
eat it but the more i would get to the
top it's probably because of the seeds
but the more i would get to the top the
more spicy it would get but in theory it
wasn't spicy
in theory
so
uh after getting that
and they served me
this
oh
[Laughter]
how you like da da da da
i like that
yeah that was yummy
some good meat very juicy
very tasty
very good
meat
yum
yeah with the rice of course i
i ate all the rice
all the meat
actually pretty filling
uh pretty
a good amount of food
yummy
really really really good so i will put
this on my list of korean things that i
can
eat with no worries
and i was like nami mama is this is this
really
this is really fun for me to eat because
it feels like almost
too like you know the hamburger kind of
style of meat makes me feel like i'm
cheating again like i'm eating something
western again but no
and this is tokabi okay
is is korean food
yeah i used the chopsticks the spoon was
only for the soup
it's not a chili
it's not chili
it's not a chili thankfully
you can try bibimbap yeah i want to try
bibimbap and uh one more thing that
sounded similar
king kimbap maybe it was the kingdom
bibimbap and kimbo
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah kimbap and bibimbap
i remember those two things like nabi
mama and me we keep on trying to eat it
but for some reason we never get to a
place that has it
[Laughter]
yeah we wanted to eat on
on this day instead of the tokavi but
okay
maybe tomorrow
tomorrow
eh bibimbap spicy i don't know i'm
confused
okay so so
and then we ate that that was out of the
lunch
uh and then we left
this place to go shopping in hyundai
and and it was
really cool i really like this place i
went again today alone this time
i took a few pictures to give you
a feeling
of what it looks like kind
of so
this is just one of many
impressions
impressions no that's not the right word
they were you know those people dressed
in red on the right side those are
tourist guides just standing there
ready to help tourists
ah very very helpful very nice
this is like this was actually um
there were a lot of
clothing shops here and then there were
a [\h__\h] ton of smaller streets
and
and then there were also some really big
streets like the place was huge okay and
it had so many different atmospheres
yeah
i really really liked it i took uh
one picture today that uh oh no wait no
that's not the picture
where is the picture no
[Music]
oh well i mean this was a little bit
later in the day but
uh why
why do you do this to me
uh
this was already when the sun was
starting to set
and this is one of those smaller streets
that i mentioned
i was trying to capture it like in a
really artistic way
because i i really liked those
small streets with the small shops that
are they were all like really
like i don't know aesthetically pleasing
and some lights and yeah there were bars
and
shops in between
[Music]
am i
was i able to capture it nicely
i wanted to capture all these small
streets somehow
but i i am not doing it any
what's the word i'm not doing it
what's the word what was it again
yo nando yeah oh yeah at this point i
think uh at this point we're in yom nang
dong
yeah yeah
wait yeah we went somehow from hongdae
to yom namdong oh thank you yeah i'm not
doing it justice
that's right that was yom nam dong at
this point
you recognized it very well
and
uh
so
one really fun thing is hey i wanted to
do this we we took uh photos in a photo
booth
and it's so different from japan
so i was really fascinated
with
so
i censored some stuff but yeah this is
uh
uh there were so many of these and they
all kind of most like a lot of them look
the same
it's just really like relatively simple
machines in there while while in japan
you know they have all this editing and
they have like these voices that are
like ah please enter the book oh do this
personality i'm gonna try this oh you
look so cute
please move on to the next section and
decorate you're pretty gonna see put
some stickers on yeah
um so there is like a lot going on and
the japanese party could have moved with
really loud music too
and yeah it's crazy but so this is
really different in korea
no wonder you didn't get money out of
this city
it does look a little bit like an atm
yeah
and it's really cheap too
i think it was like um like 200 uh yen
we keep on saying uh the prices in yen
because i have no feeling for
prices in one even though it's just like
one z one zero yes less pretty much
but yeah
um
so
one big difference is that
uh there's no decoration
for the photos afterwards
no editing like japanese political that
makes your eyes bigger your face smaller
your legs longer and all that and there
is a uh
what was i gonna say
ah i forgot
i forgot it's just everything's
different it's so different
it's so different
but i liked it i liked the simplicity of
it
it's still like we still got pretty
cute pictures out of it
and nabi mama sent it to me
and then the background
like in in kurikuna machines in japan
you get green screens there's a big
green screen behind you but uh in these
machines
there's like a this blue wall
for most of them i think like it's just
a
uh
a pastel colored wall
that you stand in front
and you don't get green screen so it's
just like a
nice
pastel simple color behind you
and then what they like to do is they
decorate
the walls
in the
in the photo booth thing
uh with like these pictures that i guess
they didn't need
for whatever reason
[\h__\h] my chat died
hello
yeah
yeah all these pictures that they didn't
need that's what they look like so maybe
you can get like a feeling for
what you get out of it
oh yeah yeah one more thing that they
give you is like some head decorations
yeah you get some like had decorations
like i wear cat ears
and navi mama wore
some some other hat decoration i think
it was a penguin oh yeah she put a
penguin on her head
show me
[Music]
um
it was it was cool
it was not so crowded not so loud as
japanese purikura
i like both things though what did i
just delete
i just deleted something and then
i don't know what it was ah
there you go okay
so
that's a nice memory i have some photo
with
photobooth
i will treasure it forever
thank you navi mama
thank you mama
and then when we were in yon namdo we
went to
uh
a chill
cafe like a
apparently a cafe that's popular
with like the youngsters
who take instagram pictures
navi mama looked it up for me because i
wanted to go to a cafe like a cute cafe
and so it had
a lot of scones
yeah
really
yummy really yummy we got a scone and we
got some
cakes too
yeah this place is really popular
apparently
they have all kinds of cakes there
and they're so big i think in the
picture you don't really understand but
the pieces are huge
definitely one piece for two people
and the problem is we took a little bit
too much we overestimated how much we
were gonna eat
we took like two pieces and a scone it
was way too much
it's frosting so shiny yeah
um they were like all over the cafe
there were like mirrors like in the
stairwell
and uh next to the cakes and all that so
everybody was like taking
uh mirror selfies in front of the
mirrors
um
yeah like everybody was taking fancy
mirror selfies for instagram
yeah me and navi took some
becoming one of the cool hip instagram
people
[Music]
when we left the cafe
um even like in in front of all of these
cafes in that area
everybody was taking pictures inside and
outside because even in front of the
cafes they had usually
some nice
architecture or structure going on
uh where you could take cute instagram
pictures like it's like it's all about
cute instagram pictures there
so
we were we went out and we saw a couple
taking
pictures
uh the the boyfriend was taking pictures
for the girlfriend in front of the cafe
and they had the shutter sound on and i
swear to god i'm not exaggerating when i
say that the speed of the boyfriend
taking the pictures was like
pizza pizza pizza
pizza pizza [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
puzzle pie
i'm not joking it was really that speed
it was one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten didn't it keep it kept on
going and going and going and going and
going and going and i'm like
this
is
the perfect
boyfriend for this girl
this is the perfect dynamic for these
two
this guy
probably was scolded by his girlfriend
a lot of times for not taking good
instagram pictures and probably
his job is basically being her
photograph all day in fancy cafes in
fancy streets in fancy buildings
yeah that's how you get the perfect shot
that's how you get um what's the what's
the word
how you get um uh the candids yeah yeah
where you look so natural because you're
not looking at the camera you're looking
you're looking to the side looking down
closing your eyes and looking like
you're
enjoying it so much sitting on this
bench in this lovely weather
having the greatest time having a little
chuckle little giggle
but
i just i just found it so funny because
he's definitely been through some
training being able to go like
he's been for some [\h__\h] man
yeah
he probably has had a lot of criticism
from his girlfriend but honestly he's
doing a great job he's been the perfect
boyfriend for this girl man instagram
boyfriend
and i
i said that too i was saying that to
navi mama saying like he they have a
perfect dynamic like he
he's like just her photographic
boyfriend for instagram isn't he and and
i said nami mama you know what you are
you're my you're my instagram girlfriend
because she kept on taking pictures of
me too like i didn't even have to ask
her she kept on saying do you want me to
take a picture of you in front of this
do you want me to take a picture in
front of you
of you in front of this oh you look cute
right now should i take a picture of you
now and let's take a picture can i
challenge take a picture oh you look so
cute i'm gonna take a picture of you oh
should i take a picture of you
[Laughter]
she was so
helpful
i didn't even have to ask so i didn't
feel annoying about it very nice she was
my instagram girlfriend
yeah
[Music]
exactly what i need man
yeah
no i didn't have to train her at all she
knew exactly what she needed to do
she knew immediately she was a natural
yeah she wanted to capture the kiwawa
phoenix beauty
so
um we were just you know i'm strolling
through the streets
of the cafes and we wanted to walk back
from yongnan
back to hongdae because we wanted to go
to karaoke
we did so much on this day holy [\h__\h] so
on the way i had my eyes
on this one
store
that was
a painting portrait
story
but not like the
like what i see a lot in europe
of like really really really exaggerated
features
but a bit more like natural looking
caricature
so i was like
navi mama this looks kind of
fun maybe we should do it
so
we went inside
and first it was only going to be me
navi mama said oh i don't need one
but eventually she was like oh i guess
i'm gonna get one too
and i was saying you know what nami mama
you should be the one drawing the people
in there but
let's be the one who's gonna be drawn
for once how about that
so it's actually pretty cheap you got
like a little picture i think it was
like a five size for like
oh
how much was it
i don't think it was even five bucks
it was really cheap and it only took
like two to five minutes
and they all sit there
most of them were couples or like two
female friends
um
they were all sitting together there
having their pictures taken and and
everyone had the the artist they all had
like a cute
uh
uh hat on like a brown
fun cute hat
or a female couple or or male couples
who knows yeah
uh
what's it gonna say
what was that oh one thing i noticed
that the turnaround was really really
really fast
but
when they were drawing me
like you know we sat down next to each
other okay in front of one artist and
she was going to draw me first and the
moment
like a moment a moment after
we sat down and the artist just started
literally just started a korean couple
sat down right next to us
to uh in front of a different artist
and the artist started drawing
the couple uh both of them at the same
time
and
by the time that
um
not quite actually uh half
halfway through my picture which was
taking a surprising amount of time uh
the couple next to us was done
so
two pictures
ready
done
when my picture was only like halfway
through
i noticed
she was putting a lot of effort into it
no i don't think it was about not being
used to you know drawing phoenix's but i
think it was just like
she was she seemed like she wanted to
you know put a lot of effort into it
yeah
and then after i was done she gave me um
the picture
and i i kept on um
staying in my seat and waited for nabi's
picture to be picked to be finished
and
navi's feature was done way earlier but
i mean there wasn't like an insane
difference in quality but um so we look
we compared our pictures that we got and
there was a
huge difference in how the eyes were
drawn not because of the shape but like
the inside my eyes
she drew like a [\h__\h] ton of sparkles
like kira kirakira in my eyes very very
very sparkly shiny eyes and then for
nabi mama it was just
plain
black eyes
i mean black because you know obviously
all of these are black and white okay
navi mama obviously has what was it blue
eyes
yeah
she fell in love with you i don't know
but i think she really wanted to make me
happy so she put so much effort into it
spent way more time with it than she
needed to i took a few pictures of the
stuff on the walls
oh my god on the left that's jyp and the
top one the top dude i've seen them on
tv too those are some um
korean uh
tv
personalities
and yeah some other stuff that not not
human portraits but i think the animals
looked so cute
there's a corgi doing a sploot
so cute and some more portraits from
people who went there or like maybe who
worked there
to get a sample of how they look like
usually that's pretty much what nabi
mama's portrait looked like and mine was
similar but a bit more
sparkly detailed eyes
i love the pog face
the big one
but i i really liked all the art in here
i thought the style was really cute
here's another
another wall ooh
oh this this girl wow she has quite the
attitude i like her hair though she's
kind of sad
she's a big smile
wow
she's cute oh she's cute she she gives
me um
innocent saiso idol wipes
but pretty
very pretty
oh wow she has quite the
the cheeky look
oh pretty pretty oh
wait aren't those
maybe those are portraits from kpop
idols because now they look like k-pop
idols to me
the but especially the the bottom left
girls
actually all
is this itsy
wait is this wait that's itsy isn't this
it's c wait [\h__\h] what that's itsy i just
recognized it yeah oh
that's totally itsy
oh now that now i see it that's 100 itzy
those five
[Laughter]
the more i looked at it the more i was
like wait a second wait in the top wait
that's
[Music]
i'm so sorry for my comments
what did i say
oh my god
[\h__\h] i love both of the grooves okay
what did i say about the
about juaza
what did i say
what did i say about her that she has an
attitude or
i mean i sentence an attitude and then
she looks sad and she has a big smile
she used to say so i don't
wait it looks really hacker
how did i
how did i not notice before i didn't
look i i honestly just took a picture
without really looking at it much
it's so funny
oh my god
they didn't actually go there i'm
guessing i'm guessing they just you know
tried to make some sample pictures to
put on their walls
unless
oh my god
you know if that was bts or so i would
have had no idea
thank god it was girl groups that i
recognized because i i can only
recognize girl groups there was one more
insanely detailed picture that stood out
to me
uh
maybe you recognize this person
wait
it's so good
[Music]
it's so good you recognize this dude
recognizing frodo my boy
he's trying to catch or let go
of the ring
[Music]
his face oh my god
oh my god he's desperate
he's so desperate
holy [\h__\h]
i want this
actually actually um later in that day
nummy mama asked me what my favorite
movie was and i told her it's lord of
the rings
and she didn't know it so i was like
nami mama you have to watch it
you have to watch it
yeah i think she's interested now though
please watch lord of the rings navi mama
did you ask what's yours ah
i think i didn't but she did say that
she liked harry potter
no i don't think it's her favorite movie
though
so we got portraits that's really cool
too that's another takara mono another
treasure from that day
i know
it was very fast too
really really um cool stuff i normally
wouldn't
do that in other places also normally
like i don't quite like the caricature
style from
did i say harry potter again i didn't
right
i don't quite like the like typical
caricature style from like
overseas
the really
exaggerated one
but this one i i liked
it had a cute look to it um
yeah and then there was one store i
wanted to show you because i was
fascinated by it because it was
aesthetically pleasing and exactly what
i needed i told navi mama that i needed
to buy some more masks
um and then she brought me
to a store that was called i think mask
lab
and i need monthly shippings from this
place please
just
oopsie
what i'm doing what am i doing look at
this why is it why is it flipped
completely around huh
it doesn't even seem off
but this is how it's supposed to be
match club oh [\h__\h]
so many masks
so many and they looked so pleasing all
the nice colors and patterns and there
were so many different types like there
was um
it was here i was thinking like you guys
you would love
if you had a store like this
right now wouldn't you
to get some nice masks you deserve a
surgical style
yeah so colorful
i bought a couple
i have like
five boxes or so
look at those colors
oh
they're so good
so many beautiful colors
so aligned so pleasingly
where is that and it was in hongdae i
think
oh
i bought like five boxes man
yeah cause we don't get these cute
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum i'm a cat
sorry we don't get these cute masks in
austria so i had to
buy them especially because like um
uh here
in uh
these ones in austria
got them it's turned around again you
see over there there's ffp2 max and in
austria like for the longest amount of
time they only allowed like
ffp2 masks
uh which
are
way more sturdy than the surgical ones
and a bit more annoying to wear but
i was like okay let's get some cute ones
in case i need them again
yeah
how full is your luggage yeah um i put a
stop on myself today to a spider view
to buy no more because i think
i'm gonna have some problems especially
with all the merchandise i got from
annapolis today holy [\h__\h] i don't know
man
i know i said i will come with an empty
suitcase but partially the reason why it
was so heavy is because my laptop alone
weighs like 10 kilo
feels like honestly it really feels like
10 kilo and then i had my ipad and my a
second monitor which i'm not even using
right now because i was too lazy to set
it up
but yeah the laptop
uh the microphone is heavy
and uh yeah
another monitor and an ipad so that's
like all the heavy stuff and then you
know i didn't bring so many clothes and
so many shoes and so many bags not so
many
but most of the weight comes from that
and
yeah volume wise now i think i'm
[Music]
i'm a little bit flat i took a second
monitor yeah but it's like a like a
portable small monitor for traveling um
not that small but
um
yeah my gaming laptop is pretty [\h__\h]
heavy that's why
you know
remember when i told you that um there
was when we when we went to the hotel
you know there were several people
helping us to
carry my suitcase and um there was one
occasion where this there was this dude
right where i was like oh my god you're
you're our hero thank you so much
who totally regretted helping us after
seeing how many stairs there are left
so
today i passed by that place again
and i noticed
right
next to those stairs
a little bit hidden
but indeed there
was an elevator
[Laughter]
i
am so sorry
[Music]
i am so sorry
there was indeed an elevator so i i
wrote that to nami mama i was like now i
remember remember the guy who helped us
and was so
so regretful after helping us
there was actually an elevator right
there
oopsy
but no the other time you know inside
the station where we were um
changing
somewhere
there was indeed no escalator and no
elevator
for
that specific area
um
even though we walked around everywhere
there was nothing
that one was indeed not our fault
yeah
i pray that dude never notices it i
don't think he will he doesn't have the
phoenix eye that i have to notice that
[Music]
all right so
uh
next
oh my god i'm pretty much at the end of
this day hallelujah because um
my my this this air is dry in the room
my throat is starting to hurt
so
uh ah then we went to kanoke
we did so much on that day we went to
karaoke
in hongdae so we went we went we walked
for we walked off we walked all the way
from
yum yum yum
yum
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
[Laughter]
we walked all the way to hongdae
ah it was quite a walk was like 30
minutes and i was i was i had so many
shopping mags um but we finally got
there and we went to karaoke and
korean kanoke
is
so different from japanese karaoke
um i will have to say i prefer japanese
karaoke
uh it's
more advanced and more uh
technically
easy for a foreigner to use
um like the maybe it depends maybe
there's better places but this one navi
mama said was still like foreigner
friendly because at least they had
english songs and english subtitles
but
so
like the first of all the input machine
the input
pad
had
only korean writing
no english
and if you wanted to look up
a a japanese song
you had to look it up on your phone get
the number and then put it put number
into the pad
um
yeah
and
the the the audio
the sound
was not as good
uh
yeah so you know
that was not as good as japanese karaoke
but what i did like is they had like
themed rooms and all that uh it was cool
actually today i saw
a different i walked by a different kind
of okay place in hongdae where um maybe
maybe the korean people who were there
before know what i'm talking about
there's this one kind of okay place in a
big shopping street um
where you look up to the building and
the like you see inside the karaoke
rooms you see them dancing
like the whole
everything is like windowed everything
you see through windows
and you see them dancing inside we
didn't go to that one
but
you see them
singing and dancing and having fun
inside which is pretty funny
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah yeah yeah for the exhibitionists
among us
um
i think there's several of those places
yeah i feel like i saw more than one
we don't we we were not visible to the
outside
we also didn't even get a special room
navi mama said they have more special
rooms but they gave us a normal room
kind of sad but oh well
and now this is kind of the nighttime
night time
uh
honda
um
transform flip
now
looks kind of different from the first
pictures i showed you of hongdae right
yeah so this has
this this was
big street
i passed by this area a million times
today
and then i saw like free streamers on
separate occasions hanging out here
streaming talking to their phones
room escape oh i don't mean that i just
i just wanted to take a general picture
of
the road to give you a vibe
a vibe
but this was also where one of the
karaoke places was where you could look
inside
was it was really cool because the later
it got
the more street performers were there on
that day as well a lot of street
performers like magicians and like trick
artists and
some foreigner
was
playing drums on buckets on plastic
buckets really loud had a big crowd
everybody had a big crowd surrounding
them um
yeah yeah yeah some somebody said
somebody played violin and all that
yeah today i saw no one performing
though
only streamers for some reason
did you see anyone doing k-pop dances no
no i didn't
i thought maybe i would see someone but
no
not
here
yeah
oh yeah now your mom said baskin good
it's called basking
basking
here
basking basking
it's called basking
the bucket guy yeah he likes his buckets
basking
[Music]
performance together
yeah it was a nice atmosphere really
loud lots of music here and there lots
of people
[Music]
lots of young and hip people cute girls
lots of couples
yeah but we went after karaoke we went
to finally get
some
fried chicken
korean fried chicken
yeah with some mozzarella mozzarella no
it was probably not mozzarella but it
was some cheese bowls
at this point we already ate a couple
but it was a huge serving of fried
chicken
oh my god
yeah we went to bbq
bbq
yeah
i finally got the fried chicken that
they all talk about okay so i understand
now it's it's very crispy um very very
very
good quality meat inside soft we had
boneless
yeah
and uh yeah i love i love the
uh breading what do you call it in
english breading
panade
why are they laughing cannibalism
no guys get a breading
yeah it's i don't know how to describe
it it is definitely
kind of different from like
fried chicken that you get
in in my country
and and then this was like a pretty
normal basic version i guess you can get
like spicy versions and all kinds of
like
different special versions
um
now
now everyone told me that this serving
you know from the top it doesn't look
like so much maybe but now mama told me
normally
you would get
a serving like this for a group of three
three
to four
girls
if you girls if you're in a group of
girls you don't eat with two girls
you're either free to four girls
minimum
and
we were two
and then nabi mama said
after 20 me 20 minutes
where she seemed to have given up on
eating more chicken
but hasn't eaten much even though she
says she eats a lot normally
i asked her what's wrong
are you full and she says
she says
[Music]
she says i have to make a
confession to your kiana
and i i thought i thought that she's
gonna like
confess something really serious to me
now
[Laughter]
no it's not about the diet no but she
said that you know besides
salad
the other thing that she can't eat well
is
agamono fried stuff
so i'm like well [\h__\h]
because
i can't eat all of this alone girl
do you really wanted me to eat some
fried chicken and here we are getting a
platter of a serving for four people
and we're two
but then you tell me you can't eat much
more because you're done because you
can't eat fried food that well
what we had i'm so sorry we left over so
much and i felt so bad but now my mama
was like
it's fine it's fine it's fine you know
it's um not something you would eat with
two people but yeah
it's okay and is it just not like that
big of a deal in korea to have leftovers
because so far
nabi mama gave me the impression that
having leftovers is not a big deal in
korea
i'm surprised
not too serious not too much
[Music]
um they probably would have done
takeaway but i mean i was trying to eat
as much as i could
because navi mama didn't eat so much
and i have a small stomach too
so i was like
i was feeling really bad but i didn't
expect such a huge [\h__\h] serving
the cheese balls were great too man i
really like those cheese balls
they were so good they were kind of like
sweet too like
sweet kind of cheese yeah another porn
moment
[Laughter]
um
no need to feel bad i hope so
taking leftovers isn't really common in
korea
or taking the leftovers home
see this is also very different
depending on the country
if taking something your leftover home
is normal or not
in in uh
i think in america
it was quite common
and then in europe it's
a little bit less in austria it's a
little bit less common but you can
definitely do it
in a lot of places
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah you guys told me that's what
the po why the portions are so big in
america
it's pretty normal to take the rest home
[Music]
navi mama seemed to kill the phoenix
she she stuffed me with so much food and
like before that we had all those
sweet
filling huge ass cakes and there was not
much time in between all the times we
ate food you know it was
we need to spread it out more normally i
eat breakfast and dinner and maybe like
one small
tiny snack in between
but that's it i don't have lunch
normally
although my you know the times are kind
of
at different times but still i only have
two two
meals per day normally so while we're
here
in korea navi mama
actually
yes
yeah
we had three meals
actually i had four meals yesterday
breakfast
then
the
tokkavi then the huge cakes and then the
fried chicken
that's four meals and i normally have
two meals okay
so
i was i kept on saying to navi mama i
don't i i'm not gonna be able to eat
much i'm not gonna be able to eat much
okay navi mamas i hope it's not a big
portion i don't wanna leave too much
food you know
and then there's this huge [\h__\h] plate
of fried chicken
[Music]
bhc yeah um nami mama told me bhc is
better but we were like
right in front of a bbq so we went to
that one and i kept saying barbecue
barbecue barbecue and nummy mama kept on
laughing like it's bbq
baby barbecue
[Laughter]
kept on saying barbecue barbecue it's
bbq
oh man
yeah
okay so that was the dinner and then
and then uh oh and then we taxied home i
was gonna like taxi home alone but then
suddenly nabi mama joined me in the taxi
she was like i'm gonna come with you
after all i'm like okay
okay then you sure
it was pretty late and i i wanted to
stream
so we went home to my hotel
she chilled a little bit
waiting for me to prepare
until i was done and ready to stream
she looked at me setting everything up
while cuddling into my
blanket because it was cold as hell in
my hotel room
[Music]
yeah and then and then i streamed for
you guys that was yesterday
yeah
that was yesterday
what time is it
almost midnight oh okay
okay okay i think
it's already been two hours and 20
minutes but i think i will tell you
about today
although i just ran out of
water i think i still have some iced tea
from the combini
my fruit man it gets so dry
it's so dry
okay
lip balm are you gonna put that inside
my frodo what
talking about not my lips but my throat
man
lip balm doesn't work for your fruit
six minutes to midnight we are right my
clock is wrong
you have to eat cookie i want to
ah maybe tomorrow
i can eat something
more korean maybe like
but toboki the problem is it's usually
um spicy right so
probably gonna go for like bibimbap or
kimbap tomorrow
wait which one was which one what which
one is the one that looks like sushi but
is
definitely not sushi
where's that bibimbap or kimba
that's kimbap okay so that's what we
want to eat tomorrow probably
[Music]
because that's not spicy
and i should be able to eat that i hope
i need to eat more korean foods
[Music]
while i'm here but i don't have much
choice
yeah but i feel like me and nabi mama
talked about it
and came to the conclusion
that non-spicy tofu is not quite really
too booky anymore
it's not the same thing
in korea people eat kimbap with toki oh
oh you know if nami mama like i told her
if she orders it i want to try one but i
don't want to eat the whole thing
because i probably could not eat the
whole thing because of the spiciness but
i want to try like one so i at least
tried it
would
probably be the way to go
cheese kimbap there's cheese kimbap
no not
no
cold icy noodle dish oh
that sounds good
that sounds good did you eat corn dog
not yet i wanted to when we were at the
at the
uh river
but
you know i was full
and what was full man
i will eat it
before i leave i promise because that's
something i really want to
eat okay let's talk a little bit about
today
[Music]
so
remember yesterday i went to bed early
and then i woke up today i was picked up
at like eight a.m or so
and um i was brought with a car
a fancy car
two
annie plus
so any place so i think it's in hapjeong
i think
um which is close to hongdae
ah
and uh
it was so early i didn't get much sleep
it was really hard to get a little bit
and i didn't eat breakfast because i
knew that i would be eating a lot of
food
at the animals i went there before the
opening
and um
i requested to eat the food at the cafe
i didn't say i want it all but i was
hoping for everything to get a bite of
everything the good thing is i didn't
have to eat it all alone
i i tried to eat as much as i could
but i will confess i did have to have
some help i gave my my leftovers
to um
the
uh
management person in korea that was with
me on that
day mm-hmm
did you um didn't you see maybe i saw
maybe i didn't but i entered from like a
back entrance
uh underground
i entered secretly and so there's like
the part of the store that's like all
kinds of normal mixed stuff
and normal stuff that they have all the
time
and then
you enter
and actually i have a video of this but
i think i might upload it on twitter
because i didn't wasn't able to send the
video to myself on the pc yet
but
you you go for you know did you do you
remember those curtains in the
merchandise that we were so confused
about so it's those it's like those
short curtains you go for like a door
with those curtains
and then everything
is
whole live myth themed it's incredible
it's so incredible it's oh my god i did
a video walking through the whole thing
i'm gonna upload it but let me give you
some impressions so you walk in and
there's like the walls are plastered
like this this is before i signed it
yeah
the walls are plastered like this and
there's all the tables with our faces
and different outfits
and this one was for example me and my
my kimono
so cute
and here's another view
oh you have to turn your head for this
one
yeah
you see inna over there
and then
and then this is uh if you turn around
but if you look if you stand right there
and you turn around the exact opposite
then you're looking at this
uh it's uh
where you get the food
that you've ordered
then you see the the general menu that
they always have besides the limited
menu
yeah
so for some reason
there's something standing out there
under the dessert section there's
something that doesn't quite look like a
dessert does it
the prices by the way if you get uh
if you get rid of
uh like
three zeros
was it three zeros then it's like
approximately the price in us dollars
i think
so like six bucks for a drink
and 8.5 for the desserts which i think
is very very reasonable
for a collab cafe
yeah
good prices
and then
and then there was a special menu that's
currently going on for two weeks or um
in a different uh
annapolis that's not in seoul it hasn't
begun yet they're they
kind of started later than the soul one
so right now i think there they still
have the cali menu it's like cali and
then kiwawa and some of the other girls
and
uh yeah kelly's menu is already done and
now it's the last few days of the kiwa
menu that comes with this mug and
i've heard
that i was told you know remember when
in the beginning we heard that it's only
10 per day
they changed that there's more now
there's way more there's a good amount
per day i'm not sure if i'm allowed to
say the numbers i'm not going to say it
but it's way more
way more reasonable thank god
yeah the beginning apparently was 10.
i'm glad they changed it
yeah
it's more than 50 now
not so limited anymore uh
i think it's not so
not so hard anymore to get it
and then there's
uh
there's like a screen
uh that's in there at the entrance
uh before entering the cafe it's a
screen that shows like the different
girls
and
ah that's
that's a view
[Music]
where they i don't think this is
normally how the tables are there but
that's how they put it together for me
so i can have all the food there
and there currently are the
kiara and the cali standees because
that's the order of the limited menu
apparently afterwards they're going to
change to stand these
into the other girls standees because
these are the only ones right now that
they have
and you know there's like screenshots
from streams of us
and
uh you know the especially created uh
artworks from jazz jack
and
yeah
really cool
i love the screenshots they took some
great moments the one on the left is
when i was doing a waiting stream for
for bails it says on the top left i'm
looking for my rat
yeah yeah yeah good moments good moments
outfit reveals and uh oh that was the
the collab stream after the
outfit reveal for the elegant dresses
and then there's ammo's commercial
oh yeah right before you enter the cafe
so here's this like
relatively small section of merchandise
and as you see there's it's not much
there's this and
and uh
here this sorry have to turn your head
again
and
and they apparently they switch it out
like depending on the day they have
different stuff
switched out switcheroo
depending on what they have in stock and
also to have some variety
yeah yeah
and i got everything though for free so
nice man i was i was gonna pay but they
gave me everything they gave me a huge
bag with all the merchandise
we're seeing this danny like looking at
the mirror yeah it was also the same
size as me
employee benefits no ceo benefits
yeah but i mean
what i did you know signing everything
um
and testing everything and how much i'm
advertising this whole thing on my
streams like no other
whole life member
um i think
the amount of advertisement i'm giving
them is
100 worth giving me all the merchandise
for free
like nobody me me saying i want to go to
korea go to this cafe and sign
everything
was my will my idea
and
uh i think they were super surprised and
happy that like you know i was actually
coming there to check everything out in
person so i think
it's actually pretty
obvious that i would receive this kind
of treatment yes
so the staff were really nice by the way
um
i said hi to all the staff members and
they were working hard so i said
fighting
and they were so sweet
we're so sweet and here's a here's the
the view from where i was sitting so
this is kind of like the corner
of the uh cafe where the standees are
if you go
um
to the front and then to the left that's
where you leave the cafe
yeah so this is like the right side of
it and a good overview overlook there's
some monitors here and there showing
um what food items there are and also
the whole time there were original whole
live song whole live english songs
playing actually perfect timing the
moment i first entered this place they
were playing spikes
thank you very much for that
i think it was a coincidence though
um
that was a good look so uh then after i
took some pictures they um put down all
the food in front of me yeah somebody
one of the staff prepared all the food
for me
early
[Music]
so i post this on twitter i guess
but
i tried everything
this was my breakfast
and i must say my taste buds were
very confused
i wrote down notes
of my thoughts
but
at some point
i didn't know
what the simplest things tasted like
anymore i could not recognize
what any of these things tasted like
i don't know what was going on but yeah
okay so here's my curry this is the
limited menu currently
everything that you order comes with
like a card see see bottom left and the
sticker
that is related to to the
thing that you ordered i guess
yeah so this is a a typical
japanese curry i think with some fried
chicken on top
[Music]
um
so that was
really good like it was a typical
japanese curry
tasted perfectly fine
um i mean curry is not normally what i
eat for breakfast but
it was a good serving it was very yummy
it was not spicy thankfully
i wonder maybe you can add spices but i
didn't see anything
that's a mild curry they didn't give you
the money it's probably with all my
merchandise in the bag probably
so that's the the curry and i didn't eat
much because i saw how much i had ahead
of me so
i gave a good part of it to
manage your son
so then
here we have my dessert
oh also they all come with the cookies i
guess
my dessert and my drink
so
i told them
that the plate is too small and they
were like yeah you're right
everybody says
that well yeah it makes it look bigger
that's my dessert yeah
uh
[Music]
wait
so
what i can say when i wrote down
chicken very sticky crispy and fresh
the sauce on top is so
sticky it kept on like
every bite i took it was all over my
mouth
and my hands
it was very sticky sauce but a very good
sauce and the chicken is the breading is
so crispy
[Music]
and it's so versatile to two good chunky
pieces of jimmy's legs yeah
really really really tasty
the fries were good too really good
fries too they also work well with the
sauce
i liked it it was not a cake it's not
like you cut through and it's surprise a
cake just because all the other desserts
are cakes this is also just
just the perfect dessert
no jimmy
and then uh we have the
kiwama drink which
was really good but i i had a hard time
figuring out
what like most of these things
ingredients were um it tasted a little
tiny tiny bit like grapefruit and orange
um like you know
i mean you look at it and you can kind
of imagine right it's like a lemonade
with um
a fruity citrus orange
kind of flavor but i don't really like
grapefruit and uh the grapefruit didn't
give me
a bad taste at all
so it was really mild and uh not
bothering
mmm
it's a mix of those things it's not a
pure orange or whatever blood orange oh
maybe that maybe there was some blood
orange i'm not sure
[Music]
that's my menu
and then we have
after that i
had callie's menu
i was surprised i looked at the cake and
there's like some berries on top right
so i expected a berry a taste but it was
actually
grape
i was so surprised i was like wait a
second i got bamboozled i mean i could
be wrong but i'm pretty sure
that was
grape flavor
oh and then the staff was like oh yeah
that makes sense because the koreans
really like grapes apparently
oh that makes sense because of wine
oh
wait i didn't realize i didn't make that
connection
hey
yeah the purple purple grapes not the
greenish ones
it was really good this was um maybe one
of my favorites
of of the cakes
it's a layered
cake layered crap
crepe
and then we have a cherry coke on the
left
which
uh i enjoy i love cherry coke yum yum
yum yum
rarely ever able to get cherry coke but
yeah hallelujah
oh my gosh
okay sure then that's that
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah with some nice
cali cards coming with it and a sticker
and a cookie of course i have yet to try
the cookies actually
maybe with the snacks that i'm gonna be
eating in the next stream we'll see
we'll see we'll see
and then we have
[Music]
now
enos cake
um
this was soon after i got served but i
ate
ina's cake pretty late
and by the time
that one
got into my belly
it was falling apart
this one this one had a tendency for
falling apart and kind of melting on its
own
uh it's a very very very um
soft
jelly-ish cream
uh i guess
and it has a it just it just runs
away from you you have to eat it fast
but i i i did have it standing around
for quite some time so
yeah
normally you wouldn't
wait
20 minutes to eat it i suppose
yeah yeah yeah yeah but it was really
good it had lots of berries and i really
love berries so
very very very strong sweet very taste
and the drink
uh
whoo
this drink
ah yeah it i was like
what is this what is this what is this
and then i was like it's bright
it's sprite with a really slight hint of
um some berry taste i guess
but yeah it's basically sprite
now my taste buds were so confused
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it tasted like sprite
not dr oopsie
blueberry was maybe blueberry i don't
know it was very like slight it wasn't
that strong the the berry taste
[Music]
okay
well that was very yummy i like this
cake but i felt so bad for it because it
was like melting
right in front of my eyes
[Music]
and then
we have
[Music]
a miss set
this one
you know when i
when i when i talk about cakes you know
i
normally cheesecake is not really my
favorite but this was some kind of
cheesecake with like caramel topping
and
even though cheesecake is normally not
my favorite this one was one of my
favorites out of this whole
selection
so it was really good
i think the caramel was gave it a really
interesting
taste
uh additionally
and uh so i like the decoration with the
the waffle
cone on top and her drink looks like a
banana smoothie but it's actually like
like kind of like a tropical
juice mixture smoothie
it was so good i took so many sips from
that one
really good one so this one was overall
really really well balanced and uh
a good combination
i like this one
really refreshing too
i feel like it harmonized
very well
taking notes when i go oh you should go
before the limited menu from kiwa is
gone i told the staff that i really want
to try the i'm a limited menu
but hers is like the last one
so unfortunately
i'm not there anymore
some people think that i'm gonna be in
korea until popcorn
and no i will not be there during
popcorn although now i'm wishing i would
be because
um
i have to um either stay up really late
or wake up and a really awkward time for
popcorn they told me
they told me the time for when they need
me
it's a really [\h__\h] time for me in europe
so
we're gonna have to
deal with some time adjustment
adjustments
um
popcorn there's a convention in korea
that invited me in bales and
uh
people think that i'll be staying in
korea until then which would be better
at this point for streaming
to the convention on that day
time wise
time slot wise
but oh well i'll get through it
it will [\h__\h] me up again
streaming at what like four or five a.m
holy [\h__\h]
oh well so that was um there my throat
is dying so i'm gonna try to go through
this quickly now
oh here we have good ass set
i love the looks of it it looks so
childish and playful
yeah
so it's basically a buffet with corn
flakes at the bottom and these ice cream
balls that does dissolve into
um like a creamy
ice cream kind of i think it was
something like bubble gum flavor i
wasn't sure
what to make out of it flavor-wise it
was good though and um
it's a good mix with the corn flakes
it's a typical
puffy ingredient yeah dipping dots and
then on top is a macaron and there's
jelly sharks that i ate as well even
though i normally don't like eating
jelly but you have to eat the sharks
you're cute
and then the drink
was uh
i
i really had no idea
it looks exactly what i have in front of
me i'm still not sure about it
[Laughter]
i think it could have been it it
definitely tasted so familiar
like i don't know calpis or
or ramona
i don't know
i i don't remember
it's like
all of these flavors i've tasted before
but in that moment i couldn't remember
anything
any name of anything
maybe somebody who went to the cafe can
tell me
what that
flavor was
is her mic off no i'm talking you have
it muted or something
everybody else hears me you think
something's wrong on my side
my spiral
blue hawaii
i don't i don't know what that
tastes like but the drink itself tasted
really familiar
um
anyway it was good
it was very very good uh really um
playful
design
uh i think it fits gouda very well and
kind of captured her character i also
talked i talked to the person who made
um who came up with all of these menus
and recipes and all that
so that was nice
yeah
i talked about how i found it really
funny
how my dessert
stands out so much as
not quite the dessert
uh yeah yeah but i think it's it's
really funny and it plays into the
character lore so
yeah i told him also that everything
looks so good visually
yeah
everything tasted great i just
afterwards i have to say i felt kind of
sick
i
i tried to eat as much as possible and
then it was so many mixes of ultra sweet
things and then the curry and the
chicken and oh my god at the end
i did feel sick i didn't tell anyone but
i was like [\h__\h] i hope i i hope i don't
throw up
now it's my breakfast
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
yeah i wanted to try everything so i had
to go through with it and then after
eating everything i started signing
everything i signed
um
several uh like table place
table those those table cover thingies
that they have on top of the tables but
i'm not sure if they
like replacing it or if they're doing
something else of those
and uh i signed my big ass standee i put
this on twitter too and there you can
actually look at it without breaking
your neck
thank you
and i signed
um
i signed this wow i had a lot of fun
with this i was like can i keep on
signing can i keep on decorating
then thankfully they allowed it
[Music]
on the 14th august 2022
look look
amazing sugoi
wow
cookie master
i asked if they have like a thicker pen
for this wall they have like a you know
a
calgary pen
uh a
brush that would be a good size
no they didn't but yeah
it's a bit thin but
it worked it worked i tried to fill it
up nicely
um that was fun that was a lot of fun
and i signed some more things and um
oh yeah i didn't show you the posted
wall so this was before i put my post-it
on it
and but as you know
my post-it is gone now please return
thank you
um but i thought this was so cute i
didn't know about the posted wall but
there's like so so so so so so
many of them
yeah
many especially at the bottom because up
there you can barely reach it without
going on a stool
a little chair or so
[Music]
i offered to maybe make another one but
what if that also gets stolen you know
you have to
put it somewhere there in the in a
separate frame maybe if they wanna
maybe on top
in a separate small baby frame
for one post-it
if they want to i don't mind writing
another one
but uh i don't know if i have time to go
to the store again at 8 00
a.m in the morning maybe they can just
pick it up or something i don't know
we'll figure something out maybe maybe
um but at least there's a photo
of my post-it
so it existed at some point
[Music]
no it's okay no need to be ashamed or
anything
it happens it happens i was also just
thinking maybe it just fell off and then
someone picked it up and you know
thought oh i mean
it's trash because it was on the floor
or
maybe someone lost it or i don't know
you know a lot of things could have
happened doesn't necessarily need to be
like the worst
possible thing but
even if then please return it you can
just flip it somewhere act as if
you know
it was just you know you just
hide it somewhere where the staff member
can find it so you don't have to be
directly confronted with
bringing it back but yeah anyway
i will leave it up to the person who
took it
yeah yeah yeah
it's okay no problem no problem
i'm not angry
just disappointed
it's okay
i'm not sad i'm not angry no no none
look at my face i'm fine i'm fine
now i'm really fine i'm good
now it's just kind of sad because i i
was
i was hoping that people would
find it and be like oh my god what i
didn't know she wrote a post-it because
i didn't tell people
i wanted people to find it by accident
and be like oh my god treasure
mama mama
[Music]
and then i left
and went shopping alone and i might tell
you more about today and tomorrow and so
on on another stream
but now i have to sleep
uh so thank you guys
for listening i hope you enjoyed it so
far thank you so much anna plus for
treating me so well and being so kind
and fun
and giving me all the food and all the
merchandise holy [\h__\h]
i had some fun days so far
[Music]
very sweaty everyday i'm gonna
take a shower
so
um i will
i'll talk to you guys soon
and
phoenix nice translation
[Music]
hopefully this night i will not wake up
at
[Music]
5am as i said i will read super chats in
a stream when i'm back home
so please wait for that
thank you for
listening i hope you enjoyed it so far
i'm gonna enjoy the rest of my trip um
[Music]
yes
goodbye everybody and in german we say
au friday
[Music]
and young
i think we took like a super long nap
today but you know the heat the heat
all the sweating and the heat makes you
so tired
love you kfb
thank you
[Music]
don't forget to follow me on twitter you
too korean bros who don't have a twitter
account you have to make one
understand
[Music]
can't get away from kiwawa's gays
follow not unfollow
i smash the like button while you're at
it
[Music]
i'll hit the notification bell
g a
z
e
[Music]
no don't block me
no
[Music]
ah thank you
thank you
bye bye
[Music]
you