[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
questions
[Music]
ah sorry
I'm here
I'm here again hello sorry for the wait
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
can you forgive me
um
forgive please
oh I just realized something's missing
something's missing where is uh
where's my corks are laughing you oh
that's weird hello wait I'm I'm where
where you guys should be
I'm covering you guys
here let me go here
ah
Julie Put the gun down I need to protect
myself at all times
from the anger of angry chickens because
I started to stream too late I'm sorry
did I say
hello
oh well at least you guys are not on
unarmed you know it's a it's a fair
fight here see you have a knife
oh
come on come back
one more one more that was fun let's see
if I can if I can hit you from here
um
wow well nice nice
you guys are good targets to practice
with
thank you
[Laughter]
flying over rainbows
these chickens
welcome guys we're going to play GTA
[Music]
oh there's like an advertisement for a
sick car on here
sm722 it looks so cool what the [\h__\h]
never seen that in game just about the
the game
is is here
I'm gonna make it a full screen I think
last time we had it full screen
yeah you came with a knife to a gunfight
should I keep you guys I'm gonna just
stay here in the corner
yeah there's not much space here if I do
it full screen but
I'm gonna keep you guys and then you
guys go go up here
full screen gaming yeah
okay
all right looks like we're ready
to get back into it it's been like a
week or so so my memory is
a bit blurry
uh I just remember that last time our
our sun
drugged us and blamed it on us uh okay
Michael Discord what Discord is in the
chat this guy on you want to play some
GTA huh where is this chord
ah so we love the new song
oh it's cordless and to my new song what
thank you do you do you can you guys
like integrate do you into Discord so
that
um everybody who gets like called on
Discord by someone now here's do you
playing as the ringtone
and then when people started complaining
about it we'll just say sorry our
service got hacked oopsie doodles
how about that how about that can we do
that was there is anyone
to change the ringtone in Discord
because I I've never seen the option and
I would would have never changed it but
uh if there's no such option then I will
gladly volunteer to have my song be uh
you know one of the or the only other
options
the only option there isn't well that
just seems like
like you know
a gap that you need to fill a
possibility so many possibilities
I see Discord has become quiet which
probably means they're working on it
right now
[Music]
um
yeah different notifications not that I
rarely ever
oh I don't I barely I barely do like
one-on-one calls like through DMs on
Discord but but I will tell you the the
function of calling someone
with the ringtone has
um helped me
at least two times because at least two
times I was able to wake up Kelly by
calling her
through Discord
uh because I had no other ways to
contact her in such a moment and tagging
her did not seem to wake her up but I
was like you know what
I I doubt that she has her phone or like
her Discord thingy on on like you know
not muted
but
I tried to dire situation is called for
desperate measures is that how you say
it
or desperate situations call for
desperate measures and so uh and do a
little ring ring and then surprise it
worked
a long time ago and I was like you know
what I'll remember this if I ever need
Cali to wake up
um because I can't reach her and I know
that Discord might actually be the way
to go we would never work on me because
I always have uh my Discord on on mute
on silence my whole phone
my whole phone is always on mute
um yes yes yes but you know we we don't
really give each other each other's
phone numbers because well we live in
different countries a lot of us and
that really normally there's not really
a reason to share each other's phone
numbers with each other's with each
other
um
but then but then every now and then we
do have these situations where someone
is missing for something really
important and they're like how how do we
how do we contact this Personnel [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] and then we we try to like write to
manage yo do you have this this person's
phone number or over contact another
member or do you have this person's
phone number and no one ever has it
yeah so that's that's actually quite the
problem sometimes
yeah so thank you Discord for saving me
in such situations that will not work on
everyone but it works on Cali smoke
signals
yeah no no no it's not about being
disorganized it's like a big reason is
also just you know privacy and security
like like like
uh I think jenma maybe
has my phone number but if if she has it
then only her and
and maybe one more person in the company
who would be in charge of sending
packages if there's a need of sending me
a package you know so that there's no no
leaks and whatever yeah so no not Yago
Yago does not have my phone number
yeah I gotta gotta keep it to the very
bare minimum you know the people who
have such information
anyway
ah I don't have ama's phone number no
I don't have Amy's phone number
uh no I don't think so
I don't have anyone's phone I don't even
have Kelly's phone number because even
when I lived in Japan uh we would
communicate for a Discord
so
um
oh we will talk about the the robot a
little bit later to trigger some people
you know when we're like when we're in
need of a tangent I will trigger
something this car this car what can I
get this like in the game no that's GTA
online what the [\h__\h] I want this in in
the game
but yeah if we need to trigger some
people if I feel like triggering some
people I will talk about well what's
happened
I will tell you
um
yeah during the import dialogue exactly
that's exactly when I will start talking
anyway
Franklin oh wait wait if you don't hear
that that probably stop stop stop stop
stop stop
when I Tab out does it pause the game I
hope so
oh that was loud
hey
wait I'm too big
oh you guys want to see the map don't
you maybe it's actually better for me to
be over here
but then my gun doesn't look over to
that side
like I'm guessing like normally
normally the phone doesn't matter so
much right
I'll probably use
good right okay
I kind of mirror not now
uh I would have to open Photoshop
whatever that's fine oopsie oopsie I got
an interesting opportunity for you
acquaintance of Daves an FIB contact are
you joking relax the guy's private
sector very wealthy could be lucrative
why don't you meet him and see what you
think
all right all right yeah yeah I think
about it all right me and Trevor will be
there too I promise you it's a step up
for you a real opportunity
okay I don't know what's going on at the
moment I I don't remember
maybe if we go there we will understand
everything a bit better uh
um
let's see that was not it how do you ow
my ear
how do you open the map there you go so
we are blue uh do we want to go to S or
to D what would be that Devin Devin
what would be that meaning that they
just mentioned
s or D Devin who the who's Devin Solomon
Solomon or Devon
s is for the movie guy D should we go to
D
all right
whose shitty car is this
oh shitty car is this what Michael
how do I change this again uh
it's cute
all right uh wait d
ude it feels like it's been like five
weeks since the last time I played this
let's go welcome back to GTA everybody
my left ear hurts why
does my left ear hurts honestly every
everything hurts but now my left ear
hurts
uh
turn that bang a music up there's no
volume button like a quick a quick
volume button
just like me for real for it your ear
hurts too
let me move the chat a little bit closer
to
aging
it's not bad
ear wax if if I had so much ear wax in
my ear that it would make it so that it
hurts I would be extremely worried
oh we're going for a channel
wow Channel
that's a short tunnel I want a longer
Channel I want to go for like a mountain
mountain tunnel
it's not the way it happens well well
never happened to me like that
I mean I once had my ear so full blocked
that I
had to go to the doctor to have it
vacuum cleaned and showered which is
really funny I was that was some weird
[\h__\h] man
it's because it's that doesn't happen
naturally normally
it only happens really if you push
everything deeper and deeper inside
how do you run again why does she not
run
what's going on
you're gonna dress up as traffic cops
and you're gonna Rob two trust fund kids
that I know and dislike intensely oh
gladly we can get a good price for the
vehicles in Asia look complete the work
you'll all be well paid you're late
sugar tits yup sugar what's going on
and to realize your childhood dream and
dress up as a cop Mr Weston research
team suggests the two boys
you two get going let's go t everybody
is in the [\h__\h] mid-life crisis here
oh I don't know if this [\h__\h] is for me
homie my life's already way the [\h__\h] out
of control all right look
I'm a darwinist brother all right some
Prosper
now are you out of your goddamn mind
this is your lucky break choose now are
you gonna do this or have you simply
found your level in life
I guess we'll find out yeah I'll get you
a wheel homie what's up him
Evolution guy
uh-huh
Evolution scientist uh-huh wait oh they
switched me to to
um Franklin Fine of me
no no
on the radio I
come on
um
there's something special about you when
I see you I know it's true
you know it I just can't resist you your
eyes are like a spell that I can break
through and that should scare me
you're captivating me and in me and you
let me count
with love hey all the same if you know
play the game am I locked up by the side
no I can fight the feeling and which way
oh [\h__\h]
thank you
[Music]
now I know I can like relate a bit more
to when I'm sitting in the passenger
seat and the driver misses the exit
hey I think yo next exit is the one and
they still they still I don't know
forget it within one second
you can save me I'm in too deep and I
love the rash I just can't resist to
your eyes are like a spell at my phone
[Music]
yeah I guess we look pretty ridiculous
all right man look I see you soon yeah
we'll pick you up coming through grape
seed get the drivers there get them
going at speed
what does that mean get them going and
speed does that mean I need to make them
go fast
I mean
[Music]
I know I'll never be the same
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm in breakfast I am not a day
me feels all right breaking me down down
they're here
oh what's that orange car
seven millimeters
oh it looks like a spaceship so get in
your cars and let's see if they move as
fast as your mouth the fool wants to
race us we were just getting out of here
anywhere right
hahaha
all right it seems like
they accept the challenge race because
where are we going where's the goal and
why am I so [\h__\h] slow
wait
also how am I supposed to what how am I
supposed
I need to be smarter than them
oh there we go okay I guess just they
they seem to have more speed than me oh
[\h__\h] why we're going that way now can I
redo oh my special ability and what
what am I supposed to shoot them
wait wait wait wait wait
just have to use the traffic to my
advantage it seems like they tried to
stay on the road
how about I do the other thing and not
such a rebel a hit
yeah yeah yeah
I see him catching up
wait wait the [\h__\h] radio is playing
what the [\h__\h] no wait what that's that's
that that was my radio
that was my radio never mind
what about this um just they don't they
want me to use the special skill just
for like getting through these cards
right in slow motion it's not really
necessary
ah [\h__\h] I'm losing control
I'm not gonna press I have to go faster
[Music]
that's not a boost
what do you mean it gives me a special
boost doesn't give me a boost just gives
me slow motion
oh oh that one's slow why is that one so
slow should I Ram them is that is that
fair play
oh wait [\h__\h] out sorry I'm sorry
I'm trying to impress some trust drunk
kids Michael and Michael
s hey we're coming up now man be there
in a few seconds oh it's fine
oh ah okay all we need to do is really
to make them go fast so that we have a
reason to stop then huh
wait no can you can you not I can't
change
well great
I can't change it
oh is that in-game in-game like not dmce
why am I supposed to show
I mean this this music is good I mean I
don't mind keeping it
I'm trying
I'm I'm really trying
to keep with them we'll pull this off
okay okay how long is this highway and
it feels like we're going to Mexico at
this rate
what does no oh sorry I mean
highways
we're never gonna stop
keep going
smoothly
I'm just gonna drive on this side
stay on the T they'll stop eventually
why the [\h__\h] are they so fast
uh-huh it feels like it I think I'm
getting closer
I'm getting closer
I think at least oh there's a [\h__\h]
owl that was a deer or something
oh
[Applause]
you look like they're going down yeah
yeah yeah yeah my ass is dead
that's what I'm talking about baby
racing game
guess getting scared
oh I will shoot
you want me to shoot
they actually stopped oh good boys good
boys
stick car there oh boy no more no more
of this
you're gonna call me daddy to make me
wild I'm gonna keep it under the Limit
Oh really that looks like it big racing
from where we are sitting there so uh
why don't you get yourself out of the
car come on
is there a chance you need to make up
for something you don't have
Trevor just looked for it
give me that orange car
I need it
oh yeah
[Music]
oh maybe maybe I should not break it huh
oh you talk of good games wait what
happens
don't stress oh yeah that's what I'm
thinking like they want to sell it right
so
I'm assuming it's not a good idea to
drive recklessly and speak ah the lady
from before Devin's assistant oh wait oh
my God the music that's playing it's
Molly Schultz senior vice president
I love that one and
y working with common thieves well
you're very mistaken I don't think you
guys hear it though old resume
yeah we got the cars bring them to Hayes
Auto on Little Bighorn in South Los
Santos Mr Weston and I will meet you
there
I'll be waiting in Hayes for you idiots
to show up
[Music]
I'm sorry okay did you heard it a little
bit I have to change it now escort I
[\h__\h] hell
can we do
well okay what happens if I just you
know trash it down there what happens
let me let me do that
I want a perfect score hey Frank
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm going with swim you want to join
oh that was nice yeah it's called me and
you you know the song
I love that so much when when it you
know was in the radio back in the day
I love that I'm happy I'm not the only
one who knows in the girl who was
singing it was so sexy
um
[Music]
okay just don't scratch the car scratch
the cars don't scratch the cars don't
scratched cars
hey no scratch baby
[Music]
ah the lady from before no scratch baby
good to be working with you think we're
good Schultz senior vice president Mr
Weston's holding company and if you
think it's good to be working with
common thieves well you're very mistaken
have you got the cars I got the guys the
whole resume
yeah we got the cars bring them to Hayes
Auto on Little Bighorn in South Los
Santos Mr Weston and I will meet you
there I'm on my way
to Devon person I'll be waiting at Hayes
Auto with South LS for you idiots to
show up okay
I'll change the radio
to that song though oh wait what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
I was actually now is which one of you
is getting the silver medal right excuse
me for talking I'm so sorry
please take me officer arrest me
hey Frank
can I tell you bro these cars this is an
opportunity
come on it's not scratch
well now it's scratched
that's [\h__\h] scratched
[Music]
okay
I mean I don't know how how much damage
is acceptable
um I guess until it tells me the car was
destroyed it's fine maybe
oh
his name is okay maybe I'm like two
careful oh you talk a good game okay it
does look that's good oh
all right sorry
sorry about that
[Music]
it was fun though driving into the ocean
now we can hear this conversation a
third time isn't that nice ah the lady
from before Devin's assistant she tells
me to speak she's on my side senior vice
president and general counsel to Mr
Weston's holding company and if you
think it's weird Okay as well you're
very mistaken have you got the cars wow
[Music]
Mr Weston and I will meet you there
hey
that's fun
give me more of those oh I sat in it for
a treat
did it
these
ah this is an opportunity
she's humping my car
shake can you move I'm in a hurry
no no no
we're jumping my car man
I swear it's not fair life's not fair
there you go I'm in the lead again
myth or treat
anyone you work for
[Music]
oh you must know who this guy is look
him up he's the real deal I've seen his
house he can make things happen
me I see your house I think this dude
can take me places yeah maybe something
like that it's really hard to listen to
the dialogue right now and I'm focusing
so much on being fast and careful
maybe I should be faster and Furious
instead
oh my God
[Music]
wanna ride with me
let's go on a dog
oh [\h__\h] hey I didn't get that for Frank
you know
next exit please
[Music]
I'm taking it I'm taking it coming
through oh they're actually like still
taking the same route as I'm taking
even even when I [\h__\h] up oh God oh God
okay
okay left left left left
[Music]
my car is very fine
I committed to this okay I'm taking this
very seriously
[Music]
we have arrived
[Applause]
he did worse than that oh oh God
gentlemen I love you all oh God
fantastic
did you take some substances dude
you seem a little bit too excited for
your age
oh yeah he he took something right
[Music]
you got the [\h__\h] paper I'm so [\h__\h]
lutely look let's finish the job you
beautiful I'm not mistaken that's only
two just give me the [\h__\h] money now
oh I'm so scared I really really am but
you know what I have a payment on
completion of work type of guy I
completed the job done take a [\h__\h]
walk
so what's next man well it's the Z-Type
Chad Mulligan lay it on him kid
Mulligan's a record producer he's going
through a messy divorce he's hiding his
valuable assets including the car so
that makes it complicated he'll clock
any ground surveillance we run all we've
got to go on is that the cars in a lock
up in Howick so we just go house to
house not quite
we have access to an LSPD helicopter the
computer on board can ID pedestrians
fly a helicopter Mulligan and Howick
follow him to the lock-up someone on the
ground collects the car
all right so who does what
you are not needed for this job Phillips
you're in the chopper Clinton you're on
the ground yeah I don't know like
Michael has nothing include him I don't
understand the deal between you two
either but you know what like what it's
just one long mystery but bye gentlemen
and Stacy
it's spiritual really friend Solomon
all right good
it's Michael
oh did you see how they just drove
through the the gate
oh Michael oh
yeah yeah whatever all around me in a
million places I fought the law
was it worth it Michael was it worth it
I feel so sorry for him
man do I have to switch to a different
character now because uh oh [\h__\h] no when
how do you switch again
all right
[\h__\h]
ouch thank you
I guess if I can play Franklin then I'm
happy
could do s I can do the s
um
that's oh it's okay it's okay
uh are we supposed to go to
d right let's go to D
with Franklin no car here what
cool will be the lucky one there's a
taxi
this is fun okay we can do that
afterwards don't worry this this looks
fine that car
gives me
vaporwave Bob sorry
sorry homie sorrow sorry homie it's my
car now you understand right
you understand I got some business to do
let's go
let's go we're gonna apply helicopter
and be absolutely terrible at it
probably
initially the car guys guess
which is perfect because right now
there's My eurobeat remix playing on the
radio
do you like muscle cars I know I mean
and they're all very nice to look at
those muscle cars mean um
just you know sports cars or as muscle
cars the big ones
the big link
muscular cars
muscular looking big cars
eh
big engine ones huh
big American cars big American cars
and you have to show me a sample is that
a muscle car
oh that that's a muscle car probably
right like a like a like a
um let me call those
right okay yeah well do I like them no
when I get myself one no
um would I mind being inside one
I was in one of those before I actually
like really even bigger than that one
like I felt like I was five meters above
the ground
it was kind of weird being so high above
yeah
it was actually in Japan
um a friend of mine had a car like that
but imported from I think America or so
uh because the wheel was on the other
side
like it was definitely an important car
because it was not on the right side
that it would be normally on in Japan it
was like
Homer or something insanely big like
getting into the car was a challenge
already and then sitting inside was like
this doesn't feel like a car
those are SUVs
aha another muscle oh well now I'm
confused
it looks very muscular
[Laughter]
maybe someone will have to give me like
a PowerPoint presentation about all this
kind of stuff
stand when I
all right you know how to work that face
recognition [\h__\h] already well figure it
out can you pick me up switch to Trevor
no I wonder if I don't wanna
I wonder if I don't wanna
oh God we're gonna suddenly be thrown
into a
helicopter okay
I forget I I don't remember how to
what
what's going on what's going on
look at him the scanner accesses the
database and pulls that record what
what
hey people
[Music]
what what
um what
can can I play Franklin instead because
what the [\h__\h]
you want me to take it out of the LSPD
representative sitting beside me man
just get the house
down that way I'm following the call
which way you heard the man do I have to
control this thing the Cowboys
my mouse can't go that far all right I
see something
American friend for a minor infraction
the LSPD
[Applause]
time for me I mean there's some bad
don't tell me about it
it's not gonna happen again
how do I fly
already
like on the autopilot right now
is this an autopilot I feel like it's an
autopilot
and fly with the other okay yeah that's
right okay good thank God all right then
then we have a chance
all right Chad Mulligan Roger that how
do we know that there's something in
here what the [\h__\h]
what is the system
what is this
something should be here
holding
um
right click
I think he isn't a job and all they care
about is the bottom line
says
isn't it weird when there's a helicopter
hovering above you not moving
hmm
I will remember this for real life if I
ever have a
uh if I ever have one hovering above me
I will stop talking I was in there
listening to me okay skin
okay
two guys on a rooftop going at it
oh I didn't even see that
are they killing each other
Disney trying to throw him down the roof
uh gonna keep looking
suspect's not in the area I repeat
suspect not found in the area and it
looks like he's trying to kill him
Roger that
no you're misunderstanding they have
their clothes on and [\h__\h] it looks very
violent
look they're fighting even like this
doesn't look like they're making love
you guys
you guys what the what kind of love do
you make if this is your kind of love
trying to kill someone by throwing them
in over the roof
[\h__\h]
very violent
oh well yeah that might be different
this is probably different
um do I have to look at that I'm not
looking
I need to see what the result is though
oh the other finished
they're finished
what the [\h__\h] okay
this dude's kind of dead
oh
here's another one
get the dog go no
hmm
I think the dog will play is a really
important role here
oh hello
yeah but there he is Chadwell again
we've got a positive ID on the suspect I
repeat we have visual on Chad Mulligan
no vehicle in sight all right look cool
we look looking for his lock-up dog all
right stay home his dog is like a dog he
was there
track him to find where he parked his
car okay you have to listen
he's not talking about anything how
boring
fragile state emotionally
the dog only understandable
he's still looking for the ball that he
buried two years ago
where is that ball
terrible pilot here not doing his job
properly oh there you go okay got him
got him got him got him
that's him right
now
I ain't far away
I'm gonna come out of here
had a nice conversation very friendly
oh
[\h__\h]
wow [\h__\h]
ing structures for Franklin
I have no idea is that him
oh
guys I guess zooming out will be better
here
I I can be more than just your eyes
I could be in your car
can I switch to Franklin
ah homie I appreciate
what is this chin okay well I [\h__\h]
don't
what what is this Mission he went that
way I think
[Music]
I don't know what you're talking about
dangerous flying perhaps if she doesn't
go faster anytime soon I'm gonna kill
the pilots
[Music]
tell him
you're a good boy I believe in you go
out girl
you're a beat and you can get him
hey where is He Man uh good question I
have my eye on you you know like your
requested
[\h__\h]
uh
you're kidding me
you kidding me
what
what that's it
all right okay I'll keep an eye on me on
him this time this car this car this car
this car the one that drives like a
crazy person
so he just has to be on camera all right
I don't have to like scan him again
we're still
are going
okay
[Music]
we have a possible Joyrider heading west
on Howick in a black
[Music]
what will I be doing if I was Franklin I
would just be following him now he goes
this way I know that
go Franklin
and this way
if you guys look so beautiful tonight
you have this aura about you not only
the aura everything about you is so
gorgeous Flawless chickens um
I wanna put some of my spices on you and
then eat you up
to hold back
I have to focus
Drive
there's a present
GTA man how often has he played this
game oh I'm switching lanes
um
[Music]
I see oh oh he's turning over there
Trevor You're Gonna Keep Up
oh he's in there
near a parking garage request ground
units to investigate
hey buddy lower our altitude so I can
see in
lower altitude please thank you
it's probably gonna come out at the top
now
[Music]
aren't you always violence
hello hello
[Music]
uh oh what the [\h__\h] was that sound in my
headphones just now I can't
I can't I really can't see him toggle
the thermal what that's him
maybe I mean there's more than one
person
do you have to scan them again
I'm seeing things a little more clearly
no which one is it though
go to the garage man right here where
can you wave is that you
is that you
in the middle of the carp what do you
mean what what do you mean well how do I
know it's him
Roger we have visual hey take a look
around
okay that was indeed him
hey look at the next one
look at this one
this one
's phone
okay that's probably the person that I
thought it was in the beginning like
he's waiting to chill maybe it's him oh
oh we're going here first okay
that's definitely not him he's way too
chill
he wouldn't lean like that in a
stressful situation
what about him
[Music]
but he's also just chilling though
that seems like it's him whoa what's
that called
or something
put it in it ain't but it looks really
cool I've never seen something like this
before
thank you
wow what is that guys you're inspired by
right I got that it's like an old-timer
type Mr Weston will be glad you caught
us he wanted to see it before we took
off for these cars personal hangar at
Los Santos International I'll tell them
to expect you at the gate it's so cool
hey I'm delivering the ride to Los
Santos internet so elegant
so original
Batmobile [\h__\h] I think they both gonna
be there dog yeah
I already scratched it no no no no no no
nobody for you man at least the ball
hurt why
not watching
some [\h__\h] this girl man she got balls
she needs some serious stones to handle
your ass
all right are we like in a stressful
situation right now
it doesn't feel so stressful
[Music]
what if I do time in here
they won't find me if I'm in here right
chilling
I see you but you can't see me
ah hide and seek is my specialty but
hopefully I won't scratch my car too
much
let me go up the floor so I can re like
the U-turn properly
scratch I mean as long as the game
doesn't tell me
um
that I [\h__\h] up then then I'm good
right
here they're all in that area
yeah
why are they all scattering there
why are they all Gathering there are
they going away please scatter please
scan oh thank God
oh that's that's scary but thank God for
garages imma remember that
that was at the right place at the right
time
[Music]
oh
police tell out
um you don't remember the task that you
had just uh one minute ago right
you wouldn't remember anything about
that hello
um
this is exactly the kind that you were
just looking for they were in here
what they didn't think about going one
floor higher damn
Circle busted it down in
oh my God it's very stupid NPCs very
very stupid but I guess at some point
you have to program them
so that they forget it at some point
cool
I was wondering why they're not sending
any police after me well there you go
how much is this car worth guys so
something like this
something of this
type in real life
three million
10 million
two billion okay and this is very very
different guys
30 million in an auction at least five
million at least 10 million okay okay so
I'm not gonna buy one
but this is be so sick to own
not exactly what I would normally go for
but it's definitely in a looker an eye
catcher
[Music]
I don't have a million to spare no no
million at all so this is ain't
happening
needs more orange
don't ruin this car with orange I love
orange but this car I don't need no
orange
maybe I don't know gold and color would
still be fine but
only like a couple of these exist but
can't you just build one like why won't
they build more than if there's a lack
then why don't you just build more you
could even 3D prints them probably
everything can be 3D printed nowadays
don't you just 3D print it huh
you can get a kid really
for them to keep the value
every once in a while wouldn't it be
nice to do a restock so that you know
more more can be so it's you will make
in the end if you have free cars of five
million dollar volume out there in the
world
there's only so much money you can make
out of that
how about you just you know make
um ten more and then you know the value
might go down a little bit but I think
in the end you make more money out of it
no
[Music]
I'm just I mean
I mean am I so wrong
[Music]
should I use that ramp
of this car nah
nah nah
[Music]
I'm a genius business lady
yes I am thank you is
a muscle it's hard to understand what
the muscle car is
Los Santos International
[Music]
I'm here
that was not one oh well good then
because I don't like that one
hello hey I'm supposing me Devin Western
here Mr Weston's hangers up there on the
left thank you sir thank you kind of oh
wow Devin Weston oh is that Trevor
whoa
a whole hanger
hey everybody oh there she is don't
don't mind the scratches you know this
beauty was
you would have to break my 20 and under
rule man I'll just stick to driving all
right hey tell me something you know how
many of these things they made oh [\h__\h]
like teen nope not like 10 man
don't want people to have happiness in
their lives Snowbird retiree palsy yours
you are sharp man man I'm just looking
for a paycheck for my services
right now it is life lesson Time Pal you
have got to wake up to what's real in
this situation you know take me right I
am opportunity I'm security I'm fast
cars [\h__\h] I got the world on a plate
those two clowns oh man they are the
worst kind of disaster that can ever
come down they are a full core meltdown
and you're just standing there soaking
up major radiation you have got to take
stop man make that call before it's too
late yeah all right man I will
before it's too late man okay
still got no money from that
uh is it really worth it
Franklin
or one if I stand in front of it you'll
never be able to leave you'll be stuck
forever because you're you've been
programmed to be absolutely stupid
you won't understand that maybe you
could get out of the plane and shoot me
to make me go away no you'll be stuck
here forever
stupid NPCs they'll never learn
they will never learn
steal it
interesting is that option
and I already closed the entrance though
what
oh it's locked
there is no such thing as it's locked
in GTA as far as I know
can I get in the passenger no man
there's no other no wonder in here damn
it what if we shoot it
what if we make it go boom
oh
well I think that was well deserved
they underestimated me and they didn't
want to include me in their fun
are you just playing around with me just
using me
so I say [\h__\h] you
perfect
take a car oh and maybe I should take a
call
oh
boring cars
very boring
oh action
wait no I want nothing I don't want to
carry anything when how do
ah
[Music]
there we go Okay so
uh we're going to the meeting point
let's go home
can still plan while in here if you want
really I saw the orange one over there
orange yellow maybe we should give it a
try
ideas
maybe a smaller one that one looks like
Lufthansa
oh that was nice
well
it's a burp Airline oh yeah it's the
same one air emu
no one's in here so it's not stealing
okay that's how he that's how you break
into a closed plane good that seems very
easy
I have no idea how to fly this finger
um
no idea
why why is there no police
worrying about what I'm doing
how do you fly this
so from I I've been on planes oh [\h__\h] I
ruined it
many times in my life
and by experience
I know that it just goes fast and at
some point it just goes into the air so
let's try
[\h__\h] hell come on come on
[Laughter]
that was a good first try I think I
think there's potential there
you respawn me here
Medical Center
oh
you guys didn't warn me about that I
thought I would just respawn there what
the [\h__\h]
no
where am I
mean I'm probably I'm definitely not the
first one to do that
and then die there and then just respawn
here uh where is that point where I need
to go
you God damn it
yeah good health care hmm
I wonder how much I got for those five
thousand bucks
um
all right
uh where do we go
maybe two
which was question mark Or that one I
don't know s
where's s
I don't see an s ah but I see one but
it's blue
I have to go there with Michael
okay if you guys really want that
I will gladly take back my Michael
okay
Michael didn't you miss me you were all
alone and you're home oh
it's okay I'm here honey I'm here Uncle
don't panic
maybe you should sleep under the covers
next time it gives you a feeling that
you're being held like a baby you know
it's a good feeling
much more sense that's what the covers
are for you know did you not know I
don't think he knew I don't think he oh
oh yeah baby
nice
nice Okay
[Music]
um
where are we going first we need to get
out of this house
[Music]
poor Michael
yo he had some nightmares
oh [\h__\h]
no cars
cars don't go what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
is there one in the garage
better be a good car
in my garage oh
nothing nowhere no car at all
nada
take this [\h__\h]
invisible car yeah I know I know I got
stolen but I thought I had like maybe
more more than one car
you must can't complain
do you who do you say you don't feel the
same
[Music]
it's the game we play oh
just let me try to
if you guys
have a that's a great song even sit
around and debate about snotty coffee
and what did you just say [\h__\h]
she said that's a great song for people
who sit around
and enjoy snotty coffee
was that supposed to mean
did she just insult me or compliment me
I feel like that was an insult but
what's bad about drinking coffee I mean
I don't drink coffee but
it feels kind of kind of like she was
roasting my song
does she know that I'm listening to her
roasting my song huh
been holding one in for
eign
[Music]
I still see some
newcomers trying to do the do you
challenge and you guys are all welcome
to join in if you feel like dancing a
little bit
obviously that part is not so difficult
I'm gonna get in here
a part that I am
had to do you challenge
B
it's not that difficult I think you guys
can do it okay what gate
I don't see anything oh into the film oh
the the S didn't look like it was
supposed to go in there
oh okay
nice small
yeah
ah go in here first and then
may I thank you kindly
homes
huh
what's that sound
Memorial Building
what are we here for
come in come in thanks thanks
[\h__\h] is that decorations
now I have to make my own coffee and
give myself is that a real dead person
you have in there okay I hope it's just
movie props but the walls will hold us
Nelson in Naples Pluto I said Mars you
[\h__\h]
shoulder variety
two
it's not real can't be around would be
super stinky in here Michael
Devin Weston did he does he want you to
bump me off no not at all he said you
were retiring but might need some help
on a movie only [\h__\h] retire Michael
him and my son they want to put me out
to pasture so they can turn this place
into condos or a theme park or something
theme park would be nice it's a Dream
Factory well maybe they have different
dreams
some days
I don't blame them you know they always
say never work with children or animals
well I want to add to that list uh-huh
never work with directives or actives
that would be difficult to make a movie
gonna kill me
all right so what's it about it's
perfect
set in Liberty City
meltdown it's all being shot on green
screen right out back there uh-huh we
take a look at the financial crisis and
then we boil it all down into a really
simplistic battle between two yuppies
what's that lots of training montages
what's the problem Milton McElroy I cast
him in the second lead because he's
cheap zero Talent incidentally well he's
got this new agent Rocco Pelosi he's
been hassling us about reading yeah
he's holding up shooting until it's paid
that sounds problematic it would be if
the director wanted to shoot Anton
bodelare ever heard of him that doesn't
surprise him now he's having a mental
breakdown pissing all over himself
never heard of ever before looks like
you got yourself that new it's a cute
word though
but no happy endings
all right
go to East Los
Santos Los Santos
um
no I have to take this [\h__\h] car
do I have to ah I will not be held back
by Rose oh wait is that
that is the car is this a muscle car
that's also very shiny is this a muscle
car
s hey Solomon I'm just doing that thing
I realized in my excitement I forgot
some details yeah seemed obviously you
want this Pelosi guy clipped no God no
is that an option no no no bad idea bad
idea no clipping anyone just teach him
some Madness he's also in my director's
ear as well I should believe it so teach
this Punk a lesson bring the talent back
to set ideally in a more collaborative
mood I'll see what I can do
they all going to be at the club I'm
told it isn't a club so much as a rat
pit Anton and Milton are supposed to be
there and Pelosi's on the way to pick
them up he's taking him to his lawyer to
sign the contract so if he hears that
someone from the studio coming he'll get
him out fast all right I'll go in quiet
now I want to drive that way I see a
million cars like this on the street out
there but this one no that's so rare
baby or is it just a pro prop a movie
prop
oh no it's a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] they don't like me stealing this
one what about the other one man you
don't care about the other one but this
one you can't touch about [\h__\h] out
I need a garage
I mean
somebody to hack but it's only one star
at least
only one star manageable hopefully
um
uh
where are they anyway
I don't see any cops on the map
I'm doing a bad job at finding me
sorry sorry
[Music]
for our day
oh I can hide here will this open up
parking
no not for me why not
should now they're coming now now I see
them
oh [\h__\h] I lost them nice yeah what did I
break the car for now oh look at it
I broke a light and can I keep this car
can I keep this one
Oh I wanna keep this one
how can I keep it
can I go to my garage and then keep it
if I park it in the grass
where's my
oh it doesn't show my home now
where's my home isn't it like somewhere
up here
um
can I see it somehow
fail the mission
can't do it on the mission wait till
after but what if they take my call away
or like they they they're like in the
middle of the mission they're like okay
let's switch people and then they spawn
me somewhere else and I lose this car
stay on the street and Drive North
already
all right all right
protect the car I want this one it's
pretty how much would this one cost this
one this one seems a little bit more
common than the other thing that we were
driving
finished the mission first should I
a few hundred thousand one million
125k Resort oh
one what the [\h__\h] is
it doesn't exist
you guys are just telling me [\h__\h] oh
I do live somewhere in this area don't
die ah wait I think I know I think I
know up here the hill
yeah I should please be should be
somewhere
is that it over there
send it
go to the rides
or even higher
can we go much higher
Wrong Turn
this this car makes little room sounds
cute
oh it makes different sounds than the
other cars
so what about we go even higher huh
up here maybe Ah that's
it
it really was just going north
okay now will it allow me to keep my car
even when I'm in the middle of a mission
I brought home a new car I adopted it
it's needed a new Daddy
okay so I get out of here but I feel
like last time I did this the car wasn't
there next time we're not I don't know
do I have to register it as mine
is it no no if I take it out again and
leave it somewhere will it despawn
forever or is it now mine the game saves
it I'm good nice okay
okay
very happy hello
[Music]
okay can I sue her now like what oh my
God
she was
threatened is that is that a muscle car
okay
she
why is there no justice for me huh why
is it always like I have to pay for
people's mistakes but the mistakes that
they make like legit I don't get
reimbursed for anything
huh
I don't think that's quite fair this
this game has double standards
maybe it's kind of like
trying to teach me that the world out
there is not quite different than the
world than the world in GTA
well be careful there buddy
[Music]
like it might not be entirely sure I was
ready for that song
that's a compliment no
what was I gonna say
I feel like
it's they're trying to make me stronger
for the world out there
no you can tell me take that as a
compliment maybe she meant it doesn't
insult but you know it's just so it
depends on how you look at it is the
glass half full or half empty you know
whoa whoa
Sparks
this song is really nice with even just
the instrumentals
[Music]
anyway guys
uh
past few days I haven't really been you
know streaming much I know
I mean members only stream was five
hours though but you know if you're not
a member then you probably haven't seen
much of me did you guys miss me
you guys miss me
I'm sorry
but you know sometimes
even the top streamer of En
Emy needs a little bit more time uh for
herself
some private time you know to get some
things sorted and [\h__\h]
always miss you thank you
the mom presenting it's gonna be October
and then the day after tomorrow
spooky months guys Pokemon
I think I think I'll do my frog week
during the spooky month maybe maybe even
in the Halloween week because it kind of
makes sense you know being dressed up
and all that
maybe that would be a good fit because I
was wondering like when should I do it
maybe I can get one more
um
one more frock game approved until then
well hello there
nice helicopter
that is really interesting design
s
[Music]
[\h__\h] stamps all the real [\h__\h] that's
below Spidey buddy I see I understand
it's a minute gotta go grab something
inside
Gianni we nearly got the club we're
finally a goal and you take care of
these guys no cold feet let's go
let's go
8 am I like KDM
I like idiom but I'm not I'm not like
these people okay
huh
why don't you DM song damn
[Music]
um
I think
my songs already have like some
maybe some EDM
was there an enemy there
EDM elements is what I was going to say
what exactly is my mission here
do I have to kill him
or sneak
no no kill okay
here's an opening
that leads nowhere what the [\h__\h] okay
and then there was a ladder
let's go go up the ladder I guess
chocolate
oh okay
um the bird will surely not rat me out
right
how do you take cover again like he's
sneaking right now but I forgot how to
take cover
okay I thought so
um
I'm going the right way
can I
close take out take take him out
wait how do I
okay
I had a little bit of a panic
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] of a quiet one a quiet gun which
gun is quiet I only have like a I think
a sniper that has like a thing that
makes it quiet but is that even on this
character
um I guess we don't see no one just
can't have people noticed and then we're
good
we have to be a bit more careful on on
that front
self takedown
I have like sneak up behind him and then
like Snap his neck is that possible I
never did that before in this game
interesting
as possible I remember doing that when I
was playing death Loop
sneaking up behind them that felt always
really good when it worked out
okay can I do it when I'm like above him
though
do I get like a like a prompt for it
how do you do it
because hey
I didn't even noticing me wait is he
like knocked out no oh he seems
so really
that that did the trick oh
shh I am amazed that that actually
worked
um
excuse me I can't be here this is a
close sight
um
I mean none of these are wait
okay that was quiet that was quiet
that was very quiet I don't think anyone
heard that
I'm so sorry dude
you're at the wrong place at the wrong
time
it's not your fault
wait who's talking
where to go
where am I even going uh up there
see I see I see
he had a girlfriend
I mean she might be
not so unhappy about not having a
boyfriend anymore who knows maybe we did
a good thing
a good thing there's a 50 50 chance
oh
all right I guess I'll keep you alive
what if I get up there do I just kill
all of them what am I doing do I steal
the helicopter
Molly what what's what's the what's the
mission now
hey
oh Mr Richards has been working sick oh
is it fine okay
being seen was fine in that situation
hey you
guys
can you believe this [\h__\h] clown
oh
we're using only fists okay
fine
how many
two what in your face ah
sorry that was not your face I guess I
toss you off this room
oh yeah okay sure man sure all right
let's get back to the lot Michael
deserves a good day
right and I think that was
that was just one hold on potential to
be a good day
can I fly this again how do I get
altitude
ah there you go
Purity I ain't security where am I going
anyway
scared by flying at high speeds on the
bridge is endangered I'm supposed to
scare them well I mean that's okay I'm
even just scaring myself uh oh God okay
this will take a while
wait there's a bridge there
it doesn't inspire me maybe I can fly on
the net
let's see let's see it
oh
does that scare you because it scares me
too
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
uh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] it's really difficult to
control this thing
oh Anthony
I scared all of us to death I'm even
scared to helicopter
yep that's how you got into the
helicopter exactly
um
I think we should like scare them
another ways why does it have to be the
helicopter
him but you can't bully Talent buddy
we're not shooting until I get a new
deal can't can't believe
[Music]
okay one thing we can do is fly as high
as possible I guess
there's another bridge over there
how high can we go can we go much higher
can we go much higher
back to you this is not scary
what about now look up look out the
window
look at the ground is this not scary
no
don't get much higher
this is the best way of using that
I mean the dialogue is continuing so I'm
guessing
it's working do I at some point kill
myself if I go too high
I mean that's that's really [\h__\h] high
[Music]
um
how is this
high enough all right I'll try a
different thing
how about we fly close to buildings that
was apparently a thing that works too oh
when they're talking now
[Music]
are you ready
what's so scary about this stuff
okay it works
that was not scary
you're
working at all
right I am an artist I am not flying so
bad
I've always appreciate the opportunity
he's given you
look I just wanted a better deal
everyone wants a better deal everyone's
serving coffee selling cars sometimes it
just doesn't get better and sometimes
it's better to settle for oh God oh God
oh God
[Music]
okay okay
nice rooftop pool though and Landing is
something we have to work on oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
put it there okay I'm putting it
around okay please tell me I can stop
the helicopter now
do I have to
okay
[Music]
we're done scaring him
God oh God Landing Landing there there
there we can do this we can do this this
is a free zone lack of free space yay
don't get your hair uh your head chopped
off by that I know Solomon is anxious to
see you look feeling a little keyed up
oh really that guy going a little jolly
and call Solomon from wherever I wake up
no not about you see him right now now
or never mind again if you even look
like you'll feel a piss test at any
point on this shoot
understand huh
check that
go
come with me Honorable Men
follow me
or who knows what will happen
a wonderful surprise Anton my boy you're
an artist I know that and this story is
the best kind of art a simplistic cliche
ridden pilot he's a nice dude you will
turn into magic get a grip I love you
so so Milton here has a little something
he wants to say to you say it ah I'm
sorry I just want to say that sorry for
any misunderstandings
so proud of you I appreciate it uh-huh
all the opportunities that that you've
given me of course of course course
oh wonderful you're natural I love you
you had to do absolutely nothing for
that that was all them totally would it
be okay for
if shoot seems cursed for some reason or
another I need an associate producer hmm
I'd love that we'll talk soon I gotta go
his dream come true hell yeah
what like
what qualifies him for that where's the
car doing there
this is just like a respawn right
my car is still in my garage hopefully
hey Mr madraso how's that rebuild going
good I need to see you come to La fuerta
Blanca my Ranch off Senora Road and
bring Mr Clinton Hey look Franklin I
hardly know the kid I don't want him
caught up in this you'll need another
pair of hands all right there's another
guy Trevor Phillips okay I have my
people messenger him
oh why doesn't always have to be Trevor
this Mission what what um oh God
[Music]
please can't make the beep beep beep be
sounds please stop
whoa whoa whoa
all right
because Trevor is great why do you guys
love so much
why I don't understand you guys
anyway we are going to where wait what
where where
well what where are we going
I only see a question like
in blue
he's literally me bro oh I would worry
very much about that
and
um
oh
thank you
you guys have good eyes I respect that
uh
I've been laughing at his Antics well um
there's a difference between laughing
with him and laughing at him and if
anything I'm always laughing at him him
because he's ridiculous and disgusting
and so beneath me
if I met a person like that in real life
I would run for my life I don't want to
like even stand close to a person like
him
like just his existence
makes me question
like everything about this world about
this universe
yeah
I mean people like him literally exist
so I'm already questioning this world
very depressing
oh oh there's a oh wait let me do that
for you
[Music]
will the police be against me or will
they understand that I'm like trying to
solve a crime here
is it okay will it get a star if I do
that
oh yeah
wait should I keep them alive no okay
good we've heard trip is still an item
you can choose to keep it or return it
for a reward oh where's the where's the
stolen item
I got the gun
well
where's the stolen items in here
how did I get the stolen item
a card oh the car
oh
I mean why not we're turning I don't
mind returning it I can't even bring you
a body which you're welcome to do with
whatever the hell you want yeah I'm
taking the body as a souvenir
it's not not scary at all right
wait where's the how do I know where I'm
returning it to
where is that person
um
it was like really close by but it
doesn't show me now green don't I just
don't
know right here
[Music]
no wait what
that's a dead body no
ah the Green Dot is the item well then
um squeezy everybody for messing with
traffic
ah two thousand bucks
you know what I'm keeping it
I'm keeping that that's not worth
returning anyway
for the village ah just show me the dude
there now
um like this only two thousand
it's not worth keeping it's not worth
returning
oh man
do I get like some kind of like honor or
what do I get if I return it maybe even
more money
this car is slow as hell I broke that
[\h__\h] down
[Music]
this kind of stuff is worth it oh is
that is that a muscle car
it just looks like a normal car actually
never mind
we'll never find it
do you want the dead body pill
incredible dude you should keep some of
that for yourself I should I agree oh
huh
books
[Music]
no well that's so mean I'm hungry though
oh yeah
hello hello
please don't drive over me I just need a
car
is that a muscle car
literally every time she sees a car is
this a muscle car
oh nice music
all right back to the mission
that's a Hummer oh
we're gonna see number one another
robbery happening but no I don't care
this time
wow
[Music]
you guys wanna know what I got today for
my from from the post
Al service
um
Channel we had a collaboration where we
updated everyone about some Valkyrie
connect stuff the thing is I could have
already had everything yesterday it
seems
um I was just told you know
that there's these free packages uh uh
on the way to me but they're missing
like
a part of the address so I had to call
them in order to
let them know if I would have done that
one day earlier then it could have been
there in times well that's a little
unfortunate but
wow hi Mr Freightliner oh he's worried
about me
oh phone session told me totes
oh it's funny
so ah today they arrived
and it was
for one of course the cat toilet I
haven't unpacked it yet but it's really
big and I'll test it out maybe um later
today or tomorrow
I'm very curious I'm so excited to use
it it's so big
it's so what a cute yellow card it's so
big
the reason I could never have bought it
myself is because they didn't ship to
Austria and I looked at like different
models different types
um but I didn't find anything
equivalent that would ship to my place
so no I'm not gonna personally use it
you know what I'm talking about but
anyway I want to say wait a second the
other thing
the other thing that um arrived
something was even bigger than the cat
toilet and that was already huge there
was a huge separate package which was
like
um it was not in a box it wasn't like a
like a paper packaging
um and it was like wider and bigger than
me I wrote this on Twitter I was like
what the [\h__\h] is this what
did they maybe by mistake also sent me a
takodachi because they or maybe not even
by mistake maybe maybe they thought I
would like to have one too but it was
really lengthy so I thought it can't be
the taco dutchie
it can't be the taco that's because it's
more lengthy than you know the taco that
it was very square if you would put it
in a box probably
um
so I took a photo I I opened it up and I
was like oh
it's so orange is this maybe a huge
lengthy Taco Daddy
but I was looking for a face and I
couldn't find a face
I was right with the beanbag doll here's
the photo
it is
huge that is a single bed
my guest bed it takes up the whole bed
it's pretty much as wide and as long as
the bed it is just a bean bag a huge
giant sized bean bag and I was wondering
requesting for me
the first first I thought was this like
a request from the viewers but no you
guys only had like several cheap
relatively cheap wishes right this
probably wouldn't have been in the
budget so then I was trying to remember
what were the the suggestions from the
other members I only remembered the one
from from Eda which that one did not
arrive yet
um
but oh you guys seem to remember it is
the one from pecanox
it's huge I was like where the [\h__\h] do I
put this it's huge like it's not even
like normal beanbag chair size it's like
double it's like for two people it's a
two-seater
so now
um since it doesn't fit into my living
room style wise nor space wise
I put it into my office
um it's now like uh on the ground
waiting for me to be used when I need to
rest during for example a VR stream I
suppose yeah sometimes you know I I
figured it might be nice to to fall onto
something to rest in the middle of a VR
stream when I'm exhausted that is the
only uh usage I can think of
you can draw a face on it and when you
see Kotori the plushie for Kotori on the
side maybe I can put a cotoni's face and
feather on top of this one like recreate
it uh make a big lengthy quarterly out
of it but it's definitely not dakimakura
Material because it's like way too big
for that like I can't even give this one
a full hug
it's too big and it would take up so
much space in my bed that my cats would
probably not sleep in my cat in my bed
anymore
so that was one of the things and one
more that I didn't take a photo of
because I have to first build it was
another
um I think relatively small
judging by the package uh cat tree
yes I think that one is from Netflix I
think I remember that she requested cat
toys
but what came was uh was a cat tree
which um if I think is in my opinion
better I I have used for an avocado tree
I'll just put it in one room in the
corner and hopefully the cats will use
it yeah oh yeah yeah
a little a little cat treat medium sized
small size something like that I didn't
build it yet though because I got it
today yeah
apparently if I remember correctly I'm
very sure about it I was gonna get me
luxury sunglasses because I don't know
why those specifically didn't arrive yet
it would have been a really small
package but maybe soon maybe soon I was
really surprised that everything is here
now pretty much except for Ina's gift
and the viewers gifts the ones that you
guys suggested
because how many was it 20 or so
did they say they were gonna give us 20
little gifts or ten
twenty right yeah that you guys
suggested for a certain amount of time
those are not here yet
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
funny was funny it got upgraded to 40.
oh my god really what
oh I'll keep you guys updated on how
that goes
if something arrives
exciting
it's like Christmas
okay am I supposed to just walk in
hello
oh
my God Trevor jail
cop it a little bit slower is the thing
you said you wanted work this is work me
still with the gunshots
yes
oh
Trevor are you good
Trevor gets a little literally horny by
anything
[Music]
that's my friend Trevor uh sit down sit
so what did you tell him about me about
Russell Martin's an old friend of mine
Trevor the truth Martine
is a terrifying cycle tried to kill me
exactly
some people
they no longer fear me as much as they
used to I appreciate the honesty to me
still too low you met in Michael and
maxed it well apparently he's thinking
about testifying against me so I have
him killed
going to
by you all right that was settled it's
as high as it was before my friend
what does friendship mean nothing these
days uh
hello what's the deal this is him
Javier
he was flying off the Liberty City this
afternoon
should be better now it was lower for a
second maybe now it's back to normal I
need back there's a gun set up in the
hills
I have a man watching at the airport
we'll let you know and when he flies by
shoot him down and get the files back
man what's a pay huh Trevor come on
Apple Juice you want to drink not now
she was just trying to welcome our guest
vehicle something versatile I'll handle
with God
okay okay
I can be the shooter
hey wait oh that's my car
we're gonna use your shitty car Trevor
touch on the headsets I don't want to
know how much pee and poop is all over
your car okay never mind I guess we're
not using it fine with me
we'll catch some disease if I
stay in your car for too long so I
prefer it this way
I don't want to be in the hospital for
the upcoming year thank you very much
Trevor you want to hear how your tax
dollars aren't working and then few
minutes let's go to the news
what's that mean
team finally coming Santos it's open
house at the Epsilon Center
and paper yeah I was listening
I'm the shooter he's the driver
I'm listening
oh yeah
okay well I ain't at the observatory yet
start heading that way
that he's a terrifying psycho and that
you might have that in common what is it
we gotta work for him
what are you talking what does he think
I'm saying
stuff
we weren't cases
okay
well is this where Franklin lives but it
does mean he's got money to pay people
who help him when the time comes he'll
do the right thing if he don't please
let me handle it
the [\h__\h]
musical cocoon I have no idea what
Trevor is talking about
there's so many animals
is that our house wow
wow it's so mean it's trying to keep up
with me you want to race you wanna race
yo
I almost got killed be careful oh
there's another one holy [\h__\h] is this
normal
maybe maybe you'll you will be someone's
dinner one day but before that I hope
you live a a long and pleasant fulfilled
life
scare me but I don't know baby bunny
um
love hate all the same if you know
I was saying hi to me they're like oh my
God is
I need to start my car right now and say
hello and ask for a signature on my body
parts
[Music]
I am copyrighted music
um excuse me sir do you not know this is
myself I know it sounds so good that you
might think it's not me but it's
[Music]
everything that's playing on this radio
is my music not not actually not
everything
get in the bed
that sounds like a fret
you can save me I'm in too deep and I
love the rash of that one
with the gun in it you nearby
I might have mercy on myself
to not copy copyright strike myself
whoa
how do I operate it though
well while I'm like in here
how how would that even work that does
that's not logical that doesn't make any
sense
T and makes no sense let's see this gun
it might convince you Marty madratso
hate someone to be messing with
the sale take down the jet legit
want to see a jet and for the red target
calculator to compensate for the
distance
ah oh I got her Southwest of the city
Jets moving how long does it take for my
thing to reach it though that didn't do
it
I I'm not sure like what I'm even
shooting
ah ah do I just aim for the red thing uh
I aim for the red thing and then it
should okay okay I see I see
oh dear
oh baby yeah
not bad
[Music]
no more in here you stay with it
Phoenix this one now oh cute back you
got there follow the plane and get the
pack
of fluid okay this seems actually really
difficult all right
thank you
nice driving so far this is a good bike
oh it's wild time baby
oh
okay we're ready
ah
it's going so well I thought it was
dying right now no where's my bike well
can we redo
this this is not gonna work now
radio please
[Music]
um where is it
dark clouds I guess
ah I'm not the only biker here it seems
I see this is probably the route that
they intended me to take huh
I'm like so far behind this this cannot
be a success
[Music]
oh I see it
targets found once again
[Music]
I'm not I'm not too late
[Applause]
yeah I'm faster than an airplane
oh [\h__\h]
well [\h__\h] hell I was supposed to use
that as a wrap nah
foreign
but then my brain was too slow to make
it out and now I honestly
you guys will not believe what I just
did I pressed space right in front of
this thing hoping that my bike would
jump
[Music]
that's not what works
that is not that one works
I'm surprised I still didn't fail the
mission
all right and okay I see whoa what's up
big Hummer
sway
trying to catch up a little bit
rapidly I'm gonna have to break it down
in dirt God help us
whoa God
your status is God help us
don't worry baby Trevor is here Trevor
will help you better than God according
to all these Trevor fans in my chat
let's see bro coming all the way up here
we gotta get paid
get hands on the bike
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh oh that's not good
can I just take something else now
instead of the bike
I missed the crap
crash
I I think I don't need the bike anymore
though right
you don't you know
I'm supposed to shoot people
silence
silence Javier is that is that him I
silenced him
I might wait he's still alive
okay
he's been silenced get into the plane
yo you guys alive
how's it going
this wouldn't have happened if you would
have let uh Franklin fly this thing
wow wow wow Karma
[Music]
fine I got the files I'll take them to
Madre in the human costume I want an
explosion
we'll talk about that later
I gotta get rid of
this it won't go boom
ER
nice oh
that bike was protected by the plot
plot armor for the bike
very helpful
all right we're leaving the area
imagine
[Music]
whole life myth performing this and
other songs one day
and an actual proper venue destroyed
event oh
okay
can you guys leave
and then you guys shout out babe oh tree
everybody together do I have like a
grenade
no but okay I see
we just pour this
around it I'm not pouring it on top of
it though let me try
okay is that enough that should be
enough and then we have learned
to just shoot
the trail
I'm just gonna lay a little bit
and then puke
hmm
sorry guys I'm trying to um erase
evidence but it's not working
more do I need more
all right let's just use it all up I
guess
hmm there we go
I used it all up
no
oh it's burning
I thought there was a person in those
leaves
it's raining yeah
oh beautiful
evidence eliminated and maybe take away
the gun put it away
I am an innocent person look at me I'm
in a suit that should be enough evidence
I I am innocent
I'm just a normal
businessman
I've missed my meeting
because my Uber
bailed on me
would you be my Uber please
would you like to drive me what oh
there's been a change of plans
Stoner cement Works Sonora Road from
there what are you doing Trevor nothing
you wouldn't do oh
Trevor Trevor
I wouldn't do
somehow I don't believe that
I never believe anything Trevor says
wow this car feels like I'm driving on
ice
what's travel going to do hmm what is he
up to now
where's the drifting car
is this a muscle car
probably not right
[Music]
I just wanted to be an [\h__\h] for a
moment
oh
yeah
baby oh
[Music]
what is that what is that
it looks like [\h__\h] but at the same time
it looks like it has potential to be
something better than [\h__\h]
it looks like a wannabe all the old
timer
mixed with like a
truck buggy whatever
if only it wasn't so [\h__\h] dirty
is that a bug here
[Music]
so it's not a muscle car huh
punch buggy
a souped up Fox
flag and Beetle cool oh
how much does this cost is this cheap or
expensive
what am I getting myself into this I
want one of these
maybe in a different color though it's
cute
it's cute cars it's cheap
it's so cute but imagine someone driving
with this in like a normal City
all eyes on me
oh why is he put come on
come on
it's cute
it's so cute
yeah with a different color
you know get that rid of that texture on
top of it that dirty texture
who wants to listen to their
did he just call
My remix by Halo 20 remix a load of crap
oh where is it it's [\h__\h] excuse me
this game is so insulting to my legacy
wow what
I don't find that dude
I'll find where his house lives
the [\h__\h] has happened why do you have
his car
so turd huh no wonder people are
stabbing them in the back what happened
cheap bastard you know I really don't
know why you mess around with people
like that Mike I mean really yeah we say
it in German answer [\h__\h] question
it's a funny thing to say
okay
kind of got a little angry so I admit I
kind of got a little aim did you kill
him what kind of [\h__\h] animal do you
take me for no I didn't kill him oh [\h__\h]
but I didn't get that why oh no oh [\h__\h]
what did you do oh I just told you what
I just did
no she's probably liking it
unfortunately she's probably we're gonna
have to feeling like this is this is one
of these moments that she keeps on
seeing and um
and the drama novels the Romans dramas
that she's reading
she already called shotgun she's like
how cute
I don't think she's still not enjoying
this wait I'm not driving
I'm not driving what's going on
was that spot on
who's a good boy
look at you
boy would you how do I pet you
pee no oh nope he was not it I'm fine
was there a pet button
jumpy jump play ball
take it
oh I got it back nice go go Champion
yeah a good boy
oh my God he's so excited about the ball
that's so cute come
[Music]
on come on that one there
what good boy
putting it down there making one more
okay how about yeah
go get it speed
before it goes down the mountain
Pro grenade next no don't even have one
oh [\h__\h] I do
[Laughter]
that
we don't want that
go get the ball oh oh [\h__\h] is uh
that's a bit dangerous be careful
can my can my dog die
be careful now
oh what a good boy what a good boy
he's Immortal wonderful wonderful
oh you know this this wouldn't really be
the type of dog I would get but he's
really cute
he's so sweet every dog is a sweetie
even if they look a little bit you know
dangerous they're all clean tights yes
dogs are just so loving
and charming and caring and make you
feel like you are their hero
all right uh what is what is Trevor
supposed to do why don't we uh Franklin
why why did we switch to Franklin Ave I
have an M I have a d I have an l
I have a t
do we go to m Maybe
yeah I miss that Bubba likes you a lot
yeah Bubba liked me but um
top you stay here maybe Chapel full of
bikes and other vehicles you cannot get
enough we we want him to follow us okay
why why do why do we need him with us
oh he's safer if he doesn't
follow us but okay what happened here
yeah
that was not me
um what was I saying I am it's like you
know
I I like like medium size and big dogs
but small dogs they kind of like a lot
of times they creep me out a little bit
because like their eyes are kind of
creepy and
especially with like Chihuahuas and so
on now Bubba's eyes didn't scare me but
I don't know small dogs they're like
not quite my type
I'm not quite my time no no no
no no oh hello car is that is that a
muscle car
wait
and all but also like I have this
problem with dogs and this doesn't
matter it doesn't matter if they're big
ones or small ones but I really don't
like that they try to like lick
everything and then they are they just
don't know
what like social distance is because
like what's what's it called not social
distance what I'm looking for is the
word for like you know
keeping keeping a certain distance just
just you know
because personal space thank you they
don't know personal space they come up
to you and they they try to sniff
like not even the most intimate sections
of your body which is really
a way to make me feel uncomfortable
[Music]
yeah it's it's no tingly
tingly and
[Music]
yeah don't don't want that don't want
that at all I mean honestly I would be
happy if when I reach out my hand to my
kitty cats if they decide to slurp a
little bit on my hand but they normally
don't do that but even if they would it
would be like gentle and sweet and not
so [\h__\h] slimy and truly like it would
be when a dog does it like that's just
too much you know what I mean you guys
if you have had both experiences before
then you know the difference
the dog's drool is like the saliva it's
like everywhere [\h__\h] everywhere it's
like you're taking a shower in the dog
saliva
not for me not for me
depends on the dog
really
from my experience they all just have
too much
too much drool going on
okay
I had to kind of lay low for ew yeah
that nice Mexican we met
me and T did that job for him and we
fell out
of me I wish I was
where is the lady desert out by Alamo
sea
with Trevor's place
absolutely uh oh
Trevor's got his wife
come on the Mexican's wife well it might
soon be his wife
nothing
it was that see intro
it was that see you drool because of my
graveyard and gravy in my hair
I'm gonna cut your arm off
what the hell's that you're made
oh business partner good guy very loyal
ew Ron oh
and this is Patricia
beautiful sorry about everything
oh oh do you feel the tension here she's
gonna come to you
chop you up into little pieces before
spraying your pulp mess down the drain
no no no no not Trevor not like that
I appreciate your honesty
you are a good man oh I can see that you
need your eyes examined then
run
you miss me yeah Trevor a bit I mean
[\h__\h] business
sob story I'm gonna rip your [\h__\h]
throat out and shove a turd down the
hole it's not a soft story it's just not
quite come good yet
but I heard about something to do with
Merryweather those [\h__\h] big cash of
weapons they got coming in so I thought
you might want to uh requisition it fans
fantastic let's go I'm in whoa no no not
you she's spilling it I wanted man stay
low and watch her okay she's a good lady
let's go Ron good to meet you Michael
come on let's go
all right they're having fun but what
about the lady
for [\h__\h] sake
[\h__\h] fucktastic [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] Trevor
and the plane this is not a plane that
said Dad honestly said get into the
plane
but I got into a car
not gonna take out a private Army
on underground we gotta meet him in the
air uh
okay well I knew that you were pissed
after the Merryweather Heist do they
mean gets to the plane that was [\h__\h]
right right so I've been monitoring
chatter tapping into Merryweather
networks feels good to be back in the
company of a professional
I was expecting something a little more
impressive I want something like that I
wanna I Wanna Be an advantage YouTuber
right no longer called van life forever
not been terribly kind what's the end
game man we had a good thing
that's a muscle car where's my
consultant
I want a franchise Network Ron I want
reward cards merchandise I want to make
gun violence and drugs dependency
accessible to every man and feast from
Whole feet to Vespucci and one country
clubs and a depressed wife with blonde
hair and a hospital secretary who
bounces on my boy
maybe if you'd buy him to Oscar's
business I'm hearing there's a lot of
Bounce in the Firearms sector well I
heard there's a lot of Bounce in your
head where's the TP Enterprise windfall
huh it takes time time and money
the [\h__\h] face is gonna give that to me
you guys you know what I'm starting to
think that you guys are trying to
deceive me
a feeling that muscle cars
don't even
existed militia our family don't exist
because every time I ask is this a
muscle car you guys say no
so perhaps you are trying to Bamboo me
but I see right through you guys
I see what you're doing
we're trying to pull a funny on me again
huh
who dances with the funsies yet huh
you think you got it all figured call a
car
I think you got it all figured out you
think
[Music]
you think you can fool me
there's no such thing as a muscle car if
there was such thing as a muscle card
and there would also be such thing as a
as a no muscle car well never heard of
that have you ever seen a no muscle car
huh
I don't fly this thing
how do I go up again
[\h__\h] I don't know
I forgot how to fly this thing
hopefully a regular car no like an
unless killer I'm sitting in front of
the little PC all day car like me
bye
oh I tried that though maybe I didn't
have enough patience
inverted red is like
oh
um I think we did it
why is it tilted
there we go
[Music]
[Applause]
fly as low as possible I don't think I
can get any lower than this
I can't move
oh
stop
[Music]
getting it much slower
I can't get lower than this
thank you thank you the crab duster got
stuck what does that mean
you mean my plane got stuck yeah that's
exactly what happened thank you so much
for realizing
okay I need to relearn how to fly this
[\h__\h]
oh
um
fly fly a little piece of [\h__\h]
now
we're talking okay how do I stay up in
here how oh whoa whoa whoa
hey
what what happens
I was pressing 5 and w
ow both of it
okay come on come on come on
we'll figure it out one day
recommend the controller you say but
if I just plug it in now
will it work
s good
ah my audio switched to oh no oh my good
we're good
how how does it work on the controller
what's the oh
okay the triangle is getting out of the
thing
R2 back on the joystick what back on the
joystick okay well first of all
before that like I don't even know oh
there we go
to the side though
uh
uh L1
how do I go backwards
this way okay okay forward backwards are
uh two out two and then
um
oh God
this is a whole new world that's opening
up to me right now God oh God
okay okay and then what what is the
equivalent for five
maybe just the joystick downwards
[\h__\h] I'm stuck
destroyed
well it's not my fault it's so [\h__\h]
weak
okay
now
um forward and then like this okay okay
oh wait oh God this is really difficult
[Music]
we'll take some time to get used to as
well
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] hell
I'm in the air it will be easier but
you get stuck so easily with this [\h__\h]
unbelievable
and unbelievable
how what
what am I supposed
what what
okay it's kill me again please
I can't get
[Music]
control it doesn't really make it easier
for some reason
how do I make it go again
[Music]
how do we make an explode
nice
too bad
totally didn't want that to happen at
all
okay okay you can do this you can do
this Kiana
nope stop stop stop stop turn turn turn
turn turn turn turn turn turn turn
[Applause]
[Music]
so hard
it's so difficult these controls are so
weird
it's like not doing enough at all
oh
I made it out I made it out I made it
out
now
tomato
put away a keyboard is easier somehow
okay
uh
wait just this way this way this way and
this way this way this way
okay
that's why that's why okay okay we are
straight
we are finally straight
well yeah straight guys
now
I have to lift this baby up
and taking off in three two one
okay okay okay one time once you're in
the air that's not so bad anymore okay
thank God
okay okay
no problem
okay we had this before
but this time of a controller now you
can't tell me to press F because it's
not app I don't have an F button
on my controller and I already figured
out what the leaf airplane button is
it's a triangle
sorry
cargo planes on my 12. we got the
weapons they're using to enslave us
okay okay
it like vibrates sometimes I don't know
why is it because I'm too little
land again
I thought I said that oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
yes what I'm saying
what can we get even lower
shut up you want me to put my nose into
the dirt
thank you trailer for once I agree with
you
but he just wants the best for us I
guess
[Music]
all right what now
reflect
let's point
[Music]
s
I've done [\h__\h] up
hmm interesting okay I'm guessing that
that whole thing I was flying over is
like a fort
the the landing area the airplane
okay now we have to go for the suffering
again
um
we can do this believe in kiwawa
yeah oh
she's doing it
smooth
[Music]
once you got it figured out it's okay
it's quite all right
is monitoring air traffic
okay I'm low I'm low
I'm really low
but like tell me when I can go high
again
he wants me to to like I don't know Ram
the cargo plan a lot I don't know what
exactly they want me to do I got the
cargo plane right ahead of me
better in our hands uh-huh say close to
the ground
it's not close enough
okay
didn't I say we had to take them in the
air to have any kind of shot at this I
thought I said that good going kiwawa
such a natural
[Music]
oh
to fly over the trees sorry
wow
press the green button there's nothing
green on my controller I don't use an
Xbox controller
oh I need to get ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's right I know I know I know it's
not green for me though and I know what
it does
I'll get you on the radio
okay this this time first time is the
charm let me drink some water though
what I don't have a custom controller
just a PS5 controller there's nothing
green on here what are you talking about
and here we go again
oh this is my third try my first real
try we don't count the tries where I was
not even flying
it's not fair
you didn't even give me a chance
to be monitored from the military base
what is
it vibrate so much
you guys don't own a piece five huh oh
[Music]
really
like when I'm in the car I can literally
drive over everything and it won't be a
problem
and now you're telling me that this this
little itsy bitsy tiny bitsy
think of an obstacle
is enough to take down my whole plane
that's what I get for flexing
well you know
I I should be flexing I guess because
[Music]
um
sorry nose was itchy because
I didn't even pay for the PS5 oh wait
what that's a flex too oh let's see low
[Music]
um
is this a muscle car
guys is this a muscle car
yeah my PS5 was a very generous gift
very generous from Bandai Namco so in
order to play
Tales of a rise which I then never end
up playing on the PS5 because it arrived
too late
okay
I am
tracking the plane are you planning on
forcing them to land didn't I say we had
to take him in the air
kind of shot at this I thought I said
that yeah I noticed my PS5 a few times
already on stream
I used it for strength
and uh used it for a couple other games
which ones
what can I play on PS5
also should I go right side or left side
now because after that Hill
is the base
I'll fly left side
clear they're too high drop down
I'm in control of this
what oh oh
I see okay we're funny guys very funny
you confused me very much uh Yakuza and
deaf Loop is when I played on PS5 yeah
yeah yeah that's true
yeah yeah yeah yeah and I'm in a crop
duster this is something I'm acutely
aware of enough
uh-oh okay okay now I can turn the big
turn
okay okay I think we have dodged the
fort successfully
can I fly high yet no still no okay okay
but then we're never gonna reach the
altitude of the plane
look at them having fun on the beach
what's up
oh [\h__\h]
how's the wind feeling
and impregnating her
mother hung up on appearances in LS just
far
the [\h__\h] are you you're the most
[Music]
honestly
wow he's like really it's like the cult
of Trevor he really believes in Trevor
if Trevor had a cult that dude would be
his his top man
would do anything for him probably
oh wait is this like one of those zones
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry just fine Ron
I mean that's I don't know what I'm not
supposed to fly over but I guess maybe I
was just too high and that's it
where's the plane there
you speak to Oscar just a regular town
okay
I'm not risking life in limp for a
shiminate soul are you sure it's just
Oscar don't like getting messed with do
the deal
Phoenix called so much better thank you
oh that reminds me guys
speaking of cults
who's like really pissed off
the other day because something woke me
up
earlier tonight
[Music]
long
please give me a checkpoint oh thank God
oh thank [\h__\h] God yokata
thanks you thanks you for the checkpoint
all right
um
what was I saying wait I don't even need
to press uh R2 anymore I was pressing
that the whole time
huh
only the joystick now
I can be myself out here bullying
Reckless totally yeah things that make
me
wait a second they talk so much we
already heard it though
I lose speed
thank you for telling me
who are you is there a cable car over
there on the mountain
the lights indicate it's a campfire
cool I want to ride that can you ride
that too
in the game
all right anyway so
um I Heard a doorbell ring and I was
like okay well I guess I'm gonna wake up
and you know open the door in case it's
something from Amazon or something you
speak to Oscar the Mexicans the steel on
I'll let them know it's in the works the
work I'm not ready
am I allowed to talk am I allowed to
talk or am I gonna get canceled
okay
and then I go to the door and I look for
the people
and I see two ladies I'm like and it's
probably not Amazon but they they
reacted as if they saw me looking for
the people that always makes me so
nervous I'm almost like do they see me
because sometimes they act as if they
see me through it even though they
shouldn't be seeing me
always makes me question
so I opened up the door because they
were like waving at the door
that's
[Music]
[Applause]
all
so I opened up the door and the first
thing they say is
[Music]
the 1989 crop custard just enjoying the
beautiful Sanitation
really shoot me down well that seems a
little extreme doesn't it
okay so uh
the first thing they say is
what was it
can you find happiness forever
and I'm like
[\h__\h] you woke me up for that stupid
cult religion whatever kind of [\h__\h] so I
said I ain't got no time for this sorry
and I closed the door on them normally
oh I'm flying inside are you [\h__\h]
kidding me I don't know about that
normally when there's like I don't know
what's wrong with you some people at my
door then want something from me I often
feel sorry I feel bad about like just
closing the door right in front of them
so I would like oh
often entertain them but in this
situation I was like
[\h__\h]
[Music]
and this in this situation I was like
that's not even like they're not even
asking for like um donations for for you
know for like a
samarita bond
I don't know what that is in English but
we have like some kind of like uh first
aid people that work voluntarily
see that I will entertain and I will
have a little talk with them at my door
even though I don't want to
oh God this is really difficult
but those two ladies I feel like they
were part of a cult
and in just that first question
I'm like
I I just quarreled out of the out of the
bed and I opened the door with my fluffy
bathrobe
and the [\h__\h] they say to me can you
find happiness forever yo you woke me up
for this what
L one R2 okay okay this is really
difficult though
[\h__\h] I was so mad I was so mad
really angry
never again this is why sometimes I just
completely ignore the doorbell I don't
even go looking unless I expect
something like Amazon
because I know that something's coming
for sure
okay let's just uh smoother than before
oh [\h__\h]
chill
ah [\h__\h] why do I lose control like that
ah wait it's so difficult what the [\h__\h]
why does it get so difficult here is
this the air from the airplane
and then like blocking me
also
do your hair
[Music]
is on fire and it's now in the Glide due
to the interesting
controllable maybe lens I'm not gonna
land it away
[Applause]
so difficult
oh
wait L1 you know I mean I I don't mean
L2 and RT you mean l one and RT okay
okay
what's wrong with you
this feels like a completely different
game now like Nero automata or something
like that what the [\h__\h]
yeah
what the
what the [\h__\h]
what I'm trying to also use the other
buttons but like and then here it makes
me like swing around
it's so crimp and [\h__\h] up go somewhere
else [\h__\h] you you're cringe
this is not easy
do I not have to go like exactly oh
that's it I just have to get close to it
oh come on
I was trying to get like in the Middle
Lane
on the switch controls
oh
you've gave me notes I am
I did it on my first try well good for
you I hope you achieved anything else in
your life too because this honestly
sounds like you achieved nothing else
if you're mad at me for missing a plane
a few times then I don't know what to
tell you
yeah I don't need I don't need those
people in my chat if you're just here to
[\h__\h] on me
and go somewhere else
okay
anyone else
[Music]
oh
wow
yeah I gotta get another article I saw
that
[\h__\h] article was on my side at least
oh
[Music]
guess we're learning how to fly a cargo
plane now should I do this with the
controller as well I'm guessing it has
similar controls
lbr before left right
I'll be Arby is at L1 l r one which ones
are those
oh wait what is this changing frequency
over
um the cargo jet is now part of the TP
Enterprise Fleet you with the max
it is the same okay
are we Landing there
oh manageable
can we lose speed a little bit thank you
stop uh where the [\h__\h]
and look at where are we going
in the long run
ah
it's there okay okay
oh
[\h__\h] okay
not here
wait no it's not wait where am I have
one against my look okay I'll go go go
turn around Cricket airspace
I'm trying to divert my course
Please Don't Shoot Me Down
am here at the bird of my course
sing around
how funny isn't it flying solo
threatening everybody's lives
isn't it just so fitting for Trevor
what do you mean
this is normal right this is supposed to
happen
okay okay
this is normal okay thank God
I'm going higher now what does
[Music]
straight up Star Wars
what
it's like a different game again
can we get much higher
did he has aliens no way I don't think
you understand the effort I've gone to
be here pal
I feel like I'm a big whale in the ocean
and these are the fish that are like
sticking to me
cute
what you wouldn't shoot me down anyway
think of the ground casual indeed in
detail that's that you should think of
that otherwise you're the evil one
but I think we're doing pretty well
um
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I'm not entertaining your wishes
for baby
aren't you
to the V to the o to the r
Trevor Trevor trouble
Trevor higher if not should we go higher
who can't keep up with this can you huh
what what does that mean what does that
mean weapons free
[Music]
weapons
what am I supposed to do
you use
is this a script is this supposed to
happen
I should not control it no control no
control okay
yeah
it seems familiar uh
Andy to turn as just slower oh sure okay
parachute to safety all right
oh what's that is that my car my my
airplane oh
Our Father should I like go towards that
oh God don't fall into the water
whoop
where's it going oh
nice
nice no casualties except some dead fish
I'm such a hero
couldn't have done it better than that
this is beautiful music
and out
down nicely yeah no
got it
[Music]
yeah
minor turbulence it's just a minor
surveillance
what about the plane
first try indeed
what what now someone call me Ron
[\h__\h] are you okay I saw the plane go
down I survived and lizard Army didn't
do so well so that's something oh thank
God the fuselage went into the Alamo sea
you might be able to salvage the
hardware with dive gear or something
oh good idea
but it'll take time tell Oscar he ain't
getting these guns okay look I gotta ask
are you in with the federal government
an agent Sanchez was around here saying
you and Michael had to meet his
supervisors at the garage the cook site
[\h__\h] I gotta do this okay but I'm using
them all right they ain't using me let's
make that clear
I'm sorry for being mean before
that person is probably not in the chat
anymore but I'm sorry but you were a
[\h__\h] butthole too but I'm sorry I
don't want to be this mean I'm not like
that normally
you're triggering me and that's not okay
I'm so mean such a meanie
it's like a little question mark uh
thing going on here
I'm becoming like Trevor yeah Trevor is
doing this to me it's not my fault
you're gonna meet of it that's where
you're gonna meet one you know what I'm
saying hey totally know what you're
saying give me a sip of that what come
on my throat's dry as a [\h__\h] why
is your mother dry when you're
[Music]
well it didn't sound like nothing all
right it didn't seem like nothing I
don't think that it was nothing I didn't
mean nothing by it old man old man old
man
you old [\h__\h]
that's right
shoot it for me
you'll do me a big favor
oh come on
loser you had one job
sorry man we're sorry one job you had
what
neutralize 25 rednecks
and yo
what what even our red X I don't know
what it was done with that is that
rednecks
okay what
we're in the Rapids now
I'm taking out the traps Sandy Shores
uh maybe some cover would be nice too no
I don't need cover oh I'm dying though
I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying
I'm healing I'm healing
I have one minute left
oh God
who's who the [\h__\h] is shooting me
come on Redneck oh I'll give you redness
wait how many did it say 20.
this is what I get
one more
[Applause]
that should be done just don't die now
and I just don't die
survive survive survive survive survive
survive
oh God oh God oh God oh God oh God
[Music]
I'm winning
two one
[Music]
anymore
[Applause]
what do I get for that nothing
[Laughter]
that was interesting we stumbled into
something
very interesting there
and we get my favorite
car
but it's not it it's like very similar
at least
[Music]
yeah I don't want to listen to music
right now I just wanted to be quiet
oh I know we ain't cooking but since I
held one I'm thinking I thought you
might think of me if you need extra gun
on a job or something [\h__\h] all right
thank you uh
where where am I going next
there's a bee
let's go to the B
[Music]
sorry a truck
Martin what's up
you know I've been thinking about it I'm
not quite sure if I'm ready to accept an
apology
[Music]
Patricia doesn't want to speak exactly
neither do I I will find you
okay well I'll put some coffee on that
I'm tired
no am I tired can you give me your tire
ah it's okay buggy I love you no matter
how many tires you're missing you're
beautiful the Way You Are
that's more than just a flat tire that
is like no tire
you can't call that a flat tire anymore
that's okay I'll I'll use you
nonetheless you're still useful to me
just because you're a little bit damaged
and injured doesn't mean anything
um
that was a muscle cut which one
what was the muscle car
that red truck over there
oh that thing
it's a muscle car
yeah
that doesn't look muscular why is there
yeses and nose and almost
okay not a muscle car not a muscle still
not a muscle car wasn't close
wait B what what am I here for
foreign
looks like a rust convenience store
hello
I'm here for some booze I guess
someone here huh
oh I got heel dipping
what's the B for
is the bee literally for Booze or
upstairs oh
oh
at a small place oh I haven't been here
in a long time huh
what
I remember this place still I remember
like shooting in here
I'm running down
oh
my
God
ah come on I did not have a toilet yeah
this place you got here oh yeah this
this here is my place
for my place all right relax I was just
being sarcastic yeah well don't be all
right because the world doesn't need any
more sarcasm it's the blight of the age
and I get the point you you're gonna get
the point you're like every other
[\h__\h] you made a bit of money that's
illegal
yeah news for you I was always a turd no
you weren't man you were something but
now man you know you like this place
you're a shell go [\h__\h] yourself are you
some kind of pure morally justifiable
[\h__\h] but because you're you're you're
totally psychotic somehow it's okay I'm
honest all right oh yeah you're [\h__\h]
hero so far above it all oh yeah well
I'm not ripping open your [\h__\h] chest
to see what's replaced your heart rip it
open see what's there baby cause I'm
ready so mean hello
oh ladies ladies what's up
I'm sorry but we've got a problem
government funding thing we need you to
uh
investigate a research lab Upstate
investigate experience nerve gas
biological Terror
God I don't pay tax listen You'll need
some fairly standard gear
boat
heavyweight helicopter truck weapons
you'll have to Source all of that
takes time perhaps oh no worries there
Trevor he just came in with a lot of
money
is that sarcasm oh you're [\h__\h] a
right it's sarcasm you [\h__\h]
a few weeks ago I was happily retired
sulking by my swimming pool my psychotic
best friend shows up out of nowhere
mistakes I made honest mistakes I made
over a decade ago we are a little posse
are flat [\h__\h] broke but hey let's go
out and spend two million dollars on a
tandem rotor [\h__\h] Chopper so I can go
steal nerve gas for [\h__\h] terrorists
forgive me you ignorant [\h__\h] but sarcasm
is all I [\h__\h] got
sarcasm and a room full of you Cuts yes
whoa welcome back man it is the old you
yeah yeah yeah well we gotta go it's
been great for it to be the new Manny's
class now remember ladies you keep us
way out of this thing Michael very angry
[Music]
I'll give Lester a [\h__\h] call he said
he knew about something now you tell him
when we're driving towards Polito Bay
come on you're driving we're on a
mission
let's go get into your car I will I will
you don't have to tell me don't I know
what to do Ah that's my red car
get in there
you might go surprise yeah that's true
but um
it's running so fast
oh I don't want to wait for him turn
that up up
I want
serenity
Muslim
what now we got a funding problem so we
need a job before the beautiful sunset a
Bank in the sticks I need you to meet us
there Polito Bay right that's the one
I'll get on a bus
could have given you a ride
what must you beat us there whoa and
expect that here no way good call
a million sorry sorry I know I'm I'm a
bad driver
oh
this AC Bank you're gonna be carrying
that kind of change local law
enforcement extort money from all
Sunrise oh
in the area they
cash in safe deposit boxes then there's
all the normal small town payroll stuff
well
you know I've been thinking about you
Trevor your lifestyle oh have you really
yes I have
people always try to label you you know
Maniac psycho friend industry leader
some ways you defy categorization but
then what
what think about it where you live Sandy
Shores you precious ass I'm sorry there
ain't a place nearby for you to get your
colonics right but why are you out here
it's off the grid we're away from it all
it's somewhere real and authentic this
is America
and real people ain't been priced out
yet that's American I'm sorry I'm
passing oh [\h__\h] move okay what about
the way you dress what about it thank
God America has all kinds of places
right if you don't
you don't [\h__\h] it's not all like this
that fit so yours are all right a little
out there you're a little wacky
whatever's in the shop is what I get
Jesus what what is this it's not an
absence of taste tea it's the opposite
of taste you should be a stylist and
then there's this
the hair the weird music the funny toys
the niche straw yeah
everything Niche is that how you
pronounce it
you are a hipster
your oops I
hasters I don't think he's a hipster
hipsters are cooler than him
oh he's he's very insulted now
I love saying they hate it am I upset
really [\h__\h] do
self-hatred common hipster affliction
maybe I'm a hipster just by being a veto
there yeah you guys are saying
the skinny lattes and then I don't drink
skinny
maybe you're not a classic Garden
variety hipster
sure what the hipsters Aspire I'll even
drink Bubba tea Trevor are the Proto
hipster
I don't care about boba tea don't know
what you're talking about
I don't agree with
what the best conversation so far try to
wind me up but I'm very
very
I want this conversation
it's the only one I'm able to follow so
far the only conversation in the whole
game
no continue please
please please continue
please roast him some more
make fun of him please what's up here
all right get out to take us to get out
here from LS
beautiful mountain
oh
wow
time travel
sick
all right where's the bus
[\h__\h] and knock it off what it's like
a child
break your [\h__\h] fingers you don't
knock that [\h__\h] off well please all
right you alleviate the boredom
he's [\h__\h] time
ah finally downtown
hey hey hey Welcome To Paradise you know
what I hate when I hate with a passion
just like you hate me stopping in the
middle of the dialogue is people that
like no matter if it's a bus or Subway
or so people don't stand in front of the
door that's about to open even though
people are gonna go outside and then
they don't even move when the the people
are trying to walk outside of whatever
door they're walking through and you're
you are like in the way and even then
you just gonna say you wouldn't move
even a centimeter they just I don't know
what they're thinking like sometimes I
really want to say
um like Ayo like people are trying to
get out you [\h__\h] idiot you [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] like do you not realize what's
going on there you are not going to get
in as long as I am not going to get out
because I will be blocking the path for
you to get in as long as you're blocking
the path for me to get out you
understand what's going on here huh it
is so difficult
in Japan this problem doesn't exist
because in Japan people really follow
this Unwritten rule of please line up on
the side and don't don't be in the way
for anybody I wish that every country
understood this by nature of how to do
that
why is it so difficult to understand
I can't
I can't I can't this way dry out here
don't worry brother Mike will take care
of all your moisturizing needs thank you
thank you for listening to my TED talk
thank you we'll get started thank you
uh
if you're one of those people who stand
in the way guys then stop doing that
please you're triggering me
at the entrance if the paperwork's
correct the alarm will be a relic we
should be in and out before the local PD
knows what's happening okay
I'll find out about us
I'll wait the other side is that a
muscle car or is that the muscle car is
which one is is one of these in muscle
car
just asking for a friend
that's the entrance to the bank nothing
special take us around back okay no okay
oh why is this person so depressed
hey it's okay it's a sunny day everyone
should pay attention to us back there I
like it yeah the place is remote it's
got the right amount of foot traffic
this will do let's check out the alarm
to be sure
dude Dad they wake up and they do his
dreads first they wear a snail and then
they become snake
Long Long bucket
what are we doing
yeah he told me to like look at Alarms
or what was it
the cameras what well am I supposed to
look at it
I'm supposed to get in the car
all right all right
empty lot with the open top dumpster in
it huh I'm here
am I not seeing like
[Music]
what am I not saying the the the the
yellow light again
Mission failed for chasing cat
here here
yeah okay
it's gonna cost more to break that
system than the score is going to pay
when we're gonna find a new score no no
no no this is the score what are our
options it's a dumb idea but we could
trigger the alarm see what kind of
response they throw out oh that's a dumb
idea hey you heard the man all right
shoot the sucker
come on I don't think there's a fine
idea
focus on the alarm but once they're
alive
is this the alarm
well which one is the alarm I don't see
an alarm
that's the alarm
okay I brought my police scanner to
drive over to the gas station opposite
the bank and we'll monitor chatter okay
okay watch from gas station all right
Savings Bank all cars in the area please
respond I'm responding I'm kind
okay
Roger that four units backup team
station is available they've dispatched
four cars in 60 seconds and more on
standby and it isn't even 30 Victor
shots fired this is a real headache what
do you got on the clock 40 seconds
normal the response is out of proportion
wow tops in this County are dirty they
just had nothing else to do piggy bank
this is them what is that a 67 second
response time
yeah four Cars
one and a two Garden dirty mind free we
can take this wait right here we'll see
if anything about their routine suggests
a weakness
they're very slow to get out of the car
from what I can see
they're just chilling
checkpoints on the great ocean High away
and the Sonora freeway card a car
searches and record checks checkpoints
searches
caught because Lester needs a wheelchair
hey wheelchair or not we're still faster
than your ass bastard wait do I have to
switch to him
nah I'm gonna outrun a cop we've gotta
go we're going it goes up for the Trevor
could be the one running from the cops
yeah
[Music]
Trevor you could have at least had the
courtesy to close the [\h__\h] door here
this is kind of windy oh [\h__\h]
come I should have known you're fine I'm
gonna get out of here Trevor Phillips of
course this would turn into a car chase
for that being chased not yet not at all
look take a deal they'll never figure it
out fine we just gotta get back to
Trevor's office what Trevor says office
he really means a burnout gas station by
the Alamo sea I've seen the title of
ownership
get off the road up here okay it must be
Trevor I could have said that a little
bit earlier
okay
and judging by the glassware he ordered
a year ago I'm guessing it's a meth lab
a meth lab and there's some some song
you guys know that one sounds like a
classic but I've never heard it before
where math is made great nothing like a
pharmaceutical that's good though I like
it oh [\h__\h] don't worry it's gonna be
safe look you had any ideas about the
bank are you sure we can't disable the
alarm the alarm is a uxvf 111
classification minute longer
third-party verification multiple
monitoring centers sure I can disable it
you can do anything I believe in you
it's more than the job Earth of course
so what do we do we went away it's not
like we need the money uh about that
you've been day trading no
I mean yeah yeah I've been straight but
no that's not why we need the money
then why do you need the money I always
need money so
money runs the world on the coast the
IAA are using it manufacturing poison
gas
[Music]
let the government
well that sounds idiotic and improbable
enough to be possible looks like the
road takes a dip and a turn after that
bridge slow down okay so I got to do
with you and Trevor sticking up the
Blaine County Savings and Loan agent
Steve Haynes needs 2 million plus to
finance a raid on the left and guess
who's doing the raid and guess who's
paying for it ah I see yeah well I don't
really see but I'm doing it and it
sounds like Trevor dmca
I I guess I've lost all my [\h__\h] sorry I
had on the hit
this is uh it's too loud though now tell
me can we do it or do we move on yeah it
was a good song I want to listen to it
how messy we talking taking the cops
head on messy well they are dirty cops
that's what Trevor says
we can do it guys out here aren't
treated like the LSPD they are going to
be prepared for a well-armed
well-drilled team coming straight for
him yeah well we need an edge something
to tip the odds in our favor and I got a
couple ideas all right
all right we're done talking now
that was a good song maybe I'll add that
to the list of songs that I want to sing
in the karaoke I feel like maybe next
week I'm gonna do an unarchived English
karaoke the one I did for Members Only
Yesterday the archived one was sorry
it's quite fun
for a second I thought I was travel I
was like yeah but I'm gonna fail my
mission if I kill him but wasn't him
lucky
yeah I got some songs I want to sing
um
yesterday I heard uh one song on the TV
show
that reminded me of the fact that I
should be singing that one what was it
again it was also um it's a song that
also happens in in Shrek
I don't got my reputation
[Music]
I think that would fit my voice I'm
gonna sing that one so I added that one
to my karaoke list too he says what took
you so long had to let you win we have
bad reputation
[Music]
all track songs are good but uh actually
yeah I wasn't reminded of it by Shrek
but the different show
ew blood sugars are low I'm making you
some leftovers what is that it looks
like really soggy cereal and milk you're
hungry right then you're gonna be making
the wrong decisions but I've been making
wrong decisions my whole life that's how
I ended up here
same TBH just like me for real for real
what is that Jesus Christ Trevor what is
that good question what's wrong with you
looks like you pooped it out an eyelid
that's probably not even human unless
that gas station job gentlemen
good I'm gonna stay here I have some
standards Trevor
not very high but you don't show that
the response will be too quick to beat
and too strong to walk through it means
you gotta face the cops head on the
dirty cops no problem the dirty cops
head on head on
man I don't know
you'll be prepared convoys carrying
military-grade Hardware past near here
to get to Fort Zancudo and I propose
hijacking one and using the equipment to
get an edge on the locals
we're done here
anyway you won't be outside the bank too
long well it's a bay so you're straight
away from the water where Franklin can
be waiting in a boat to get you out of
there because this is ideal but the only
way I can see of taking the score and
providing for your FIB pay masters
fine
we need Personnel just a gunman they'll
be taking on the coffee okay my advice
choose someone good
14 but this one's the best one probably
seven percent six 12. talk about my
buddy he wanted to join us and honestly
it's not so bad he has a lower cut and
his skills are not too bad
to be honest
you're fine should be good enough yeah
yeah I'm sure this is the guy
pretty sure unless we already have you
know a personal connection that's
important too
that's important yeah that's the guy
confirm that should do I'll get the
equipment together Michael you reach out
to Franklin Trevor you do what you do
Roger I'll call you when I'm ready to
move on
I mean it's gonna be tight but you know
Mikasa
it's all kinds thank you very much I'll
give you a ride I'll sleep somewhere
else
you you you you everything in this
fridge must be yeah yeah that's it well
that's what I thought because like you
haven't even been here for such a long
time how long was all of that in the
fridge
you're not gonna clean it up are you
you're just gonna leave it there forever
I know you Trevor but now I know you
um
[Music]
guess these redneck dudes been looking
for you homie some angry [\h__\h]
oh because I killed 25 of them Bernie
actually okay well it's got to be 101
Brothers what's left of them I'll pick
up Michael and we'll come to you the
coincidence
oh I didn't do anything I don't know
what you're talking about
I didn't do [\h__\h]
I mean the scent
[\h__\h]
I am innocent but uh next we're going to
the tea maybe we're going to the tea
Trevor goes to the T
is this a muscle bike
let's go
it's just a short ride though
bounce bounce bounce yes what do you
mean it's a muscle bike what does that
even mean
[Music]
oh they're joking okay I thought so
I knew it oh what is that blue dot
I wanna hump you right now
hey hey you buddy can you do us a
massive favor you want me to take a
video
ah you drive us back to our Motel our
car's right there
give us a ride man uh okay I I'm gonna
censor mission
I'll take you like five minutes really
we're gonna look at it really I have to
have them you know Justice
they need to where's my frog where's my
frog
I I seem to have lost my frog but you
know what this works uh maybe not
you don't take up it's fine actually
really okay I'll have it ready just in
case
two or a hot mess I love it but not yet
obviously
where's my mouse
say
what is a tag on the chicken Airship
stats do it
the man Mongoose is that his name
a little chicken
you're a legend bro
oh we'll get in the back out of your way
baby don't breathe whiskey I would
prefer you to separate it in the car
while I'm driving okay we staying at the
hotel Southwest from here thank you so
much I think you're so much is it the
yellow line Southwest
oh
yeah just wait till we get back to the
motel I'm gonna get me either what is
Trevor thinking while doing this I
wonder
I feel like he would
I don't know this doesn't seem so in
character
shift that sweet little ass over here
but the Wolves see the rabbit you sound
like cigarette and buffalo wings it's
making me so horny
buffalo wings I understand the
cigarettes not so much
oh oh God what
what what
yo where you couldn't even wait let's go
I can't see the road like this I can't I
can't I can't see the road
crazy kids doing back now Trevor is
enjoying it now open the front porch why
don't I work on her back Plumbing huh
what did you say how about I suck those
kidney stones right out of your balls
big guy get this party really started
what they're all about it oh wow okay
man it's cool it's cool stop okay no I
really thank God
chill these kids these days
have absolutely no patience
we need to teach them
a lesson
didn't I tell you this would be the best
birthday ever I'm too old for this [\h__\h]
sleepy yeah yeah
boy 40 bucks a night we're gonna get our
money's worth
would you have like a a home
okay go easy on the paint job I won't
question it on the pink jump
uh-huh well have fun guys
thank you you're like the best oh my God
have fun nice to attend to
don't ask me to drive me to the hospital
later when your pregnancy is ending all
right
the box that is so not worth it
I'll take your card in
see you later sucker
[Laughter]
bye-bye
[Music]
right
yes
I wish you all the best
yeah yeah yeah
kids these days right am I right
am I right or am I right guys
oh the door is open again
[Music]
grab on the paint job
40 bucks in the car I didn't really need
the car though
it's not like I needed it
is this not a muscle car I thought so
I knew that
oh what a dose
a dose
a lowrider
oh sick
pretty
oh they find aliens I knew it
I knew it that didn't look like a
typical satellite thingy no no no those
are devices to find aliens before they
find us
foreign
[Music]
you didn't hear that you didn't hear
that
you wouldn't hear that
I'm gonna say Senpai she's not my Senpai
why would I say Senpai if she's not my
senpai unrealistic no would never do
that
doesn't sound like me
[Music]
well I'll be [\h__\h] mm-hmm
oh shh hi
sorry that was awkwardly placed
what am I here for why am I here for
what am I here for
that oh nice bid
what lady doing
how's the lady
get this can you give me a ring that's
why you have your water in and Tracy
please son daddy's been a bad boy
[Music]
the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
oh wait it's actually gasoline now see
the way I see it this country was built
by and for gasoline so I'm just trying
to prove my patriotic Duty by you know
but it's good she's just living here now
wasn't there a song like that
Jesus Mikey you want a beer
oh [\h__\h] I'm sorry I don't have any low
carbs [\h__\h] you
right
where'd you two go when you went out
yeah
why do you care I don't care
trying to conversate well I was out
putting some people really old ah you
know there's more to this gig than just
going crazy all the time killing
everyone in sight just because I like
the life and you feel guilty about it
you know what deep down
I don't know if I can isn't that like
not English and your street philosopher
[\h__\h] that's got you real sounds
difficult you've achieved Perfect
Balance balance all things are balanced
and 10 years in the sun your brain is
melted you say words that have no
meaning what is balance huh huh did I
[\h__\h] kill only on the weekends so
Monday Wednesdays and Fridays I'm doing
yoga and meditation Tuesdays and
Thursdays hookers and sticking up joints
huh you call me mad compared to you I'm
the same as [\h__\h] right now
I am so [\h__\h] saying that I should
open a [\h__\h] mental health clinic okay
yeah [\h__\h] now you're gonna stop being I
heard alive Trevor but I'll try
how like your honest how is that
possible
I need to question Michael senpai
I spoke to Franklin we need to talk I'm
like you he hears that his home is
having trouble right and he has no
problem coming to help so you're
ensuring that we like when flares him
for dinner
something must be wrong with the
Japanese translation then
they probably made it like more harmless
now so typical
about the trouble
so he seems like less of an [\h__\h] in
Japanese Maybe
you're right
I did do that I I don't think they would
like translate all of this so accurately
that it really comes across the way it
does in English
I think it's even difficult even if you
wanted to you might die
probably because it's happy I'm happy
hey I'm coming with you no yes I am no
nothing else to get out of this [\h__\h]
[Music]
she's like totally integrated into the
household now
okay
back to the music do it for you anyway
he's tailing some guys Mikey tailing
oh okay okay
we're speaking of Franklin so we moved
to Franklin
damn these Reds
okay
chase him is it bad if we get noticed
that we're chasing them
we can't deal with them yet whoa that
was close the [\h__\h]
it's called Trevor
hey man me oh they already know wh
north of chuma
oh sorry did I did I hang up on him I
was gonna try to like aim and shoot
was right click hanging up
oh
[Music]
am I supposed to shoot them
oh
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
it's fine if I die but don't not with
choppy
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay it's okay we just started we just
started maybe we can now listen to the
message again
one more time please
get your sex Sebastian
[Music]
that's right chop we gonna [\h__\h] them up
as soon as Trevor get here
okay I just follow them okay okay whoop
whoa
that was fun
all right all right the O'Neill brothers
are coming to us I think they was about
to send one of them anti-tank rockers
into your best booty condo when one of
your roommates told them that you was
gone okay so if you're on the wh that
means you'll be coming through Raton
Canyon right [\h__\h] I guess good me and Mt
are gonna take the company Chopper and
meet you there company Chopper yes
Michael it's a tax write-off Frank you
still there yeah I'm just about holding
on to the road we're taking the chopper
and we'll head you off deal with these
business stealing Pricks on the road hey
dog can you like get on it cause these
dudes is rolling home we're five minutes
out from the chopper all right
what
okay okay [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I think I have to do it again
I can't
sorry sorry it's rad I tried never drove
by a mountain well I never drove
anything in my life before
that's what you're asking
use his power oh
okay
no Chuck we can't deal with them yet
there's too many of them
I know that it didn't ask me to show
them but I kind of want to show them hey
man me and Chop on these funks we coming
up to wh north of two miles all right
all right the O'Neill brothers are
coming to us I think they was about to
send one of them anti-tank rockers into
your best poochie condo with one of your
roomies showed them that you was gone
okay so if you're on the wh that means
you'll be coming through right
oh [\h__\h] sorry I did it again but we
already had heard him before
oh now they shoot me too oh
never mind I stopped oh oh oh
[Applause]
it's very slippery
[\h__\h]
what is this Banker music I wish I could
listen to it
I wish I could I'm sorry guys for taking
that enjoyment away from you
sorry
hey man me and Chop on these funks we
coming up to wh north of chumas all
right all right the O'Neill brothers are
coming to us I think there was a button
okay shush I've heard that a million
times
enough now
no more no more
this time I will not fail
I'll show you guys my driving skills I
know you're going that way what if I
just cut him up and I go first can I
oh God okay but no okay if I had skills
it would maybe be possible
see I'm very careful now
oh very good very good oh
no gas gas this is break break
hope you like it
there we go beautiful
[Music]
thank God it wasn't Franklin yeah we
even
I was gonna warn you I was gonna
you know what elk is on my team
good elk
I got your back homie find her good job
can I shoot them now permission to shoot
granted
Trevor
Trevor man [\h__\h] you there there was a
deer in the road man these [\h__\h]
crashed out
no they gone they ran into the [\h__\h]
woods man I need air support like white
[\h__\h] name
easy to say of course
we have immediate access to air supports
no problem
no problem for us look
we're on our way
incoming man you're all business yeah
well this is kind of important these men
don't like me and they know we're back
in the Sandy Shore so ah here she is the
biz alley remember she ain't mine she's
the companies well nice graffiti on it
it actually looks cool
normally I don't really like graffiti
but
um in this case it looks nice
okay
helicopter time
should I use my control
why do these guys how does this work
with the controller
anyway
[Music]
very small
why I like it
but I set your heart ain't in it yeah
I'm lucky my heart ain't in a pie on
your kitchen table always with the quips
you're such a depressing Senate
triangles means shut up Champion I know
I still know
my short-term memory today is
I loved her memory I remember everything
I've learned
so if your panties aren't all in a Twist
over stolen office supplies can you
please
scan the foreign
okay okay
is that dog moving or is just is it just
me
oh I I see what's going on it's in the
air I thought it was like on the
mountain
[Music]
in the woods
uh-huh
Heat
I don't see [\h__\h] ah sorry I'm still on
the controller
to the river
Shenandoah River
[Music]
I press F I thought it was already on oh
wait ah
yeah but thank God nothing happened
wait
ah wait what button is it on the
keyboard though
because it says he impressed oh whatever
I'm just gonna press it on the
controller ah okay okay
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] huh
wait
no how do I
I turn it on again
I'm gonna do both at once wait huh
that's Franklin oh
okay
now I see a lot of animals
that looks like someone's trying to swim
oh
um
[Applause]
how many was it three people right
oh
look at that
[\h__\h] is that oh it's an elk too
looked like some kind of monster ah is
this Trevor at Franklin
it's Franklin too right
oh only animals
oh oh Missy animals
what the [\h__\h]
no wait that's him
with the dog so this is one of them
never mind never mind
he's behind the rock I can't get a shot
holy [\h__\h] it's on you homie you know
what Hicks
what are we doing
where should I go pull chat okay
[Music]
he knows what's best
Frank we're about to get shot out of the
sky here
we gonna handle this
leave it to me
I am too [\h__\h] swim this water is cold
um we're next
job we're supposed to follow you you're
just hanging out there
uh you were just marking your territory
all right all right I get you and Doc's
gotta do what the dog's Gotta Do
I'm so slow oh
dinner time boy come on
assault rifle
I can't see can't see can't sit
[Music]
[Applause]
right now
that is you that was all you choppy boy
oh yeah I'm so proud of you
oh that blood
pick up Franklin and shot from raging
Canyon Canyon all right goodbye
let me reconsider
ation
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] am I supposed to land
uh
slowly descending into madness here
I see it I see it don't worry we don't
see the map I'm sure
ah [\h__\h] hell
why do we have to be so exact as if they
couldn't walk over here as if
what a [\h__\h] luxury to have a
a helicopter right at your [\h__\h]
doorstep okay okay okay I did it I did
it
don't don't chop the chop up into chop
sushi
no no no no
decent Landing
[Music]
have I regained your respect guys oh
yeah you can afford a Runway but you
can't afford to move out of that
corrugated metal death shot well
yes cool home and
for you chop I never lost it
that's the right answer wow I didn't
even know the answer was an option
[Music]
can't we gain what you never lost oh
killed a lot of them
killed Justin I killed Ernie Earl Dale
Doyle Daryl oh my God and a few other
guys when I blew up the farm in
alphabetical order
[Music]
all right we're Landing again
oh
how the [\h__\h] am I supposed to do that
where where ah here are all the h
ush
please tell me it's okay here
oh man
[Music]
so excited about it
take that [\h__\h] stick out of your ass
please uh Rockstar Games
eh wait it's not it's not the age
but that's [\h__\h] [\h__\h] that is just
[\h__\h]
stuff
oh yeah I am gonna spread a strongly
avoided complete leather
Trail man we're gonna bar this and head
back to town sure come on Michael man
I'll drop your ass I thought the thought
was on the edge
Phillips Mike yeah we're so close it
would have made more sense indeed thank
you
no I'm looking at the map but this
distance it was so close and I couldn't
see the dot on the on the real world so
I was like okay I guess it's on the H
probably
anyway
Columbine is delivering a military
command
um to HS okay am I supposed to pick that
up
um I'll go there okay
do I have to do it with him
foreign
[Music]
I was just answering
not senpai
um that s
it wasn't for Senpai it was for koyoni
shots because
that didn't sound like coyote that
wasn't her
yeah but I was answering her and anyway
[Laughter]
[Music]
Superstar
there's so many ways to describe coyote
I was about to say it again
so many words all the words in the
dictionary all the positive ones belong
to her
oh yeah oh yeah why is there a blue dot
here what
can I get a ride bro
um
what what dude
no okay okay okay okay now now you must
be [\h__\h] kids
oh
thank you
little [\h__\h] you hell [\h__\h] yo little [\h__\h]
I'm gonna lose money now aren't I
don't tell me it's 5000 again
wow
wow uh where's my car
boom without my car
now I was giving him the benefit of the
doubt and giving him a chance I was
gonna help him
makes me distrust the world
look at this piece of [\h__\h] car
action's beautiful just need to use a
coat of paint
nice shirt
okay oh we still have to oh
why why do I have a marked error
that's why we don't pick up hitchhikers
ah yeah
I think in Austria
you can pretty much safely pick up
hitchhikers but I've also never never
seen a hitchhiker before
here
well I think it would be good here
Austria is pretty safe and like you know
we don't we don't do guns here
normally so I don't think this would
happen here in Austria I believe
there's a bit of car on your wrist
you're saying my car is Rusty
he even makes Rusty sounds huh
can still get knifed I don't think they
would do this yet like I've I've never
heard of something like that happening
ever
nope
maybe maybe it happens once in 10 years
but
yeah
whoa monster truck was that a monster
truck
say yes wait are the highs moving again
okay ah
okay okay I see what's up I see I see I
see what's up
wait are you guys saying yes for
yes four and you know it was a little
thing what I said monster enough just a
huge pickup
[Music]
am I still on track yeah
let's hope it doesn't go this way next
what's the best way to capture these
thingies
I'm just first have to
get some distance
some get rid of some distance
okay it's still going straight
oh
ow I feel like I'm slow right now
no never mind I'm so fine
on the road okay okay okay you guys
still though I know you're looking at me
all the time cause you love me
where the [\h__\h] is this thing going
can I not like Mark the moving thing so
that it will continue to go after the
moving thing
I mean what I mean I missed it
it's going uh
it's at the end
what am I supposed to do
at the end of the road
intercept intercept I mean intercept
it's like what's gonna what's gonna
happen how how would I intercept this
we're right at like a military base I
feel like
this can only go wrong
out now this is foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
mom
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
um that's not good that's that's
not good that's not good at all that's
not good that's not good
Country
Roads take me home
to the place
for I belong
s
take me home yeah I got one of them
Country Road
oh yeah oh yeah
Mountain Mama
West Virginia
helicopters on my [\h__\h] ass yeah
can you move please I need to get home
oh no I [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] yeah
let's try once again
I never try I feel like I only had four
stars because
um
I killed so many military people made it
very
very blatant
look
I think if I intercepted in the middle
of the road it shouldn't be
such a problem right
what
um
yeah it's because I was at the base I
think so too
okay okay so this is coming towards me
on that road anyway that's beautiful
that's nice
I think it's coming towards me
ah look at that you gotta love Rural
America oh oh
well they're all busy there that's good
for us
I'm not gonna bother with that though
that's not not my problem
sounds like a you problem police
are they coming towards me yes okay okay
okay okay okay
and then I park my car in front of them
right
there it is there it is
oh there's oh they have a bunch of like
protection
Cars Sorry I'm I'm just here to um ask
for a signature I'm a big fan
I am a big fan oh so how many stars do I
get for that
no sign so far
[Music]
see I will not even try to kill you
because I am so nice
I am such an angel
where are my stars I did my homework
teacher
foreign
how come
how come wait I I hear shots I think
are they trying to shoot me
I feel absolutely no no danger I
couldn't be more relaxed than this
except for tomorrow because tomorrow I'm
finally like getting a massage in the
first first time in a long time I'm I've
been like in so much pain I just swear
to God I know I said the last stream but
it's just been getting worse and worse
um
I'm getting a massage tomorrow I'm so
excited I really needed it
it was long overdue
oh they're really up my ass but
the goal what happens if I'm at the goal
but still being followed
uh oh [\h__\h] wrong place
don't ruin it now
ah this is bad
God I regret it okay okay grab
everything
okay okay now I'm here now I'm here now
I'm here now I'm here just Rockstar
Games I swear to God I swear to God you
and your stupid yellow dog
and funny you're funny you're funny
you're so funny
whoa
okay okay okay okay
we're still alive
who's alive
I need to heal
oh
wait I can't I can't I can't I can't I
can't no no please don't kill me
foreign
first try first try guys
so proud I didn't expect that they would
force me to take out the rest as well
[Music]
magically disappear sadly I wished I
would
I'm just really hopeful you know
me too meant you wear the lab where is
the lab
there's an H here
wait are we meeting in here
I am here
oh wow
didn't have to go anywhere
because it's not inappropriate oh Trevor
in a low-key suit another one of your
[\h__\h] disasters that's what it is
first take a hostage against my advice
would you start some kind of crazy high
school romance yeah it's a romance on
the hostage she's a 60 year old
housewife she's 57.
she thinks very important to be exact at
that stage 30 years of marriage to the
world's angriest mob boss would make
anyone insane you're not making myself
switching the rooms that's a surprise I
knew it would become about you I miss my
family oh you're full of [\h__\h] all you
ever do Deanda is just like
ignoring them because they're so used to
this I'll tell you what's incredible
hey why not you got me out here Franklin
good boy
[\h__\h] if it was lies new ain't [\h__\h]
and arguments about how good life used
to be I could have stayed my ass in Los
Angeles hello Franklin what's up all
right
here's the shot yeah you're here too
we're going to paleto Bay we're gonna do
this thing any questions comments
yeah I miss Brad that crazy [\h__\h]
was with us now he would have loved this
I don't remember who Brad is or enjoy
himself molesting white-collar criminals
in a federal penitentiary thanks for
sharing
anybody else
what about me you'll be waiting for them
by the river handling the getaway all
right
these three go in and grab the tape hey
rendezvous with you you get out of there
is that a work for everyone
um okay I thought so
partnering Ninja
we don't need him
we're the perfect team you're gonna make
Franklin feel bad come on we got a score
to take
look for real read the [\h__\h] air the
room whatever anything read anything at
all and you'll know it was kind of rude
I was kind of rude towards Franklin
makes him feel like he's not wanted here
and he can never be good enough drive on
the job my boy Lamar Pool guess it's the
same kind of [\h__\h] we doing now right
nice bro what was the take [\h__\h] I don't
know man I can't remember come on
everyone remembers
not me huh Mikey bro what was your first
bank score 88 outskirts of Carson what's
up franchise for 10g yeah things were
easier a bank that you scored by him
breaking years ago Jesus and they're
asking for the numbers as in how much
money you got from it about your first
job see man you could just as easily you
tell them I understand Insanity check
Trevor the ultimate judgment I get you
well it was uh part of the interview
process I guess is how you call it
Trevor knew I could cook wanted to see
if I could handle myself this cash for
gold guy comes through town it's the
reason he had funds next thing we're
burying him and his bodyguard in the
junkyard well most of them anyhow 50k he
did fine he's better at all aspects of
the job
what Minecraft bird
so that M pretends can pretend he's dead
is that a spoiler
now from killing to dismemberment or is
that something I should know
I don't remember the details man leave
him alone no I mean like chocolate
cookies is an important moment Michael
Austrian ones on our way to almost
certain death bonding pouring our hearts
out and this guy is sitting here soaking
it up and giving nothing in return hey
if you don't remember if he don't
remember I'm supposed to trust this man
with my life and he don't trust me with
the details of it now well how about you
yes can you share with the group I'm
here I'll back the facts that checks
cash place
I went in took him for eight grand
walked out yeah it was a bit more
complicated than that though it wasn't a
t maybe I knew the guy maybe he id'd Me
Maybe you did six months maybe I was out
in four and that children is why we
don't leave witnesses that children is
why you don't Rob people that you know
[Laughter]
Franklin share yeah oh we're doing like
a story time here I'm so sweet
okay the score was like two stacks man
2G take home on your first gig
that ain't bad man man the whole score
was too stacked only I didn't see none
of that [\h__\h] oh God pack went off
you amateur
this is like them telling each others
about their first time and now Fellaini
Franklin we all gotta start somewhere
last time I tell your ass something
come on sweet bonding time
but they bond about different things
this is GTA me yeah
that might work that's a sports car
right not a muscle car
in our asses we
sense of humor hey let's just do this
thing all right
let's do this
is it a muscle car is that a muscle car
is it a muscle car
have you guys noticed I'm at this point
just doing it to you know tease you guys
and internet we have something like you
know going on you and me chat
um all right Frank have you realized a
discipline
get ready although I really still don't
know what a muscle car is I'm only
asking so that you guys feel included
[Laughter]
I care about you guys
I want you guys to feel needed and
valued and appreciated and smart
I'm here all right you know where you
gotta be I got it damn I'll bring a die
back just for you
Mark the van near the bank okay
[Music]
I'm already valid and appreciated don't
need the help
ah come on you enjoying it we ready
don't be like that I could use a
restroom break and risk getting ID I
don't know muscle cars myself yeah high
five number two yeah we'll pinch it off
I'll go in the bank
I got a baggie I'm Becky he's caught him
turkey he doesn't have a bag
oh what we already look like
really
um suspicious people
doing this window on this yeah
why are we not running
[Music]
a minute can we shoot that no are we
trying to avoid shooting now
what am I supposed to do why am I so
useless
employee okay you got the crowd what cop
should be here soon so keep an eye out
power is ready get over here hi
I'm kicking it thanks finally my time
has come
foreign
there's other ways of beating it I'm
here
[Music]
[Applause]
mm-hmm
I don't care if they surrender I'm
killing me some bad guys
oh you're happy for some action huh
look at action time
they don't get much action out here what
the [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
keeps on Rising
humorless anyone else
[Music]
that's
that's fun where are we going
move to where
in here okay
you hear that guys [\h__\h] we are getting
out on the water oh hello we're not
going through this now with 50 pounds of
gear blast it
the way you have to wait
baby just don't shoot me I don't want to
be your collateral damage
let's go take down the fence bro fence
what fence defense
[Music]
we're not letting you get out of here so
friendly
they still have manners isn't that nice
oh oh they're bringing out the big guns
but we have the bigger guns you want to
compare guns
I feel like I might run out of ammo at
some point but I hope not
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
do all the work we're taking this score
to buy one of them unwieldy
[\h__\h]
wow amazing or if I got hit I lose money
ah okay okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
am I supposed to take cover
how the [\h__\h] is Uncle Sam
I
have a compliment
what did I do what did I do is it what
shooting that thing
that don't sound complicated at all
the longer ref takes to get here the
fewer notes will have
did I was I killed where when you where
were you when you always killed oh oh
okay
I will not kill you but I'm under 8
million that's very sad stop losing
money guys
yeah Pre-K ammo
wait why am I so [\h__\h] slow why are
they shooting me
that's why I guess we shooting our way
out of here
for real bro
I literally didn't do it
it's a construction worker
all right all right all right all right
at least the good thing is since I'm
going so slow
since I'm going so slow I I can aim
pretty well
please don't shoot me
what am I supposed to Rabbit oh you made
a restricted area nothing's restricted
for me
I'm just gonna ignore your existence
wait I have to go the other way
when is it gonna shoot me is it gonna
shoot me please don't shoot me please
don't shoot me that's that's not that's
not fair like look at me
laughs
he's
[Applause]
good
all right this is it man all right L and
ckrl
oh
well okay uh oh was I supposed to like
lift it up
hey man these guys
I'm supposed to Ram everything but the
tank but I don't need to turn around
pretty well
I can't lift it up okay okay
hey [\h__\h]
I mean
on this area wasting my time to try to
lift them up I don't need to build that
if you ask me
so I guess we shooting our way out of
here
anyway
[Music]
fit in there
diet was perfect
[Music]
yeah I'm all right it's really cool if
we find something couldn't we have
stolen attack
I see I've seen I lifted up and um you
know oh I can't lift it anymore
okay okay go to the factory all right
all right oh God
please do not shoot
they could shoot me anytime
actually they're really nice for not
shooting
why are they not shut Ting me actually
y'all look hot in the [\h__\h]
oh hello
should I shoot you they want to be shot
what go to the railway platform they're
all over us
oh hello
what why are they already in here this
is the way out chicken
I can't look at this
don't look campy don't look don't look
close your eyes
close your eyes close your eyes use me
as cover Frank you don't want to get out
front
don't look I'll take care of it
foreign
[Music]
just [\h__\h] off already hey Frank you good
that's not me
where the [\h__\h] do I have an alarm at
this time
come on come on
[Music]
we knocked into a chicken factory
give me
[Music]
give me they're making some nice crispy
chickens and yango Burgers I told you
Chef was good people Keith are running a
business is surrounding yourself with
talent I feel like the right manager
unlocked his potential
hello how you doing back there Frank
this is the reality guys
can we go
oh more army showing up well where
there's nothing there
let's go let's go
oh
if I'd known you'd be this annoying
[\h__\h] off already
that ain't even fair
super Focus mode kiwawa
in your butt
[Music]
I would say it's pretty good
for my first time
grenade
[Music]
make me loose nothing that much we get
clear not a big deal
[Music]
you might
be right you do what you can do Chef
this is really worth it
in here Chef's holding them up might
give us the window we need to jump a
train
paychecks no good one
and we got a train to catch
you're trying to control
okay hey slip out of town and call
Lester for instructions I got news
you're wasted at Trevor Phillip
who is you on my team oh yeah
what what else what else They're All
Dead
Fred Chef caught us a break people oh
hey
[Music]
boom Hedgehog
let's get our train
we're trying it's our only shot here we
go here we go go go go go go go go go
can't stop the choo choo train
[Music]
8 million let's go
I guess that's what oh friendly really
agent Sanchez have her very own
corruption you want a little a little
cut you gotta be careful buddy all right
because because we are looking around
these trains for illegals and if you're
mistaken shot at me does he know what's
up yeah if you expecting them two to
bring you up you're gonna be
disappointed he knows what's right back
at you got the money oh my God okay
here's your cut
considering present scrutiny on public
worker remuneration and that's a small
cut this is a big win that's a tiny Club
what the [\h__\h] that's a huge [\h__\h] win
well how much is that
5 000 bucks agent Haynes will get in
touch with you once operations save the
world I want a million at least what the
[\h__\h] together okay
how much is such a stack I don't even
all right oh no we should probably split
up they're gonna be looking for a three
10K that's four okay per person come on
Frank no way
what's the highest dollar bill 500
let's go serious
what's your highest dollar bill
how much are we getting
100 oh then that's not 400 000 or so
how much did we get
oh you guys knew that because you
already knew it
[Laughter]
do that because you already knew it
hey that was in like never that would no
that's not 400.
like a stack like that can't be foreign
okay right
right
hello sorry uh
the father was gonna pick up
automatically can I call you back
can you call me again
dude I'm sorry
Moshi moons
oh whatever
he's gonna call eventually
yeah
push down the freeway that's fine
it's fine if he has something important
to say he's gonna call me again
or or I can yeah check maybe the
voicemail if that's a thing
it's probably out somewhere nice high
still nice Heist very aggressive that's
he's not that bad really
okay he is pretty bad but he's got a
sensitive side very sensitive and he
gets his feelings hurt he's devastated
so what's your story
I ain't got a story I'm an independent
thinker as that has nothing to do out
here away from the man from what I can
tell you're like a high school athlete
living off old glories you used to be
able to manage heat and now you're
worried if your loafers are getting
scuffed
any more [\h__\h] comes out of your
mouth you're gonna learn all about my
past lawyers firsthand you understand oh
oh what does that mean I don't think so
that came out wrong all wrong
tell Trevor the monthly train is coming
through what monthly train the monthly
training where have you two been some
fresh air YouTube together
it was very nice this time of year
that's your mouth boy all right
in a dream of ours
I ship it I feel like she will be good
for Trevor I'm talking about gold and
she'll improve him running trailers and
you in therapy enough so that we can pay
off that Mexican and get you back in
town baby
yeah I just want my family back though
what the [\h__\h]
Jesus ah man we've talked about this
hygiene thing before bro I invite you
into my home this is how you repay me
that's you dude you're so stinky that
you're smelling yourself which is really
just too much cycle
oh it's cute where'd you get that from
huh
oh you can never oopsy wrong with the
wrong time why are we going Separate
Ways
that's the size of it make it a fast
boat
s
it's like sometimes this is a high value
Courier Service run by itself and
Merryweather
this ain't a weapons train it's good to
sure for air travel trail
[Music]
ERS just Antiquities sometimes enough
for you me Ron everyone you guys are
always like that like new Mission starts
and you were like ah this mission
time ah this Mission ah suspicion and
here she is a magical train
I like trains do you like trains JoJo
yeah choo choo [\h__\h] go
shopping list we'll need some bombs
Master remastered look at the trailer
where are you you have to jump onto the
train what do you mean oh
wow
not good not good
I kind of failed still get onto the
train further down the elephant yeah
um how do I wait
oh that one didn't go so well
but here good good rescue
[Music]
oh oh oh oh
okay
let me try to catch up first again
oh
can I just jump onto it from here I feel
like that's very realistic I like I'm so
close to it and it's so slow
[Music]
that's my chance not my chance but how
do I get off will he just automatically
do it
it was on top of the train
hey Wes I think we caught it on 4K
free games
Rockstar Games you and me I see
you want to be
my enemy
[Music]
we could have been friends
back in the trailer where are you we
wow what have you turned into I
think without me
get on the train RTA
[Laughter]
something
four seconds
[Music]
sorry I'll do it again
I was kind of on the train
uh is that the end yeah that's the end
okay okay
awesome go next
next oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
that is such a sweet checkpoint though
I fell off
so sad last time I fell off it didn't
make me fail the mission though
okay just just try to stay straight and
then it doesn't seem to oh oh
what was that mean l plus ratio what's
that even mean
what are you saying
oh
ah I've heard that before but I don't
really know what that means it's gonna
take a while
lose it oh God oh God okay okay focus
focus
[Music]
yeah Travis missions are generally
for me quite challenging
maybe this is better with the controller
maybe oh come on come on maybe I can do
a bit more you know accurate turns
more detailed you know because with the
wasd it's a bit a bit that's a bit rough
question I'm here
hello
I did it small
yeah high five kfp
hey
foreign
[Music]
[\h__\h] morning
okay
so this is how you conduct a train that
[\h__\h] bridge when we go past Polito
station
[Music]
do I slow down when there's curves
because I just slowed down I think I
don't know
wait I don't know what I'm doing to be
honest
I don't really know oh Emma ain't far
out you under the bridge
I guess that was fine
that looks like a nice boat
go to the Reno bridge and wingo
bones
[Music]
okay can we can we just chill why do we
have to boing boing so much I'm living
the life my friend there we go beautiful
oh
holy
[\h__\h]
oh what what
[Music]
got very Brown I could have landed on
him
what the [\h__\h]
what you sticky bombs to blow open okay
wait what how uh
now if I was a speed free cannibal
blow up a train I have grenades but I
want to stick it no what the [\h__\h]
uh
why is it switching the radio I'm
that one's cooler you need several ones
on this one
yeah yeah okay okay I'm gonna leave now
yeah it's about [\h__\h] time I'm sorry
why do I have a gun
oh funny funny where are they oh oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I'll have much more time
are they all dead are they dead yet oh
god oh oh oh oh oh
Mamma Mia oh that worked okay
here bro
hey
no that's too high level for me what the
[\h__\h] do you want my rifle which one
sniper rifles trouble sculpt a little
kid
it's this one though right oh it's a
different one no there's that one how
the [\h__\h] am I I don't know I don't use
that
you wanna die
damn are there more
there are more no more snipers so you
can come out
find something
went through the helicopter too
oh not really oh uh
I need like a grenade launcher
bro I'm gonna run out of here
[Music]
faster what the [\h__\h] is wrong with this
dude I'm gonna fire Michael
and only go with Franklin this doesn't
mean that I suddenly like
Trevor no no are you done hurry up man
easy
hello I'm like too fast it seems
wow
let's see Dad hang around here let's
move it move it
you don't have to look over your
shoulder I'm doing like everything
I think I was too too fast using uh too
fast for the game
there's one more
really
well they're doing a bad job then oh oh
they're doing a bad job speed you up man
that's shooting me I gave them so much
time
she's still alive
about [\h__\h] time okay hooray
can you pick me up
got in the dinghy
in the book come on get into the [\h__\h]
boat Trevor what the [\h__\h] Trevor
[Laughter]
oh nice River
[Music]
oh why are those people suddenly alive
oh this reminds me of them nature uh
that game I played with oh I'm shooting
nothing
the game I played with Cali
you know those Escape moments
good times good times [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
Women and Children First okay okay oh
wobbly
I forgot to say nice outfit and by nice
I think I stopped it okay
oh
oh that answers are just hikers Mountain
hikers don't want to hurt you
oh
wow wow
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] no I'm fine I'm good
I'm good I'm good yo
[Music]
um
land at the beach okay you mean a very
specific Beach don't you Rockstar Games
I know I know you think you make
Mercedes killing huh a couple nickels
times are tough have been since we put
you in the ground hey you had your
savings that I couldn't I wish Franklin
was there to see no there was nothing my
gaming skills there and organize some
transport for us
okay I'm here uh-huh I see that that's
really hard to see though
yellow on yellow
I could have missed that
but I've got Eagle Phoenix eyes
oh shh
hey one of the getaway vehicles is like
my favorite
my new favorite car oh his and hers huh
he's gonna be your independent Spirit
I'll take the small one
before you go show me the loot
oh what's that [\h__\h] is that
perfect for [\h__\h] what for squaring
things with that Mexican psycho is this
pure gold and your relationship with
that little lady looks like a baby a
golden baby I don't [\h__\h] see that
silicon City again it'll be too soon but
this is my job not your call to make
your job [\h__\h] things up with the
Mexicans oh
oh you give me that case I'll give you
something bigger oh
what
something
I'm sorry
they're they're like [\h__\h] off they're
like impossible
these dudes verging suicidal that a line
you're afraid they're bad influence for
me
come on t
you remember that it feels like
something they would say a couple of
kids pulling jobs the big one
I know it sounded crazy back then huh
but hey you and me together with Lester
and Franklin on board
we can do this thing t
this ain't no dream no more
no a dream don't let your dreams be
dreams
you keep the case oh it's working it's
working
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] and you can keep Patricia as well
all right because I respect that that's
her name ain't gonna hold her back
thank you just remember I'm going to be
keeping my eye on you every inch of the
way all right and if that faster don't
be so angry
I don't know what I'm gonna do yeah very
threatening
I don't know what I'm gonna do
great to be back
in business baby bring it on
there he goes Michael Michael look great
my cuddle grain
derailed funny
what the [\h__\h]
they fly so fast
Bird shooting
[Music]
hello townie's on the line too
all right I need your whole crew over at
Cape catfish we're moving on the
chemical weapons plant no no no no no I
just gave something to Lester I need to
deal with some stuff get back to Los
Santos just uh give me a week we got the
equipment with your Polito money the
gang bangers already on the way the
windows open my friend and you are
jumping out of it I'm hungry [\h__\h] Los
Santos ain't going anywhere bud
guys we played for five hours now when
koala are very hungry so Chihuahua
thinks now good time to stop because um
wait but that boat
wait before I stop
how do I turn on the furnace never mind
I don't need it
oh
I want the boat
you're giving me the boat yep thank you
should have a star
oh no no no no no I want the boat please
I just want
the book please
they can't find me in the water
if I dive
you see they're already losing it
I just want the bond
and I can't see me like with one star
they won't send out a helicopter so how
how are they gonna see me in the water
oh both cops oh oh [\h__\h] rather see him
oh oh who's gonna get there first
[Music]
how do I how do I move this thing
let's go
how much is a boat like this cause
oh yay
oh now I have three stars and some nice
riveting background music hello
[Music]
isn't this a nice way to end it today
well what is this gun I have oh [\h__\h] I
don't have time to change the gun
sniper Gundam was it a shotgun oh well
now we're getting
here
[\h__\h]
I [\h__\h] hell
we're playing
the tank oh my God there we go man down
man down
and you want the shot too I'll give it
to you cop s
[Music]
who will do it who will take you out
down no one good
how many shots my God
wait how do I get the hata I can't use
tab
uh what's it oh yeah
um
wow why a shotgun I need I need
what the [\h__\h] where are my guns where
are my guns
oh they switched seats
going pretty smooth
hard to aim I can't get any higher than
this can we get much higher
like literally I can't aim higher than
that oh there we go
ah
[\h__\h] I need to make use of the of the
waves
I I said [\h__\h] shotgun
useless
[Music]
the one piece is real yeah
oh there's another one here let's sing
that one down oh wait that doesn't have
a shooter
[\h__\h] I'm I'm bad
[Music]
oh we're on the big waves now oh can we
go much further it doesn't seem so I
think I have to turn somehow it feels
like the game made me in turn
it's like telling me the game ends here
wow
oh [\h__\h]
I am
I I can shoot from the but that's what
I'm doing that's what I'm doing what do
you mean
um
a bastard
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
times it's pretty smooth I should I
should I should shoot when it's like
Smooth
where am I where the [\h__\h] am I anyway
it's two days two yeah but the other one
is not shooting at me I think
use my sniper man it's not all right but
I guess we can't really sniper while
you're driving a boat
realistically
so you think man maybe a pistol is
better
he keeps on like resetting my aim
because of the Waves I think
easy way easier oh yeah oh yeah
yeah I got him
that one was fatal
pistol
oh at the end of the map again it seems
yo go move what the [\h__\h] move move what
what's happening is my boat broken
is my boat broken
yo
wait there's oh no I'm good we're good
we're good
okay we just have to take down
everything
how come I cannot take down this Chopper
it's just accompanying me I guess at
this point we're just having a good time
oh there's one on the other side
I think I see feet
the the
one who's riding the chopper
there we go
here we go
that's gonna be fun for the fishies to
explore now with this one I have a
problem oh oh there's new boat seats
okay
or is this still the same boat
did they send back up oh wow that is
backup
and I just finished what I
am
I wanna I wanna get on this other side
you know
[Music]
Bing where are you getting your recruits
what the [\h__\h] you got some revives a lot
[Applause]
at this point
this is like an endless Mission it's not
fair
it's not fair
[Music]
they're resurrecting each other
I'm using up all my ammo ones
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] hello
I'm sure I killed all of you by now what
the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] is up with that
police injured you guys Gravely
I guess I didn't get like the gray
screen the the monochrome
this is never ending I bought this would
make for a good ending
ah this one I can't really
yo Trevor you need to do your morning
stretches
you need to do your morning stretches
how am I supposed to reach him
okay okay okay got it got it got it got
it got it got it got it
I got several shots what the [\h__\h] why is
he not dead
oh hello
I'm I'm unbelievable you guys are
unbelievable oh there's an extra boat
coming
we're gonna send me one of those those
air tanks
he's having some fun you know Trevor
she's lonely too
he's just lonely
capture police boat
um
why I like this boat
this is the good boat oh what are they
doing they're sabotaging each other
military
yeah
exciting
look I'm like I don't even have any
cover like how come they have yet to
kill me I'm like all out there
there's nothing protecting me
it'll be difficult once it's completely
dark out here
maybe we should capture the submarine
that they're gonna attack us with
Walnut shot
foreign
[Music]
that's not a thing is that not a thing
oh how disappointing
okay this is literally never ending I'm
sad I don't want to die though that that
would seem like as if I lost
I don't want to keep up like that
how do we end this guys
I think at this point we can say I'm
stronger because I've survived this long
press f
m
I can't win this fight I can't lose but
I can't win
no
I will not oh hello other phone hey
mom what if I can I
can I
like
kind of like load game
you want to end this
oh
Still Still the police bone is that
gonna help me
you guys
bad idea
now we lost the [\h__\h] out of ammo and 5
000 bucks for what
you know what worth it worth it worth it
we got link
honestly
that was that was an experience on its
own a nice boat ride
I have seen zero fish and zero sharks
zero Dolphins zero everything but I
always wanted to do something like this
in GTA
um but maybe next time we can do it on
land and then actually somehow win the
fight
because I'm on the middle of the ocean
it doesn't seem very winnable hmm
[Music]
uh anyway guys guys doshio I only have
super chats from the members only stream
right I know there's a quite a lot
though
um but I kind of feel like reading those
in the members only Super Chat rating
because if it's only those I'm kind of
feel like doing them and the members
only but when would I be doing that
maybe on maybe on Sunday night I could
maybe find some time
um I'm really hungry now
oh
maybe if I have time I'll I'll do a
super chat reading for members because
all the all the super chats are from
members
from the members only
stream I think and there's 15 from the
last Super Chat reading oh okay I'll get
model do those really quick
[Music]
bye
I'm scrolling thank you guys so far for
watching today I hope you had fun
[Music]
that was fun for me we have once again
made a lot of progress how far am I in
the game I wonder
do you guys know
oh I found I found the spot Sky dances
Flora
thank you
oh wait my my marking thingy doesn't
work anymore the colors or is it just
no it doesn't work what the [\h__\h] it
doesn't work on here let me switch the
window then
to homolyzer it doesn't work here for
some reason halfway through
a third left
[Music]
66 50 out of 70. wow
oh there's 70 missions and I've 50 of
them
there's something you say about it do
your Koreans what what what
what what's up
what's up
uh Super Chat now
[Music]
depends on how many side quests well
generally I don't really do many huh
team up with the person who showed uh
the second lyrics Kayla has nothing to
worry about oh
you want to team up with them or you're
telling me to use Airlines this time
we've made a team so there are people
who can sing God samples and people oh
oh
you two the two lyric writer teams
teamed up and you guys gonna make me a a
guide video with someone singing it for
me oh that would be amazing that would
be so helpful
okay
oh it's a happy ending that's that's
great thumbs down
subscribe because then I don't have to
choose and I don't have to feel bad for
like choosing one of them
thank you also because I can't really
like judge uh which one is better
because I don't really speak Korean so
it's hard for me to tell which one is
better
[Music]
okay
now I read those 15 super jets
[Music]
from I'll just stay on the screen
because I'm lazy
for the pinky flora and an orange one
too congratulations on 290k reviews for
do you oh that's already very outdated
we're at like 750k or so
foreign
thank you yeah my tower still exists
it's like
um there's enough materials for it to be
uh existing for several seasons if it
wasn't gonna be
uh
like killed after a season
but I don't know when like what day
they're gonna do you know the ending
fight
so it's hard to plan for me right now
800k so let's go a million foreign
let's go
anyway
uh where was I uh I really liked it you
did it again and I passed the electrical
license it was the number one score yet
today and it's my birthday oh
thank you
[Music]
since December last year one thing I
wanted to achieve has been achieved I've
made mistakes recently and I'm
embarrassed or nervous so I can't talk
wow but it's all thanks to you no
problem I don't know what you're talking
about you're doing great
and I'm I'm happy for you
congratulations for the for the license
thank you thank you for supporting me
and saying hi on your birthday I hope
you had a lovely birthday
yeah thank you for the support and you
love I wish you all the best oh Ellie
Smith thanks for the pinky here's some
late money but I think to you might be
my favorite song of yours yet oh that's
great to hear but I did notice something
weird about the music video there were
two pianos but Kiana out there was
nowhere to be seen I hope she's doing
okay
there's many chihuahuas having them all
in one spot would just be too powerful
you know
did I miss the Box story yeah yeah you
did
you did in the end
um I'll show you the one thing the big
thing that was in the box was this huge
insanely big
beanbag thingy
um orange huge double Cedar beanbag that
I I had to think really hard about what
to do with it
it's now in my office serving as an
emergency seat uh in case I need to sit
down during a VR stream
[Laughter]
oh maybe there's someone inside yeah
maybe I should look
I think yeah it's the gift from pekora
Sanford probably don't know why she
fought I needed a bean bag and don't
know why she thought I needed such a big
bean bag
um but I'm gonna try to make some use of
it
maybe
[Laughter]
that would be nice but I don't hear
anything maybe maybe she's sleeping
inside
anyway thank you
Elizabeth
um there's she's she's somewhere she
just couldn't be there because otherwise
it's too much power in one spot
um
thank you for the pinky raising fund
money for the release of the first
full-length album of takanasi kiwawa at
least EP or single please thank you well
I'm I'm actually
um still thinking I'm not sure if it
will be an EP or an album I've been like
thinking of Concepts and choosing
producers and stuff
um
but
I might be more of an EP than an album
but you'll see I'm still figuring it out
yeah nap would be easier definitely and
still I think enough
enough for
helping me to create a concert well
we'll see I can't really say as I have
not decided yet and I also don't want to
spoil too much anyway
India Taylor thank you and also happy
belated birthday yay
again oh
you had to what you were making your
ex-girlfriend's Myspace page
uh I will not tell you about the next
songs genre I can't spoil it that's life
it's also because I'm not thinking about
about one next song I'm thinking about
several songs for an album and then you
know
I can't spoil that like like no no no no
I can't spoiler your dad
Mr Kyle Brown thank you for the pinky
thank you Kiana for making my days
better all the time it's been two years
and being here since the start it's been
a ride brought kotoli and Kiara plushies
and the omo cat t-shirt Chad can you
agree you are as real with us Chad can
agree you are as real with us as it gets
glad to be kfp I try
I try I want to
no when I Tab out um it pauses so I
don't think I can have it run on the
side
ah thank you so much Mr Cobra and also
thank you for getting the plushies and
oh my God t-shirt yeah maybe maybe
within this year there might be some
happy news regarding a long-awaited
restock
I can't
guarantee or say an exact date but I've
heard some good news
so look forward to it
yes finally
cast form five thank you for the red
super chat
while I'm not here too often and you
should prefer to lurk I recently got a
decent raise and a good job so I feel
like paying my dues for all the
entertainment since debut congrats came
out for two years and an absolute bang
over new song thank you
yeah
crazy ride not as crazy as the rides on
GTA
but it gets pretty close to it so thank
you for being part of that um
could you have permission for other GTA
games
um I honestly didn't see any other GTA
games on the permission list I only saw
GTA 5.
people I know keep on asking for GTA San
Andreas but I didn't see it on the list
um maybe no one asked for it yet but I
don't know I just chose it because it
was on there and seemed convenient
hmm
anyway
[Music]
I'm enjoying this one so and even if uh
San Andreas also was an option I
wouldn't play it immediately afterwards
so you know I like to take some breaks
and play different games in between
so that was it cast form five thank you
for the original chat
kiss for you and then I'm done with the
those Super Chat reading super chats and
uh the members only super chats I feel
like
I feel like I'm gonna read those during
a membership
um Super Chat reading stream either on
Sunday or Sunday next stream next week
I'm gonna try to accommodate maybe even
if I don't manage to do all of them I
always want to read as many as I can on
a member stream
yeah
because I feel like it just makes more
sense uh
yeah what's for dinner I'm not sure I
have free recipes
again from hellofresh
and I'll choose the one that looks the
easiest to me actually I think to this
time I got two repeaters in there
I didn't even choose anything but it was
automatically chosen because I missed
the
wait [\h__\h] I missed it again isn't it
first day
[\h__\h]
wait no I think it's before midnight
maybe is it before midnight okay I gotta
go and check so that I don't miss out
again because this week now they sent me
uh one of the recipes is something with
mushrooms
and I'm like what the [\h__\h] am I supposed
to do with this it's not even like
mushrooms that I could just leave out of
the recipe no it's like those
um like noodle thing is filled with
mushrooms and those are the like those
little thingies are literally in the
base the whole the most important thing
for the dish so
I can't
that sucks
so next week hopefully I get what I'm
asking for
um
anyway today was fun thank you very much
for watching and in German with selfie
doesn't love you guys see you tomorrow
we're trying a new game called carto
looks really really sweet really lovely
I saw it randomly on my steam like in
the advertisements or so I was like wow
that actually looks really cute
and sweet and
relaxing and healing and pretty
so we're gonna check it out
good night everybody have a nice day yes
[Music]
good night
okay oh yeah I'm getting my massage
tomorrow I'm so excited let's go bye
[Music]
foreign