foreign
[Music]
thank you
a little bit
[Music]
foreign
and frog
[Music]
s
[Applause]
[Music]
laughs
[Applause]
[Music]
how are you
it's time it's time it's time it's time
it's time it's time everybody hello I'm
Maury Calliope from Whole alive English
myth and welcome to the
underworld welcome welcome I have many
things to show you check it out check
out my stage
he goes oh check it out look at the
skulls with the wings in the background
and oh man this this is the best venue
in the Underworld you know it you know
that this is the place to be check it
out oh hey look at that look at all the
dead beats in the crowd swinging the
light stays
and it's on fire
so yeah nah
check out the big speakers too
yo that's actually dope thanks glad you
think so that's me correct that is you
and you and you and you and you and you
and you and you and you that's kind of
hot not gonna lie correct correct it's a
little hot in here but we're about to
make it hotter because guess what you
guys this this before your eyes is not
just a regular place to chill no no no
no no no
we have performances
performances action romance maybe not
romance but lots of lots of performances
so get ready and thank you for the many
congratulations you guys all right now
now for the first performance I want to
do I have something special to show you
check it out uh oh it's over here I
gotta go I gotta go grab it really quick
hold on I'm getting it it's now in my
hand okay just so you know it's it's in
my hands now stop a song stuff a song
it's here
the first song that we're singing today
is wanted
wasted
[Music]
yes
one man's trash is another man's purpose
day one flying high come tomorrow
[Music]
they want me
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
tonight tonight
[Music]
tonight
thank you thank you so much everyone
look at him go but it's not over yet
because now I've got another song to
sing
this one's called nezumi Skin
here we go
[Music]
all right all right hey
let's go come on everybody
[Music]
look boys and ladies what poison haters
what underrated girl born
[Music]
come here
again
[Music]
those opinions
no weight my biggest fans internet
business women drawing up plans why are
you trying to pin me for a pyramid
scheme I refuse to be a part of Any
derelite Dream slide over and hear the
screams and they say us face girl you
guys get to stay in those prayers
[Music]
can't you guys study yesterday
foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you very much everyone
thank you thank you thank you I think
about I take a bow thanks so much go
Kelly go thank you very much
Uncle Ray Uncle Ray Noah got it right
now I have something important to
introduce to you
my dead B backup dancers guy cuts John
hey hey guys
so cute hey hey let's go let's go
dancing
look at Mr and Mrs bones wow thank you
so much for coming see you later
bye bye
man I'm already worn out from that but
it was so cool to dance together with my
skeletons y'all look cute thank you very
much they did a great job I'm glad that
I'm glad that you agree
I'm glad that you're Reviving
no Mr Bones oh it's okay Mr and Mrs
bones they may come back I don't know
but for now I do know that I need to I
need to chill for a second you know
there's one thing that I always really
kind of wanted to do
and that was
drink a nice glass of wine during my 3D
I don't really drink wine very much
anymore but but but but but
I told myself that I would for this
special momentous occasion right so that
that's what I'm going to do and the team
here at the great jigok theater
decided to set up something special for
me my own little wine tasting corner
rise
very nice
there it is ladies and gentlemen check
it out my own little special corner for
the tasting of the line it's got a bunch
of different types of wine but I chose
the most I found the cheapest one at the
convenience store to try for today so
this is where we're going to be enjoying
some time together
are you guys really Swank very fancy
thank you thank you thank you well I
guess it's time oh stuff some poured
some water I mean got the wine bottle
ready for me all right well let me go
ahead and
grab this sand okay
well everybody
should we have a cheers box wine no no
not box wine not quite
um it's uh it's convenience store one I
asked Stefan to get me the cheapest one
um hydrate up thanks for watching this
will definitely keep me hydrated
um not like I just had a ton of coffee
before this or anything but here we go
Kanpai shimasho are you guys ready you
ready for cheers everyone everyone at
home Calliope Fancy Pants Mori what can
I say oh
all right well let's cheers come by to
3D for myth here we go
oh Ma'am that does taste like
convenience store wine
um
sometimes you just gotta loosen up
Deadbeats sometimes you just gotta
loosen up you know here I wonder while
I'm here drinking this wine maybe you
can
take a couple screenshots of my face
screenshot the [\h__\h] and use the hashtag
check out my face oh
[Music]
check it out
my expression
hello yo yo yo cute cute
[Music]
I would like to try drinking an even
cheaper wine but oh well this is all we
have
foreign
[Music]
give me a break
um
but I have to finish this glass I have
to I promised myself that I would I was
inspired by by Lamy Senpai Lami Senpai
got to drink Sake
I think it was on stream for her 3D
debut so I figured I'm going to do the
same as one of the only alcohol okay
members of Ian
[Music]
ah let's see what chat has to say Kawaii
oh where me whammy whammy
based land is great
yeah where's the god
chat you're right hold on hold on I got
you I got you all right listen listen
Yoko kite
[Music]
if you missed it I'll do it one more
time hold on we're almost done
[Music]
that one had a bit of a different tone
to it all right done with the wine
wine on this
I can't I can't do too much because you
know we have stuff to do oh
what's going on here little skirlingtons
hey Buddies thank you for all the super
chats everyone these are this is my
garden of super chats all my deadbeat
sending supas they're coming in with
roses coming in hot look at them gather
oh hey Buddies
my sopas
oh so cute
oh there's a good Debbie you're a good
Debbie you're a good Debbie who's been a
good hey it's me it's you
what what's that what's that Debbie you
want me to step on you
oh gosh okay hold on hold on
deadbeat you've been bad
what do you call
what do we call
bad deadbeat bad
you've been bad
yes
oh you know what
you know what I also have
um
I have my Scythe my side
my what is it well I have I have my big
my big Scythe you know Ricky Right but I
have something else I want to show you
yeah
an instrument you saw it before hold on
I'm gonna go grab it again okay just
stay right there stay right there I'm
going to get this side
[Music]
I got it I got it I got it everyone look
it's the rocky base pretty cool right
you can play it of course
I'm I'm messing around but but you only
you don't only have to play it no no no
you can use it as a weapon if you want
I'll show you I'll show you okay I've
been training a lot so okay get the
stance perfect and then
huh what huh
that's struck uppercut and
back around
Isn't that cool look at it it has
multiple purposes but but did you know
back in the day Farmers used to use the
site to to harvest the crops and the
grass cut the grass like this yeah that
was the original use of the scythe and
then us Reapers decided that it was such
a waste of a great Tool uh to not use
them to take people's lives as you know
word a murder weapon yeah
oh look at the little deadly playing
he's having so much fun oh look at how
cute all right so as I was saying this
is usually how you know we reap the
super chats and the souls and stuff like
that down in the fields uh we kind of do
a similar thing to what the farmers used
to do back in the day
Debbie what are you doing
IRC what's this are you stealing the
super chats hey
deadbeat stop soup
hey wait no no not that wait that's my
side
wait a minute
I can fight back you want to fight me
Debbie all right that's fine you do know
who you're dealing with right though
I am the Grim Reaper's first Apprentice
if it's a fight you want it's a final
jet
come on
he's still alive oh yeah that's not
funny deadbeat uh stop laughing at me
ah we're gonna have to use more than
just Weaponry to get back at this
deadbeat okay fine fine we'll figure
something else out until then
come at me
what uppercut uppercut come on now
wait ah he really knows how to use this
knife oh gosh
come on now
let's finish this
huh
yeah
[Applause]
that's what I'm talking about
[Music]
whoa yeah baby burn baby burn
I burned so many evil skeletons but
who's gonna help me enjoy my 3D now
those guys were my backup dancers camera
crew
I didn't think they'd get so money
hungry and rowdy
oh will you guys hang out with me
my friends are here my friends came to
party everyone as you expected I've got
my bodies here my myth friends they came
to hang out with me so I guess
it's time to to do myth related things
come on come on
come on out come on out friends
but here's the catch you can't see them
they're invisible
they're invisible I think
where's the where's the camera they're
going to be my camera people well I have
I have two camera guests today come on
over we've got
is here I can't believe I died
their mysterious uh Spirits drifting in
in the wilderness of the underworld hi
and you've got the camera now you've got
all the power all the power so they're
gonna help me get the best angles and
then I think we have kiwawa and Gua in
here yeah
how's this there
well we'll talk about that a little bit
yeah so
so I got it I gotta say
um I'm worried about kiwawa your voice
sounds like it's dying yeah because of
your sick ass performance
oh yeah
you reap my voice can you stop raping my
boys please no no
what do you guys think of this this
crazy stage
bring down the house
yeah Ian is on the camera now I'm in
control he knows in control all right
well we're gonna hold that thought in
Ahmed what do you want me to do I need
something to do
you first you know what I'm gonna ask I
do are you gonna ask me to do the worm
you know what all right here's the thing
okay I'm gonna do it to prove it can be
done okay
I have one advice Callie you know if
it's difficult for you you know the worm
how you normally push yourself up with
the arms you can you can bounce yourself
off of your boobies
what the [\h__\h] that is really you want to
not have
you wanna you wanna [\h__\h]
um
okay all right all right oh there she
goes all right I can do this hold on
yeah
all right hold on
dude
[Music]
our payback wait it's fun okay this is
only the beginning here you see okay
excuse me no no not not you you're the
camera person okay okay
is in control what is your request
kiwawa
so I want something cute and that will
be without music but can you please do
the caramel dancing dance with your
hands on your on your do you know it I
do you're taking me way back
here we go
and then full body and also close-up
Place camera both girls yeah
tall order I guess a zoom in okay yeah
however you see fit to do it Watson all
right okay
yeah yeah
[Applause]
it's the caramel dancing okay we'll just
we'll fix it let me do more tests it's
like this
okay okay okay
you guys are gonna Tire me out before
the end
is it my turn okay girl what's your
request
what was that cartwheel
are you are you kidding me
[Music]
soon
all right here we go
you're so difficult
[Music]
come on man okay
action roll yeah oh okay all right I
don't know that was the action
I thought you wanted another one
all right all right well I guess that's
it
[Music]
it's my turn on the camera
[Laughter]
all right Callie what
I want you to give us wait what are you
doing here
no why are you turning around leave me
alone
why are you running leave me be why are
you ready no no no no yeah okay okay
okay I want you to give us
the most
cutest
thank you for coming to collide before
it's 3D
right away you can't run away
my [\h__\h] yeah oh boy put your heart into
it
mom come on you can do it I've been
working for years do you want to cause
the entirety of these skeletons to
cringe so hard they die a second time
it's on fire might as well put out the
fire with some you know embarrassment
second hand embarrassment with tears of
joy from Deadpool
is this really what you want deadbeats
but let's look at Chad Chad is this
really cool
[Music]
all right let me think about the
choreographer okay she's thinking she's
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
all right here I go here we go let's go
let's go
it's all your fault right this isn't
your fault this is
[Music]
a problem
pretty nice right you want to give
everybody a full body look yes I
did not yeah you did I did not okay
we're exposing you now okay
you know what you're doing oh I did not
you have any up close things you guys
want to see your eyeballs
oh
God
I think we saw your brain oh really it
wasn't very big was it I don't know what
could have happened
why are you doing that with the camera
oh yeah you know why are you getting so
weird with the camera right now
love me
oh you know what this is
let me kind of pretend to be walking all
right welcome to my Senpai watch and
fight impression
wacky what
you what
you know
you could bro here's the other one but
we're washing my Senpai to compare this
is what is Empire's property left side
right side
I wonder hold on I'm sorry
I'm sorry
here we go oh my God I've seen this
before
[Music]
look at me I have um
[Laughter]
see now I'm having fun now that now that
you guys aren't puppeteering me like
evil faces
laughs I just realized I have I have
some power here power of the ancient
ones what does that mean I'll tell you
to freeze
now oh now I can
um
what are you doing here
why can't I move
no what are you doing what is she doing
today
no no no no this is evil
oh my God I don't know if you guys could
see that but there were forces moving me
I think it was easy I think I don't even
know that here you know but I still have
my power we're ghosts so yeah we can
move stuff I guess so oh I mean I can I
can move objects you can you can you
wanna go ahead do you have power to move
stuff too you wanna try it you try first
it's your idea okay okay all right well
let me get the size a comma uh I'm gonna
get the regular size
here it is what do you think
it's Ricky
uh no kicks Ricky Ricky Kiki is the base
here would you like to hold it yeah you
know of the Void
what would you say would you like to
hold it then we know she's just holding
it holding it my Powers Yeah with her
powers behind ghost power that's right
this is my final power
wow
final attack
hey what are you doing what are you
doing
what are you doing don't worry about it
it's fine oh look at how well you can
really talk with that Scythe huh yeah
looking good please don't hurt me I'll
think about it oh God I guess wait hold
on
let's see how low I can go oh yeah
time lady
all right
fine okay
how low can you go how low
control
can you hold it properly
oh can you go
yeah all right all right all right we're
just dancing too much
all right you know back on the camera
oh God
okay
yeah you said I was I was losing too hot
it was pretty cool all right all right
all right hello here you go okay okay
okay
all right final level where are we gonna
make me go
how low can you go hello can you go
hello can you do it yourself
[Music]
[Applause]
everybody's more flexible look at that
look at that oh the wink you're pretty
flexible you had all those days yeah
like what no no no and you you did like
the
that bunch
I saw something there no you didn't okay
I did not do we have time for one more
request
can you give us like some sick chemicals
and then I want the camera to do like a
360 as if you're like a figurine oh
that's a good idea okay okay let's see
what is maybe with the Scythe oh
cool yeah okay okay
all right
and now 360 yeah slowly and smoothly oh
yeah
it's her figurine on sale right now
oh yeah that doesn't have the side no
it's like a yeah I can't do with a sized
version oh yeah that looks good with the
side too yeah
figures
I'm really good at standing still
check it out
nice
camera work I'm doing that yeah
yeah that's right almost feels are super
good with the camera
anyway this is a cool for shortened pose
this is the last thing yeah when you die
oh yeah
I want to see something else
[Laughter]
okay oh okay let's get there yeah I'm
stepping okay
[Applause]
oh no little deadbeat you've you've been
bad bad little deadbeat I gotta punish
you punishment
[Applause]
thank you
anyway uh anyway anyway anyway
thank you ladies for coming to party
with me for a little bit it was a lot of
fun I love
I love
very cute thank you very much
as well for joining in thank you so much
I wish I wish I could control the camera
yeah
we'll have more chances down the line
yeah definitely yeah thank you Ina thank
you
thank you guys are the best thank you
I'll see you guys later
[Music]
see you later friends there they go
there they go off into the distance
goodbye friends and now we are here with
only Mo we if you don't mind I'm gonna
get a little a little drinky where's my
drink hold on I have my my water me a
zoo I'll drink
Kiara's water bottle because she's not
she's not here that's okay she's resting
anyway
uh so I would say I'm all alone now
sadness but I'm not alone because I have
some friends here with me now uh you
guys have seen me do some 3D stuff in
the past right no oh but like concert
and stuff and at those times I always
ask like my Holo Holo Senpai to come
hang out with me but this time this time
uh I wanted to do something special
so
um yo question mark question mark friend
time more guests indeed more guests are
here
um so let's see I see a lot of guests
guesses Ayo Adams there's no Adam
there's no Adam and y'all hey yo
um a lot of people are saying kohai not
kohai in fact die die die die die senpai
so
without further Ado ladies and gentlemen
let's do a song
here we go
[Music]
yes
let's go
[Music]
everybody
all right guys grab your shift let's go
let's go it's always been my first week
since we are so sick Cry of Mercy Mercy
as they run for the hills got you in my
sight and solve that it takes watch Bend
to the side but call it Nature's mistake
yeah made a friend for today but like
you don't spend the night play pretend
that you escape
[Music]
don't you definitely time to me up whoa
table the name of the meme
[Music]
taking the Eagles
all right let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
did you know steps
you told me earlier to tell you what we
should do death is all near the health
might as well be a crucial
take the skeletons in the closet Hunter
hanging with the trainers who's finally
lost
[Music]
come down here
foreign
[Music]
to reach your head
now parties
[Music]
let's go grab your [\h__\h]
thank you very much everyone
thank you thank you we have Ashoka show
guys
[Applause]
thank you so much
not you know
not beautiful
[Laughter]
back in the day back in the day these
two we we knew each other in the
underground long time ago so yeah
yay thank you
Japanese Kim song
cute no cute okay
[Laughter]
so basically uh these two uh part of
Boogie box they're a music unit
um Undead music unit yeah yeah
um they've been making amazing music for
a long time but the truth is these two
are actually going to be stopping their
musical activities I think this month
but it has been an amazing ride
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
they said they're very happy to have a
chance to perform with me on stage
because we always wanted to right we
always wanted to perform together on the
same stage so now before their musical
activities together end we get a chance
to do that and I think that's really
amazing so we've got another song to do
this will be the last song for today
This song is called Crown please enjoy
foreign
[Music]
got nothing for me
then walk the road alone no high hopes
for the stop that ship for me
a pack of Big Dreams
broken foreign
[Music]
will I ever make a picture is it worth
it to try like could I really see my
picture on that billboard sign am I out
of my mind crashing back the days
[Music]
I can't do
yeah yeah
[Music]
so foreign
foreign
[Music]
you can talk tonight
I could understand
foreign
[Music]
thank you so much Boogie box
see you around bye bye thank you so much
thank you wow
[Music]
very emotional man those guys they've
they've really been there for me ever
since back in the day when I was nobody
they always cheered me on so a big UPS
to Boogie box for being who they are and
may their Journeys continue and and I
hope that they still create wonderful
things thank you so much you guys that
was amazing I'm glad that you liked it
thank you
well I guess now that we're here
um and it's just me alone again on this
big stage but I'm not alone because I
have wonderful deadbeats deadbeats
everywhere I'm not alone I'm not alone
because you guys are here that's always
how it's been thank you so kindly really
truly now speaking of live shows I
recently made a big announcement about
the calliope Mori new Underworld order
Blu-ray Blu-ray Blu-ray Blu-ray Blu-ray
Blu-ray if you didn't get a chance to
get it check it out this is how you can
find it you go to my channel hey look
that's me
um you can you can also check it out in
the description of this video you can
find a link to the Blu-ray but there's
the trailer click that go down yeah baby
thank you for making this video
go down to the description click that
little blue link right there and you can
choose what store you get it from either
of those links okay and the shipping may
be cheaper if you choose a local place
but if you're in the States you
definitely want to use the calliope Mori
official shop because the shipping is
going to be way way cheaper there let's
take a look there's the Blu-ray and with
the limited edition you get a special
tapestry
check it out
there's so many songs so many songs so
um it's really a fantastic piece I would
I would really I would love it if you
would check it out especially if you
didn't get to see the show
um and then on the Twitter you can check
it out on on the Twitter on my Twitter
if you scroll down you can find the
Tweet there click that link as a matter
of fact go ahead and check out and
follow the official Mori Calliope artist
Twitter that pretty much gets notified
about everything right away if you want
the earliest news about me and what I'm
doing go follow the official artist
Twitter and that's all that I have to
say about the Blu-ray please get the
Blu-ray and enjoy enjoy show it to your
friends and family just kidding don't do
that um please enjoy the Blu-ray and
enjoy watching all your favorite Mori
performances because it's it's really
amazing and I think the audio has been
kind of like specially you know
um put arranged and put together I
watched the whole thing I watched the
whole thing and it it's good it's good
um it's good sound quality is what I'm
trying to say so the sound quality is
good uh now we also have another thing
as you may all have
guest I too have 3D merchandise it is
tada
a very special pendant accessory set now
before you say wait a minute that's just
for the ladies Calliope Mori what the
heck I can't get that wrong wrong you
are anyone can wear this ice okay anyone
it'll look cool on anybody and you know
what if you really don't want to wear it
as a necklace you got two other options
okay two other options you can kind of
you know make a keychain yourself you
just take the you're gonna have to you
know use some tweezers and stuff you can
make a keychain out of it which is
pretty cool or you can set it up just
like this as a collector's piece with
the special Scythe acrylic and it just
it hangs down right from there it's got
my signature on it so you can you know
put it somewhere special show your
friends hey look that's the special Mori
Kalia dependent I really wanted some
some cool jewelry uh for me so um so
anyway that's uh that is my 3D
merchandise is a cute pendant everybody
else is kind of well from who we have
seen so far right
um with with Ina and Wawa they had kind
of like life essential things I wanted
to do something uh that is kind of like
out of the a way of that I guess so
here's this pendant
so yeah anyway you can purchase this
after the big myth collab on the fifth
uh everybody's 3D merch will be
available so please wait until then
um I guess that's it
wow we did it we did a show
here in this big stage with all of you
together with me
um thank you
well before this place Burns To The
Ground I just want to say thank you so
much everyone for always supporting me
and for for looking out for me I'll keep
doing my best
and I guess
I'll catch you on the flip side guess I
gotta go back to the Overworld because
there's still stuff to do there's lots
more to do all right well I gotta go
uh
goodbye everyone
[Music]