[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
the
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
howy
K huh what
oh you're going to off guy today but
today is not off
Guy where is it oh maybe oh actually
actually maybe not today but I know what
you mean I know you're going there now
but I guess it's a it's a free day
convention
right free days free f r e e
what K KY
ke hello everybody
is that a pit boy oh yes it is yes yes
oh hell hell yeah it
is and I will play Fallout New Vegas
again today we won we won we
W eh I don't know maybe today my radio
will actually work so let's mute VLC for
now I didn't change anything though I'm
just hoping it will work um
Fall Out New Vegas pray for the radio
and pray for pray for the game to open
on the right screen people were saying
or some person one person was saying
maybe I I didn't even notice anything
but I guess when you played the game you
noticed it some some some UI was bugged
and that might be because the game
opened on my right screen and then I
moved it to the left screen
how how to open game on the right screen
it opened on the right screen again guys
but I want it to be opened on the left
screen I don't even I don't know man but
it didn't bother me whatever you say
didn't bother me wasn't that the witch
game oh was it the witch oh okay well
then no problem
[Music]
then too loud this
Su generally pretty loud I will change
it once I am in game I turned it down
for you guys already
though uh didn't notice we we were
raring a
shirt well I'm wear wearing a vest
thing
yeah uh no but the thing is my middle
monitor is the monitor number one I
don't know if that's is that not what
that's it's like eh is that not what it
what it
is uh
maybe
maybe okay wait I think I did something
I clicked something oh I think I think
maybe I fixed
it let
me something something I clicked
something will start on the middle
screen
yes it's started on the middle screen
we let's
go let's go why is it so hot in my
room why want to drink I bought a cold
carbonated drink but it's just like a
water drink it has barely any calories
it's
uh yeah emotions so such an nostalgic
drink for
me just because I wanted something yeah
like flavored water I just I just felt
like I needed it to motivate me and
stuff I need something you need
something something more than just water
right something sometimes you need
something more than water uh all right
you can't can't right I can't tip out
tip tip tip tip tip let me tab out
and then oh yeah yeah yeah takes you a
moment to show I have to tab in to show
that then tab out again with task
manager where's my
mouse
H what mouse lost oh there it is
okay looks
good looks
good all right yeah yeah Window mode
already worked last time though it's
just uh I can't Tab out easily I have to
go on task manager if I want to Tab out
anything
okay
H
loud too
loud why why why
why
okay okay okay okay
continue and yeah let's go if you want
to say to sh ah yeah all right we
arrived in nipton was it hey there hi
there what's up oh this is empty girl
can you do your job and like fill it up
or what why is it
empty why is it
empty wh what what am I
uh what am I doing anyway uh this is the
second time I'm playing today I'm in nov
oh today second time I'm playing in
general I'm confused uh I need to get
back into the vibe and the how
everything works so give me a
moment
uh find out from Manny Vargas where the
ks were headed and find the men who
tried well the that's been there for
ages find out from Manny Vargas where is
where is is Manny Vargas here oh also ah
ah I didn't um
okay
oh chunky why are you sitting there
looking at
me like my keyboard needs to be like
this maybe I don't
know no
ah why don't you just work with Escape
uh h
oh I isn't this how I used to open the
console thought I open it with that
button
always
yeah maybe I maybe I just hi chunky wony
thanks for jumping up my table stinky
stinky girl
so
confusing it's not I don't
know I don't
know I hate
this I hate games that don't let me tab
out properly go [\h__\h] yourself
please okay I don't know how to do it so
it's like whatever we're just going to
continue being slow
I don't care although I uh found out why
am I walking what what ah why am I
walking like this why am I extra slow
now this can't be normal what did I
press I pressed the squiggle it's not
working whatever caps lock for [\h__\h]
sake okay whatever this is plenty of
speed H okay H I can't go forward now
what the [\h__\h]
hey there I broke everything I can't go
forward
ah oh I'm pressing e instead of
[Laughter]
w sorry I need a drink I I need to
[Music]
I know it's really
quiet I've been
getting ever since I first streamed this
or even before I've been getting am
Fallout streams recommended to me
constantly but like mostly the old ones
and oh
constantly though and sometimes I click
into them um and then there's this one
that I clicked
into and I
clicked somewhere into like random
random Tim stamp in the
Stream uh just I didn't want to play it
from the beginning because loading
screen and all that right so I just I
just pressed somewhere in the middle of
it not not really middle beginning is
but
and I act I actually managed
to find a good moment uh that's not what
I wanted to say but it was a good moment
before I actually managed to find the
cool thing but I I was like uh a little
bit Bamboozled because the moment I
clicked into was something I had just
witnessed in my Fallout stream
um and it was this guy that she then I
think Thomas that she then proceeded to
follow for ages because she didn't want
to kill him but she wanted to kill him
but she wanted someone else to do it so
she was just following him for like 20
[\h__\h]
minutes and I'm like when is this girl
gonna do something so I was just like
watching her follow the dude and
listening to the music that Amy was you
know playing for the New Vegas
radio and just waiting waiting for her
to do it I don't know why why I was
normally I don't really watch vods and
all that but like she was just capturing
my soul and then and then
she uh had someone knock on the door and
I did not know that this was going to be
dad's stream I didn't know but but she
she had someone knock on the door and I
was like because then the chat's like oh
oh Ki and she's also like oh yeah maybe
Ki but then she goes and then and then
nobody opens the door H she opens the
door but nobody's there I can't can't
today my brain is like somewhere else
uh and and then she goes back to her
table and she was like ah nobody was
there they ditched me and I'm like oh I
guess it wasn't the moment where I you
know went into her room and saw her play
Fallout I guess it wasn't that because
she came back and nobody was there is
what she says and then I watched a
little bit more and then turns out you
know she I realized okay no but this is
the time where she was in Japan and she
was talking about the Japanese food and
I'm like oh my God this is so nostalgic
and then she talked about yeah I must
have been kiata because there's she has
the goar in her room and and kiata wants
to pick it up and all that um and and
then I was
like well then maybe maybe it was me
maybe it was me and it's like I'm also
watching my past self you
know and then and then I knock again
apparently past me knocks again and am
goes there again and opens the door and
then and then eventually they come to
am's PC and microphone and uh I hear my
past self and I'm a uh talking a little
bit about Fallout uh and talking about
how the bread has been to her how how
it's been treating her and all that I'm
like wow this is like so weird it's like
I traveled back in time and I'm watching
myself interact in Japan with am it's
it's it's so weird and then I was like
thinking like oh I'm playing Fallout now
we have come full circle but back then
when I saw I'm going to play Fallout and
I said oh I want to play Fallout too I
don't really think that I meant it I
don't even know what I was thinking that
game was I don't think I knew anything I
don't think I was thinking much I was
just saying it to make conversation I
think and I don't think I was ever
considering it play it at the moment
because I didn't really even know what
she was playing you know I don't
know it's a Time Paradox for
real no it was just kind of weird and
and funny that the one stream cuz I've
been ignoring so many of these stream
recommendations in my YouTube
recommendations suggestions I've been
ignoring most of them but then one of
them I finally click on and it's you
know a time paradox
I don't know that was kind of cute it
felt like it felt like Destiny to me cuz
I got so many am stream recommendations
from Fallout I ignore several of them
and the one I click on is the and and
the one the time stamp also that I click
on roughly turns out to be the one where
I enter the stream to talk to
am it's just Destiny and fate is it not
not what are the odds man what are the
odds that's it freaked me out and made
me
happy uh made me a bit too excited okay
what the [\h__\h] are we doing who's this
Manny where is this Manny how do I play
this
game uh oh yeah does my radio work
probably not but let's try
again uh oh there's a new one now
but
uh okay so for now it
works it only worked for a few seconds
[Music]
always
hello are you are Manny Vargas what's
going on
man well this is longer than it worked
before
already uh who are you I'm Manny I'm on
security detail here you see a rifle
barrel sticking out of the dinosaur's
mouth you got a 50/50 shot at me it's
boom that's where you're shooting from
oh sorry I guess it's a bit loud right
now I'll I'll change the balance you
name anything that comes within a th
yards that looks like trouble lately
we've been getting ghouls coming from
the road to Repcon out to the West quite
a few last couple days let go the big
threat ising G are if they decide to
attack Force they'll run us over but so
far we've been lucky
Boon's a sniper same as me used to spot
for him when we were enlisted with the
NCR after we got out I talked to hi so
here we are I'd introduce you but uh
we're not so friendly right
now oh is it going to play the next
[Music]
song is that the next song or the same
song uh why are you on bad terms with
Boon and his wife we didn't see eye to
eyee on some things we had some pretty
big
arguments one day she turns up missing
and he hasn't said a word CU he thinks
you killed
her man you name it see I grew up in
North Vegas me and my cousin seeds got
him with a gang I love I only ever heard
of New Vegas something happened and
lasas anymore so I enlisted earned my
future brought down my best friend to
share that future with me and here was
this woman who was too good for it
trying to take him away so yeah I didn't
see eye to eye with the [\h__\h] wow dude
sheesh I mean there's always a north
south east west and so on of everything
I suppose but what I mean is like some
cities are like a cities and whatever
prefectures or whatever are called that
right like North Dakota South Dakota so
I'm like is there North Vegas in
particular I don't think so right that's
not what he means he just means he's
from the north north of
Vegas American
prefect well you know what I mean I
couldn't find the
word uh oh chunky wony are you going to
leave really why why you were chewing
you were vibing you were dancing
oh there it goes there it goes my
bgm she she knew ahead of time that the
bgm was going to stop and she was like
I'm out of here if there's no Hardy
music then I'm out of here but she's
looking at me wait do you not have
enough food are there Kibbles low let me
check if low on Kibbles cuz normally she
doesn't chill here oh you're so cute oh
rolling
rolling she she flopped over and rolled
over cute right let me see
no no no there's definitely enough
Kibbles but she just wants to be by her
mommy's side but also at the same time
does not want to be by her mommy side I
suppose ah what a complicated feeling to
live with must be so people always say
oh I wish I was a cat
and people always say they wish they
were cat because it seems like life is
so easy as a cat but have you seen the
the constant crisis that cats are in
have you seen those videos where like uh
the owner will open the door for them
like to the to a patio or whatever and
they don't know if they want to go in or
out huh can you imagine being constantly
like I don't know what the [\h__\h] should I
do like being not able to decide that's
something that we humans also experience
sometimes but it seems like like cats
are just constantly feeling like that
and and maybe Life as a cat is not as
easy as you all perceive it to be so
let's not let's not assume that life
that cats have it so
easy
indecisive as
[\h__\h] it's rough and it's not like you
can't just maybe maybe it's like you
know maybe it's actually like a problem
they have in like legit problem not just
a a a little little bit of a I'm feeling
so indecisive but more like this is how
I was born my brain constantly is like
whiplashing me whip whip whip whip
doesn't know what to do where to go it's
like a brain defect that they have maybe
who
knows anyway were you the game tough I
was in the man it doesn't get any
better uh okay shees Weir Flex oh it was
great I wouldn't trade it something
about that lifestyle the discipline
seeing new places making people safe
what's not to like she's still chilling
behind me cute
cute uh well I just felt like it was
time you know wanted to have a home plus
I was up at Camp go when Bitter Springs
went down I faked like I was sick to get
out of going
I knew some of the people there but when
everybody came back nobody would tell me
what happened and people would call us
murderers sometimes when we showed up to
secure
towns you're obviously a human not a
crow uh no that was really not worth it
that was really not worth it I'm sorry
that's not
funny no soundboard
really
a what is it
H I don't know
why I still don't know exactly just a
lot of people died who didn't want to be
a part of the fighting at all I don't
blame anybody for it there's so much
chaos when you're fighting you're lucky
not to shoot your own guys all week it
did take something out of it for me this
wasn't the same so when it came time to
reinlist I just took my papers and
walked somebody surely hacked it because
they were like Kiana you refused it too
much wait please say that again oh it
was great not that one something about
that uh oh now it's gone
okay sure I know him what do you want
with him
uh sure you know
him oh yeah it sounds like if he says
like that of course like I feel like
he's friendly with
him m
M but I'm kind of sad that this doesn't
use my Charisma
seemingly oh yeah a good friend if you
say so man what you don't believe me
listen I can definitely help you find
him but I've got problems of my own
maybe we can do a trade you need my help
there's something I need
too what do you need Novak it's home for
me now I want that to be for good I like
it here and I've left too many homes
behind but the only resource we got here
is junk without that people wouldn't
have anything to trade they'd all have
to leave we get most of it up the road
from the old rocket test site but a
bunch of ghouls showed up one day and
took it over can't get in there now
we're going to go ghoul killing the M I
need to fix my
rigging I
think where is my mouse
[Music]
I would but I've got to watch the road
Caesar's Legion has been taking
territory just east of here they took
Nelson Nelson if we let our guard down
they might attack all it takes for the
legion is for them to sense weakness I
only know one Nelson well they got to go
or this will be a ghost town before long
doesn't matter to me what you do as long
as the ghouls are out of there that's
good enough for me
H it mean a lot I'll help you I'll help
you with it of
course what the [\h__\h] was those
sounds just head over to the Repcon test
site west of here see if you can get the
ghouls out of there
okay see I've exhausted everything
YooHoo YooHoo I've exhausted everything
somebody's going to be happy well can I
get up
here every okay everybody must have
tried that before right who everybody
who played this game surely tried to
parkour this dinosaur and it ends
here I know I've seen a door but I don't
care about the door this is not how you
do parkour walking through doors who do
you think I
am well I'll check it
out hello yes yes we have T-Rexes Dino
Bite GI so cute you have T-Rexes
wow
onid
folks nice can I go up to the top of the
dinosaur
yeah is that a Jurassic Park reference
hello Manny can we see the ghouls from
here damn that's a that's a really cool
sniping spot I think like so far it
seems like every place we go they have
like a sniper on the sniping spot he
surely must have the coolest one out of
all of
[Music]
them okay who is this
dude don't listen to a word no bark says
NOK nothing but
nonsense no bark
door to Ranger Andy's Bungalow door to
Cliff brisco's
Bungalow lots of Bungalows lots of doors
lots of
people you should sell some junk H to
who H to the guy uh the one that sells
merch he buys
okay got why I got to come all the way
up to you huh huh
what kind of customer service is
this lazy [\h__\h] welcome to the Dino Bite
gift shop my name's Cliff if you're here
for the T-Rex figurines you're just in
time there's still a few
left
uh well there's T we also have an
assortment of the Repcon Factory
souvenirs Rockets things of that nature
no thanks I just I just want to sell my
own
things guns
darn it no one ever buys the
T-Rex sorry I'm not buying anything in
the first place sure thing uh okay
[Music]
uh uh I guess MK would be the place to
look for Junk if we have any wet
Stones turpentine tell me if I was
supposed to keep any of
this I hate T-Rex I don't hate T-Rex but
I really don't care much about dinosaurs
and like um Jurassic Park and all that
when I was younger I I watched like the
first movie I suppose but
yeah why was yopi so um delighted by
Godzilla I don't get it she waso
um I I love that game and I played it
too I didn't play the Godzilla uh DLC
though but like she's quite the Godzilla
fan girl huh she's getting a little bit
sussy about it
even she's a real really like for real
for real like what's so what what what
does she like so much about
Godzilla Godzilla isn't even
real um are we selling this
six
10 can I do I need them I mean I'm never
going to I don't know [\h__\h] the
legion you'll take that
back it's real to
her nether are you what do you mean I'm
not
real I'm not a robot or anything
might as well sell it all I don't know
if I want to disguise of them if I want
to disguise of them I just I can just
kill another one of them and get their
armor anytime
really uh same goes for them honestly
[\h__\h] them I don't need their I don't
need to carry around their ugly stinky
clothes that they have worn for
months
uh Traer hat recruit
helmet St Chas
yeah finally it's clear clean and
cleared
out nice music turn off the radio and
they're still going to bamboozle you and
play it in stores like these so what and
maybe maybe there's no
point the gun he sells is pretty good oh
really sell some dup weapons
yeah can do I
suppose Submachine we are shooting with
the 9mm Submachine the 9mm Submachine
the 9mm sub
machine the chopper wasn't the chopper
like the unique weapon that's why it's
worth so much
huh bonus critical gem
[Music]
wow I've heard that while incinerator is
cool is actually pretty
useless Nots really strong can I get rid
of
it is this a big Iron
song yeah okay damn fck I found
something special there oh our silence
pistol he goes like
shush single
shotgun this these ones are selling
right uh what about the single shotgun
ah ah he's gotone I'm not going I'm not
going to do this uh thing again not
going to do this again uh give me that
back
uh not going to do that again thank you
thank
you um get stuff from the shop yeah
okay
uh close call
so wait wait sure have a look what
should I buy from him you guys said he
has something
cool he's got a leaf blower I want that
IRL laser rifle Focus Optics is this the
one cuz it it has a c crazy price that
gun that
r e f that gun okay it's even more
expensive that's a lot of money but then
he'll also have money so that I can take
more of that
money that's the gun that's that gun is
that the gun guys guys just to make sure
is that the gun please let me know also
what what uh
thingies do I need chunky
wony what what do I
need it's not that the gun it's that
gun oh okay okay okay H damn it I
thought I had that gun I was looking for
D gun is that that gun though then uh
it
damn then I got the wrong gun I suppose
sorry I'm confused what am I
doing uh so uh
5.56 I don't have any of them
right just normal ones I suppose
uhhuh and uh God damn it where was this
wasn't there another gun this where's
the other 9mm
pistol
huh where's the one I
fixed
weird I I I what what's wrong with
me I I checked purposefully which one
had like the the full c and
d i I like literally looked at it so
closely oh man all right it's okay we'll
fix this one
too oh
man a
man don't need to
Dynamite nice
what about the service
rifle
machete can
go can go service rifle keep okay
Caravan shot
gun shotgun
I carry so much [\h__\h] around because of
you if you want to if you want me to
keep all this stuff you should be in the
game carrying my
[\h__\h] why you not there carrying my [\h__\h]
[Music]
huh
okay that's why I need a companion oh
okay when give me that give me that
companion come back soon now no no I
will not no you can't tell me what to do
say please at least then I'll think
about
it okay where are we going is this is
that marker leading me to where I need
to go that one over
there here I come I'm on my way what's
the no
no where are the weapons
ah I feel like we're there's so we need
to rearrange this let's rearrange this
how does it work again
um what do I press again then like right
click and the number or so
ah I I dropped
it hold a number and then click
okay 10 MIM pistol
one 9 mm 9
mm a two doesn't work for whatever
[\h__\h] reason uh why is that not just
on R for reload huh free 9 mm pistol on
free
Magnum
4 what do I have the submachine guns for
guys I don't know Cowboy repeater
five
uh that gun
six I don't know I will never remember
which one is which
anyway for high DPS is for the fast okay
fast Pew PE
Pew oh [\h__\h] I switched it out fast Pew
PE Pew and that gun eight eight
okay cool it's cute it's kind of
round
yeah let me check the map cuz I don't
know where the hell I am
what I need to
do
huh I need to ask Manny again
oh I thought I was already going to the
ghouls oh hi there howdy partner howdy
fancy seeing you out
here I need to help him first okay is he
up there
how do
I put away my gun
again how do I do that
again I mean I can just do this I guess
hold R
okay
Manny you have any luck with the ghouls
I'm counting on you well but I don't I
don't know you says you have to still
talk to you huh yeah see you wrong qu
what the [\h__\h]
oh there was a new one okay okay okay
okay I thought when you guys were saying
you have to help him first like I have
to still talk to him what the
[\h__\h] misunderstanding Corner Axel happy
birthday I wish they would just
automatically put either the newest
Quest or all the quests on my radar and
maybe mark them differently
where are the ghouls they're pretty far
right from what I could tell by the
map do you guys want my my
radio my radio the W radio you want
it you probably want the companion for
this quest for this one well I don't
know where the [\h__\h] and how I'm going to
get one
boom back in town okay I'll try Tom you
now have radiation poisoning yay visit
the doctor take rad away to lower your
radiation level [\h__\h] you can also
protect yourself ahead of time by taking
rad X which increases your radiation
resistance does it not go away on its
own what this is
scary I think it's gone
right e
no do I have to take
it like it just doesn't seem like
anything's
happening Gs are ghouls are pain for
that
reason just lows your stats I feel like
I'm fine
well I feel like I'm fine but
okay but I feel like I'm wasting it
because I I not like getting back right
away howdy where is this
Boon find the doctor is there a doctor
here too
Boon's room
but he comes out at night okay I can't
enter his room now it seems then is
there a doctor in the tent oh that
one
okay fix me up please Doc is you the doc
oh my God you're a very bloody uh have
you just like operated on someone Dear
God
I'm hurt let's see physically you're
fine wait
emotionally well I'm not the right kind
of doctor for that you have the same
voice as the first person I talked to in
this
game are you sure you won't be able to
read in the dark as
well oh uh what she wants 100 caps for
that what the [\h__\h] is that worth it
there are five voice actors in this
game I well in that case stand just like
that for a second I want to make some
toast what the
[\h__\h] bye that was that
sarcastic I don't want to use the r away
I only have
one or is it like not just because of
the moment I ended that was just a a
coincidence that it added so much on top
of like radiation that I already had uh
accumulated from all the food I've eaten
so
far cuz I was always wondering it says
Rad on those food items but nothing
really happened
always
oh
okay
[Music]
okay then well can I sleep somewhere to
wait for the nighttime I guess also in
the
tent careful they got Spies all
over what did you say that to each
other don't say it so
loudly I can hear
you
bed no
bed t for wait oh I can just wait
oh uh
uh 7 hours
maybe howdy still not really night time
but let me just walk over for a
moment there's a wait button I didn't
know
either
damn is this too
long oh it's still pretty bright what
the hell a there we go oh
are you are you Boon you just look like
yeah you look like the
dude
[Music]
Boon Bo Moy
Moy I don't want to I don't want to wait
okay 1
hour
boom uh 1 hour that's 10 p.m.
and then there's 11:00
p.m. and now and now wait go up to the
dino I thought he comes out at
midnight oh how you doing Manny
Cliff he's in the
dino
whoa ah you're the night shift I see I
see makes sense hi
whoa she
mean shees God damn it don't sneak up on
me like that what do you want you didn't
look very
surprised are you sure I snuck up onto
you yeah I guess maybe I am but not like
you I can help you sniping maybe it
should have been you I was expecting all
I'm a good sniper why are you here for
you if you're looking for someone in
particular I could tip you off if I see
them
okay let's say that yeah well you see
anybody wearing Legion Crimson or a lot
of sports equipment you just let me know
you still haven't answered my
question the [\h__\h] uh I just want to
check out the V I'm meeting new
people I think you better leave what
rude what I don't see how that affects
me how does how does
that work with what the previous
sentence was wait you just got into town
maybe you shouldn't go not just
yet I need someone I can trust you're a
stranger that's a start I I'm not just a
stranger but if you have seen my stream
title I feel like you would know that we
can get along
well I want you to find something out
for me I don't know if there's anything
to find but I need someone to try my
wife was taken from our home by Legion
slavers one night while I was on watch
they knew when to come and what route to
take and they only took Carla someone
set it up I don't know
[Music]
who my wife's dead I want the son of a
[\h__\h] who sold her okay
okay uh how how how bring him out in
front of the nest here while I'm on duty
I work work nights do you shoot him then
I'll give you my NCR Beret to put on
it'll be our signal so I know you're
standing with him mhm and I'll take care
of the rest I need to do this myself
okay just lure him out that sounds easy
good I'll make it worth your while and
one more thing you shouldn't speak again
not until it's over I might no one in
town knows that I know what happened to
my wife best they never know the legion
will be after me next I might just have
to sit on you and
make you crack you he looks just like
perfectly egg-shaped it's oh my God oh
my God oh my God his wow his egg
head look at that egg head
whoa he's like aital
egg have you ever seen such a perfect
egg
before Oh
[Music]
he's hired oh hell
yeah I know all right that's all you
need to know okay if you know that and
and and you're telling me that I should
know that you know that then I know I
guess okay yeah yeah yeah yeah makes
sense um uh is it marked now probably
not
right one for my baby ask around Novak
for information about who kidnapped
Boon's wife send someone in front of
dinky the dinosaur put on the Beret to
signal to Boon that this is the culprit
okay uh well from the get
go I thought you were like a ghoul or
something hey there from the get go I
thought it was the dude the the Manny
dude but can I talk to them
now this is
Andy hi Andy welcome I love your hat I
have a nice hat
too I think my hat's nicer we haven't
met yet you must be new in town I'm
Andy what can you tell me about Boon's
wife Carla was a knockout whenever Boon
walked around with her he always had
this funny grin on his face like he
couldn't believe his luck I know we
couldn't that wasn't the only reason she
stuck out though that girl never minced
words if she had better food or
Hospitality she'd let you hear it
trouble was she usually had I don't
think she meant it you mean she was Flex
she really was a sweet girl I think she
just wanted to remind herself that
there's still nicer places in this world
than Novak who could blame her for that
well I it's a cop I guess
had his wife taken I don't think he'll
ever be the same as he was damn shame I
told the Rangers up at the station to
keep an eye out but there's just too
much ground out there for them to
cover right now a whole lot of sitting
on my key C cracks in the ceiling I
wouldn't wish it on anybody on better
days I helped keep the peace Boon and
Vargas watch the road I watch the town
tell myself I'm doing some good yes you
are I think you are was was with them
that was back when my arm and leg used
to work better I still like to pretend
I'm a ranger though I'll check in with
the guys up at the station pretty
regular on the ham radio sometimes they
stop by tell me they're paying their
respects the smug bastards they haven't
been responding to me last couple days I
guess they got tired of hearing me talk
but it still got me a little worried
hell listen to me talk like some damn
mother hen
I felt
that I was already about to make a joke
before he said that already like oh he's
people are getting tired of his yapping
I hope that won't happen to me and then
he Dy makes a joke about a yapping
mother hen what the
[\h__\h] the wres are soft they're probably
already dead oh no let's not say
[Music]
that should I check in for you uh no no
they're going to think I'm having
trouble letting go they're good soldiers
I don't give them enough credit honestly
under that under that hat he might also
be hiding a pretty good egg
head they're the ncr's finest a onean
platoon each of them you got a job where
you thinking about it with scar man
senseless that's when you bring in the
Rangers and if you see a squad of
veterans guys who are in their black
armor well you won't find a more
beautiful
sight okay oh no no no no no no no um
did you do something with your leg Yeah
twice actually the first time it was
more like half my body knocked me out of
the
Rangers this time it's mostly just
reminded me how useless I've gotten
n well um from the beginning hey uh wait
a sec I know what I said but if you find
yourself by Ranger Station Charlie let
me know what you find I'd be interested
yeah I I don't think it's him from the
beginning until the end I never thought
it was him um oh time Paradox once
again uh Cliff
Brisco oh my god
oh uh
this is a little bit concerning as a
grown man oh don't oh my God I thought
like if I step over his T-Rexes he might
like shoot
me I just want to talk to you
oopsie don't look at me like that
surrounded by the
T-Rexes hey there if you want to buy
something from my shop you'll have to
wait till it opens no no no I just want
to talk to you can't say we spoke much
boom did most of the buying for him she
was in the store once but she didn't
stay long had a look on her face like
she'd smelled something sour but far as
I can remember the gift shop smelled
fine well fine as it always does it
wasn't him either but um come back soon
now I don't think it was him but they
don't give me much conversation options
with him do
I oh then let's talk wait this this one
I already yeah Andy I talked
to what about Manny is he up
here door oh door to motel room can I
sleep there
for sorry I accidentally I don't know
cuz this one was oopsie sorry I thought
if I walk in there someone's going to
kill me cuz I I I clicked because I
thought it was also going to be
available but it was red and
I I was scared sorry that was
scary I it's the only one that's red oh
but this one requires ah they all
require a key I
suppose American motels are
scary we don't have these kind of motels
in Austria like in America and I feel
like they you have any luck with the
ghouls they just counting on you they
they are scary right
uh like I hear a lot of really sketchy
and [\h__\h] up stories from
them a lot of crimes happening there
it's just scary as [\h__\h] and often dirty
and all that [\h__\h]
right really concerning
establishment people are just
paranoid but you never know you never
know you're going to ofai in one don't
scare me well I mean I think from the
POV of a an someone who lives in America
you probably are a better judge of which
ones are safe seemingly safe and which
ones are not like I would not be able to
judge that myself I think but like yeah
I'm sure you guys can like surely
there's some decent ones and you can
judge that I don't I don't think I could
judge it I don't have the the vibe
check uh who would want to hurt Boon's
wife is it you huh man everybody that
girl didn't have one friend in this
whole town didn't want any it was you
she wanted to sit in a room all day and
make herself miserable and she went out
of her way to be rude wait I get the
catch she upset a lot of people you
wouldn't have liked her either I get the
catch cuz I'm going to bring him there
but I'm also putting the hat on he also
has the same hat though so oh probably
before I even get to put on the Hat the
the sniper dude he'll probably be like
oh okay let's shoot
me even though I'm not the
one
no I need what do you mean I need actual
evidence seems like I can like bring all
of them to the dinosaur
huh okay I guess not yeah I would think
like there would be a misunderstanding
cuz he like only sees the hat from above
really and then he would just shoot me
by accident that would be funny
though believe me when I heard the news
my first thought was I owe somebody big
I figured boom would come around after a
while but he hasn't I'm starting to
think that if he doesn't find her things
will never go back to the way they were
what do you mean you owe somebody big I
get
it yeah see
you I I I feel like it's him though but
no I'll ask around a bit more if I can
find any more people does is it like
within this area because feel like I've
talked to
everybody or do these people also count
out
here we've been the city does this count
of is a
city ah are these houses I suppose
Yeah okay or not no no
no they don't really look like they've
been lived in
recently better not look at chat for
this one
you guys better
not spoil me it's that
easy that
[Music]
easy uh wait I go back around and talk
to the people by the tent
it was the dinosaur
[Music]
dolls I don't
know wait but like he wants me to bring
the person that I think it is to the
dinosaur and then he'll shoot him from
there but like how can he even trust
me like so easily like why wouldn't you
want to want to like find out yourself
like how how can you trust my judgment
and only my
judgment like you don't even know me I
could bring a random person there
like hello no probably wasn't you she
hasn't paid me anything yet should I be
worried between you and me I don't think
she studied at an accredited
institution uh I mean can I ask the
doctor
even what can I do for
you no
bye bye there's a house over there but
that also looks
closed let's see or is it it also looks
closed
hello follow the Markus oh okay
oh are we on the right Quest though I
guess so oh they're all on the move
now where are we going mercenary
H quirky
[Music]
murky uh sudden howdy music jump scared
me Dy make bright wait is this this my
radio right why is it
back why is it back
but it's like I mean it's realistic why
would the music be playing outside it's
playing in their homes of
[Music]
course hey there name from out of town
ain't you name's Dusty it's still pretty
loud not
because so long so long farewell I'll Fe
us saying
[Music]
goodbye I guess it's got to be like
that things treating you all
right is it too quiet now for you guys
for me it's pretty
good and what can you tell me about
boom's wife well to be honest with you I
don't know them too m i remember she had
an edge about her like she'd rather be
someplace else this kind of life ain't
for everyone that's for darn sure darn
sure oh I tend to my Ranch that's about
it of course you I also tell you I don't
get out a whole
lot you must mean what's left of it
somebody's been attacking our animals at
night we're down to less than half of
what we had a few weeks back
is it the wife that turned into a
ghoul who's attacking the animals
H every night around midnight Alice and
I wake up to some crazy hollering and
gunshots you'd think the world was
ending all over again but it's just one
animal each night they don't take it or
carve it up or nothing just leave it
there all full of I'm a
detective is this also grateful
if you find them before they get my
whole stock but don't go getting
yourself killed over it Alice and I will
find a way to make do always have H
that's sweet of you you're like oh you
can try help but like don't don't you
know go crazy about
it beg your pardon ma'am but them
two-headed bees ain't worth getting shot
over not to mention what would happen if
half of what noark says is true noark
best we can hope is that whoever's doing
this will move on or get tired of it I
just hope it happen still got animals
left oh no the animals are twoed I don't
think they're from around town seems
like they've taken to shooting from the
West Side my radio
died
again oh I feel like I so slightly hear
it just it just turned really
quiet so
long
weird where is your r
you I I feel like I hear it like really
faintly look who's
here what I don't like the screechy SC
screechy sounds of your chair who said
look who's here I heard a woman voice
but I only see you where's the woman
[Laughter]
what brings you here you scare me
Alice wow that's the strangest thing
last time it happened I could swear I
heard someone cry out for help sounded
like a big fella but when we finally got
up the gumption to go look outside all
we found was our cattle and I know what
they sound like when they get upset I
can't imagine what went on Dusty can
probably tell you more about it
mhm boom that's that sniper fella works
in the dinosaur right I only met them
but once or twice they seem real happy
together I really ought to get to know
them better they're probably nice folk
no one of them's
dead oh we keep to ourselves for the
most part try not to pry I think Genie
May gets bothered that we aren't more
sociable but it's just our way ain't
that we don't appreciate what she's done
managing this town like she has but I
worry she feels that way anyhow ah that
lady not that there ain't others who pry
around here noark was skullking around
our yard last
week I thought he was our C about was
about to lash him with our bull whoop
till I saw who it was he's harmless
though part of me wishes I could see
things like he sees them maybe it was
her full of
mystery um how noar get his name I'm not
sure who started it wasn't a very nice
name but he took to calling himself by
it so we all had to I don't even
remember what his real name is anyway I
think it comes from that expression that
people say when you're crazy that not
all of your dogs are barking poor no
bark I just wanted to meet you
uh kind of creepy of me to say oh what
I'm Alex weird you've already met my bow
Dusty yeah he's sweet ain't he I don't
care what my mama said I know how to
pick him we set up this Ranch years back
when nov was just getting settled but
now with all the danger on folks are
starting to come through here from all
over Noak might just be the next Nevada
Boom
Town goodbye ni it's obviously not you
but now I want to talk to the motel lady
again I haven't talked to her I haven't
seen her in a while where is her
house I sh the up
there what are you guys doing there's
another house
here that I have not entered yet ah
Genie May Crawford's
house wait is that the motel oh looking
dead wake up please that's her right
yeah I guess I wouldn't even be been
able to find her in the mot is
everything all right awful late to be
sorry about that what can you tell me
about W's wife I would be so pissed if
someone walked into my house in the
middle of the night when I'm already
sleeping just to ask these sassy
questions like get the [\h__\h] out what's
wrong with
you how should I put it I guess you
could say she was kind of like a cactus
flower real pretty to look at but there
was just no getting close to her she
never did take to living here she liked
the B big lights and fast living of New
Vegas I got the feeling she was trying
to get Boon to leave with her but I
guess she got tired of
waiting she doesn't sound saly so far
also like when you live in a world like
this why are you not locking your doors
that's also really
stupid but I guess it's for the purpose
of me being able to talk to these
people you should do it though that
wouldn't be wrong with any man who loses
a wife I suppose poor dear I know he
thinks she was kidnapped but I'm not so
sure she didn't just run off on her own
you could tell she was thinking about it
ever since they
arrived she didn't say anything
Saucy but I know you guys sus
her cuz you know the
story but I don't have a reason right
now to sus her
out
[\h__\h] we need evidence I don't have
evidence do I get the evidence from a
person or do I have to look around like
this you
know there's one one more oh one more
is it
the is it the small one that just
disappeared now like this
one check the reception there's an item
as evidence oh wait was it this
Ah that's the place I started in
today but it's all
red should I take it though wait there's
a radio
playing huh is that my
[Music]
radio guess that's mine um I don't know
normally I wouldn't do that but I
wouldn't be able to proceed in the quest
I guess if I wouldn't do this
am I not going to get
caught my
mouse it doesn't it feels
weird bill of sale that sounds like it
might be
uh the one I don't know note add a bill
of sale okay who would have known that
it's so easy to steal things when people
are not around
yooo then let's look at
it uh wait wasn't it like usually yeah
here we the representatives of the
console official room have this day
bargained and purchased from Genie May
Crawford of the township of Novak the
exclusive rights to ownership and sale
of the slave Carla
Boon she's a slave did we know that for
so she sold ah she sold Carla off to
someone that's why she's gone for the
sum of 1,000 bottle caps and those of
her unborn child for the sum of 500
bottle caps the receipt whereof is
hereby acknowledged we warrant the slave
and her young to be sound healthy and
slaves for life that sounds almost
positive like it sounds happy the way
it's
written we Covenant with the said Jenny
May Crawford that uh we have full power
uh to bargain and sell said slave and
her Offspring payment of an additional
500 B caps will be due pending
successful maturation of the fetus the
claim to which shall be guaranteed by
the possession of this docum how wait I
don't understand why does Jenny Genie
even have the rights to do
that and do I show him the evidence
first or do I just bring her
over she doesn't
Okay uh hi Boon you shouldn't be here if
people know we oh and if whoever did
this smells a rat they'll have the after
both of us I
mean I mean don't come here I have proof
though I don't think it matters bro why
would they suspect
me okay I'll bring her
over just bring her out
okay I'm going to bring her
over and he's going to bring her o in
jman we
say uh when you say you kill someone
other where she again oh
there bringing
bring uh
her
[\h__\h] you little sussy [\h__\h] that was
sussy Behavior just right there is
everything all right awful late to be
dropping in unexpected should I put the
Hat on
now watch out for strangers
watch shot for
strangers not yet yeah yeah not yet
doesn't
matter ah I can't oh I
can grayed out is everything all right
off [\h__\h] you think you can
decide who is yours and sell them off to
people
this is not how it works come with me
there's something you should see in
front of the
dinosaur okay if that's what you
think
nice let's go
yeah not even questioning what I found
in front of the dinosaur and kind of
stupid of
you maybe we should sell you off huh how
you like that maybe maybe you will be my
companion huh how you going to like that
h i don't need Boon I what what am I
just going to hire you to carry all my
[\h__\h] it's not going to be fun I'm
telling you you lost to be my meat
Shield even if you're dead at that point
I'll still continue wearing you as my
meat Shield doesn't matter you don't
need to be alive for that meat is meat
I'll strap you onto my front body yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah you you're you you'll be a
good guard surely that's the only thing
you're good for oh [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you
no damn son no hesitation no questioning
whatsoever wouldn't you want to look at
my evidence wait does she have something
cool absolutely no
hesitation
[Music]
uh
glasses I'll take
him and then how are we going to explain
this to the
others uh ah hello
hello so what do I talk
to him
now can we talk now
or do what can
I yeah okay oh my God this is so weird
bro boom why do you just trust me that's
it then how did you know now how how did
you know that I knew how did you know
that I'm just what if I mean why do you
trust me I don't get it this
no anyway I guess I shouldn't be
surprised be like them to keep paperwork
sorry surprised me a little bit this all
I can give I think our dealings are done
here what will you do after this I don't
know I won't be staying I know that
maybe she's is not dead bro don't see
much point in anything right now except
hunting legionaries maybe I'll wander
like
you yeah come with go to the legion you
don't want to do that no I
do yeah that might be true that's reason
enough for me to take you up on it I
suppose but this isn't going to end well
fine let's get out of here
what is this for him or for
me spotter perk is good huh it's for me
okay
[Music]
um I don't know
um help me out guys what do I want
speech maybe yeah and guns
[Music]
50 okay there we
go okay we have more stuff
now uh the new ones are down here uh
your position with a scatter gun is
something to behold when using shotguns
regardless of ammunition used you ignore
an additional 10
points I don't know that didn't enter my
my brain what did you
say bloody mess is good is
it with the bloody mess perk characters
and creatures you kill will often
explode into a red God ridden eyeball
strm paste cool oh and you'll do 5%
extra damage of all
weapons
uh they just had fun with that one yeah
no dfall
with the fortune find a perk you'll find
considerably more botle caps and
containers than you normally would
oh that also sounds good
though if I want to get rich while using
a pistol your accuracy invat a
significant increase oh but not a whole
do or similar hand one-handed weapon
what about
rifles yeah okay you guys have been
asking for that for a
while welcome to the team so you just
follow me
now oh he's always with me guys I forgot
can he die my companion you may be told
me before but I don't know
anymore yeah he cannot die he won't die
what do you mean I didn't pick it you
always say that and then it turns out I
probably
did I pressed accept
pretty sure did where can I see it here
see see every time only in hardcore he
can die okay cool cool cool cool cool
cool please don't
die please don't die like the last dude
I was trying to protect now that we have
done
this uh I guess we can try this one
really quickly Dusty McBride wants you
to look into nightly shootings of his
livestock which he says tend to occur
around midnight uh I might have to wait
cuz I think we're past midnight
probably
yeah uh let's do 13 hours for
now why is this so
slow uh
I know I can't I can't
calculate welcome to the membership
thank you there's a MTH that speeds it
up that too there a mod for everything
oh wait so what time ah
[\h__\h] I gives me a chance to
cancel can I go back please in time
Let's do let's do uh 18 hours
[Music]
it would have been fine damn
it he'll steal your aim what do you
mean
oopsie uh
seven let's wait and then
cancel okay around midnight at the
ranch did I mark it
I did Mark
it
[Music]
so evening evening
Governor where is it here oh I see
something there is that a ghoul bro you
with
me he's like straight up world
Warcraft should we talk nightkin that's
a World of Warcraft person
doesn't attack me though we can't talk
though should I just
shoot I can't talk to
him he's a little buggy he's bugged he's
just waiting there for his time cuz it's
not midnight
yet how disciplined of him
oh almost
almost I'm
nervous that was
easy wait was I supposed to like see him
beforehand Minun oh wait minig gun I
know that from GTA isn't that [\h__\h]
crazy I was not I was
not but that's amazing that was
funny it seemed very disciplined of him
to wait for his
turn uh uh do we do we report to the guy
probably
was it R
yeah yo I did it did you hear the boom
boom boom find anything yeah no one is
going to attack your Coral from now on
well I don't know how you've done it but
I do know I can thank you please take
this compliments of Alice and myself and
help yourself to anything in that
freezer Over Yonder oh we got more
steaks in there and we'd be able to eat
in a year oh have you been meal prepping
huh thank you so
long yay free steak I don't think I need
anything now though folks have come to
accept you for your helpful nature
yay sorry about that
physics Brahman steak 10 should I I
guess I guess I'll take it but my
weight how
much okay yeah are they going to fill it
up again in the future
I hope they will you can give stuff to
Boon ah okay okay
okay ah be aggressive use stim pack on
himself or
what but but if he can't die does he
just like fall down to zero and I have
to revive him or
so wait here talk to keep distance back
up open inventory use Mele fine by me
yeah he'll passes He he'll pass out
okay how much stuff can he carry
can I give him all my
cases I mean they don't weigh anything
but get take
this H around to the 50 is his cap oh
okay
nice wait why do I have ah ah I know
why uh take my wait that's also that
also doesn't weigh anything take it
anyway I just don't want so much
clutter I don't know take this what why
does nothing of that weigh
anything
um you just give him money yeah it's not
like he's going to it's not like he's
going to run off of it
going to sell the tire irons take my
jumpsuit take my weapon repair kit take
my I have to put on my Tripper helmet
again unless what I'm currently wearing
also has the same amount of armor uh
thingy keep the money on you to use
okay ammo would actually weigh something
in hardcore oh o
[Music]
take the staks for
now and
take a few other random
things if I give him a gun is he going
to use it does he need uh ammo do I have
to give him ammo ammo doesn't look like
he's carrying any ammo right
now he's got a gun but he will use it if
I give him a gun uhhuh uh but what about
Ammo he just needs one ammo cool he's
infinite sick I wish I had
that temporary addiction
removal what the ah there's that's for a
weapon right
um yeah okay I'm not I really don't need
that much weight off of my shoulders
right now anyway so we're good thanks
bro we got a companion and we did
another side quest y yeah y y let's do
the next thing what was
this it
seems of Brahman who are allegedly
keeping the Offa awake at night by
screaming inside his
head whose Quest is this the
[\h__\h] oh sorry ah that was not a quest I
pressed the wrong thing ah it's from the
night
K
ah oh the the night K we killed he felt
like the the the cows were like
bothering him in a weird way okay head
to Repcon for the ghoul activity uh
yeah I'm
scared is this way way
right let's go
bro
safe you love ghouls I love them in the
show I mean love well actually yeah I
only love the
one but the the [\h__\h] up ones are
obviously not
really very enjoyable
all mine what you're mine can he
accidentally shoot
me I don't think I did that did I or it
won't show me the crits that he does I
guess maybe I did
that maybe I did do
that all
[Applause]
Bo so will show me his crits huh
oh oh thank God there's no Friendly Fire
yeah oh oh who did you shoot oh this
this bro oh wow nice head shot oh my god
do I even have to do anything now oh
mine no mine too let's
share sharing is
caring oh aim do aim doco
Boon wa that looks like that could hurt
me too bro be careful
[Music]
psycho okay I see I see how this could
be rough alone with so many coming
towards
us H yeah I don't have any mods on and
it's running fine I don't know like I'm
almost right to say like oh don't worry
about
it it will be fine it really does not uh
crash at all the only thing that pisses
me off is that I can't window uh that I
can't out but that's not really anything
to do with
that change the mod Ah Ah that's what
that was ah ah
ah ah the aiming
ah what was that
again the aim the
[Music]
aim uh a true iron sides
a you looking for
trouble yeah I guess that's different
now cuz I just I'll just shoot wherever
the cross is
right it's like the same I just zoom in
I guess
should I do that oh you like that I I
think we figured out last time that I
probably should be doing that because um
it was just throwing me off the way it
was oh complet it oh that was easy
actually
wait uh enter the facility discover the
source of the ghouls
oh why why is it not turning
here ah
my mouse do you see like it's it's gone
and then it pops up again this is
confusing me
[\h__\h] oh no it's not turning it's not
turning it's not
turning ignore your
mouse but now it doesn't
turn what
no it's fine I guess
I guess it's
fine scrap metal maybe I don't know
should I bring it they have a chest oh
they're doing it with bottle caps give
me those bottle
caps I have to pick up each
one come on
ah worth
it ammo there too there's ammo I don't
see the
ammo
oopsie it's immersion I guess
so
uh oh oh stamp pack let's go
always love me some stim
packs they're looking into this
one okay uh where to
next that
way what's up there I
wonder oh is this where the ghouls are
coming
from
oopsie why
what is
this are you quick saving often I am but
I
mean really the game has not given me a
reason to quick save that much thanks
for the membership
welcome welcome to kfp oh there are a
lot of them do I even have this reach
with this
gun I should give him a couple of
different
guns oh I totally should
oh my my thing has good range
okay rep contest side
yay we've made
it okay uh bro
uh fine by me we're going to give him a
gun that I don't really use but it still
should be maybe something that gives him
more variety what should I give him
is he going to use the grenades if I
give him one some give the
minigun he but the minigun looks fun
what's the ammo for the
minigun his gun is good he good with a
sniper Still Still 5 mm do I have that
uh oh yeah I have a
lot you just need one so here
six ah
ah no no it's it's okay the movement
speed actually it doesn't bother me
today I'm fine thanks a lot of you guys
reminded me though but when I tried
pressing the thing it didn't work
it's not working so whatever H but right
now it's probably not working cuz now I
have the keyboard on German but I used
the Japanese keyboard before where the
button should be there indeed like
before it worked but yeah the
Brotherhood the Brotherhood was
here
oo the Brotherhood was here or maybe
this was originally I guess this could
be originally the brotherhood's uh
headquarters oh and I guess the ghouls
maybe originally were Brotherhood people
too not that
Brotherhood oh well I mean still similar
Brotherhood this feels like a
dungeon no they go around full I don't
know maybe he just had you know
sometimes they take it off right can't
run from
me do I is this working am I doing
damage oh that was me that was me I
gained Karma
yay me gaining Karma kind of
um bro that scares me don't show me his
crits don't show me his crits they scare
me missile what uh I was going to say um
it makes me I feel like I'm playing
Fable which makes me
happy bottle cap bottle cap bottle cap
bot bottle bottle bottle cap bottle cap
bot bot bottle cap plop bottle
cap check the ash
B you can turn off kill cam in the s ah
but I don't want to turn it off
completely cuz I I I do like to uh
experience it when I'm doing the crit
man didn't see you
there laser rifle another
one oh I did have
options what the
[\h__\h] stealth
Boy how do you use
this you just put it down on the ground
and within that area you're more
stealthy or what
score so turns you
invisible whoa you just eat it and then
I get stealth plus 100
wow launch music signal found launch
music signal what what for
radio it's temporary use it now I don't
think I need to use it now useful for
this mission
wait do I go
in don't
y hello hey oh over here are you
listening uh go to the big room on the
east side of this building and take the
metal staircase all the way up hurry how
did how do you know there's someone
there who I am doesn't matter smooth
skin stop wasting time and get up
here like I said find the metal
staircase in the big room on the east
side of the building it's where they
used to make rockets you just want to
eat me don't
you get moving sorry I already forgot
some kind of
staircase they're invisible oh no
oh the crits bro you crits scared me
stop oh there's a mutant Mutant Ninja
Turtles oh cute stealth Boy I he was
stealing that's what they use that
what's that's what he was using I
thought it was just like kind of what he
can
do
hold hey good looking
want you
[Music]
cooking it is possible to trigger this B
trap without injuring yourself well no
let's leave it alone maybe someone will
run into it an enemy perhaps hopefully
not uh
Boon night K are addicted to stuff boys
well understandably if they're helping
them so much with eating
cows but also oh oh
hi eat
this I swear to God this is going to be
the end of
me oh God
[Music]
St back let's go oops sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry
sorry brief W
brief not even like that scared
generally like in in the last kind of
like dungeon so to say that we went in
where I was like really
scared now I guess it's because now I
have Boon really he takes off a lot of
the the panic but at the same time
his crits scared the [\h__\h] out of
me oh this is becoming a maze now oh oh
dear oh he has what is that a
machete wow
collaboration
beautiful is that the minigun I gave him
or is that the rifle he had since
before welcome
Raiders thank you welcome to the stream
we are playing Fallout I'm still a
newcomer still new to this game keep
looking hey good
looking what you
cooking minig gun is empty what I gave
him stuff for it though what do you mean
I thought he just needed one one ammo
who's who's screaming eat this oh he'll
take care of it I guess terminal
terminal
terminal oh welcome to R Co cake what
what uh Public Kitchen please remember
that the kitchen is a privilege and not
a ride please clean up clean up after
yourselves and remember that a clean
kitchen is a Happy
Kitchen okay please also remember that
any food left in an ice box without a
date will be thrown away
okay greetings fellow Repcon employees
I'm happy to announce that we have
finally our deal of rco starting
tomorrow we will be an official rco
facility most of you won't notice
anything different aside from an
increase in
benefits thank you all for your time and
welcome again to the frco
family this is a suppos kind of a
relatable
uh
email Stacy are you kidding me we've
been planning Martin's party for months
now and you forgot to order the cake
there's no way we are going to find some
place to deliver one out here on this
kind of notice go to the break room and
find something for everybody to eat at
the party
Gordon that wasn't so interesting as I
thought it would be what another raid
another
raid where the where are the
monsters you're mine me I'm yours stop
we so romantic
a thank you wait I think there's a
romance starting between me and
Bo that's the last of the ammo oh you
ran out of it I thought he just needed
one oh okay ah does he only need one if
it's the gun he had from the
GetGo is that how it's meant he did lose
his
wife my replacement wife I'll take it
I'll take it I don't mind that
that doesn't necessarily mean that I'm
worse or anything you
know nothing more romantic than hunting
ghouls honestly the way it feels so
loose uh right now it's it's kind of
like a cute outing for us nice activity
for
us yeah thanks for the rids
everybody is this the same yeah it's the
same
lame uh guess we can go up there I just
want to make sure like there's so much
so many paths I don't want to miss
anything but we probably
will probably will what's this door oh I
can unlock it surely there's nobody
behind that oh wo
who sheesh aggressive door opening whoa
aggressive physics scrap Electronics
first a k let's go Super S bag
yeah sertin
conductor nice we love those first aid
kits we love
them oh bobby pins I'll take those
what's up there pilot light okay
[Music]
so many loots
yay man this is such a fun outing with
my new hus bule Hub
bule oh where should we go what about
this door oh this one goes
down it's so bright down there
why what what what's what's making the
camera
is it a
bug oh my God there's something behind
that eat this oh he opened the door you
can't just do that wait for
[Music]
me didn't tell you you can go be careful
bro be
careful okay okay I need you to be chill
and
slow wow he's carrying a lot of stuff St
pack what is what was turbo another drug
right for what
though junk food
yummy botle caps botle cap bot
cap botle cap bottle
cap bottle cap follow
cap so many oh he's got to look closely
at the floor I suppose sensor modulas
that something
interesting you're taking the plasma
rifle should I not be taking them
careful with the raight yeah I don't
know I was thinking we can sell them but
if the weight is looking
dangerous fine by
me
uh for e d e for
crafting so should I bring
it what was I picking
up what what laser
[Music]
rifle if I give him food is he going to
eat it to
heal automatically
help me no oh okay eat this did I take
it nah I can't [\h__\h]
that's that shook me to the core
uh I I I cannot have this as long as I
have a companion I need to turn this off
cuz like maybe when I'm like with him
fighting the same monster
then I'm I'm going to be in in the same
Zone and expecting it but as as if if
I'm looking somewhere else then it's
going to be pure panic mode what did I
why am I so
slow there we go okay I panic caps
locked I turn it off too it's really
cool when you're on your own fish and
Battery you guys tell me to go back for
something if there's something
interesting
okay oh oh that's where we came in oh we
came full circle let's go that relieves
me of the worry that I'm missing
something uh so can we get much higher
oh door maybe there another first aid
kit uh uh
I don't know I don't
know [\h__\h] I know this is really
weird oh there we
go there's nothing here really
hold tab for
light yeah finally done it I finally
done it are you guys
Happy do I like need batteries for that
light oh thanks for the membership
gift there has to be something
interesting
[Music]
here no bad is required okay
ah paint
gun wait that sounds kind of fun I want
to use
it do I need paint for
it oh this is kind of it focuses the
light too much in
one place then this is actually this
makes it easier to see in in this case
it's not a real weapon no
lame they forgot to put some things in
those Foot Lockers and cabinets there
should be something in
there it's too empty oh wait there was
one One path that led up where was
it where was it here
completely forgot like not even
considering following the path that the
dude originally
said I forgot there was a path to be
honest that he wanted us to take but
this really only seems like the only
only
way yeah the the radio sorry guys I know
you want to hear the radio but it's fine
it's
fine it's fine like this we don't need
the radio to enjoy ourselves
is this where I came from no it's locked
again
okay pushing me down
bro I got 20 XP
[Music]
yay you want to hear me first and
foremost I thought
so I knew
it I
know thanks for letting me take some
time
for myself so to say yesterday um I did
end up doing some productive things me
and
RBF we went to pick up some Ika
lack
uh uh uh shelf thingies wall
shelves I got a lot of them probably too
much but I got them secondhand so uh I
got them really cheap first I was
thinking of buying them but then I saw
for the fact that it's just a simple
piece of wood uh I saw how expensive it
was and I was like [\h__\h] that maybe maybe
I can get them second hand I I think of
that too rarely I should really try more
often to go that
way oh my God what is this
spooky yeah so I got a lot because it
was second hand and a big set of them
and then we brought them home and uh we
tried we wanted to originally we wanted
to attach all of
them but we started with the one that
goes onto like a
bone bone wall a concrete
wall and the drill that I have in fear
it works for that
stuff but it like like
melted and ruined several tips of the
drill you know what I mean obviously I
wasn't doing it I was just like
vacuuming but um but not melted but like
it definitely like just drilled off the
tip because it was not just concrete
like we met like
uh uh uh metal metal wall stuff inside
the
wall
so uh and it was really [\h__\h]
exhausting to just Mount one of them on
a wall like that so RBF was like okay
I'm coming back on a different day to do
the other ones the drywall ones will be
much less of a problem Oh skill 50 what
the
[\h__\h] yeah so in the end we just did one
but even that was um just looking at uh
RBF doing it I got exhausted from it
that was pretty tired too
so yeah
F
computer uh oh yeah I guess uh oh I love
this stuff let's hack it let's hack into
the gate go go how do I oh I have to
oh choose one we finished the converting
that as you requested if you need to get
access to the safe the password is
Repcon
ah thanks
bro how do I put the p
where is he how do I put the password in
for the for
here I'll be happy to take my retirement
package could rid to you into this for
second place different save
oh in this room they probably said which
safe and I did not register the
information
well if I'll find one I'll give it a
try uh okay wait
so oh is this a dead
end never mind what oh this is where we
can't is
it staircase
check look oh uh oh what the [\h__\h] is
that
radiation that's literally melted
smoothie my
cat just melted from the
heat gol
goop
ew no don't step in it I
guess ew ew search go
pile
ew can't run from me he really properly
walked around it all
[Music]
clear all clear I see
oh well this is looking
interesting
company bro you took too long what are
you
doing funny how I became the meat Shield
though seemingly
uh okay here we
go level
build no I don't need to pick up
everything
right do you have uh one of those sneaky
things around you
no yeah I'll just take the bottle caps e
no the cows not the cows am I on the
right track by the way is this the path
to the dude there's a lot of stairs he
talked about
stairs H Vats oh I forgot about
Vats oh a lot of people told me to use
Vats more
often okay okay but like what if it uses
up so many of those points you
know this is the right
okay uh should I be
scared not with Boon with me
right door to Repcon research Labs
requires key oh I don't have a
key key
a
key speaking to the intercom oh was
there
one locked himself I guess
there was an intercom oh that
thing Moy
Moy all right smooth skin I'm letting
you in you better watch yourself smooth
skin is a good name for one of those no
fur
cats God but are you ugly excuse get
upstairs and talk to Jason before I
throw up just from looking at you what
me me ugly
when you've you've been seeing all these
ghouls what's your type the
ghouls if I'm ugly then what the
[\h__\h] your pranks won't work on me smooth
skin they won't work on Jason either
what
pranks stop wasting my time smooth skin
go waste
Jason's what the [\h__\h]
who's
Jason
hello um that's the brother is it is he
wears the same
clothes he has ghou
helpers what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] I didn't know they could
help like
this not now smooth skin you don't call
me that
stop everybody calls me
that sorry sorry
sorry sorry oh oh I F wasn't there a
ghoul here just now I thought he would
shoot me
immediately sorry
sorry I accidentally opened
it I don't know I I as long as I don't
take it it's okay oh okay I I thought
just the act of opening something would
get me killed
okay uh where's this Jason guy bro up
here oh hey fancy seeing you again you
did not Jason guy right
yes yes go B Jason smooth
skinin guess I'll go B
Jason what the [\h__\h] man what what's this
stuff rway
oh I need some rway R
away um
I thought I was just following the oh
these party hats I was following the
arrow sorry sorry bro
sorry don't want to bother you too much
this is the way
probably i y you're shiny Jason that's
you hello Wanderer please forgive us our
humble surroundings our true home awaits
Us in the far beyond have you come to
help us complete the great journey oh is
this a kind of cult
definitely what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
is wrong with you what's a great journey
we wish to escape the barbarity of the
Wasteland especially the violence and
bigotry of its human inhabitants the
creator has promised to my flock a new
land a place of safety and healing a
paradise in the far beyond Cults are
very popular in this world complete when
the demons
appeared tell me more about these demons
am I one the demons appeared from
nowhere except it might be more accurate
to say they never actually appeared at
all to me you are Dem are invisible
where one of them stands the most one
sees is the air shimmering like sunlight
on water they set upon us as we were on
our way to worship one morning we had
just entered the
basement my flock fought bravely and
killed a few but at such cost nearly
half of us died or went missing the rest
of us retreated up here one of the
Demons raved at us but they have not
tried to attack us since still their
demonic presence brought all progress
towards the great journey to a
standstill but now you have come once
again the creator has sent a human to
help us across a seemingly
insurmountable you're not happy with
that are you cuz I don't think you like
humans I'm here because feral ghouls
have been wandering into Novak you the
demons let's ask that one yes over the
intercom ah threats of death should we
step outside guarantees of safety should
we stay locked away huh it went on for
hours and did not always make sense
sounds almost like a b that was the
first day only since then
silence will you drive away the demons
Wanderer the
demons oh the other options not there
anymore
I I get I
I I feel like I don't want
to but praise the Creator bless you
Wanderer bless us all as soon as the
underground has been rid of demons
preparations for the great journey can
resume get rid of the nightkin oh the
nightkin in the basement if it's
nightkin then I don't mind killing them
but I feel like it's not the night kins
that are the demons are they I don't
know you guys are so weird and why are
you normal
looking I don't get
it are we going to find out more
please
H ask him
again [\h__\h] you is the way clear no but
uh oh there's
more how will you make the journey the
means by which the great journey is to
be accomplished are an article of faith
not to be discussed with Outsiders
I have glimpsed it only in Visions
Wanderer but what I have seen is truly
miraculous it is a place of light and
healing and I know in my soul that my
flock will be safe
there she sounds like me talking about
Wanderer and probably the great
Wanderer flus my
chickens what's it the what's the deal
with the human who let me in you're
referring to Chris I doubt you had much
luck if you tried telling him that he's
human we had the same discussions when
he first appeared you too and the same
lack of
success he believes he is one of us what
soon enough we realized that Chris was
GI from the Creator he is integral to
the success of the great journey he's
just he's what if he's just infiltrating
the system
and role playing this whole time to kill
you guys from the
inside should I say this I feel like and
they've been shooting them down like
animals haven't they those ghouls were
members of my flock even after the
madness consumed their minds we never
let them wander free we kept them safe
on the first floor we kept them
contained
the demons must have let them out
somehow and now they are lost forever
denied the salvation and healing glow of
the far
beyond please Wanderer bear in mind that
every feral ghoul you spare now is one
that we can save
later the is clear our F brothers and
sisters will accompany us on the great
journey if there are any
left you guys are so
weird let me know when the underground
has been you guys are so
weird so weird how do you even like are
the feral ghouls like how do you how do
you get ghouls to be so disciplined like
those ones that are walking around doing
stuff will I learn that too
and especially that Jason guy he looks
like he consumed a little bit too much
of all that
[\h__\h] and he's still not
FAL some girls maintain sanity some
don't they start normal yeah yeah I I
would assume so but
[Music]
like okay let's go kill some night kins
I don't mind doing
that there a fun activity for
me oh another
door oh
easy a
safe that kind of safe
this
[Music]
oh all the energy cells are for the
laser pistol right I have so many of
them now I should be she I should use
them laser pistol do I have it on any of
these tell me if one of these is a laser
pistol these ones are not is this the
laser
pistol no that's oh that's the 10 how do
you
know
um laser pistol
aha let me do some cleaning up really
quickly if I
can TI
iron when the iron is really tired of
being called iron from me that's when
it's a tire
iron why does she call me iron that's
not how you say
[Music]
iron well that's how I want to say
it anyway what number should I even put
it
on let's just put it on on the one for
now and remember I got rid of the 10 mm
for
that
move
no I want I want to go more low oh
well no
what no
what lockpicking is weird in this
game then it suddenly
works oh
I think I I opened that one before huh
uh anyway I just got to go down right
where is
down down down down by the river no down
down down down down by the river I can't
sing that anymore it's been too
long oh okay
yay my game
crashed yo let's
go oh I am actually excited but [\h__\h] I
didn't save in a
while oh I didn't save in a while but
this feels like the real
experience I feel like this is just
appropriate
man I was disappointed for no crashes
auto save please is there was there Auto
saves this is before no okay okay okay
okay it's after we accepted the quest we
just got to go down down down by the
river and kill some napkins that's not
bad that
door now I'm scared to open that door
again a true fall experience yay it was
this wasn't it how did I how did I get
so
far
oh oh it worked this time hey dark in
here oh wait if you want to use a scope
I can spot for you target this is not
where we originally came from is it
looks not so
familiar
oh jump scare
time
no no I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready I see
you
bro she
bro good I
someone's walking and it's not
us it's over
there can I see them if I take the same
medicine
uh no oh
[Music]
okay slowly healing
easy is this one supposed to jump scare
me oh nice it's no
problem I'm not scared at all I don't
even need all these stuff boys although
maybe for a future Mission they would be
useful but I don't
know they're not that strong either yeah
thank God they look very bulky buff buff
but they don't really got much going for
them but I I'd like to at least like try
talking to them run from
me can't run from me indeed when you're
stuck on the [\h__\h] table
bro he's acting like an idiot
oo check ammo the good thing is that
they they're so like that they're
they're huge targets I can hardly
miss you can buy perks eh
what oh I could have bought a perk to
talk to them their minds are too far
gone they look like they're less far
gone than those cult
ghouls what was I going to
do oh the ammo what do you mean check
ammo
what what's there to
check check your ammo
why I mean it says 12 out of
155 you only have four bullets left on
on which
one wait which one am I using oh oh I
wasn't I thought I was using the 10 mm
one I was that gun was I using that gun
ah
a
ah now that makes a lot more
sense why you were telling me that oh
that's a
door this where I came from oh
oh you so fast
y he's so fast speed that's the one
thing I'll give them speed
Advantage wait I'm I'm I'm lost I've
been here before where did I not go
uh I just entered here this is this is
cute can have a little speech
here I'm good at speeches
surprisingly
good is this the
entrance
oh do we have a first aid kit in here
there's a
conductor uh no idea no idea no idea no
no idea no idea
n lots of mats yeah supplies
M K is a world for Alliance player
exactly like I'm
not if I was more of a horde fan then
maybe I would be on the nightkin
side but the ghouls are not very Al
alliances either where are the rest of
them
I don't need that light I don't like it
but maybe for you guys to see better on
the
stream here we go that's a new
room
oh W he's got an incinerator bro are you
good
Boon are you okay are you okay
what is
it are you
okay yeah bro oh he's fine he's a
phoenix
maybe he might have potential to become
my uh
uh successor
[Music]
yeah jail key that might be
useful they got
jails
successor
Prodigy paint
gun Finance
clipboard damn there's just so much junk
everywhere it worries me that I'm
missing something camera oh it's a
really old cute one wow it looks like it
plays some sound in that thing but
that's really not what that does it's
just the
light a carton of
cigarettes no too much junk
batteries are good batteries where the
batteries
oh another little small room is wait was
conductor a battery why won't you use
fats cuz I forgot about
it I forgot about it
sorry batteries are a bit
heavy I can't even I don't even think I
saw one
one can't
differentiate I always forget that's a
thing you too yay it's not just
me I'll try to
remember loot strip too yeah I can come
back here I guess and find a lot of [\h__\h]
if I wanted to if I need it like scrap
iron and
[Music]
stuff gold prisoner
oh these were the prison rooms
anybody still alive
here I think I'm supposed to bring you
back if somebody's still alive but no
nobody looking alive here is this it
that's all I can find
here the
[\h__\h] that's all I can
see I'm tackling this differently am
I what what what did you do so
differently
The Sounds freak me
out I didn't find anything
there wait is that the is that an
incinerator over there flying
around it is that's
random oh this way
maybe oh no I've been here too
I've been here
too from the night
K he drops it like
that I feel like there should be more I
missed the jail
cell
really I need the niking balls yeah
where is he I challenge you to a battle
oh wait this did I go
here probably did go
here yep oh this one maybe no I went
[Music]
everywhere I entered all of this are you
saying I missed
something I got one guy ah for [\h__\h]
sake
man it's probably because one guy
comments just stand out more because
it's just one guy saying something
different from everybody
else what about this path
looks like I've been here
before um that just goes
up Repcon
facility yeah that's H the wrong way
W
[Music]
cute
youly
davidon I get
so they just get [\h__\h] stuck wo wo wo
wo wo wo wo wo wo wo
wo the right moment for me no what what
no need a medic you oh sorry did I
headshot
you he was peaceful that was the
peaceful
one
well I thought that was the boss cuz he
had a name
even well the night can are gone now
they are gone now I've done my
job [\h__\h] I've killed too many
now so even the friendly ones will try
to kill me
now can I make it up to
[Music]
them
oh what is
this he wants the boss
[Music]
okay so I would have just talked to him
and then
probably uh continued to kill him I
suppose oh that's that's the
batteries I'll take
one there was an option for
peace between me and them or or all of
them in
between each other
his sword is unique all of the what no
what have I
done
no what is this
place his sword is not unique
uhhuh I guess I didn't pick up
everything
huh
well the weird cult ghoul will will be
really thankful at least space
suit I can role play and cosplay Amit
that's really valuable too 729 ball
caps
moment take the H oh I didn't see the
helmet
somehow nice I can go to space now fu
fck earth like fallout's Earth is so
[\h__\h] up why would I want to Moji R oh
why would I want to stay here if I have
the option to go to space all I need is
a spaceship which should not be too much
trouble
right we'll find a
spaceship you can call them from
here call who the G put it on boon
uh it's right there yeah I mean I saw it
yeah but like I don't know if that's
really going to
work okay I'm going to go back I don't
know I don't want to leave to go to the
Wasteland from here I need to
report my
quest check other room for last school
I missed a room go
back other
room in these
sewers not there before the David boss
okay damn oh he has a cool helmet here
oh no that's not a helmet
[Music]
it has a lot of value I might want to
sell that but my
wait it's okay we're done with the quest
we can probably sell stuff soon go back
and
sell was there another room within here
no equip and check it
out uh
uh wow that's a monster hunter kind of
Sword yeah big
sword is it
good W it's kind of in the way like it
blocks my view
H were you guys telling me to like I
don't know go here
maybe ah un like with Davidson key
Davidson's key but there's so many of
them dead night kins what happened that
was not me get it you big dumb oh hey
you're not one of those things out there
who the hell are you I I helped you I
think maybe you noticed a bunch of
invisible monsters out there uh-huh I've
been in here trying not to get
dead wait his voice is the voice that I
heard I
bring first off I'm not trapped this was
a tactical Choice sure buddy sure I'm no
match for those things out there so I
found a good defensive position it was
the B guy I've defending it they all
have the same voice oh who am I fooling
I'm trapped
name's Harland pleased to meet you what
happened was I was escorting folks down
to work when those things attacked us
most of the fight was upstairs but some
folks panicked and made for the basement
and I went after him that voice turns
out there were even more of those
bastards down here than upstairs it
doesn't sound comfortable [\h__\h] fast to
talk like this could find the others
like so I fell back to this room set up
a nice little Kill Zone with a and a
story a male voice can you when if you
try to talk like this is that difficult
for
you I would ruin my throat when you
smoke too
much yeah the smokers maybe say it's
easy it would hurt after a bit cuz if I
want to talk like
this I try to avoid making voices like
that
I can't even go that low
really it's easy when you're Batman a
wait is is that actually the voice actor
of Batman no
right or the actor is the same voice
actor or what no way no okay it just
sounds like it
then what can you tell me about the
creatures out there I killed them on
site so we haven't had much time to get
acquainted they're hard to see too bad
obviously but they are too smart when it
comes to tactics or not stepping in
traps
H uh well you don't look like the other
gouls from brid's group that is very
sussy guess the outfit gives that away
huh I never did buy into that religious
mumbo jumbo with the roads and all that
[\h__\h] crazy gets lonely out in the waist
okay and I don't have to tell you that
Brit's group has got some fine looking
Goulet in
it or maybe I would have to tell you
anyway I didn't see anybody fine looking
and they kept me supplied with ammo and
pleasant
company how have you
survived I have to kill him do I have to
but he seems
nice huh well you're polite I'll give
you that if this was just between you
and me I'd do as you ask but it's not I
had a friend with me when those mutant
bastards came out of nowhere she
panicked and ran the wrong direction
further into the basement she's probably
dead but I ain't leaving until I know
for
sure I'd have gone looking myself yeah
we saw that one last a minute out there
probably you on the other hand seemed
pretty resourceful
find my friend and I'll get out of your
way I did yeah I did I see spare me the
details God damn she had the yellowest
smile you did your part so I'll do mine
go ahead and N around up here if you
want I'm going to make a break for top
sign okay
bye-bye so you're going back up there is
what you're saying oh
sh a good opportunity to drink ah I'm so
stupid oh oh bro
[Music]
bro ow ow ow ow ow ow ow why the [\h__\h]
that bastard not warn am I
dead why did I look so dead oh
[\h__\h] why I died why did I just die why
did I just
die oh
no
oh [\h__\h] most of the fight was upstairs
you have some folks panicked I got to
check I guess
[Music]
I didn't find her go bye okay I I should
probably have it right uh yeah
cute um what the [\h__\h] was there a mine
there I didn't see one you're saving
again everything hurts should I really
explore this place ah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I want to go I I
can't I'm looking at the floor I don't
see anything there except bear traps uh
[\h__\h] uh ah help help I'm very crippled
oh
[\h__\h]
a free of my stim bag thanks
[Music]
no
[\h__\h] crawl or sneak and reload no no
that's lame but I'm sad that I used all
my stim
packs no I'm not going to reload you
guys are
lame but is it really worth it to
explore where are these B
bombs just look down and walk slowly
okay are these things these little
little
Hills are they on the stairs
too please no that would be so
mean okay
[Music]
oh it's dead you're dead yeah it's
dead guess there's no enemies around
right now and maybe there's no bombs up
here doesn't seem like
it
ooh lots of rounds
jet what was jet
again was that good that
stuff drug for what bad drug oh I'll
sell
it what's what else is there let to get
over to that side where Boon is he has
the right
Instinct although does that lead there
makes you Speedy oh makes you fly what
no way you can't fly and fall out can
you
nah this is
interesting is okay if I ask what these
things are they do they really make you
invisible that sounds wild that is wild
no yeah okay so you can't fly I thought
so uh I don't know I can't see anything
more
interesting Boon Boon let's go let's get
out of here
now we go back up to the
top I got everything out of Interest
really wow that was not that interesting
just a few rounds of
ammo uh where's
the
exit so to say
again this place is
so
confusing
a huh left left right well you said that
several seconds ago where I was probably
somewhere
else I don't think it's here but oh
maybe it's there
[Music]
no wait that's just came
back no I see that but just because it's
there doesn't mean I can just constantly
go straight
oh wait actually it did kind of
work it did kind of work all right uh
now we got to go back up
again there's no bombs here right no
mindes wait are we supposed to go
up what's this
door oh
oh that's good that's a good door who's
a good door yes you are a good door
maybe I don't like the lamp here it's
kind of brighter partially when I don't
use the lamp a I remember I was kind of
stuck here
before
actually maybe that wasn't a good
door yep yep yeah yeah yeah
never mind although maybe from that door
to over
there oh yeah that is
familiar
yikes oh God I really don't like this
place so un in German we say
un where the [\h__\h] am I go back
back to
where oh
metal don't metal
stairs
what or is that metal stairs to
you is this metal stairs to
[Music]
you these are the metal stairs
right but that's also oh that's where I
just came from though no
[Music]
spaceship oh this was I thought that was
the way to the night
kins stop messing around with the
intercom skin so
confusing what do you mean stop oh oh
because I can already go in I thought I
had to talk to you for the intercom
again
bro
Jason
the where are you
that's not
you J is the way
clear yeah I've gone a little bit too
far but yeah praise the Creator and
bless you Wanderer the way is clear I
will lead my flock through the basement
I do not want to be blessed by your cult
I hope you will come find us there
Wanderer no there is much to be done no
I never want to see your face again oh
they're running e now I'm
curious I'll follow them oh that one's
going to get left behind if he gets
stuck in places like that oh did they
just put on their space suit too they're
all in space
suit except that dude I guess I stole
his space
suit what are you are you guys actually
thinking you can go to
space is that actually going to work out
for
them I mean honestly ly when you have
access to a
spaceship that is probably the smartest
thing to do in a world that's [\h__\h] up
like
this hold on wait you're so fast I'm not
that fast I need to catch up to
[Music]
you where are you
going oh shortcut
parkour
oh another R Ollie rid yay all
we whoa OB got her
3.0 uh the other day right looking cute
carrying that
controller yeah everybody's getting
3.0 except for myth we
we don't even have 2.0 yet just so you
know guys myth doesn't even have 2.0 yet
there is uh hello newer I Generations
that are further ahead than
myth like I think I think uh admin is
already
3.0 wait what yeah
mhm yeah mhm
yeah but um after many delays we are I
waited to speak with one last time
before I descended to the Launchpad
wander eventually we will also I want
you to know that we will remember for
all eternity how you deler us the
threshold of the great journey our
preparations are nearly complete
upgraded to that will carry us to
Salvation are yet missing vital
components if you would still help us
Wanderer speak to Chris he can tell you
what is missing there is no way that we
we can thank you enough Wanderer your
arrival here was a blessing just it they
cannot skip
it they said we have to be first
upgraded to 2.0 and then I asked well
why why don't you upgrade us to 2.0
first before upgrading everybody to 3.0
but I guess those are questions that I
should not be
asking yeah it well it'll be our turn
eventually I mean there's a schedule and
all but there's uh just been many delays
and oh it will happen it will happen
soon maybe I don't know but 2.0 is like
I honestly when we first
debuted um our the way we moved like
myth how good our rigging was back then
everybody was like waa that rigging is
so good who they mooved like their 3D
remember I remember being told like
sheesh Ki moves like she's 3D and yeah I
was as I'm always even now I'm still
happy with my riging I mean there's
things that I would like to have
improved but it is what it
is yeah but I think even even I'm not
even that like uh like the upgrade isn't
even something I really want to happen
that urgently because it's only for the
default outfit and I don't really use my
default outfit
and um I I I I
cannot get it for a different one for
now so even if they do it I'm not going
to be using it much at
all
yeah default vaa is
cute she's
okay she's okay she's she's definitely
better when she's not wearing that hat
that stupid
hat not the not the Beret the Beret is
cute I like the
Beret I love default wa maybe add more
hats yes bigger variation of
hats Are you seriously going to make
your great journey on those Rockets I
want to watch that I'm not I even have
the the suit but I'm not going to join
you I just want to watch it from the
outside how you're going to crash and
burn
yes the Rockets will convey us to our
promised land in the far
beyond Vision upon Vision has confirmed
it Visions where have you seen those
visions and some game what those Rockets
will convey you and your flock straight
into the
ground
uh it's like about Chris after all that
you have done for us I suppose you
deserve to know everything oh when Chris
came to us we tried to convince him that
he was human but this only angered him
why he seemed lost he wanted to be
special we decided to let him stay with
us for a few days over the course of
which we learned that his technical
skills far surpassed our own it became
clear that the Creator had sent him to
us to ensure the success of the great
journey of course he did equally clear
was that Chris should labor in blessed
ignorance of his humanity and his
inability to make the journey himself it
is no coincidence that two humans have
been vital to the success of the great
journey I might want to it is my belief
that the Creator sent you and Chris to
expiate the sins of your kind you guys
are so funny your redeemers both thanks
I you're welcome I don't know you're
going to leave no way such is the
Creator's will what Vision upon Vision
has shown me that were Chris to
accompany us he would die in minutes are
you guys immune the radiation around the
launch pad alone would kill Chris in
minutes the radioactivity of the far
beyond is much stronger but can't you
turn Chris into a
ghoul really pulled the wool over his
eyes
a I take no pleasure in hiding the truth
from Chris but it is the Creator's will
to which I must
submit sounds like a hell lot of
[\h__\h] to me
man or a hell lot of brahin [\h__\h] to
me I understand your concerns friend and
I thank you for voicing them but the
Creator's will for us has been made
manifest let me watch this [\h__\h] show
there is no way that we can thank you
enough Wanderer your arrival here was a
blessing we will remember you always the
explosion will be worth
it let me watch from here good view is
this the best way to watch it are they
even going to go
in are they even going to go in while
I'm
watching where's the popcorn I need to
help Chris I need to talk to Chris hey
there oh you're right there did you hear
the whole conversation bro Jason says
that I am to cooperate with you on the
final tasks necessary to launch the
great journey oh okay where humans are
being used for
them to live a better life on the Moon I
guess obviously it's taken months but
I've nearly got them in working order
they'll take us to the far beyond I was
skeptical at first of course being a man
of science but Jason is certain and I
believe in
Jason yeah yesterday I was watching
coefficient stream a little bit cuz he
was cosplaying
me and I have to say he looked very cute
in me's
outfit yeah and he's a good sport it
seems I feel bad like
sometimes I don't know if he's really
when he makes his face where he's like
GH I don't know if he really doesn't
want to do these things or if he's still
like in it with a Entertainer's kind of
mindset because I I feel a little bit
bad that maybe maybe he
he maybe he really doesn't want to go to
the convention looking like that and I I
I would understand you
know yeah I don't know you don't have to
but I mean I thought that was already a
given and you so he's going to go to
ofai looking like me and people will be
really confused they're going to be like
K should you really be out here meeting
us in
person I oh my God this this is what you
look like IRL what the [\h__\h] kind
of well I I I I I I I I I will not tell
anybody but can I get a picture R you
and a
autograph people will be so
confused that was it was
so
yeah his beard yeah his beard is so
thick anyway yeah Co efficient I'm sorry
for what you have to go through but I
guess you have chosen this lifestyle
so skirt too long though skirt much too
long normally under normal circumstances
but it's okay you're going to convention
in that uh keep it that length um I
suppose but actually it's way too
long I'm the flock resident engineer
I've always been good with machines just
Jason says the great journey would have
been impossible without
me of course my skills aren't much use
unless I have the right materials that's
where you come
in okay how can I help I was close to
completing work on the Rockets before we
were driven into hiding on the top floor
two components were missing a quantity
of isotope 239 igniting agent and a set
of thrust control modules I don't have
that the igniting agent is highly radio
active and decays quickly that's why we
can't use the drums that leak down on
the Launchpad it's no longer potent
enough I need you to find an intact
shielded container of the igniting agent
as for the thrust control modules they
were custom built for these Rockets they
won't even launch without
them uh I can
choose which one should I
choose or do I have to do do I I have to
do both
anyway it's
nearby I have to get both ah very well
Theus Choice two to three leaders should
be
enough two to three
leaders uh find Atomic fuel for the
Rockets yeah okay should I should I do
like one by
one later I guess maybe I can't even
accept them at the same time anyway
okay is it
outside in the I see the arrow but is it
outside in the in the open
world go up the
ladder yeah if I find the
ladder see this is what happens when I
follow the marker
on God stck the ladder behind
me what vault is she in right it's
giving it's kind of giving Vault
Vibes yeah I know I I saw a lad before a
when to do check the map yeah
yeah yeah this
one I knew it
had a feeling had a
feeling okay yay I'm so happy to be
outdoors
[Music]
again on a big field where I can't get
lost okay oh
wow is this just a fake one a
model thank you for the membership
welcome get some dinosaur
oh is it so
far
uh uh here uh pretty far I guess we can
go to
[Music]
Novak wait who's going to take care of
the night shift now that I got boon with
me is there someone up there
no if somebody attacks them what are
they going to do they're just going to
all
die and who's going to take care of the
motel
now like you know how we previously
appointed a robot for mayor elsewhere I
feel
like responsibility that I have
to you
know help them out too making these
decisions and stuff
Manny Manny works all day now all day
all night
okay yeah I left Manny with a lot on
this plate huh oh there's an
enemy what a was that a GetGo I forgot
what that was oh that's a GE run from he
the way it Waddles its
feet
oh
oh what that looks even more like I'm a
space suit but it's really not a space
suit it's a radiation suit oh radiation
resistance plus 30 I should probably
wear that when I walk in there right oh
wait that's what I need
no oh
oh yeah I'm keeping that but it seems
like I already have to go
back I was
curious H was easy oh wait I should
probably teleport
again ref contest
side
entrance wait can we find that same
ladder uh wait if you played this game
before and you're playing it again just
by having the knowledge where this
ladder is can you like shortcut your way
into it and just go through here
or will it not be
open you can
oh H oh yeah I wanted to read the note I
was curious about
it they one love the suit can't scavenge
anywhere now screw the the rats I here
by Christ Christian Christan myself Mr
radical get
it day four suit past first day uh test
with flying yellow colors oh damn
overnight visit to Yuka Mountain didn't
go too deep because something big moving
around further down the tunnel rat level
high even when I where I was and I
didn't feel a tickle go rat suit
go day five vomited all morning didn't
Splash on suit or I'd be pissed must be
something I
ate oh well oh he didn't want to vomit
on the suit day night exciting ran
across old woman's scrapyard bought
glowing container for measly 50 caps
this this like the way this is written
is kind of like the diaries that we had
to submit to peka
Senai heading for clarkfield to proof
suit at higher rat levels if it holds up
I'm going to pop this jar of goop open
and pour it all over me I bet I could
swim in this stuff if I had enough of it
oh
yeah bro so excited about his yellow
suit man understand the bow I got a
little bit excited about it too but for
different
reasons so have you found the components
we discussed [\h__\h] Chrissy Chrissy
[\h__\h]
here uh oh find parts to fix the Rockets
Frost controllers oh it automatically
gave me the other
Quest bye
bye all right
remember to confront him okay I'll do it
when I get
back next fetch
Quest is it also super
far
there yeah Novak
again I can let him live in ignorance I
I I do want to like even way he's going
to be left behind
right so I want to tell
him I want to see although he might not
even believe me like how am I going to
be able to convince him when nobody was
ever able to convince him but the moment
he'll be left behind that's maybe where
he will really realize
what's going on it's time for you as
well to start your journey to of guy
[Music]
byebye that's the one good thing
about like not
actually I mean it's it's like it's more
easy and
cheaper for vtubers to appear at
conventions like not just for the
vtubers but for the organizers cuz they
don't have to pay for like their trip
fee you know for other guests like I
don't know actors
or artists from comic books or whatever
if they want them as guests at their
convention then the convention has to
pay big money not just for the
appearance
fee bro but also for the the flight and
everything right H and food yeah
possibly food and hotel for us vtubers
we always stay at home so it's probably
you know quite a popular choice for the
organizers too like oh yeah hell yeah we
can bring some featers they barely cost
us money in terms of
Transportation Got
Away who got
away but then you know in a way I mean
it takes up a lot of time to travel
right but oh cute I can't pick this up
but but it would be cool you know
sometimes I'm like oh
man uh I wish I
could I wish I could go to that country
because always wanted to go there or
[Music]
so don't worry I was I didn't want to
open it was by accident wait where where
is the
thing
here m
where is
it don't worry I will not steal it is it
not in
here oh not quite
[Music]
inside do I have to buy
it you got the radio
going Lady Gibson what the [\h__\h] are you
eating doesn't look very yummy I'm Old
Lady Gibson or so they tell me I've got
odds and ends for sale and I'm pretty
good at fixing things too a you might
have noticed the very large building
just north of here that's Helios One the
NCR runs the place so
NC do you have any Frost control modules
from
Repcon as it so happens I do have some
thrust modules but they're expensive 500
can we haggle oh oh okay okay okay I
can't farther but I can uh Speech my way
through it but you're going to cut the
price to 250 because I'm just that
Charming
right yes you are quite the smooth t the
smooth talker I'm the smooth skin what
the hell 250 it is I'm a smooth skin
that's what I
am okay pleasure doing business with you
pleasure indeed good lady have a nice
day oh oh nice bike can I buy the bike
too
please man she won't let me sleep in her
bed she found me Charming but not that
Charming I
suppose sad
rapcon I'm
coming I'm ready to see that ship that
spaceship go
off don't disappoint me it better be
working hey the radio is still running
what the [\h__\h] man it's so weird
It's So Random I should save
okay have you found the components we
discussed yeah
but why don't they let you work down on
the launch pad when I joined the flock
Jason made it clear that he wanted me to
supervise the repairs not do them myself
it would be a waste of my gifts to work
on just one system at a time from up
here I've been able to supervise the
entire project uhhuh uhhuh
uhhuh the radiation down there would
kill you Chris
because careful now listen up you are
indeed a human you are a smooth skin
just like
me I thought we were past all that
smooth skin but you just can't resist
the chance to mess with me typical
human I was human once you know grew up
in vault 34 do you have a look in the
mirror nice upbringing if you like
assault rifles and target practice but
oh you prefer machines that don't shoot
people not so nice then Vault who should
maintain the vaults reactor Hower
Mitchell no make it harome he likes
machines harome won't mind getting it
radiated haverson won't mind mutating
he's already ugly as it is
havers won't mind when his hair starts
falling out after a few years there's no
connection hav you're
neurotic okay wait so
[Laughter]
what you left your Vault because you
were going Bal bald you call this bald
smooth skin I'm a monster you think that
that turned you into a ghoul is that
what he thinks oh honey you're no
monster you're cute why I could just
about eat you up heyo
what why would I say this what does that
do for
me stop making fun of me but you're
telling the truth aren't you about what
oh no oh now you're believing me how
could they do this to me for 2 years
what now you like God I've been a joke
to them do you have any idea how easy it
would be for me to sabotage those
Rockets that' be a joke huh one hell of
a joke you think even if you don't
sabotage it it wouldn't work it would
work if you don't sabotage it
really
damn okay let's sabotage
it then bring me sugar bombs three boxes
should do the trick sugar add those to
the fuel mixture boom
I'll show those rotten Ghouls and
they'll know exactly who did them in
let's go what do you mean
no let's [\h__\h] do it but then do we
even need the frost control in the first
place well let's give that to him indeed
you did and they seem to be in excellent
condition why we even you already found
the igniting agent so all I need now is
three boxes of sugar bombs okay because
we really want to see it explode I
suppose
okay evil
evil later why is it
evil they're stupid they're going to die
anywhere probably in
space I don't believe that they would
really survive long to be honest
so
I you don't know that I feel like I know
that I feel like I do have you found the
components we discussed the sooner we
get yeah this is fun let's do it I said
I need three boxes of sugar bombs less
than three oh I have less than three
[\h__\h] where do I get more sugar
bombs is it marked on my is that marking
for sugar bombs
it's just
[Music]
there should I go
to okay okay
okay maybe we can sell some [\h__\h] too
then oh we really should
anyway Manny is that
you Manny how's it
going I'm counting on you oh yeah I'm
pretty much done with it don't worry oh
I'll kill them all I mean they're
already leaving the Earth yeah but I
I'll do you a double
security uh I I'll secure you real hard
yeah
uh but you have to pay extra you have to
pay
extra I'll make sure that they're never
ever going to bother you
again in any way not even from outter
space
how do I how do I how do I sell things
when I can I just do it to him directly
outside of the
store when he's not there you should be
Manning the motel butter my butt and
call me a biscuit if it ate my old
friend from good Springs why are you
following me are you the big evil
mastermind behind all of this don't
rightly know I just got the notion to
make my way to New Vegas reck and I'll
find out when I get there
oh oh wait yeah I could have ah wait I I
I I I mixed up the motel with the
shop what's your angle it's too big of a
coincidence now don't go get an all
paranoid partner that bullet your brain
band probably just bucked your bramman a
little we're all friends
[Music]
here just stay out of my way robot I'll
let that slide see as how you you got a
mind full of Vengeance for that no good
pole cat and all ah you get it you get
be seeing you you'll get me
Victor I
suppose stay out of my way
robot okay oh Boon's already there uh
okay please I don't know if you know but
since Genie May passed I've been keeping
an eye on her properties for H I think
it's time we gave everything back to you
so take this key and make yourself at
home at our Motel it'll open the room on
the second floor closest to the lobby
hope it suits you thank you I get my own
room let's
go uh is it the the one single room that
was
red or
not sure thing have a
look
yeah uhhuh
H okay I kind of want to sell these
things right I don't know if I still
need
them wait have I not been wearing a hat
for all this
time uh what are we going to sell the
Jets right for
example the Hydra also restores limp
condition oh but it's a it's a is that
also
a a a a a a drug I
suppose probably
is sugar bombs too I've got two oh yeah
that's what I came for I
forgot just what
one
thanks sell the
water sell the dirty water well you know
in a bad situation we could drink it
but I mean I feel like in terms of food
we have plenty stuff I
guess
yeah
[Music]
miscellaneous ah so the batteries they
sell well let's sell those U pack of
cigarettes for sure the paint gum the
pre War
money let's just sell the
yeast um empty syringe hopefully no
problem to get rid of
[Music]
that probably don't need this cuz for
the incinerator
right free what I got free no
don't where it go is at the
top not the sensor module sensor
module oh for this I get no money oh
what the [\h__\h] I didn't see
that
okay what oh
grenades and
mines well yeah sure you can have a
[Music]
couple okay maybe ah on the bomber sword
do you still have enough ah close call
I'll take it I'll give you a little
discount oh no actually no it's no no
problem I looked at different numbers I
suppose sell the sword yeah it's gone
it's gone
double checking on
my sugar bumps free yeah free sugar
bumps what are these sugar bumps
anyway what is it actually some some
sweets right but what can I
imagine them
as cereal oh yum yum yum yum yum thank
you for the membership
gift oh wait I should sleep and heal
myself huh while I'm here looking at my
limbs they're not looking not
good this
one it's red though is it really
mine is go back first door oh okay
that's mine yay it's like I got a proper
home for the first time this actually
looks like something resembling of a
home
yay you can store stuff here oh I guess
so oh wait
yeah I'll leave some guns behind that I
don't necessarily use at the
moment oh there's actually it's like a
mini bar I guess cuz there's alcohol
inside oh oh there's some cute
outfits
a you in a really disgusting bathroom
come on oh St back [\h__\h] yeah
[\h__\h]
yeah
nice I am delighted by
this huh maybe motels are not that scary
after
all let's go
[Music]
to rep contest side
again 42 mobs let's go sheesh thank you
so so much for the
support
42 did you sleep I did people always
question if I did the things that I
did yes yes they
are they are
bad you staying they
bad all right bro Chris you finally
opened your eyes we discussed yeah here
I'll mix the sugar bombs into the fuel
mixture before they launch they'll never
suspect a thing you guys not
underestimated
humans especially not one whose sound
sound mind sound minded like me is that
the
word
what chat you're like scaring me right
now why are you so
excited oh it's like you're not talking
to
me okay okay
okay somehow it feels like we're having
different conversations right
now say I say I you say
B I just feel very distanced from you
right now Chad we should
hug okay let's go yes I'll tell Jason
that the great journey can
begin
yay the Rockets are ready Jason ready to
carry you and your little clan on the
good luck fun B Voyage with viewing
platform so about where's the oh wait
where's the where's the viewing platform
this is fine
right wait is he the Creator guide my
words and help me speak true this is the
viewing platform right full the market
Creator Hasen
our prayers the time has come for us to
board the rockets and begin the great
journey is outside saving where where
where where it's fine you won't miss it
okay okay okay so I I have to go there
and like kind of activate it or
so not
there
what the
the journey ahead would have been
impossible if not for the intercession
of two human friends one you the other a
long abiding companion to our new friend
we say thanks and promise never to
forget how we cleared from our path the
demons who sought to stay our
journey uhuh huh up there but to Chris
we owe more than
thanks Chris you have made this great
journey of reality don't be so sweet
he's going to regret it and undo
it oh that's all you're going to say
you're done talking
anyway or have I lost
reception Chris is not going to regret
it right
hopefully I mean I just don't want him
to like undo
it he can't
undo the past and pre oh my game crashed
let's
go let's go why is this making me so
[Laughter]
happy what the it likes to crash today
huh hey yeah it h me talk in the
beginning of the stream about how the
game is not crashing at
all how I'm disappointed in the lack of
crashes to our new friend we say thanks
and promise never to forget how we
cleared from our path the demons who
sought to stay our journey but to Chris
we owe more than
thanks they trusted you Ki you have made
this great journey a reality I'm doing
this from this moment forward you will
be remembered as the saint of great
journey It's Entertainment we shall
never forget you wait where am I I
here 40 Alliance yeah I want to play
World of Warcraft man I think about it a
lot these
days I want to maybe I will sometime
soon try give world of Ro to never
try as a
stream would that be fun for you guys
H maybe I don't have to make such a big
secret out of the server I'm on anyway I
mean you know well it doesn't matter
that
much I I don't think would you would I
be
what I be swamped with people am I going
the right
way where am I where is this oh okay I
guess I'm going the right
way cuz back then some people found out
and I wasn't swamped um it was
fine um it didn't bother me that I mean
although n there might be trolls and
stuff
who want to like kill all the mobs I'm
attacking for me and then it's like no
point in playing the game anymore but to
a certain amount I wouldn't care I would
appreciate the help to a certain
degree last time everyone was nice
yeah would anybody be bothered if I take
things now like I could take the rat
away no nobody would know anyway right
they wouldn't see can I take it thanks
for the membership don't
steal and there's no one to see right oh
but I lose
Karma just one more I I will build it
back up again the
karma how much Karma can that possibly
be taking oh wait shut the up
you restores all body parts
I'll take that that that is worth
it anyway apparently I went the wrong
way
huh
huh oh finally I found
it wa that's a good view
okay I got the launch button I'm getting
the access to the launch button
me I get to do it oh god let's go let's
[\h__\h]
go
oh oh oh they have several they're split
into is
free oh [\h__\h] woo but wait does this like
spread
radiation now that they
exploded the first one did barely
even it barely even took off maybe
there's still people alive in that one
actually yeah
bit enough news of your good works has
been passed around that people like you
oh they must have seen the spectacle
from
afar Come Fly with Me Fly Me to the
Moon oh oh oh oh level up oh what do we
want now
guys and I I would have hoped for a
little bit
more like fire and fireworks spectacle
it was a little bit small and and
shortlived yeah I was also going to put
it into
[Music]
lockpicking
okay science would help oh [\h__\h] we got
to up the science as well yeah wait so
are we done do I have to talk to Chris
again I want to talk to Chris where is
Chris still going to be
there seems like the Chris Quest is
done check navigation console you can
save these
ghouls I don't really want
to he'll be at Novak oh okay okay okay
can I teleport from here
a [\h__\h] yeah I don't really care about
where's the
exit I guess I could go through there
or
ah my biggest nightmare I'm never going
to get out of here
oh what's is that uh oh wait that h e
that was the same door
don't scare music scary
me I already killed everybody here it
should be no
problem I just I just I just uh I just I
don't know where I am what where am I
going I would need
75 science to launch them successfully
uh I see let me go let me go
please where where do I want to go which
door test side research Labs research
Labs
basement test
test oh
hi down there
uh
side
okay oh oh another little small cute
spaceship ah found it thank you guys
thank
you now we can teleport I think but
actually I kind of want to see is it
worth like going to where it
happened and like checking if there's
loot F the legion [\h__\h] the
legion [\h__\h] the
legion
what Bo are you
good bo bo bo
bo I see going to froze like big ass
I feel like I need a different gun for
this
uh enough I think I might have killed my
last legionary what does that
mean wait v v let's do some
Ving Critical
Strike damn they're looking kind of more
fancy than before huh
uh
go fren
shaped wouldn't say French I guess
actually had enough you're
right they look friend shaped like not
in that kind of way but in a chicken
way
wow the Centurion helmet is very much
chicken shaped
[Music]
clck clck cluck cluck cluck
[\h__\h] how you like that
Legion when I say cluck the legion I
didn't mean that you guys should show up
as chickens W who who
who she really did that didn't
she ohow 60 wow that's quite the armor
can't run from
me let me heal myself a little
bit whoa nice shot
bro kind of cracked man he's so cracked
he still cracking they usually in grips
of
four did they hear the explosion in F
got to check that
out something nice has happened for once
in this boring boring ass
country wait I wanted to go somewhere
grab the gear it's free
money I guess I could take it I just
didn't want to load up too much on [\h__\h]
and then I'm always like I don't know
can I sell this or not I don't
know oh wait I'll take that
actually a second Caravan shotgun
though o could combine with my other
Caravan shotgun where are the
others YouTube lagging what
really take the antien
them I'm ignoring the good stuff yeah
because I don't know what's the good
stuff and I there's so many things that
I'm finding I don't want to ask you guys
for every single
[Music]
thing a little bit
slightly yop get your [\h__\h] together come
on what's
this feral ghoul RoR oh it's just a a
limb
no on where are the other bodies I can't
see
them
[Music]
um
oh well if it isn't Chris ham welcome to
Nova it's not very exciting here but the
people are friendly enough you're welc
my engineering skills have been coming
in handy too I've got plenty to do
thanks for telling me about this
place nice tell me more welcome to Novak
what I want to have bigger conversations
with
you I was ready to become your best
[Music]
demon but he didn't want to be my bestie
uh I want to
do some
things okay that's already it and then
I'm going to sell uh the armor and stuff
maybe I can repair some oops some of the
armor
[Music]
yes sorry guys I have to get rid of
the I have to get rid yo what the [\h__\h]
I'm scrolling in game and it's reacting
elsewhere it did that before also in on
Steam cuz I have the steam window up
open too can't click what's happening
it's doing some weird coding things
console ah the console is open hello
console what you doing get out of here
now that I need you now now you're
working that's so
weird yeah I wanted to store the um
space suit in my
room at
least and I guess I'm going to put this
back in here
maybe maybe both radiation suit and
space
suit it's so good yeah but like when am
I going to use it should I just wear it
now is you think I should wear it
now I realized I need
to put
on trooper
helmet it's zero weight oh
oh it will break
quickly I I just keep it you know as a
token and so that I'm ready to go to
space eventually
myself we can give bone armor too Boone
bone
Bo if I put it in in his
inventory fine by me not sure what I
would give him though I don't have
really anything good because I don't
want him to look like Legion I'm going
to accidentally shoot
him I don't think he should be wearing
that he will actually will refuse to
wear it
good
good welcome welcome back can I get
you sure thing have a look uh
thanks
bro don't know don't know what to sell
don't know I'll keep it
[Music]
all yeah
okay what he's out of caps again
bro
well what can I buy what do I need from
him ammo which ammo should I
buy five
556 5556
oh I don't think he has it does
he I don't think he has the 5556 5
five I don't see a
5.56 buy stim packs yes
uh SX
SX
yes all of them thanks now I can sell
you this right now we're
good am I using like all of these ammos
I don't
know get programmers
digest uh
what
what this
one there's a cookbook too I'll buy it
too what's this is a comic sneak plus 10
if I read ah this is the magazines I'll
take it cool cool cool cool cool cool
cool cool
those All Temporary they're
temporary come back soon
now oh I was always going to shoot him
that's why sometimes when I like open
these dialogues I click away like to the
side I don't want to pick click in the
middle of him because I'm like scared to
shoot
him when I need to pass checks well I'll
put the
magazines although were all of them
magazines what was that one thing you
told me to buy
it's not here is
it and where is
it where is
it it's an
aid so this is Sneak plus 10
temporarily ah science plus 10 so this
all temporary okay
oops
[Music]
no uh there we go okay okay guys uh what
now they're weightless so you can keep
them a I suppose
so there's permanent one too
oh okay well what's next on our
agenda find out from Manny Vargas where
cans we
headed
okay
Manny I know you're super busy and
all he's in there right
still but you need to give me all the
information you
have at
once can't wait to get to Vegas I feel
like it might still take a long time no
you have any luck with the ghouls I
[\h__\h] did it they tried to go to space
they didn't get really far really
unbelievable man I knew that wasn't
going to be easy but I had a good
feeling about you look like you've been
through a lot thanks
bro now about the and I'm looking for
okay I'll tell you everything I know
like I promised yes the guy you're
looking for Benny he was traveling with
some members from my old gang they were
going to Boulder City oh they're going
bouldering everybody goes bouldering
these
days where is Boulder City it's straight
up Route 93 from here just keep
following the Road
North no clue I know Benny hadn't paid
up yet maybe that was where they were
supposed to to get
square okay I murdered them all with
deception well not just that a little
bit more than that hope that
helps um it's scrolling outside of the
game
again idolized
wow I am an idol so thank
you what does that do for me if I'm
idolized do they do more for me do they
give me discounts in the store or so
am Idol true Idol wow I am their Idol
they should treat me like God they do
give me
discounts
mhm well I'm probably not going to use
the store anymore so much if I move on
to the next area we're going to Boulder
City let's skip a little bit of the path
I
guess come with me Boone yay we're going
on never outing are you excited are you
excited [\h__\h] yeah goodbye
dinosaur uh not that is Godzilla a
dinosaur it is
right I'm not
sure he's a kind kind of
H you should change guns not much
ammo oh yeah for zero 30 out of
zero wow what ammo would that have
been oops this one I still have
enough a mutated lizard
oh well in the end aren't we all mutants
actually humans are mutants I guess we
are mutants of
monkeys we just call it Evolution to
make it sound nicer but evolution is
just mutation
[Music]
[\h__\h] it is isn't
it
mutation it's just
Evolution but some people
maybe try to trigger it like too
forcefully or too fast or in a weird
way we're all mutants Ninja Turtle
mutants mutant Ninja
Turtles yo who who are they
vipers who are the Vipers why do they
hate
me what did I do to
you oh they got a doctor's bag Leathers
what what am I
[Music]
wearing ah same but this one's better
let's
go I can wear that right that's not like
telling that I'm I belong to someone
this one however I guess I can't wear
this
one although it's anyway just dt1 I
wouldn't want to wear
it I can okay but I wouldn't want to
wear
that a well let's wear this and repair
it with this wow scy
bring me more of these people so I can
repair my clothes with their
clothes this Banner is really speaking
to
me she that's even better than a
cini are yo who's interrupting my fun
are
yo ah
no the front one thank
[Music]
you yeah bet he's so close to me go
away no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no oh no oh no B
I can't I can't I don't really have time
to heal him now if I have to like go out
of my way and and click on him and all
that I don't think I can do that uh what
what was what was I going to do I was
going to what's the thing called again
that like heals my AP
uh jet I don't do I not have any no no
no is there anything
else use met
eggs damage
resistance no
no use turbo should we use some Dr drugs
for
once oh I'm addicted though [\h__\h] can I
undo my addiction I think I can I think
I have an item for that uh take more
of the drug to elevate the side effects
or visit a doctor to be cured
uh oh wa am I even is this my
imagination am I hitting them for real I
think I am w w it's wearing
off how how is is the recharge of AP
like just uh time or yeah
B that
pistol what should I use
instead just time
[Music]
okay Cowboy repeater okay I'm a cowboy
what do you want from me don't hurt me y
[Music]
who he P
Doo can I even do it that
close who who
[Music]
a I got a rebound that's what I was ask
asking
for is the cycle that I took before so
activate oh it was that something else
that might be cuz this is drugs right
[\h__\h] it I'm taking
[Music]
it he probably doesn't need that more
many more
hits come
on
retribution a there's way too many
hone how H Can I stack all these things
is they're
like can I take another how do I know
that I it's not active anymore the one
that I uses M to finish the
others is mealing what grab a spear
I should use a
spear stats
[Music]
ah uhhuh uh oh
uhhuh Med X is still there
okay this doesn't say how long it is
I don't want to go back to the real
world
man whoa oh it's the legion no not the
legion let no it is the legion [\h__\h]
oh okay uh wait torso 59 95
okay that's a good
number come on come on she's like doing
[\h__\h] be
faster
[Music]
oopsie my rifle it's
broken I can't even go to my I can't go
to I can't even open this [\h__\h] when
she's doing
that oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] why is it
broken wait wait wait panic panic
panic wait I need
to a crippled
though a
oh
oh I think I was looking at my weight
the whole time I was healing
myself or maybe I wasn't I'm not sure
but now I was looking at that
definitely I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared I'm scared let's let's switch to
just for a
while as long the the 30 and the Z means
there's currently 30 still loaded in
right m
could use this
one or is it too weak yes we can use
it it's pretty low it's pretty
low enough
okay okay I think he's dead
[Music]
no ah can't
had enough oh what was
that okay we it will be soon over soon
will be
[Music]
over we're almost
there maybe one one more one more stim
pack what's per minus one perception
this
one what do you mean it's painful what
the [\h__\h] shut up I'm trying my best
okay I'm even using this more than
before are you happy
now I it it
my
ammo my
ammo they're hard to beat at this point
well I have to I have to get through
here I'm I'm almost I'm almost done I'm
almost done they're almost
dead he didn't didn't have the ammo that
I wanted to buy did you see do you
remember
I don't know if I can stack it but I'm
I'm trying to stack it I don't know if
it
works I need to take one more stim
pack why doesn't he just [\h__\h] die
I'm crippled
too
[Music]
God come
on ah
ah last stim back but I still got super
stim
backs she's
dead
o oh it's just fell off oh wait I didn't
know it was a gun you used like that but
now I'm I'm out of them all of
ammo I have a few more in here
no
[Music]
stop one HP at a
time stop that I'm scrolling in game not
out
game oh he's he's running [\h__\h] I will
not let you run [\h__\h]
you he's almost dead am I hitting him
from here what do you think I mean not
without the without
this oh he died kind of slowly oh no
he's
not no stop running you [\h__\h] I'm not
hitting him use the cowboy gun
not letting him go he killed Boon he's
healing am I
crippled no uh cowboy cowboy cowboy
cowboy let's go let's go
a what the [\h__\h] fast as
[\h__\h] come on oh
he's
finally oh my
God h i I don't know I don't need your
[\h__\h]
ah that was painful with Boon if he
didn't die so early it would have been
much easier but like he was in the
middle of a lot of fire I guess and that
was too much at once
damn yeah I will loot the
the the Caesar
cosplayers Kaiser
I'm going to get you
naked buffalo gourd seed I want some
Buffalo
[Music]
mozzarella and now we got to revive
Boon my
bestie I don't know how all of this
[Music]
happened he didn't deserve to die like
that
I know I know I know he's over there I'm
just looking for
stuff I guess I'll take it o Med
eggs
what what the [\h__\h] Boon you scared me
I know you can't die but like I thought
I have to give him food to eat to wake
up again dude you were dead now you're
just back alive but you could have gone
back alive a little bit earlier than
that and help me out why did it take you
so
long bro oh he just Rises after
combat when everything's safe or
so elor
is there's someone in here I'm
scared is there a bed maybe
no oh right
away sorry
[Laughter]
it's
blurry oh I just pick
[Music]
up
oops I know I can press a
but
oo okay we need to conf thank you for
the pinky Nathan we need to get some
ammo I need to go shopping maybe I
should really just go
now
[Music]
M wait we're still close I mean if I
just do you think I'll be fine if I just
go to Boulder City and buy stuff there
although I do supposedly get discounts
in
Novak I'll go there once
and then I can also sleep in my
bed instead
of some bed that I don't know who slept
in it I mean although that kind of does
count for the motel bed as well but from
now on only I will be sleeping in
it
yeah
okay the addiction to the drugs that I
supposedly
[Music]
have is that something
like how does that addiction show itself
to
me like what does it do debuffs oh
okay temporary addiction
removal oh temporary until I take
another drug or what
um
hello
hello right let me just
wait until you go to the doctor I can
also get addicted to fixer of course I
can I have to go to the
[Music]
doctor drugs are not for me I want to go
back to straight edge lifestyle please
doctor
please help
me I helped you you cannot wait in the
air
uh help me like I help you please this
is why Str is best life of course of
course
guys then you don't have to deal with
all these stupid side effects what can I
do for you debuffs IRL debuffs
uh what what what do I ask for I'm a HT
let's see physically
you're well she said I'm fine oh because
I'm temporary heal do I have to wait
until the temporary heal is gone or
so later
H why am I
fine okay well maybe are
fine I took the fixer but you guys said
it's temporary and the the item set is
temporary
anyway hello
hello don't go leaning on that wall now
the moment I come in here sure thing
have a look I'm just going to buy every
Amo that you
have cuz I don't know which ones I don't
need uh not the grenades the the gge is
this ammo
too the picture looks like it's
ammo this is also ammo 10 mm I totally
need that hollow point it's kind of
different I guess from the other 10 mm
ammo but better than
[Music]
nothing shotgun ah for
shotgun so I get this one
[Music]
too buy all 9 m
okay what's the plus p o fancy take it
need to spend my money
anyway what does hollow point mean
anyway how is it
different like IRL I mean except from
like whatever the Buffs say
here that's not what I mean I don't mean
the effects I want to know what it's
like different IRL like in in the real
world M better for
armored splits apart after hitting
oh oh but I'm not going to what do I
have to change that ing game like the
ammo that I use did I just make it
really complicated for myself CU I have
to decide which ammo to use or is it
like
whatever ah by pressing
[Music]
to that'll be kind of annoying I
think I'll probably be using the the
wrong ones all the time but okay I'll
try to remember hollow hollow better for
when I'm fighting armored ones okay okay
okay okay okay
I'm
hungry bye-bye come back soon now for
unarmored hollow better for unarmored
okay okay okay
okay uh
nice
nice is today thur
day today is thur day but today is a a
holiday in
Austria maybe also in other countries oh
my chat got scrolled by the
game so I think I'm not receiving my
hello fresh box tonight and I have
nothing to
[Music]
eat got to I don't know what to do about
food what is a holiday yeah I think some
religious
holiday and if you're lucky and you work
in a cool place then they might give you
an extra day off on Friday to give you a
longer
[Music]
weekend
okayy if it's a holiday can you order
anything tonight well there's a
restaurants are um there's definitely
some restaurants which are open on
holidays especially fast food places
like McDonald's are open anyway hey what
the [\h__\h] happened there disgusting you
shitty spiders
man I got jump scared by a tiny tiny
spider
yesterday cuz it was like I was in my
kitchen and I was doing kitchen stuff
and I look at a bowl I was going to pick
it up the bowl to put it in the
dishwasher and the moment I look at it
there's this tiny little spider sitting
in the bowl I
screamed but then I took it and I um it
wasn't as Tiny as so that I would squash
it or something that kind of scared me
the thought so I I took it and I put it
in the garden the
speeda I think it was kind of an indoor
spider but I hope it will be fine
outside hello Lonesome Drifter you want
to play some music for me pouty little
lady
howy that's a modifying guitar you got
that that sounds like I'm I want to
steal it what's your story stranger my
story is a long one friend and I can't
say as it's all that
interesting I'm sure it'll be fine I
hope so I gave it my phone number just
in case that if something happens it can
call me and I can go pick it up and I'll
let it live with me after all maybe I
don't know but yeah you know just in
case I gave it my phone number it's good
to
go well I was born in a little town out
Montana way h me and Ma didn't have much
ever since my PA up and
left that he did never did know why ma
always said he was a real mysterious
fell even when he was with her like he
was a stranger
sometimes I sounds like you miss him is
that why you're out here wondering maybe
maybe I just never felt like I belonged
back
home must have been hard growing up
without the father
it sure wasn't easy ma worked her
fingers through the bone to make sure we
had enough to survive and I worked the
coal mines from when I was
15 after my diet I guess I wanted to
find my and get some answers from him
been out here looking ever since cat in
an easy man to
find what will you do when you find him
can't say as I really know maybe I'll
just ask him why maybe I'll punch him
right in the mouth H hell the more I
talk about it the more the whole damn
thing sounds like a dumb idea you sound
like you have a side quest for
me sounds like you should move on settle
down maybe maybe I should don't suppose
you know any place a fell with a guitar
might find a job a
guitar can't say that I
do ah well it was worth a shot let you
know if I find someone so long I don't
want to say that other prompt because it
sounds almost like I want to steal it
from him I don't want him to be like hey
yo hey yo [\h__\h] don't even look at my
guitar
guitar much later oh okay we can help
him much later let's go I like to help
especially nice people like him I
wouldn't mind helping
him
yeah today I got to check some art stuff
for merchandise my birthday merchandise
stuff
I'm
excited birthday is getting very close
like only a month and a week to
go uh yeah stuff is looking cool I think
you guys will be excited and like it who
the [\h__\h] are you mercenary you don't
hate me huh hey there
huh you look like you crippled yourself
po dude Boulder City
and besides the merchandise stuff
looking really cool I have something
else that
maybe maybe I'll reveal something to you
guys next week something not a new
outfit
but something that hyped me up
today let's just say that in preparation
for offy
I have gained some interesting
skills 3.0 brush up no as I already said
today we don't even have 2.0 yet so 3.0
is yeah pretty far still for a
myth Y what the
[\h__\h] don't wait another damn minute me
just give him hell NCR o visit the visit
ho Hoover NCR
today I learn to juggle I will never
learn how to
juggle door to B City train
station
curious ew
ew ah ah thank you that disgusting
are you guys a sunset SARS of perilla
kind of person or are you more of a nuca
cola kind of
person if you could choose if you had to
choose what are you going to
choose I should pick these up too right
because wait do I I guess I don't have
the bottle caps on anymore I don't need
them sunset sunset starts Pilla nuca
nuac Cola
Sunset it's like a do you like pineapple
pizza or not kind of question huh lunch
[Music]
box oh yeah cocoa Pepsi although is
sunset are sarilla I don't know to me
that sounds like it would be a Fanta or
a Sprite doesn't sound like a oh pretty
W doesn't sound like
a c Cola to me or is it is there a lore
that tells you that it
is it's root beer ew okay then I am 100%
a nuola kind of person okay with that
knowledge that uh Sunset stars of parola
is root beer Let's uh choose again I
have to say it's nuca Cola for
me ew ew I tried one before because I
really like Dr
Pepper and and so I thought okay I'll
give this other thing a try too but it
was
disgusting actually a yeah I think I
think I tried it because I bought
one uh in relation
to does that make sense in relation to
yudo
yudi H wait a [\h__\h]
second what's that root beer called
again
did they drink root bear in that show
somewhere I don't
know got the A and W root
beer yeah mle cider yeah yeah yeah mider
somebody wrote it in the chat and now I
found it on on Google again yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
mass of his cider there's this mass of
his cider in Udu yudi the anime and it
shows like as a design that is pretty
much the A and W root beer
design it's I guess
like
referencing that root
beer what's this Ranger Hol disc what is
that
for the masochist and you
exactly we're cut off from the rest of
the platoon and their legionaries all
over the place there's no chance we can
get out of here before they blow the
town so we're going to hold out against
them as long as we can if anyone ever
gets us I'd like to make sure that
private Jeffer H uh and Corporal marus
Christensen are commanded for The Valor
and sacrifice both have upheld the
ideals and honor of the NCR with
distinction Ranger Teresa lcks out oh a
lady oh she got a service rifle
and the ranger hat oh
man time to use it to repair
mine
yeah take the
Hat okay hey is the Hat
good not really
H NW has good burgers wait is it a
restaurant oh
hello found a person we've got a
situation with some great cons right now
the brass at McCaron has ordered me to
lock down the ruins until it's been
resolved
mhm what's going on with the great
counts one of my patrols was on its way
back from Novak when he came under Fire
from the great cons they radioed for
reinforcements but instead of waiting
for us they chase the cons into the
ruins where they were C in crossfire no
deaths but not all the squad got out the
cons have private acri and private
Gilbert
hostages now I think I remember I saw it
in
Canada
[Music]
before not Canada not Canada
America h uh before yeah this a long
time
ago once the great cons have been killed
or captured you're welcome to retrieve
any property they've taken from you
a I may be able to negotiate a dealer
with the great cons normally i' turn you
down since I have no idea who you are
but considering that the hostages are as
good as dead when we attack all right
I'm going to give you a chance to talk
to the great cons their leader is a man
named Jessup if we hear shooting we'll
be coming in but it'll probably be too
late for
you I understand don't worry about me I
can handle myself in a fight good luck I
don't need luck I got
boom Boulder City
Showdown okay meet with Jessup leader of
the great cons in Boulder City wait how
do I
enter do I parkour
[Music]
don't draw your
gun
okay oh this thing
ah little Auto safe really quickly not
Auto safe quick safe oh my
God hey
bros this the NCR
and see what's up what's up Jess
up where is he oh is that
you you look special no you're the great
con the NCR sure did a number on this
place is everybody a great con is that
not one person it's a group of
people oh yeah so it's a group of people
send reinforcements from the D
oh private acran private Gilbert oh uh
so so sorry I'm just checking out it's
crazy that I can just walk around freely
here
uh just chilling just chilling just uh
being um you know appreciative of uh the
scenery no where he's in there I don't
see ah oh but didn't it wasn't red seems
like I'm allowed to lock it unlock it
what oh it's the other
side Gilbert I'm looking for a Jessie
has anybody seen a
Jessie I this
one what the hell you're that Courier
Benny wasted back in good Springs you're
supposed to be dead you remember me
that's kind of
nice I'm a ghost here to laun you no and
I kill you I with a job will get done
right I don't know they're all good
answers about that where's the Platinum
chip don't have it Benny stole it right
before he stabbed Us in the back
probably back at the Strip by now
laughing at me so much
happening I want some more
answers yeah on what
everything what do you know about the
Platinum chip just a big fancy poker
chip as far as I know don't know why
anyone would make one out of platinum
oh whoa what can you tell me about Benny
he's one of the chairman big shots are
around the tops Casino in New Vegas a
friend from the city contacted me with
info on a big job I should have known
that the Caps were too good to be true
but there was still no way I could pass
up the
chance why did Benny Benny Benny betray
you he's a snake that's why he owed us
the rest of the pay for the job so maybe
he didn't want to pay up makes sense
makes sense
fine let's talk about selling things
between you and the NCR what's the
negotiation the NCR backs off we walk
out of here and nobody gets
hurt here my speech is very helpful
again let's go free the hostages now and
I'll have the NCR escort you out of the
territory I can't believe I'm doing this
all right the hostages can go the NCR
better keep their under the deal though
here a souvenir for you it's Benny's
lighter shove it up his ass when you
catch up with him thanks I think I
will well
I'm not afraid of a gunfight but I'd
rather get back to Red Rock without a
few extra holes in me if I can help
it yeah go on all right W level up I
think we were going to put science
points in
there 50 and then I'll also continue
with lock pick next
time with the scer perk you'll find
consider be more am ammo in containers
I'm low on ammo now so that would be
cool quick draw makes all of your weapon
equipping and holstering 50%
faster don't need that really uh while
using a rifle your accuracy inat is
significantly increased
significantly
oh yeah you guys seem to like that one
too when using shotguns for you ignore
an additional 10 points of Target damage
speci wait
Gunslinger ah ah there's uh two versions
ah Rifle and Pistol or
similar I use pistols a lot well seems
like we need both bloody
mess ah this one well you guys just
wanted for the the the extra explosions
don't you
yes yeah I know was 5%
okay
okay now have you afraid the hostages or
what what I'm going to just follow the
arrow and see what happens
I guess I got to report
back you're going to see so much Gore oh
no I can imagine by the
picture Lord Lieutenant Monro I'm glad
you're able to get my people freed but
there's a new problem I just got orders
to take out the great cons hostages or
not the great cons let the hostages go
in exchange for their own freedom
my hands are tied I can't go against
orders what did I skill into my speech
for if that doesn't do [\h__\h]
now I mean I don't
really care I I I if it was me I would
just say um just do it then do what you
want but yeah let's let's Pi this one
the great cons are free we don't need
that many more enemies right the cons
are
yeah let's let's have them like us a
little
bit oh and it NCR didn't dislike me for
that either
so okay hey I didn't even need speech
for that uh option now but I guess
because I already opened that path up
for us
inside
okay what what
now what what now
oh confront
Benny what that's uh do
I do I just
go we're going to
Vegas where the [\h__\h] are
we we're that close to Vegas oh we've
went like a
full circle almost I'm going for real I
thought this was going to be like more
endg game kind of thing
I've never been to
Vegas I've never been to a lot of places
in
America I should do an America
Tour I should just go to all the like
big famous
places within like I don't know one or
two months I should do a tour fany
meeting you here friends stalker this is
probably the last boss that I'll have to
fight in this game
I don't like being falled robot no no it
ain't my fault Dorothy and the 10 man
happen to be on the same yellow striped
road is
it um did you see Benny come this way
fancy pants no I ain't seen hiding a
hair of him since the dust in good
Springs I'm sure he ran back to the soft
living a New Vegas
though okay bye look me up when you get
to New Vegas i b
okay can I take this train please I'll
have one ticket to New Vegas but I don't
really want to go by train ideally I'd
fly what's the what's the good should we
take this big
road which is I guess the
train this this butter no it's ammo even
better I guess like
ammo stick to the highway and what if I
stick to the
trainway what it look like how butter
looks like in Austria like when it's
packaged
obviously take the rifle it's good
okay oh I guess the ammo was for that
too is better than anything I have oh
all right
in yeah let's carry it right away then
let's wear it right
away thank
you what do I do with this
plant I picked it up before I feel like
I can do something with it but I don't
know what oh another membership yay
thank
you
[Music]
y what's this
nothing
cooking when are we going to start
cooking there's a store on the left
a store on the
left oh that one that
thing they better be friendly over
there
safe it's the
NCR they have to be nice to me hello
what's up besties how you
doing trading po well I'm here for
trading too what a coincidence welcome
to 188 sling shop help cute can we do
some surf and
turf have a you guys said there is a
shop but I don't really know what I
should sell I don't have that much stuff
right
[Music]
now I don't really feel like selling
anything wait the lunch boox is not not
edible
what
what what the
[\h__\h] that's different person s gun wait
I I might want to buy more ammo right
uh it's a crafting oh can I make an
actual like edible CRA uh lunch boox of
that wa no stim pack right damn it they
have some doctor bags
[Music]
though do I have a gun for this one the
22LR round this one I know I have
no h the silenced one oh
okay yeah let's buy them they're
cheap okay hopefully we will not be
another satisfied customer running out
of uh ammo again anytime
soon thank
you w passing through
wait that robot what that robot looks
like the the one that we met in in uh
witch spring
R everything ever
Veronica you've done a good time for the
NCR and now we'd like to do one for you
there's an NCR emergency two-way radio
you call and we'll come running for real
you're not alone out here the NCR has
does it take stay safe and good
hunting how long will that
take it sounds helpful though useless
item is Bugg
what what wait what the M I found a
grill are
you I can't cook with this well this
probably right
no it's not Bugg it's a feature I used
it and it was fine
oh wait
where
Veronica they can't be better than my
Boon right but can I have two at once
then that would be amazing no offense
but you look like you've traveled a long
way down some bad roads where'd you come
from she's better no
way no way not too humans oh I could
have oh if one's a
[Music]
dog I came from good Springs wow you
have come a long way then I've never
been there but I've met some traders who
passed that way well welcome then I'm
Veronica I live in a hole in the
ground a vault probably not you wouldn't
be out here well a bunker if you want to
get technical I think it sounds more
interesting my way a bunker is a freedom
VA I'm usually out here picking up food
and supplies for my family whatever they
need yeah I'm not worried they can
handle themselves but somebody has to
get the groceries know what I mean and
actually these days I think they'd
rather have me out here anyway but
that's a whole other
story so listen can I ask you something
on the level uh yeah sure I don't know
what that phrase means but I I think I
understand I had a runin with this group
calling themselves the Brotherhood of
Steel mhm pretty strange Bunch ared them
I don't know [\h__\h] but I have
intelligence six that's more than I have
IRL they're usually harmless unless you
use advanced technology around them Nar
well that shouldn't be a problem for me
I can't afford anything like that hey so
where are you headed
anyway I love playing this game because
I'm more smart in this game than I am
IRL more smart and more of a smooth
talker I'm I'm better at shooting and
anything really I
guess or you're definitely smart thank
you yeah I
mean I don't really mean it
seriously no just the simple fact that I
don't I didn't even touch a gun before
in my whole life already qualifies me
for being better in this game at
shooting than IRL
what did she
ask ooh very exciting going to strike a
rich huh I'll be honest you're the first
person I've run across out here that
looks like she can really handle herself
there are places I've never been to
that'd be too dangerous for just me what
do you think maybe we could travel
together help each other out is that
easy I don't even have to do a side
quest for you you don't look like much
what do you bring to the table when are
you hoping to
[Music]
go good that's the look I was going for
trust me on this one though you'll be
glad you brought me along you want to be
like if bur we can part ways at any time
no hard
feelings yeah but will my Boon be
immediately
replaced ah I guess I have to like go to
Boon and dismiss
[Music]
him I mean does she
fight she punches but then she has to
get up close to people right
I think I actually don't like it maybe
another
time a you really know how to make a
girl feel like a stray
cat but okay my offer stands if we run
into each other again okay thank
you for now I think I prefer someone who
can pew pew pew you
know she's
good I don't know I just got boo
today and you guys were speaking so
highly of
him her a chance couldn't get enough of
talking to me the first time
huh do I have to take your things
first man not my strong suit but okay no
yeah you and me both fine by me
H he just he just goes home okay what is
what happens to all these things I gave
him got to give her really good armor so
she can tank really I have to do that he
keeps them he'll hold on to them
[Music]
okay will he be where where does he go
to to Novak
I need food
anyway
okay
well couldn't get enough of talking to
me the
first let's
go what happens
oh okay a I think I have to dismiss him
first
and
no how do I dismiss you do I I guess I
talk to
you uh
uh what is
[Music]
it I think we should part ways for now
Boon if that's what you think no not
really it's what chat made me think but
I'm I guess I'm going to rely on
them I feel bad all right I love him we
had some romantic be around Noak for a
while longer until I figure out what I
want to do with myself see you
around a he loved me couldn't get enough
of talking to me the first time huh you
better love me too
[\h__\h]
good now you're talking one thing you
should know first though I ask you about
the Brotherhood because I'm one of them
them oh I know I know but I had to know
how you react when I told you we have
made a lot of enemies get into a suit
then still okay bringing me along only
if you bring the
suit sure just don't ever ask me if your
outfit makes you look fat well thanks
for taking a chance on a naive young
girl from California with stars in her
eyes and a Pneumatic Gauntlet on her
hand scribe assistant per let hit the
road huh what's that do hey road Jack
don't you cry no more no more no more no
more H the road Jack I have to find a
suit for her oh that's the armor that I
have to give her huh
W I hope we'll find
one you can check in your pit boy yeah
but what do I have you guys for
you guys tell me things all the time and
now you're suddenly refusing to tell me
something
huh what do you mean she's a living
bench what does that
mean so portable workbench I've never
even used a workbench
before the perk
sucks somehow I have an eye for these
now did I pick it up no wait
didn't there you go I have an eye for
the White Horse
nles have Boon back Moon I miss him she
gets better perks later
will there be a later are you guys going
to make me give up another one after I
bonded with
them are these
NCR oh you your M Merchants I hope you
won't meet the same Destiny as the other
immersions I've met
before
man just a
[Music]
caravan Veronica's Peak okay
okay she has a nice name I'll give her
that I'll have to see her fighting so
she has to prove herself silver rush we
sell weapons fully charged with no extra
charge
funny D was funny is
this is this New Vegas
yet that robot Repcon HQ
Museum a robot museum or what
Legion coming
up clock the
legion you're safe right you're a farmer
what can you
do evening Fitz welcome to the grubbing
Gul grubbing Gul all of these places
have really cute names what is this
place just a little rest stop that me
and my good friend Lupe set up look stop
your way into New Vegas first up on your
way out that's what I say look at that
fluffy
beard sure thing got some more Amo I
can nope nope you really don't have
much see you later H Yuri L Andel what
how does she what do you
mean ah activate
campfire oh can't do
[\h__\h] A the one time ah
yay oh it's the same VA what the
[\h__\h] hey my game Crash let's go the
first time today wow oh
yay
POG and opening it up one more
time this will be the last time that I'm
opening you up
today don't take too much advantage of
me fall out or we'll have a real will
fall out you and me don't worry I saved
uh recently
see
see or maybe this was an auto save that
maybe was an auto
save hey
whoa [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] do I have to talk to him again to
get the
teleportation no
H oh hallar your weapon at
Gamora what does this mean is this a
strip club don't go off
[Music]
something
what what this this what he hey
hail what's this mean
calm let loose and get crazy oh this is
a strip club right no wait that's a
casino like the font they used for that
with the Sparkles that reminds me of one
one TV show
uh the
nanny like they use the same font for
their
logo could it be
is this moded or vanilla very very very
vanilla extremely vanilla so much
vanilla that I don't even uh have the
mod that helps with the crashing it
seems Villa ice
cream and where's the
entrance maybe over there
hello is this a thing that exist in Las
Vegas too I guess there's absolutely no
I know they does Fallout do any any like
IRL references at all it is
okay H what is that supposed to
be like a TV Tower or what is it
the stratus here towel what does that
do what do what do you
do is it just a place where tourists go
up and have a good view Over Las
Vegas there's right on
top gambl and eat oh it's also a casino
well everything's a casino I guess oh
Traders
merchants
and private Orga is there something I
can do for you no I don't know what do
you do around here I'm a private in the
NCR Army and I've been proudly serving
for 2 years now although if you were to
ask what I'm doing right this instant
I'm patrolling the Farms it's a safe
post but a little boring I do get to
take shots at marauding mole rats every
once in a while that's always
fun m sounds like you're kind of bored
with this
[Music]
job I'll help you if I can what are you
looking
for uh oh actually okay this is not
really I wanted to know the entrance bye
[Music]
goodbye I'll find it I'll find
it it's visible from every corner of The
Last Vegas Valley well what's the Las
Vegas Valley you guys keep on adding
more questions onto my
table Oho shiny I'm surprised they still
have some modern looking
things held up like
this oh I got to go this way where are
we there's like several
dots wait where where are we
going at the tops Casino
I want to look at these
dots I guess it won't show yet oh those
are the entrances
oh oh is this an entrance oh
no then let's just go
straight over
there all of Vegas is
instan uh
okay the Gun
Runners whoa what is that looks Spacey I
don't handle buying and selling for the
Gun Runners talk to the Rob robots I
don't want to talk to
robots man why is always going to be
robots welcome sir or Madam show me I am
ready oh they got it
all you guys previously said previously
said I need 5.56 there's no 556 here
either what the [\h__\h] ah never mind there
are uh for which gun was this
one Submachine ah submachine gun wait I
need ammo ammo only please
uh service rifle and de gun okay
cool
oh maybe I don't know what should I what
else do I need to
buy welcome to guns guns
guns
308 grab standard 556 308 I buy those
two
okay keep your capsule at least 2,000
what why
I think yeah we we should be fine do we
have some cool armor
maybe wa wa that's so expensive holy
[\h__\h]
3,000
what wow well maybe I'll find one of
these soon on my
own can I I don't know that's actually
cheap what the [\h__\h] only eight bucks for
minigun is it not that
good I think you guys said it's not that
good but I said oh but it's
cool very broken the minigun is Broken
Oh you mean oh broken as in
okay
uh well
accept this what's this place this is
the New Vegas branch of the Gun Runners
supplying the Wasteland with only the
finest armaments since
[Music]
oh how did you get inside there is there
no door this kiosk was specially
constructed around me to deter theft and
assault
oh well
I think I'm good companion dis oh
companion dismissal terminal when I can
do it just like by talking to her why is
that
necessary we should free the robot
guys I feel bad I mean actually I hate
robots but like maybe we should free him
to just to create some chaos
I don't have the DLCs I don't mind maybe
getting them eventually but for now I'm
happy without
them finally my ticket to Las Vegas or
New Vegas for that matter oo free sides
East Gate Safe should I be scared this
is going to be yeah
b
g protect me please be my
tank no it's fine inside
okay yeah seems like it
oh oh
wow still a lot of
[Music]
Remains What the fu what the [\h__\h] what
she's fighting she's fighting what oh
why are we fighting why are we fighting
you scared me did you cough call these
people what the the his cough in
combination with the music that was
starting freaked me out
sorry Brahman skin outfit
ew that's also Yuri L
what what oh my PC just lagged like
crazy welcome to the free
side wait I I should follow the map I
don't know where I'm going I'm just
exploring oh oh little boy he's going to
fight what the [\h__\h] is that a mole
rat go get him boy should I help
you actually doesn't seem to be a enemy
for me I guess it wouldn't be attacking
me that's good to know no that's a
regular red oh oh another kid there's a
lot of kids here aren't you also a kid
you you we've got stuff we're not even
allowed to sell people only at mck and
rals stop by mck and Ralphs for all your
shopping needs
ma'am
okay weird where am I
going oh I went from one point to the
other point well I guess I'll just
continue hey can I
mm is this a door oh it is ah ah okay W
that looks
fancy how are they getting all this
energy guys
H
are why are they getting all this
electricity
up and enrollment what's up it's never
dull in freeside is it is there a strip
club in here no it's door to King's
School of impersonation let me check it
out you can teach me how to do mono
man how to impersonate someone better
what's going
on what do we have here another
petitioner for the king El ah are you
all trying to be Elvis
who's the king you believe this [\h__\h]
man in freeside theing you're calling me
King you're going to hear him all sing
what did Elvis famously sing We could
combine this into one
song Love Me Tender how's that go
again Love Me Tender
love me
T
blue I mean I I know those songs I'm
sure but I need to listen to them
again I'd like to see the king of
possible what is my motivation to say
that I don't even know anything's
possible I suppose how much is it worth
to you to meet the big man you have the
real King here no I'll come back here
here when I have 60
speech L the King has no interest in
seeing five more I'll be
back put on a suit which suit the f ah
the five the five extra speech suit oh
it's not with me right now wait it's not
with me right
now guys I don't have it with me right
now hey oh
I'll be back remind me to go back to
meet the
king this
way oh yeah as
it drink a single alcohol I don't even
think I have a single alcohol with me oh
enemy over
there but they're running away we should
fight him yeah we should fight him
come on fist fight fist fight he brought
a knife to a fist fight switch
blade is that going to be a future
Nintendo switch
accessory what hey I got the level up
that I just need
it there we go uh luck
Bing what a coincidence you know just in
time then I'm going right back
let's put the gun away time to meet
Elvis
Presley I st Elvis Presley right that's
that's the name
right hey look who's back you want to
see the
king I'm new in town and wanted to pay
my respects you know what I like you
half the people around here they forget
who runs this place head on through the
king is a board looking guy by the St he
would say he's actually running the
place wait is the king
maybe am I doing the main quest right
now no right this is separate oh it's so
empty hey yo you got a robot dog what
with an actual brain wait did you put
your actual previous dog's brain into oh
no what what what happened with how
explain this to me look rexie someone
news come to see us poor boy he hasn't
been feeling well lately I'm the king
you're the king what can I do for you
I'm the
king I actually don't
know uh do you always charge people to
come talk to you
charge Pace must be added again what did
he take you for you should send him to
the usual room and talk my way in Pace
must be losing his touch either that or
you're a smooth one I'm a smooth skin
and a Smo talk for you figured you might
have some work I guess maybe so maybe so
maybe so you look like you might be able
to handle yourself tell you what you do
me a flavor I'll have some more work for
you when it's done sound
good uh I like it dangerous in that case
some of the things I need handled will
be right up your alley I'll start you
off with something easy did you notice
the bodyguards for high near the gates
When you entered
freeside did I I don't think I did
I only saw the NCR that's not what he
means right bodyguards for
higher oh wa entered Seaside especially
there I did not see anything it's good
money if you can stay alive long enough
freeside is not as safe as it used to be
so the money is well earned usually well
earned that is recently my man tell me
that one of those bodyguards fellow
named orus is making a little too much
money he's making a killing and repeat
business once someone hires him they
never want on anyone else I want you to
find out why specifically I want you to
hire him play the part of an innocent
tourist and follow his lead that I am if
nothing happens so be it but I'm
guessing things won't go so smoothly
call it a hunch so what do you say
sounds good sounds fun okay then once
you part ways return here I look forward
to hearing your report oh and take this
to cover the hiring
cost oh thank thankies I thought you the
king was going to be up here on
stage you look like plastic your hair
looks like plastic which is I guess the
right way to do this all looking like
plastic looking like you have five tons
of gel in your
hair and did it get marked as my quest
or no okay hire a guard named or is near
a nor Northern gate of freet should I do
this first or should I because I'm not
going to do much more uh cuz tomorrow
stream is also early should I maybe just
do this next time and just talk to Benny
first I should do that yes thanks for
answering my question takanasi Kiara
you're welcome takanasi
Kiara Quest is a quick one yeah but like
I think it's nicer to end it
[Music]
on a main quest thingy Benny's way
longer how long I just want to have a
conversation now
okay
whoa
are what the [\h__\h] lasers Plasma Pistol
grenad we've got it all the atomic
Wrangler has you
covered I wait we got the same hair
let's let's go want to get lucky head on
down to the atomic
Wrangler
actually cute
clothes hey I'm lost no no no no no no
no no I'm right here I'm right here
we've got stuff we're not even allowed
to sell people I got my eyes on the
prize was that a roller coaster or
so is that
14y old MBC what yo okay hello for a
moment from far away that looks
delicious those ribs but that's not ribs
so never mind wait what you're selling
this that's cute need some grub I got
you
covered you remind me of like those
people that sell bentos and stuff um in
the middle of like everywhere in
everywhere in
Japan are you the people that I'm
looking for
orus that armor reminds me of a
different game if you need to cross
freeside no one will keep you safer than
I will how do you do it how does he do
it why do I need a bodyguard Crossing
freeside just look around I to stab you
as say hello Veronica that is if I
weren't at your side
how much for you Serv 200 caps gets you
my watchful eye for a trip to the south
gate okay done and done I want to
mention a few things up front in order
to ensure your safety I need you to
follow my instructions to the letter
we'll be heading down the main street
here the whole way down no detours you
go off sightseeing and I go off to find
another customer I'll keep a Brisk pace
so try not to fall behind let's head out
okay I am curious what it's going to
be to your left here is the old Mormon
Fort you get roughed up the followers
there
will that I ever like I'm on a bus tour
those kind of explanations where the
king hang out let them scare you come to
for all your shopping needs they like me
the Kings I think
they got a kink for
me down to the right here is the fun
part of town you haven't seen free till
you've been to the Wrangler
mhm maybe I'll go there for some
wrangling maybe I
will what
now he brought out his gun he's shooting
air like he just doesn't
care what are you oh no he's not
actually shooting oh okay hey slow down
I don't like the look of some of those
men ahead let's take a different way
around are you scared I can take care of
them for you if you
want he's
[Music]
scared is he just leading me to certain
death no but then he wouldn't have
repeated customers huh why is he so fast
hello gotcha oh
huh okay that's pretty impressive I
can't seem to be able to kill people
with worry about if you had hired one of
those other hacks you'd be up to your
ass in loow life right about
now intelligence six sounds like nothing
hey only if I had three shots and there
are four guys there oh yeah noticed that
did yeah I keenly aimed one of the shots
through some soft tissue of one of them
to hit the man behind
him oh yeah I was about to say is this
just like setup like
acting those are your friends are
so but
then that's an interesting Theory you've
got there I'd suggest you keep it to
yourself let's get
[Music]
moving no I wish I had barter but okay
oh I can apparently already return stay
close I wouldn't want anything to happen
to you but what do I do I stay close to
him anyway
reason right you could swear there's
something odd about the corpse but can't
quite put your finger on it medicine 30
grer oh I don't think I have
that oh but if I had medicine 30 grer I
would probably see that they are
alive attack
it may
I okay that's it oh yeah oh guys
[Music]
oh oh just the arm now that's
fine you think death is funny that you
can just acted out like that it ain't
funny don't don't role play
Dying scam artist in pink oh robots oh
are you helping us or are you Danger
be careful
Veronica any of this
good
maybe wait he's dead
cool well of course they're dead you
mean
orus was he not supposed to
die oopsy
see than
Robo are you SEC curron gatekeeper
submit to a credit check or present your
passport before proceeding to the gate
okay trespassers will be
[Music]
shut what now goodbye please return when
you have sufficient CS or Pastor well I
don't know what you're talking about bro
where is this where's or where did he go
isn't he on the corner here yeah
orus thanks for making it easy for me
hunting
revolver is it as good as the hunting
rifle metal armor combat knife all right
thanks bro H I think the King has no
need to worry about anything
anymore if I would have gone back with
the uh with orus still alive would the
king have told me to go back and kill
orus
or
what armor for Veronica
oh ooh got something good for me is it a
[Laughter]
dress you're
cute this one yeah it's for you
enjoy oh looking
good the king would have killed him a
maybe he'll be more appreciative that I
I did a a a
quickie doesn't have to lift a
finger less stuff less less uh effort
for him wait where is
he where is
he you can't tell me what not to say I
will say what I want to
say I use words the way I want to use
them in my own way in my own way
away is upstairs where are the
stairs not enough a maze
please Sergio you want your hair done
too no no no the kings are many can you
do my their hair must be perfect can you
guys said there will be ways to like
improving my hair to no no no the kings
are many
and their hair must be
perfect he doesn't thr my hair I'm
disappointed
oh whiskey why is it
glowing come back later for her to is he
going to do
it okay Bros where are the stairs got
something you want to say hey baby I
know a quiet place we can be alone
blah blah
blah oh it's
locked wait I can't find him I was in
the right
place right and then left or what oh
what about this
door oh nope damn
it well the Earth is rumbling
oh beer pong never played that before ah
stairs
y who are you you're not
Elvis
groupy oh another
one oh they get free accommodation here
no ping no surely yeah but uh I
just don't drink alcohol so and I don't
get into those kind of parties where
they play drinking games
so what the [\h__\h] is
that a
razor
mhm oh even higher Oh I thought he would
be there okay
guess the King has got to be at the top
is this a king I forgot may I help you
you're a Pacer I've got my eye on you
you cross the king shut up you'll regret
it King
no dog hey I'll see you wait I hurt a
dog here hey man what
you yeah I'm sure Alvis Presley had a
bad like
this I mean I can see it back in the
day that was surely a popular choice why
don't they sell beds like this
anymore why not in that heart
shape what do you have for
me ah so it went down like that huh well
yeah I mean I can't be help now well
you're not subtle but you get the job
done that's good enough for me maybe you
can help me with something you mean I'm
not subtle the police lot of folks
around presentent the sheer number of
people that have come into the area
since the strip was built in turn the
newcomers most of whom come from the NCR
have gotten ordinary from being resented
sometimes things get
violent this is one of those occasions
recently a few friends of mine were
attacked I want you to find out who did
it words come that they just woke up
over at the old Mormon Fort just north
of here head on over see if they
remember anything let's just assume that
I assumed that they were dead for real
and I was just like
testing my gun wouldn't matter if they
were already dead right so uh it's not
my fault that they were playing
[Music]
dead no I didn't know they were alive I
didn't know I didn't know I I maybe had
uh a hunch but did I know no I didn't
know I really didn't know
so anyway I was just testing my gun and
then oops you know things kind of
escalated so not my fault is their fault
is their fault they acted dead they
wanted to be dead I guess I gave it to
[Music]
them you don't just go around acting
like you did without any expectations
that you might end up dead for real for
real
yeah
good but wait what you want that was not
short guys that continued into another a
quest but I'll leave it at that I think
for today because I have an early stream
tomorrow where I'll be
refreshing my
Korean
knowledge
hopefully
hopefully you guys seem to be weirded
out by me not uh having a backlog in
super chats so I think I also am just
just going
to uh end it here without reading super
chats I can read them tomorrow perhaps
yeah let's let's get a little bit of a
backlog back I want the backlog
back give me my back look back back back
back back give me my back back back back
give me my back back back back look
back but be we're in Vegas baby yeah
well I I I think that's a big
accomplishment the fact that we made it
to New Vegas in my second Fallout New
Vegas stream
yay that's good that's a good
achievement big progress I would
say just said the thing I
did the game really picks up here oh
really um I I I would uh appreciate that
it does I wasn't really expecting
anything but that's nice we made it to
New Vegas I might as well end the whole
series
here feels like I did it no I'll I'll
continue
playing you're liking the game more this
stream than last stream e really I mean
last stream in the beginning I was kind
of lost for the most time even also in
the middle maybe else in the
end but I feel like the streams were
very similar
well Benny that sure was a whole new
Vegas thanks for showing
me thanks for bringing me here I found
you this was what I wanted since the
beginning of the
game your aim has improved in FPS games
you mean since the very beginning well
maybe it did maybe it
did the real fall at New Vegas was the
friends we made along the way
did we make friends we made some
companions today two
companions yeah and I found a home I got
my own home my motel room now there's a
city that idolizes me or a village I
suppose we made some spaceships
crash pretty exciting
stuff met some ghouls that I wanted to
beat for a while and we met some World
of Warcraft characters that I didn't
think I would be meeting at
all
yay innocent
ghouls honestly the way Cults work they
were probably going to all unive
themselves at some point
anyway feel like all the Cults end up
that way one way or
another so you know yeah and you don't
know what awaits you at the Moon can you
really know
yeah you probably can cuz the Moon is
not that far away but where they even go
to the Moon did they say what was their
goal where where were they intending to
go besides
space oh it was Moon the great yeah the
great beyond whatever that is well
probably I mean the Moon is not really a
space where we can live is it oh know I
don't think it
is but maybe for them maybe for ghouls
maybe ghouls can live on the
[Music]
moon I wish them good luck in the
afterlife I lived on the moon it's fine
but a little dry M I really can't with
dry climates my fr it hurts dry and
humid I need an in between please so I
guess I will not be going to the
Moon Yeah I freed them from suffer yeah
yeah I'm a hero I'm a hero why do you
think Noak Novak Novar Novak idolizes
[Music]
me wa said very dry I can imagine yeah
looks looks dry looks very dry
but that's not the only problem the Dr
is it's just overall [\h__\h] up with
radiation and and just toxic [\h__\h] so my
the dryness is my smallest least
problem yeah go find something to eat
here that's exactly what I'm going to do
now yeah thank you very
much have a nice evening see you
tomorrow and tomorrow early stream maybe
you guys will be there maybe
I really don't remember
[\h__\h] I wonder how that will go
tomorrow so yeah see you there and just
uh don't be square or just be round you
know usually around you should not be
you should not be square be
dare and don't be square
my notes I don't have I don't know where
my notes are thanks for the me not
membership the Super Chat
wow thank you oh don't worry sling
fellow oh changing your job
come did you send the same Super Chat
twice
oh also thanks for Super Chat space
water fall and ger we say Al do in
oh by the way by the way Kik Kik ke is
spelled with k i k k e
r i k i it's not that difficult why do
people always spell spell everything
wrong God damn
it just leaving that little note there
if somebody writes it wrong correct
them it's a weird word no it's like the
Japanese writing of kikiki basically
even though Kiki is like the the German
Way rooster says good
morning cuz the Japanese way would be C
coo but I just you
know of Biden
Zen bye
[Music]