[Music]
so
oh
is it on kick it again
[Music]
it was it was probably worth it probably
um we are having a special vr collab
today welcome
everybody my name is tata nasakiana and
next to me is
pavilion rainey
[Music]
[Applause]
and she's visiting the small vr worlds
today
for the first time
it's one thing i noticed already because
it's the first time i'm here with the
preacher models of the low poly models
that we're using is that the furniture
is like so tiny
yeah
i think i want to sit down but also
[Music]
oopsie like look can you can you like
yeah oopsie
it's too high yeah this is like we're
actually we're using um these cameras
while we're playing uh some games today
but uh ammon is controlling it so shout
out to emilia watson behind the scenes
i'm gonna reset i i changed it but let
me reset it again there you go okay
um
in this
vr world we're gonna play some games
today i have prepared two games for you
to two exactly
and that are kind of vacation related
because me and dana are going on a
vacation and a real vacation
in the real world
and we're both really excited and
nervous about it but we also have never
met before in real life
so maybe by playing these games in the
real world we'll kind of get you know
like a little warm up and and get yeah
for the vacation
yes
so
uh the first game
are you guys ready do you already want
us to start i think we want to start
because everybody waited so long and i'm
sure i'm sorry my expressions are going
crazy uh
so the first game let me explain the
first game to you
yeah
yes please
yeah yeah you also maybe also need an
explanation yeah i want you an
explanation too because yeah yeah please
please
okay okay so in this big vr world you
know with all the rooms like the small
inner world and so on
and there will be items
hidden that we have prepared prepared
beforehand new items so for example like
toothbrushes or socks and whatever all
kinds of things
and uh we are gonna try to find our
items because there's a version of those
items for me and there's a version of
those items for renee yes
and you will probably recognize them
because reyna's items are mostly blue
and mine are mostly orange
and they'll be scattered all over the
myth world and we'll go looking for them
it's kind of like a scavenger hunt in
that matter in that sense
so
yeah i i'm honestly i don't
i don't know where they placed them so
it's not like i'm cheating or anything i
really don't know i think they placed it
in every room because i asked them to
place it everywhere
so it's pretty big elena we will have to
do a lot of running
[Applause]
okay i'll do my best though
i will do my please do please do and
maybe you'll get some ideas for
something you forgot to pack for an
actual trip you'll be like oh
[Music]
there is actually something like a cheat
sheet
uh to so just so we know like that we're
missing something if i turn around
wait
how do i turn around
here you guys see this there's a
that is a cheat sheet i mean it's not
really a cheat sheet we're not cheating
but looking at it which is like okay
this is what we're still missing i've
been trying to like
de-attach my own camera and be like yo
this is what it looks like i think
they're i think they're seeing it yeah
okay so this is like this is my side you
see here we have a boarding pass with
sunglasses a switch a swimsuit a
hairbrush
sandals flip-flops
[Applause]
[Music]
insta camera thingy
headphones passport a book a nice book
toothbrushes two different socks these
count as different items and stuff
clothes and for later we have all the
same items but in her color variation so
and then after i press the start button
the game will start and we'll be um
collecting them thankfully we don't have
to run all the way over here and there
are the suitcases here there will be
once we collect them they'll be
automatically teleported into the
suitcases and then later
there will be more there will be a
second game so we don't want to continue
to click so do we just like pick it up
and it'll be teleport and so we can just
like start looking at everything for
everything in one go okay and it will
also
and it will show up on the screen as
well and it will say oh
lena has found this item so when i find
something it will also show up on your
screen so you kind of know oh my god i
need to you need to be faster yummy
do you think you can do it can you give
me your ikigomi ikigomi please
[Music]
wow did you drink water you're so
excited and then let's go
[Music]
i'm really nervous
it's basically actually um kind of a
race so whoever gets all the items first
will be the winner of the first game do
you think you're to be the winner right
now
i know this world's better than you so
maybe that's an advantage
[Music]
that's all right
i think you'll hear me sometimes so
i can give you some hints that for
example i saw your item in the room
in a specific room
i'll tell you i'll give you some hints
okay
you'll see my items and i'll see your
items too
uh-huh don't pick up the wrong one i
mean i don't think you'll be able to
pick up the wrong one i'm not sure
yeah i guess yeah
let's go
we'll be fine we'll be fine yeah yeah
and it says before you pick it up it
will say this is elena's item for
example so thank you thank you
shall we begin everybody
yeah this will be fun so we'll run in
different directions probably
will be switching the cameras every now
and then
and then let's startle
okay
let's go let's go
where's looking i i don't know what to
do with the camera so like sorry if my
camera like you know it's just like that
one
is it oh
14 out of 50 miss they have found
clothes it says lean upon clothes nice
um there's like other normal items here
too so everything is immediately it
could be where is it we're in between
very very
good the camera is like don't tell it
[Music]
i'm doing like a race thing so oh
there's something you know you just suck
like jeez
[Music]
[Applause]
probably
[Music]
look at this look at that
let's go find more oh wait there's more
idea this one is elena okay okay
there's like a lot of two dana items
[Music]
didn't see them at all
she found her sock
okay i have no idea oh i see uh
[Music]
to show you
what
[Music]
okay
oh yes okay
[Music]
okay
running around so much man is just too
much
[Music]
okay that
i fixed some audio things i can hear
lena now i think
oh nice nice okay okay
okay
[Music]
uh
okay now if i find something from rodena
i shouldn't say it out loud because
she's gonna hear it
[\h__\h] put a plane ticket okay she's from
playing tickets
elena can you hear me
yeah i can't hear you
what is this
[Music]
wait tell me how many items
how many how many items do i have
each 15 i think 15 oh oh so 15 15 is
just me my flip flops found my flip
flops
oh [\h__\h] did you see about an item from
you
oh yeah where is it oh the kiana
you're so nice
[Music]
if i put it in front of my face like i
won't be able to sh can i just can i
climb here see i'm not in my home turf
so it's like
[Music]
and i would like you guys to see this
was my idea
oh [\h__\h] i already got rid of it but it
said um i changed songs of ice and fire
to some songs of sparks and hinototis
that's my book oh hello oh my god it
scared me
oh
did you look into the room
[Music]
no there's nothing here
okay there is something there for you
you should check
aren't you nice or too nice man
where is it
open
look for something blue
we're going into my world now
[Music]
i didn't look too close but i think it's
yours
two items what
two items i think i'm blind i don't know
[Music]
they stand out so much
no i know nothing but i already found oh
i found your i found another item from
you
and another one looking like behind the
buildings what do you want how do you
keep finding items
[Music]
oh i am just a little baby i have no
eyes can you please okay there's another
two items two two questions for you in
the cali room
at least at least
i was like the first oh my god i'm blind
look at
oh
did i look at
girl and um
i think there should be more in the
keana room
i think i found some did i find
something in the kiara room i don't even
remember oh i'm so dizzy
i told you i told you this stuff for you
[Music]
for you in every room every room
oh god it's so hot
this is like it's so hard it's so hard
it's not as hot as is it as it is in the
maldives probably it's gonna be even
this is just like multiples training
i don't know
oh wait maybe i know
if something's there then maybe
something's stupid sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe i'm hallucinating what is this is
this like part of like this part of
something like how am i supposed to take
this i can't hear you
i can't i can't
maybe maybe you can't because it's mine
no i can't take this it's like
how do i taste this
what is she even happening
what is happening
i'm in a room
i think she's having some problems
oh okay oh
um where's my toothbrush did i get my
toothbrush
[Music]
i see yours but i have a feeling that i
thought mine but i might be
hallucinating i thought it was like part
of the um
city
i don't think i saw yours yet but i
found mine that's for sure
yeah i saw you
[Music]
let me see a blanket
so now
uh let's run one camera right here
now
you see it's filling up nicely oh
there's so much rain inside
[Music]
oh the bikini bottom i'm still missing
i know i know where your flip-flops are
and i know where
i just had to reset the camera
[Music]
okay
okay it's all right it's already sorry
i'll just am i looking something here
look i can't look that holy i looked at
the cali room too much i think i think
like
i don't know
i'm not gonna put it in like a very like
evil place right like a very evil place
like the moons and crannies of stuff
well i think you should because like one
thing jago was carrying one thing was
hidden on the wall so we should
definitely look at the walls more
[Music]
did you find something
i don't know i didn't
[Music]
i didn't maybe there's
wait where is space do we have a space
room i don't remember
[Music]
is living in space
i'm pretty sure
[Music]
this is here
oh i was wondering if we can go through
there
[Music]
wait so how do i grab these then how do
you grab them
they're gone forever
they're just one
can we go
oh i think every teleport outside
yes we can let's go
did you
did you make this world and not tell us
did you prepare this
[Music]
oh i found something oh that's mean my
passport is hidden
yeah there's a bunch to go
[Music]
later go outside
i film you
okay
wait wait i can't grab i could grab
yeah now i got it
[Music]
swim swim into space swim
are you just dancing
i hear you tapping
is that sock my sock
is it
is it is it
is it hmm
is it
there
wait i'll put this
[Music]
uh oh
wait as i get back out here
gosh
i need a shower i need a shower
where is my camera my fish
let's take my passport
yeah
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
the camera
oh my god
at least this is fair you're taking a
break i'm taking a break but the moment
i see you collecting items again i will
collect them too so
when you stop
when you when you start
[Music]
i don't know how do i check uh
i think you can only see like if you're
collecting something
then it shows up
how many items are in your head you're
ahead of me you're ahead of me i'm
missing i'm listening to you we can
when i don't know is in my legs
although i think i do know i think if i
if i get all the items then you don't
have to
finish yours we can already move on to
the next game if you want to
okay but now i'm just curious okay fine
i'm not you know i'm just curious
where's
oh yeah
but does it
i know where your earphones are
you okay show me
yes yes i do
oh no i've taken it yet though
have you taken it bikini top
my bikini top
i think i only took my panties
my bikini pants we can exchange
yeah we're gonna get information i don't
mind
okay
your um
but
i'm not sure which worm it was i'm gonna
go look
i'm gonna go look
okay
[Music]
like a
i'm gonna i'm gonna do the crab
we're like spiders
it was not here oh
so slow
you can only see like the top of my head
you look so weird
[Music]
huh what my thing in the stage of her
thing in the state only hurting is on
the stage
okay um actually i'm going to show you
first here's your there's your bikini
top
i was thinking there should be there it
is i was thinking there should be more
in my room
all right all right all right now i'm
back to serious baby
yeah my bikini top
mm-hmm yeah that's yours uh-huh
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
okay
in the auditorium it should be on the
stage on the auditorium
it's in the auditorium
yeah where's my camera okay never mind
wait
one one one more one what am i missing
what am i even looking for i'm going one
more time and i probably know what
you're i probably wanna i probably know
what you're looking for i'm gonna go
through that auditorium
i've passed something that belongs to
you so many times and you still haven't
like taken it but i don't know if you
have taken it now
maybe it was your item
not mine i would have taken it but it
says
that's yours i found your toothbrush um
where is it
i won't tell you
until you tell me my last thing
wait okay wait no where's the hours
where's my where's my oh my gosh here it
is
okay i'm not telling you anything else
i'm not telling you oh that's so mean i
thought we were i thought we were
announced again
okay
i'm gonna take a i'm gonna take like a
bread light stick just because i can
do something you go
bro have you seen something
no need to tell me but have you seen
something new
[Music]
what is this anyway what is this this is
not wait you found my you found my
toothbrush
yes and i also know where your passport
is
oh my hands right here
well did you find him where is she
laughing like that
uh it's not that's not me laughing
that's me about to throw up
let's go
[Music]
don't worry once i have my last item you
will not have to look it for any
anywhere else don't worry no but tell me
where's my toothbrush i need to pack my
brush your toothbrush is actually really
blended in a scenery it's actually
pretty difficult to see
right right like i thought i saw
something but then
i guess like not but then it didn't look
like a toothbrush but i don't know where
it is i forgot oh wait i think i know
what i'm missing and why i'm not finding
it because it looks so normal okay okay
i'm looking that's me with my
things
[Music]
your toothbrush i think i think
was and i hope i don't regret telling
you this but i think your toothbrush was
in the good of room
because the room is so blue and that's
why it blends in so where oh my god i'm
going so slow sorry guys i look like
this because this is the anti-reverse
drinking gesture let's see yeah i
thought i saw it
what am i missing
[Music]
did you find it
this was just like like our normal items
it felt like that's just you know
amen
[Music]
can we
now can we lie down please
please
yes that's just true
so i actually i also know where your
passport is but i guess you don't need
that even though that's the most
important thing
[Music]
[Applause]
it was somewhere obvious
don't forget it oh my god did you did
you know i forgot my passport once and i
had to like come back and then when i
arrived at the airport i missed the
flight by five minutes
after the next flight
and then okay it was the next day but
you know listen learn the hard way
okay
yeah you know what
the next game will not um involve much
movement so
that's good that's good that's very good
that's very it's very good
okay i'm gonna slowly walk into the
studio
i'm just like hopefully yeah me too he
had me to me to me too
i just want to close my eyes oh you're
standing up well i'm so proud of you for
standing up for yourself oops
well
i'm just gonna slowly follow you
okay
man wise
[Music]
yes okay okay amelia manage your son
yes
as you say
i'm still missing my book and passport i
think
yeah let me locator still some space
and for me it's all filled up
[Music]
[Laughter]
your your suitcase uh your your password
sorry i'm like so
what let's go
let's go to the film studio let's go to
the
yeah you know what let's go
hello hello hello my camera's like all
over the place but you know forgive me
guys what a surprise this is very
special
oh did you already see it on vayner's
point of view
oh sorry guys
it's okay
all right sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
you should be holding the camera i think
i should
like move this away
all right cool so welcome to the yeah we
don't need them anymore welcome to the
mountains
i think i need to calibrate there we go
okay
welcome to the mountains our vacation
spot do you hear the ocean sound yay
[Music]
this time
can you put some sunscreen on me
of
[Music]
gently okay
okay i'm sorry
screen on your legs
okay okay okay
[Music]
i mean your legs you can you can put
sunscreen on your legs by yourself but
honestly you would only need help with
your back but
[Music]
yeah don't forget to put some sunscreen
on your nose okay yeah you know it's
very important
[Music]
with sunscreen on your nose
[Laughter]
okay so the reason why we're here it's
not just to put sunscreen on one another
but actually there's a gameplay
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think i think this is a game that
i i think everybody knows um
your legs i do okay
okay yeah the side effect of sunscreen
but i'm good yes
i'll tell you guys what this game is all
about it's very simple so all the items
that we have collected are now lined up
here right now it's mine but later it
will be um
don't worry about it it'll be switching
and for example
i will put for example my hair brush i
won't pick it up right now because we're
not starting it but i will take my
hairbrush and i put it in my suitcase
and i'll remember that because i don't
have a bird brain
and then dana will remember that too but
she has a bird brain so hopefully she'll
forget but she'll remember that i chose
a hairbrush she'll put the hairbrush in
her um suitcase
and then she'll take a second item of
her choice and i'll try to remember that
when i'm watching her
and that way it's a memory game we'll
keep on continuing when you're sitting
in my suitcase again why do you like my
suitcase so much you like my cats
are you my cat
and why only one way to find that way in
the wow
meow i am a bird
no sitting in the suitcases we gotta
pack our things because we're going soon
our flights are leaving soon
okay we need to get packed immediately
so i mean was that game was that
explanation uh understandable
it's basically just
something and then you pack with ipad
and you add another thing and then i
pack when you packed what i packed and
you probably branded another thing
exactly and i think we're gonna
um probably break pretty soon and then
have to do a second round then i think
we'll do maximum three three rounds it
says two on my hand but i mean three
rounds yes yes matching probably
depending on how long we can go but
first let me just drink some water um
okay i'm gonna drink
my
noodles i can't drink in peace
hold on
my hands are you know
are you guys jealous do you guys want to
come to the vacation too
yay
you guys are welcome
in a different island no no no no
they're not yeah
no no no no no
we want our private alone time obviously
all right are you ready to start the
game nina
yeah i am ready my big brain is ready
okay
um
i haven't played this game in a long
time but
uh i am apparently the one starting
so first turn i will take
my hairbrush
can you get out of my suitcase
[Music]
okay and then it's gonna be my turn
right then i'm gonna be taking my
hairbrush and then i'm gonna be taking
him
and then
and then mom
my what is this
glasses sunglasses yes sunglasses okay
okay
[Music]
so you took the hairbrush chat you also
try to guess along along with us if you
can remember everything hail bruh don't
worry i can't read the chat so i can't
cheat with the chat either don't worry
yeah and the sunglasses
sunglasses
and then a new item
which will be
the pile of gloves
nice job okay
okay um okay okay my brain can handle
this
so hair
okay
this is two items now three items and
you add the fourth one three three three
yeah yeah and then i'm putting my
glasses to me
and then i'm putting the chocolate
cloves
yes
wait wait why can't i grab it okay hold
on
you should be able to
yeah yeah and then i'm gonna pick my
my
i don't know uh right sock
[Music]
yeah it was my idea and i regretted that
we have two different jobs
[Music]
are you sure sunglasses
when you're showing up otherwise i'll
forget about
[Music]
is that the right sock it doesn't say i
think it's i mean
ah it should be
[Music]
a new item new item
i will take my passport
[Music]
why is it so hard to like
stupid ceiling
the ceiling is so stupid i'm not ceiling
sorry though
gently why that was the hairbrush not
getting it oh [\h__\h] no sorry
i think it got reset because you didn't
put it in properly
are you
serious
just do it again
okay
okay sorry you you scared me
see it's like it's like it's like
release the drop but it's like
it says release to draw but okay fine
i'm gonna can you go any longer
yeah i can i definitely can
okay there we go
i already forgot i already forgot what i
put i'm so sad
[Music]
no the technical difficulties
all right
[Music]
you know like the passwords are so
detailed
[Music]
and then okay
one new one we're doing pretty good so
far hmm kind of okay
[Music]
normally this game is like played
without the visuals just with the words
i think actually the visuals make it
easier
because you can literally pick it up and
then put it in did you see what i put in
no really
it's a fashionable personal brush
thank you very much
[Music]
and we have the sunglasses
and then we have the
the pile of clothes oh god i feel like
i'm gonna make a mistake soon we have
the right sock
uh
yeah
then we have
the passport
yeah
and then we have man i don't even
remember what she said
[Music]
oh my god
hair brush and then shoot what is it um
hair brush and then
i don't know
um
i know this some glasses i think
then i should listen to what you do
and then the i think it's the clothes
[Music]
you should be relaxed on your vacation
later
remember
i i don't
what i throw down something on my table
i need to get further away okay continue
[Music]
i'll take the earphones then
okay i see that i see what you're doing
[Music]
come on
is this your first time packing a
suitcase venus
yeah i'm like a little bit um
well you know
uh it's not even some health
and i know
[Music]
again
[Laughter]
i don't think i can put it in i'll just
um i'll just pick something else
i'll choose something else that i can
put in
okay
[Music]
i hope oh god
[Laughter]
[Music]
i think so i think so
okay and then then
um
i think the the boarding pass
yeah
and then the bikini bottom i think not
the top the bottom right
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes yes
okay
okay what's your item
[Music]
nobody can tell okay ever again that we
have a bird brain
because we're doing so good it's your
turn
oh my god
it's hairbrush i think i think it's
hairbrush
yeah yeah yeah
glasses and then clothes i think
clothes
clothes um
i think that's the annoying item right
sock i think
specifically the right sock
yeah specifically the right sock hmm oh
[\h__\h] that's it i loved it
i think it's this one i don't know
it could be
i think i think so okay
[Music]
this one i think
it's the toothbrush i think could be
[Music]
it could be
the boarding pass maybe
maybe it's probably the
hey okay the boarding pass okay and then
okay i'll give you that bikini
the bikini bottom i think
i think and then i forgot what you took
it's probably this one the polaroid i
think
the camera
[Laughter]
[Music]
i don't know it's the big greeting
it's the big brain
yes
okay you need your your extra item
what's it gonna be
i don't know um
[Music]
i will get rid of our suffering
[Laughter]
all right speedrun
[Music]
the right sock i i think
right zach the passport man
i should listen
faster
[Music]
oh yeah i need your opinion on you know
like this very good christmas like place
over here like dude do you like sushi
i'm not your favorite here i don't i
don't like sushi actually i don't like
it at all
what do you like
what's your favorite i like
burgers and pizza and lasagna
oh yeah okay the thing is that because
you were asking me questions you weren't
quite paying attention either you might
forget what i put in there
i might forget
i'll get
the book okay
the book
i don't think that you make it so far
damn me too
respect
[Music]
yeah all i can think of is sushi right
now
uh-huh
and then what uh oh dammit i forgot i
heard the clothes but what i think it's
this one
i'm not even like i don't know
maybe i don't remember anymore
my brain is like
i don't remember
i really really don't remember
um i think i hope i hope that the
weather is gonna be this nice in the
maldives time when we go there
but i'm doubting it
yeah i guess so fast
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay bikini bottom
bikini bottom and then
i know i know i think
i know
are we clearing this
don't you want to be a top entertainer
a top entertainer would fail somewhere
in the next rounds just you know for
entertainment purpose
just telling you
i forgot
i forgot maybe um maybe it's this song
what is it
she
right you should show me how to be a top
entertainer because i really have a lot
to learn from you right
right
[Music]
don't you dare like be like why are you
bringing a switch to a vacation because
it's gonna be [\h__\h] raining all day
and we need something to play okay we're
gamers we're gamers we're allowed to
bring a switch to a vacation
yeah
um
i'm gonna observe
and then
pile of clothes
uh the right sock
uh it's getting dangerous really
dangerous
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
i think oh god okay okay you can do this
you can do it
[Music]
and then i think next was yours because
i did the pudding passion you did you
did the bikini bottom
and then and then and then
i did i did the i did the camera
i did the camera and then and then and
then
and then you did
the laptop to relieve release us from
our suffering
yes
um
and i did the book uh the song of
the song of uh sparks and phoenixes
oh yeah mom by the way my book's also
different
yeah yeah i came up with the ideas by
the way
you see that nice nice nice zooming
and then
that was mine and then you added
the switch we're gonna clear this let's
go
oh we're really gonna clear this
for real
what the hell
i didn't think it would be that's easy
i couldn't yeah the thing is like i
can't like put this in there yeah
oh but i can try it i need to put
something in
yeah do it
okay
oh my god um good luck good here
you're not moving like an idol would
[Laughter]
[Music]
vacation spirit getting to
yeah and it closed and then i think um
oh it's an annoying item yes is this one
[Music]
i think
and then
i think it could uh it probably is the
passport g i don't know
is it is it though
it could be
[Music]
we don't need that
we don't need to point out anything
anymore
[Music]
did i distract you successfully
yeah you did
um
[Music]
and i think
i think it might be this one i could be
wrong
and then
[Music]
and then i think it's oh [\h__\h] i can't
remember is it this one or that one
[Music]
okay are you seriously confused now
finally it was a bathtub finally it was
about time i think
it was about time
[Music]
[Laughter]
for entertainment value right
yes
like
because i'm your bird senpai and you do
as your birthday tells you
that's so menacing but yes of course we
are totally like super smart idols and
we have big brainies who just did this
for the sake of entertainment yeah for
the sake of
funny comedian points on my right or am
i right
yes
comedian yeah comedian destiny
comedian dissident
yes
[Music]
should we do a second round or a
revenge round or
what do you think
um
let's do one more
one more
i don't wanna
yay
[Music]
[Laughter]
overlapping is
we have to make this
family friendly
um die
yeah
okay
uh it seems like the first turn will be
you i think
because your thing is open
oh my god
my big brain is ready
[Music]
um the most important item
i want to see if my earphone the
earphones can fit
see it now oh oh
okay okay
every time in the future where you have
to put that in
okay yes i'm very scared we have them
and then oh yeah headphones and then
i'm gonna put the
the book in
that's my decision
[Music]
okay earphones please
thank you oh yes
do you know what preferences
uh no
because i um one of my favorite movies
is the great gatsby so i said how about
the great old tree
i see
is
[Laughter]
okay so it actually gets confusing with
do you know the first round
items so we have the boom look and then
we have you first wanted to take the
left sock but then you ended up taking
the right sock
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
birds
that was just a testing testing round we
did the testing round um
um as the second round because
we we're not part of your system
[Music]
do you want to do a round two
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's probably a smart choice because
um
the maldives are currently in the moon's
monsoon season
so
that was
we may have been able to be big
big bird brain to pack all these things
properly but i think it was a not so big
brain decision to go to the maldives
during the monsoon so i'm at least very
happy that we have the mom lives here
with no rain
[Music]
if i'm very very sad about it raining
too much i'll just go back here we'll
rain it and i'll act as if this was the
real vacation
the spirit that's the spirit
[Music]
no but guys we'll um don't worry we'll
have some kind of content on our
channels we'll try to stream while we're
on vacation we're gone for about a week
but we'll try to stream on both of our
channels anyway and upload some stuff so
keep an eye out for that
but for now this is kind of our
kind of our goodbye stream and then uh
you're welcome to be jealous i would be
jealous too i mean
these cute birds going on a vacation
together
who wouldn't be jealous
what are you doing are you showing me
your dance moves again
i need to teach you how to do idle dance
no this is the people idol dance and in
our world we do it like this
[Laughter]
yes like this that's such a weird dance
oh there's actually also chicken dance
it goes kind of like this
but my trackers are kind of acting up
right now that's not what it's supposed
to look like
what does this mean
i don't know how it works
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh singing that's that chicken song
please do not ban me please or maybe we
do because i wouldn't mind re-debuting
again
again yes
i want to hear like your impression
because it was your first time
in the small vr world and also in the
studio like what's your impression
about it
it's so cool it's so cool like you know
i never knew about like this whole thing
especially this yeah thank you so much
for you know like coming up
cool
can you show her the other the other
studio thingies
she's on it she's honest
what else did we have
oh oh this is
kelly's a room made into a stage here
very
about dangerous
it's a safety hazard we need some we
need some railings i think on here
it's a side effect it's a side effect
what else do we have
oh that's all really
oh we have this like kind of like main
main studio room with all our colors on
the ground so i would stand here and i
would stand here kelly would stand here
and so on yeah this is oh that's so cool
oh yeah you didn't see that did you it's
over here i bring the camera
it's still following okay oh yeah
[Music]
it's so cool it has a really nice color
i'm left-handed would i play like this
[Laughter]
it's only a water pistol anyway
[Music]
was that all we had on it so we have
another one
need to show up somewhere oh this is
just a
basic colors maybe for green screen and
so on oh yeah
[Music]
oh my god i just bumped against the wall
that's not good
like sense of where you are in your room
when you do vr oh then we have roll
orange for example
oh you playing flute cute
i can play oh that i didn't know this
one
did i know this one
i don't remember this world what was
that
what is this one
[Music]
oh this is cali i suppose cali color
no no
this is cool with the spotlight here in
the middle
very fancy
[Music]
[Applause]
so many we should like film movies in
here or the white backdrop for the cute
idol shots
oh
nice
yay
a nice camera work look at the camera
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
we need to size them up for the
preaching models this is too small it
doesn't fit
yeah it's like it's cute though it's
like
ben's first instrument
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's kind of nice right
yeah
did we show it all now
[Music]
we have so much stuff yeah that's it
yeah
okay
well then back to the moldeds maybe
okay okay
where is it
[Music]
let's get into the suitcase
oh okay
i want to say uh
want to say thank you to priy2 obviously
who made the mod models previously maybe
we should get some swimsuit models at
some point let's say thank you to the
seafoam boy and now
for taking up my uh
kind of last minute commission one week
time they had to build these props
and the background and program
everything and
program the game and the sounds and
everything
so thank you for your hard work
[Music]
uh one week before she was like hey
before we go to the maldives we should
do some kind of vr collab and i'm like
oh wait if you want to do a vr collab
don't look under my panties
and how about we're doing something more
special that i suddenly was inspired and
had
some ideas for some games so here we are
thank you everybody for joining and
watching thank you to alex
for something
to do the camera work and the
troubleshooting with us you're amazing
thank you so much
[Music]
you're the best
thank you soon and we are now take a
shower
i love you love you love you
we're now going to take a shower so
i will see you guys soon
and um yeah
hope you enjoyed it hope you enjoyed it
of course i enjoyed it i enjoyed it
thank you
and now the birds will go fly to their
vacation that's why i actually have one
more stream tomorrow and i think you
probably also have one more stream
maybe
i do yeah
but just pretend that we're now going
off and flying
to our vacation destination
um
thank you
[Music]
you