[Music]
so
do
[Music]
hello
can you guys hear me
chat
hi okay you guys can hear me cool
so for now we're in first person so i
guess you guys are on it for now but
it's only for a little bit and then
we'll have the cameraman take over
there's also um
a candy cane here
a magical candy cane
do i sound okay do i sound okay is the
music okay can you guys hear music
yeah you're on it today
whoa look at my look at our hands hey
what's that
oh
christmas stuff
this is where i'm reading chat by the
way chat is right there on that buzz
sign
but uh you can only take it if you're
special i mean you can only read it if
you're special
uh you guys make sure to check out kiara
and sana's perspectives i'm sure things
are starting out
looks like a party over there so let's
go ahead and join them i just wanted to
uh you know
set things up a little bit
we're gonna go on a field trip today
actually so
let's see how everybody's doing at this
christmas party
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
what are you holding what is that oh
it's a martini
it's a nice drink yeah
it's very nice
it's just christmas cocktails
cheers is there a drink for everybody i
want a drink
i think this one's inna's drink this oh
this one must be mine
this looks like a drink for me
[Music]
oh you got a whiskey mame nice
can i have a sip
here we can trade let's go
oh it's got like a ball in it
i know
[Music]
iris with the soda of course the hope
soda
it's not good for your throat
the hope is special
come on
[Music]
[Applause]
we have 20 minutes to kill so or 15
minutes to kill till we start the field
trip
clink oh my god
it's just it's just being in small form
it's just you know it also makes
everybody's brain small okay you guys
that's all
you know
you know it's the holidays it's this is
this is when we celebrate by the way
guys i'm looking at chat chat is this
plant uh by the way guys i'm just
talking to the plant while we're at a
party but uh does everything look okay
and sound okay you know
is it does the stream look okay
[Music]
is this does it look okay it looks good
yes okay everything sounds okay the
levels are okay
that looks good okay okay all right all
right
oh cara is here the party started
maybe we could have somebody show off
their outfits
i'll show off my outfit first
yeah fashion show on the bar
i showed you my
please respond the runway's over here
my one fan
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh we gotta even we got a light stick
here too
hold on this this freaking window moved
my chat window moved
how do i grab it
there's money
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
of money
oh i like that drink santa it's like a
like an ice cream or something like a
float it looks good
yeah i saw it for me
oh
[Music]
my chat window's flying i gotta fix it
if i can
better go
i'm trying you got him girl i heard that
that was good that was a good one
yeah it was a real good one
[Music]
there we go that's good okay i fixed it
oh
all the rooms have decorations i think
so i'm going to go look at them really
quick
got presents presents what could be in
here something for gooda
were you a good shark this year
no but there's presents there's presents
to open later not this one though
yeah there's presents
[Music]
you guys ever like burn a piece of hair
over candles have you done that
no that's kind of weird
yeah it does smell bad your eyebrows
that's true yeah it's dangerous
oh it goes like
it like does sparks and stuff
sparks like the flame and fun and a fire
today
yeah you got lights in here now and some
candles oh they're snowing
[Music]
pretty lights
thank you for holding this for me i
really appreciate that thank you
okay
outfits it's always the sexy role
it's always uh
it's like a cookie bra
hey hey whoa whoa oh my god
oh i know you can get one of those
in the past okay i'll see santa we'll
see what what uh i could do
okay
taco maybe the taco is the real scene
santa's on break
[Music]
hold on i'll fix it guys
okay i'm just fixing something
[Music]
your outfits
[Applause]
[Music]
oh everybody's in here all right let's
go to i'm going to go to the next world
i want to see kiara i think kiara has
snow in her world
i want to see
oh this is the wrong way
does it look like the real australia
i think it's accurate
of course it has been snowing a lot
recently
[Music]
how do you say it gloss coconut oil
has anybody kissed you cronie
have you gotten a kiss yet comes true
you gotta kiss it
[Music]
well you don't have a red nose wait i
just can't see it
this scarf
oh it's soft it's like so good
wow
oh
[Music]
it does look like a baby head
did your room get anything
i got it i want to see
oh god i miss his dad
yeah that's true it just it just freezes
oh there's some lights in here
cool
oh the tacos have uh santa hats too
have you wear santa but you still had us
tried it what would you use it for like
to
you know get the kids that are bad maybe
you hear that chat
shish kabob
you see this three pointed
i can eliminate three of you toddlers at
once oh dark i can limit it to your
house
i mean that's that's pretty efficient
like as santa you you don't really have
a lot of time so
these look like halloween lights maybe
they're from halloween no of course not
no it's just the reflection under the
water you know
oh
i don't know atlantis isn't really big
on christmas are we even in the ocean
maybe this is like a fishbowl
oh
[Laughter]
this is a dentist aquarium what
what
um in your toilet well
no
this cat or kelly's room has some
lighting too
oh
it's just like a summoning circle but
christmas themed this taco looks sweaty
let me see sweaty taco
sweaty
scared of what cali is about to unleash
i guess yeah there's a lot of presents
in here maybe there's a nice
present um
good present
it's not scary
what are you talking about there's no
per no the presents are for later
they're not in here all right i think
it's time
what time is it you gotta watch
party time okay we're at the 20 mark all
right i gotta make an announcement i'm
making an announcement it's not me
actually somebody else is making a
worldwide announcement on
discord oh
um oh it's a secret
okay hold on
is it your mommy
no
hello
world
uh please gather at the elevator the
field trip is going to begin shortly the
elevator will leave without you
i think everybody hears that i don't
know
[Music]
wait don't go in yet we'll wait okay
everybody gather at the elevator
remember the instructions when i give
you the signal count to 10 and then
we can join the winter wonderland
[Music]
sorry there's double for you hi
oh yes
uh i will leave i will give you a signal
and then you all need to count to ten
and then you can join the magical
wonderland
okay
all right let's all go into the doors
wonderland
all right guys now don't don't press any
buttons yet but you can press the button
for here winter world not yet but okay
now i want you guys to count to ten
starting
now
okay don't look guys
all right
hello
oh yeah it's a snowball
wow
can i ask you something yes see my body
because i don't see my body anymore oh i
see it looks normal to me
but when i do like when in front of the
mirror i couldn't see myself and with
selfie camera i can also not see myself
oh you could try to do the respawn
option it it'll respawn you no wait i
can see myself again okay it's back
okay i didn't see myself okay okay it
works yeah
i want to make a snowman with you guys
i have a camera here but it's not the
only camera that we have
[Music]
look how pretty remember guys do not
touch the gnomes the gnomes are
deadly
yeah they bite
you gonna make it really big
you're making a snow in the house life
size snowball
lifestyle oh yeah because we're small
oh my god bae
this place is so pretty it's snowing
everywhere somebody brought a drink
i don't know you could do that
oh it's like we're giving birth or
something i'm sorry i'm in the way i'll
push it this way
[Music]
oh it's a cookie
inna watch out it's dangerous
wait can we get a science comparison i
think santa could fit inside that yeah
we'd never know you could just hide in
there let me see
oh
nice all right i'm going to push it
ready
okay
i think you need to be like you need
some gamer skills to stay on
[Music]
oh yeah yeah you work it work it work
that snow flower
i
well you guys are making like a big pair
of snowballs right here
all right remember guys do not touch the
gnomes no gnome touching
the gnomes are dangerous look at my
shadow wait i get a really cool
screenshot good uh
i look cool
yeah you look really cool
can i get up there too thanks
oh yeah
oh we're like they're like the circus
act where they hold hands and then they
like
[Music]
we're circus or circus
[Laughter]
no
i'm gonna get that snowball you're too
snow can't grab
it away
yeah that's chat i think it's on that
camera right now but uh what we can go
to the fireplace
let's there's a fireplace this way
[Music]
oh my god
i think we can use a bubba uh i think we
can use camera number three
no uh camera number three
oh there we go
[Music]
my
oh there's a mirror here if you guys
want to see yourselves here i'll turn on
the mirror oh did we turn off the mirror
you know i'll be right back you guys
i'll be right back
i gotta turn off the other mirror so
i'll be back
sorry everybody sounds far away for you
guys don't worry
i'm is here
it's just uh sometimes there's some
performance issues and it really helps
turn off this mirror
over here
okay going back
and we're back
look at that
oh my face what's wrong with my
[Music]
the star on the tree
um
should we do
well i guess a few more minutes we'll do
snowman decorating huh
all right
camera hey
hey everyone at home hi kiara here we go
hey folks
oh yeah kiara was saying with our
christmas outfits
we could do a nice sexy dance
[Music]
me too me too
did
[Music]
let it go you don't want to know what's
inside of them candy canes you don't
want to know what's inside of them
oh you know what you get for christmas
tiara for being such a good phoenix you
get cold
she done flips at the top
um
[Music]
little little is it like an outhouse or
something i'm just kidding this is like
where they put the candy cane
i'll take that that's where they put the
top one this is where they store the
bodies
this is a
this is a wood this is just wood it's
like rimworld
the finished sauna
oh no this is where the finished sauna
is no there's a oh the finished sun is
over here
yeah yeah for real
let me see everybody going
i'm like i feel like a creep can we get
away open it
yes oh my god i think i can
[Music]
bye
yeah open it
i left you there for a reason let me in
knock knock
[Music]
oh thank you
hi
oh i can just walk through it i can't
help
okay okay
don't lock me out again
[Music]
yeah it's really hot in here they're
about to be some until dawn [\h__\h] in here
[Music]
yeah i think it works if you you guys
know how that sauna works
please it's hot now ladies it's hot and
then you put water you put water on it
oh my god i'm so down here oh yeah it's
soup it's complimentary soup
[Music]
all right i'm going to quickly check on
everybody else give me one sec how do i
open this door
there we go
i'm probably the only one dressed close
enough everybody's here
[Music]
is this a sauna or something what is
this
[Music]
do the magic do the magic trick
that's okay i'm sure you're doing a good
job
[Music]
cody has like a fan attached to her to
cool us down
[Music]
this is one of my favorite things
they've ever made
[Music]
you guys want to come a little closer
hold on
i'll help
[Music]
um
oh
outside
[Music]
let's go let me get out of here yeah
it's too hot open the door
[Music]
you've released me from
i'm just imitating
[Music]
don't jump don't do it definitely see
people's pants from here
oh hey
charlie's in there you like it he's
angry okay no you're wearing snow pants
girl that's really classy now
keep following you put pants on me
[Music]
i'm
i think this is a lake since finland is
known for their lakes chad's looking
pretty i learned that oh same as
australia oh there's just a lot of lakes
over there finland has an ocean we don't
have an ocean oh
that's true
camera
i know sometimes it's a little difficult
to use it's so cute
it's fine you figure it out edible [\h__\h]
yeah i can just eat you all in one bite
[Music]
i do flip wait i'll do a spin
they work
hello
oh father skating cute
did the shark skate the shark escape
[Music]
i am
oh
[Music]
oh i'm just taking the camera back
oh cool action shot
wow
[Music]
it's like those really cool skater
videos
it's christmas
it's like a music video
get low get low on
christmas in the middle and they're
are you angry
needs a kiss to calm down
[Music]
last year to save you from tears
ah
oh okay so if you guys come over here
there's snowmen to decorate we each get
a snowman to decorate
[Music]
oh so if you guys want to draw with
these pens on desktop you can use i j k
to rotate and you can draw with the pens
okay
you can draw with the pens pick your
pick your snowmen there's hats to choose
from
and uh let's see what else we got hold
on i'll show you guys the hats
all right bubba on camera hey
all right over here we got the snow the
snow pieces if you guys want to add some
additional snow pieces to your snowmen
we got a whole army here
uh you could add some mounds to your
snowman we got some hats here
we got we got ina drawing
i'ma pick this snowman over here
[Music]
oh
i don't know if you can erase actually
did we think about that i don't think
okay
[Music]
oh
from
[Music]
i disappeared
nice cali
thank you i know they're a little
lopsided
it works you know yeah it looks good
thank you
oh nice funna oh it's a
it bunny supposed to be like a sprout
but oh
it didn't really turn out right i mean i
could i could see that yeah
oh good over here with the tutu
nice okay it's not a tutu
what happened
i mean why why is it disappearing
time limited there's a limit
well you know we're testing as we're
going it's a work in progress guys oh
god what's up
this is so evil
this is like the ancient ones have been
unleashed from the lake
ooh dark lore
[Music]
i don't think there's any carrots
there's hats though
i'll bring you a hat
oh there's chiara's hat here actually i
don't know
i don't think this hat fits hey guys i'm
invisible now 3d 3d effect bam what is
that though
what is that oh wow
that's i carry is anybody else dollar
is she disappearing still yeah she's
disappeared
oh my oh my god what is that
what is that wow that's beautiful
[Music]
is
chad's here uh bubba on camera hey we
got a message for chat
can you see me yeah
[Music]
okay ready turn
ready um beautiful things don't last
forever
[Music]
it's like a disney way you do the thing
or it's like
[Music]
[Applause]
uh yeah it's backwards i think
it's backwards it's bad
no don't worry i'll go we'll go from the
other side all right let's switch sides
till then we'll go for this side
all right
yeah go around it yep go behind it
there we go
[Music]
oh i didn't do anything but
oh we should try and do our autographs
that'd be pretty cool
that'd be cool yeah
oh god hold on let me check up on
everybody else hold on one second i'm
stuck in this i'm stuck okay
all right we're good
[Music]
hey
where's the camera hey
[Music]
all right let's go this way it looks
very big and fluffy yeah what do you
guys think you guys like it
yeah now she's really sansa but she's
like
she's like an evil santa
oh god what the hell is
what is this
[Music]
she's looking good it looks really um
groovy it looks pretty groovy i like it
i like it nice job eena
where's it looking it's
looking at the moon the taco forever is
stuck
frozen in time
[Music]
save me it says
i'll take a picture with him
okay
this is like the famous taco in finland
cool
you guys chat did you guys take a
picture
who's making a line is that your mommy
making a big line across
no
you didn't do this
oh we could play like uh we could play
limbo
ready watch
get me on the cam i'm about to do a sick
trick of course ready
okay
hey wait i'm too cool i'm too far away
hold on wait that doesn't count
i went under it guys okay
oh my god no is this is this where turns
evil and destroys
[Music]
let's go check up i'm going to go check
up on gooda
who's doing that
who is it everest you know
was it you
i no i'm innocent yeah
it wasn't irish
come back here
we gotta set a red trip oh god she's
good
she's testing the limits
of course oh god crony we're making take
care of red
i'm making my circle to keep away from
alaskan bull worms can i get in i don't
know
if i fit yeah sure
yeah
who's tying yourself up
the
[Music]
yeah
the only thing i can draw these days
uh a piece of snow they're a little
stubby hands that drive really it's so
beautiful until it melts away
that was good
lyrical genius i am a lyricist
i am a lyricist after all we have
um i made a heart right next to yours
it's kind of hard to see oh really
it's really bold it's really bold
[Music]
she stays behind and then gets all the
way to the top even though she was last
place no
no that's true
oh my god
good lord what is this
what is that
it wasn't me this is a rat's nest it's
just in your nature huh you just gotta
make a little nest huh
you didn't do it
yeah okay
catch you red-handed
[Music]
ah
that's cute wait am i am i visible now
i'm invisible okay don't worry about it
well i photoshopped myself in my heart
we tried
that's pretty good i'm going to check
over here
oh good lord we're standing here
[Music]
there's too many goddamn lines
everywhere
wait i want to take a picture
[Music]
okay
huh
[Music]
tomorrow i'm gonna wake up and my hands
are gonna hurt again because
what
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't worry about it
oh nice hat yeah
i'm just kidding i wouldn't do that
i wouldn't do that we're gonna put a
different hat we have a witch hat hey
who wants a hat
i'm the snowman now
[Music]
putting some
just another
[Music]
you look beautiful i'll give you some
anime blush lines
mmm thank you so i can be extra cute
yeah i don't think they turned out too
great
[Music]
why is everyone in chad laughing
shouldn't you be saying wow so cute
[Music]
i think the
soul patch really brings it together
[Laughter]
release you from your prison
am i really thanks appreciate that okay
hey cronie get in there
does it fit
it's like a unibrow for you
[Laughter]
just go a little bit it's a little bit a
little bit closer it's just like
yeah that's good that's good
nice how's this that looks terrible
[Applause]
what do you mean that's beautiful no
matter which angle
uh oh i just realized i just realized
that all of us going on like these
wintry fun trips and stuff like that
it's so much like those slice of life
animes like no non-glory or some [\h__\h]
when they go to like a sauna or like a
cool wintry place and like all the girls
like
jumping around having fun
[Music]
oh god what is that who did that believe
that we're anime girls man will never
grow up crazy [\h__\h] yeah he found
something bubbled up take a look at this
like what a year older what did that
suck
somebody finally
oh yeah so there's a bunch of there's a
bunch of snow pieces over there you guys
can use
a
cage
i'm coming out of my cage and i've been
doing just fine
[Music]
hello
it's like bearing in the sand but being
buried in the in the snow
see it kind of looks like a taco
cheese
[Music]
cute i like it it's an abomination
well i want to see what they're doing
over
happened to here
sprawling
[Music]
yeah continue what was it
oh guys more like more like
skies
because the sky is tall i mean am i
wrong holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
off the dome
can i drill something small fries
you got something on me oh fries
wow
today
all i did was drink some lemon tea
oh
[Music]
i'm drawing a bear
a bear are you making a rock a teddy
bear
yeah
it's now a reindeer
[Music]
now it's a dragon let me see
oh
are you guys ready i'm going to show you
guys a magic trick
bubba you ready
all right just wait okay
[Applause]
well then we got to get the camera ready
here we go
all right ready bubba all right here we
go i'm gonna count it down in three
two
one
wait bubba are you ready i'm gonna do it
three two
one
go start the sky
[Music]
ah yes
what the gnomes do
they they do magic stuff uh there's only
one other gnomes but don't touch it that
one's special
special hello
it's a secret for now you gotta wait
until until it's time or else the gnome
will murder you
you don't want that right moment can be
foreign
[Music]
because the creator is from finland
yes the the 3d modeler is from finland
and they wanted to recreate their
homeland here and show how beautiful it
is because apparently the people of
finland are very proud of their country
and how cool it is they got the sauna
they got like reindeers and they got the
northern lights it's beautiful
yeah look how pretty
[Music]
oh yeah we'll still be here
it sounds cute
gingerbread i know the word for
gingerbread too actually what is it what
is it
oh my god
[Laughter]
[Music]
we can go gather around the fire if you
guys we could tell some more stories
fire sure
fire
but i'm happy to listen to you guys new
christmas stories
story
no not not scary stuff mom it's okay we
see you kiara
it's less of a scary story
how do i come back
that's funny
blueprint nice
okay cool stuff cool
[Music]
whatever
oh my god your legs
[Laughter]
[Music]
i can't take it she doesn't care for
that one oh hey
[Music]
no
is
[Music]
uh what's next the house yeah i see it
i defeated your house
[Music]
graffiti
i gotta clean it up
oh what does this gnome do i'm gonna
press this one
oh
is this the graffiti you did
yeah
where's the graffiti
oh i see it
yeah that's not too bad actually i like
it
i'm gonna sell it yeah
yeah it's mine now because it's my
property and now i'm gonna sell it for 2
million dollars
what you making
hey hey
what is that
[Music]
okay
is oh is ina back
does ena hold on
can i get oh sorry you know
okay
[Music]
greetings from the golden state
you're sleepy
oh my god i didn't know you could draw
even more on top of it
this had a hard time
getting darker and darker
where did
drinking tea
sipping tea in your hood what the [\h__\h]
is that
are you sure
are you sure some tea and not alcohol
don't mind that
i'm just holding
that's it
i'm just holding it
you're holding it oh it's like why are
you all now why are you all i'm not
eating it this is
judging me
what about the judgment all of a sudden
i'm just holding
i think you can only grab one
oh no
you guys want to check something out
oh my god
[Applause]
give myself the key inside the cage but
i can't get out thanks
this is my secret circle my this is my
safe space right here and you guys can't
enter you can't come in
this is my safe space
all right yeah well it's in his back
it keeps me away from you oh my god
welcome back
to my safe space thank you thank you you
feeling okay drink some water i thought
nobody could go in yeah i got some water
okay you guys want to gather by the
campfire we could tell you guys have any
christmas stories or something all right
this way
oh there's also these big candy canes if
you guys want to pick them up or
something
i guess santa's a candy cane too
candy cane
i wish i could pick to the campfire
if i move like
[Music]
no i want to sit next to taco
there we go
[Applause]
[Music]
i got my chair here i sit down
sharks and stupid
stoop soup sharks and soup ladies
[Music]
oh my gosh kiara you're wearing a
similar dress to me i didn't see that
oh yeah it's kind of like like a mix of
my party whoa i could see your brother
yeah
all right there's a bra oh yeah well
what a small chippy paper
thank god anyway
scooby-doo
finally my wish i'm moving this candy
cane i
does anybody want a hot cocoa we got a
hot cocoa here
[Music]
that's cute there we go fix the whole
chocolate
here who wants a hot chocolate pan
um
oh yeah there's more over here
there you go
this one's for you
thank you thank you
[Music]
a
on marshmallow corners and fonus and
irish horns and then oh
yeah use them to roast
oh hold on there's a don't know there's
a special gnome here
wow
[Music]
cute
we have lights and stuff now it's
christmas
does anybody have any christmas stories
merry christmas
[Music]
please
marry me i have a christmas
[Music]
[\h__\h] up right now
no he looked beautiful
got a big old head
yeah
you too
all right here's my story
once upon a time
in a snowy village
at the north pole
there was a very large man named santa
claus
he wore a red outfit and a red santa hat
and his only joy in this in this lonely
cold dark and despairing world was to
give presents to the little children
essentially he was the giver of all
things hope related
however
someone else someone else could not
could not stand the fact that this this
old gentleman
was giving away presence and hope to the
children so late in the night
hold on there's an ending
when he was on his sleigh she's the end
his reindeer taking him away into the
night
suddenly something very strange happened
it appeared that there was a sabotage to
his sleigh
and suddenly the reindeer were cut from
their reigns and santa was left to fall
to his death but
who was it that came flying out of the
sky to ride on his reindeer and take the
remaining presents to the children
but the one
oh
who could it be it was
[Music]
[Applause]
we need the council to decide her faith
[Music]
now we can do whatever we want to or we
can arrest her
okay
uh
twas the night before christmas
well good are you got a story
[Music]
make a story as you go around things we
used to do in improv classes so
everybody starts off
someone starts off making a story then
everybody adds like a sentence to the
story
yeah it's like
less brain power
[Music]
didn't we didn't we do something like
that for uh the last christmas something
similar it was a mad lib it wasn't yeah
we created the story
with the candy g string remember oh
yeah
okay i remember all right how do we play
how do we start it i want to do it
somebody start
and come up with an intro to the story
so like
start up a story that you would write
and then
say next and then the next person will
continue the stories okay
is there like a word count or something
are you sentence each
it's like yeah it's like a sentence
a sentence or two yeah sentence or two
i'll start
one day there was a snowy night and a
a giant snowball fell down the mountain
and came to life
gouda and upon its giant head rotated
mistletoe and
large lifeless eyeballs
and a tendency to consume the flesh of
humans
and suddenly
you know
suddenly
it grew very muscular snowy arms
very
thin
legs it started marching towards the
city
next
it began its slow yet motivated march
toward the city however it need not walk
because after a while something akin to
a ceiling fan emerged from its head as
it slowly was pulled upward into the sky
and made its way towards the waiting
homes of many children
and families across the nation
next up sauna
okay
ah
a helicopter realized that
it did not make his body anymore
because nobody is perfect
[Laughter]
and yes the body continued moving on its
own without the head
suddenly gaining skills of its own
and it wanted revenge upon the head who
had left it
i think it's the bay next because
[Music]
it's lore
[Laughter]
oh okay hey i'm back i'm back i'm back
what's up what's up
oh can someone paraphrase the story for
you
oh god um there was a sweet little
snowball that like came down the the
mountain and then it turned into a huge
monster that looks like crony and then
it has a helicopter head and then it
came off and it plopped down on the city
and then its body separated from its
head and now it's getting ready to
attack the city
oh that's a horse
um
what did you say fona oh i wanted to get
ribbon oh okay um
in a temps
revenge upon the head
the body looked itself in the mirror and
realized
man she never skipped legs
don't worry about the details
just those are logistics
it matched on crony you too
oh boy tell us your story marched on
to the gym
to
not skip leg day but saw
saw itself in the mirror they thought
oh man
so beautiful
they opened them
and then
it opens its mouth and
and then inside of the mouth
appears a little fairy a little fairy
dressed in santa claus
clothes
mary jumps out out of the mouth
and looks like uh not crowley that did
the monster or whatever looks at the
monster and says
you are beautiful no matter what they
say
and words cannot bring you down
next moon
[Music]
the santa fe
also reminds the monster of how it has
lost its way
and so it abandons his lands for revenge
and takes up a modest job
dude and then it gets to a familiar home
and then
oh is it ending is it ending yeah
again
and this wait who was going to the house
the big monster that like turned into
now
the big monster that turned into a new
leaf
and then he turned a new leaf yeah
very delicious looking stack of cookies
and milk
he couldn't he couldn't
couldn't help but take a bite of the
cookie
the cookie was poisoned
yeah forget your happy ending
so he died
and
everything is all better again
[Music]
sweet and christmassy and wintry and
then as it went around the circle it got
dark
[Laughter]
all right let's go to the trees
[Music]
all right guys can you help me clean
this up we got to get these balls out of
here
all right oh
put my hot cocoa down i ain't got no
balls
now get it out why is it so big get them
out of here
[Music]
put it on camera is it three or one
three
put on camera three
all right you guys ready everybody look
at the tree bay's up there i don't know
if you want to be up there bae you're
not going to see it there's something up
there
all right santa's about to fly over
here we go
everybody
[Music]
all right you guys ready you got to get
off the tree before it before santa
comes to visit or else he'll throw you
in the pit
all right here we go
[Music]
he's so happy
and you guys will see presents don't
open them yet don't open the presents
but every present is labeled so we'll go
uh i guess
i guess we'll start here we'll start
over here at this present whoever's this
first present is
but uh give me a second don't open it
yet whose present is it
bae
oh base present
[Music]
damn connie
what is it
[Music]
[Applause]
it's creepy
scary
[Music]
preface this oh hold on let me tell the
chat really quick okay uh we did a
secret santa where's the camera we did a
secret santa where everybody uh
everybody was assigned one person an en
so there's 11 of us and uh everybody
made a design a sketch for an ornament
to be put on the tree and so this is
bay's ornament right here and everybody
uh made and designed one of these for
each one of us so cali made this one for
bake
yeah
we should have the present opener guess
who it is oh yeah okay we'll do it on
the next one yeah that's a good idea
again the next one who's the next who's
the next president
though
yeah you can put it on the tree put it
in the tree got my vibes on it
oh nice
[Music]
all right next up we have a green box
who's this for
i think it's it might be fun is it for
you mommy
it's movies
i think the box opens from the other
side if you want to go on the other side
um
what's inside what's inside
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah who do you think did it
who do you think made that one
it's kind of hard to guess huh
i have absolutely no idea
i said
it was yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
how do i how do i make it
not like this oh you can rotate it with
i j k
[Music]
[Laughter]
a little bit
yeah you can spray i'm joking you can
spread it out
[Music]
oh whose box is this i think it's
santa's next
[Music]
oh
i want to see you closer
cute let me see your routine adorable
inside oh who do you think made this one
i love that
you mean inside space
inside and then we're going to rotate it
i don't know how you made this one
right here
yeah it showed the camera
did you make this oh did you make this
on it no i didn't it wasn't me
[Music]
are you putting on the tree
i'm gonna put it i'm gonna put it high
up okay
there she goes
yeah up in space
it's side yeah that's the one oh wait i
can't open it
[Music]
all right next up who's next
[Applause]
oh yeah yeah it does i can see that
[Music]
who do you think made it fonda
who made that one
she's so adorable
[Music]
no
no i can't make something so cute
sure your art is adorable
thank you
cute
who made it i think it's basically that
baymax
[Music]
yeah i can kind of see it there
like a ceremony and put it in a tree
[Music]
nice
adorable you thank you iris
[Music]
whose box is this over here we got
another one
let's see what's inside
oh
oh wow
adorable wow this is so close
it's got a little irish
[Music]
what do you think who who would have
known
who would have known who made this it
was santa
myself
[Music]
no i didn't make this one
no i didn't make it
it's from your koh hai
[Music]
[Applause]
oh put it on the tree
[Music]
that's so cute
okay i got another box over here
it looks like
blue
grommets oh
[Music]
oh that's true it's not rainbow just
make your rainbow
stone cute you're gonna put it on the
tree oh yeah who who made it
[Music]
no it wasn't me
who could have made this beautiful
little thing
ami no it wasn't me
[Music]
i was already worried about when i saw
everyone else's i thought mine was so
lame no
no it's got the chains
it's got the two chains
[Music]
looking a little naked maybe we can put
some on the right side
okay should be like
herself just a mini version
put yourself up on the tree yeah
[Music]
and we got more boxes over here
yeah
open it hi
[Music]
santa
i wonder who made that one i wonder how
long it took him to grow up
[Music]
yeah i could see that oh it's like a
cream
who made this one
[Music]
no it wasn't me it wasn't me
was it
wasn't you
no
[Music]
is
masterpiece
i like this
this should be santa instead would you
want to play something cute
into the beautiful night
so suspicious you wanna so
i guess this is my box take a day off on
christmas thank you
[Music]
uh i don't think you can close it but uh
could i just close your eyes you didn't
see it good at what's in the box
gonna open the box whoa she opened it
oh wow
that's the thing we're building
minecraft
oh sorry i grabbed it i'm sorry
[Music]
it's got a mini good in it i think i'm
getting a good look at it
[Music]
no i didn't make it now
no
someone really talented must have made
that one homie was the last one i think
no
oh i haven't really been playing
[Music]
oh
it's so cute it's so cool
[Music]
very cool
i want to get a close-up of it
yeah
everything yeah
is graphic design your passion perhaps
that fake design is real some man with
the cans on their head and blue
thank you for the interview
all right very much this way
is this a watson box yeah
what's in what's in the box
i actually i haven't what's in the box
like i've i handled mostly everybody's
um like stuff oh then i just moved this
i handled everybody's like uh sketches
and stuff and i gave them to the
modelers but i haven't seen this one so
it's a really it really is a surprise oh
and what is this
what is that
it's got pepperonis or something like
this it's purple it's macaroni
oh yeah it's actually it looks so
is this garlic bread is this a chip what
is this
ah
it's really cute i know who made this
oh where is she
where is she
good
this is cute
it's really cute yeah
thank
i think maybe i should cook it first
into boiling water and you get some
fresh pasta
that's true yeah your hair gets super
soft yeah maybe the center is just a big
ball of cheese
yummy yeah i like the chip yeah it looks
tasty thank you
thank you
it is garlic bread i knew it christmas
um
i guess here's like right here is a good
spot right there
i guess this one's mine looks like a me
box
okay to cali here we go
open sesame side
[Applause]
hold on give me give me the one
hold on i can't reach it
oh
oh i can drink this just as it is
delicious
very well crafted is this from sana
oh oh no it doesn't mean
really watson you made this i made it
how'd you know it oh because he's doing
the process of elimination
thank you
this is
amazing oh thank you
i'm glad you liked it i grabbed this
bonkers i love it it's bonkers
oh [\h__\h] i fell down
in the eye only mine is left yeah it's
so good i'm putting a tree
[Music]
it's so so cute with the light
wait who's left who didn't i don't i'm
not sure it's only one person
[Music]
oh
yeah
i think so huh
[Music]
right there
merry christmas
[Music]
chrysler okay
here
yeah that's perfect
[Music]
yeah the tree is finished
oh it's actually really cool
it turned out so cute
[Music]
what a christmas miracle yeah
yeah let's take a picture we could do it
i guess we can't use the mirror because
the mirrors kind of messed up
all the markers and stuff
[Music]
what if you guys if you guys look over
here if you guys
oh
would you like this one oh yeah yeah
ah the freaking maybe there's a way to
move the marker stuff hold on give me
one second guys
i'm sorry it wasn't me
of course not i believe
i where do i put the camera here
[Music]
oh thank you
i feel like
all right that's all right we can do it
with the we can do with the camera even
though it'll look scuffed in the mirror
we got the camera
it's okay
all right i'll just put the camera over
here
[Music]
oh we got the b camera already
all right guys that this the stream view
is is clear so we
we still get a good view but it's
beautiful it's perfect
oh is it a little it's a little hold on
it's a little high let me fix the camera
one second it's like a old film camera i
got to fix the sound is so small sonic
you could fit in the middle right here
or not on the tree yeah
i can fit on that trail
nice
looks good
bubba looks
good okay yeah
all right uh
oh cheers
well then i'm gonna get on the camera on
the tree
cheers oh cute
[Music]
a little better too
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you guys thank you for making the
ornaments and stuff cheers
merry christmas
yeah thank you everybody
[Music]
no it's not over but we can gather over
by this side
yeah christmas is not over yet all right
we'll gather over here
on this side of the tree
[Music]
yeah
and we actually i have a small
announcement before our big announcement
so we can gather in front of the tree
like just like we were
um actually this vr chat world will be
available publicly for everybody in the
community to use so it's like a gift for
everybody yeah
and it'll be available um on the 23rd on
wednesday uh so you guys can come
explore the studio the halloween map the
winter wonderland and of course the you
know the default map and we'll push
updates when when uh we need to update
you know maybe council could get some
rooms or something someday huh
that'd be cool yeah yeah
yeah
and um we have another announcement is
it time yet actually let me see
uh i guess
i mean we're a little early we got four
minutes but um
should we no problem it's good yeah
who wants to announce it i think kiara's
good at announcing stuff kara you want
to announce it
oh god oh god no not me please i don't
even know okay
okay i'll do it
looks like that guys so home live
english who live english has created a
special song cover of the classic
christmas song the 12 days of christmas
and it's gonna be
premiering
in 20 minutes i believe it the link will
be up so you guys can watch the premiere
of it has all uh 11 of us and yeah look
forward to it today
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah um well do you guys have any
closing thoughts any closing thoughts
thank you for making my christmas every
year
okay i got an announcement
okay
[Music]
on my channel on the 22nd uh like
depends on your time zone but for most
time zones is the 22nd december
wednesday we're also doing a stream
about it so yeah please check it out the
rest yeah
up about 24 hours before
oh yeah i don't want to check it out
nice
all right
exciting a lot of things a lot of
presents for everybody
yeah yeah definitely big presents i
actually have presents as well
giving back to the audience
yeah 24th and 25th i have special
presents that are going to be uploaded
to my channel oh um so please check them
out there are three of them they're a
series um and then also during my
christmas party um which is happening uh
about
uh it's happening tomorrow it's more
than 24 hours though
during that party i'm going to uh give
you guys a small visual preview of an
original song i've been working on with
someone here
please come be there to check out check
it out uh it's going to be cool i hope
that you're excited
but
it's one image
it's an it's an animated but we're going
to show you it
um it's uh it's cool it's a cool song
that's your head
exciting it's a cool song yeah exciting
yay please look forward to it that's all
i have merry christmas everyone happy
holidays merry christmas
happy holidays anybody else have
anything else they want to say closet
closing thoughts
no there's a mustache inside your head i
have one short one
oh crony okay what is it
yeah i just wanted to say um
i'm really glad to have met everyone
this year
we can have what no and i hope we can
have fun more fun next year yeah
[Music]
that was really nice yeah i feel the
same way it's very wholesome
[Music]
i'm glad you guys had fun
thank you a huge shout out to the
developer and seafoam and the vr chat
team who have been working like day
after day punching in hours getting
everything working and looking really
cool and working well so thank you guys
for giving this present to us and also
the community yeah thank you team thank
you
[Music]
it's really fun for me thank you most
importantly i'm happy that you guys had
fun
thank you
thanks to you my dude
i'm really glad you guys have fun yeah
the year's closing out and you know last
year we closed out with only the five of
us and now there's 11 of us so i'm
really glad that we could do this
together and you know there's this whole
week there's a bunch of cool streams you
guys are doing
so you know you guys in the audience
make sure to check them out everybody's
doing christmas streams and stuff so
make sure to check them out and happy
holidays happy new year thank you
everybody for watching
all right we'll say goodbye now bye
thank you for watching everybody
bye
[Music]
um
you