[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
we did it we did it
feeling good after that wait
already in the game i thought we wanted
to show like the characters off and then
again
you want me to get out of the game would
you like me to exit the game
it's not even i'm outside the gate no
hold on how do i get out of this
okay kelly open no that's why you're
afraid
let me get out of this world hug the
gate
how do i get out of here how do i exit
what the [\h__\h] wait
no it's not fair i'm still in the
freaking loading
hang on all right disconnect do it
we played this game before a while ago
but back then we played it with
normal characters however one of the kfp
members called
zero duke has made
mods for all of us as you can see we're
using them
um each of our characters are now modded
into the game and each character has
like
not only these cute outfits but also
like special like skills and
and and i don't know funny interactions
they can do
yeah yeah i mean glutam doesn't have
much power
well go watch someone else's stream guys
little
i'm pretty much and uh i think every
character also has a little
variation for example here i can take
off my hats and it says i agree but i
also don't understand a famous quote by
takanas tikiana
[Laughter]
i'm not sure if the taking off the hats
or whatever uh
changes your skills but anyway i'm gonna
go with the regular clothes
what about you why am i saying oh no
halo
cute
[Laughter]
this is how we're going to do things
from now like this is really cute too
like yeah why why is it when i take your
hat off
all it says is onion what does that mean
guys we have noticed that when i take
off my hats
um i look like an orange onion you know
ah that is true i could see that
wow oh by the way
the announcements will be um at the end
of the stream but we won't play for too
long so don't worry guys
just play around with the characters
yeah
okay let's test them out welcome oh my
gosh thank god someone else is here huh
stop it
if i'm close to cali then she loses
sanity when i'm too close
which is pretty ingenious i think we've
turned it off
[Music]
too close cause they're 20.
you know the
this is so cute
yes
okay
juice you got to pick up flowers and
that will help your green juice get
bigger
can you eat more brain this is adorable
you can eat seeds and berries but
if you build a crock pot it's like
better because you make full meals
open bubba can i open bubba yeah you can
open it
[Music]
no i got a i found a turkey
guys i found a turkey my mom
i can go into water but i get weaker or
something wait how did you go into the
water
[Music]
they're aquatic oh but i can't go there
get what
it's okay thanks
[Music]
yes i got the turkey guys i killed a
turkey die
frog i got so many turkey legs yeah look
at all these turkey legs i got guys
kill frogs no i have five left i'm gonna
die
i'm gonna die all right no
no it's okay thank you
yeah i got you guys i got you guys uh i
killed the turkey and now the frogs are
killing me
probably i mean kind of i'm i'm kind of
i'm okay okay boston kind of revived me
somebody revived me
i'm not fighting on birthdays i'm really
proud of chasing that turkey down okay
listen
thank you
i'm not dead but i'm really not doing
great what's with all the frogs y'all
is it is this because of chiata i am
frog did they like make it spit a ton of
frogs spawn around us
oh you stir it what's happening cool
down
wait where did my berries are it's gotta
be it's gotta because it's buddy's fault
a hundred percent
oh frog
because of your i am frog that's why all
these frogs are here i swear it's
written into the coating
and frog yeah exactly it's all your
fault
do i have to win
[Laughter]
another
[Music]
let's haunt the girls here i am here let
me look at you oh that's so cute
everyone has their own like individual
little picture
girl's got a floaty too that's so cute
what about me what do i have i can't
look at myself
oh where are you girls i want to show
you my ghost form
you yeah i can do
soul strike i need to reap more to do
that
i don't know how to use my ground pound
i want to see the watson ground pound
[Music]
too close kirsten too close wait kiara
carrick you can be like
stuff ghost yeah
like if you try to possess this grass
you set it on fire
i can't everybody
wow that's cool it's getting a little
bit late so i'm going to head back
oh does anybody have wood
[Music]
we made a really awesome pot before i'm
kind of i'm thinking about it again it
was a crock pot
don't go away um
oh okay on fire just your bad normally
oh
i guess i can do that i've been killed
how do i get tentacles
what what i have
everybody's built with great power great
responsibility
i'll pick somebody can i revive normally
pick a separate
give this to me um you could try on the
gate maybe
but it depends doesn't do anything ah
whoa i want to get some wood
when i break that next to cali some more
no stop there's some oh
i found a mole stop too close because
it's already easy
i can't actually hit this with my scythe
that's unfortunate it's very accurate
you can't just chop trees with the side
they're made for soil how do i get in
health back
uh i have an injection i can give you if
you would like what's the concussion
i have 20 health it's counting up
all right go to the cover your board
when you're burning
okay i'm going to start
look at
yes here you go ina drop wait hold a
drop
it's right there thank you you're
welcome
what the [\h__\h] wait was that supposed to
heal me
uh the water can come true
i just sent me on earlier with cali
i can't remember i'm ghost forever
i see it taco
[Music]
and there is light just like my future
all right so let me see i can probably
look at it you need to tactile you can
make that good
you can make a rabbit trap and you can
lead the frog into the rabbit trap and
die nice idea uh i want to make rabbit
traps because
i actually i was getting pretty good at
that before actually
how about a fishing rod yeah grass and
twigs
fishing around you need um you need
spider webs i was thinking good i would
be good with that
we need to find gold so if anybody has
gold or
things
[Music]
i shall go hunting hunting is my
specialty your mushroom wait you can't
come back to life
i did it i came back to live once but
now i die i
died again and now i have a super long
cooldown so i'm just waiting for the
cooldown
but then everyone has to come to lunch
so you see how i revive you have to see
it
okay i want to see tell me hang on it's
maybe
maybe 60 seconds left i'm coming over
i'm on my way i want to see christmas
what do you revive i would like to have
a buddy
but you have to have a safe distance
like social bases
because everything around me will burn
okay got it
just like that one time in minecraft
i'm gonna die for this i'm too hungry
who would have thought watching
concoction wouldn't heal you who would
have thought
which is make thought it's i'm here
three two i'm it
three two one
cake oh my god
[Music]
i need flowers oh no i'm sorry i'm sorry
my dog
you need assistance watson i can send
you to a better place
are you dead forever
you guys i have to guide you oh my god i
have to find
a touchstone so you have to explore or
you'll have to build a
resurrection heart what you need for
swamp habitat
okay are there monsters in the water
i think there's monsters in the ocean
but not in the rivers i'm going to make
a torches
i want to get like my sword but i would
probably die okay
oh i don't think so can i hurt them
but i really need something i mean you
chose something
oh
[Music]
yeah that'll definitely help
i was really proud of that i was
really proud of
hp are you scared by any chance to die
oh wow holy there's a lot of spiders
over here
and a goal spider webs come over here
get me spider webs
all right i'm gonna go lazy mushroom
okay i'm i'm west
can i just eat the frog legs
i'm fading quickly i'm just gonna eat it
oh my god
oh i dropped some food if you guys need
to eat it i dropped carrots and berries
thanks because i'm really not feeling
great okay
where's where are you oh mary um
[Music]
linton logs i
i only have one full of them today
okay oh never mind i didn't need to do
that
my body it's a nice skeleton
nevermind
a really nice skeleton there's nothing
there to eat i'm gonna put stuff on the
fire
oh good idea i got some carrots
although you can see me right yeah i can
see
[Music]
because if there's a ghost nearby it'll
like lower yourself oh wait
really yo i didn't know that happened
the insects are so cute with the things
that make very
so adorable i love you
my sanity is going down we know that's
because of a ghost oh really is it
really no it's from i think they turn it
off though
it's from a ghost it just goes down that
phone from amelia's ghosts
[Laughter]
oh nice nice thank you
it looks fine
spider webs i see some off in the
distance we need this gold here
yeah we also you get that and then okay
uh you can
set up rabbit traps for the spiders oh
cool
okay awesome i'm really not doing it
oh
i killed it and then you know what
i pick up so with this spider glad
you can make health styles if you burn
like small stuff and make ash and you
can mix it with the spider glands to
make like a booster
shot oh my god leave
[Music]
fine
no wait don't pick it up put it down
no i'm gonna die i'm getting sleepy
oh wait can i not actually die because
i'm dead you're immortal
oh
[Music]
we won't get any of the spider web from
later glenn
[Applause]
oh
i have a trap i'm gonna use it i just
i need to wake up and eat first it needs
to be the first thing i do
or else i die immediately
i just want to eat
[Applause]
you guys
okay
oh
[Music]
wake up there's some gold nuggets
i'm scared not yet not yet i know you're
hungry but
why do i keep falling asleep okay hold
on we're fine
we'll be back we'll be back to tango
with the spiders i just need to go back
to
pick up the ground
for now this pick up the spider webs if
you see any those are useful
yeah i got a lot of those i'm gonna make
a fire
the same as stones
oh i can make an axe oh i can make a pic
ooh i can make a
camera i'm scared um
why are you scared i used to go wait
you being near me is lowering my sanity
i hate the
i mean if you cook it it's okay
oh wow there's a really big oh my gosh
attack the crawling horror can i hit it
with my soul scythe
my soul strike and there i go
and there i go
[Applause]
i can see all the beasts they're
everywhere
oh yeah it's funny it takes a lot to
lower my sanity
kind of sick that i can't die though
like that's
radical i don't want to be alone on the
half year anniversary come on
that's like a double whammy on my
insanity
if we didn't turn it off
so many creepy monsters
gosh they're everywhere all right you
guys are good
what else can i make i think we're all
gonna die
probably
science machine hey i can make a science
machine
should i make that like we're actually
trying to accomplish much today we're
just trying to showcase these
and then have some announcements so it's
okay we don't
[Music]
okay
i mean i'm still here but that's because
i have to be
i can revive in like five minutes
just give me five minutes i'll save all
of you maybe we should
really timeline yeah
[Music]
i want to go hunting
should i come to youtube
uh i don't think i can be saved anymore
i'm a little uh
i'm a little uh dead can i
[Music]
maybe we should have like a like a ghost
meeting
um what do you call it like
[Music]
am i doomed to just be alone in this
universe because i can't die
yeah why is kelly still sleeping it's
because i'm deaf
coming back yeah
just wait for me okay i'll wait for you
give me those seats
all right i just want these seeds good
morning
really quick give me the seeds please
please
[Music]
oh my god you just got this shark cat on
top of you that's so funny that one's
fast
yeah it's blowing me in the swim yes
i can swim
[Music]
girls tried it
oh
[Music]
if we find a thing in the map called a
touchstone or
we have to make um these revive potions
thingies but yeah it's gonna be hard
with me because i continue to kind of go
to sleep over and over again which is
the
which is actually kind of worse than not
being able to die
so that's fine i like how the frog right
next to you it's like that's me
yeah and you're also right next to me
away with you
is still alive having a really bad time
oh those are enos
anything though yes i am dead
[Music]
i'm just living off of seeds to be
honest at this point
my health is still in my body
welcome back to the land of living
running like not a problem in the world
look at you
i am invincible oh that's so cool your
book
oh you're punk
where's my sword where am i going to
keep picking no flowers
i lost my sense of direction where's my
goal where's my sword
is that oh yes you killed him
[Music]
what happens again uh you start going
crazy and start seeing monsters then
they start attacking you and then you
die
oh okay cool this is like
i'm gonna lure a spider here what how is
this like my spiders
come here because most of the games
yeah and you have to click a lot hi come
here dummy
i can clean up yeah
i know you want something
is
oh yeah it does look like this must be
there okay there's a lot of flowers over
here but there's a lot of
also deadly bees if anyone wants sanity
yeah
my sword
[Music]
are there like caves and stuff in this
game um
i think there are caves in single player
but because of the way caves work
it's not easy
okay it's getting late so i'm gonna head
back but i got a bunch of i got a bunch
of [\h__\h]
where i am now yeah oh
yeah yeah yeah how do i drop it again i
picked picked up to try this oh wow kuda
is not gonna revive anymore anyway so
i'm just gonna use it
maybe we can find a touchstone we should
do that try to look for a touchstone it
looks like a coffin
uh surrounded by a sticks with pig heads
on it
oh no those are my seeds
[\h__\h] oh are they nearby or typically
it's like random you found them
that's all right wait don't don't use it
if we keep playing
oh i'm not using it at all don't worry
i'm just keeping it safe because
uh you are a ghost
i'm gonna recharge it oh that's good oh
my god you can recharge it but i think
you need like some electric to do that
or something
oh i do that i found this and this is
good
oh i can make that i have some gold
actually yeah yeah yeah
are you like at the bottom of the top
where the [\h__\h]
i have lost my [\h__\h] way the way
you're going in if you keep going
straight past that water and you keep
going
you'll see it's this one there okay i'm
gonna google it
how about we all just die hmm
oh no okay okay it's really bad all
right
what should i do tell me what i must do
what we need is um
spider glands do you have any of those
yeah i killed a bunch of [\h__\h] spiders
okay okay um what next
okay if you have spider glands we need
three grass and if you
go into like the tabs on the left side
you should see a heart
okay it's called the telltale hearts and
you should be able to make one it's
gonna take some hp and you'll die
okay then you can resurrect one of us
with the heart sure thing
yeah i got your bag demon show yourself
and i'm gonna die yeah basically the
rings and i died enough but is this
what's this payback is that why you
followed me the whole time i'm hungry no
hang on where is this where's the
goddamn fence
all right i'm going to sleep again i'll
do it it's just i can't find my way back
so
that's okay yeah just just haunt me for
a while i'm gonna
protect you i think it's kind of strange
though that my sanity goes down when
seeing ghosts considering who i am but
it's fine it's just a little oversight
just a little oversight
yeah i love that the book
those should boost your sanity instead
yeah give me strength you like collect
souls yeah exactly i love seeing this
video
take away sanity from other people yeah
oh yeah
we're so hungry
can i eat this
[Laughter]
i need to build a fire really quick if i
cook the meat
then it'll be fine i can definitely make
those things
two ghosts walk into a pie what do what
do they do
what's grass without
oh my god
i have no grass that's the problem you
know it's really hard to think of jokes
like that in english because it's not my
main language no not my mother tongue so
i never like to praise myself i'm proud
of you i'm so proud of you
hey guys a little problem okay
close to the gate really close to the
gate because i died there and i dropped
it so there's a there's a spider gland
there
hey guys i have a little problem so i
want to help you
but when i open the tab i don't see any
heart or anything like that
uh it should be under survival the news
oh it's under survival okay got it
good news
i need ashes that's the problem is that
i need ashes and actually i need to go
kill more spiders
i will revive you guys leave it to me
just i need to make sure that i alright
okay
all right gotcha no no wait is it
nothing
this one pick
some of us should have a ton of grass
because i picked up a bunch oh really
there should be some here by the heat
yes all right
there's a turkey there's a turkey i'm
going to kill it really quick
thank you how do i open this
right here
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh we need one spider glam per person so
there's another spider going on spiders
too
all right i'm gonna go beat up some
spiders then i need to get back to the
gate first that's my problem wait wait
hello
uh yes i do but it's not marked on there
oh wait i can see where everyone is
though
yeah yeah okay and it's raining
how do i make one potion is it in
survival
yeah it's in survival it's called
telltale heart and it's going to take a
smoking cookie so it's probably going to
kill you
oh cool oh my god
you can raise one of us if you use it on
us you know you want to go first okay
you can go first you're you're more
knowledgeable what is this okay come
here i'll revive you because i'm phoenix
this is this is where we're fitting here
we go
what's your stuff
there's so much [\h__\h] around here okay
that's okay because we have
spider web yes
i'll give it you can make it you can you
make it
here you go so you want um
who wants to come back you know
[Music]
no problem not that much i'm gonna eat
it anyways
[Music]
more spiders do we need to kill more
spiders
um is there a gland yeah
there's a gland in this spider nest it's
gonna be dark soon though so
yeah maybe tomorrow does anybody have
two stones
i have four rocks i don't know if that
counts as stones oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
here yeah oyster drop
there you go thank you yep little lady
we have that one and then just vibing
yeah okay fine i'll go pick up out um
can we do a group picture once good eye
is back alive i want to do a group
picture with everyone
yeah too close green
there's no too close there's no such
thing as being too close slippy get away
[Applause]
oh we also i'm also losing sanity
because of good ass though oh my god
oh no wait no it's going up wait it's
going up
oh it's going up actually cause we're by
the fire yeah right oh okay
oh yeah right okay guy here
how old are you mother f wording
meredith
oh there's that ashes
we got that okay okay okay we can go all
right let's
do it let's protect come out
with my life yeah i have a tendency
from there saying it right when i got an
accident
huh
[Music]
okay
god damn it come here all right does
anybody have over 40 hp
i do oh i can carry it over
two glands then we can raise kiara with
the heart oh like don't be alive oh i
couldn't important
announcements oh my goodness can we do
it in four minutes
yeah yeah we can if we pick up the other
glam
and the nest can anybody revival yes
i got one okay oh okay nice okay we have
two okay yeah
and then i have enough grass and i have
i have ashes as well don't we do we need
ashes
uh well if we were to keep playing we
would need them because then we could
use it to heal
to make it like oh i see oh that's right
you have the healing one okay
never mind then all right i'm gonna drop
my [\h__\h] here
okay okay let's see here's the gland
oh you shot it ah
oh here i'll drop it i'll drop it on the
ground for you so here you go
all right yeah do you have grass
[Applause]
cannon in three seconds i think you know
okay don't do it over here go somewhere
else
okay okay so you know let's get it and
then good luck with me
three two
[Applause]
it got shut okay it's fine yeah it takes
hp
now red is good enough i need to heal i
meant for his feet
here
just give him the heart i'll kill the
frogs lead them
you just click on it and give it to
graham if you can catch me
oh whoa
[Music]
okay
careful there's a frog here again sorry
i'll kill it wow that's going back
i'm back on hp almost oh my god oh my
god
yay we did it
okay everybody press y okay and then
when in the typing box you can type
forward slash dance and we can all line
up and we can all dance at the same time
forward slash all right
ready for the photo yes
i'm gonna get a little bit covered up
from this knife oh sorry
what is this let's line up maybe there's
a different way to get in the line right
here
okay next stop all right are we lying
next to me hmm
oh to the right like this yeah you might
have to rotate your perspective if
uh like you know oh we can't yeah
we're insane
[Music]
thank you thank you
slide okay
everyone it is the whole live english
myth half year anniversary unbelievable
but it's been six months can you believe
it guys oh my god
wow crazy not so nice
yay exciting yes so of course we
prepared
uh some things for you many things
actually yeah and we hope you will like
it
yeah and we will
start off with uh the second slide
everyone move on to the second song
okay
english myth acrylic stains merchandise
merchandise english myth
mascot penta keychain
[Music]
stand yes
absolute standing standing perfect okay
so with these stands
um you can buy them separately or you
can buy them together
i say buy them together so that way we
can all be together and we won't get
lonely and we won't miss one another do
not separate
these on your table you can put this on
your desk above your bed
you can get creative and then send us i
guess send those pictures about how you
plan on displaying them that would be
really fun
yeah hopefully you think they'll be
life-sized
[Music]
slide everyone and uh it's being
introduced by inna
yes let's go this is our second merch
it's gonna be our mascot penta keychain
the five in one key chain you get all of
those charms at once yeah
yeah it's gonna be um put on a leather
strap i think and it's gonna the leather
strap is gonna have the hollow life
english logo
uh yes very cute five in one what a deal
adorable
[Music]
um the key chain is it's possible that
we won't have like a second
um like a second wave of orders so
only one way of avoiding getting mother
hut
yes yeah yeah if you want to get them
the first time
yeah it's not completely
impossible but prob probably no
yeah yes the page to buy these will show
up at booth
at uh 5 p.m pst
at which is 8 30 p.m est yeah soon
soon in 30 minutes from now on yeah yes
it will be on geeksback
and on booth both and just follow check
the official twitter for the links and
uh
the announcements that's it
you would think you would think
however oh it's my turn
okay well i guess um um
it's it's i'm supposed to uh introduce
this one but
we uh have a little it's actually more
of um
sorry big stretch it's actually uh
um we're gonna let it do uh the talking
itself
it's a video and then talk about it
afterwards indeed
um so anyway i guess we'll go ahead and
kind of count it down but uh
you guys um you guys will all get to see
in real time with us
is something real special something real
special coming
extra soon okay so everyone
shut up i'm gonna mute you guys really
quick okay and it's accounting
i'm counting
oh right okay so maybe well i mean i'm
just gonna i'm just gonna mute you guys
yeah after countdown okay so let's count
down from four
and then click on go okay it's very
important just click on go okay okay
all right so ready okay four
three two
one go
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
we're back that was uh ready to paint
the next slide
yes indeed let's go let's move right
along to the next one
so this is
an image soundtrack for whole life
english myth
yeah yeah all of us got our own very
special
our own very special uh i guess image uh
bgm made for us it's instrumental um
i think we'll actually probably be using
them in streams i know i will at least
um as vgm that was kind of the intention
but you guys can also get it for
yourselves as well releasing everywhere
march 14th local time for you wherever
you are
2021 so uh get it or be
be square be circle get it please i beg
of you it's so dope a lot of people ask
but yeah there's no vocals there's a bgm
yes
and it's like i can't hear cali
yeah i was like oh man am i going to rap
to this like oh okay
it's bgm but still hey it's dope i love
it um
and all tracks are made by uh camellia
yay thank you
super [\h__\h] sticky incredible every
track really
uh suits each person so i think we maybe
want to get a little give a little
comment what do you think about your
song callie
freaking dope when i heard it for the
first time i was like wow this is like a
combination of um
everything that i think makes up me it's
got like this kind of regal
and like um almost like a gothic tone to
it i guess dark
mysterious but it's also [\h__\h]
dope i don't know it's uh it's gangster
there's a little bit of hip hop in there
yeah i like i can bob my head to it
which is why
the title is really good um
that's not good it's perfect for me what
about you guys
and my second track is mine yeah and
it's i love how the title uh actually
um is like for it stands for kfp it's
kiana fry fry
but it's also like you can also say like
at the party you can be like oh i get i
get all the
other popular kids and the clubs are
like i get i get i'll get boys
my song is uh my phone is pretty
energetic pretty happy
pretty kawaii cute bobby poppy puppy
style
perfect so i'm really excited to um have
that being played in the kfp
stores all over the world worldwide
franchise obviously so it's going to be
played in every store
for until we all die yes
yeah of course the first track is the
enos jack
yes uh i really like mine because it has
like kind of like the oriental feel
and it's like really chill and i can
listen to it like forever on loop
i probably will i really really really
like it
[Music]
thank you thank you either too i was
bopping to it while i was playing while
i was playing i was like oh that's
so good yeah
and the fourth track is i think goodness
track right
shark adventure with that delicious
absolutely delicious finger looking good
baseline
i get the i get the snake face every
time i hear it the first time i heard
that
i was
the rhythm gamer senses
you gotta play it very loud get that
baseline to full potential
it's like super funky in your song
it's so funky it's got the i think it's
the shamasan maybe
also it's got the hall my favorite
instrument shaman
and the bass line and i melt when i hear
it and then i i dance to the beat i'm
just i'm in love with it i'm over the
heels
over the moon over the hill
these are real old
yeah the last one is mine and it sounds
like a pop
yeah it sounds i don't know it kind of
sounds like a nostalgic like it almost
sounds like a song from like an older
game
this is really nice it's called miss
tvis like mistress you guys
yeah i love all the tracks like i'm
gonna be having it on loop
for five months i want all of them all
of them in my playlist
immediately yes slam dunk them into my
place
i think it's the first time that like
some like whole live members like
release
like just like background oh oh ost like
kind of music just the soundtrack
normally everyone releases songs with
their singing in it but we
we're going to do things a little bit
different right i mean would be cool
if one day we also have songs together
where we're actually singing
maybe something for now take this
song image soundtrack means like image
soundtrack just means like
that i think yeah like
yeah it's like concept art but like yeah
like music
exactly your life's if you have your if
your life had a bgm
that reminds me one of my goals was
actually to make vgm for all of you guys
but it looks like i got beaten to the
punch
maybe someday yeah it's like the album
cover i'm just looking at it now it's
like a shield and then it has his size
and like the tentacles and yeah
the middle is my shield is like in the
middle protecting all of you from danger
yeah yeah yeah speaking
of like another portal yeah
it's super surreal i like it this is the
portal that leads you into the darkness
the rabbit hole of her life
with that being said i know we're all uh
very excited but there is actually
one more thing why not
whoa really yet okay after my drum roll
that you guys can show okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
we renamed it very recently actually the
reason
why i asked my viewers like two weeks
ago or three weeks ago for a name is for
this
and we named it kotori
which is
my last name normally is read as koto
di so it has two
ways to read it so actually we write it
differently for this one but
actually my takanashi can be right is
kotori too funny
funny thing cute that's cute and it
looks like a little feather at the top
too it's got to happen
[Music]
it's perfect and then uh we have bubba
and blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
it's
like a anime it's like the it's like an
anime scene like a battle scene where
it's like
[Music]
it looks like he's about to commit very
very very very illegal crimes
as the darkness comes blue nothing for
him
[Laughter]
i'm so excited please coming soon
let's do a balancing contest who can
balance them on top of each other
yeah yeah no cheating no cheating you
have to there can't be any support
around them
you just need to be on top of each other
winner gets
you know my endless love and affection
maybe if i feel like it
yeah i designed all of them and
um thank you
[Music]
they're gonna be very thick right
they're gonna be round and thick
i'm looking forward to my thick fat ass
burp i'm
um i'm excited to grill it grill yeah
i think if you burn it i don't think
it'll come back yeah probably not
maybe don't do that i want all of them
i'm gonna put all of them on my bed
well yeah so that is uh key chains that
then the
acrylic stands and then the album
[Music]
will be posted on twitter and i think uh
if you're not on twitter then maybe
we'll do community pros or i don't know
probably also going to be on the under
hello live
um maybe i don't know hmm but if you if
you're not on twitter i'll probably put
a link in my description in the future
streams maybe the other girls will do
that too yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah you got it
thank you thank you thank you
thank you i had so much fun drawing them
also
please look forward to it thank you very
nice
well then that was pretty much it thank
you everyone
uh for joining in on the streams today
for celebrating together with
us does anyone here have some individual
announcements that have nothing to do
with the merchandise then do it now
yeah um so basically
first i just want to say to everyone uh
thanks so much for your support in the
chat
super chats will be read next time next
time okay
so look forward to that uh at the in the
just chatting and also um
my my new ep is coming out very soon
um yeah on april 4th
my birthday yes that's right it's coming
out on my birthday uh so please
anticipate it
um i'm working really hard on it and you
can actually pre-order it
um as well uh you can check my twitter
for the link i'm gonna go ahead and
retweet it again after this
you can pre-order a physical copy get
special stickers
um and it does ship overseas um
and uh yeah if you don't want to get a
physical copy because
overseas shipping is uh kind of scary i
understand that
um you can just go ahead and stream it
as well it'll be coming to all streaming
platforms
um on the same day yeah exactly so
so you guys can check it out there um
please please check it it would really
it would really make my day and make my
birthday really happy if you could at
least
uh get give it a shot give it a little
listen just a little listen you know
um it would make me think forever yes
so yeah look forward to it that's the
only announcement that i have for now
and also
i have announcements everyone can also
just say a nice message
so move on with ame yes ah
yeah uh yeah i wanted to like talk a
little bit like about how six months
have been for us and stuff like that
uh for me i don't know how life has been
like kind of life-changing
and i know a lot of you guys too it's
like so much work
and i don't know i'm really grateful to
be with you guys too because i think
everybody like we just contribute so
much to
the group in general and
everybody also who worked on hololive
like behind the scenes and stuff all
this stuff
too everybody puts in so much work so i
want to thank you guys for six months
and more months to come and we'll do it
again on the one year anniversary
we'll have more stuff thank you guys so
much for the past six months i really
appreciate it i don't have any
announcements other than that
thank you okay
i would like to announce i love you all
for a better generation you got me dance
like
i'm gonna announce something
yeah six months past oh no i'm
seeing the ceiling's about to leak but
oh yeah
thank you let's do our best from now on
too
yeah love you all and thank you
thank you for all everyone's hard work
emotional that's all i would like to
also say
oh my god say
thank you to this absolutely incredible
team of the most lovely people my gen
mates that have changed my life for the
better
oh
i'm really lucky to be surrounded by
such really great people
did you write down a letter
to you guys each one of you you've been
so incredible in this fashion
and i want to say thank you to all of
you that are watching no matter where
you come from thank you
oh my god you're crying go down come on
don't come out come here
i love you too
oh my god well
okay i think that's okay um
no don't be sorry i love you too man
happiness
yeah no tears are very happy
yes well uh from my side uh um
i'm celebrating the half year
anniversary
in a few hours when i don't know 15 10
10 i don't know how many hours
uh with a whole life original songs only
karaoke
i've been learning a lot of songs from
our senpais
to show them to you guys tomorrow today
oh i heard a
kitty cat is that oh that's my cat
that's my cat uh yeah and um i also
just uh i'll probably get more into deep
detail about how i feel
about this half year uh in that stream
but generally i just want to say
i hope that when when we do our one year
anniversary
that we can all be together in one room
and just hug each other
and yeah you know that would be really
nice because now i hear gouda
cry now makes me sad i want to hug her i
wish i could hunger
let's work towards that making that a
reality making for dear reality making
new outfits our reality and making a
long long
uh future together with us and with some
kohi's as well
and a reality and making whole live
english even bigger than it already is
yeah yeah it's still good
hey wait a minute i want to give a sappy
message too
um actually i'm really bad at the sappy
stuff but i just want to say
i just want to say um i really wanted to
do
um creative stuff full-time when i was
just a reaper
um and because of everyone's really kind
support
i was able to get um the chance to do
that uh but i wouldn't have been able to
continue on uh like this if it weren't
for you guys i definitely couldn't have
done it alone so
um thank you guys for uh having my back
for being great gemini's i don't i think
that um i mean i can't even imagine a
world where anyone else
um where anyone is not here or
different or anything like that um i
don't i don't want to
uh because everything just kind of fell
into place exactly
i feel like how it how it should have
been um
and i'm just really grateful thank you
so much
you guys are great i'm so glad to have
the
exactly these memories yeah yeah give
your hug so badly
let's do it someday it's a promise okay
yeah yeah no running from this time yes
death grip
it's a promise i do want to give one
last thanks to to the viewers yeah like
good like good
side it's really yeah the support you
guys all show
all of us it's crazy so many people from
all around the world to me that's like
the most mind-boggling thing that's just
from
everywhere people are watching and i
really appreciate it i know everybody
else does too so thank you guys for your
support
thank you we wouldn't be here without
you guys for real yes we wouldn't be
able to do this at all actually
so thank you thank you and meets
teammates taco
buddies and kfc
thank you we love you
[Applause]
many many fun memories from now on as
well
together let's do it
let's do it all right then i think
that's it we're gonna have an after
party privately right
thanks guys we'll catch you on the flip
side
[Music]
peace
okay
bye guys see ya
peace
[Music]
you