[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
K there was a cat running around the
table at this very
moment
welcome everybody to wa's Second cookie
baking stream cookie cooking no cookie
bakon you guys have bgm right there's
bgm I don't have to put any on I
[Music]
think touch the
microphone
yay oh my God they're
zooming
did you hear that they're zooming right
now not a good
sign bgm is playing
okay oh we are
making different types of cookies this
time meow holy [\h__\h] she has like a crazy
meow right
now she's
like oh she she yeah she's she's
running she's running all over that
smoothie yeah she uh just ran from one
side of the room to the other oh oh
don't come
[Music]
here okay she went under the table
bye-bye oh my God this is not a good
time for the cats to have the
Zoomies this time I separated some
things the only things are are attached
because they have to be attached to the
PC to the laptop are the camera
my second
monitor but the power supply of the
second monitor is not applied to the
laptop it's just the
HDMI uh The Mouse and the microphone I
could still de attach the mouse but I
would think that the mouse doesn't like
take so much energy from it
anyway
yeah I hope okay uh what else I going to
do oh yeah
my my orange juice
okay I got some orange
juice in my Atelier Risa stainless steel
[Music]
cup so maybe some of you oh my god did
you hear
the maybe I should turn off the bgm so
you can hear it clearly um where do you
go I don't know scares me everything
scares me um also the camera is like set
way higher this time I I've been trying
to get a good angle but it's difficult
ah you know how fun it was last time to
clean these
lines that was fun no it was fine it
wasn't it wasn't a big
deal you hear her loudly ni nice loud
and clear really oh oh she's running
she's running she's running oh oh oh oh
she's running what are you
doing I want to um I already cleaned the
surface but I'm going to clean it one
more time I reach with the headphones on
yes thank God these headphones have an
extremely long cable so let me clean
this
again just to make
sure no cat
hairs
wonderful I already cleaned it before
though with like actual cleaning stuff
okay uh uh uh
so I am I was thinking should I make the
dough again from
scratch because it's almost the same as
before but not quite turns out so
whatever I'm doing it because it
shouldn't take that much time and it was
kind of fun and that way we have like a
compact you know tutorial for you guys I
don't want to be the one teaching you
you shouldn't be watching me but you
know it's not floor tiles it's my table
but extended so these parts are
the extended version otherwise these
sides come together and there's just one
line in the
middle anyway so wait I have a video
for
reference um that I was going to like
there's so many different like tutorials
for this so like so
[Music]
many different oh my God
different
recipes but I'm just going with this one
so oh cat toilet yeah now I know why
they're zooming it makes a lot of sense
cat toilet is working so that means 5
minutes ago they were on the
toilet so let me mute the audio but let
me see what he's
doing so yeah we're going to put 200 g
of
FL and
uh powdered sugar 65 G then mix it or
maybe already put in a little bit of
salt and I think all where where does he
put in the vanilla
Tuka probably can put it in there at the
[Music]
same
yeah I know I know how to say it
hopefully no blood I feel
very humidified
today very hydrated so if anything my
nose is running so like not with blood
but like normal you know oh wait I
forgot to bring
the uh
scale
okay I've got the scale wait scale not
very clean
problem here's my beautiful scale again
don't you like it it's nice quite
pretty okay let's begin let's begin I
feel more confident this time like after
last
time okay zero and 200 g
male let's just say it in German say it
with me you're learning German while
baking isn't that
great 200 wait why
did why did it go back that's weird but
okay I guess maybe because I touched
it
[Music]
um80 190 ah too much ah okay okay 200
now it's exactly 200 I don't know if I
want to believe that that but yeah uh is
there a dangerous reflection here I
don't know what I'm seeing what what do
you see here I can't see so
closely me yeah with m e h
l is there's something there you tell
[Music]
me fine can't tell right can't tell
really okay okay and then reset and
let's add the 60 5 G of powdered
sugar so yeah that's quite a lot
okay
60 64 yeah that's
fine I can see you can see my credit
card number I don't have a credit card
tell me what is my credit card number I
don't have one [\h__\h] I I I want to get
one like like a while ago for my last
Japan flight but uh yeah oh by the way I
still have like so many cookies from
last
time uh and I I did end up uh coating
the leftover ones in chocolate in Nut
Chocolate they were all right I also ooh
I also added um some sprinkles on some
of them not on all of them it was all
right though and so wait let's add how
much how much vanilla
Tua does he
add oh one full package awesome vanilla
Tua vanilla sugar vanilla sugar I love
this kind of stuff this m vanilla is so
[\h__\h]
[Music]
good let's go really all of that right
now I hope I'm not
mistaken yeah I wish I could add two two
of these
[Music]
packages let's hope everything works
this time I hope nothing like like you
the
camera um malfunctions at some point not
like what
[Music]
no so that's uh that was apparently like
six G or something like that
approximately
um let me see what he does in the video
yeah yeah
yeah and then he makes it a little bit
like that and then he adds the butter
and then he adds eventually I think the
egg or the Egg first what came first the
butter already
is let me get my little my little salt
container and I I bought this
in you put grease or the moldes and then
and I wanted to give it to my mom as a
present cuz it's like wait let me show
you let me show
you I thought she would like this
aesthetic
see like
this thought you would like it but then
she said I don't need it so now I'm
using it and I have sugar in one and
salt in the other I already put in some
salt right I did right somewhere in here
there's some salt
right yeah it's pretty nice I mean it's
not exactly the style I was going for in
my kitchen but why not why
not oh by the way oh I I should explain
I we're making these cookies that have
two layers of cookie and then in between
there is a there's there's a jam and I
mean these cookies you can get them with
all kinds of jam but I am going for
apricot jam because I feel like those
are at least in Austria the most
classic so and then it's going to be
like the the floor layer the bottom
layer and this will be the top
layer uh can you see it they usually
have some kind of opening in a
circle or a star or whatever they don't
even always have to be this shape they
can be Stars
themselves I like that you can use that
somewhere else but it applies to cookies
this time H or like they could be heart-
shaped or my mine are just general
circle shaped and then the cutouts are
different things but they come in all
kinds of shapes and sizes just like you
guys too
yeah um so those are called lint aan in
Austria and lint is a city and means
eyes yeah so um I'm excited for these
because I love eating those I hope they
turn out good I really hope so so
now when does he put in the egg before
the butter or after the
butter still has the egg here oh no oh
he added the
egg you can't hear this anyway I
think okay I think he put the egg in
before he put in the butter
think looks like it looks like
it no no he put the butter first waa
that was dangerous okay okay
okay mix mix mix a little bit roughly so
ever since last time I realized doing
this with my own hands I definitely
prefer
that do the X no no butter first so
there's still a little bit from last
time so I'll use that it was
uh how much butter 130 G butter okay oh
my God I can't believe it's butter no
this is actually real butter we squeeze
it a little bit before putting it
in m that's going to be a lot of butter
holy
[\h__\h] I didn't even prepare I didn't cut
the rest of the butter
[\h__\h] uh
[\h__\h] um Everybody register it's 44 G now
because it's probably going to turn
itself off while I'm cutting this the
new
butter 44 G now so I need what did it
say m oh I need like 90
G 0 more
grams because it was 130 G okay let me
get a
knife
okay oh it's off of course it's
off okay so 90 approximately 90 more G
you don't melt it first no no no it has
to be cold it has to be cold and then
like
you massage it into the all the the
these other parts that things that
ingredients yeah and now we are at
[Music]
20 like a short bread I don't know about
that it's I think it's pretty typical
for cookies to uh go for
oh cold not melted
butter that's the only right way to do
[Music]
it where oh this is only very slowly
going up I I I don't even the other
recipes they didn't even do this
squeezing
thing but this one guy is doing it so
whatever I I I'm doing it too it's like
still pretty hard this
still pretty tough oh we're at
60 room temp yeah I think for some
cookies it has to be room temperature
too but
melted I have I don't know what what
kind of cookie needs melted
[Music]
butter oh by the way today I had my last
my very last guest announcement and that
was two guests at once
wasn't that
exciting I was so I was so excited I
wanted to announce it earlier but here
we are now o it's uh 84
now oh 88
oh oh you might not need this squeezed
butter okay now 92 okay
good yeah can Senpai and R uh not
senpai C have Master yay let me put the
B into the
[Music]
fridge okay now I think first wait let
me see what he does does he massage it
in there and then adds the egg the egg
by the way no egg white for this
one not sampai not sampai
mhm but feel so s exactly that's my
problem that is exactly my
problem yeah so all the guests are
announced now to be honest like
originally I was still planning for like
some other guests but like things didn't
necessarily oh he did add the egg didn't
necessarily work out the way I wanted
so this is what it
is okay only did
egg yellow egg yolk # w hash
yolk can you see what I'm doing
me I think this is pretty legit already
my mom taught me this or I watched her
do this when I was younger you go from
one shell to the other one shell to the
other apparently this
works I I must say it works oh but now
now it's separated a little bit oh no
here go
in okay
and now we squeeze the [\h__\h] out of this
but let me take it off the
scale oh this going to be exhausting
it's going to take a little while
to
[Music]
yay okay so the guests are Calli Senai
Senai CI I never said that before CI who
no one surprised about uh who who no one
was surprised about but honestly like
the song
release is
basically like when I was like planning
out my life guests and I was thinking of
possibilities the song was like still in
very early stages and nothing was really
happening nothing was moving so I was
like cie if you
want if we finish this song by the time
of my life
[Music]
you know wink wink that's all I'm going
to
say she she did debut first yeah yeah
but I'm not going to be like that and
say she's my sire no no no no no no no
wait went on the same day gooda and Amma
were on on the other day for
[Music]
me yeah did you guys like fire
eyes our first ton original
song This exhausting oh just like last
time was it Banger yeah you
did yeah really wow I think I think the
MV is like
crazy like I told you the M was done
like before anything
else [\h__\h] this is [\h__\h]
[Music]
exhausting
krina Banger yeah thank you thank
you kind never
disappoint yeah I would agree with
that like I
mean I'm that's why I why I keep on keep
on uh going back to him
yeah total sausage what do you mean
total sausage Phoenix W oh yeah we all
we both were like really powerful and
like showing off our
skills our
powers don't use hands we have
technology but I I tried that last
time and you know most people who put up
these
recipes they do it with their
hands because it's just you want to feel
the dough you want to connect with the
dough you know on another
level yeah you can do it with the
machine but uh you know I I when I did
that it didn't feel like it was working
but maybe I was just not patient
enough
so I don't have strength in my hands in
my
arms come one
the and honestly I I don't think I would
enjoy this much if I wasn't wearing the
gloves so cuz I I I hate having like so
much [\h__\h] under my fingernails and then
the the fingers get so doughy
and so I actually prefer this and it's
it's it's turning into
something
okay get the stupid small parts in
here
squeeze and
squeeze oh [\h__\h] my I actually I recently
noticed my left
arm um like here this part to the
wrist when I like like for example when
I get off a chair and I push myself up
with my arm hi Mooney I noticed that I
feel pain in here and like it it it kind
of spreads from the wrist into the hand
and I was wondering if that was from me
signing all those [\h__\h] and I actually
got carpal tunnel
syndrome because I was really worried
about it back then because it was like
honestly I definitely strained myself
and like overdid
it and I think I [\h__\h] got it because
it's only over here and it's been like
this for a couple days but does it
happen like delayed because I I haven't
noticed it in immediately after signing
all the
cards [\h__\h] man I really got caral tunnel
syndrome but I already looked it up on
Google and it says it goes away on its
own after weeks and months right no I
got to be more careful
[Music]
[\h__\h] the swelling can be delayed how
much but as as long as it heals on its
own it's like
whatever okay we got a dough
dicta yay I'm so happy the guy in the
video I don't think he cooled it I see
some people cooling their dough some
people don't but seems fine uh
so so so so
[Music]
so seems fine to not do it is there any
hairs uh
probably I cleaned
[Music]
it
damn it why is there always hairs
[Music]
everywhere I was wiping it but that
might not be
[Music]
enough
okay but I don't want to now that it's
uh wet I should dry it I bought kitchen
paper let's go I usually don't have this
in my kitchen but I noticed it would be
useful for stuff like
this kitchen paper definitely doesn't
have cat hair on it cuz it's
new
looks
good okay okay this can go away
[Music]
too also going to bring over my baking
tray but it needs new
[Music]
paper I feel like such a
housewife perhaps a desperate
housewife
okay haven't watched that in a while but
it's pretty good it's pretty good okay
how my hands a I see a hair let me
switch gloves let me get new
[Music]
gloves
ah it's okay these are like throw away
one like short
use anyway this is what they're supposed
to be
[Music]
doing not bald did you see my hair what
do you mean you saw not bald what what
do you mean not bald confirmed oh
because of the hair on my
finger okay that stressed me out for a
moment what do you
mean but maybe it's just my cat's hairs
but no that one I wasn't sure that could
have been from
me that could have been mine almost
heart attack
man
y so we're going to roll this
out and
then make different types of
shapes and we got to count though so
that I have an an equal
amount of uh
everything I wait there any FL FL FL
yeah wait wait uh uh let
me again let
me my
headphones one more wipe one more
wipe one more wipe oh what the [\h__\h]
where did
[Music]
that okay one more wi one more go it's
really clean now really clean and
okay cuz I still can't say that [\h__\h]
word I will never
learn and let's
go let's go
let's let's try to keep it within the
[Music]
square okay and
then I hate that feeling it's like
[Music]
sandpaper ooh
okay it seems
[Music]
I think this is how it's supposed to be
though it because it's mve I think it's
supposed to look like it's kind of like
flaky a little
[Music]
bit Yeah kneading on the floor I said
it's not the
[Music]
floor it would be crazy if there's floor
on the
[Music]
floor sayak that's the worst that's
absolutely terrible I hate that I hate
that thank
[Music]
you it's too
sticky
okay how thin is this I think it's a
good
good good di diameter or whatever
[\h__\h] talk okay so we'll make some
bases this actually I thought it would
be way more I'm glad it's not too much
cuz I have so many
cookies from last time I'm glad it's not
too much
seemingly
okay and there's like a a little bit of
a like weird side so we got to cut it
with this
side okay let's Crouch
oh no and I'm going to put them straight
onto
the uh
[Music]
tray I love
that oh [\h__\h] didn't come out why why you
do this to come here come here
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[\h__\h] uh wonder how many bases I
need
[\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] it's a little bit
broken
whatever squeeze it back together 1 2 3
4 5
[Music]
six
six let's go like until half probably
that would
work they don't want to come with me
anymore what the hell maybe I need floor
flower over
[Music]
here 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
14 15
right let's do that for now
15 and
then
[Music]
one taada like this and so I guess there
will be
umby it broke it
broke we'll rework that h
[Music]
one
two
three
four
five
7 don't do
[Music]
that
ah it also broke maybe it's better that
these don't come with the the
cutter uh 1 2 3 4 5 6
[Music]
eight nine how many was this 1 2 3 4 5 6
7 8 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 uh 13 14
15 uh one two three four five six seven
8 nine 10 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 eight n
nine no
[Music]
nine o I think my dough may not be
perfect oh no this worked this kind of
worked
nice
uh uh
nine I can't count I literally forget
everything
immediately maybe it's too
thin
oh it wants to go on a walk with me
tada
[Music]
okay what where was I
what was this one 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
[Music]
uh
12 uh
14 oh [\h__\h] oh wow that was actually
perfectly aligned with the other one
it's like almost cutting n it is a
little bit cutting into it but whatever
okay we'll make one more or even more
with the remaining
[Music]
dough got to get all
the remaining
[Music]
parts oh thanks for the memberships 50
what the [\h__\h]
pbnk oh this is ooh it's like really
risky oh [\h__\h] why did I do
that
ooh cuz the ones with with the cutouts
they're way more
fragile [\h__\h] I don't know how to lift
it just like
stick
[Music]
drop
that I'm doing it it's kind of
working
W what a joyful merry Merry Christmas
season where there's so many membership
gifts
nice thank you so much
pbnk you're so so what's the
word
so
uh I cannot English right now I am not
English
Jer yeah generous that's thought I knew
it was something with
[Music]
g
people people of kfp pray for my cookies
oh this one is deformed now what the
[\h__\h] that's not going to fit why are you
deformed all right remaking that
one [\h__\h] there I think ah I cut off one
a
no get out you still you will still do
your job whether you like it or
[Music]
not [\h__\h] out
of
[Music]
okay little formation is fine that warp
in the oven uh yeah I guess
[Music]
so
Hearts turn out my hands are not gentle
enough so I got to do it with this
[Music]
tool let's go back I actually I stopped
talking about my life which is tomorrow
tomorrow for real for real
tomorrow
tomorrow I'm so excited oh [\h__\h] I cut
off a little piece whatever
uh so have Callie Han and and
uh we announced matui
Senpai and we announced Aki
Senai and I am so
excited because there's also wayen not
Senpai so we have someone from ID we
have someone from Ian we have someone
from um
Japanese
side what I said yesterday by the way
was I was fully serious like we were
planning we were trying to get
pomu on board and pomu was ready she was
ready to fly to Japan for it but
unfortunately her 3D is not usable in a
not in Ausable
State I don't know in what state it is
Michigan or California but
[Music]
um why are they sticking is it the
but thank you thank you and also I was
trying to get like like an IRL person
like a real person as well um but that
lady never replied so I kind of gave up
on it I waited pretty long and then it
was like [\h__\h] like oh I I can't wait
much longer because like we got to we
got to get this
going and eventually I had to give up on
it um but I if I get another
chance at something like that I want to
try it
again give it another
try Gutenberg would be a huge get
that's a Pity yeah it is but it's okay I
mean it's my first
time like being able to do something
like this within cover within whole life
so
um I personally like I I wanted it to be
like relatively normal anyway I wanted
it to just be a classic kind of life
because I never got to do it before
so I think it's fine to not like be
crazy with experimenting and making it
some beam or so as I said before it's
just like pretty
[Music]
normal and then who knows in the future
we can go crazy we can go
crazy I
think uh
uh I'm just going to count how much I
would need
[Music]
still look come here bad boy okay we
have uh 3 six9 12 15 wow she can
actually count like that
surprise what did I say 15 right 369 125
uh fre
69 uh 10 11 12 13 okay so I need two
more I'm just going to make those two
more because I'm not in the mood to do
this
endlessly and I already have too many
cookies
anyway so Mao let's
go this is not
[Music]
good let me do it here
two more right I said two more ah I
didn't put
Flo it's immediately
[Music]
noticeable okay separate yourself like
that if you don't want to be connected
to K Fe sure sure I don't give a [\h__\h]
you you you do your thing if you think
you're better off without me
okay okay I'm not going to stop
you that was the wrong side no it wasn't
okay that's it that's all I needed
hopefully they don't fall
apart I did powder the
roller I did I
did oh no
why does it smell so good I have the
window open so I I I smell someone else
is cooking damn every time I smell
something really good from someone
else's apartment I'm like I wish I could
ask them what it is what they're
cooking so curious
[Music]
okay let
me let me put this
stuff into the bowl
guys that's a table yes it's a table do
people really think I'm doing this on
the floor it's an extendable table have
you never seen a table with like these
kind of
splits before wish it's a table Mama Mia
Mama
[Music]
Mia okay oh I didn't preheat the oven oh
[\h__\h] but it's going to be
fast
right
[Music]
okay that
is going byby
[Music]
and
and preheat
[Music]
oven dry my
hands W thank you guys for the
membership renewals thank
you did it say here
no
uh uh I think I think it
was
H oh yeah 165 celius umlo
umlo
umlo is the
one
um the
one this one I
think
[Music]
65 roughly 165 is I think the one with
the fan only the fan cuz then there's
the grill with the fan and this and that
it's so confusing but I think it's the
one with the fan yeah okay um
now I realized I don't have this like I
want I want one of those plastic bags
where you can squeeze but I didn't
didn't have one so I'm just going to use
like this and then cut it
open what we're going to do with this is
we're going to put Jam inside and half a
lemon
uh uh juice half a lemon's juice the
juice is not in every recipe
but uh in this one it is and it seems
like a cool thing to do by the way look
at
[Music]
this
we will put this into the oven once it's
hot enough we have in total 15 cookies
then because it's 30 things but they're
going to be layers so it's going to be
cookies and um they will be having some
nice yummy apple cut Jam in between make
sure if you're going to do this to get
the jam that doesn't have all the little
pieces inside but it's instead fine p in
German fine p and
smoothly P I don't know what that is in
English yeah yeah but uh they did say
they like warm up the jam a little bit
is that really necessary I guess so let
me put it put some of it I don't know
how much I'll
need
[Music]
[\h__\h] I can't help
it oh did you hear that did you hear the
Flop
see that is really smooth
texture
okay did did it actually say how much in
the
recipe no
okay oh I guess it's it's kind of
jellyish now so it would be nice if it
became more like a little bit more
liquefied maybe this should be enough
honestly
probably let's do a little bit
more I mean it's just 15
cookies I don't want to waste too much
of this cuz I don't think I can put it
back looks good
right and then let me cut this open
really
[Music]
quick not sure if I'm supposed to warm
it up before putting the juice
in probably doesn't make a big
difference let me warm this up
first is it too early to warm it up now
maybe it's too early maybe I'll do it
once I put in the cookies but the
cookies apparently just need like 7
Minutes who cuts lemons it's so that I
can squeeze
them yeah because I don't have like I
would cut it like halfways like in the
middle if if I had like a like a lemon
squeezy thing but I got to do it with my
head and it's easier to squeeze it like
this for me but probably not with my
left hand because I currently have
carpal tunnels in drum thanks to signing
all my cards so you guys the ones of you
who are getting one of those limited
cards just know that for you and for
these cards I got myself carpal tunnel
syndrome
yay the things I go through to serve my
beloved
chickens thank you for your sacrifice
you're welcome I love you thank you for
your guys' sacrifices all the time as
well for sacrificing your time of the
day and your
sanity and your money in case you send
super
[Music]
chats never had any siles to sacrifice
me too yay high
five
just chilling out on a nice Sunday
morning Saturday morning oh yeah it's
Saturday tomorrow is Sunday what day is
that my birthday and of year live let's
go let's go
woohoo yeah it's going to be great it's
going to be great I'm ah after the
stream I'll put up the reservation and
gartic phone as well oh I forgot about
gar phone why do I keep on forgetting
about that
stream yeah we have another stream today
at I think midnight for
[Music]
me with some nice artists I hope they
all wake up in time cuz I think I ended
up getting a lot of uh Japanese artists
too and it'll be really early for
them I hope they don't forget about it I
wonder if it's ready to put the cookies
in what do you think do you think that
was long enough to heat
up there's like a
sign there is a sign with like a
temperature thingy that probably should
tell me if it's done or not oh it never
beeps
though but yeah I don't
know I don't know if that what what what
what what that has to look like to
indicate that it's actually really the
right
temperature what made you decide on that
time uh I don't know I just thought it
would be easy to get these artists to
participate if I make it easy for Na and
somewhat good for like a realistic time
for Japanese artists too because I don't
think I have a single European artist or
like residing European
artist uh anyway
so you know typically a light turns off
oh well I'm UNS sure about
that also like yeah I kind of was like
hoping to squeeze in a few more streams
before the birthday life to also promote
it
so you can draw
money I don't know if I believe that h
money money you have to watch the
birthday life though tomorrow you have
to watch it even if it's a shitty time
for you you have to
because your songs will be performed
tell the other angels too wake them up
wake him up I got to tell k for k at
least it's a a good
[Music]
time okay maybe I'll just put it in
now
probably
[Music]
fine okay 7 Minute Timer go
guys let's go and let me put turn on the
[Music]
microwave a little
bit I'm doing 1 minute 600 watt
shouldn't be necessary to like make it
cook you guys are putting a timer right
let me also see wait actually so my
stream is now 59 SEC 59 minutes so that
could also be a good indicator for
me we got you thank
you 600
what 600 watt don't you guys say whatt
as in English
too so 600 watt
[Music]
what they just messing right they just
messing with
me seems like everything's stable H the
camera didn't die a single time so
having threee things connected seems to
go well free things plus the
HDMI
hiie hi
hi oh it's like smoking
hot no that's too much I think that is
too
liquidy but do you think it will like
get a little bit
more solid again [\h__\h] that was too
much see how liquid that is that will
like go
everywhere so yeah let's put it back
back into the fridge M why are you
standing in my
path why
why I want to show you this cat she's so
sweet meow she's so sweet I want to show
her to
you now let's cool it down a little bit
not too
much she's literally standing between my
table and my kitchen when I go to the
kitchen she's there
meow
meow you're so sweet I love her so
much yeah 200 watt might have been
better yeah it was probably too
much over mix a little bit of the cold
Jam back
[Music]
in
I'm so I'm so excited I'm so
excited so excited I got a sticker you
from the Tokyo Station hold life oh
thank
you thank you thank you wait the sticker
are those the the ones you get for free
when you buy a couple of things you get
some freebies so you only got a freebie
of me you didn't want to buy anything of
me that you actually have to buy what
else did you buy huh what did you
actually buy to get those freebies huh
oh spofy poofy getting curious huh I'm
streaming I'm talking so that means I'm
streaming
baby it's okay though don't worry about
it I'm just roast roasting
you oh she
violations yeah yo yesterday I was
talking for three hours with pom after
that uh uh stream it was so nice talking
with her like we actually I feel like we
have this like
weird natural
automatic uh
connection where like for the longest
time we didn't collab right but we also
didn't really talk much behind the
scenes either cuz I never knew what to
say to her like I just knew I like her
without even talking to her you know
that's so
weird we never really got to know each
other much until like we collabed for
the first time but even until then I was
always saying I love po I love Po and
she was always saying she loves me she
loves me but like I feel like she knew
more about me than I knew about her but
still it's like yeah I think it's
natural chemistry and just like a like I
just had this immediate understanding
when I just saw a little bit of her that
I like
her it was clear to me yeah hello
puppy we could
probably yeah and then like these this
freour conversation was the longest by
far the longest conversation we ever had
I
think on the phone like normally we
would probably mostly just talk by
chitchatting
[Music]
typing she's so S I actually like I
wanted to check back on the stream last
night so just just to hear the Audio I
wanted to hear how scuffed it was how
long I actually had the wrong microphone
phone and if it was a big issue and I I
was watching that part and it was fine
and then it was so funny that I
continued watching it and I couldn't
stop like even though it's my own stream
I watched the whole hour a second time
and experienced it as the viewer this
time and it was really entertaining I
know that's kind of cringe to watch my
own stream I used to do that when I
first debuted the
first hard to say maybe the first month
or so
I would re-watch my own streams a little
bit quite a bit I think um to just
like reflect
on what what things I said and what I
did and if it's like it was entertaining
I guess like just learning from
myself I guess no I did that a lot and
then I stopped doing it at some point
because I mean
time and just not interested anymore and
just kind of f found my vibe thanks for
the gift thank you thank
you oh by the way new decorations by
blue blue uh
blue it's good to learn from your own
streams yeah but this was the first time
in a long time that I watched my own
stream again
[Music]
and I got to do this
again and um it was yeah it was like
really funny so actually I was so
surprised that it was so funny because
when I was doing it when I was actively
streaming it I felt like there may have
been some awkward silences and maybe it
wasn't as
exciting but uh you guys didn't feel
that did you because then when I watched
the archive it was really
funny and frog bird I [\h__\h] love her
frog Persona so
[Music]
much it was great right and that little
little upgrades to the winter world I
just wanted to reuse the winter oil to
like give it a bit more exposure again
um but then like
I seaone boy offered to add some things
s minutes are over okay to let me
[Music]
check no they're still soft so we got to
Freestyle it again and make our own
[Music]
decisions okay so sea boy he like
offered to add some things I was like
yeah okay but don't go overboard because
basically I just want to reuse the world
and you know no need to add too many
things but then he adds a whole [\h__\h]
Christmas Market which looked so nice
but like
dude that's so much man yeah the
Christmas Market but I feel like if I if
we use it again during the winter time
with perhaps
members then maybe we can update it one
more time to have actually like mascots
uh whole life mascots working the Stalls
I think that would be nice talk about
overd delivering for real but he's a
goat like it looks so beautiful and the
the little Huts the Finish Huts like he
implements a lot of his homeland into
his creations and I really like
that yeah it's honestly so beautiful
like I feel like you could use this
world as a map in a game like in an
actual game because the quality it's
just so good like he I wonder if he
works on any games because he honestly
has the skills for it like creating game
Graphics he
should let me get the jam looking
better oh yeah that
actually I think that helped already
[Music]
look it's not as wobbly
anymore maybe H I'm not sure about
the ACT uh well okay it only really did
it for the top
layer the bottom is the you see here
this part is still very wobbly let me
put it
back let me put it
back we did
it that was a a big oopsie by the way
for VR I moved I have I have in my in my
like office room I have uh
so um I have this huge orange bean bag
right bean bag yeah bean bag is it bean
bag yeah um and now for to in order to
have more movement in my room for the VR
I put it out and it's now next to my
desk and guess who's sitting on it
smovie she's like right next to me so
cute he likes to sit on it also in the
office I'm I'm surprised because even
after like a year or so it's still
stinky I hate it I don't know how she
can sleep on it with her face literally
touching the bean bag because when I
like go there to like face plant her
body and
you know enjoy the fluff I I smell the
bean bag and I don't understand how she
can enjoy that stink because it's like a
plastic artificial chemical smell even
after a year it didn't go
away so I hate the bean bag kind
of it's so stinky okay hate was a little
bit too much I dislike it a little bit
the smell and it takes up so much space
cuz it's not just a single catar bean
bag it's like you you can I can lie on
it with my full
body let me check the cookies
[Music]
again oh that looks good that looks good
I
think oh uh they still seem kind of a
stof but I guess that's probably how
it's supposed to
[Music]
be
uh AFP
[Music]
glove so I'm just guess it will probably
cool down like when it cool cools down
it probably gets hi it gets probably
more
solid now I'm kind of worried that I
actually had it in too
long cuz they're a bit too Brown I don't
think they should be so
[Music]
Brown
wa
[Music]
look h h h h h hot it's a bit too Brown
it shouldn't be this brown but I was
unsure because when I touched it it uh
made a little
Dent so it didn't feel
right let me let it cool down for a
little while longer a little while
longer oh it's only been an hour so far
anyway it feels longer
[Music]
though
Hina cuz if it's this hot it's going to
melt
the the jam all over
again they look yummy yeah they are a
different uh dough than last time so I
wonder how they taste now cuz last time
when I uh made cookies last year I think
I had the same dough to make the the van
no actually no never mind it's not quite
the same but very similar m is van far
um similar but I had it store bought so
this time I made it myself I wonder how
different it
tastes it's fine even if they overbaked
a little bit it's fine it's probably
fine now let me get them off of the tray
[Music]
actually
let can I just do like this
no do
[Music]
you it doesn't work like that okay okay
okay okay fine fine
fine
uh cute G glove right it's so
cute I like this
one it doesn't quite protect me from the
heat as much as I
wish nice
that's that's that's fine you go here
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay looking good don't they look good a
little bit over baked but that's
fine m
m calm down what what did I what
happened color very nice yeah inferior
looks nice but it's not supposed to be
this dark
actually okay let's let's make the
[Music]
jam oh okay it it's hardened again but
let's see what happens if I break the
surface
all oh that's pretty good that's pretty
good I think that's pretty good
E I don't even know why it had to be
warmed because I feel
like had a better texture before okay
I'm actually going to add just a little
bit of the cold
gem
sorry just just a tiny
bit
okay all right and then we add the
[Music]
juice I hope
this here we go squeeze with right
[Music]
hand okay a little bit
help I can barely I can
barely oh there's a lot of seeds in
there one just flew at me I think that's
probably enough probably there's even
more juice in there to get but no
[Music]
need
mhm the seed out of
there okay and now we mixx we mix we mix
but that made it a little bit more
liquid again okay I'm just going to
trust in the process I'm just going to
try to
believe that this is
fine and not like My worry is that it's
going to like when I put it on the
cookie that it's going to like spread
all
over that's what worries
[Music]
me m
okayed on it we don't have to do this we
can just put it like directly on but
it's a bit easier to do it like
this
supposedly and I'm going to cut a hole
and make this reusable plastic bag
forever
unusable except for I guess stuff like
this
okay
uh and not close it I hope this
works I hope this works oh it's really
not much
[Music]
how let me guess I'll cut a hole here
where's my
scissor oh
[Music]
here I'm excited I hope they taste good
cuz I really love these
cookies I really love
them okay I made a small hole but
actually it's pretty big y
b yeah I'm really worried now I'm really
worried please don't immediately like go
all over the place look I'm
scared I don't know about
this
you're supposed to hold it kind of like
this right y y okay here we go here goes
nothing
oh
okay oh okay that's a good
amount oh
oh not too
much not too
much this is the moment of
[Music]
truth
Yoo definitely easier like this than
doing it with a spoon or
something and I do I do feel like I have
good control over
[Music]
it so
they're they're good when they're warm
too but [\h__\h] I heard from the
recipes that you want to put them into
the fridge a little bit like once they
cool down they're even better [\h__\h] this
is [\h__\h] because I barely have
ah it I barely have anything left so
it's like I'm trying to get it this is
not good this is not
good let me squeeze it back here
okay just two more cookies how
about so I'm going to eat them like one
or two warm for taste testing
but they will be better after they're
chilled and then hopefully the gam will
also become more like
[Music]
jelly cuz that's my
jam okay that's actually fine I mean
these are are messed up little bit of
[Music]
accident oh here also
[\h__\h]
ooh M okay the lemon juice is very
strong okay and then we just put them on
top and the the jam once you
put got you once you put the the tops on
the bottoms the jam will squeeze a
little bit through and it will like kind
of Pop you
know and that's really nice to see okay
like this okay I probably put too much
Jam there overall on these
cookies like
[Music]
this but this is good this is good I'm
trying to align the
little um what do you call this the wavy
Parts but see they look so nice when you
can see the jam poke out of
it and say hello good day to you sir
this one the shape is kind of [\h__\h] up
do I have one that's like
that not
really
whatever o the jam
yum looks tasty right looks
good cute they're so cute they look so
[Music]
aesthetic they look like
gems and they're
orange they're orange guys
guys just want to point out the
obvious now you can either leave them
like this or you uh add the final
component that I will be adding because
it looks even nicer and even more like
Christmas
okay which is powder sugar
and I
have I have this thing here that I
barely use but I will use it this
[Music]
time and you top it with the powdered
sugar all over a [\h__\h] I forgot I should
have done that before putting the tops
on
top you do this first H oh well because
now you don't see the color so nicely
anymore more when I do this
now okay then just let's just do it
lightly just lightly also I think it
will melt kind of anyway just lightly
not too much so you can still see the
jam like
[Music]
this why did I do
this it's okay it looks like it's snowed
on top of them Yuki
gauta yeah it might dissolve into the
gem
so I'm really careful now but normally
you you go really hard on the powdered
sugar you cover it like completely at
least the tops and then you put it on
top of the G I feel like it's already
melting cuz of the they're still a
little bit
warm okay con they're complete
let me let me zoom in a little bit can
[Music]
I oh
W look how pretty they are even even
though I messed up the order but
honestly this has its own
[Music]
charm I'm going turn
it
ta yay they look so nice nice they look
so good let me let me show
[Music]
you from last
time these are the cookies from last
time Zeno
[Music]
cookie the chocolate ones I have
somewhere else I have them at my
computer so I won't show them but these
are the ones from last time and now
these look even more proper cuz these
are just really messy and easy
cookies but they also like solidified
properly so they're better to eat now
than from the day when I first baked
them but okay they will be better when
they're cold but let's try one
[Music]
now mhm
m m
yeah the jam is too liquidy but very
good mhm the dough is perfect I think
could be maybe a little bit less prone
to fall apart but it's pretty
[Music]
good yummy
mhm m
M and it's so good
because this dough generally is a bit
dry right but the gam gives you
something
wet and uh some some extra flavor that's
very
fruity
[Music]
oh that was only one and a half hours I
mean I think you can do it way faster
than that too if you have like good
practice with like cutting them out and
putting them you know if you have
practice then it will probably be done
in 40 minutes also I had to wait for the
oven and I [\h__\h] around with the
gem so that's that oh let me me W this
one this one's going to be good when it
dries
because let me show you the see how much
it's like
[Music]
plump very
nice thank you camera for doing such a
good job today love you camera good
quality everything works today kill I'm
so happy everything worked out really
nicely and the cookies I definitely like
them more than the last
ones they do taste amazing I want to eat
more but I want to wait until they are
uh
solid no disconnects at all
yeah nice Ian stayed away
yay I used to make these every year with
my grand Grandma did say grandma sorry
the comment already disappeared but I'm
happy to hear that I I don't remember
making this with my family but maybe I
did when I was really
small USB stay strong yeah cuz I
connected like something to the actual
power outlet
directly yeah yeah yeah
yeah nice so are you guys maybe
interested in trying this out yourself I
forgot last time I said I was going to
put the ingredients clearly in the
descript deson I forgot about that I
will do that for both streams now
afterwards I'll put the ingredient list
into the
description so please give it give them
a try they're pretty simple all you need
is these shapes I mean honestly you
could do it without the hole I guess but
that's what makes them so
Charming see the the the the sugar Dy
DED not dried it it melted more or less
you can't really except for these you
can't really tell we'll try it out yay
I'm happy to hear
that the cookies look good b a waa does
it again yes I'm such a
baker yeah you need them with hols also
like they come as I said in all kinds of
shapes and and forms and size is because
like I see them being a star shape
sometimes or even a heart shape yeah but
this is like the classic way to make
them in Austria in this shape you will
see them in the supermarkets as well or
in the
[Music]
bakeries I only know them out of the
store and then they are even with Jam
pretty dry oh yeah but that's I think
that's kind of un purpose
M no I also i' I had these from in the
supermarket before and other cookies but
yeah I I was kind of unsatisfied with
them surprisingly so I hope I will enjoy
them cuz they're
self-made I have so many cookies thank
God actually that this time it's not so
many although actually no this time I
might be a little bit feeling regretful
that they're not that
many it's only 15 cookies and I already
ate
one I can't even M I want to give like
maybe three of them to my
friends yeah I could just make them
again cuz they're so easy yeah all all
you need basically is flour FL flea flow
flu sugar powder sugar vanilla sugar an
egg and jam and you can do it with any
Jam you can do it with strawberry jam
you can do it with any kind of jam
really you can even do it with chocolate
sometimes I see them with chocolate
filling but I don't think that's like
that's not this cookie anymore that's
just something else that looks like it
but it's not the same cookie it has to
be with
Jam
yeah bacon jck no no ew disgusting how
dare
[Music]
you I made them with mixed
fruit Jam you mean right as I saw you
retracting the message there you mean
Jam right mixed fruit Jam yeah that
should be great that's got a tropical
but this is most the most classic one
apricot jam Jam so
[Music]
CH also like the the lemon juice is like
optional but I I will say uh it was it
was good to have it in there MH mhm let
me take a picture wait let me one more
time
why do I do
this let me take a
picture piure
piure W with her high quality
photography
skills oh it looks like I'm in a [\h__\h]
V Bakery Christmas
Bakery ooh the light is perfect
too thanks to my LED light
[Music]
well okay I got it I got some good
pictures now I don't want to put on the
gloves again so
uh
uh can you see the mouse right now no
right if I put my hand here oh okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay yeah okay good
um well I guess that's it I got to
prepare for the um GC phone stream I got
to make thumbnails I got to put up the
other reservation so I guess I'll leave
it here short and
compact really
nice I'm really
[Music]
successful it's great I have a nice
snack for watching my frie live tomorrow
cuz it's pre-recorded woohoo
but let's act as if it's live
okay I might I don't know I see I saw
like uh other members when they have
pre-recorded ones they even live tweet
their own um live maybe I'll do that too
with like screenshots and
hashtags should I live tweet it so I can
bring even more attention when I say
live tweet I only mean like I I make
some tweets where I say this next up is
this song with these
members maybe I'll do
[Music]
that with the hashtag too and you guys
please please um uh make sure tomorrow
to tweet a lot with the
hashtag yeah I mean you don't even know
the hashtag yet you will see once I put
up the stream but it's a KF party
2023 KF party I I was going to just use
the same one from last year but then I
realized m i I don't want to claim it's
my birthday now cuz people might get
confused like oh happy birthday but it's
like half a year late so let's not imply
that it's my birthday
again um this just KF party 2023
exactly I like doing like little puns
with the kfp my KF
[Music]
people please support the Waba let's
spread the word all over I worked so
[\h__\h] hard on
this was is like the most this is the
most stressful time of the
[Music]
year we have all the dance lessons and
the coll of collabs every
day it was the most stressful time of
the
year h
oh okay I'm really in a good mood right
now I'm so [\h__\h] happy that this went
so well let's go let's go let's
go so I guess this is goodbye I I'm
having a hard time saying goodbye right
now but I'll see you later for GC phone
so you guys can all take a
[Music]
nap byebye and enj when we
say yeah yeah yeah yeah now don't look
at my hand there's no hand there's no
hand because we're zoomed in
[Music]
byebye ho ho
ho so
[Music]
excited