e
e e
uh
hello hello hello
[Music]
hello we're here
welcome to the Minecraft game
Minecraft have some mines welcome to the
official Hol live e in Minecraft server
it's a
face welcome look how cute every when
you click a button too much on your
keyboard and then you get that and then
the message sticky you mean the sticky
keys
sh but yes shut up that's what it's
called even I know that and I know
nothing about technology real quick
before we get started I would like to
double triple quadruple check
everybody's
audio uh so that everybody can be heard
nice and loud and clear
ow okay we'll do that in a second we're
under
10 hang
on so I fell off excuse me just a moment
I'm on the way I hear the ground them
don't worry and I got okay get out of
the house get out of the house wait wait
wait what wait what's that noise Aon a
dragon already why there a
dragon
dragon I got him I got him come
here what the that's not a dragon
that's a pctl
I se them in the history books careful
watch I'm going to die going watch
that's fine we'll get him let's get him
apexed okay got
Hing down don't let him I'm sorry that
was
me that was friendly
fire who put pterodactyls in the game
why is our house attacked by dragons
e they knew they knew come here here you
scoundrel you will not turn me how much
how much health do they
have so tiny but so powerful I mean we
could also sleep I have a few beds in
here maybe we should
sleep okay how many beds do you have I
have one more wait extra okay I I have
one of my house right there okay sleep I
like your pants
Callie thank you me too somebody's your
hor is good Jan Jan is safe s nap I I'll
go to my house you sure okay you don't
have to join this Lumber party if you
want I don't think were there enough
bed really not you can sleep on the
floor you in my house but there's a
creeper right in front of my
door it's okay I'm almost to my
house oh yeah I can't sleep cuz there's
monsters
[Music]
nearby Jan
in my house is he safe my roommate safe
yeah he's the best roommate he's very
cozy I want to meet joran Jan
yes how do you
type T hit the t button y good
Mone
morning what they're on fire oh yeah cuz
the
Sun cuz the sun oh God they're on fire
on
fire my house is by the nether
portal why why did it start like this
how did it end up like
this only kiss oh no not near my new
home no I'll drive away oh thank you I
appreciate that it's very time call at
me thank you oh jeez how's the audio
sound
everybody audio
good audio good audio
good game froze yeah I'm I I Ted out
there we
go good everybody yes audio we're all
alive my could be louder oh ah hello ah
is someone getting is somebody getting
assassinated I'm on the way all good all
good
quiet okie dokie I will try to speak
louder I will bump on hello hello hello
hello
I'm okay
okay all
good everything good all right we got
Minecraft music whenever it decides to
uh turn
on yeah I wish that it was on all the
time it's rather Pleasant isn't
it it's beautiful I like it Amelia has
three trees on her house now there's
more more
growing so does anybody want to show
their house progress so
far yeah
sure mine's not created yet I'm just
putting some finishing tches online you
guys can go first okay okay uh I guess I
can start with mine is Ena I'm the
cameraman today there there isn't much
wait why is Ena so
big
[Laughter]
wait
yes sorry about that I uh I had too much
uh
too much uh whatever I mean spinach too
much spinach too much spinach and milk
e
spinach yes uh oh the lava uhoh uhoh
this is this is my house this is quite
bad very small it's so cute um I made a
little farm here making the wheat are
you growing wheat the wheat the
wheat the wheat you come in hey there's
two beds
tle why do you have two
beds thanks nice one for sleep and one
for me
ooh yes can I come your your uh your
house is a bit far from here so you know
whenever we have guests over see buddies
got to
together uh downstairs is still a work
in
progress work in
progress you just
who oh there's a downstairs what you can
do it you can do after you after
you dummy proof Oh
no I got to
squeeze you know how do you go down this
the oh has a house in the
ground
made oh you just let go and it just goes
down you have a garden underneath I
thought Gremlin
proof Gremlin
proof uh there's nothing down here yet
I'm just making a there that goes
nowhere oh
progress
gremling how do I how do I how do I get
it's a just let go if you like go on the
ladder oh I'm not on the ladder though I
can't even grab onto it I like your
shiny pants Callie thank you I
appreciate
everybody up up
up up I like this red stone and I'm
going to use it to create
house all right who's next my house is
ready okay let's go
see oh there are stairs over here on the
right side oh
nice build those
there are
fish oh you have a walkway and
everything wow
yeah something in your house it's a
horse
it's this
horse what w this is here can I ride him
uh you hit yes you uh what is right
click my go are youa
[Music]
oh my
gosh how do sh that's right you're
burning yourself you're burning yourself
press the shift
button how get off
shift shift yes excellent wow that was
fun I always wanted to do some more
horse riding you go very fast with
youran ena's
house's house
I like your color scheme with your
purple flowers and your yellow bed it
looks very very cute very well
coordinated Hasty color
palette man your your house is in a very
nice location I was quite surprised when
I looked down my house this
morning I see this and I see a bunch of
trees growing on your house nice it'll
be like a natural looking house with a
lot of flowers and trees is there
something h
kind of want to live in that
mountain the giant hole in the mountain
yeah I like that hole in the mountain I
want to live there I think I
will what about the other house just
trying to build I will take the
materials from there and move it I was
saying we should build the tunnel here
like that in line with my path good idea
this the right way uh the right
direction G
uh wait
G in
directions
wait it's a
squid oh it ran off I think it's in the
opposite
direction dang it okay well no no you
know what we can do no no no no we we
could easy easy we do this right you
build a tunnel you build the staircase
down and then you you hook a hook a turn
right hook a left and then we just spin
the bus around and then we go that way
so we end up going underneath your
house uh okay if we go deep enough that
should be fine we can go deep enough
let's go deeper I'm going to craft
another pickaxe and then I will join you
got to go deeper must go
deeper all right I'm going to I'll pop
by my house right right here it's real
quick uh you must prepare the materials
the start of my house is uh
we're going under the
water this is all I have so
far there's going to be uh glass you
have a house farther further away I do
but I would like to have one closer to
everybody too so I'm going to put glass
here so you can like look out and stuff
maybe a how did you do it that the water
doesn't come all the way in uh just keep
digging and then it stops
wow I mean it's it's the power of
[Music]
Poseidon makes sense makes sense thank
you all right do you want to show us
your house Kiara well um yeah I would
like to um actually I have to say me and
Callie played Minecraft the other day
together mhm and then we built a house
together put two beds in there together
no no and yesterday yesterday I finished
the roof I I was really trying hard to
give me and my wife Cali a roof up
above and I spent hours Gathering wood
okay hours and I can I have some of it
maybe and then and then today I come
into the Discord and cie says she's
building a house somewhere else I'm like
what I need my space so I have all this
space now and I'm I'm looking for a
roommate now because Callie decided that
she does not want to sleep next to me
anymore look this is our beautiful bed
aligned next to each other it's nothing
personal cator I can't live with anyone
else well I'm officially my personality
okay not I don't like you I'm officially
looking for a roommate now so send you
applications
please it's just it's Callie's home away
from home it's her second home come
visit I just honestly can't be there all
this time
what's the uh what's the rent how much
is the rent is nothing your Endless Love
and Affection probably and maybe some
some
coal hey what did you steal coal what no
this in this chest you have a lot of
wood
holy oh yeah lots of wood wow yeah I
gathered that for us so have one one
yeah yeah yeah thank you you're welcome
so has any has everybody here played
Minecraft before no my first
time years ago yeah a long time ago M
really oh wow okay yeah I only started
last week I
think wow okay it was a very chaotic
experience you've come so
far oh yeah you guys did lots of fun and
we can like do so many things here
especially like now that we have our own
service so exciting so but I think
eventually we'll probably also hang out
at the Japan server right oh yeah I hope
so but I think here we can build our own
Empire yay yes the start ofan Empire
decorate however we
feel yeah sounds good to me tunnels lots
of underground tunnels I am creating
many materials in order to be oh there's
a noise that sounds like okay are you
okay where are you outside alone in the
dark I'm coming there's something
chasing
me I don't know what it they must save K
it's a zombie it's a zombie I with you
before jerks I hate you I got good thing
should she hit me with her bone
what
you oh you guys
building yeah I wanted to build my house
here initially but then I found that
cool hole and now I I don't want to
anymore I just want to take the red this
red
stone can't wait to see your home in the
cave oh thank you I'll do get him
on yeah beat him up beat him
up GAA keeps getting hit it's I am
merely collateral damaged it's all right
up oh my God I'll protect you creeper
[Laughter]
oh
man never leave your back uh how do you
say that unprotected or so always watch
your back oh yeah and watch your six and
all your other numbers too
six who is building here H who is
building
here uh oh that's that is that is the
remains of my first choice of house
placement that I decided not to go along
with so you may take that wood your
first choice was our house but okay
whatever take them down grab gunpowder
you can make TNT let's make let's just
make ridiculous amounts of TNT for no
reason you can use it in our tunnel I
see an end yeah who wants to challenge
the Ender let's go how do you how do you
mess with him just look at him in his
eyes look at his eyes what does he do
take uh take this take this stick and go
poke him with it
okay here I go hold on I wonder if I go
cie okay he's a friend of you from he
will not touch you where'd he go over
there this way behind Amelia's house
show me show me oh I see him on the side
what do I say to him do I just say hello
yeah look at his eyes okay look at his
eyes he he will like you since you're
the death s yeah yeah yeah yeah closer
you look
at yeah good job guys good job what's
happening he's going to
explode no I'm kidding he's moving
blocks cuz he want to build a house
too he how kill him uh whack
them oh your Stu I got it don't
worry w w wo wo buddy I'm not in this
I'm not in this
buddy uh-oh can I go in water
maybe hey w w w
I'm I'll drop it for you did listen end
I I didn't do oh
on he hates Water by the way you just
got to get into the water okay let me
I'm
put no is
unly other worldly is he
gone wait he's still there I almost
looked at him him I almost looked at him
wait I'm coming with the camera the
content the content oh jeez your is hey
skeletons what's up buddy he's going
away he's scared okay no he's
[Music]
not get into the water I'm very afraid
wait that's not KY I thought those were
her guys huh where you at where sorry I
meant to throw it I didn't mean to hit
you thank you it's okay floating away
where did he go where did he go he's
right here we can kill him from the
water don't wor guys I'll find it I'll
find him don't worry I have a wooden
sword will that be useful there it is
there's the chaos him I think they were
over here where we were where we were
let us go oh yes this must be all my we
should go up the stairs so we get a high
advantage point so we can find them
okay get him oh he's weird who whoa whoo
wo buddy what is that over who gave the
zombie a bone
I work so hard for this map oh I am not
losing this
map we got him nice you killed
him yes nice nice good job everyone good
job team sorry I
was right here got my oh there are many
monsters following us oh that's an arrow
from a scr okay I'm going to take them
to everyone so they can kill them for us
right cool that's a good idea hey you
guys are warriors right me too actually
though I want to fight
where's my
sword your arrows are
cowardly arrows for cowards oh sorry
watch I'm
hungry oh
armor I got it
[Music]
where now I have shiny golden pants so I
don't need these um so I will drop them
over here what do you have oh I think
those are mine oh wait no not those no
no oh I'll drop them here they're not
iron leggings I have shiny pants so this
is for those are
M oh there we
are yeah get
him you got a couple arrows in your KNE
you
know so are we going to
be oh she said it she said she said it
she said it freaking
hurt I was hoping to Coast right by that
one but
nope never miss a
chance so are we building this uh this
tunnel yeah let's do it let's do it all
right we're going to need have materials
pickaxes say does everybody have stone
pickaxes I have I have um yeah I have a
stone and then I have a golden axe a
golden axe whoa I do W okay we should
bring uh we can bring here I'll go gra M
hold
on Kelly had a had a golden uh pickaxe
with silk PS the other day and used it
all up on gravel and then it broke yeah
a you said I could I hey I asked you
katori I said hey can I use this and you
said it's fine we won't even need it
away later and it'll be gone by then so
I used it don't try I didn't know it had
silk touch that's kind of changes the
game all
right oh hold on uh we should bring
torches I have a bunch of torches yes
torches and and um lots of packs and
food don't forget some
food I'm going to go pick up my oh
rations right I got to go grab some
rations we are going exploring today I'm
so excited I hope we find diamonds I go
ooh find Diamonds oh yes I need a new I
want like a new chain a CH
yeah chain diamond diamond chain some
ice oh thanks wel got all right so I'm
bringing my furnace and crafting table
in case we need to do some uh emergency
crafting to make more stuff idea so
pretty hey look at that guys get this
zombie look at how much he has what
do you mean where get him get him right
in front of me look where where are you
silk touch helmet and and leggings oh I
see it what is your location I only have
a hole though I'm in front of ena's
house okay come a hole you got to get
him hold on oh my sword's gone ah wait I
don't have a weapon I've got a sword I'm
coming I only have a hole oh hang on cow
iron sword and he's got wheat
him my ah
no
yay go anything are you freaking kidding
me what was the point what was the
freaking
point oh
it's all right we live we're
goodam let's go let's go uh oh wait wait
I'm going to go give this to
your he's in my house I closed the
door safe in town the horses like wheat
[Music]
you go
J I lost a ton of hell I'll be home soon
[Music]
Janan all right Morgan but we're not
supposed to go right straight right G
you got to lead us where we going to go
organizing the ship oh we got to wait
for everybody else uh does everybody
have like food and stuff or should we
just uh bringing some from my uh chest
my chest got blown up oh
no so this is going to be you have a
pickaxe okay we can build pickaxe uh
here I'll go build I'll build some uh
Stone pickaxes for everybody just so we
have extras extr is always good so for
those of you that uh maybe just arrived
to the stream what we're going to be
doing is be building a uh underground
tunnel
the beach to the Atlantis exactly which
is about 1,000 blocks in the other
direction
so I have rations and digging materials
wait where's my wood Chad says music is
too loud thank you I shall
[Music]
adjust all right I have just to the
music does anybody have wood I have some
Spruce plants has a has a lot of
[Laughter]
wood can I go steal some
Kiara yep for the
tunnel for for pickaxes ah oh yeah yeah
go ahead make some
sticks yes make some sticks so we can
make some uh sticks
some what was I
doing wait you got sticks can I steal
your sticks here oh yeah it's not many
but sure okay it's a full stack but
thank you I appreciate it a full
okay
wow was excited to start our adventure
wait where am I going down under the
water a spr
hello I'm just making more sticks just
in case good idea I'll make some sticks
too how many are we we are five
people oh I got my own I got my own
pickaxes oh I five that's
should um all right who need a lot
pickaxes well take a you I give you all
righty are they in your inventory or
yeah come here come to the tunnel and
I'll uh I'll start Doan up oh yeah
whoever needs
pickaxes all right you get a pickaxe you
get a pickaxe you get a pickaxe and you
get a pickaxe
you not picking up any now I'm picking
them
up yay
[Music]
pickaxes all right so
what you doing
a fishing
fishing so with this should we dig uh
ooh o a cave Kelly you see this found
one yeah I tried to cover that up again
but uh it's kind of in the way a well we
can start digging down because I think
for this okay we have to dig down and
then we got to do a complete 180 I see I
see face the opposite
direction like that way which way yes
that
way why don't we start over that
late because the tunel it'll look
[Laughter]
cool I'm trying to
help I'm trying to help we're going down
we're going down so we definitely have
to dig a up deep enough to you pass the
water that's the
thing oh that's true now it's
professional I'm the camer
man we're going down we can't can't drop
down too much this has fall damage so oh
yes please be careful torches to me
leave the Torches to me potato you're
the
fire oh something broke oh that was my
ow
uhoh o cool cool we can make more
torches yay oh it's starting to get a
little dark I am the cameraman I like
it a now it's white the Hol doent hard
work hi you
watching
hi oh yes stairs stairs I can uh oh no
it's fine here I'll help uhoh I heard a
noise he something wait should we uh
okay do the 180 the
360 uh as soon as we get uh deep enough
so that we're below the water cuz
otherwise that'll be unfortunate oh yeah
I found gold I found gold wow someone
has a steel axe a steel
pickaxe did you just yeah I took it
that's that was just iron that was just
iron that was just
iron wow you got me real excited
there
iron does everybody have a
sword me uh I
can realiz I have a St one okay okay
Kiara has a sword I have a sword Callie
has a sword
has I make a
sword with my fist she's got her fisty
cuffs we'll be perfectly
fine don't worry all right getting real
loud huh as long
as oh that was me that K that was Cara
that was not
me I would never hit
KY oh on Kelly what's that noise ah
what's that a rat that what the
what's that a
rat get get him there's
coming oh my God I have to something oh
my God there's so many freaking rats
there's so many rats when did they put
rat
[Music]
in
dead God close the hole close the
hole hey silverfish
called the silver
fish what is wrong with them never
saw I'm just staying down he just ate my
sand wait what's the picking up my stuff
or is everyone dead I'm alive but I'm
hiding in a hole hiding hole boy oh boy
oh boy oh boy what
the that was spooky I'm grow
yeah where's my stuff is my stuff still
there
must dig
onward I up hold you good Watson are you
good fish want fish yeah I had I had
grilled fish a bunch of pickaxes and uh
some other stuff oh I have your grilled
fish would you like it back yeah fishy
do here I'll drop a couple pickaxes for
you here you can come get him where'd
you go I hear more Silverfish
oh how do you also does someone have my
sword uh sword what kind of Sword did
you have a normal stone sword I don't
have it I only have mine I think I think
I have it I have it I have it o I hear
them
hissing make all of these stones into
gold it'll be like a golden stairway
once golden Stairway to lead to the
golden yo yeah exactly oh
wait you guys think we can start going
please uh is Everybody's Health okay
yeah I'm fine Y how about you I
have all right all
right I'm good going to make a I gave
you your fish oh I tossed it them
somebody else must have taken it cuz I
uh I I toss my fish no okay I bring new
food I'll bring some new food and some
new stuff
new
torches gosh that growling is really
loud
huh oh Ghost Rider stop you can't play
with
us uh I think we'll build stairs now
going the other way you know what I mean
you want you want
to so you want to turn around here yeah
all right all right I think it should be
enough you want to like go left or right
or
now we're going to go straight down I
like the way you think good
drop we'll just we'll just make a U-turn
like
uh now we build stairs going this way
okay nice
idea wait maybe we need to go a little
further yeah I don't like that hissing
that's a it's getting real intense
huh you have some food Kiara I would
like a little bit yeah yeah I brought
some some lamp
perfect thank
you oh wait you mean for you can I have
like two two or
three oh sure I have uh 10 but let me
give you some now turn around two two is
fun Sho perfect thank
you uh-oh oh that's really
loud don't worry about it fine are you
sure everything is d d
I can we go
straight I wonder if it's a straight
from
here yeah maybe let's just go straight
should probably be deep enough yeah I
think so uh
wait surprisingly relaxing isn't it I
would like it if the music came on but
like yeah I wish we could choose when it
came on
this is tunnel building
everyone I'll make a higher ceiling GAA
is the mining supervisor I'm the
cameraman the
cameraman there's a piece missing out of
the oh was that a
squeak are we going in the right
direction now yes I hope so really well
good good said it was in the opposite
this is the right direction
yes dig until we get to the ocean right
yes oh no she doesn't know
behind oh again it's died it died nice
nice finish you protect the coordinates
I'm so concerned that girl's the one
giving us Direction no no no no listen
listen it'll be okay are we not building
into
nowhere no of course not we're build
we're building an adventure we'll get
somewhere yeah I can't wait to see where
we come
out this is what keeps it uh it's uh
keeps you on the edge of your seat you
never know like where you're going to
come out yeah exactly no I'll check the
coordinates that scary sound F3 we won't
make fun of your
PC I know that's a lie but don't worry
it's okay oh iron
nice we can start making uh armor for
Kiara and then uh some better pickaxes
or actually swords would be a better
idea oh wow huge iron W wo nice W let's
fill that up though with normal
Stone
K you're hitting with the sword yeah
excuse you want you want to change that
oh another
iron ar oh
man this is mining ASMR how does
everybody like it it's really relaxing
feel like I could take a
nap just just keep pressing forward and
your left Mouse button and you can sleep
yeah
okay I just can someone Place torches oh
yeah well well that's Oh I thought that
was a cave it just it was just
Dark Void mode yeah that really it
looked like the void that was scary W oh
is that the sound the void
Mak how you doing
crew we are cleaning up the ceiling look
at this teamwork
[Laughter]
I'm a bit worried where we're going but
other than
that get there nah don't worry about it
otherwise GAA if we end up like
somewhere completely else and you just
got to build your your Ocean House there
where we get out sounds like it's got to
be like this is where it was always
supposed to be uh yes a change a change
in the
plans did you even get very far and
building it uh no I haven't started
building it yet oh wait wait a minute oh
wait I was supposed to say that after we
finished the tunnel my
bad you haven't uh
What uh what hey though we're going to
go see the beach
yay are you sure I feel like maybe I
should go back up top and Scout to make
sure we're going like somewhere we're
perfect I'll be back hold
on was there
recently it's the beach episode you are
right that's exactly can we can we build
a hot spring in onang yeah please let's
build an onang for the back episode
IR interesting good stuff the house of
GAA never existed in the first
place thingers girls
house has there ever been a house hey
man hey hey hey hey hey hey hey I hear
lava uhoh lava is very close uhoh you
can hear lava I've never heard of that
before I don't
know oh the tunnel's getting real small
now you got to be careful I give if you
heal lava you got to be careful where
you a where you
digging
uh this lava we just go straight no
swerving just go
St I'm feeling a little
claustrophobic oh got the ceiling yeah
all right I'm going to check the
coordinates just keep going team we're
good we're good we're
golden what are you doing Cara I I'm to
go straight yeah keep I'm just covering
up the
lava I got I got to write these
coordinates down in my in my in my map
hold on let me pull up my map
notepad all right so we are 30
pieces okay now start
[Music]
um how are we doing supervisor
uh how's it
going
well oh no where's
an uh I'm up top checking to make sure
you guys are going in uh towards some
goal okay that's yeah Fair that's fair
that's fair all right I'm going to I'm
going to F3 real
quick our coordinates
are uh 355
my oh wait hold on I have to do math
wait okay the
end the maybe I should post the end the
end uh these are the end gold
coordinates um where you posted in the
in the in the Minecraft chat
oh and and the the Z
is right
[Music]
um so we're good we're doing fine are we
are
we we're
doing uhoh oh that was not mine I found
mushrooms no they're not mushrooms never
mind are they flowers a just purple
flowers I like mushrooms from far away
apparently GAA has a good P SE the chat
says nice be
wellingt that's a tasty steak yummy I've
never eaten them before what is beef
wellington what is it it
it's baked is it a
baked
um it's well beef
Fon be well beef inton
Bellington it's the beefiest
beef beef
[Laughter]
swelling I found pumpkins she found
pumpkins the
pumpkins uh yeah so I'm pretty far like
it's pretty far I haven't found the
ocean yet
I'm still
going I
me Adventure something spooky let's hope
we run into something fun yes
yeah I'll take on any monster except for
the silverfish and
zombies what also creepers and Ender
whatever those blind
things the dragon the the pterodactyl
what was that all about yeah and the
timing though the timing the
timing yeah oh my God sniped on the
rooftop oh dirt interesting oh Chad is
saying that those were not dragons those
were Phantoms
Phantoms
yeah they spawn when you haven't slept
oh
interesting remember kids is important
or the Phantoms will get
you I kind of like them more
now Phantoms are my
friends in the pickax
Department I I got pickaxes too here
I'll drop some okay I got I need one to
oh thank you thank
you oh yeah I didn't think it would be
that
far the track huh she did say like a
thousand us can use a morning J on our
way to the beach it's fine J the tunnel
well here's here's the endle right who's
going to want to walk this entire way
right
nobody yeah but if it's for fitness and
exercise maybe it's
fine no no no no no okay okay okay
here's my pitch ready for this we cover
the entire bottom with ice and then we
get a mine cart so we or a boat we get a
boat so we can
just that is a perfect idea it's like
the
Metro
I that's right Hall's going to have a
Subway huh yeah Subway and not the
sandwich kind yeah I was about to order
my oh that sounds good I want to order
something what should I have for
lunch breakfast pizza
pizza good taste good taste always pizza
so I had pizza yesterday
you
can if I die do I lose
everything you're going to have to uh
remember where you are cuz that's where
all your stuff will
be all of it yeah I don't see me dying
no I'm not dying yet I'm just thinking
I'm really far and I'd rather just die
to spawn back than walk
back way to do
it oh light
guys I don't see an end to this I don't
see any ocean you just keep going
straight don't worry I know the way okay
okay know the
[Music]
way do are are sharks good with like
coordinates and
orientation of course of
course don't I would think shars are
quite intelligent
normally what do you mean
normally
[Laughter]
hey hello I'm pretty good when you got
blood in the water oh
yes what the hell I heard a train
track really I heard a train yeah it was
like like an abandoned M shaft
maybe to find some uh some real good
goodies in there yeah like diamonds for
my
Cham spider spawners yay yay I squeaking
I hear squeaking it's a bat get
ready a bat or that silver what's myall
it shrimp looking thing silver fish we
just find everything except a good ass
home no we'll find it don't worry I I I
trust you get
okay
okay so do you guys want to me
find
H can you find it if it doesn't
exist oh oh I see I
see wasn't this a thing with Atlantis um
I I feel like I saw that in the
movie Atlantis is hard to find you just
got to look really it does exist of
course it exists
I really dang
it the the coordinates you put in the
chat is that for where you were or is
that your
coordinates is her house that's my
that's my house I HIIT my house did you
find it no no no no no I was just
wondering did we go past the M shaft oh
I think it's this
way oh there's iron here
exploring the M shaft could be something
we can do maybe on another time but I no
pickaxes anymore I have pickaxes wait I
someone spot me thank you thank you of
course I'm just going to fill this
up all right I'm going to I'm going to
wait where's my okay we're fine don't
worry about it
while they dig I'm going to I'm going to
set up shop here
okay is the stream not going to end
until we find a tunnel could this be a
24hour
stream 24hour here we go tunnel or
Diamond a hole here got a B I'm going to
kill him careful I'm going to kill
him huh no you you will not disate
tunnel oh
ouch
yeah I don't think we're going the right
way what you mean we're going the right
way hold
on I
colle hello uh
ohep you look like a pink
pish I have a exploded to creeper help
oh there was a creeper are you okay come
yeah I I just lost one height I'm fine
he okay okay are we going the right way
app shamies love apples we're going
the right way guys don't worry are you
sure I feel like we barely made the
progress it was a big project to
undertake I I started going the same way
that you guys were building and I'm at
the Z coordinate is at
990 and it should be going the other way
shouldn't it cuz good as Z coordinate
was 137 or something like 106 so if I
start going the way that I came back
from then it starts going the right way
maybe we should have made the
360 excuse me is
that wait wait wait wait wait
wait listen we just need to um we just
need to reroute we just need to Route
yes did you start going the wrong way
no yeah we've been thinking for 20
minutes all right fill her back up boys
fill her back up no no no
wait what's going to be down here huh I
mean this is this is the right X this is
we're on the right way for the x
coordinate yeah yeah yeah yeah sort of
yeah I mean it's going up the X the Z
who cares about the Y right the Y is in
the middle right I I don't know I don't
know I don't play this game I don't know
and then the the the wait which is the Z
wait why is the Z like that hold
on is is z is z up and down or like what
what is chat can you guys help us a y is
up and
down okay so Z is the one that you're
going the wrong way on
right Z doesn't matter sh X we're also
not moving forward at all I feel like
going this way like this way yeah the
way we go X doesn't move a centimeter at
all what I'm
trying I I still believe in you I
believe you can you can take us the
right direction let's just figure it out
okay at the very least we're going the
right Z direction right X Direction X
direction we have to go this way like no
X I mean that's fine once you get get
out you can like go that way but the Z
direction is really
important wait
what
oh all right te here's the new plan
we're going to we're going to we're
going
to what we're going to bang a
left right
here yeah left in a hole here we go here
going to trust you
[Music]
ah yes nothing smells like
teamwork and we probably should have
checked this before we started instead
of trusting her sorry maybe we
can maybe that's a whole subway line
that we just made automatically right
off the bat we can use it later yeah
wherever you guys turned we can make
like a stairs upwards and then we can
use that as like a building ground and
like flatten it out we can make little
train stops and we you can write numbers
on them okay okay okay okay train
station okay it's a big plan we can make
a big colored map like like
like wait that's too much isn't it no no
no we can have little colored dots on
the side like real Subway we have to
okay yeah like a little map key yeah a
map key
lines we can
calline gine all name
the
uh can I make
boots everyone needs nice pair of boots
nice pair of
boots yeah Here My Dear take this put
this on and put this on oh well thank
you
yes this back
up is this gooda fashion
yes shiny silver like a
shark neat oh I hear
skeleton
Skellington to your
right I hear water ooh this might get
interesting oh hope we don't flood the
tunnel that we just
made is the only Survivor
yeah that's you guys can just seal it
back up if anything happens yeah should
be
fine wait I'm a time traveler she's
outside does she know what's going to
happen hey wait a minute now wait a
minute if you know something water I
hear water oh guys wait wait stop stop
look look above us look oh good
eyes water above us let's pop a hole and
see what happens the ocean wait
uh yeah here's a sand gravel sand
whatever keep going forward we won't
have to mess with maybe we should get a
little lower if we if we just carve out
a a bit like one block down maybe we can
n come on where's your sense of
adventure it's not that I don't have it
it's just as death I really don't want
to die in this game
dying in Minecraft is just a part of
Minecraft
oh oh I keep thinking that water's
coming in yeah getting kind of intense
huh oh yeah it's right above us it's
even leaking through the Cobblestone oh
baby of course of course G you'd be fine
with the water right of course
you yeah
sure must I remind you I have a human
body
now
unfortunately I'm going to I'll meet you
guys there I'm too lazy to go all the
way back and in your tunnel so I'll just
uh I'll just meet you guys
there
sounds traveler I I'll start digging
from from from uh good as coordinates
and then I'll meet you there meet oh
good idea are you sure that we'll be
meeting are you sure that we'll be
meeting though I feel like you'll just
be digging somewhere
else we can try okay I'll just wait
there for you guys you're not that far
right boy just like a thousand thousand
units away don't wor that a lot all
right I'll go back I don't know what our
home coordinates are I don't know how to
get back oh we're going down oh
me is that anybody I think we have the
home coordinate somewhere right uh yes
yes they were yes oh yeah K car posted
them okay uh yeah uh you want them
they're uh yeah I can find them I can
find thank you wait we're going down
down down away from the water I think
okay oh no I just kind of duck down cuz
there was our oh okay detour this works
this works oh we are going forward okay
okay now you're making some progress but
we still got to oh wait I see a
cavern careful only a th more really
deep one things to go I think I see gold
oh
care oh my God don't fall down here
what do we do what do we do let's
explore yeah do you don't want to fall
down there go down I Che it out okay be
careful be careful how do I do this
Crouch
whoa
okay that's really
deep oh my oh my wow okay um
whoa yeah I did it oh man good find wow
wow wow whoops how are we going to make
this into our tunnel though I wonder we
can put glass up so people can walk
through it and like look and be like wow
yeah it's like it's like uh in the
subways you sometimes like go like in on
a bridge and you see outside idea yeah
exactly for now we should make this a
bit wider so people don't have S
yeah
oh watching she's got
it you I felt that in my heart I knew
that was going to
happen oh no
oh no I did not have enough practice
with crouching and making Bridges yet
what can you well just I don't think I
had much important stuff down there just
leave it
there hey who has glass does anyone have
glass oh that's sad make glass I I'm
going to be there soon oh cool yes
please I'll bring some glass end is in
my house Ender is in my house again just
don't make ask for roommate but not for
this roommate I wanted I wanted a human
roommate why is he back again I kicked
him out on a different server already
and now he's back
again he want to be your roommate wants
to yeah you said the rent was free I
mean good deal a good
deal oh God I'm going to post this on
Twitter right
[Laughter]
now oh oh there's iron I'm not greedy
enough I'm out of pickaxe out of gotcha
pickaxes thank you oh
yes too much Stone now uh I can take
your
stone okay I I'll throw that out okay
that's good a little window here and
then a little window here here
cool you might we might find diamond
wow we need
goep I want to find
some hey how do you build
uh R you can't have
them oh nice music yeah I think I should
probably do this real quick wait there's
music do I have the music turned off
maybe everyone gets different music at
different times oh probably I hear like
some magical music I don't hear any
music but the sunny is coming
up we don't see
it we can build a six sunroof someday
it's been
3,563 days since I've seen
sunlight
a minute so to speak but not really a
minute it's been longer than a minute
but that is what that is what people say
when they say that it's been a long time
is they say it's been a
minute uh um I think our tunnel is
getting bigger I think it
is to make it three three blocks again
yeah let's do that let's see we
can just take three blocks from here
yeah yeah from here we can do it like
that where everyone oh where is it I'm
Mak glass and then I'm I'm joining your
tunnel okay
okay it's fine we'll just keep we'll
just keep digging
[Music]
away is this this is right
right yeah we're making progress in the
X Direction and then we have to go all
the way
up like 300 blocks Z Direction
afterwards that is
fine wait is this Sandy yeah it looks
like sand are we in the desert are we
going the right
way going to the beach the beach has
sand beach oh that's you guys getting
close good at height what are you tell
be careful it doesn't land on your head
when you die
yeah a long way
back some how much glass do you guys
need um just enough to make some windows
in the in a hallway so I mean probably a
decent amount maybe like is there any
way to speed up the furnace or it just
goes no that's as fast as it goes dang
okay well I'll be there in like 10
minutes goodness
gracious I'm on the way back to you guys
now I'm running and running and running
and
running go k go it's fine Ena and I are
still digging
away take a tunnel take a tunnel than
can you place the signs higher oh I
see oh are you making signs GAA yeah
just so we don't get too turned around
there so many the sand keeps falling and
falling we're not going to make
progress I see name
tag hello hello I'm back she's back that
was so
funny that was not funny it was I like
had hands on my on my forehead on my
temples like this is going to go bad
and knew okay we're going to have to get
rid of the sand here in order to
progress yeah okay a what was I doing oh
[Music]
yes I have so much I have so many rocks
so much Cobblestone ah we could need a a
shovel for this that would be easier a
shovel I have a shovel oh really with
the shovel that
one and be careful I once suffocated
from being covered up in sand so don't
stand directly under the sand or you
will probably die
okay
it'll here why am I build why am I doing
upwards what wait a minute a shovel just
so you guys know I'm ready whenever okay
coming to suck up all the
Stone thank
you first I eat sand and now you just
eat Stone
girl it's
tasty make sure you chew 2 minutes
before you
swallow important things to remember
this is a really long
tunnel oh yeah the digging is getting a
bit uh
repetitive F your reward will taste so
sweet at the end yeah it will if you're
going the right way have you guys been
checking
um
yeah we've got 100 more blocks yeah okay
let's go let's get it
H life Ian myth Powers
[Music]
unite
yeah my power is the power of fire
what's yours o the power of
direction oh yeah if we were each
elements what would we be
o guess Ena would be like air and gooda
would be would be uh
water fire then I'm Earth and then cie
is the element like Spirit element
element it's
here okay it's just a bat don't worry I
scared it
off I just want to see
hello oh anything useful
here like a
diamond perhaps
wa
mayhaps do you guys think 52 is enough
glass y that sounds perfect that okay oh
baby zombie E I don't like it okay
there's like iron here that I'm going to
get you can keep going or you can come
help if you want just want take anyways
okay I'm just trying toel stay in the
tunnel oh you're here here hi
hello everyone go up there Wonder
there you guys are yeah we should keep
on digging though although otherwise it
will never
end where where was the tunnel people
are asking what we're doing we're we're
building a tunnel to
Atlantis GAA was setting up her uh her
City my big underwater city project I
will be recreating the entire city of
Atlantis underneath the water that's
pretty nuts though isn't it yeah that's
pretty cool
is it going to be like uh you can walk
around somewhere that's not underwater
or will it be like underwater underwater
it'll be under water
underwater and there will
be bubble columns you can utilize for
air that sounds cool yeah I'm excited
it's a lot of work though wow lots of
work wo wo wo I can help you whenever
you
want and you sleep first uh after a nap
are you good
Ina yes
okay oh where's everybody oh I just
covered up the hole that they went
through so that they can cannot come
back
oh don't don't worry emit we just we can
do this together they they'll just he
I'm lost no no we're good we're fine
don't worry about
it no they didn't where' they go oh
they're in behind that wall that I just
built
why where's the wall yeah where's the
[Laughter]
wall well everything is out of stone
so oh I see them through the wall right
here
noem let me let me
in come
on o I'll build an alternate tunnel
it's dark in here now it's really dark
in
hereone she's
crazy got to get out of
here don't worry I'll have we been
betrayed have we been
betrayed think we're okay here I
brought
goodness how do I drop all of what is
this careful careful careful yeah lock
them can't I pick it up hold on I don't
think I have enough room I wait do you
see this do you see this okay watch
cover that wait wait what is
[Music]
that Yar I'm going to go put the
glass what did you
find it's a big hole oh boy I'm going to
go put the glass
up
whoa all right I'm going to find the one
down like a drive through window
Drive the window can you get me a
milkshake hello we would like to get uh
what was it girl
milkshake milkshake we actually we
actually chicken
sandwich um would you
like find way
back we like to get the uh don't worry I
put signs down the combo number
one wait that's not lesson that's like
uh two
is here uh not just
confusing it is confusing we need to
fill up like the whole where are we
going I don't know where the way back is
this way this way this way don't worry
about it uh I think the drivethru is
where we're supposed to yeah the
drivethru window oh my gosh
iing okay well yeah just wanted to have
a little bit of fun you know it's okay
who doesn't have a sword going straight
I don't have one I will build you a
sword
Watson thank
[Music]
you I need another pickaxe too mine's
low yes coming right up here you go
Watson sword pickax
pickax thank you okay okay okay okay
okay thank you ooh yeah
nice I feel like there was music playing
and now it's
gone hello place all the time
whoa cool how much further are we on the
coordinate
supervisor uh we are um we made it about
100 wait let's speed it up
[Music]
we're almost to
500 okay only like a 20 another 20 more
minutes
right yeah this walkway looks cool I'm
proud of forever good job Kelly thanks
Amelia for the
glass oh you're welcome it looks
nice let me see
what
on how's everybody's Food level
pretty decent I have plenty of rations
though I'm still full for some reason
oo oh this is cool fancy yeah it's like
a bridge it's really cool you can see
down where a
phoenix yeah Kiara fell there so it's a
nice memorian quickly hand flowers yeah
yeah I have a sign we we put a sign
something like
Phoenix live number
2,999 here I'll let Callie write it I'll
put it down and you can write on it
thanks I'll take care it to me no no
don't leave it to call she will write no
let me take care of it let me take care
of it just Rite some bullying
words won no I won't no I won't no I
won't no I won't I won't no I won't
I'm going to get there fast I'm going to
beat you guys this is a
race I can still dig in the dark right
yes
yes she's going so fast I don't even see
her
already it's okay I'm on the Ceiling
clean up Duty now oh there's a cave
there's a tunnel over here oo no Comon
wait no I got to make more of
these more
pickax what is this gold or bronze how
do I tell the difference that's
iron iron iron
iron IR okay okay iron iron iron iron
iron let there be light B guys
big
[Music]
IR sorry that's the light orange spell a
r
[Laughter]
n I hear to where you from to see wait
did you die huh no okay thought you died
for a moment wait I have a bed can we
put a bed here and we all save it and
then we respawn here yeaha that works
good idea yes all right I got I put a
bed over here you guys save it why do we
want to respawn here I you know just in
case my
spot go all the
way yeah if you don't want to walk yeah
I mean do you want to walk the rest of
the way here cuz of
thought I'm in here didn't think so did
not think so
all right I'm going to go get quick
there's a really loud growling noise
like right next
door we seem to be dodging all the uh
all the scary
parts I hear a
rat
squeak I hear squeaky
too who needs armor does anybody need
armor I have but give it to Kata give it
to cus she needs it more than me yeah
cuz her uh her last one's kind
of disappeared ah you went you went one
level down Amy oh uh wait I guess it's
all right let's all go
down down from
here oh dirt
blocks uh is that good or is that bad
it's dirt dirt don't hurt okay I thought
I thought if it was dirt we were like
closer to the surface or something just
kidding no torches here no fire
maybe good at iron pickaxes we got to
make sure that everybody has uh sword
and at least some armor before we start
getting crazy with that I would say I
guess squeaky squeaky
what what h well does anybody have iron
like that they they want me to smel yeah
I have IR I have a bunch I'll leave it
by the bed I have a crafting table there
cuz yeah then we can have iron pickaxes
cuz those dig even faster yeah I'm using
an iron pickaxe oh hell
yeah
tasty St
one on the XX we're only halfway there
[Laughter]
we're halfway there even though we're
currently um actually digging towards
the xax oh yeah you need iron pickaxes
to M diamonds so that's actually really
that's actually really that's
good H what's there's more there more
iron wait a second hey okay never mind
what how far did you
go it's like
[Music]
sand it never stops be careful don't
suffocate uh oh okay we we're we're
walking but it's probably
fine pain I heard
the yeah I heard a villager right yeah
oh yeah they're annoying s
sound what are they doing down here are
there villagers
underground the
underground the real you're so far
yeah I'll give you some
light thank
you
pop I'm trying to speed it up a bit go
really fast you guys can clean up my
dust I will fill in the holes until
everything is perfect a here's some
armor well thank you oh
yes does anybody have some food I do
want some just a little bit yeah yeah
let's see I have some potatoes potatoes
okay yes thank you go yeah you got some
potato you're welcome the PE and potato
stands for power power
potato you got it
you power
s the power of potatoes
I like hash
browns hash browns hash browns are good
I think it's the best way you can eat a
potato in my opinion what
about it's not is it hash browns when
there's like it's like shavings of
potatoes that are uh that's just hash oh
I see that is hash browns oh I guess so
oh po hash hash hash hash browns are the
like the kind you can hold in your hand
it's still hash brown even when it's
like a pancake like you can't hold it
yeah I think
[Music]
so hash brown potato dishes can you make
different dishes in this game like cook
I believe so I think so you can make a
pumpkin pie yeah you can make pumpkin
pie you have pumpkin pie for
Thanksgiving oh pumpkin pie
now I'm suddenly hungry I am
too just so
speed m is really
fast I'm a
gamer tunel he a Zoomer there's a tunnel
over here wait one I don't help you guys
clear it
up a natural tunnel but it's sort of off
it's not like exactly lined up with ours
but it's going like the
the right way pretty much oh that's good
we can hold it yeah I think it's fine
okay like where's my
sticks stick nice
stick ah creeper
no here
I'm
go did you did you save the bed did you
save at the
bed yeah
I'm going to I'm going to take that as a
[Music]
no we told you we told
you well I mean walking over there
didn't take so much time but can someone
pick up my
stuff there is still some stuff left
over all right all right I got some some
armor and some some
meat
oh uh-oh r what's going on it's another
creeper is a creeper no I got it I'm
coming with the camera don't die yet I'm
coming no don't be a heroa don't be a
hero I only I didn't even lose a heart I
I mean one good thing is that my
Enderman Roommate is gone so that's good
oh this are in here oh
hello you guys have some more pickaxes
for when I come back or yes yes
okay I have iron pickaxes too yay
speed oh this is where she
died went pretty far she went so far
maybe you should Place another sign this
is also where the food
died a little face I have sign Reed her
here Callie I I'll let you do the honors
again all right
cool these will be
Memorial cool
where are you guys wow you're deep oh
there you are GAA hello I was looking
for you
okay thank
you I'll pick it up there it is I got it
here I got iron pickaxe for you this
cave just Curves in like a little circle
so we got to start digging again yeah
where did she die by the way can you
tell me I didn't I wasn't here for it uh
it's at the bottom of the stairs where
all the her stuff is right here okay
okay cool oh I'm sorry I picked up that
pickaxe does someone else want no no
it's okay it's iron it's good here okay
here's all our
stuff I'll put next to this
[Music]
torch
yes here lies
kiar I see the sign here lies K who LOL
no surprise died again ha well well
smite copi Mari you have a typo in there
what do you mean typo okay where in
surprise you wrote s u p r i s e you're
missing an r no
[Laughter]
cares I'll light your way whaton you can
correct it if you
want
nah how we looking now on the
coordinates let me check that for you we
we are oh wow lots of progress we're
[Music]
750 so we still have like
300 what was it 11 12 13 600 we're more
than halfway there on the X ACC we still
have the Z AIS to Y AIS the Z AIS to
take into consideration y I will not
take a nap until we find the other side
listen this is like a road trip we are
bonding this is
bonding this is a te
building window here there's a window
yeah we could put a little window here
looks cute nice IDE oh
nice how bu track uh you need to find oh
hello you need to find the
ooh the recipe for it uh I think you can
build them or maybe you have to find the
abandon M shafts will have a railway or
yeah yeah yeah Minecart stuff oh she
beat me to you have to find it you can't
build it uh that'll be a question for
chat
chat tell us CH pocket Wiki Kiara is
hiding where's kiar oh kiar on the
screen I ran out of pickaxes I got
you here
a window oh hey wait this is an iron
pickaxe this is
faster it's a little bit brighter yeah
you yeah iron here you
go thank you so now everybody should
have one then whenever Ki comes back K
are you
here yeah ceiling a little higher it's a
bit it's a bit short for me I know that
all of you ladies are rather small
um I need it to be a little taller did I
miss the sign where the sign no I put it
up where you exped it's it's getting a
little claustrophobic in
here there's a skeleton trying to kill
me you need help in our tunnel no no no
I'm just leading the skeleton to you
guys
now okay you got to F it
off oh delicious coal I see sparkly
stuff on my screen oh
nice sparkly is fun isn't it good you
got some pickaxes does this happen to
you guys like right here sparkly uh here
take this one this one's wait wait take
this one this is a faster one it's an
iron pickaxe but here's Stone if you
need extras cuz I
got yes of course
is oh lava lav we got we have any glass
we can build a glass Bridge let's see I
used it all on Windows darn it Bridges
bridges very good yes I like wait are
you still up top I know I'm here behind
you I hang on I'll go I'll sacrifice
some from the
window it's closed now we never going
toble can open a
s oh the music
what music I haven't any
music music
like I wish it played all the
time playl on the background Minecraft
playlist oh yeah oh yeah you could just
turn on the music but then it clashes
mus start
playing excuse
me um
this gives me great
worry what oh nothing we're okay don't
worry about
it what worries you GA let me listen to
your wor oh no it was just a it was just
a a
dark dark actually we we're like we're
supposed to go to like X around thousand
and we're now at X around 830 that that
is something oh
1300 oh well I
mean I did not I've been very clear in
in in uh yeah it's just a bit more a bit
more maybe about 50 more
minutes this is the part where you go
are we there
yet are we there
yet are we there yet but we'll be there
soon I bet not even 50 minutes
50 I'm making I'm making a lot of
progress well careful there's a giant
hole here Kiara oh maybe I should have
told her
that keep it a
surprise I'm going to go get uh all our
stuff so we can uh make make equipment
closer to the action yeah good
idea
yes ah how do how do I how do I uh okay
okay okay I he lava in here where's my
axe okay there you
are hey you're in my track I'm
helping got to make sure everybody's got
what they need right chat
right uh we should be good we don't need
any of that right wait
okay oh yeah we we were going to wait we
talk about the golden yo
no yeah we were we were going to build a
giant golden Yago but we thought it
would take too long um as good I said it
would take like six hours
probably and we didn't have enough
materials either like we put the golden
Yago through like one of those imagify
thingies that turns him into like a grid
for blocks mm and there was a lot we
needed a lot of stuff I don't think we
had enough but we'll do it at some point
I think that'd be
fun H you went down
like all of us will surely have a lot of
gold this is so loud in my ears right
now keelly you have to come up one one
block oh whoopsie
doodle there's water water there's water
here wait and it goes down what the heck
water a
water a water no this is is fine this is
this is fine oh what the heck what are
these whoa I'm coming there's a there's
a look there's a room here room spiders
spiders uhoh I'm
poisoned uhoh okay um nobody panic I
don't have my I don't have my sword
equipped I'm poisoned got it run run run
run run Kata you're a warrior
right yeah fight him I got one get him
I'm out of stamina ah are we good are we
good I think we're
good okay okay okay for now now that's
nice yeah I don't know well I guess it's
fine look there's a thing
here oh can lava lava is close this it
like goes all the way down goes down
really deep
whoa hey I can ride on the water
look I'm on the
water maybe this will be the boat will
be like the river path the boat slowly
moving we need a fairy man get a fairy
man we'll hire a skeleton oh all right
fine we he
lava bubble bubble all right what do we
need we need
water uh we need um
how do you
crouch uh shift
shift never mind yep I thought shift was
just walk nope oopsie oopsy I flooded
flooded everything flooded flooded
flooded River a
river what sorryyy come on
huh upwards upwards why we can have a
boat yeah you can have a boat yeah I
want to build want to build a boat a
boat thing have a
canal I stopped the fling I stopped it I
want to see the boat I'm coming
no that was for our
boat where did it
go wait what did I miss where was it it
was way up here wasn't it
I thought I opened something
accidentally oh well it's oh here it
comes oh there it is yay yeah so then
next time when we come back we can have
like a cool boat pass cool that sounds
fun how we going to get the boat back
though figure it out
later it's like a oneway kind of deal
don't you put the boat in your inventory
I accidentally took out one of the
pleas oh yeah probably maybe we can have
a walkway
next it doesn't go far enough
a my boat dream I know how about we make
like a little underwater Lake River
thing I like it I like it it's like a
little little Scenic Tour on the on the
way to the ocean
is
this oh did
you yay more water more water more water
more water more water more
water right here we have our stairs to
go back up okay yeah maybe we have like
a pathway that doesn't have water for
going back
yeah I I love you guys I really do I
love you too I love you
too
me fine
kiss did you did you guys
uh did you see the chest right
here nope it's got diamonds in
it justest where with the spiders yeah
it's sitting in this mine cart right
here you guys kind I guess you walked
right by it there's a mine cart I mean I
found that like area but I didn't know
there was a chest yeah get us the
diamond
pickaxe uh
okay I'm going to clean up this
area let's thrill this out of here we
want that m
God oh we can use
this um Granite who needs Gran so this
is an abandoned M shaft where that
spider I think got you
guys yeah that's what I thought it was
but I didn't know you could I didn't
know how to explore it
more yeah it goes on and on and on and
on o
SPID oh my God go strangers not it's not
karaoke stream Ena but you never mind
keep going I like it be a karaoke
stream I hope I don't get you copyright
strike say hey let's change it to
something
that's your B down free domain yes free
domain is this too skinny what haven't
we usually been doing three wide instead
of two wide I guess it's too late now we
got go speed and then we can expand yeah
we can always expand yeah we can always
refine our tunnel oh yes always room for
improvements it's just it's been uh
almost two
hours yeah but for the first hour we
didn't really work on the mine we showed
everybody our house I'm really far back
oh wait I was going to do
something oh it sure is a lot of water
does someone have some food I have some
bread I have some bread but it's
everybody gets
one actually how do I throw it everybody
gets um who I press to
throw
[Music]
uh throw it out of your inventory drag
it out okay got it can I just have can I
just take one out of my inventory y here
I'll give you I'll give you three it's
the
[Music]
music thank you welcome I never thought
I'd hear the music
catch I have the playlist on wait I went
the wrong
way day 4,000 we're running low on
food we're going the right way right so
supervisor girl in days hold on I got to
go check on the the iron
Supply are we going the right way um uh
yeah p a thousand we're past a thousand
pretty
close it's like 300 more to go wait are
we going to come out in the
water
no no be fine right yes oh I'm out of
pickaxes uhoh I have one I can give you
here you're welcome uhoh there's a
squeaky dang it dang it dang it dang it
this is
bad right there oh Pi it back up all
right oh I
did oh that's mine that's mine you okay
you
know have a and a
dream my pickax is R get I need pickaxes
I'm coming I got it got it I bet is dead
it's there it's there oh okay hang on
here it is you try again there it
is
myh okay okay okay oh I got it I got
[Music]
it going to D some Stone
cuz
Okay can you like uh like you guys were
saying before that you need we need
yellow dye for the golden
yo down again I'm alive we can use um
alive all right I'm building a bridge
dandel give a yellow dye yeah but how do
we uh like can we what can we die
uh the wo from the Sheep the wool when I
was building the yo it said that we
could use a lot of terracotta like
there's uh skeletons here with arrows
and also uh chests chest diamond diamond
diamond chest I don't see anything down
I'll Build A Stairway I don't see anyone
anything guys don't fall don't fall I
started to build a bridge but I'll Build
A Stairway a Stairway
proper I'm coming don't die yet let me
catch it on camera
where are you did you guys fall yeah
yeah I got too ambitious I fell
again where myself up I learned a neat
trick it's called jump and place a
block go no I can't do it anymore where
is everyone oh it's dark down there you
guys want some torches I need a pickaxe
here you go I don't see anything where
is everyone help hey the good thing is
you're closer to the diamond down there
so that's a good diamond yeah there's a
lava and waterfall over here on the on
the right oh you need
pickaxes sorry wait if I toss this down
then they're just going
to it's fine I'll build up some floor
for us yeah I'm all my way down uhoh a
skele a
skeleton I'm hit I'm hit I'm hit I'm hit
I'm hit please um um I don't I don't
have my pickaxe wa nobody panicked the
first step is nobody
panic oh sorry about that oh my
[Music]
Goda careful careful you know be
careful okay there's steps
here where I'm trying to build this oh
my gosh you have you're
hit here let's step here there's a
Creeper down there a zombie down there
too jump here I can't get up I need a
pickax
hang on uh I think I might have one
extra spare let me see there we
go are you good okay I think I think
good has yeah oh yeah I got pickaxes
here you want you want I only got one
left I'll toss them at you here take a
iron pickaxe
and yes oh thank you where is our tunnel
now what
what that let's kill those guys cuz they
have chests maybe they have like really
good loot in there yeah let's get them
yeah I'll make some uh I'll make some
swords if anybody needs a CO are we
still going in the right direction now
we still here stop what I think we
should start again on doing the three
three
wide all you guys ready let's go attack
yes let's get them okay wait wait got to
build stairs before we fall
yeah uh anybody uh okay um maybe you
catch him by surprise if you go this
way okay
does anybody have
wood not right now I have yeah I have
some Spruce planks awesome do you need
planks GAA I love some here you go 16 of
them thank
you our coordination is a bit
go down down why don't hey guys why
don't we go this way and surprise them
flank them um okay I need I need food
please Kara you have food right
absolutely nothing because I died to
here I'll give you a bread hold on
here's one bread rationing bread oh
thank you you're welcome
wait inventory wait oh I have my
red oh God ACA that was
familiar okay okay okay okay okay PS
your
head guys I'm trying my hardest all
right I'm trying better
way I see him down there I see up ready
to attack I'm anybody need a
sword all right lad we go in there's no
turning
back oh my
God there's a spawner right there
what is that what do that mean they are
going to be nonstop spawning I need to I
need to think please don't die oh my God
okay um think think think on your toes
how do we kill the spawner I think you
just smacked the hell out of it I'm
going to die I'm going to die you're so
many chests in here guys we can't we
can't
lose help me get the spawner
guys all right all
right oh there's behind there's people
more
find him on my way back all right maybe
we should um help
help I'm on my way back I'm running
light speed at least get the chest at
least loot the chest there were so many
chests oh yeah we could try to loot the
chest and then get out then get out of
there
[Music]
h I wasn't really carrying any no no no
no good night we are going into H
noise
Ina I will win okay don't give up Ena
somebody says Place torches put torch on
the spawn
okay are you guys winning
don't go in there don't go in there
don't go in
there oh my God it's okay but I put I
put lights I put lights
in oh they're coming for us quick
getting black close up close
up did you guys win uh
I want those chests to find toine Wind
wait
put on our way
back put torches on all sides of the
spawner there's five six seven skeletons
in
there can we make a
shield yes okay I'm going to make some
space so we can put down I have a
crafting
table what if you guys what if you guys
um like build them you trap them in
there and then you kill them one at a
time you have any
TNT good
idea no does anybody have gun have an
apple oh I just I think hey if you guys
are up there can you um can you get some
I think I just ate all our R I don't
have a
sword hey
gu Shield GAA Shield thank you okay
Shield okay okay
okay there's a zombie okay I got to fall
down he's gone no I died again what okay
I got a shield who
wants oh my God no he's got
gold guys I'm think I'm going to never
mind that won't work do you want to go
in that you know what's your health at
I'm I'm Max I can tank
okay here's a
shield um I'm just going to get rid of
this
Stone this is fine What's happen right
here one of the zombies had gold
armor I got him I killed him I spammed
him to death hitting him with a block
nice wait where are
you where's the
sh oh creeper no come on man not now not
now no how do I help
I I reached the point
where okay we're fine we're fine we're
fine you have food no I ate all the
rest okay I'll give me some salmon thank
you okay here's here's the shield I see
you guys now I'm coming to join you
uh-oh oh man oh man oh man here here
here you see us here here here okay uhoh
where are you guys uh oh I'm there's no
way I'm
Ming oh well them's just a break some on
my way
back I tunnel your way to the spawner
that's a brilliant idea yeah I was
thinking that's idea okay I really want
my sword back all right we're going the
other
way I want to come to you guys but I
have no weapons I'm unarmed and I'm
scared
yeah we don't have pickaxes either so we
can't keep digging um if you guys
go there's um permission
to oh God it's all right we got this we
trained for
this you know which way the the spawn is
it's this way it's towards the oh it's
that way
yes I hear I hear
noises no please no no no no
well how many how many blocks tall are
they well I
mean uh oh I'm just going to wait up I'm
thinking I'm thinking if we okay if we
stay out of their L sight yep okay
that's
SP I don't even know what's the right
direction maybe I tried to come to you
guys but I was unarmed and they just
killed me not the spawner not the
spawner hold on I see the spawner I see
the spawner be careful kill it no uh put
do you have torches do you have torches
yes I do I do I
do
okay how do I have to put four all
around
it uh
uh uh spam torches cover it in torches
Light It Up can mine and break
it is this what I do torch on top
oh
uh just light
it don't break it they said don't break
it just to be safe we're going to like
this I'm going to oh that skeleton
really sees us okay hey we got music
disc I got a golden horse armor get
the get the right
I don't have anything to fight with but
I want to help you
guys may I can snack give that the J
over there girl have iron horse armor
too but gold is better right there right
a little to the right oh hey I
see got a weapon oh Golden Apple just
kidding a saddle I'm I'm I am I am
covered in um hold on we can we can uh
where where are you guys at up top up
top wait how up top we're we're at the
bridge okay we the we have nothing I
mean I don't know about you Amelia I
have nothing in my
inventory cuz my I got lots of stuff I
can give you guys cuz I have like P
pickaxes and stuff I'm back again
and welcome back cuz I can't take all
the loot safe down there I'm here yes hi
okay here come uh
here you guys find a safe spot nice yeah
it's safe Ena Ena conquered the uh the
spawner oh no there's a skeleton where
what come
here I will save
you yeah spin
around I need food I need food I need
food I'm like almost
dead here I got um I got stuff I got
stuff here uh we got pickaxes thanks
we got swords here's a sword thank you
I'm just sad that I lost my my golden
leggings you're going uh we can make you
more we can make some Enchanted ones bu
yeah one more uh here's here's
uh thank you here someone else can have
this
one I'll take it just in case anybody
needs anyone help me r
I did sleep in the bed but um yeah it's
still long way oh yeah we should
probably put a bed down huh do we even
have a
[Music]
bed I can go back I'll go back and get
the other one okay it might take a while
though need
stretch oh you know what I'll just die
and then I'll come back with
it just let me die I'll drop your
pickaxe though I guess oh yeah
he's way faster than yeah oh my gosh
he's here oh you guys killed him all
right I'll go jump in wait let me drop
my jump it
offu is not the answer make armor that's
a great idea we need to light more stuff
going to
die H we need
armor arrows uhoh oh yeah hey there's
like a guy wearing purple pants over
here purple pants right don't die don't
die cuz I'm picking up the
bed all right I have the bed I'm
coming
here how many people need helmets I
think everybody needs a helmet um except
for you and Ena yeah yeah cook salmon
yay I'll eat
it you going carry one at a time oh my
God is there another
spawner hey kada here put this
on uh this thank you and then those
boots right there if you see those
floating on the on the table here Cali
here's a here's a shiny hat for you oh
thank you a shiny hat thank you I'll
wear it now I'm going to make you
boots thanks oh you guys are really good
at the crafting part of this game
huh no I'm
just okay uh wait boots yes here okay
here take this fashionable booties
booties are
we am I going in the I should be going
in the right direction I'm going to
Contin mining because yeah if it's on
the bridge it's fine but I'm going to
put the bed like at the side of the
bridge yeah we had a bridge yep that was
where kiar fell down uh here ky take
this too silver pants not as fun as your
other pants here
kiar here
go take yes
excellent M I'm on my way I'm almost
there minutes away
the bed in my pocket which way are
we you're on the bridge what bridge I
don't see a bridge it's where it's where
we you came out of we all spawned on the
bed and then we walked in the tunnel and
there's a bridge at the end of that
tunnel and we continue at the end of the
bridge go up
again up there yeah
ah there's the reason I put up the wall
K I took it wall done that's me that's
me that's don't die don't die I have the
bed
yeah careful K yeah they so shoot up
there don't fall
please should I bring the bed to you
guys sure uh or should we should we get
back wait yeah there's a furnace and a
crafting table up here hey we're only
200 it away on the X on the X
AIS are you guys caning get back up here
run
[Music]
Kiara just build up the wall on on on
your left yeah build it
up that he can't shoot you there and
then you can come up to
me I don't even know where I got shot
from from which
[Music]
side I hear
Ender
uhoh uh
uh wait what are we doing come up here
to me okay this is where we continue our
tunnel and the bed is up
here also I need a
[Music]
picka wait where's up
here right here some
gr
hi so we go this way really growl a
lot I'm going to move this torch really
quick
there's a lot of
growling yeah someone's real hungry well
okay you guys save up the
button
hey oh there you
go we're very close now I wonder if we
should all right that was
fun uh
Amelia yeah put this
on and then put this
on uh
and and
these and
this
[Music]
okay yep and you should be I have a
pickaxe yes of course uh here we need uh
more torches uh okay torches thank you
no one falls again no one Falls K here
take this proper Bridge we need to build
a
bridge no one fall another one here well
this one is not that deep that's okay
you K
here take that put that on what was that
oh thank you more armor some you you
want to get that to me I'm probably just
going to die again no no no just believe
in yourself you be fine
die don't
die don't die forehead don't die
good advice thank
you go just don't die not a
hole build the bridge over
this oh depends on what it looks hold on
light it
up might be able to does anybody have
any iron or iron iron block on them iron
uh yeah I have a lot hold on I'll
take thank you wow you do have a
lot oh there's one more here too
actually what are you
doing I'm building a
bridge I'll take this no we're doing
three wide no yes okay yeah I just want
I just
want I just want the ore
oh okay oh I'm sorry did I totally
like
uh fild it up fild it up all right
let's all right right we're good we're
good we're good pants for cie we're
working on pants for copy oh yes a
thanks guys oh yes did she lose her sexy
golden pants yeah they're
gone oh my this is a lot of dark
space Oh I hear a lot of cling
clangs skeleton someone smacking bones
together hear them bones
uhoh he was Trapped In The
Wall that's one way to
fight need a tactic getting so much
close you're like a piggy oh it's a
pigman who's sticking with the
bone I have two hands I have for two for
some reason I have two hands with things
in
them I don't know why or how hands with
things two hands with things in
them multitask doal wielding doal wield
one
thank you oh oh another M shaft oh
railroad tracks oh it actually leads
somewhere wait hey Cy when I get
cobblestone what I had pants for you the
whole time I'm sorry it's okay here here
for you I think you picked them back up
after you dropped them for me I'm so
sorry they're behind you I'm sorry guys
come here anybody have a torch I got
torches what you need it's fine I P with
something
we like
pants who it goes pretty far okay here
you go careful now there zombies over
there I ain't scared of no zombies I
don't have a
sword
ra that's an end that's an end that's a
zombie all right yeah what you want
yeah continue digging digging and
digging okay
thank you for your hard work but I I
don't have torches unfortunately oh
that's a spaes more
tracks uh oh that's a spawn
a oh nice how do I how do I tamed it
that torture on it Torture careful those
spiders are nasty careful careful
careful I'll all their
webs y those nasty spider webs
bye-bye uhoh
that's a Nast spider that's a nasty
spider okay we're good we're good we're
good I got 19 railroad tracks so wait
you can't build railroad tracks you can
only find them no you can build them oh
okay okay you can build all of that make
your own
Subway I'm going to just grab some
string from all these
weps useful for it looks like dental
floss yeah probably shouldn't put it in
your mouth though M
tasty
unless unless hey what's that spooky uh
glowing purple stuff back here that's
the end oh let's not be
here hi hi do I have torches no Dam I
only have
three don't wor guys I'm going right I
can I can make more oh wait I have like
60 never mind
oh well we're almost at the uh 1,300
X oh my
goodness have a shovel I have one stuff
here I had
one yeah it's just the breaks I need
another pickaxe Comon I got some okay I
have a lot of Swords if anyone wants a
sword
it's all right we don't need to go down
here guys don't worry about it don't
worry about it you know what some not
every adventure comes to a happy ending
sometimes you just got to retrace go
back start over right
yeah I block up the let me out you okay
oh yeah we're good don't worry about it
oh yeah we're good yeah I'll clean up CU
tun yeah beat him up yeah beat him up
beat him
up we a fist
fight
oh I hope you guys don't die over there
don't die oh there's another
one let me kill it let me kill it oh
sorry okay this is a tunnel
right fre experience
points can I have a pickax
that here
I got to make some more yeah which way
is the okay I'll go this
way yeah get him Ena
broke H oh there's another one you have
the Torches torches please and be
careful there's a hole
here who where's
that every time there creepers in there
I'm closing them up closing it up no
wait wait hey yes don't don't let me die
all alone here are you in there oh
oh my God
K there here I'm back and back oh that
hole no not not thatle hole oh my God uh
oh there pretend it doesn't
exist what saw nothing saw nothing don't
need this we just need to put this here
oh wow build a bridge
okay I'll
help okay I'm bringing
pickaxes all right we're safe my chest
is all the way oh I have chest here well
where would I be without chat where
would I
be I feel like we're
close yeah then we just got to fix the
we are getting close we just got to move
the Z
so 14
more I'm not letting go of my map that
map is I worked so hard for that
map boinging check the map we'll check
the map look at
that oh wait the map will tell us if
we're
close that's what a map does map does
yeah well see us on the map already or
no yes yeah we just got a we just got a
uh wait where am I on this wait maybe
this isn't where my house
is oh yeah it is yeah it is yeah shut
up yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
we're on the map we're on the map we
just got to
turn H Kelly Kelly Kelly Kelly yeah I
think we reached 1,300 so okay I'm just
I'm just cleaning up amies tunnel we got
to come back okay we got to go in a
different in a okay I close it off yeah
that the that route is this way 106 so
we got to go this way yeah
yes all right
ladies all
right this is going to lead out into the
water isn't it no I'll make sure we come
up on land I have a map don't worry
okay when should we start building up
will we know do we have to build up or
will it l straight out cuz we buil down
so we probably have to build up at some
point I guess when we get when we get
there yeah I have a map don't
worry uh for Z was it what was it 100 or
106 106 okay well that's another whole
lot to go oh we be there in no
time what do we
at oh that a spooky noise right now we
are at uh 1289 and then minus
278 can someone place a torch yes all
right okay we down to Cave we got water
here oh another M shaft oh I fell
uhoh operation save
a help help trying to get the M shafts
mine thingy mine cart
thingy oh yeah and the the tracks so we
don't have to make them yeah oh there's
a creeper over here water running more
water more
water a it's a creeper a
creeper wait we're building into the
water we're building into the water
maybe we go
down yeah Up's may we go up we yeah we
can go up oh there's a zombie a zombie
water oh it's
dark okay right here this is probably
far enough up I think yeah
well getting that tasty
iron where are you guys up here have a
pickaxe yep I got a pickaxe here uh here
hey take another one just in
case you thank you yes yes
chef so we're going up now
yes yeah well we're just we just went up
a little bit cuz there was
water water there's
water please have a pickaxe if I sure I
have pickaxe is there need
my hands hurt from
mining a hard life of a miner yes you
picked up behind
you nice thank you of course kind of
want to seal this off so that we don't
get lost oh there's a tunnel here watch
out you'll
fall hey Kara watch out there's a tunnel
here watch
out that's a long way
down yeah you'll definitely die for sure
oh sorry oh God oh God oh God where are
you guys oh there you are okay I'm just
closing off this area so that we don't
get lost and think we need to go that
way that
way build a little yeah you're really
close to the edge okay don't worry don't
worry I back
friend
right someone me very hungry right now
sorry that's me oh there's a spider
above us o spooky yeah walk it
off I have no watch watch
watch I must
reconnect where dark here oh lava if
only there was glass there would be
another great yeah uh I left glass like
cooking oh sorry oh my God that would
have been so bad it's my fault back into
it hold on oh this is
a oh this kind of sucks huh I'm uh I'm
going to be frozen a be back
soon okay we got a lot of we got a lot
of stones to use
so oh I see skeletons down there a lot
of zombies
okay they don't see us yet we'll be
fine o sweet
level are we going to go like a bit to
the right
side or let me take the map keep on
building the
bridge um we don't have to build it for
that much longer
map Che we should build up when we get
on that
corner
mhm ah I have no more there's rubies
down there rues yeah there's rubies down
there thank you good yeah should we go
for it no no Callie that's a that's not
Ruby it's not that far down oh it's like
red Redstone yes so rare
find
Atlantis yeah Atlantis that's not built
yet hey man I've been in this
server yeah I guess I'm getting a little
sidetracked
huh okay I can feel we're almost we're
almost there I hope we get there soon
yeah about 300 more uh since we got to
go to 100 and we're at minus almost 200
so for the that but X we're pretty much
there no more
X oh iron hello iron iron oh I guess we
can just go this way buing on the
outside well this is a Scenic rout and
then we can just go here yeah no I
didn't want that
does anybody have any
wood wood no that's good nice I have I
have 29 Spruce planks I have three
planks oh wonderful wonderful wonderful
wonderful go I dropped mine I dropped
mine too thank you yes yes
delicious can you imagine all one
person take way too long yeah I'll make
it three leave it to
me I'll make it three leave it to me
yeah I left I left the diamonds but it's
all right they're in a they're in a
chest they're very safe wor they're safe
M okay cool oh sorry sorry what happened
to the I guess I took it
back that's payback for when I smacked
[Music]
you maybe for the golden Yogo we can
build a big pond pond with like water
coming out of it and then we can have yo
in the middle and then we can build the
pond up to his eyes and then he can be
crying perfect
idea maybe don't come here okay I'm
ready to start moving again
no need for Ender thank
you yeah stop putting torches on the
left
side we're we're
extending one second how many uh
like back to
life no go away Enderman go away go away
I need uh I need I just need to uh build
this
this yep yep it's all right G's got this
don't worry G's got this G is on the
case I hear water I I hear
water oh he must be
close well not
necessarily come on I want believe we
still have to build up oh building a
bridge yeah it's looking how about we we
build up after we build our
Bridge we start the Ascend after after
the bridge oh actually yeah we could
build up now go
yeah okay oops
all right we're good you want to do
this uh oh
sorry
uh away the ceiling
oh sorry
sorry that would have been
bad MAP cheick ah
yes we begin the Ascend back to land the
air the grass the green
e are we close almost there
guys just a little
further hey how'd you how'd you get
here hey your guys' steps are different
than
mine
sorry yeah hold on consistency everyone
consistency
uh okay
this okay okay we need to put some down
here whoopsie
Dole uh uh yeah uh yeah
yeah
uh I want to see light I know I love the
dark but I want to see light I hear a
waterfall nice I do too
Shields that's
brilliant uh pickax
someone uh yep think I've got I'm coming
too excellent I have lots to give you
yay here you go okay hold on I got one 2
thank thank you thank I don't need that
much OK do that's fine
yes all right we got what else do we got
we got uh what was I going to build
Shield so everybody can have uh okay
well not everybody can I have another
Shield if anybody wants it
though okay here's a
shield do you know where to put it equip
it yeah yeah I'm a profession I hear
raining
[Music]
we did it wait a sec oh yeah we're at
the
oan already
bean I like the sound of grab your sword
this time we go to battle like three
skeletons
here feels like home
moving got this creeper can't get us if
we just keep moving oh my God they
land I want the
pick okay I'm going to build like a gate
over over our tunnel so that we don't
lose
it oh yes I know exactly where we
are really there's horses no
fin we need a bed okay we need a bed
before one of us dies and we spawn like
really far away good
idea horses you are my horsey now oh
there's a skeleton there there's a
creeper
coming oh no he he G where did he go
you're my horse now how do I get a horse
I need how I a horse how do you get how
do you claim a horse you need a saddle a
hey I know where we are yeah I griefed
these guys to I looted these guys wa no
come here come here there's a village
here there's a village
yes I stole everything they had but it's
all right there should be some beds I
think good
land I can't there's
land hia buddy how you doing sleeping on
the floor all right that's good to
hear I like this horse this black and
white one I want this one maybe they
have Saddles here yes they do they got
beds stuck bed they have maybe some food
s sleep hello we are here to take all of
your
things please tell me they have oh are
these like eagles I think
so oh can steal their
Ice steal their ice let's just take
everything I'll take their lamps let's
just uh take their beds first where's
the
entrance I like where you guys go house
um I don't know where that our tunnel
entrance is
anymore way over
there who's building
a monument someone's over there I'm
going to go back yeah that that's uh
that's where I'm was oh nice I want to
teame a horse I want food did you guys
go in the
mountains no they went to the village
Village
yeah oh I see I see H yeah for Hol live
perfect Hol live and the great tunnel
Adventure the Hol live Subway we have to
we still have to you know fix it up at
some point yeah it's a little scuffed
but that's just life all right if I
start walking I'll be able to reach my
house in another two hours and then I'll
have food for everybody what yes I'll
start now oh oh the the house house your
house we're going back now
already what
wait how did you do
that I don't know just click right
clicked yes this is the right way take
our horse in the mine ah I didn't mean
to hurt you
maybe I want a spotted
horse where are you okay how do I how do
I get on it I don't want to hurt
it uh you have to like
you have to like I tried to find food
but I couldn't find any my brain don't
work
anymore this is the wrong way this is
not the wrong way I guys I have the map
I have the
map with an empty hand okay is how did
you I
got I'm going the right way we're
officially on the map control it yeah
you need a saddle I did it you press
left shift to this yeah we need a
saddle why do you need like leather to
make a
saddle uh I think so some cow High did
you go did you go back into the
tunnel no I'm going to my house where
are you I thought you guys were okay no
I'm coming back I'm coming back I'm
coming back and also does someone have
like a tiny little bit tiny bit of food
oh there's bees
here don't attack the Beehive but it
looks delicious I'll try to catch a fish
down if no one has something I have a I
have a fishing rod I can give you you
can fish for some fish fish fish them my
hands you tamed the horse see you can
ride it without a
saddle I tamed it but I do have a
saddle oh my God I can't wait to tell
jorgan about this
adventure hi need my horse you know you
have a cool black and white
one wait I'm too slow to catch the fish
cuz I got no energy I have I have a
horse I I don't I don't have a fishing
rod I lied okay I am going to my house
now cuz there's food there how do you
move on the horse
hey cute what's horse's
name I don't know yet your horse just
changed color oh I just gave it the the
iron armor oh the armor I see
yeah need
it guys fall Dam if I fall in the water
right I think you need a saddle saddle
yeah he care sh okay
me off the
horsey I no I just want to get off of
you oh wait I think this is your
stuff don't worry guys I'm bringing the
bed wait I don't know which way to go oh
no guys don't die don't die okay
whatever you do it I moved the bed I I
slipped in the village so
of the
game yeah don't worry guys I got on
camera drink some
water oh wait there's chickens here I'll
go kill this chicken then we can eat
chicken now I can eat chicken before we
all die of
starvation nice
there's a cow don't worry we'll be
eating good don't worry don't worry
don't worry don't you worry beef beef or
beef uh
chicken chicken or beef there's an egg
here Kara did you leave this huh there's
an egg on the ground I don't lay
eggs all right I just
need dang
ah wait can we can we get to your house
girl maybe I
can oh yeah I thought I travel fast
didn't want to go okay we go now okay
I'm going to my house how do I get off
course how do I get off of it shift
thank you sh I'm already back wait wait
can you guys wait for me yes we wait for
you I just need
it it actually didn't take that long
from where we last put the bed it
probably take like I don't know less
than 5 minutes to get back to where
everything
was
[Music]
oh
go this is the goal isn't it aren't you
building here GAA you're going to build
here
now ah see first it was a question then
it became not a
question very quickly it became not a
question
well this is where you're going to build
right it's like a really good spot
actually I think for like uh underwater
stuff yeah yeah yeah yeah there lots of
space is Atlantis going to be underwater
Oh yes it has to be
cool it's really cool with glass
everywhere yes and
prismarine that sounds amazing I want to
see it it's you are all invited once
he's done y we're very close now
yes if you fill out the
paperwork how's the how's the rent uh in
Atlantis to
[Music]
know paying fish and seashells you
paying sand
dollar home sweet
home oh is this your house it was and
then it got blown up but it's all right
I'll get food for everyone don't worry
yay gener at G's Place oh it's getting
dark wait where's my food Oh Baby M my
inventory okay what do we want W what do
we want wow you have a lot of stuff how
do you already have so many things lot
of in here gosh darn it okay I'll
make food for
everybody and park a
horse what oh yeah in that giant hole in
the ground just make sure can't jump
out okay okay there's chicken here
chicken can have that and then there's
beef coming wow I'm this was
tiring
yep like well we found Atlantis or what
is soon to be Atlantis I have a
smoker yeah okay beef who want beef here
beef I want some and here chicken wait I
keep taking it good uh I took it it's
okay you take you
take chicken's not so bad
oh
okay W made it excellent we built a
tunnel the whole way ah don't to do that
no it only took us 3
hours though 3 hour
tunnel wait where'd you go
horsey he's up here
yeah just ran into the
ocean it's dark I need to make a Lea
sometime we all sound so absolutely
[Laughter]
dra a lot of building that was a lot of
tunnel that was a lot of
dark oh the tunnel didn't come out like
right to your house we can adjust it you
guys want to go around too
no I'm good I'm good I need wanted to
just move your house that'll be
easier I mean I
guess no we can move the tunnel we can
move the tunnel yeah we can extend it
later on but probably not today all
right here's the fun question how do we
get
back the tunnel follow the tunnels back
the tunel
move I ran out of energy to move again
everyone move again soon
though make any sense but okay I don't
know why that
happened all
right shall we you remember the way back
to
tenel you want to go all the way back
sry well yeah next time next time when
we spawn back in when we play we're
we're back wher every you know like
where our houses are right M he it
doesn't take that long to walk back cuz
I walked from where we
spawned okay all right one last journey
or we're walking back way back again you
guys remember how to get back to the
tunnel I have a
map oh okay okay okay let
go it should be along the shore at night
this is risky okay it's
okay I found all safe
yeah lit
up we just spent three hours in a Jorgen
is uh jorgan at the other home he's safe
don't worry he's at's
house lots of monsters on the
way really trying to mess with us o hit
I'm running fast oh they're fighting
each other yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah kill
each other kill each other I see the
tunnel whoa see the tunnel
that was a good idea to make that giant
H should probably move like the bottom H
part
[Music]
up oh no horse does not fit in the
tunnel
a oh no
spider I'm swimming because oh we can we
can build like a a little house for your
horse here until we fix the tunnel up a
barn that's true or you can you can just
run back over the mountain
mountains with the
coordinates
music
finally let's
go okay I'm in the J let's
go I'm going to quickly build oh oh no
the creeper is
following I'm going to time it
you know how tall does the horse have to
be three uh three yeah I think
so sorry seebe you can bring him in here
just a little bit cuz I I I extended it
a
bit nice
okay there's a zombie look at that guys
just like brand new look at that fresh
fresh fresh
da me and cie just running in the front
line far away from you guys cuz we just
want to go way this way okay okay I'm
timing how long it takes to run through
the T this is good this is good it's
good for uh
T yep we can we can now how about you
get inside and I'll close the tunnel
okay okay okay oh you guys aren't in the
tunnel
yet wait are you guys in the
no it's okay go on without
me oh no I died oh my God
you guys abandoned us come on you you
heard we were in trouble you didn't come
save us I didn't know where you
were I didn't know where you were I'm
half
I I just I just got to find I just got
to
find the tunnel I'm coming back for the
village I'm coming back I'm coming back
I'm coming back I didn't go too far
where the H is oh bum bu bum bum
uhoh no no uhoh only oh
yeah hey I see your horse your horse is
still here I just okay up your
level I'm at the Village I forget which
way the uh know did you name your horse
no not yet what got any name ideas
I don't know going to feel it
out I don't want to walk over it cuz I
know think after I'm going to Safe Place
good
idea I actually don't know which way the
CH from the
village all right I'm coming
[Music]
up you're in the village you know yeah
yes being chased by like five zombies
and a creeper
okay Serpentine Serpentine Serpentine
Serpentine
Serpentine BM see can't hit a
serpentine do anybody tunnel entrance I
just left I'm going to get Ena so we all
make it back yeah I'll
wait oh nice
bow oh hey snow oh I think I see you I
see you hell
Ina all righta okay oh my goodness okay
this way this way oh Ena I picked up
some of your stuff sorry okay it's okay
it's okay I'm
dying I'm a body for you okay it's this
way do you see it do you see it okay
yeah I have like no food okay don't
worry I got food here here eat
this uh
I have I have snowballs take this take
this take
thisk yes it's not very good but it it
it's okay it's okay so it's this way
it's if you just jump out and you go
that way okay okay going to make a run
for
it
[Music]
yep Oh
My wait where where's your safe point is
that the in my my house is all right
they can't keep me down I'm coming back
I'm going to die I
di okay I'm still the I'm still at the
Village I'm still at the Village I'm
coming back from my map it's going to be
daytime soon it's daytime soon bro
listen all right it's been a long day
we're trying our hardest
[Applause]
here the
map I don't need a
map good
look at the Sunrise isn't that
beautiful oh I found our stuff okay I
found home I reached home that didn't
take too long oh that was fast yeah
Callie's also almost there she's yeah
we're we have seen the sunlight on the
other side of the world it feels like
it's the other side of the
world feels like we went from Brazil to
Japan and the other way how many
Minecraft meters is that Minecraft miles
over 9,000 it took exactly it took
exactly 5 minutes 10 seconds what now
imagine that but with ice on the ground
that's going to be 60 seconds
top well I shall s in don't even don't
even don't don't don't no no time being
asleep in the house that Kor made for us
cuz I don't want to have to I have
enough beds
here I see you girl I'm coming I grab
the stuff all stuff grab the stuff we
can go stu
okay did it YY Callie we
did that was a long long long
journey
run sh the stuff you had it's down here
on this
step okay well
um you get there's still stuff here
that's yours so you didn't pick up your
Shield oh good I picked it up I got it
we can go we can go wait can't
go there like a monster outside or
something hor Too Tall raining so
they're not they're not um losing Health
Horse Too Tall hor Too Tall you're
suffocating it's oh skeleton oh
go go team go I got
it okay it's okay I'll I'll slowly make
my way back bring horsey back it's all
right we're all getting home we're all
go at home
today I'm going to give yoran a
friend do you have my map it's nice to
be back so nice oh yeah I
do the map get it
yes are you leaving your horsey up
here yes I'm uh bringing I'm just
clearing up so I don't
Sate went back all the way up
topy come
back all right if you have the right
side some real food
where did you
go surprised Calli didn't freestyle with
the the sound of the
uh I know right maybe some other time
I'll find a
way uh get a up ahead what up
stop hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
ow he's got Stone in his hand he's going
to Stone us to death ah okay no problem
no
problem it was another one I don't know
where he went he saw what happened to
his
friend okay
okay oh there's a how did they get in
here are you guys coming to
so far away yeah we're trying to we're
helping clear like a path for her
horse that's nice where are you Ena oh
she's trying to get her
horse yeah youa where'd you go I'm on
the way this needs to be a bit
higher no I
think maybe I'll just lock him in here
and then I'll come back
for to the
ending okay
can't run away okay that's fine I'll
come back for
you so we we played like a some of this
first part I'll just keep doing it until
you catch
up okay I'm making my way
back
okay all way home I see you guys hello
hello I am late
no worries where is we just mining when
we when we do the uh oh this is how they
got up
here close it
up when we do the uh rail carts or what
is it the train thing yeah does it have
to go in a straight line or can it curve
I think it can have turns I
think maybe
probably probably it can have turns yeah
oh okay okay can it go like up yeah I
can also go up but St need um you would
need something to accelerate it uh that
it's like a red stone torch or whatever
it was called yeah you can make it like
a roller coaster up and down on big
Hills ah is that like a one time use
thing like once you put it on it works
no it will always work yeah yeah hey
Callie welcome
back a
face the time I was here the whole time
don't
worry if you run and spam the space bar
you run
faster hold control wait how do you run
yeah hold control and jump yeah sh not
Shi control yes yes oh yes I'm zooming
I'm
zooming you just found out so fast
oh too
yeah
I'm oh I ran oh there's water we close
up this water cuz
like close it up it's spun on the way
down but not on
[Music]
the goodbye water water
we're almost
there what a journey G just hold space
Oh I when I spam it it go faster yeah it
goes faster for me
too but only when the wall is low cuz
you like bounce
back yeah uh any do you guys maybe have
some food I is that is that why I'm not
going fast anymore yeah I'm I'm a tad
bit
hungry I got food I'm right behind
you
ah Bliss
yes uh I think
it's here you
go that' be really cool if we can build
like a the mine cart
stuff but the mine cart like uh it only
stays one you know what I mean like if
you get on it on one side it'll stay on
the other
side uh I think so I think I can it can
slide back though if it gets caught in
the in the Redstone trigger it'll
it'll uh send it back yeah you can place
one in the beginning and one in the end
then you always can go either way
M yeah that would be really cool if we
could do
that imagine
that multiple Railway systems
up Hello
wall was that the end of the tunnel the
white
light I think it's just the render
distance thing oh which tunnel I enough
for a
second oh my
God there's an Invader in our Empire oh
my God what H you know how those what
are they called not the villagers but
the the other
ones what do you mean what called the
ones with the the gry looking ones with
the noses the sign is great the ones
that want to kill you what do you mean
the ones that want to kill
you oh my God they're looking at me and
aiming at me with their thingies
pillagers
yes have invaded the whole olivian
empire
what they're not attacking me at
interesting next time on Hollow livey
and Minecraft server we tackle the
villagers okay you better not come back
right now girls you probably shouldn't
um don't get close to my house they're
at my house oh
no I'm I'm scared they're like
oh has Magic ah ah
we're almost there did you did you sleep
in your home make sure yeah I did I did
I did I did I'm trying to kill them
through my window now it's working it's
working ah oh my God one is dead woo
they they're killing each other oh my
God I I want to see oh we're
back
land we're back where are you my
home I got to sleep in my house first
that's a good
[Music]
idea oh hi ga
hi welcome back oh he's got an enchant
he wants you really bad that's mine
that's mine he really wants Kiara oh wow
wow don't let him
in get
him he died but he didn't give me his
enchanted bow Arrow so them nice hey you
can take his flag you want his his
banner
yes hang it up so they know wait but I
feel like I forgot what you can do with
that what what does that do
again well the pillagers are dead so
that's cool we're safe don't ever come
back to the H life Empire or we shall
you and destroy you your butt we kick
your butt very Square Jorgen let's go
put this shiny armor on
Jorgen wow what a
journey I know what a
journey
hi like I've lost 5 years of my
life but you've
gained it feels like 30 years what what
did I
gain time spent together with friends
that's
true wow what a steed what a steed Yan
you're
beautiful oh looking
good that cheddar cheese horse what a
beauty he does kind of look like a
cheese
stick H you tired all right is everybody
we all meet up yeah meet up at Jorgen
meet up at meet up with house party
getat up with the cheese
horse oh my
goodness that was a long journey that
was an incredibly long journey you have
at my house or what yes yep very
organist I'm
friends oh I see a
here
wel welcome welcome welcome
I can't see oh down the
stairs oh that's
right the giant Treehouse oh the trees
grew while we were gone oh wait I want
to see
I what Amelia you're putting a new
meaning to treeh house yes more
trees is this treeh house or are these
house trees wait did somebody just say
that
house I'll make another one can go
inside where it's bright okay wait go
inside yeah look at look at us look at
us look at us we entered as amateurs
we've come out as Warriors what a
team that was fun
I think it's time for I think it's time
for some some food and some rest for
everybody
yes so I want to say brain fuel yes
recharge the brain
battery uh we all like to say thank you
so much for watching the very first
thank you the Ian collab on the the the
Holo Ian Minecraft server yes thank you
yeah thank you
yes thank you so much I hope you guys
had as much fun as we
did yes now does anybody have any uh
upcoming announcements they would like
to talk
about I have a show is
happening yeah Friday night PST Japan
time it's
Saturday check it out and then yeah
we'll announce the results of the remix
contest after that too so it's going to
be going to be fun ooh that's big big
big yes got a lot of rest before
then not stream until
[Laughter]
okaying pushy cheese horse come
on really
you
[Music]
a anybody else with an announcement nope
no no all right no well then I guess
H my model froze for the last time cuz
my my device that has my human body uh
keeps turning off over and over again no
I know how to fix that but I'll tell you
later after
thanks all right everyone uh I guess
it's time for us to say goodbye for now
but we will all see you again I'm sure
very very very very soon yes yeah yep we
post our schedules for those that don't
post schedules and yeah we'll see you
guys
soon soon yay schedules a new week of
content let's go let's go on number two
yeah yay all right
everyone and say
byebye bye
bye
e e